Alexandra Thurston color
Novelty beverages
Talk a little bit about
Alex Jones
Grow your hair out to absurd
What is the most aggressive
Hair Choice
Happy birthday
Are we including
Honorable mention goes to the time that I got to
Trimmed down low on the beard it went with the
The chop stash
What was the
Shaved the chin area a mutton-chop mustache combination
Younger days
Beard with no mustache
Mennonite Amish beard
Iraq that look and tell everyone
Not not time to build
Peter cell
Quite drunk
My buddies were
Just talkingshit
I am so excited
Be fun if I got the
Your money haircut
Does that my name shaved on one side of my head and a dollar sign shape
Drunk friend that happened
Vietnam
So I got a mohawk
Blond
Real
Classic blond
Cuz I was going to try and
Diet
Right color and then another color
Hunters like f****** I really enjoy this Mohawk much
I can't even I can't get it to work with a mohawk
Control the least like whatever
An important lesson
Hairstyles are not for me
Ones that require even
Littlest bit of gel I just can't handle it
Nope
I don't know
Or Alex
July 9th
Present day
Yeah I know there's some interesting things on this here Friday episode of Alex Jones
Michelle butt before
We got a bit of business
Mystikal
First of all I got to say shout out to
Who is from Australia
Knowledge fight Studios
I apologize it and I won't have time to
You go meet up and have a drink
Butts
He was kind enough to come over and gave me a nice hot sauce
From Australia
To try
Accidentally put it in one of the boxes
So it'll be a housewarming
For the new place
But also you want to breathe
Stuffed
Some Australian treats
Tim tams
Brenda mix
Bright
Our natural reaction
But another thing
Service brought is
Cherry ripe
Which of the Cadbury product apparently
Has a bit of a coconut in the middle of it and
Cherry flavor
It was described by Andrew as being a either you're going to love it or you're going to hate it
Equation
I'm going to love it you're going to hate it
That's my prediction
That is a very good predict
Alright
Just going to take a bite of it
I guess you're one that said want you to that ass shot
I love a you while you do
How's that how's that
Is Australian good
You're away to Pence
Audio recorder
I am getting first
Wonderful
Lovely
The right.
I think it might be good another one of them I will hate myself
I don't think I can handle another
Vegas kratom
Hot sauce
Now Jordan
The next
Very large
So
300 and something episodes
Whatever this podcast
Entire time
A sound drop that we heard on the first episode it's good enough
Now
Someone who listens to our show
Has some skills
A gentleman by the name of
Okay
Reached out
Is that you
That is Express
I don't know how to put
I think we're going with a theme song
Here I'm going to play for you Jordan
You haven't heard this before
This is the Extended Cut
How's the theme song shortened version will likely be our theme song
But enjoy this
Casey's Pizza
I have great respect for knowledge but I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Need money
Dollartree.com
Just incredible
Pyro
I can't even express my gratitude absolutely
Right now I feel like I never am
Imagined
Usher Woody Woods
Kind of what I would have
Tried to express
It just amazing
Differences
I think
Apartment
Theme song for a podcast
400 episodes the times of change
I really appreciate that
All credible
Thank you so much
Text Missy
Christopher Noth Christopherson
You are not
Fell in love with the movie
Highwaymen
Give somebody who donated on the elevated level Weaver
Appreciate it very much so
You are now attacking
Heroin
Freakishly large
7 a.m.
Bespoke
Dropped
Here on this episode
Because I have a little bit of a musical out of context drop
Start off the dark show
Lubbock
Guitar Alex Rose
What a dick
What are the reasons
Stay in the present day
Stuff out as opposed to retreat
The past has
We are watched
To do from time to time
Is that someone in our Facebook group
May or may not have confessed to killing a dog
Yeah we always got to pay attention
Dog situation
The allegory analogy
Baymax
Sometime I was
5 years old
The time I was 20
Dad
Lab
Add
And I would steroids switch later to make your battery explode
Can make your muscles
Fall apart to mess up your joints
Daddy couldn't get up
There's no surgeries for that
What's a catch-22
He went three more years
4 large animals at Sun all about
Depo-Medrol and stuff
Somebody special Getwell
Going to give you a little bottle but
Don't get more than that cuz it could hurt him when the regular dose would work I give you more
Because I'm a call back
I made the decision
Supposed to give me supposedly and a doggie be operated a happy running around still have three more years
Summit explained that so I know y'all need to disagree if you wanted you could agree but
It's like this country ladies and gentlemen
Is a Labrador with hip dysplasia
You trying to empower the people
Tsheets
So another day
Conversation about a dead dog
Try to pretend that I don't understand
I'm only taking the time to discuss this clip 42re
The first is pretty obvious
That is compared to normal people Alex Jones brings up dead dogs
He Compares almost everything any situation
Do what that dog he uses memories of dead dogs in
Use for emotional outbursts
He on multiple occasions
This compared his enemies
The dogs that need to be put down
I'm not in any position to say with certainty
Absolutely have a preoccupation with
The death of dog
Based on what I've heard on the show if he talks like his psychologist would be negligent
If they didn't ask follow-up question
Oh yeah
The second reason I bring this up is that I don't think the allegory
Conclusion
Any story you had an alien dog will everybody told him should be put down
But he was stubborn and didn't want to listen to their advice
He worked part-time in a farm setting
You sure that he knew better than all the doctors and veterinarian
In order to keep his dog alive broke the law
Scammed medicine
From multiple Veterinary
To give to the dog which allowed the doctor survive three more years
At which point is
Still died
According to drugs.com Depo-Medrol is generally use a dog's quote
Associated with acute localized arthritic
Condition
And generalized arthritic
When a dog is being given Depo-Medrol they're generally
A great deal of pain
Drugs
Depo-Medrol is also used to help dogs with
Seasonal allergies but
The decision to put a dog down as always
Incredibly difficult to find it hard to criticize
Someone too harshly
Come down on either side of the
On what hand do to the animal you love is
In constant pain
Is really hard
The deal
But on the other hand it's really hard to fight
Canfield they can
Vicksburg
Pet can be blinding
And rationality can go out the window replaced by naive notion
So you can make things
Writing help your love won't help your loved ones stay around
Forever
The thing is
Alex's actions which would definitely illegal
To put off the inevitable
Which is that his dog died
This is why the allegory doesn't work
What he's describing is the very definition of exotic
He's liking it
Open up his dog on painkillers instead of putting
So what Trump is doing for America
Knows better than the metaphorical veterinarian
In order to keep things moving
But just like Alex's dog
This doesn't end in a miraculous cure
He's better for is
Structurally
Sweet Leaf
Have accidentally stumbled onto the real truth
Trump has created traffic illusion
You can pretend it isn't going to go away and then
The dog will just
Look man
White people
We were going to be a minority soon
Let's just move on
That's just how it's going to go
What is the dog
Instead of giving your dog an opioid
Skip
Maybe this is where we first met
No
I could have been
I'm so
Are we start off on that
Just really salty allegory
Straight in
Anti Elon Omar
Straight
Bigotry
Evans first clip do we have
Alex
He's just like
You could not be more blunt about what
Complaints about her
That she said
Venom
Because I hate
How they come and they talk about
Fuller brush
She's an Arab
Be more blunt than that
Really gross
Anaerobic
False
Booties with readout in order to make sure that you don't appear to
To just be
Responding
To that aspect
If it creates
False ideas about you
You better by tonight 11/8 America
Talks about
Supposed
Her family
This is how Rome use black
Until Arabs taught them
Europeans did not have black slaves
Until
And then it's the perfect thing to have someone
Scanning a lot of black people
Somalia
Rumors
They are the leaders
He's just responding
2 visual cues that he takes
And has determined about what he knows about her based on that which is the definition of
I don't know prejudice
Define the color of their skin that I took that has a
He said European countries he was specifically talking about Rome earlier in that that conversation
Rome large
Have
Non-whites
Was because they took slaves
From Concord area
And Their Kingdoms
To Africa except for the
North
Most part of Africa
Did they didn't have it
Conclusively
White slaves yes absolutely
The slave trade
It's an irrelevant conversation
Because the answer is they
Write any of the Aborigines in Australia in play the Latin American people Dan
Right
I mean it
It's not that simple
Interesting position
The show on the nights
That is because we are not Trump rally
Where people
Kerbeck
Where to post rates
Alex's listeners apparently a responding that Trump is
He's backing off
Spelling about whenever he's come out and said I didn't like that chance
They think that he's being
Globalist
Or whatever
Send her back
Is that a lot of people
Are that mine
What did you think the lock her up
Type mentality was going to morph into
Like this is the obvious next stage
Only people are surprised New York Times And The Washington Post
But we all know that the real answer was
You wanted a chat send
That's what you really wanted are fun
The only real defense
People who want to
Pretend that they are not idiots
Can have
Look the mob
Justin
Lauren Justice
They're not changing lockherup summarily they're saying give her a trial at lock her up it's
After
And that's the same thing with this Omar situation or not saying just deporter they're saying
Every trial and then deported that's what the intellectualizing Buckhead
Alex
Just trying to live in
Counterpoint
Shut the fuk
Sure
Fair enough
Trying to live in that space where there's the heir-presumptive
We're still trying to follow the law
Whitehouse.gov
And then deported really nice of him
Guilt to make sure she
I mean the guilt is really presume
I wanted a particularly disgusting is that if you
Listen to show your Clips like this
He understands
He actually wants and with actually motivating him
He's her being
Now the way he would prefer to kill her
To send her to a dangerous place
Gacha forced her to leave the United States go somewhere where he will be killed
Will settle go for going to multiple veterinarian
Injecting her with
Basically
I don't know either way
Square Biz
It's Helen
I just know that I'll send her back
Fraudulent
She won't last
A month over there
Because she's famous
It's on their head in her own
Russian somalis
We'll kidnap her so give her a week before she was kidnapped
Airport
Whatever
Squatted
Cheez-Its
Right
I mean if you are
You have made a vow
Very strong case
Even
If she is found guilty of
Immigration fraud she's a refugee
It should not be set back
Standards around the world
You cannot send people back
Two places where you have any reasonable
Awareness but they will be absolutely
We killing them
Ethically speaking what you are doing is you are
Want he's relishing in this idea of like
Yeah I will do what I do to a dog
I want
Well it's almost in the same way always looking for somebody to be the
Aggressor so they
Somebody the way that they want to right you know
They're trying to get her killed without
Terrorism
So they're trying to follow quote
Killer
Let's
Did she murder somebody
Alien Omar
Did she get you run somebody over with a car
I'm not unaware of that
He just talked about how we should be
She's spoken Waze
Be very easily misinterpreted and lied about by the
Right wing
And particularly these right
Propaganda
Trigger finger for
People
2 don't like America the right way
Somebody to die for
Skip this next
It's just Alex
Omar came to America
At the cross hymn
And the people
Sure those that people
I need to be clear about this
He's all over the place
Incredibly
On this episode
This is one of them
Nothing
Anybody
Saying something like that
Deeply ashamed
Omar does not have
Penal parts
Mattamy
Intuit if you're not going to get into it cuz you realize oh f*** what am I
What am I talking about
Speculating about her
Genitals
Baby wild of course
Obviously
Right that's what he's trying
His listeners
If you think this is appropriate
If you think this is an okay okay way to carry yourself
Even if you hate every single thing that a lot Omar stands
For this is not okay
I just I can't I can't say enough that's
Credibly disqualified
Horrible
I can't imagine
You have to be really really f***** up person
Absolutely
But there might be a reason that Alex has really sucked up
Completely
Easy simple
I know that he's very affected by food
Like when he forgot his
Child
Teacher's name
Chile
That's not an isolated incident
Because it turns out
There is dietary issues
Maybe the reason that the Fourth of July sale is still going
Lunch yesterday and then I went and got one of my fast-food indulgences that I don't
Sounds like a deal but I got a big order attendees from Popeye's and I ate the whole thing
Just a few hours but I was in a coma
What's a on there
I love chicken tenders
Popeyes
I thought that might have been a regional thing
You can't do that
I think it would be a profoundly
Weird things
Looks like you know what episodes
Ivan
Generally will eat something unhealthy while I edit
Put the episode out weird if I texted you the next day
What's up
Chicken tendies
Really would cut it that really wouldn't cut it
Like a real shity week excuse
Alex
You know he's so affected by food
That maybe that explains
Like everything
Maybe his diet
I'm trying to I'm trying to thread a needle that I'm not interested in threading
Getting depressed
Clinic
Play so to the point where
Eating his food
I've been unable to do any work
Or possibly there's some side effect of denote
Well
In combination with all of his
Looking for worst product
Maybe they have created
Such a digestive
Destroyed by a food that normal people can digest easily
Little like some of those
Things that might
Like maybe it makes it so you can't
Maybe you should just get a regular cleanse
Maybe he's lacked
10 the intolerance
Alright alright
OxiClean
Hogan Road over Iraq
Sew-in t'god
Episode
Normal
I don't care as long periods of time talking about.
Exactly the same way he always does
But he
He makes this
Comment your about
Using the Lord
Zayn
But I find
Really interesting and
Pretty
I think it indicates
His relation
Kinship with religion
God fearing that I have a conscience I have a soul like a
Field.
University
Cheetah Hillary Clinton hell
I want
So what year is
Alex essentially saying
Like you're not supposed to take the lord's name in vain
Understanding
Good
I don't know if the standard by which
God
Set down his rules are like
Hedonism is the key to understanding the Pleasure Principle
Your Guiding Light tour
You know that I don't I don't know if
Is like a
I had a really bad headache and then I called the Pope the devil and I feel better now
To have like a
This weird
The Gorillaz
Relief valves whatever he says really f***** up religious
It's not
I don't think that that makes them
True or good
I think that says more about his psychology than
Maybe it explains why
You sucks it's wearing so much
Much like he can't eat
In the right context at all
Calling upon the strength of the Lord
To destroy his enemy
It isn't so good at it
I don't know if it works
No I'm pretty sure it works
Call Alex
Alaga Paladin
Going to get into that business with
Omar's genitals
And now he's about to
Does gets back into the theme of genital mutilation
I don't want to break down his thoughts about this
I only in playing this
This clip because of the sheer lunacy
How this goes
But
The part of the female anatomy
This is serious business okay
This is a family
That's why I kept
What are you doing
Kind of f****** family show is this
Lizabeth Lizabeth little little Terry
Five-year-old little Terry
You're going to need to know this
Metal trigger a
Alright
Now I know how to make a ladies
What the f***
Holyshit
Not this is not a family show
He was like
I think I want illiano
Like that
I think years ago they're stopping
So what are the things I love to do brings me the most Joy
Is hearing Alex
Tell stories I've heard him tell and
Whenever there is a
Repeat story
Tracing the little details that seem to shift based on how he wants
To use this is always something I really enjoy
Sweetheart of course
The classic
Halloween apps
Stories
We have the globalist in a hot tub
Recent days is when
Some gays
We're talkin
Muslim Muslim
Isla Mujeres
Alex tells the story again
Take note
See if you can point at this is like one of those things and Highlights magazine
We got the two pictures and get it's alright different
Too pretty sizable
Ways in which the story is
Mexico
After I left
Little Island
Lisa got shot in shoulder
Chicago butt
I said about 5 days
I couldn't have it man washing these BJ man
Perfect
Wobbling
A bunch of
African Muslim
Arab
Fleming
Urgent
Your girlfriend
What
Monster
And they're worshipping the Muslims
Wolf
Wow we know the term and we stopped using it because it's
Terrible thing to say does kind of rhyme
Yeah
Rock band
I'm just because it rhymes
It's funny how both words
Isn't that term our offense
Alone
Kind of
Kind of lame
Slightly differently
But
Leave the two major differences with see if you found
I'm going to go with African Muslim
Write that one's pretty big for typed into the story helps
His eye is a piece of the Omar story as a
Supposed to just being a
Generalized I don't like Muslims years how they behave kind of narrative
To understand if this is what he does
Absolutely
I'm going to go with
I don't remember them meeting Alex in the other
I don't remember Alex being in that other story
At all
Do they're all afraid of him
What's
So stupid understand
Include areas where and he can
Those little pizza
Looking to suck
Pretend Arab trade
Slave trader class
He's too powerful
So f****** stupid
This is ridiculous he's held every story he tells either has him
The source of all
Nobody is ever just unaware of who he is
Right you never blamed
He's pretty pissed
Let's
So if we get to the Alex talking about the house
This is part of a long
Deconstruction about the devil
Heard before
It's not worth it it's not worth our time to read
Go over this
However Alex doesn't do bring up something
There's a reason the people side with the Devil
Okay
Beer people generally side with the devil out of fear
You would think
In the Bible
You would think that but it's actually fear
Okay
Alex has a really good source on
Most people don't you stay
They choose it because they brush up against it may get scared
And the Devil comes around and says sure of me
I'll protect you
Give you power
I'll do that
What is Palpatine
You have a powerful enough to defeat Obi-Wan Kenobi
Yoda
Tell you
Channel.
Go to the prequel gonna feed going up there
Well there can only be to say that any one point in time
The first thing that
Alright
Sports Authority the basis for his a religiosity in the original Star Wars movie
Is the prequels is conception of the devil
The most midichlorian
This is
Ludacris stuff
Insane
Like I know you love doing that voice
It's kind of like
In the neighborhood
Alien Omar
Banana
I know it's offensive
I know it's offensive I really don't know
He was trying to
As far as an accent
He's talking about this licky brush up against
Great midichlorian
This
Do him
Discussing
What the Satanist
Told him what
He was younger
Was your dog
Oh my God
What should cut your dog's heart up
And it just goes from there
If you know that it goes from there that implies that
Cut your dog's heart out
Because how would you know where it goes from there if you didn't follow the first
Stop
Of course I don't believe any of this stuff
I think this is nonsense I think it's a
Absurd fantasy that you've come up with
Told him to kill his dog
But I don't
The amount
What time you spend talking about dogs
Killing of dogs
I don't believe there's not some sort of trauma that's based around motivating
This to be such a focal point
August conversation
It has to be some deep buried thing where it really feels
Like I don't
The Goldwater rule
But I
Would be
Surprised
There is
Incident in his past where someone did tell him to kill his dog
There has to be
Yeah for someone else killed his dog
He saw that
There's some sort of a
Resonant
Trauma
The ripple effect
Arcgis
There's still effective
Never ever ever talked about
As much as I have
In the past
Year-and-a-half
Yeah years of our podcast
It's
Sane
And it's not again I have to stress
It's not like
I'm just cherry-picking every single time we talked
About that dogs do a lot
Even if this was
Every time that he's talked about dead dogs
That is 10 million times more than I've ever
I promise you there are
Yeah I believe it
Alex
Is rambling
S*** about
Emperor Palpatine
And the devil
Satanist
Can you tell your dog
Right
Alex gets on to
I guess maybe more than
Inspirational message
And that is about how again his idea
Can BV tools
God's vengeance
Wichita
Be how Alex wants
To look at it
Bookshelves
A man and woman in history has been used implement
Or the
Device
Panda
God's plan
And that I be a vessel
Everybody else plays a mascot.
Nice. She don't get things you asked for
You get
What you pay for
Suffocate yourself
Presence of God
You also need to be careful
When you do ask for something
Make sure you're going to be up to it but that's God's Secret
Really want to stand up against evil
God's going to
Put you through trials and tribulations
More weight on you
Powerlifter
Or drug dealer gymnast
I don't see any
Real Subs
Listen to difference between what he's describing of God like giving you little tasks
Telling you to kill your dog escalating
The same Playbook that parallel and I'm trouble site
I also just I know we talked about this
Before but like
When you take in the idea that
Humans are the imps
Instruments of God's vengeance
And sometimes you know you just admit yourself to God's will
Instrumental
Calling for God's vengeance
Against people who politically disagree with you
It is the sort of thing where you are
Almost
Intentionally hoping that someone
Is in such a
State of Mind
And we're hearing God
Calling
To them
Instrument and Carry Out God's Revenge
Quote
This is not an acceptable way to carry your
This is the sort of thing where you are almost certainly
Hoping to find someone
Suggestible
Implant that suggests
Absolutely
Of valid
Religious conversation
It's not a valid
I don't even know what other like
Category to put it in political conversation it's not a valid conversation
To be having
I think it probably is legal but
I do think that
Should things go bad
To be taken very serious
To hurt someone that Alex's demonizing and putting a big Target on
Do you know oh what do you know they listen to Infowars
I think Cliff is very relevant
Clutch like that are very relevant because they're giving the audience
Who maybe suggest
The excuse
Absolutely if you are not committing a
Because you are a living will
In the presence of God you have
You know you're just like it said in the Bible
Everyone of your actions
Justifies anything
Just say I was suffocating mice
There's literally
Well
Yeah I mean it's functionally
For someone in that state
It's really
It's really scary
No it's being kind of a consistent
Piece of Alex's rhetoric now
I don't remember hearing him say stuff like that
A lot
In the past
I know that
It certainly would have
2009 or
The 2013 stretch we're going through I have not heard him
Like this
Which are
I guess
Hoping
To inspire
Yeah
Excuse preamp
Isn't it
Started
Really doing like after after the
Send her back
Led to so many
Conservative
Luminaries
Defending
Sending her back
That kind of thing
It's like
If if somebody does something
Then
During the defense
About
That kind of
That's just a line that
Yeah I hope I hope that your
Thought doesn't
Come true but
So I just exited
Alex
Literally no reason to ever say
Omar is the daughter of
There's no there's no reason
To say something like that
About
About somebody
Who cares
F*** this guy
In the next life Alex talks about the
July 4th sale
Right
Massively discounted right now and
Broadcast
I bet they look a lot like the old now what's really interesting
Once I get off are I'm going to cut those ads
Really on sale right now
It's giving like
Almost the same thing as I QVC
So of course I cut them to the 4th power
Like he does another half-hour into the 4th power from dr. Nick begich
Intentionally needs to move more product right
Exploit Visalia
He does all the f****** time
But
He pretends
He's going into the fourth hour according to him
Because it needs
Take calls
Call well he's
He said he's going to take calls and he hasn't
F****** our complaining about
Congressman Blumenthal
Who's what
I don't care if some Stolen Valor s*** I don't know what I don't know
Just couldn't be bothered to care
Sandy Hook self
Defense but like
Haha Blumenthal helps Alex
He didn't do the
The things that he's accused of I just don't care
I just I don't
He spends an hour of a show called
Unless Blumenthal called
You didn't
Call
4th power
Before he does
Expresses
Need to take
Your failure
Are they
Jim
Kevin is it
Aaron
Does guy on hold also named hat man who never goes to which a very sad about
I want to
Codependent
That is an insane
I can read your blood
All right who's on the phone
Completely nuts
Year and him not putting on a character
He should be a padded cell and if he's putting on a character like
Characters
True
Self
If that's
The character
Who are you trying to appeal to with this character
Characters
So f***** up
I can just
Buckatunna games
Whatever it wants a Bubba list
What goes on a little bit and it's
Because I think Alex
Like his f*****-up
And I don't think it's a good
T probably never the kids might beg for Mommy and talk to my text mommy's next timings
We only talked to the children like that
I came I saw you died
TalkBack to that's why
I talked to her in the way they like to
McDonald's
It's not good I don't take anyone
Pretends is enemy
He is listening to his show
All he's doing
Freaking out his audience
But you didn't listen to Everyday everyday
The idea that he's
Talking like that in order to talk back to the globals the way they talk to the children they have
Scarcity can get adrenochrome in their blood and drink and get high talk to Demons the album Etta create a One World Government
That's ludicrous
Mirror there that's how you make people feel
No
Oscar calls
We get into the fourth hour it's a very rare thing for me to actually listen to
2/4 hour
F***
The friend of Alex's
Hosta
This though
And supposing
About the half-hour
1/4 hour
Sprout
How do you specifically says don't call and ask about
The product don't call and tell me I'm wonderful
I need to get the
I can only give you two minutes
Fox up on all that
Call
He does this for a f****** minute when he starts the 4th hour
Girl back from the front line of the information War
Alex Jones
Is it true
We're just going to let this ride
What a great Street route
Sing along
Does he have any more
Sing to me but like during it shows like all right
The big is real serious business there's a lot of s*** going on in the world right now
So I'm going to cut it
That he's allowed in the fourth hour
Because I'm a f****** sick along with Pancho and Lefty for over a minute
It's good up radio
Lo and behold there mostly
This first one is really funny because it starts out with a guy who is a veteran of radio
The Talk Radio
Okay
Reveal
In the first
Couple seconds of this called
If you worked in radio for 15 years which is not a cop
Product
He might recommend
Now just
Answer is
Talon
I have been in broadcasting part was for about 15 years of Froakie
To be honest I hadn't heard of
A lot of stuff that I felt in my Heart and Soul Surfer
Call wife
God bless you brother exactly role Kindred Spirits
You really are we really like
Body paint all over my entire life
And you know better than anybody there I think
This is a really dangerous
Want to be asking Alex
Because he's asking about
Pacific medical condition what products Alex would recommend
Which is the
Careful
He might say this product
Is good
For dealing with lower back pain claim
Which is against
Yeah
Navigate
The territory pretty well
I mean literally everything
Turmeric
Strongest strongest strongest
I mean I would
Will red pill red pill Plus
These are all
They've all bombarded us with synthetic hormones that mess up
Body
If you get pregnant on
The scientist
Woody's
Everybody is different
Text us off yourself
An antenna Nishi what works best for you but they're all
Super game-changing
Z-Best labs equinus
What he's done is remarkable because he
Specific claims for that they're all amazing
And in doing so you said about any of them could help you
Torio
Nefariously sneaky sail ship
I feel like there's a little bit of a gotcha question there
I mean all of his callers that bring up the pills
Sound
I don't I don't think that I think he's just trained as listeners to know that they will get a much better day in court
If they do an ad in their call earlier the episode
When callers bring up the supplement Drive sales because it's
The old appears to organic
Have planted
Time his behavior is so
Incentivizing people to do that
Call Natural Organics
I'll get more time on air
Strategy
Maybe I'll be able to plug my own
SoundCloud whatever
And plus if that was a
Call he wouldn't said I've been in radio 15 years I didn't know who you were
It runs counter to Alex's grandiosity
This dude is lying
No I don't think so
Six months that he's already got all the all the things down all that stuff
Dude if you listen
For a week
You have all the stuff done
This whole no medical claims
Like
From how much of this should I listen to and how much of a joke
If you were motivated
Towards him
Are you listen for a month straight
You would understand the rhythms you would understand the
Probably understand the worldview
You probably wouldn't understand where he's getting his ideas
From
A good bit of reading
Yeah
Involves clues that he doesn't give out very often
You know like those little things
It don't come up
But once every few months
Little signals video
Able to find out what he's talking about
You probably wouldn't understand that but you would understand the message
Very clearly
You doing that
Colin
And like six months
Very rare that he actually takes calls
So getting that training in the last six months difficult
I don't know
I think there's been enough okay
Anyway Alex's another thing
Overdrive
Power of the fourth hour
People calling in it doing at
That's a large part of it
And then the other part
Trump has sold them out by walking
Kickbacks
Alex B this might be a point
But he's out of step with his audience
Like they might be past him
Able
To match them because if he
.
He would
Nashua
Out now on Redbox
Red bar with pizza
Was Mike David Chicago podcast
Yeah yeah
I think I think he's out of step with his audience eclipsed him
They don't have a business
You does
He has to do this b******* about a White House
Petition to get them exposed
Suck it lets get pitchforks
Start screaming
So
That that
He also takes one call from a guy
Started
He wants to point out
Be careful with that
Because you can take two
Too much and it could be dangerous
It is very strong
Strong stuff
She done just turns into like a positive
Course
But it leads
Spiraling about t.i.
And just like
DeSoto
Talk about the iodine
Visit Alaska
And it is absurd way to try and sell iodine
Pills
7 years ago
I was coming a mile everyday exercising couldn't lose leg weight just poured off
Did I died
I was not impotent
But let's just say
I was like God when I was a teenager stuff
Remember that
Text manifestation
Is that
No wonder they're trying to keep it away from us
I'd like to remind you as a family
Just just to let you know in a while there it wasn't
Right
To get your big juicy
I don't know why my dick was big younger
When I was younger
I don't know why but the bad halogen
Coming in
Bromine
The fluoride and all that stuff
Yeah then it gets on iodine
It will not if you use
X2 survival Shield
Amazing
Grove
I don't know
I mean the family show but I don't know how
Your
Sitting here
With a straight face
And you're still pitched
The f****** iodine is
It made my dick bigger and also I lazy
Yeah
Yeah and I'm his baby lazy
Every part of it is iodine
Incredibly unhealthy loss was sober accumat is almost like I was on speed
And then I was like
Because I
It encouraged an unhealthy lifestyle wherein I got the results I wanted but
Almost miracle
I can live an unhealthy lifestyle with just the family show
This show sucks
So ridiculous
If I had to describe what this is
Triggering
Evoking
This absurd
Mexico Lobos
There is definitely yet you have to recognize the danger
He's doing
Bruised saddles
Implying
This woman
Omar
Is that
Cheese
A Muslim
Who's here to destroy America
Slightly lighter than which implies
Did anybody else who may look like her
You better keep them out of power
Sucks
So that's
That's not great
Are you saying
But when you built up this
Level of animosity
Beer about her
Spiritualist
Bucked up
And included
If you feel God
Leading a tour to be the instrument of vengeance
Playing with fire in such
Irresponsible way
Racist way
Such a
I pray nothing happens
I don't want get alarmist
And be like this is going to happen
But this is the way you would do it if you were trying to do it and keep your hands clean absolutely
You would engage in in
Operational terrorism without calling for it
This is
There is no better way
It doesn't mean that the result is going to happen
But
The
Set up
Is very cool
Yeah the results will happen or not
Way to get there is
Yes.
That's the situation
Throwing a bunch of
Shooting out all the pallets of murder
Yeah that's the way
It's deeply response
Know what I hope for anymore
With him
Yeah
He doesn't deserve violence to be done to him he doesn't deserve
I do I do I don't
I don't know where the law is
I don't know where that line is
I'm not a scholar
And those things so difficult for me
What should cause
Precipitate illegal
Consequence
I just think it important to recognize that this is what he's doing now in the off chance that something bad happens later
Because it does
2 Beats
He needs to be held responsible for his action
Absolute
Easily as a piece
Izzy's Pizza
Looks
Looks to be heading in a bad Direction
A little bit shorter probably but
Hey
I'm moving
Literally
So we come to the end of this and I just think this is deeply irresponsible but at the same time it snowed portent
You show this
Clear
I know the right word
Is almost
Farcical
Like the idea
Real
F******
Prejudice
Nativist racist
Agitation
Towards
Representative Omar
And then in the same show he's talking about iodine making your dick bigger
The family show
I meant taking a minute
I have to sing along with Pancho and Lefty
This is a f****** absurd
Kind of spectacle
I don't
If I hadn't been
Bathing in this for so long
I would look at this and I would just buy
Lafleur
It really is
But with the real dangerous
Potential it is it is fascinating especially because
Isn't it
Maybe Wednesday maybe Friday not a hundred percent sure as of yet
But we will see
But
Whatever the case
Outside it is knowledge
You bet it is
Where on Twitter
We haven't been we haven't been kicked off Twitter Dan
You haven't
Underscore fighting Garrett go to bed Jordan
You could download the podcast
Believer review
Yeah also won last week and a half or so you are
Chicago just want that at all
Terrible
Wanting Pizza
People want to come see you from Tuesday through Sunday
Shows at 8 p.m.
And then Friday
3 show Saturday
Absolutely wrecked
Also you almost
So will be
Until then
Elan Omar Adam killed anybody
Is Alex Jones
Alexandra Thurston color