Damned important
I have great respect for knowledge by now it's like I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guy
Need MoneyGram
Alex B
Nick.com
Beverages and talk a little bit
Shut up
I'm broke people
Anarchy
The most because I ain't
Designing him his own
Soundrop unique levels patients
So we are not so appreciative
About Alex Jones
Give a question
I don't know new apartment is
Who is good everyone wants
Is good everything is gone and I'm able to sleep in this house
Which is a massive Improvement alternative
Actually notice
But I just dumped
The plant watch
I have noticed in 34 days
Some of these plants
I'll really coming into the wrong are looking
Cuz you're happier
I don't know why
Think there might be something about the air hear something
Along those lines I don't know these
The Trinidad scorpions in the bhutlah hot peppers are really
Making massive progress over the phone
Couple days
Cancer affect
Queen is happy here
Adjusted quite well
Fantastic
Express their support
Going to put up with that
Wednesday off
It is much appreciated
And we are back and I promise
Stronger than ever
Interesting episodes that I wanted to do
But before we get to that guy
Give a shout out
Michelle
So first Jessie
Also known as our buddy
Thank you so much
Thanks everybody
Drew
Next George
George
Nextspace
Pkc thank you so much you are now probably walk
Journal biology Wang
Finally likes appreciate it very much
Thank you so much
You are now
Heroin
Freakishly large
Our website
Because I went to the website or our patreon
Not too long ago and stop there is a lot of
Messages but I've missed their messages there
That is not a good way to get in touch with us and I apologize that I've missed a number of messages there
I have so many inboxes I can I'm not good with one
Now we have added all these missed your message I apologize please resend a message
Do knowledge by the
Gmail.com
He'll be much more likely that I'll be able to
Answer it
What we're doing
It's something I felt what we needed
To do is something a little bit
I didn't feel like talking about the present day out
I didn't feel like going back to
Is the First new episode
His new studio
Moreland
Different
So what I decided to do was I remembered a long time ago I saw a video of Alex
Speech
Bilderberg
What is great
Let's go in
Check out one of
What is Bilderberg
2013 Bilderberg was in the United
Alex
The trip over to the UK
Give a speech
Yeah sure
Man-o-man if you watch this video it's completely in
They've set up a little middle of a field
He is yelling
Add a group of
It's in the hundred thousand
Alright
Middle of a field listen to Alex
So he's up there
And he is just
He's having a great
Living life
So we're going to listen to a little bit about
And see where this
Exploration
See what we can learn
Here's the first one first clip from Al
Are you giving
You know
No just talkin about the globe
As he's known
To do
As a lord
That was
Pretty Siri
Nonsense
Yelete with
From the
Exactly where Alex
Belongs riling people up with artificial passion about made-up subjects
Connected to reality and would like a union boss collage
Buddy would strike
So here's the next clip where are you
Explain
It will be remembered
Annals of History
This day
Bilderberg
This is going to be
That is remembered
By historian
Is the beginning of the end
For the goblins
The people love it
Rhetoric in it
Kind of
Passionate oratory that like
You got it
You see it in your life
Good or bad
Impressive
Skilled as a neutral skillets
Very amazing
To know how do you
Is very scary
Because you don't have Alex in the studio and he's such a
Without a crowd to work off of
He is kind of
OneNote
The present day
Goes out in like
Yells at abortion protesters
He's like just
With
A group of people in the palm of his hands
Something amazing to behold
On some level
Because you know he's full of s***
Evil version of life
Corporate Ross
Speaker like whenever I worked at my old job
They would have these conferences
Is every year
And you go to like
Las Vegas
Isn't there be
1000 people who do the same job is
Is Megan a tiresome
A****** to come out and be like
What are you doing
Yeah you could be could find a nice living in a lot of
Just be the most profitable and give him the most exciting
Yeah he's a real into yelling about a
Of manufactured imagine world
Power
Yep
Whitney
Easy to Coast on that for a good
I don't know half hour long
Target
But I don't know why for some reason in the middle of his speech
Gettington
It's great whenever you're just yelling abstract
The globalist
Just nothing you're saying nothing
Can't resist getting into
Specific drops
Narrative
In the middle of this dump
People in the UK
You can't resist show for too long
Do a headline real quick
Now first things first just a small quibble
Thousands of percentile point is 8.
Musical phrase
Specifically
Out of 100
You know that scent
In the middle of a giveaway of 100 100
I know that there are four months
Thurso left
In 2019 it was still in the clear to fact-check Alex's
Conspiracy
Is going to give 40% of the people in the United Kingdom cancer by 2020
It turns out
It's one that was
Nope
According to most recent data from the cancer research UK
595 person diagnosed with cancer per 100,000
Some people
So that would be
I would even go with thousands of a person if they were 40%
About 640,000
Prediction Alex
It literally
Boris Johnson is the new p.m.
And he still got four months
Large-scale like nuclear disaster
It would take something that would steal the headline
People have cancer
Soca 2013
Next Step
Evil globalist they're somehow going to give
A million people in the United Kingdom alone cancer
For real I don't know how anyone could just
Evil globalist cabal could pull that off
If they existed and wanted to
For some reason given the entire population
Here's an insanely short. Of time
426 million new
Go to be diagnosed
Alex is all trying to play this game where you staying at the globalist
Slowly trying to talk kill everyone
Put in the same breath
Cancer rate in the United Kingdom is going to jump
4.6
Percent to 40% in less than a decade
This is
Breakneck speed
Stupid
How long does it take to build
Freeman
That seems really really hard
Especially
Put their minds together a lot of cool stuff
So
Look there are plenty of people in the world who are trying to sort out why can't
Answer racing
In the world
And one of the biggest reasons that every scientist point is that we're living longer
In statistics clearly show that the risk Rises dramatically
And jumps again in the 80 or older
As our life spans of extended so two of the numbers of people surviving
The point
To become more dangerous
To excel
It's very easy to see how the single variable
Can explain a ton of Verizon cancer
Rate over the past
Fifty or so years
Some researchers in the UK
Suggested that
Two-thirds of the riots
Cancer rates in is
Clearly and see
Singularly attributable
Do that one variable
People living longer
As well to Rising rates of Obi
B3 putting people at a greater risk
Development
The popularity of
Tanning played a role in the rise of
Pollution
Factor carcinogenic
Access to our exposure to
Alex is also
So I dipped it in those trying to figure out like
What could you pay
We be talking about
Yeah cuz it's so crazy that sounds
And I figured out that he's misusing his
Statistic has included
A study done by a guy named Peterson
Gary
Cancer research
UK
A preliminary study in 2011 that Alex is most likely just
And then
Sesere followed up his
Study with a more in-depth study
It's flashed out his original finding
His show that approximately half of the people born
Since nineteen
60 would be diagnosed
Cancer in their lifetime
But
Intentionally misrepresent
An important qualifier with these data is
What's the Define their lifetime is being a fool
85 years
This is David's heavily skewed by the elevator
Set up to round
Answer ateez estimating our product
You see the general population
The number jump
August
There's a heightened risk of
Among the elderly
And if we all lived until we were 85
Then you'd expect about one out of every four people to have been diagnosed with cancer
The study literally says quote
The cumulative risk
Answer to age 40 is small
Teresa
The children teenagers and young adults will have little impact on the eventual lifetime
Business class
He's taking a headliner a study that says
Pretty Twisted to make his own son
Sensational
Completely absurd
Right I generally try to give his audience
The really big Ben
Personality
But I don't know how you can hear someone say that's 40%
In the next seven years
And not pick Theory
Complete idiot or a liar
It's just a testament to
And not even worried for a second that
His status is a leader of a guy who
Reads things
Is going to be threatened
It's not yes
Stranglehold
Do use the name of the song by guy you like
It's it's crazy
It's so beyond
The pale of what's acceptable
How you interpret those statistics
Suspect for a lot of those people especially the one that
Rally there
He started saying like
40% they were like okay cool
Let me know when you get back to yelling
Now they loved it really loved him just going like
I saw an article
Said 40% of people in the UK are going to die how about that
I don't know man
A terrifying
To think about like there was
Video that I found that was like
About Alex
And they interviewed some people who are there
And
At least a couple of them
Words
Confuse
About what was Alex Jones
He is informed
Conspiracy
So it might be a lot of them are just there because people like Alec
Around them
Well I don't like the
Power
And
Seems like a place where I can
This is where things are happening
You know the same way that people in the 70's
60s might end up at some weird hippie event
Don't really know exactly what's going on
I was told to come to San Francisco
Vectren
There might be a little piece of it.
Really scary
If you just wandering about
Good stuff I don't like
Yell so much
Breakthrough
Because in the middle of us had a power outage
Never fear the boulevard
Butts
It's pretty quickly
He doesn't actually enough
He probably just
Zaragoza
Freeman forum
F****** rock band
Yes
Dramatic
Super paranoid people where the power just goes out they must have been like
Professional wrestling
That moment when the power goes out is
We are about to get bombed
Physically look for themselves
Alex dimensions of secretive
Stylecraft
Sterilizing
How would you know if he wasn't there
Find I was there
We get back to this
But Alex's
One of his big narrative
In this
I don't know why
About how they're all going to get cancer
It's weird
Remember
When is Serena Williams child
Donating money to find
It's not a good metaphor
Analogy
Metaphor
You can do both
You're killing all the cops that's why we can't find out who
The budget
The problem is
Metaphors
Like that you really get
To have his brain
So essential
If someone is doing
Yeah
Just be something that is naturally occurring
Yeah we have to study it
To be able to
Understand better
Cars
Preventive measures
The early
Signal fires
Early
Didn't catch it
In time
All of this is
You can study and understand
And we have
Amazing
A beetle
Even then in his analogy
He's like why are you trying to
That's stupid
Well
No cancel
Zippyshare no totally that's someone's job like
Make the medic
Solve the Jack the Ripper mystery
And you shouldn't make the cop
Treat people in a hospital
It's a different job
So Alex gets towards the end of his pee
Features a lot of filler and a lot of just rambling
I am you start screaming about how you need to take all this very purse
Fremont
Question
World population
Debilitating
It's really good that he reframed rephrase the question long
Tell with his rhythm and meter on
This is definitely like
Ono Ono Ono water release
It's only sullenberger of here
Landing Landing question right in the hubs
Make it personal and take it
How you get angry about something
He wants everyone there
And what's the gold
You have like a thousand
We going to storm the castle
What's the goal
What do you mean like afterwards like when the rally
It's obviously making more money for our
Alex
What it like does
Distend
I don't like full video of what happens like 2 hours after
Blow up the Bilderberg
And some it's something
I never went back to their lives and their Infowars
Everything was good everything was copacetic
Especially because
Alex
I don't actually want any action.
Like if you go to
This is Bi-Rite
Whatever you do
By becoming aware of the things that I'm telling you
We have already taken the necessary action
No
If I went to a Bernie rally and he was just
Alright
You heard me
Let's get on out of here we had a great time hearing my message we have
Now how many yellow box
Crazy rally
With almost
No effort
It's crazy
That's bananas
Right now I tell you what my camera person
Huge crowd of people thousands and thousands and thousands more than turned away
That's so Trump
Who did turn away from this
Beatles
I don't know what
Overflow
It's
Just cuz I don't believe it
No it's not true
That pathological need to over blow
What kind of
Draw you have a malignant narcissism
Very strange it manifests in such a similar ways
Any people who
The time had nothing
Become in
Text Rick
From each other
Very bizarre
So Alex
Great
The sun setting
Time of day perfect match
Magic hour
So I wanted to do this and I wanted to talk about this
Like his ability
With a crowd is important to not forget that
Maybe he's lost some of his step cuz I don't
Do that now he probably freak out
No not not know about of her before
It's going to allow him to
Just six years
That I think it's important important part of his story
Stump speech
Without trying to get into narrative
And just like
It's pretty remarkable
Incredibly bizarre
The Jordan
Do an episode that was
Just about
I need to tell you something
It was somebody else who gave us
YouTube that exact same Rally's
No
Hi again I a go do you f****** don't
Don't you goddamn don't how dare you
Call your lovely face
Kerry Cassidy
The fluid to the United Kingdom ticket to hangout if you Fringe
Or whatever it was
And us
She gave a speech
Yes I think earlier in the day
I don't think she got as Prime of
And believe me she complains
She did not get a prime placement on the schedule
Seems to be a little bit of a sticking point
To give a 20-minute speech
That is
Completely bizarre
Bilderberg
Right
You know pretty receptive audience
Don't you
Insane conspiracy-minded people who
Who gather there to Galaxy World Elite
Be a billionaire a billionaire
That's it
Yeah and I don't want to come down too hard
Define past
Certainly
Even so it does attract
May have some
Even if the actor yelling at billionaires
Completely
Good on you
Security gives the speech
And we'll get into it we're going to ever going to listen to
Eclipse here.
Is a 22-minute
Also
Here we go this is her complaining about her
So I don't know if I should wait until the rest of the crowd gets back over here so
Repeat myself
I'm at living here because actually I was supposed to speak
Try to grab my spot again at 6
Because we were hoping to broadcast it live in California
As you know the time difference is kind of bizarre so
It's sometime in the morning or like a weekly ad
Something like that in California right now
Cover Springs
Complaints about the time fly
Had some kind of router whatever kind of things go in from
And that
The government
What
Carpet of course I don't know if other reason why
Why you walk in here and do that because you had nothing better to do
So the router is gone
Got2b
Yeah the government is coming taking the router
The Chicago boy
That's like when you're on stage opening riff
So bad that you have to derail everything
Visible
There's a number of times but it does look like she's responding to someone giving her a light
I don't know what happened
Schedule time slot was supposed to be how long
If she is going long I have no idea
But this is not a good set
I don't
Feel bad criticizing
For reasons it'll come up later
It might seem like we're being very hard
Embarking
What is
Probably 20 minutes
Thrilled
Are recorded
Consideration
The first is you posted this on Broadway
Second
Hold those thoughts.
Text Carrie talking about how she
She's too big
YouTube
To be giving a speech
In the morning
On a hill deserve by
English-style because I don't understand
How do you have a prep
Area that's the same as the place where the people demonstrate
The meeting goes on over there
A from for example The Washington Post the New York Times
UK Guardian
Or other papers that that might want to interview
You me tomorrow or actually Sunday
At least have a shadow
Obviously has a pretty big
Profile out there
I have a fairly big one
You know not
Trying to to be egotistical here at least we have a problem
She kind of insulting literally everybody else is there
It's kind of sociopathic Behavior
You got it was soon
At least
Adorable
Cross-section of the people who are there
Who travel to Bilderberg BLT billionaires
Fancy themselves citizens
There's probably a great number of people who have
Their own blogs their own
Vlogs
At this point
For her to be like you know like you know there's
Notable media
Places they're not even here
The somewhere
The other than Alex Jones I got a following
That was really
Brood
Bilderberg
What is she
She didn't have anybody
I don't I don't know where Bill and I do know where
Partner Bill Ryan
Project
You know there is a very rare type of
Performer
And they love it
Can get up on stage be like
Absolutely
Very rare steak be able to pull that off around 7
As the example
Kind of clothes
Insult people
Jeselnik
I guess some people
Charming
Carrie's
Even
Trying for that
The very people
H2O
I'm big
The router got stolen dumbfucks don't even realize that the government
Crazy
I don't know why she brought up the router
Call I don't know
That's interesting to me
You solved the mystery that no one else has
Elevate yourself
Above the rabble
Even more
For those of you who don't let me just say that my specialty is whistleblowers
From Above Top Secret
And 7 years
Long before Wikileaks with Denver and ideas somebody's head
Suck it. They're actually traveling the world
Interviewing whistleblowers and what we do is we would put the camera there and I would ask them really the heart
Hard question
For like 2 hours straight and narrow Boris Intuit
Shimoni's on the web
We have luckily been able to certify
History speaks
Made a pilot for a TV series
Scare the s*** out of them
TruTV that they put it on the shelf for two years
Finally released
He just slipped it in on truTV
You got touch with us at just ahead of time 24 hours in advance
Theirselves
The money from various
Witnesses that we do have
I have an alternative theory about how that went down
This show is
We can't put this out
Let's bury it sometimes luck is work
Contractually obligated
TV show
Very bad
You're not worth it
I would say
The child
Recovering project
Camelot I mentioned a guy named Andrew basiago
Doing a project Camelot interviews
I don't think
He has
Weird
Speeches about how
Time travels with Obama
Children
Teleport it to the moon and works on a base
Something along those lines
Half dolphin
Ikea open
He's got a lot going on
He doesn't need to have that right
One of my favorite not of this world
I've always been very disappointed that I couldn't
Find it
Kmart project
Warren
Them team
It seems like they be chocolate and peanut
He's in the season
You one of the people that interview with the truth
PVC
So I was like
Maybe that's what I
Thought
I don't know
I don't
Future give you some f****** idea with it
V-series what threatened to put it on the Shelf
Carrie
Billiard name
Now she's doing a promo
Problem Child
Adele-hello Rothschild I know after I visited him here
Okay
So I want you to understand for the past
7 years
Legitimately so to speak in the public what the New World Order is really doing
Secret government is really doing
Who's really running the planet
And what's going on and how do you put those sort of ducks in a row so that you understand it
And then once you understand the planet
I'd like to draw Sharp
Attention to how when Alex was speaking the crowd was going nuts
There was a crowd
I don't think there's much of a crowd here you can kind of hear babies walking around
People talking in the background
I don't know if I have any of the
Where is having somebody else having an interview
Like on stage
Today there was a
I think I built the stage later
Victor junior varsity tent
Somebody's somebody's like do you want to go across the field and see Belle and Sebastian cuz this
Okay festival or whatever
So important to point out like this
Various
Exquisite connect
Between Alex
Project
B-both soffit
To travel to the
The UK
To give a speech in the same
Around Bilderberg 2013
Crazy
Weird
It's very weak
Sing everybody
Through the beginning of this I'm too big
To be given speech
For WikiLeaks
Sure why not sure lock nuts
And she continues being insult
If you give you some
Set up
This was part of a much longer stretch
It was still unclear to talk about
Is talking about how
The real people hookah
Control the world
Underground
So then what is she doing there
Exactly
There's a piece of this like
Bilderberg ain't shitt
Spectro vs. like if they're having this
I'm here then that means
They're not afraid of being open about what they're doing
Okay
I don't know
Insulting
The very idea of all these people who have called
Yellow billionaire the Bilderberg
FaZe this isn't
This isn't the real go to aldebaran or whatever
Instead of the marionette
Bright
Actually do it from underground and from planet so they're doing it replaced
A base on Mars and the Moon
Interstellar
Maybe radical thinkers
Let me Translate
You don't
Talk to the same nutty people that I do and believe them
You guys think you're smart
You didn't talk to this guy in the Rothschild
You haven't talked to a murderer
Who hangs out with rapper
Nope
From The Darkside into the light
Can deliver a message
It has been weighing on your mind
Import of what they know and what it has what's the meaning of that is for Humana
That's the nature of a whistle
Tasha Smith
Has Ashley
Cuz they start to realize
What's really been contributing to
Which is the device
Humanity as we know it
No claws
You cut that part out
Nope
Not really there's one part where she gets the round of applause
When she says the people in charge of the United
Another route
It's not it will receive
Upset
With the Whistleblower stuff
I think our investigation
Of the people that
CiCi's Pizza
Indicate
Are monkey Rosewell
What
One part one cross-section of America
Like someone
Cross-section of the people that you talk
Post-traumatic stress
Disorder
Or something else
That is leading them to class
Taking advantage
The second group are continents
Just people like Sean David Morton
Outright car
Mark Richards is a f****** conman murderer
I don't know exactly what Simon parkes is up to but he is a f****** cock
It's so speed through its
Pikachu
These people are just people
Waze on their country
I want to help Humanity
Get the f*** out of here
Fun mythology
Feels like she's trapped yourself into it
Like she is completely trapped into that mythology
For her to go from
These people are heroes traveling from the dark
Into the light
And then wind up with like
Oh my god I've spent the last two years in 2013
6 years ago
Teen years of herb saying
Cogman are heroes
It all ripped away from her at 8
Bit too much of a blow to recycle
Yeah there's no
Like
That's basically being deprogram from a cult after you your entire family has
Chosen to stay there
You know there's more
She might
Beyond board widths
That I might have some
Give a s*** about making fun of her having a bad day
I think I might turn the corner on this lady okay
Her expressive narrative
Global Elite
They're trying to create
Anu
Human
You're not
Involved
You and your family are not apart of the future according to the
Club
So they're working very hard on Humanity 2.0
You're not perfect.
And if you're not at the right bloodline
Combination
You are simply not part of the future here on planet Earth and neither are your children
Well yeah they're in your children
To figure out what their genetics are coming in
Where am I
Alright
I'm on board I don't believe
Leave you but this is where I kind of like
To go where
F****** Wolverine
We're going to get into
Fanfiction
Can get onboard
Oh no but it's almost route no no
Different riddle
Why are autistic child
Children
So that there was more autism now than ever before and the reason
They're doing that because they're looking for precogs
Between being a vegan autistic child
Autism
Oh God
How how do you f****** ruin
The X-Men real you got a throw-in this b******* of autism
Why can't you have fun
You're making s*** up why you have to Moline
It is like a weird simultaneous
Dehumanizing of all autistic people is
His creation
The government
Will the same time attributing their autism
As a superpower
Like
Dick move
Dickish all over the place
What fun we could have had absolutely
To be like there
Autism or the water gives
Autism or whatever
In order to be like
There's just something missing
Physical happening
Blame
Bothers me
It also
Clones are in
Play okay that's good
Presidents of United States
George Bush for example is one example that has been used numerous times that you know the younger
Understanding is
Who are you
Wednesday really clone a lot are the sort of
Pyramid
The second level
Those people like
The people in there actually
Notice of the crowd didn't laugh
Settings
Or something
Now this is where things get real weird cuz what do you think
She's talking about
Like with clowns
Interesting
That's how I that's how I usually take
These people
Is there feel on clones right right
Quesadilla
More
Reasonable
Conspiracy universe
Motive
Send
Have like
If I am
Two or whatever I become political
Relevant figure
You could start
Clone
I don't know 2002
You have the forming organ
How to grow the clock
That's dumb but it makes sense
Are we are we carrying these as
Are we are we
Creating
Clowns and then putting them in
Women to give birth to
Growing them
Like a like I tried to grow meat
Here's the problem
No
Carry Steam
To be operating under the assumption
Like if I were to call myself right now I could
You just have another day
Like another 45 girl thing
Wonder One
In this next
Scorpi talks a little more about the Clone
They use them to
Menial tasks.
So if George is George W bush needed to give us
She didn't want to give
He could send a poem but the way the truth operator
Clone doesn't last all that long but they can certainly control them
Ashley
Transparency
So David Cameron to come out giving a speech about
They don't last long how long do they last
Terry
Mary what is the median
Just like welcomes only last about 2 to 3 weeks
Have
Form of consciousness
But they can be controlled
Are there identical
To you
Wow also
The top of the older topic
The Clones would be old
You're not replicating you're not like creating a new generation of rice rice
You can't transfer The Conch
Dismissed
But you can different process
Is real
And then refuses to explain it
It's very frustrating
Scary insults
Harper Hempel
Especially someone as far as The Fringe as I am is one
Have a few people even with all due respect
Baby
For sure
Probably at the same hotel with Bilderberg people are at
Give a f*** about all you people sitting out in the fields
UPS
Security guards
He's a billionaire operation compared to you Podunk
Give a give a
He's out there
Million-dollar Steakhouse
Getting getting his meat on before he has to go out there and sweat from
The face yelling about the global
That's always one of those
F*** you for
Yelling about
If Jesus was a rich person also is Legend wouldn't have
Gone on as long as
Be like
F*** you
You know there's that there's a really interesting
Ecosystem
What's going on here
Inasmuch as
Alex
As the celebrity
Either comes in
Endgame
Exposure for the people who are all there
Some form of alternative credibility
All the failures who are there
Mysteries
Support
Feedback in
This is
How many parasitic for Alex
But it's also
Tubi
Yeah.
Symbiotica valix list
Did those people
No
Or even
Behind it never make
Any progress
Towards something
Sitter if there was truth
I realized
Oh that's never going to think about that help make it more
Symbiotically right advancing towards working together
We're in reality what's going on conscious or not all of those people who are
You're not necessarily carry
Because she's on some other s***
Billionaires in Bilderberg and I have blogs about it
Aspire to be is the Alex
The person who gets the
Rousing cheers
They don't actually want to take down anybody what does that look like
No of course not what do we do do we
Keep yelling
Yep
They want to be on the neck
Next level of the hustle
And because I was understand
Daddy can't allow more talented people
Access to
Embarrassed
The hustle is all very transparent
Hey take a step back
Watch some of the speeches of other people
Comments
Situations like for Alex it absolutely is a zero-sum
Means that I lost
It's not like
This comes around and everybody
It's like f*** you
Didn't get out of my face
So curious one last clip we're going to listen to hear from her speech
I told you she did get Applause
USA
Is run by Nazi
Woohoo
60 years later
She's finally right
Well she's going
What you got from that
And she's going to explain why she
She came to the UK
Free American
I'm over here because I was really important for America to come to Britain
And my truth
And basically
I know I'm on a mission and I'm not going to stop
Human being on the planet
So she wanted
Eagle this riff
Between the United
State mean
But I'm here to say that
I think she brought
Long-standing Alliance
Special friendship between countries back to homeostasis
I think we should all appreciate it
History books
Remember this day
As first of all the beginning of the end for the globalist absolutely
Between
The United Kingdom in the United
Text Carrie
Between the United
Which is why
Needed to go there
You know what you're probably not far off that I was farther off
Probably
You are not true
So
One of them things that led me down this road
Towards
No I don't know if there's any Redemption
Profound
I was watching
Some new
Please put out a couple things I think she was on vacation
Or something and now she's come back
Boring shift
She's posted
What you posted one video that was just
Her sitting in a webcam
Talking about alien intervention
And how there's aliens
Real messed up
All around
I watched the video and I realized
Massive
What we have never done
Is really heard
Explain what
He thinks is going on
And then is at most she's like
And I agree with you this is also
I realize that there might be
Some stuff babe
Because she is just
In front of a camera
Okay and
This is Rick
Her beliefs are really f*****
This works
Clippers
Expressing how little
Evidence she requires to believe
Hi everyone
About my lady
Article
He was drinking
Or
Real quick I did try to go to website
I got a warning
Message that it was trying to install
First of all the
I got on my website
The Anunnaki
Escorting
Human
Prisoners along the beach
Actually that came out a long time ago and
I just
Brought it to service again I can say that
Orillia photograph
The movie
Or or what
But it looks
Real to me
Anyway I thought it was accurately
Depict
What is really
Going on
I did find this picture
I don't care
Kind of proof of aliens
Pictures of it looks real
This is how you get tricked by someone like 80-page give you a picture of a f******
Completed your ship its
Video game like this is hot like
Your bar is Sophie
Walking low
Busy with crazy
These people who are in these
He's questioning community
I'm out there I'm asking the hard questions
About this stuff
You don't ask any questions of your own shoe
It's that it shows
WowWee lawyer
Walking bar
I saw this picture
That could
Could be from the movie
I have no independent verification of it
I don't know
Bobby maybe if she was maybe if I heard the whole thing I would
She would say I think this
Picture itself is real
But from what I understood her to be
Expressing
It was.
The picture is a good representation
Is
She said that at the end
Right
She said it looks
So well I mean
That
The picture doesn't matter
It doesn't matter if the picture
Real or not because it represents what I think is going
Terrified
Proof proof
It's confirmation
Bias
That flies in the
Space of
Where's the need for absolute
Pretty scary cuz you could talk yourself in
Like she has
With
Here's where we get in
It was a picture of the Anunnaki
Who are transporting
To the spaceship
2 in her cancer
Tuner the good guy
Nice like the Raptors
The Palladium
Nordic race
In Lavale
The Graze their meddling no good
Just like little robot workers
And then of the bedside you have the reptilians
And the Anunnaki
Together
We're all that s***
Here's where she talks
It's about some people who are involved
I don't want a problem with any assessment of the future is
They do not seem to incorporate an understanding of
The fact that the dinosaur
Actually descended
Call boy
And that they have an agenda which is
As an alien race
Call Valerian tablet
Zachariah stitching information
Stitches
That reveals
Here on Earth
Zecharia sitchin had no business
Translating
Sumerian Tablets
She's been roundly criticized
Horrible
Information
And here we have Carrie saying that
Because of
He's information that was released
She has an understanding
Are the ancestors of the Anunnaki who are they
I don't believe that she's things I missed
Didn't mean any
Other than Jews
She was just Hawaii
Like
The Jews are
Descended from the Sumerian
The Sumerians are descended
From the Anunnaki
As well
Are all weapons
Yeah
Whatever wherever the Sumerians come from
What's important is that Designer
Which I have to stress
Of course he doesn't
Zionist
Political philosophy
Jewish
Little boy
If you don't understand the role of the Anunnaki in our
Pass
Then you're never going to understand
Israel
They are a fierce race their highly intellectual
Kazari and Jews have the Anunnaki
Bloodline
They're also involved
With Antarctica
I may say that
Disclosure I have some Jewish
Lucky and me
And I whisper
Respect I on Wednesday that
David ickes work
Although I
I don't think his analysis goes to
Corporate
The bigger picture
Picture of the ET involvement on
On planet Earth
To the degree
Project Camelot does
So when she's saying that she has some Jewish blood in her which means she has some Anunnaki in her that means
But she believes that
Jews are on an
Fuk up
So f***** up David Icke
David Icke
Is very gorgeous
He tries to fight back
What you're talkin about what shape
Shifting lizard
That's your just you mean Jews
Right you're using anti-Semitic
Troop to describe these
Lizard beings
Control the world
And he says no I'm not saying that I'm saying
Lizards
Factory
Joe Haden
It's crazy to me and I know that we've heard Slickers
Suffer being a kind of anti-Semitic
When I watch this video is like
Juicery
In front of a camera by herself 40 f****** minute
If he starts explaining that the the Jews
Are the Anunnaki
It's really really f***** up what you
It's
It's an indication to me
Of
Very
80 summative
Yeah so what's your first name
Are the descendants of Anunnaki
Say that
Laters
She says
That
You have to understand
Anunnaki or behind Israel is
And then what you said that
She has Jewish blood and that makes her
Four-part Anunnaki
That to me was like
You have gone
So far beyond the point where this is
Defensible
This is just you
The Jews are aliens
Is what you were saying
Look in this
You'll see
There are many International
National instruments that way
Involves only
Human
But it was Ashley
Standoff
One set
Incident
USA
Liberty
Israel
Is another such
WWE
Spiders in
Vietnam
Spider-Man
Touch
Situation
And
So we got the spider leadership in the mix
Like that is
It seems pretty cancer
She has
A
One last hurrah
Devices
Explain what she believes about the world
Israel and Jews
Are Anunnaki
They are alien
Right that is unacceptable
This is a completely
She's crazy grandpa at Thanksgiving dinners
Just like and you know what I think
Oh my God I mean like
Exist
Disorder
Next Level Auto
Why
What
You're a hop skip and a jump away from Holocaust denial whatever you're you're into
You were
You're in that ballpark baby
SA
So if they are Anunnaki
Frank
You're basically saying that they did the Holocaust
Themselves
Essentially
If you want to follow that kind of logic of the Anunnaki or always eat
The Holocaust was a good
Whoa I mean
Yeah that's why you really have to write
YouTubers are on and not really have to ask her
I don't want to speculate what you might believe
The possibilities you're bringing up I would not be surprised anymore to here I come out
Yeah makes sense for you to say that yes
She doesn't believe that the Anunnaki are good
There
This is bad
Various
She's proven
But you have a bruise
For a little bit
Condescending
Bulshit
Would you like
If you don't understand this
Stuff you sound
Dumb
A picture of a Deadpool
I think we mostly hear her when she's in a good mood I just come from talking to me
Everybody knows things knows that you sound stupid
If you don't
Understand
Holy Ship
Big hat
Video izle
Nothing else matters
Directions to another episodes Project Camelot
Listen to layout that you believe
Jewish blood makes you a descendant of the Anunnaki f******
Hell
Beautiful pictures
More life
Jesus so whenever she says that you sound stupid if you don't know the
To me I take a little bit person
To be called stupid
And
Then there could be some other races I I do things
The name Antarctica
Actually sounds to me like
Dominated by ants
Our inspector
Okay alright
That's what it called
I love that I love just that idea of Illinois
That is I know everyone's
Yeah
This is
Bizarre kind of carryout like
I want to listen
That's fine
Fight
Can't accept
Also
Cutest
Without being prejudiced
Pictures of living a more fun world without having to be like at all
But you know what the reason
Is
All
This symptoms
Of the underlying problem
She's f****** stupid
It's terrible source
Get information from a lot of places
That are full of bigot
Yeah this
This world interests
With a lot of really really
F***** up dangerous
Mentalities in the world
Like a conspiracy in paranormal World iron fortunately
With people who have ulterior motive
And also believe
60s James Fetzer on the show
It's fairly regularly
The guy who wrote that no one died
The Holocaust
Yeah
That
People
Intersect are allowed to live in this world you know they're allowed to be looked at as
Interesting thinkers
Yeah
Except like James Panthers ideas about false flag
It makes it much more like
You might also
And that exist
In a thousand different places
Paranoid
Spiritual world
The internet message board
Someone having a
Appoint
You like about Alexa
Would you consider why
If you consider why you're only
45 attempts away from believing Jews real
Eddie's it is important to remind yourself
Always said
Being racist
It is incredibly
Stupid
It is so dumb
Because it doesn't make any sense based on
Exploit
Perfect sense
There's a huge like Alex
Alex
But explain races
It's a business strategy
It's easy to do but
Just amazed
Unfortunately
From now on
My friend are an anti-semite of the highest order
Following your logic
To its conclusion is not even
You are a very very weird kind of give you that
That's true
And all racism even sit up with like kind of
The fun aliens
It's not any more interesting it's not any more admirable it doesn't have any better
Still the same
Ugly bigotry
You should be ashamed of yourself
So read
Things that aren't
Dumb book written by your friend
Vigilante
Yeah
In terms of an episode that I would like to do having moved
Like a
Yeah breaking in the new studio I feel like it's appropriate
Jumeirah
New Beginnings
We have an understanding
Carrying out
What's were in the same
Place
In 2013
And also carry
Believe
Yeah
So
I walk away from this champagne bottle equipment
Cuz it's close to it
Episode the very first episode of the new apartment I think
Perfect
Absolute
On Monday
Hey baby
Knowledge fight.
That's right
We also are on
Twitter knowledge underscore
Ross on face
We are on Facebook
You could get the podcast by going to your iTunes
Your computer or you could use your pot
Cast app whichever one
Bright lights are on an Android
Other people
Find your podcast app
Go ahead and talk
I say if you're going to grow some peppers
You could probably find our podcast there
Peppers
Justin grow pepper in Osaka
Guaranteed
George Bush
She's not
Clone
I have never killed anybody
Because they don't exist
Is that
Alex