Dammit
I have great respect for knowledge but I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Need money
Stripe.com
Jones what's up
Have you ever had
Maybe
Maybe I don't know not to not to the point where it's ever been.
Or anything like that one time I got sun poisoning on a float trip
It's quicker
Version of sunburn
It's much worse
I will
I only because my friends when I said that I went to the doctor
Like nothing I've ever
My cousins all over my body
Through my skin at all times
To the point where I was almost crying
Cold bath
Yeah just alike
Not Victor
Fight back in the way that I felt made sense
And I would lay in bed on my stomach
Biting the corner of my macro have to fight
It was
Brutal truth
But I was just drunk by the time we started floating
I was like 20
Yeah
It was if I recall correctly
Believe this
The same year that I got a mice
Temporary tattoo
Temporary tattoos
If I put it on my arm I put it on my arm
As we were floating down the river is my Big B that every time we passed somebody else
Starhub sun poisoning didn't start hurting until like
You know what I got back
It was one of the worst
I think I actually ended up
Having to drop out of a college class
Because
It was a summer school class
3 days
Because it's like really
Yeah summer school schedule
We're going and talking to the
The professor
But that's
The time that the sun has hurt me the most
Considered
Message
Where's
Come f****** sunscreen
Don't be like me
It was a dumb kid
Stupid
About sun poisoning
We got really interesting in-depth episode
That we will touch on
And go over today but before we get to any of that I believe that
To spend a little time
People have signed up
Banner sporting the show and they call this pop
First
A.m.
Mtti thank you so much
State Park
Next Hawk plus Moogle
Final-fantasy-vii is it okay
Yeah it's one of those things where I'm sure some of these names are references to things that I don't know what they are and I'm glad it's Final Fantasy
Because anyone could probably slip through
But I just assumed as a crazy name is
Well that's not the problem that's a member of the third right cool
Didn't know
Uber
Ruben Figueroa
Google
Next
Donated on elevated level
Very much so Taylor thank you so much
Business
Is freakishly large
Taylor Taylor
Like Sport with a dude you do that by going to our website
Sport the show button we would appreciate if we loved it entirely listener
So thank you Miss two episodes
And then we're just a bad
In general so weird that's what I'm talking about
Prediction
At the end of this episode
Back around for that yeah
We're doing is going over some 2013 stuff and we're going
February 27th
Tomorrow
And
Spoiler alert Alex
For a large
He's only in studio on the 27th and 28th
Comes back on
Mike Adams
One of his dumb employees Aaron dykes
Fills in as a host
Like you just gets guest host
Tefillin
And honestly I believe
Even the surrounding time
He's on vacation in his head
Like on the 27th
There's really not a whole lot to go over can we come back on the 10th there's nothing that I saw fit to pull as I
There's just nothing
He's checked out he knows that he needs to go on vacation
He knows he's going to be gone for a nice week
Yeah suck it is senioritis
Is over guys
Really not much to go over
Go back to the ER to try and have a better understanding
Bird
In particular we're seeing
A lot of
Trends that are clearly related to the phenomenon that's happening in the
Conspiracy world around
The popularity of the
Conspiracy videos about it that
Truther
Kim Coates videos about it
The way Alex has started covering all of the
These shootings with
Rank suspicion
Glom into that market
Anything
Nothing
Stretch
Think about cuz
Sometimes when we're doing the 2013 episodes
I'm almost
Oh that's right we're talking about Sandy Hook
These are so often unrelated
It is interest
To think about what's bubbling
Around Alec
He may be talking about some
Random and weird
All the wild in the background on YouTube
New Sandy Hook
Truther
Pretty
Like it's it's bubbling up
And there is almost like
I would assume
On some level Within
The ranks have been thinking like why aren't we
Moron
And you know what the other thing that I'm
About the I think it's a failure of whatever we can
Can do as an investor
Navigation
Is it we're not covering
Infowars nightly
Okay Alex's cohorts
Are doing their report
Yeah people like robbed David Knight who work there at the time
I believe Jakari Jackson
Doing the Nightly News
Like they
Might be covering Sandy Hook s*** more
Right hasn't made it to Alex's
Is Varsity show
He don't come up and he does definitely think the globalists did it
Them it isn't
Steven slow-play
For sure
Just nothing going on
So are the only thing that I really feel
Like is worth talking about comes up on
Vacation
Alex
Terrible terrible mood
And it's because of a bill
He is caught window
So we got this bill do sexually to bills
Alex is responding to reporter Melissa
This morning
He's completely lost his mind
Sp6
3in sp6
Sp63 allowed some children
To consent to receiving vaccines without parental permission
He's doing some heavy lifting in that sense
According to Texas
Pre-existing family codes there are a ton of instances where a child
Consent to their own Healthcare decisions
Regardless of what their parents say
At least 1995 a child can make their own medical decisions
Horror if abuses espectador
If the child is sick
Treatment-related
The drug addiction
There plenty of events
This is where the state rightly realizes a demanding parental consent
A treatment would put a child's life
Level of concern
Is not required
B63
Symptoms of when a child
Consent to their own Healthcare with specific language
Did sp60
C3 was to make it explicit that a child can control their own vaccinations
Decisions
Or has a child of their own that's all of it
It's really crazy cuz
What's the coverage of this device freaking out
Dreaming about it
It's just rambling about other governments tried to kill every
Event for SPC
64 this is really the
Justin Amanda gov text
Human resource
Today the people who work at license
Childcare facility
Need to be immunized for vaccine
Preventable disease
Which
Yeah it would be infuriating as I last night at the was working
Somebody was a anti vaxxer
And I went
The crowd really never know
He was giving me some like
So anyways
I was just out about that about
Amending the codes like
How to save it till you know that's pretty.
Discriminatory
People just don't want to get vaccines or whatever Pepsi
Discriminating against people
Here's the problem this amendment sp60
Before explicitly says that they're probably will quote
Include procedures for facility employees to be exempt from required vaccine
He goes on to say that it'll formulate guidelines quote
For a facility employee who is exempt
Required back
Include procedures
The employer must follow to
To protect children
Under the facilities
Care from exposure
Such as
Protective
Medical equipment including gloves and mask
Based on the level of risk the employee presents.
Two children by the employees were
Those are the children
They have a paragraph about how they need
Prohibit discrimination
Or retaliatory Act
Employees exempt from the required
For something it's allegedly supposed to be about forcing everyone to get shots
Seems like sb-6
For is going out of its way to accommodate people
Who are exempt
I'm getting shot
I respect that
I do
Maybe don't go
That
Accommodating accommodating at all then you have to go really far because it had Row Place the guy
Guidelines in order to accommodate the people who are
But you need to either going into got to go a mile
Necessarily
Some of the people who would be exempt
From the vaccination requirements
Appropriate
And right to do that
But sb64 explicitly require
Are vaccines
Conscience
Including a religious belief
That bill is not forcing anyone to get shots
It's clearly about Harbor adduction and protecting the health
Children
Respect the political and religious beliefs
That lead people to argue that they don't
Need to get shot
African comedy
Explicitly says Melissa Melton morning
28 to 20 30
And that's why he's in such
The f*****-up mood on this show and Trust
He is not great on there
Both of those bills were introduced
The Texas Senate
On November 12th 20
It's been a quarter of a year since those bills were introduced
And somehow is cracked
Had just now figured out about that
These people
Are the tip of the spear
Tip of the spear
They are the Vanguard in the fight
Bills from
6 months
Just to be
A clear about this and really illustrate my point
Here is Alex Jones
63 was introduced
This week
Did last week
Which indicates to me that he either is very comfortable making s*** up
But he doesn't know was introduced in November
It has to be one of
I was very calm
We've got the number 63 number 6
No I mean he's just a liar or an idiot
There's no two ways about it
I mean I'm going to give
I am going to go out of my way to give him the benefit of the doubt but maybe
And she just
Wanted to cover it up there's a possibility possibility
Accepting other people's made
They're all bad
I'm not going to shake me from that
Alex
In order to
Like know what's going on through this stretch of
February 27th to March 3rd
That's it
In terms of the stuff that I think deserves coverage in our show
Not a lot
So what is episodes
Co-host
Suffer not really worth
While
Alex is a giver
You know.
I often sign
Whenever they're really bad stretches
You'll find something
That merits discussion
There is one such thing that happens during February 27th 2013
Episode that sent me on
A very interesting Crusade
Oh really terrifying
Into
Potential things that Alex Jones believe
A contact
Do some of the things that we talked about for quite a while
So here is that
From February 27th
The Bible says
Always talks about
It's so big in his
He's he's constantly around the 26
15 election
He always talks about how they can't give us a reprieve
Right
It's so consist
He's always
Just buying time we heard on
Was the last episode of doing before it where he's talking about his dog
Where he
Do you know how to write
12 quarts
I think he has probably
Weird ideas about what's worth
Artificially continuous
I've always found a really interesting when Alex gets specific why what sorts of religious
Figures he thinks pause
Yeah like
Really negatively about a lot of fun
But you hate
The glitterbug churches the
Consistently negative I like
The Prosperity Gospel.
In the mainstream Christianity
Enemies
Infiltrated
But I really never found the degenerate
To specifically about what sorts of religious
Influences
Things are good right has he ever told us like oh I go to this church
I think I'll be unsafe for the church for Edsel
No I don't I don't I don't
Inappropriate
It's weird for me to make an assumption
What about it but I would be fairly surprised
We know basically that he thinks demons Walk Among Us that he's in a literal battle with a literal death that the Rapture is happening
After the tribulation
Afterwards
Within that conveniently allows them to blend these ideas of religious piety and righteous trench warfare
That's great
This Clifton we just heard as part of an interview with a woman named Katherine Albrecht
It's supposed to be about the RFID chip put in everybody but it quickly
To have these RFID chips of the little rolled biblical mark of the beast
And from there it's just a hop skip and a jump for them turn the show into outright televangelism everybody's got to get right with God
Crazy
Christian
Tell me that
Be literal Market
Never heard that one
In the middle of this Alex
Katherine Express
And that they're just going to have to survive
This is going to be important to me sites
The figure to agree
With him
The wrestler interviews boring so I decided to check in
After what
What is referencing
Am I got told me you would leave me so
Somewhere weird
Smith
Skier figured people like you and me
And the world
Right
His name is
Ones that only a very specific sort of person would bring up in conversation
Particularly in a positive way
As someone whose opinion you should take
Seriously
In 1980 David Smith founded the Church of God Evangelistic
Association
Every broke away from the worldwide Church of God
The worldwide Church of God intern was founded by Herbert Armstrong
1931 under the name the radio Church of God
Pat's Church
Possibly
So Armstrong's career was characterized by doomsday predictions that routinely failed Summit
Serialized
You're a pretty good run and when it was all over his influence would be pretty substantial
Hawkwind on the way
Too late 1970s things were not going great for his church
Armstrong son was trying to start a splinter group and he's been excommunicated from the group
Armstrong's wife passed away she remarried a woman half a century younger than him
Accusations Amalfi's
A flying around him all over the place
So it only makes sense
Enterprising member of that group with
You did the right time to start their own thing
And that's exactly what David
Started his Church of God Evangelistic Association
Too far from
Some of the basic tenets of Armstrong theology
British Israel
Which mites
Strike you as a foreign
No no because
Of course I would
I would put together Israel in Britain those two things
So closely related to
Close to work
Sort of
The subject of British is realism as a really complicated thing and it means a bunch of different things in
For contacts
So it's important for me to be pretty clear about what we're talking about as we go through this
British is realism or Anglo is realism
Is the belief that white Anglo-Saxon
Comes primarily those of Western European Heritage are the direct descendants of
The ten lost tribes of Israel
I believe that now
Proponents of the theory point to Bible stories about Jacob later to be renamed Israel
Each of them gave birth to their own tribe
The Twelve Tribes
When Solomon died only to drive those of Judah
What accept the rule of Solomon's son rehoboam
Reborn was a crew leader and is thrown would result in what amounted to a civil war
These two tribes that sided with him became the southern Kingdom or the kingdom of Judah
And the ten other tribes were the northern kingdom or the king
Israel
In the 720's bze the Assyrians invaded and sent all those but the tribes in the
Southern Kingdom into exile
As The Story Goes the ten tribes became lost
However archaeology anthropology
Simplistic and clear-cut version
Of these tribes just getting lost history
Many members of the tribe
Flight back to the southern kingdom is reabsorbed into that population
Others were taken back to Assyria and midday of where they were assimilated into those called
It's not like it was a Walmart
Time
Yeah
Nebuchadnezzar of Babylon attacked the southern population was X
This population of the Southern Kingdom
Judah was by that point to constituted of the two tribes
You stayed loyal to
As well as many of the members of the northern kingdom blue slide South 100
40 years prior
By the time exiled Israelites return to Jerusalem to rebuild the kingdom their identity was largely unify
The people are real the struggle
The struggles are real the heritage is real
Tribes got lost
Is seen by most Scholars as more myth
The consensus opinion is that between the Assyrian invasion of the northern kingdom
And the Babylonian invasion of the Southern
Most of the members of these tribes have become integrated into the larger identity
Or into the places where they had ended up like
National History it makes sense to put that myth
Together because
You almost immediately remove the identity of those
Quote lost tribes you know if you are in one of those lost tribes
You came back you're no longer
In that lost
Grab your in
So you create them at their lost as opposed to like
They came back or they got
Assyria
That kind of
In order to strengthen your own
Forward to more modern
For centuries legends about the Lost tribes
One of the often repeated myths said that the tribes were
Who flows for six days of the week and stops on Shabbat to travel
Explanations of bounded for wino and the tribes even though people were looking really hard for them
So hard so it's like that isn't that just like a really
Fun
Magical river that stops only on the time when they can't cross it
I like that that image
A book called The Ten lost tribes
The book gave the first voice to
The theory that the groups like The
The Celts the German
Scandinavia
They were in fact
The tribes of Israel that have gotten lost
While the theory didn't go Mega viral it did gain a little bit of traction early on and here's where one of the most important
Distinctions comes into
The play
In the 1600s this idea began to spread a little bit and Britain
It was not explicitly antista
The proponents of this Theory believe that the people who are Jewish were the descendants of the tribes
Judah
BlueStacks
So they were all Israel
It could definitely be described as co-opting
But at that point in history the ideas were not being spread to deny Jewish people their Heritage or to demonize
There are plenty of other problem
Which we'll get into later but antisemitism was not one
So it's just kind of one of those
Fitting together why we believe in our version
Christianity with
Why are we
Completely
Different people so you
You kind of sex
Well
Also
We're also Jews so that make more sense
Contacts it's probably a little piece of it fits that but much larger reason
Sandwich will get into light
I think it's a timing issue
These Notions small pockets for a long time
Finally reaching their peak in the 888
In the early 1900s these theories began to take hold in the United
That is the point worth it
Things got ugly
Here's the final caveat I will give on them
Therap
Still some churches that exist the believe in British Israel isn't that don't hate Jewish people
But they are
Exception
Not to the rule
If the 1920s in the United States British Israel beliefs were co-opted by outright bigots
Anti-semite
And ever since that point the ideas
Been almost there
Exclusive domain
The group Christian identity traces their roots
The British Israel
Is the belief that the white race is true identity is the Lost tribes of his
Christian identity is a Loosely organized theologically entwined overtly white supremacist
Terrorist party
It wouldn't be right to call them a group
Sunsaver penchant for
Decentralisation
And they follow the leaderless resistance model popularized by Louis
Wasn't it here until Christian identity
Christian identities fingerprints are all over the history of the people behind right-wing terrorism hate group
Since the 1950
Their paths intersect with
The clan area Nations the militia movement of the 90s
The American Nazi party and its founder George link
Rockwell
The key difference between British is realism in the
The 1600s in Britain and the 19th American is the whereas the prior believe the Jews were
Also descendants of Israel the ladder did not
As the British Israel isn't police became
Can identity movement
The Narrative change
No longer was the
The theory just that white people were also Israelites
It was now that they were the only true Israelites
And the vast majority of the people who think they're Jewish
Are imposters
Okay well
Stop that
Settings
Saved
It's the wild
Underpants Underpants
Ton of these right-wing
Yeah
How many people or what
People are
He traced a lot of the time
Is really murky and really hard about the
This world it's amazing to me
How far the people go to
To justify their bigotry
Like it all starts from you think white people are the
And then you have to
To create the
Fantastical
Situations where you like
No it's okay I think
People are the best
I think a lot of it can be traced
To the idea of wanting to retain
Self image of being
Christian Christian
Simultaneously
A large part
People who buy also
Is match
Easier
Maybe giving up whatever
Security you feel in your Supremacy
I don't know
Anyway
Some Christian identity folk swing for the fence
Doesn't argue that Jews are literally descended from the Devil
What the word Mainline position is it
Cossacks
Curiosity
Pure bloodline
Sisters were actually a population of Turkey
Who converted to Judaism as part of an elaborate plan aimed at taking out the true Israel
I can already hear you asking Jordan
What are these Turkish people
What is it that they want
I was going to ask that
Dance
Podcast over
Dancer goes back to Genesis 25
And the story of Jacob and Esau
Esau was Isaac's first born son
She was entitled to a larger share of the inheritance
And all the races lineage
The come along with being recognized
First born
The name for this in the Bible is
Birthright
Genesis 25 tells the story of Esau
Jacob for some stew
Jacob offers him food if Esau will give him his Birthright
Esau degrees
And a Birthright is transferred to Jacob
Esau later married women that Isaac
Forbade him to marry and then Jake
Still have to pretend to be Esau and Order
Bestowed with Isaac
6 Birthright blessing but the point is that you thought was the firstborn and ultimately the birthright went
To Jacob and this pissed off
Hairy arm so he lost his Birthright that's
Sure how common
That the version of British has realism the David Jason preaches specifically believe
Dipso because they are
Descendants of Esau
And even carrying out a centuries-long Khan to reclaim the birthright that was handed down from Jacob to the
Anglo-Saxon
Work to believe that
That's exhausting
Oh yeah makes sense
Spend so much time like
Diagramming the reason
Like maybe it's just me
Maybe it's just
True and everybody cool
Try that one
Pastor David
Would refuse the label of Christian ident
And from all the sermons I listen to I get a strong sense that he doesn't think he's a white supremacist
I don't disrespectfully disagree with that assessment
Alvarez out right away supremacist an anti-semite is I've ever come across doing this back
It was important to walk through some of that differentiation
In between British is realism
He is far closer to being a Christian identity preacher then he is to be in 1B pro-jewish eccentric
Espousing British Israel ideas back in the
So
History of these ID
Put simply Herbert Armstrong was realism in America
Long after the point it was very discredited
Long after the idea taking hold is a large piece of white supremacist rhetoric of the United States
Herbert Armstrong whose worldwide Church of God
Which is
In 1920s
Is when the Christian identity movement started the coop
Covid-19
Is all after these
Associated with
Behavior
It's probably because I remember specifically
Amount of anti
Images of that word
Public Disco
Articles in the New York Times being like
Like to be allowed to live in America and all this stuff
And that was one of the
When Hitler
Look like
When Germany was
Exterminating
The Jews
He kind of thought that we would be on board
Large section of population
We were
Hair's breadth away from being
Could have easily not decorate
He is when he started
Good time this was a belief he decided to hold onto
So you might be able to tell a few things about him from that
Or at least
Get some
David Lee Smith did differentiate himself from Armstrong
Church a little bit
Owatonna preaching about
Particularly about the dangers of communism
The creation of a one-world government
His sermon titles from the mid-1980s through the mid-1990s read like Alexa
Texarkana Valex Jones
From November 24th 1984 why the coming cashless
Society
From February 8th 1991 history of the Illuminati and New World Order
So that's
It might be my pastor was like
Just going to talk a little bit about the Illuminati okay we're going to go through Daniel 11 as listen to h h
Sermons
Interesting now like I always listen
So much
David Jason
And
It's it really was like being back in
Because you could
I kept thinking like
Wrap it up
I kept sitting here in my chair like
Can almost
Get up he's on he's got to be
He's very weird you later head down on the
Back of the Pew in front of you and I just took a little nap and you got that red spot on your head I really wanted to find a program
Close to John. Bullet points
So some other
Discernment
Spoiler alert post-trib
For 1992
Bilderberg connection that's a sermon
Two L's in Bilderberg
It's really hit the
The Bill Clinton
Bill
I don't think so
Of course
He didn't nine-part series called quote dismantling America for world
These are sermon 9 part 9 Park
Going to church for over 2 months
And he's just like now here is
That's what I haven't heard of serialized
Church before
He doesn't a lot there's like a side part
There's another five part one that I left
Listen to that
So bored
Episode Ford 500 like this isn't really good but listen
If you sticker it's like the wire at work
Other tires
He rails on the same bad guys is Alex
The Council on Foreign Relations
The trilateral commission the Bilderberg
Use of the same sources as Alex does like none dare call it
Conspiracy W Cleon skousen
He even seems to admire a lot of the same
There's so much and Alex Jones here
And a lot of this work
Long predates Alex ever getting on air
A ton of David Ray Smith sermons that I listen to were recorded by Alex
To the pretty young guy like Alex was 6 years old then they would submit started his church
Radio minutes
I can't say with any certainty that a ton of Alex's ideas Comfort David
But there's enough interesting parallel that really makes you start to wonder
Princeton Smith operating out of Waxahatchee
She texted early night
1880s
I was born in 1974
And in the early 80s
Who lived in Dallas Texas
A city less than 30 miles north of Wax
Waxahatchee in fact is right in between the city of Dallas and Freestone County
Where else is Dad owned a fair share of mineral
Justice Armstrong's Ministry began as a radio televangelism operation that was part of David
Woodsmiths work to
Is here and a radio show called Newswatch magazine
Who's shortwave signal almost definitely
Reached Dallas
Freestone County
I like to take that step
The shortwave is designed to go long distance
30 miles is nothing for a sore throat
So just like
My
Like on a long road trip my dad would put
A Prairie Home
Companion
On the radio
Entirely possible that Alex
In the car
His dad just puts on
Or at the home
Or as a home
Spock that's pretty wild
Couldn't shake the feeling there was something really big
You hear that Alex likes live
David Chase
Really really hurt Alex talk much about
Start to look at in the
So many similarities
Is a geographical connection
Couple of
Specific pieces of rhetoric
Add up to
Is British Israel is
Sup roof
I'm referencing Smith Beto Texas
Alternative explanation
I needed to know more so I sat down like I said I listen to
Hun's
David Jason
Radio Star
I lost count of how many hours of his rambling as listen to
But for what
I find it very difficult to imagine that Alex
The show
There's just far too many things that overlap little details
Insanely suspicious
So what I've done here is I've
Compiled from my God knows how many hours of listen
This dumbass
A bunch of clips
That I think are going to walk us through
Experience
So we can see if this
Is convincing to you or to the listener
So you're about
Disapprove
That
White people are descended from the Lost tribes of Israel
Is realism is actually correct
You are dumb what I am going to hopefully diamonds
Is first of all the David J Smith is a Proto Alex Jones
But he was a show before out
Event secondarily
I would like to give people a glimpse
Into what sort of show
Alex was listening to
You listen to David
Because
It's not
Just
New World Order
Conspiracy
There is there are other things being discussed on the show that I think
Would be
Really weird to imagine
That Alex thinks is okay
The first thing I'd like to demonstrate these clips
He's the sort of British a surrealism preacher
Who believes that most Jews
Aren't Jews
Is a huge problem
Since that this distinction put it much closer to the
Christian identity
Then just be British Israel ISM side of the road and I believe it's important because
And I don't want people to think that is undeserved so here is he saying
2% of all people on the face of the Earth who claimed to be Jews
Blood related Jews
Convert
Proselytes to Judaism
So 2%
Of the Jews
In the world
Take a survey or
Was there a
How did it get to 92%
I'm just amazed whenever people make those wild claims and made
I just picked that number 9
Percent
Nothing but
He does have something behind it
I mean something
So David Smith they're actually
As I mentioned
DC Villains in the story of world history
In this next clip Smith explains how Eastern European Jews
Greenfield's are descendants of Esau
All responsible for many of the things in the world
Including International
They were very few in number
These were the racially
Pure juice who won across and
Converted other people
And then they begin to break down the bloodline
But there is other
Jews who
Historically
The trace back
Can sleep where they came from
Then we're not going to understand Bible prophecy
So I think it's vital that we do
Then when you start studying the orange
European Jews
This becomes very
Who was it that overthrew
Thesaurus
In Russia
Oh God
European juice
International communism
Eastern European Jews
Who is a trying to Stamp Out the United States the British Commonwealth all over the world and do away with Christianity
Eastern European
Excuse me sir
Do you have any evidence that this is true
I will tell you that he does reference that he's on edge
Because you know
God tells you to
Understand everything with your scent
That's right
To be able to
Spiritually get this.
It's also a really dangerous standard of
Proof to two-and-a-half
Is that might be real
He can't even say the word
. without giving you the heart
Like anytime he says
You're already getting
This dude is f***** up
And in case you need it spelled out a little more explicitly he was David Jay Smith explained
Who's particularly
Are the descendants of
He speaks of the House of Esau Esau's descendants
He specifically means people who are alive today who aren't
It is now Esau and his descent coming up claiming to be God's chosen people when they are
I'm not
And now we want to go into some scriptures and find out
Whether this is true or not
About the Jews of Eastern Europe are the ones who are behind the push for world government
So all of this stuff
Is anti world government
We're working against
The new world order that believes being formed by International communism
Push bike
This is a very clear
It's very
Ez2c
See-through what's going on here
He believed the
The Jews are trying to take over the world
Now
How they believe God works
Fairy Godmother you know like
Oh well because
One time
One guy tricks
Dab
Clearly all of these people forever are
There's a weirder version of that coming up in one of these clips
Intersex
Bro
Is Eastern European
Imposter
Jewish Folk
They're creating International communism
And socialism
With the explicit goal of taking back Esau's Birthright that was given to Jacob
Carried on by the United States
Inexperienced arresting to me
This is just a sideline
And 17 to talks about Abby
It's going to rise up out of the sea
And it's called a Scarlet colored Beast
Red
And Woodward
The global
Network
Today that is enveloping the world already taken all of Asia
Most of Africa do not status
And yet this red
Beast of Revelation 17 is now riding
And it's going to conquer
And it's going to end up being a world government
And it's going to be
Esau trying to regain his Birthright
What's going on that's exactly what's going on
Conception
That he is just created the
Making a battlefield between Anglo-Saxon people
Andrews
Convert
The Neo-Nazi world
Between Jews and non-jews
What if they're just
And we were all
I like that I'm going to go with that way
But it's not just that the Jews
Descendants from Esau
Also
According to Smith
They literally
Q
And the Kabbalah how to have demons
How to raise up spirit
Necromancer
How much clearer
But they claim to be Jews
God's chosen people
When they're not
They're not
Scuse me password is doing a lot of raising your hands
So could you point to the talmud where it teaches you how to raise the Dead
It's like the Anarchist Cookbook
No you can't parcel of his
Explanation
Infer why the Jews are
To blame for their own
Exile from places in
Be alright
The Mummy come out
Is Brendan Fraser daddy level of Vic
Employment
Crazy
Who's a very blunt
Denial of Jewish identity
That's happening
Throughout
Smith's Irma
And it's very hard to imagine that a person could listen to him for any stretch of time and not get these messages
Just loud and clear
White people are the real Israelites and God's chosen
And the Jews
Create a world government system in order to deprive white people of their rightful place in the world
And their Birthright and also Jews do Necro
That just doesn't make
It doesn't
It does not make sense
Know that they aren't really as realize they're aware of it
Remember I'm using nothing
Jewish
Literature Excel
The show
They know the
The truth of this matter
So
Excuse me pastor
Because the reference of Jewish encyclopedia Alaska
Just like that
Not only do you have an enemy on the world stage
Explicit Battlefield
Two forces
You have an enemy that
Keenly aware of their evil in
You remove the possibility that maybe Smith as the first person to discover all this stuff
The Jewish people don't know what they're up to what's going on
No they know what they're doing and they know that it's Eva
That sort of thinking can only lead to one can
Conclusion and you do what
David Smith doesn't shy away from that natural conclusion
Obadiah 18 through 21
House of Jacob shall be a fire
And the house of Joseph
Let's the twin Sons Ephraim and Manasseh
A flame
Another words Ally
And the house of Esau for stubble
Burns up in fire
And I still Kindle in them and devour them
And there shall not be any remaining of a house of
Esau
Zoe songs going to be destroyed because they
The god of Israel
And they're trying to take back to Burke right
So
Like if you understand that clip
He's saying that the extermination of Jews will happen
And it's a necessary part of reaching his religion
The fair
Keep in mind these are old recordings but not pre-World War
It's very queer that would David Smith his preaching on the idea that
Alex would look at this guy as anything other than a kind of bland milquetoast
But
Ratably scary
Because he's talking about it
Exterminator
Yeah he said we're back we're back denying the Holocaust
She saying it didn't
Finish the job
Write it believe it enough New World Order ideas
There is still some of that like
The New World Order orchestrated things
In the funeral Obadiah tells us that
Ephraim and Manasseh
That's what he believes to be the United States and Britain
With which
The sons of Esau are burnt up and young she'll survive
What the f*** else are you what are you talkin about other than
United States
Absolutely
There's no way around it
Holy f******
How is
He's not bored.
Somebody who
Don't have a platform
Judy Blume
I want to get back to exactly what this Birthright is that Smithfield's is under attack by the
Jewish people who are secretly
The descendants of Esau who want their Birthright
It's not some kind of fruitfulness
Sir Prosperity or Nationals
That's like you might hope it is
It's explicitly world domination
According to Smith's interpretation of
Scripture God is birthright to wipe
People which gave them all manner of blessing
They're entitled to enslave non-white people they're entitled to all the natural resources of the earth even in countries where
The art they're wrong
They have the run of the show
Earlier I mentioned that even back in
The 1600s in Britain
These British Israelite beliefs didn't come
From a good place
And even if they weren't motivated by anti-semitism
Here's where this
Circumcised
Frisch's realism and it's early formation
Is largely seen as a way that ostensibly Christian people could rationalize the booming. Of British Colonial
In the late
1500 into the early 6
C100
The. That's known as the first
British Empire
Shake shake his Britain prioritize colonizing
How much of the world is possible
The fighting with other European countries like Spain
Over areas that it already
In December
East India company was founded which would go on to be a massive Force
Colonialism through many corners
About the history
Nobody
Nobody just committed genocide quite like
What the British in many other countries was immoral on its
They're going into territory that was inhabited
Claiming it as their own off and enslaving or killing the native population
Get on board with the program
But simultaneously the country of the people were trying to retain the moral High Ground
Do what they were doing wasn't
Horribly evil
Because according to what they profess
Believe
Was Orbitz
These ideas are interesting at first but I think the reason they fell out of favor and never really caught on is too full
Wonder completely debunked by Scholars from
Owatonna fields
Second the purpose that these British has realism
Ideas
Easily by pills to ideas of British exceptionalism or
Pretending that you're calling eyes in a country in order to bring Jesus
Cortical Savages
You don't need to rewrite all of history in order to get into
Excuse for your behavior
So icy
Suspect that most people saw British imperialism
Overcomplicate
Yeah justify brutal
Nationalism
Then
The steps you need to take in order to rationalize
Pretty sure
This is the birthright
The David Jay Smith preachers of
The birthright that white people have
To dominate the world
In this sermon he
Expressly points out former colonies
Lesbian counter to his version of biblical prophecy
And sauce is proof
That the sons of Esau or on the March
Just as fast as we Rose The Promise
Every one of these are being stripped
Switch control
Control all of Palestine and Egypt
All of those are not free countries
The Red Sea no longer belongs to Great Britain
The Panama Canal has been given away
From the United States
Control by us anymore
One by one every single one
Which fulfilled prophecies are being strip
From the United States and Great Britain today
Every one of them
So
This dude's f******
Easy the mask
Who's preaching yeah
Another servant expands on his feelings about Rhodesia and South Africa
Those countries
The Rhodesia become Zimbabwe already still very much under apartheid rule
He's all about it
His profound
Especially considering the prison in the background
Given these considerations
We know that it's white people's Birthright to rule over the world and colonize whatever they want
Take whatever resources they
But what do you think
Black people's Birthright is
Oh no no I don't want to hear
They get to be slaves literally forever you guessed correctly
Notice numbers 24
And Noah Walton
Came out of his drunken stupor
And knew what his younger son
Now this wasn't
The actual Sun
Had done unto him
Kenny said person be Canaan
This is the son of ham
Something to Noah Wyle was in a drunken stupor
Literally sent the course of history
And notice what happened
A servant of servants
Shelly be under his breath
What we would call basically
The African
People that settle
Ham
All the way through the rest of History
All through history forever
Okay okay okay okay so somebody got into a f****** bar fight so black people are slaves for forever
Bar fight it could have been a prank
I don't know all the ins and outs of that story because I just don't care
Cheese's
Yeah yeah some happened to Noah when he was drunk and now black people are slaves forever
And then like there was a Dogpile people like putting their hands over his mouth saying never
Give him money
Oh man white supremacist
You keeping score
Really dude that white people should rule the world in the black people are permanent slaves because someone Frank
Text Noah Wyle was drunk one time
I think I've already said this
Episode but it Bears repeating David Smith
Complete white supremacist
Ended insane
Now we've established some of these really dangerous
F*****-up ideas
David Smith
He was listening to
Stuff like this
What are you
The kit yeah if he was
Important that we need to take a little time highlight somebody glaring
Similarities
City has
Alex Jones
And he believes an international socialism
Pretend
To be atheistic but is secretly
Bring the devil
And the old world is set up strategically right now
Final conflict between International socialism communism
Calls itself atheism
But it's not it's those who control it worship Lucifer by name
So we did that so pretty it's a pretty concrete similarity
Between him an hour
And also the muddying the Waters of communism
Socialism
Also another pretty big similarities that he believes that
The Council on Foreign Relations
The globalist plot
CSR in the service okay cool
Cool cool
Policy
Can you prove it
If you can
How can you
Prove it
Formulation actually
The creation
Greece would be eliminated
Plans
Obviously the protocols of the Elders of Zion there
So I mean
A big similarity
Similar in beliefs that mean
Very similar
But it's different
Is willing to admit
He goes on to expound on his ideas about other Council on Foreign Relations
Hate people who want to put America first
Pretty precedes out in this
Next clipart
Conspiracy that Alex Jones
Is made very Central to his worldview
Terminology
There is no.
It repulses them
As America
End of quote
He says the Council on Foreign Relations
The Council on Foreign Relations
Terminology
People in America
Fourth world country
Free so all people
That's one of Alex's big ideas about
The financial collapse
Stuff that I need to destroy the economy in order to make everyone
So poor that we can merge with third world
That is
Clearly articulated by Smith
Years before Alex ever got on the radio.
This could be Alex's show before Alex
Very clearly
Alex talk about the Illuminati from time to time especially did earlier in his career
Got it
Talk about it too much now but
He didn't have that Bugaboo before
I am amazed
Spy
That guy
Turn
Well so many
Turn this idea of like
Maybe let's not go crazy on the like America First and maybe bring
Alder
Countries and everybody in
Into the fold
Everybody else
To this equal place in
Instead of
Keeping all of them down
And turn that into
What they're trying to do is kill everybody in America
Rule forever something
Be brothers with everybody
They turn into something
Perverse and awful
How is it that you don't that people just don't go lie
Oh you're an a******
Right I mean
A stunt of moral development
To Sonics
Because like
A real
Early form of moral development
Is just sort of
Your own personal
Nev
Okay so my family
Write check my family or social group
Developed understand do I need to be doing well
Expand out to a city
The state country mentally you get to the world
Hey just Beatles
Whatever principles
To care for anyone
If you
Didn't think about it long enough
Should become Universal
DIA
America First and those sorts of ideas
Really are just bad
Text stopped again
People developing fully on their moral path towards
We're old people
Anyway
If you really want to look at is the overlap between
Alex Jones
Another thing I preach constantly the population in order to take over
Carry out an operation
To solve this problem
The Simpsons
So he believes much like Alex that in this
The fairy piece of bringing this world government is disarming the population
You see that he also believes that the world government is going to use false-flag
Type situations in order to pursue their goals
They're going to create circumstances
The problem reaction solution ideas
Text sermons where he brings that up very clearly it's
Overlap
Strong
And he believes
What do you mean by that
There's a lot of s*** that he says that we all know
And he doesn't actually
Made it seems like
Real crazy thing for him to do this
Monopoly
Distance
So scary
So honestly we could do this all day
Play kalmah
Conspiracy that Alex Jones believe that the Illuminati or New World Order world government is echoed in the
Federal Reserve is evil text
Churches have been in
Infiltrated by the New World Order
There's so much substantiv overlap
If I'm being honest
Overlap with less interesting to me than some of the more subtle connection
Confine
If you pay close
Attention
David Smith has the exact same habitat
Fake documents
To support his argument
We already heard him say the protocols of the Elders of Zion is
In this next clip
He uses another fake document to make his Oregon
Revolution
Albert
Publix
He goes on to talk about it's the Second Amendment
Something different or similarities
Really 121 parallel
Revolution
In order to create a fake narrative
What they're doing is entirely the same as one of them's at a Pulpit in a radio show the other as a studio
That's basically the only difference
Between those clips
George Soros made a lot of people
FIFA sign
Revolution
Before they
Start all those as number one on the
But it's not just fake documents
Myself
Quotes
Just like Thomas Jefferson
Fake quotes
George Washington the first president
I called him
To the Constitution
Liberty
Teeth
That's the fake quote that we talked about that other recent episode
Phraseology that he's using
It's very it's a specific fake walk for both of these dudes to think is real
It tells me that Alex either got this from David's
They're both working all similar sources
It's the push this way quote I need a reason to go to option
Both are
Both are intertwining these two people as either
Being in the same Community or Alex
Taking it
And the similarities don't
There
International conspiracy from
This was recorded
He talks about W Cleon skousen talks about none dare call it conspiracy is being great books
You know what
He seems to admire a lot of the same people that our
What does
I happen to know that there's over 700 banks in the United States according to Senator Rhonda Paul
House of Representative member
That are now in danger of collapse
And yet the government won't read the word because if they breathe which companies are which banks they were you and I would go have a
So you got Financial collapse narrative to Alex's paranoid
Go to Ron Paul
The room pulls a pretty common purse
4 weirdo militia types
Support bizarre
I think it's next one alittle more specific
We have
Really
Not even begun
To develop our own energy sources
Play 939 crisis by Lindsey
For he was right there on the spot he had access to all documentation
And he has shown
Documented
Call Island
Fine
What's the largest in the United States
So
Like I've literally never heard
Anyone other than Alex Jones reference
Lindsey Williams
Charlie true I'm sorry I misspoke
I never wanted
The show is a gas ever again
Beyond that it's just Alex and David Jason
These connections are pretty compelling
I feel like
We've gotten some
Parallels baofeng
Content
Style substance
References
People
Like Lindsey Williams being referenced by both these
Like when I was looking through that sermon Williams
Do not expect to hear that there
But I feel like this last clip that I have of
The sermon
Should jump out at you
And you should just
This could easily be equipped
And that's just historical documentation
Which can be found in
Congressional Record
And there's even a movie Mike in circulation
Don't table
Call Red's
You see there and there's a
My God
You vaguely cites the Congressional Record but doesn't really get into it
Instead
Purolator
2.2 mm movie
Ethan saying that's exactly the rhetorical style that Alex employee
It's me that feels like a little bit of a fingerprint
It's the sort of thing that you can
Like if you listen to a ton of you might
Adopt
Into your subconscious
Especially if you're younger person listening
Listen to a preacher who had these
These verbal patterns
It would
Makes sense that you might
Perfect movie
To make my point
No I don't know if that
I don't the certainly not concrete but it's enough
Along with all the other stuff
Coming out to look at similarities
Piling up to mountains of circumstantial evidence
Weaponized
Cupidity
Like he's
Alex Rivera
Through here
It sounds to me like
David Smith
So f******
Stupid and crazy
That he
Inadvertently
Shot Alex like a missile
Into America
I don't I don't know a hundred percent sure
Hey it's it certainly might have contributed to the funeral
Small samples of things that I've heard from Smith sermon
There plenty
Plenty board examples
Direct overlap with Alex
I complete you hours of Smith talking and sounding exactly like Alex but ultimately all that can prove is that they believe similar things
Yo-yo their similarities
Timeline pattern
That's completely unsatisfying
Conclusion for me
I needed to figure out if there was a stronger connection
Between these two
I kept looking
Someone left on examined for too long
Add presents on
Shortwave radio
For those unaware short-wave signals exist in a band of frequencies
Huge desk
Where is a radio signal might only be capable of being picked up in like a 20 mi radius from the transmitter
Large shortwave transmitters can push a signal out that could be received easily through the entire United States
Further
Alex always used to tell his audience
Theron transmitters to broadcasters
That would definitely help him
You're playing on more frequent
But it wouldn't do anything to help
Expand its geographical
One short wave transmitter to broadcast to show all over the United
Canada
And that's station
The does that work
Is wwcr
Out of Nashville Tenn
Wwcr has an official partnership with Genesis
Communications Network number their shows broadcast
From that
Show me other shows that have been on that Network include the hour of the time
Which was Bill Cooper show before he died
They're also they have a show on there called the intelligence report
But it was hosted by Mark from Michigan
Inotorious militia agitator who call into Alex's show
Jack McLamb had a show on wwcr
If you forget mcclam was a frequent Alex Jones gas to try to create a patriot Utopia in rural Idaho
Along with militia lunatic in hardcore Christian identity
Wwcr called Freedom call
There's a show called The Radio free America which is sponsored by the Liberty Lobby and Spotlight magazine
The anti-semitic ragwear Alex's main Bilderberg Source gym Tucker work
Wwcr also broadcasted
Scriptures for America
A radio program hosted by Pete
Peters
The Christian identity preacher who organized the fascist organizing Summit the Rocky Mountains
Which was attended by Aryan Nation
Leader Louis beam
Popularizer of the leaderless resistance
And frequent Alex Jones Larry Pratt
I've gunownersofamerica
Wwcr also broadcast David Jay Smith Newswatch
Wwcr is a
Christian outlet with the right-wing militia paper
Community
And you can see that
Explicit
Do Alex and his world's you the ideas
The David Jay Smith show was Brock
Gaston the same
Transmitter station
On shortwave as Alex and
And all of these
Very explicit Christian identity program
It means something
Just think of
Some sort of like Polar Opposites
Is it can you imagine a shortwave radio station that way
Was just like f****** environmental terrorist
Doing nothing but like probably doesn't know up
Bro
Damn every goddamn
Something close to that might exist cuz I also include a lot of like pirate program
Broadcast shortwave
With Fair
Fairly easy
Abilities
I'm not aware of any terrorist
Station
What is on par with wwcr
It it the reach of it is
Exact coverage map
Once I could find
I'm not a hundred percent sure they're accurate but they go all over North America into South America
And in Europe throughout Europe
And North Ave
Africa like they have
Coverage
Of an insane
Yeah
So I think it's I think it's pretty f*****-up
To see that
It's very clear
Connection
Like why why is Alex on this Christian identity broadcast
Station that also broadcast
This preacher
Like it's very strange
Now it's not
They're all
F******
I don't know man
Connected
Tentative enough
I needed something more concrete
After digging around a little more what should I say
But it May 14th 2008 episode
Featuring David Jason
As the gas
I figured if anything could give me a sign
Sense of Alex's true feelings toward Smith
A conversation
Between the two of them
And here
Jordan
Is how that conversation
Phones in the
First
3rd and 4th
Today Pastor David
From Waxahachie Texas fighting the New World Order
For more than 30 years
Will be joining us on air
To talk about his neck of the woods
Nearby
The Baptist
Bible School
In East Texas where they
Security come in
And tell members
Arrested
Espionage
Speak about the Bill of Rights and Constitution
That's a little bit of a sort of mischaracterization of what's going on
Really Loosely to make it sound like David G Smith church has anything to do with his church that allegedly had
Homeland Security
Disconnect
Baby Geographic
Berkeley close to of like this church
In a preacher
And you are you run your risk of your taxi
Example for or against
Pacific policy
Ways to vote
Candidates
Did you want to
Keep those things
Easy to see how if you're running a church
You could
Election metal
Yeah yeah
Local election
Write set up a machine
Churches were allowed to
To be political
Tools that we know now for sure that churches are not
Political tools
At Albright
It's awesome
So good that
That seems like a pretty positive thing for Alex
Pretty enthusiastic about him
Even calls
For decades and decades
On the show they've all been done before many of them have been on you and years
I just remembered again
Undertale try to try to get
It was Health allowed
Few years and he's a WWII
He really is
The great granddaddy
Dial Mom
So you know
Viking icon
David Smith and redback
Icon
Despite icon
But read back the past episodes
To deeply back into him
But in case anyone needs a reminder when was one of the guys
16th Amendment is a fraud and you shouldn't have to pay taxes
He also wrote a book called The Church deceive
Where you at
Thoughts about what the Jews went through in World War II
It was judgement not Holocaust
The true and almighty God use the evil Nazi government
Form judgement
The evil answer
Christ religion
Of those who crucified the Christ
To the Holocaust
Nazis
Put into the Holocaust which kind of sounds
Red Beckman was a bigwig in early Christian identity Circle
Call switch strongly indicates
Something as consul
This is further indicated by his
Contention that non-white
Armada
She says which we clearly have heard David basement say that black people because of a prank on Noah or servants
Perpetuity
When Alex says that you're an icon in a particular field on par with red Beckman
You are being called a race
And an anti-semite
That is
What red Beckman stock-in-trade is
That is a positive in his world
But it is
It is not
I maybe
So interesting
Alex get the call
On this episode
What are people that I've been paying
Nope
It's a it's a it's the racist old guy
Chicago you're on the air
I'd like to say
Virginia trip
Backup
Imma riding Ram
Rampaging black
I don't know if you saw this
Oh yes wait
Alex is frustrated you can hear it that
His show at this point as a character
Set is okay to be like
Racist guys.
Preacher who prior to this has given sermon about how black people are slave
Forever
Congruence
A little bit
But
The presentation publicly to be alright Got This Racist calling in
I've got to be
Not on board with him because when he says the rampaging black beast
What are you talkin about is the primaries
Because we're in May 22,000
Primary season
So he's talking about pushing back again
Alex
Can't allow that
To be on the show
So overt
And he pushes back and it just makes lip which is something
You never here
Isaac
I want to take
I'd like to have a sum of
Tori vikk
Street dance with
The VA
West Virginia map
Mountain Mama
I appreciate your
Call Suraj
Can't hear the music
We don't need to call people black
Crazy dear Alex amen
Isn't it
It is especially considering other. The time in that like
More recently
And Alex's brand is completely change to the point where you can't say things like
No point
His thigh isn't like this guy saying something wrong it's like you're giving up the game
Stop it
You're forcing me to
Explicitly denounced you had a good time
So
And
It's not really
That great of an interview
Enforce the ideas that he has about the clergy response
Which is essentially the
Notion
FEMA has placed
Infiltrators in churches in order to get them to go along with putting people in
Episode
Smith doesn't really have anything to say other than
Okay crazy that
Churches to have them
Be okay with putting people in
Like people in churches are just automatically okay with me now
So in this
Clip hear from David Jay Smith
If he talks
About
Which is
Weird
Do your come up on Alex
How to show because
A taco
And we know that the Rothschild
Another
International Bank
All of this to get its start
Show show how do
How did the Hebrews
Two different
You got two different items here
Number one
There were Twelve Tribes
And the northern
Squared away
The tribe of Judah and Benjamin because
Perelman Center
We'll give them relief
Hayward Bell
Rewriting the Bible to be like at George Washington
You know what though it's not
I call Leanne.
Cuz reborn part of the reason that he was such an awful L was
Like you said he was going to raise more taxes
Right right
Slight that you made against
People
The tribe
They let them see likes f*** this
We are not
It takes a she was a part of it
It certainly wasn't the whole story
Interesting
You take that piece of it you make it
So Central because you're hanging out with that all of these
Text agitators
In XO
That's the important piece that's why those ten tribes
It's a it's a rewriting but
You know if it's
That Alex's
Not pushing back on it
I think he's just like well I introduced this guy is an icon
I have to make this a smooth as possible
But just at
Too far into the
Jews are
He has to walk that line
Manages to do it successfully although
David Smith.
Alright
Majority of the bar MX
Pacific Tan hours
Galveston pushback on that
Which is very weird
We have one last clip
From this episode
Ben and what I was looking for iPhone
Some really matter me all that much
Wheel of Fortune they're never going away or bring up neck
Going back to pass
Get out
Is phone number in contacts
Great books
Write research
I've learned so much
So you have the things I was looking for all along
When you go in and you look at it too
David Jason
You find
So much heavy over
So much with the
One exception being this British has
Israel list
Belize
But Alex doesn't
Professor
Victor's
So much overlap
Between the conception of the New World Order
The
Stewardesses the people the narrative
All of it matches
Much
Then you find that they're on the same shortwave station
And make his broadcast with
You know he was operating out of the city 30 miles
Away from Alex's childhood home
Damn it there's so much here that seems very similar
But it's not really definitive
Can you listen to the two of them talk
And Alex says that he's learned so much
16 to 17 years
Since he's woken up
To David
Yeah it does seem like all that he really did was
Send to David Smith
Showing
Maybe instead of
Do I say globulus
Help make a
And maybe
You know I used some of the the sources
Go in some other direction
It seems
To me almost impossible to imagine that Alex wasn't heavy
Alex is smart enough to know that like
If I am to be open about a lot of this
Enough
And where I'm getting these ideas from
People will be able to trace it down too easily and then they be like
Oh dude hold my friend
You are getting your ideas from a white supremacist preacher
Anti-semite of the highest order
Complete f****** weirdo
That you wants to be
Casinos like these ideas coming from an intellectual place right
I don't know somebody who's above
Ident
City politics
Necessarily
All of Alex's
Is come from
David Jason
His inspiration
Piece of
His backstory
That is an exam it and it's something
You don't
Really realize
Until
Alex
Phones for a week
Who's the preacher talking about
Very
Before we get out of here there's there's something else
I want address
It's probably been in the background of everybody
As we've been
Been going through this
Is that is how much Alex Jones talks about Birthright
And the fact
It's so Central
David Smith
Philosophy theology ideology
Alex constantly
In the present day
Talks about
Trump
Reasserting America
Cuz Birthright
In the world
And
For a very long time
I just took that
To me in like
Do you know
I took to be along the same lines as his like
Liberty 1776
Text 2.0 America is a complete
Different country
Existed
Before
But when I listen to hours and hours and hours of David
AJ Smith
Yukon
Harping on the idea
Jacob got the birthright
Esau Esau husband
We're trying to take it back
International communism creating a World War World Order a world government
The specific wording of it is just too much for me
So I decided to go back
Listen
To some of Alex
Onondaga Nation
And
This clip stuck out
First off let me just
Undoubtedly
Dishwasher
Providence
American destiny
This was Trump
Office Republic
George Washing
You talked about
And that probably
They were going to invoke
And I haven't talked about this
I knew
What was about to happen and I said I got a tweet
But they're going to invoke
Spirit of America
And empower the globe
So
You know though it's the context in which he's talking about the birthright
Being really involved
Really sounds a lot more like David J Smith's version of the birthright
Fanciful ideas but I might have had it like
Satisfying
I'm still on one level
Because
I don't feel
I feel on one
Outside
Very satisfied
My conclusion is that Alex Jones
He has been
Aware of and
Nose
What David J Smith stands for in season 2B
Nikon
In this world
That investigation
Open-and-shut complete
The question of whether or not Alex believes the birthright that he talks about all the fun
Is the same thing the David Jason
Believe that to be
Namely white people have dominion over the world
To me it's still an open question
Christian imperialist I don't know if he's the British Israel is
But he's definitely
Anglo Israel
But maybe that's the only thing that kept him away from being a British
Imperialism
I think the only thing that's keeping them away is
People will treat him
Appropriately
Gucci belt
Baby Christian identity
Yeah play that clip inauguration
Hey I remember that and I remember thinking about
Obviously years ago
But
I remember
Thinking like
Birthright just being like a
I was born in America and so on
And so forth
It's so much more charge
Now that I have this
History of like under
Understanding
That also means that black people are slaves forever
Today obviously puts a little bit of a
Contacts.
Possible
Yeah
You know separate from that
We have also heard him talk about Birthright
A ton
Texted when she talked about it never made it clear
And the only thing
Suggest
A slight clearing up already stalking
He's looking at
How's that word is used by somebody
Who clearly he thinks as an icon and is someone who
He's been aware of for over a decade and a half
At at the point of
15 years old when he first came in,
With with
So I don't know
Exotics
As question of
How much exactly Alex
Is in line with him
But from my assessment and looking at Alex Jones have over the course of
I mean
He uses
Terms like Birthright in the way he does
As code
I think so
When's it going to keep
Thinking about
Today is
Superman out
Stop the
Stop light
In the fifties on the radio they had
Destination
Subdued
Superman
Radios
Reveal how stupid
The leader is the Grand Dragon
That there
Secret rituals
Yeah
And
That did so much to stem the growth of
Ziggy like
If we had that same
Situation to
It would not take the girl
Enough people would call you back before you know it
You take any kind of stigmata way
Yeah
It's a bummer
I don't know how there's like real solid conclusion in this other than
Stumbled upon
Really f***** up
Inspiration
A Alex Jones
Over the years
It troubles me
Two level I can barely
Yeah
No.
Rest of the
Stuff in his shows
I were talking about so we're good
This is the value of that
Find any other way
Before I met
You still living
Maybe just a little
So let's go
Two people
To come closer to catching up
Which we won't be able to do honestly
Unless we start giving shout-outs
People as a group
I don't know if I want it might be disrespectful
Yeah
President of individual sound drops being played and now it's true
Backed into a corner I don't know what we're going to do
Next time someone who's coming in at the technocrat level thank you so much
Turing
My calendar
We met them but we also
Business
Money off at heroin
Freakishly large
Really
Next
You're now a policy wonk
Aaron you are now a policy wonk
Finally a little elevated
Greg
You are now a technic
Heroin
Freakishly large
Thank you so much great thank you
How much are we doing group
Oceans as a technocrat
We'll see moving forward
And that we cannot do without you
And we have made it to the end of what I would describe
Episode
Fort Lauderdale
It is important to get through this cuz it's only because now we're through into March
Very excited closer to
Wow the release of Terminator 2
Also I should point out I believe Illinois last episode
Teasing that big news was coming up
He had investigators working alright behind the scenes footage
Completely dropped
How about that
We do have a website it's knowledge
Ritz Cracker Barrels on Twitter
On Facebook Facebook to download this
Send listen to it I don't know how you got this far without having learned
How to download this
You should do
Is write a little note
Get a rubber band
Tape the note on Iraq
Put the rubber band around those 22
Connect to the to
Throw it
Through the window of your nearest neighbor
And they will download the podcast
Cast for you I promise you that is how it works
No but you could go to that's definitely do the trick so I guess
As far as I know that baby who's crying in the background of some of the favorite just get sermon
I don't think that baby
You're right
Innocent till proven guilty
Alexandra Thurston color