Sweaty
I have great respect for knowledge by now I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
MoneyGram
Stripe.com
Novelty Beverages and talk a little bit about
Alex Jones
Have you ever had something important
Surly important
I thought my car got stolen but it just got lost
In front of somebody else's house
Somebody's house forgot that it was there that woke up the next morning and
Thought it has been stolen
Wunderground
Don't think I really had too much
Come to my life
No not at all
The only thing I've ever had
For real
Super Mario World
Cartridge
That was stolen from me when I was in
Junior High
Sure over the course of my life.
I don't know why I remember that one
It's just a formative
CEFCU will Xperia
Stealing things in my life
Sometimes questioned the nature
How's this show
The victim of theft and I only know what you tell me about that's correct
Present day
It's been awhile
Do you know
Through 29th
It is Friday through Monday of last week into this week
Interesting stuff
And also
Hello.
Signed up
So first Kevin
Next
Mike thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Text Alex
If you want
Amapola
I'm about
Next Johnny thank you so much
Top and are supporting the show
As a group
Email and I will make it up to you with your own drop
Or something I hope there is no
So Philip
And Cornelia thank you so much you are all
Freakishly large
Thank you Courtney
Absolute
If you'd like to
Sports
What we got here in front of us
Is Friday
Episode where Alex is
Michelle
But Alex joke
Call Lynn
Little bit of content for a
To get into
It's really boring
Stupid but he does say one thing
Is very interesting
About his father's influence
On him
Okay
Alex Jones
People in college
Extrovert
History
Conspiracy behind all of these world
Courtney out the Czar in Russia
The global communism the French Revolution all of this being done by the
The belief system
Espoused by
The person we talked about on our last episode
Absolutely Christian identity
Alex
Learned a lot from
His dad Alex
Exact
No let me teach you about listen to this weirdo preacher from Waxahatchee
It does
Believe there may be a little bit more to
Dad was
Funneling
These Christian identity beliefs
Maybe that's
Bigger part of the story than we realize
What's a little indication
Sincere there that
That might say
Fertile soil there
So
Sunday
I wasn't expecting too much
On Sunday cuz
I was generally songs
Alex is on
Real crazy bull
Like
He's got a narrative that he believes
Is it going to be like
Game Change
Real stupid
And the present your 73 and everything
You don't have the internet really work
In the last three days have been lost on Facebook and Twitter of your bonafide
Then you have on both of your sweaters
Your Instagram everything else
Hundred
Million
Followers
74 million
1 + 40 something million 139
Hundreds of millions of years
Of your damned
Until
Douchebag
The Republican establishment
He's my friendship
He lost track of that sentence
He was really swinging for something
Together again
Metaphor
Part of Alex really talking directly to Trump through a lot of it
I don't know what's going on here
Is ultimately what we're going to get back to us
He's trying to backdoor on the Millions
Followers that he lost on those meme
To Alex
I think you're probably right
Motivation
So you didn't hear about this story of Millions
People being kicked off Instagram
I don't give a fuk about it
Well it's also not true story
200 million people have been kicked off
Instagram because they support Donald Trump
Worldwide you have to pay close attention
He says the 200 million followers
Which is different than 200 million
People are ticked off
It's you know it that could just be
200 million
No Rebellion follows have been lost
What else is doing is trying to over-inflate the scope of this purge
Instagram worth
Kicked off
If you want to call
To give you some perspective if 200 million accounts were kicked off Instagram
Why is the number of people use Instagram of the United States
Pancake shop
That would be them removing approximately 1
Subscriber base
Which would completely crippled their
It's the sort of claim that's just
Absurd on its face
You should be embarrassed
In reality the number of followers of the affected accounts
And whatever number anyone can come up with just take into account that they probably have a overlap in the followers of these Meemic
So the number is
Exaggerated over-inflated
So on Thursday and Friday of last week
Instagram
With a spokesman for the company saying they were disabled following multiple violations
Including attempted abuse of our internal process
At the point of preparing this episode and recording
Exactly what the policy violation
But given how large social media
I'm willing to suspend judgment for the time being and wait and see what information comes out later before I take a really firm
Position on that
We've seen countless examples of people gaming social media
Sims 4 profit from the people who set up syndicates
Tweets go viral for a
Krassenstein Brothers do
He doesn't seem too unbelievable to assume that these accounts
Last week
Shutdown
Turn on political reasons at all
Yeah they're just abusing
The system like
For some context in situations like this
Best to find examples of times things like this have happened before and why they've happened
And in this case it's super easy
Inlay French Revolution
Exactly in late December 2018 Instagram had another Purge of accounts that violated their policy
In that instance of spokes
Fritz told the daily.
Quotes we see behavior on Instagram where buy some usernames
Usernames which contain a letter or number are stolen or trade it
This Behavior violates our policies in a number of ways
We don't allow people to buy sell or trade aspects of their account including user
We're consistently take
Steps to disincentivizing
Stop his behavior
Including removing account
Policy
Is part of an ongoing process
Like social media companies create new rules
Got down on scam
Dennis cameras find new ways around that rule in the process just starts over
Exactly
Instagrams been working on this since at least 2014 and billions of entitled
What I see something like
What happened last week it's pretty easy for me to see this is
Probably just another step in the process
Define tuning
They're making it so you
You can't expect
16 Brothers
It had been absolutely selling
Screenshots of them
But we'll see what happens if it's Instagram
I see every reason to suspend
Judgment
Discount very well may have been breaking the rules
And I also looked over the screen names for all the ones that were banned
Obviously I'm not some guy out there cruising Instagram
The freshest memes
But I looked through all the account names and none of them were like
Maga2020 yoga
I don't know I don't know that these were actually
We even accounts that were
Making Trump memes
It wasn't count dankula
Anyway
Also it's all about social media all the time
If you weren't just trying to bring up these topics
Completely self-serving
Positions
Wounded narcissism
Right now I would have imagined that he would bring up how sex workers are being pushed off social media faces
At least one
In the time that I've listened to him I've never heard of her
Cuz it does seem like he would have to be
You'd be okay
Is a libertarian
Absolutely has a f****** libertarian
The reason Alex is freaking out so much about this and exaggerating
To such an extreme level of
Would you point it the first is what you
He wants to get back on
It's exhausting
Publix in order to keep his name in The public's eye
But he doesn't do that is all business
Second
Ounces to Connected meme distributors
Who are able to create artificial virality are really the best option
Is social media companies are starting to address that problem on their platform
He knows that his ideas are going to have to compete on a Level Playing ground with other people and they're going to fail miserably
So this is at one of Alex's gigantic
Freaking out of
He's trying to I have to be super clear
He's trying to
Imply
And will directly say
200 million people got kicked off which is cooked
Number in any way is to say that the
Small number of accounts that got kicked off had a large following
It's completely insane that's like
3 billion listeners worldwide
Whenever the world listens to your show
Right including Baby
Another
We are facing promoters
I don't know I feel really out of my Lane
I feel exactly the same way I would feel if I tried to wear a hat backwards
Don't do it
Instagram the part of it and then there's
More
Almost passed the bill
House of Representatives right now
Bipartisanship people $30,000
Which ones
Play gentlemen
Where this country
Thousand
Dollar
My listeners thought I was making it up
Didn't think it was real
Ichiban
Europe
I kind of like that vocal flourish there
In this narrative Alex's misrepresenting Deke alternative in small-claims Enforcement Act of 2019
The actors designed to make it easier for holders of copyrights to protect their copyrighted protected work without having to subject
Corporate
Creating small claims
Court mechanisms
Simplify the process
Expedited and make it so
You don't have to exert tons of money in order to
Protect your material right is that does disincentivize people from
Protecting what
Desert Electric
If it cost you more to fight against
Then it would be to just
Just ignore it then why
Ultimately this legislation is not just
But here's the thing
What people are doing with me in many cases is already illegal
When it involves clearly copyrighted material
Technically
People are allowed to get away with it because most of the time the copyright holders know it's more hassle than it's worth to go after someone
Colibri
The case act doesn't make anything illegal that was previously legal
It really is just about making it easier for people
To protect their own intellectual property
And for Alex super into property right
It doesn't make sense for him
To be opposed to people being able to
Defending their property
Obviously this kind of legislation could have a huge impact on me
But I find it very difficult to imagine
Succeeded going through
Do that much of an effect on how individual users of social media platforms
Used memes
I think it would just make it easier to sue people with large platform to profit off using copyrighted material
Interpret themselves by saying
It's hard to hear Alex misrepresenting the story and not think about how we just had to paint match your creator Pepe the Frog 15th
Dollars for you to use copyrighted material
It'll poster that Infowars sold on their website
For Alex's legal strategy
Immediately after Fury and Alex reach their
Show to discuss
Placate
It was crystal clear
And it was basically boiled if you want to spend a ton of money suing Alex $15,000
They weren't defending their innocent
Sports
They were clearly signalling costly
For anyone to fight Alex in court so they give up or they don't even bring the suit in the first place
That's one of the ways Alex protect himself
Yeah it's similar to
Debt collectors
Credit card companies
And then they'll take you to court right but you will get
Most of them never show up
When did they wind up losing their case cuz they didn't
Show up interview show up you find out
Traffic tickets that you automatically
But in a number of instances it's not worth it
To pay the cop
To go to court
Gets thrown out
If the case goes through
Alex is far more vulnerable in matters of copyright
I can't say for sure would lead to any actual potential
Really f****** worries
I suspected this is what's motivating
Also discuss now because it's like
He's presenting
The globalist
October
So I kind of also find it funny that Alex brings up out of the same as what was Europe last year
Because the EU rules
Also because the EU rules
Completely different thing then what Alex is talking about
He's in Europe if you posted
You're getting a fine
And that's absurd
Enforcement in the new age of two
Technology
Amateur reads about this rule from an article and wire
The most controversial part of the copyright directive
Copyright violations and material posted
Previously users not the platform reliable
People posting memes
Find
The platform wood
Maybe it might not even come down here
Forbes Facebook
Google
To protect the copyrighted material
Being misused by their users as opposed to
All the consequences
Is falling on the individual user
Become their own cops
Instead of
Yeah
Implicit in the misuse
Intellectual
I also don't worry.
You rule didn't infringe on member states
Sovereignty
Each state was specifically left to their own devices to write their own laws and come up with how they would Implement practices
To protect copyrights through Europe
Nothing that I would says
It all is real
It's a whole just blustery bulshit he's hoping you'll add up to enough inside
Went to get Trump
To somehow Force Facebook and Twitter to let him back
So much like
Please
There's so much of that
I think it's probably in
Someway motivated by
The longer things go on
The worst in situations
That's simply not a thing
It would be an interesting
Consider how he
Yeah I mean I guess you can probably like takeaway
Relief
From these companies if they didn't allow Alex back on
Like it's some sort of
Pressure on the company's to allow it
Would you be really f***** up
Just like
Alex Jones
How many could I don't know how enforceable agreed to be really weird
I think is like a real trend of Alex's that we talked about a bit but
Over and over again
Well yeah I mean that's a big part of it
Can anti monarchy
Individuals are able
Go to do ever
Yeah
Some doubt really f***** up
Internet
Mister president give me back on Twitter
Tear down this wall
Alex breaks down
We all go.
And Trump is going to go down
Deal with it
Accounts
Cuz they're coming after me
What you saying
Watching Trump closely
Out-of-pocket advisor
Florida
Forgot to get those accounts back on
A little too clear
I think that Alex knows that he's got himself into a no-win situation largely because connecting himself so closely to Trump and his
By himself past the point of no return
Like what does he do if Trump loses in 2020
Legitimately what can he do
He's made the argument that this guy become president is America the last shot against the globalist want to destroy America and kill
Your family
What's he going to do
Is it going to tell his audience to gear up for the 2020 midterm
They're trying to start a big and Peach
Play when the system is
Already by definition controlled by the globalist
His audiences so far
Pass that s***
With demons and child sacrifice
Defining of these
If Alex tried to pave it back to being an opposition voice to
The party in power by advocating for anything short of armed insurrection
His audience
His bank account
Empty gas bank account
Spend
Simultaneously Alex's and a huge problem is Trump win
Oz personal situation
Doesn't it
Prove
How long can Alex argue that Trump is in a death battle with a very same globalist enemies
Against
Without Trump doing
Sing it all to help Alex
If they were actually allies in anything more than lip service level bulshit
You think the Trump would want to protect
Austin supported
Most public supporter of the only voice in the media who
He gets it
The board more Alex us
To pay the consequences for his actions
And the longer it goes where Trump doesn't
Give a f*** about Alex
Who he'd hoped would help him Advance his own personal interest
And it has not gone that way Alex
Is going to have
Fall on his sword
Play the Martyr
It doesn't seem like there's a dumbo
Well I honestly Alex
It's kind of realize
But unless something very specific happen
His date
Anything like that
But doesn't serve any purpose
Because he's become so entwined with Trump
Escalate escalate
He can't receive
He kick given
Because the
His Alex gives an inch it's not him just trying to moderate
Stream or be
Ground to literal demons
Child murder
And that's a bad position to be in
Any negotiation
Any compromise is compromise with the devil you can't compromise with the Devil
The only
Illiana song
The only two positive outcomes for Alex right now
Harper Trump to become an authoritarian ruler
And ruthlessly suppress and depress
Or
Trump loses a of Civil War
Pisan any form is not a marketable option
For Alex anymore he is too far gone
Last year when we were talking about like
What is it going to do what is going to take for him to Pivot away from Trump
How could those days are gone
Audience city has in the revenue stream that is
Become
Universo
Crucial
Now you can
I really I don't
I think I think it's
Possible
The Heat
I could but it would be one of the hardest
Maneuvers ever
It would require going to
Advocate
Yeah but he would have to turn on the government
Such a hard way
Create a narrative
Spin the narrative
And all
And the The Logical conclusion to his audience
Would be
And that would be the Civil War option
In terms of him being able to
Retain his place
The market
Rather have qanon people around him
To get Lionel come to the f****** White House
As long as he's got foxandfriends he'll be free
Account
But I refuse
Into any of truck
I refuse
On principle
He's giving away more public
Absolute appreciation to that
Then I Alex
In the optic Salvador tarab
Eclipse like that last one to ask Taco Bell
If Trump doesn't win
I can't help but think about how much better Alex's life would have been
Straub
Like you could have maintained his imagine
The guy was above
Partisan politics
Honestly
Someone with his talent offering a criticism
Trump from
Will probably be a very marketable thing and
Environment
Even in 2016 2017 2018
Someone with the gift
That Alex has just in terms of
Computer tower
Ignore the other terrible things about him
If he was offering a right-wing
Critique make better job trying to push it into the mainstream
Try to pull off
Like a lot of people really tried to help
You're right and he's so much
Better at
Being a liar
I think he's not nearly I mean
Embarrassing
He's not like
Just any pure competent
Lago Vista
Glenn Beck
So much money
In that space
Like you could have
You could have gotten
Less people over to side again
He could have done
I like all that s***
They use do during the Ron Paul time
Actually I think maybe you could have
But my guess is
He did not want to find out he doesn't want to find out
His audience loves him more than
For Trump more than him
That's a dangerous that's a dangerous what if you've never gotten on board with him
I've been against
It would have been perfect
Because he could have retained the audience that he had
Built in a different direction
That was much more on brand
The counter to the power
It would have been like
So reinforcing of everything
You have a
On the orb and he said I'm a globalist
There were so many new stories that have come out in every single thing that falls in line
All of Alex's old narratives
Posse Comitatus
He could have made so much money off
Banking
You think about it if you don't like it
It sucks that
He's so awful
Now Eric is really awful pile of s***
But you can take some comfort in knowing that
He's only such an awful pile of s*** right now because he's dealing with the worst decision
Movies ever made
A spiraling the drain
Cold comfort
Like Vicki could have gone
Flown under the radar
With all of this
Awful white nationalist
Stream
If he hadn't made the
This decision
So now it's our great
It is the the truth it
Racism
Bad for you as well
Do you know the people who voted for Trump
Solely
White power
Butterfly
Which is most
They're the ones who are also being f***** over Trump policy
Creasing
Just internally they're not happy
Yeah
Speaking of Rage
Machine member
I was going to try
Kylie cosmetics
Former Rage Against the Machine
I don't care about Donny Deutsch
Enjoy
The only reason I left the clipping is cuz Alex is mad at.
Sierra Vista
Is
It just seems like Alex is talking about himself
Okay
I love Donny Deutsch
What a pump
Their 100,000 viewers
Average
Live video
2 million
Hillary lost a shadowban
Because you can't
No one wants to watch you.
Diaries
The few minutes
There is just such a crystallization of absolute
Brainwashed weirdos who believe you're stupid
Yep and people who tuned in order to help argue to argue with people online
That's
Alex is probably less useful that second category
But you definitely like you know that that's what it shows
Used for
Listen to calls that were specifically hey Alex
What should I say
So Alex gets back now to the Instagram
Narrative
Important because he's really saying 200 billion people
They've been cheating all along
And now Google all of them are
200 million
Facebook and Instagram
Support the president
Like what
I was born on Friday
3 hours ago
Business calculator
Open calculator
You have the roller paper
Please use I just feels like I just a picture a desk with a
200 million
Yeah. I want to watch that
Viral
So he's just making
That's just
200 billion
It would take more than a half-hour
This is just what calculators to I guess Eddie's
Another
Interesting
Looking
Articulture
Important California
Illinois
Everywhere the Democrats
Control
People are losing
There
Student Loan financial aid
Because the unions and the lawyers
Prosperous area
Now the poorest
80000 California students
What's financial aid
Thanks
California
Two teachers union
Government
Think about that
Soundtrack
Stock today
What you get under their control
His collapse
You can tell by the way
Really
Taking long pauses music I don't know I don't know what's happening
I think I can roll with it
State government teacher marigold
Yeah
California
What is meddling
These damn liberals and Julian California
Sound like that honestly I have no idea why I care about us
The blue States
Liberal brainwashing Center
Never underestimate how much he and his intellectual
Opportunity possible to Moline labor
Right out the womb he was like
Socrum from his first breath
F*** labor
He's yelling that while his wife
Here's the first of the Myriad problems
It was the result of a federal rule from the Department of Education
Well it's actually
Percent
The regulation had to do with States being required to have a system in place for in-state residents who take classes remotely from out of
With the ruling
Place for dealing with
Concern then recipients of Federal student aid
Would lose access to
She said 8
It was a measure to protect students
They're absolutely consumer-protection related issues
Andreason's
For a rule like that
Naturally since Trump Administration
It didn't go into effect until July 1st 2018
Even then
Trump's people were trying to delay having to enforce it
Judge ruled postponed enforcing the rule any longer
So they started except 2019
There's like a week ago
The education secretary
How to blame because the National Education Association
Andy California Teachers Association
To get the rule implemented
California
The states most affected by this
Because they're the only state that's not part of the National Council for State authorization rep
Prosody
Sarah
Which basically is just a series of agreements
Recognize
California doesn't belong to that because they feel that the body does not offer strong enough
Consumer protection
Now they probably should have had something in place to deal with rule
Before Genesis lawsuit
But I think it a look at what's going on in the world and every reason to think that this world would never be implemented
And until it was they
Compliance with the rules
And they had
Place just up to that rule
Bigger issue is that as soon as California learned that there was enforceable to California.
Department of Consumer Affairs
So they met all the requirements of the regulation
And just like that all of the students who were at risk of losing their financial aid work no longer risk of losing their financial aid
By the time I was already
He's misrepresenting the
The story that the students lost their financial aid
When they were only at risk of losing it if California wasn't complaint with a Federal Regulation
He's lying about the union involvement in the situation
Does roll put simply
Alex
Really lazy dude
Who's on are misrepresenting already outdated
Just to make it look like unions are bad and blue states are
He's a loser
Yeah it's real serious literature
What's the f****** cares about
Financial aid go to college
What the f***
Even try to pretend
Go fly a kite with her
That Loan program.
Doing something in their life
You will receive zero consequences other than you
Successfully delayed this rule 42 bucket
Everybody had every reason
To assume that they were going to
Create more legal hurdles
Or
Just make it so
Exactly
Yeah it's there
Chaotic environment that Trump in his administration
Creating around
Types of fish
SO2
Then
Turn around and blame
Somebody for not following the rule that the federal government
Is it a federal rule
I know that you should follow rules
Yeah but you're also creating an environment where no one knows what rules are real
And no one knows
What rules to follow its absolute
Because
It's the same thing as what we were talking about earlier
It's just too much
Travel to sue somebody
Not enough
Is if Trump just stopped
Following all of these rules
Nobody knows which ones to put their energy into
So you can see every possible
Enforce
Is the Hallmark
Of sort of autocratic
Because then you create the environment
And targeted enforcement is bigger
So
The Weeknd
There was a little bit of a dust-up
Donald Trump
And Elijah Cummings
So
Cummings comments
Director
About
Situation in
Rivalry
Refugees
And
Called
Baltimore
Rat infested
Yeah
Appreciate that so much
Clearly races
Coded language
That was you
Yeah
Don't get it I get it I think they make it
It is nice now
Disregard anything that anybody
Copc
You're all Races
Do you prioritize things
That
You diss prioritize
Your priorities are such
Take
Higher priority than
Alex response to this appealing to that video that we discussed on episode
Where he created
Completely artificial appearance
Combining
Candace Owens video from
Are you workout
Right
Specifically created
Keep kids
Out of
Airport
Appearance
Of what these eyes
Centers were like
To be like this world alive coming to talkin about so then he gets past that hurdle
Elijah Cummings
Instead of really dressing
To do is make fun of Victor Blackwell
The CNN anchor who broke down
While discussing
How he
Experience
Tweeting about Elijah Cummings
Mockingjay
Is that
Show
Lack of humanity that Alex's show
But I wanted to really drive home
Is really making a meal
Is making fun of
This
Anchor
Having an emotional reaction
Trump
Using
Dehumanizing language consistently towards non-white
Whatever the hell you are
But it gets worse
Victor Blackwell
Hypertrophic reps
Infested Baltimore
So you see already what he's doing is he's created the false appearance of the conversation
Cold black
Is not what people are responding
So he's already shifted the goalposts
Distraught man for himself to talk about
Here is some more of this
This is disgraceful
There's a Revolution going on in California so many Sanctuary areas
Want out of this ridiculous
And breeding concept
Infested he says
So real quick before we get to Alex's response
I think it's really important to point out that the
The part of Victor Blackwell
Opposed
Got pretty popular on
Import
Contacts
Alex is cutting out of the beginning of this clip
Is he's explaining that
Secure the presidents of the United States
Distantly.
Dehumanizing language about non-white people
He points out in this
A discussion of that in all of Trumps
43000 tweets
He only uses the word infested to describe
Predominately legislators that he
Instances of white
Legislator
That he is
Got Netflix
Use that same
When he does
So that is the conversation that is what
Victor Blackwell
Is about
I was deprived of the context
In order to make fun of Justice
The fact
Victor Blackwell
Which is really good
The President says about Congressman Cummings District
Watch your show
No human
You know who did mr. president I did
Home from the hospital
This is mind control
Trying to stay clean it up help
No human should have to live there it's not good
Truth
Don't you
Blackwell
Obviously there are endemic problems
And systemic problems
Send
Baltimore there are
You know it's far more complicated than I would be able to explain
To anybody
You can't just watch The Wire
Right
Where's over-simplification that Alex is doing
Gyros
Disgusting
Very shity
Expression
That one person
Can't do any
Represent this area
And if he doesn't fix it
You must be profiting off not fixing it he must want it to be this way
Which isn't necessarily good
No it's absolutely impossible for these people to understand
Yeah and the way that if you pull one lever here
It will change something
Corruption involving I probably could probably
Almost
Are there better strategy maybe should be explored
Possibly
People who care
Alex and Trump
Or not
Sickness next day we get back here
To Alex
Making fun of
Victor Blackwell
It's pretty gross
Home from the hospital
There a challenge
No Doubt
I want to hear what you gave mama
Slaughterhouse you got a car
Have no idea what he's talking about
What do you know about his personal would you know anyting
Absolutely
I don't know it
Blackwell did this for his community I'll look back
There's no it's a losing game to even Explore a
It's just worthwhile pointing out that Alex
So here's the last
Start back
What people get up and go to work
Be careful that families there
Stuff like this is indicative of
Things that are threatened
Dude
Constant repetition going back and go over it and
Behavior that Alex employees
Towards things that are
Pretty prevalent like there's no denying that this clip went all over the place
Would have access
Steward they might come in contact
It's making an argument that is
Because it does
Let me know
Discuss
Victor Blackwell
The idea that Trump uses
Language
Specifically in situations
It is
To hear it something has an effect
On people
If that were allowed to be seen
Perspective
It runs the risk of opening up his audience's eyes
Too empathic position
And understand
How other people
Is dangerous
Daddy
That's even though a large number of his audience
Intuit actually be
There's a crucial distinction
Later on at 10 episodes
Leave on the Monday episode
He plays a clip of Marianne Williamson
How hosting a apology
Where
He. He doesn't need to box
Because
Is creative
An environment where it looks like an absurd
So he can just play
Alex
Uses
Other media
And it's important
Understand this strategy
Employed
When something is a
I believe it
To the woodshed
Because of this
Cheshire
All right here we go
Easy as a pre-recorded
Message to the present
You're committing suicide
If you don't
All right how beautiful
This is
I would describe this is very embarrassing
Like the idea
First of all he thinks he's talking directly to the president
Crazy
If he thinks he's talking
The president
He has to think that the president is
Stupid is one of his listener
Exercise
An embarrassment
Admit
Memes are more powerful than
Combined
America
Criticizing
Has greenlit
The Purge
This is your distribution
24-hours
Your speeches
And they're just being annihilator
Season plying this 200 million accounts
Trumpets as
3 million illegal immigrants vote in the
Clear like he's making it
So this is your distribution Network where your truth literally almost
Right right you're not going to get rid of
I understand but I'm gone
From social media
Youth
And I'm still making a profit
Area of the market no one's going to nudge me from that right
I am in trouble if you lose
Mybranch
Right
If you don't have a ton of
Everybody with
My business is gone
Trump
Program
He's fundamental correct
Lorraine's daycare
Cedar planks
Circle circle
Everybody
This is my cousin
Dog fur
Behind all of this
This is like
It's so overt
The the the sort of
The motivations behind
It's just so much alike
In the state were in I'm sucked
If you go down
And
You need
These dudes you need these crazy dudes
You need you need to these Liars pay-per-view keep on this path
And I don't want right thinking that I don't want
Don't make me do it over it's a hard pit
Chef
I've been slow playing him for a long time
But here we are
So does next still from his address
President he just implied
Again
People gone again
Open and Ludacris
Get on and off every few hours
Dawn Dawn
Talk about
This is election meddling
People following Democrats eyes
News organizations
Delete it in a coordinated fashion
There would be an outcry
Really hate it whenever
Alabama and Georgia
Boats from the roll
I don't think he cares
Consolidate dead people
Like
There aren't any high-profile Democrats
Your life cleaning people who haven't been
Like demonetized on YouTube or kicked off Facebook or Twitter
It's absurd it's just most of them were like
That sucks
Is a shity free-speech Crusades go on
So in this next
Cliff Alex
Trump doesn't get on board something
Location
Oh boy
Did you
Could you sit there and let these
Makes me
So I mean probably means nothing
Sternly worded letter
I mean it
I don't know
I don't know what to do
Potential of danger in the vague notion of Alex's audien
I don't
Like it's funny because he's
Personally an impetus
Enforce
He has the potential to inspire in people
To do
Negative
Like he has nothing left
Like this Trump has abandoned
I could see it.
Realself
It's always funny
Because this is about memes
You really have a hard time believing that we live in a world memes
Laughable on one level but it also has the sword
Thing where you got to you got to recognize
If he all the sudden
If it weren't for that
Perform through
So Alex Adams
Address to the Press
I want I need to be clear
This is an address to the Press
Keeps
Mr. President Trump
Direct
Sage Walker support
He thanks the audience for their support
Thank you all for your support
Yeah
Okay
Using leading up to an ad pivot that doesn't come at the end of his address to the president
Interesting
Mr. president
Don't take Superman will never get back on Facebook I mean it's not really
Because he does this
Is it performative
From commercial and here's what's going on
Keep this operation going
I forget to remind viewers
Find it
Proposed infowars.com
Presentation
First to do for our body
Tomorrow
11 a.m. Central
So he had a tape recorded introduction to a pre-recorded infomercial about iodine
I don't know jujitsu
Explain
His show on Sunday
Substantial Sunday show than many I've heard
Or maybe he's important
Once again
And Monday
Instagram narrative
My friend
It's it spiraled
Pouring in Instagram
Did they see your Christian they're coming
Scare other Christian Americans
Stop talking about Jesus
I don't know about that
I'm certain it's not because of
American flags or Christians
Huh
Nope otherwise
Look at already.
The 200 million people getting kicked off
My family members are calling me
Assume that this garnish is a light
I don't know
We get the introduction of
He's going to show up later
Trevor Bauer
No
Retired state police officer
That is brother's friend of the show
Joe Bannister
We'll be popping in at the bottom
He will be getting the inside scoop
Festival
Where several people were shot and killed
Free zone
SoJO Spa
4 years
Alex says that he ran security for it I can't
Confirm that I'm not really all that interested
When we get to his actual interview he's got nothing to say
So
Legitimately
Expert analysis
Webcops
Search the guy's house like
Nothing
Delivering publicly available information with the authority of a
Retired cop
Help Alex
I guess he's related to Joe f****** Bana
Brit
Another one that Alex is covering over this time
Spend at the Goodwill
The Director of National Intelligence
Two-stepping
John Ratcliffe
To be his replacement
Noted GPS John rep Alex is
Thrilled with it
Pretty funny
Here's a clip of him being thrilled
Ridiculous on the other end
I've already gotten into
The record
That's bending
Alarm Bells
Might not be the best example of
He's very supportive.
And it's hilarious how Cravens
Spineless and full of s*** Alex Jones is
If you need me example of a f*** about anything for look no further than his
Support of Trump's nomination of John Ratcliffe as his director of Nash
Intelligence
John Ratcliffe is not qualified at all for the position of piano
He was the mayor of Heath Texas population
Approximately 6,000 48
During that time George W bush appointed for the eastern district
Texas possession he was mysteriously
Here before returning to public life
In 2014 be primary the sitting Republican in Texas
4th District in the House of Representative
He was running against Stacey
Who was 91 years old at that time
When ralphel inter-government in the Texas Senate
JFK was still alive
This was an old old man
You could make your campaign slogan he's 91 probably win
So breakfast still only ended up with
With a narrow margin in the primary democratic
So you want to see in Congress
2016 Democratic candidates
The position of DNA is a non-partisan
Positions
It's very important that the person who occupies that position not be someone who's invested in Party politics
Because should that person in charge of
All the country's intelligence
Agencies
Be someone to hold into a political party
You can imagine the sort of things they could do to help their political party of choice
No I mean
Can you imagine somebody abusing their power
Previous to Trump being elected no one who occupied this position
Came from a background as a member of Congress
These are career diplomats or intelligence profession
Who had 60 years
Career as a Republican
As well as an eight-year career in the House of Representatives
The politicization of this position is exceedingly dangerous
And you know we're seeing that happen
Even if there were a presumption of impartiality to it our intelligence Community is a dangerous thing to have exist
Partisan politics
People real trouble
It's definitely
Okay so what you're saying
Is that
Were we to have a
Partisan director of mash
Somebody who
Can direct
Intelligent
To do things
Are beholding to a hard right Republican lunatic
Thinks that everybody's out to
Him
And wants to use until
To further his own
You think him a point
Is a bad idea
Responsibility
It's also worth pointing out the John Radcliffe as a hundred percent
Conservative score from Heritage action
And ranks as one of the most
Conservative members in all of Congo
He just yelled at Mueller
He was on the shortlist for Trump
Attorney General
Even though
He's a team
Give me some context
Text Ted Cruz
Score
Louie gohmert
Ratcliff is Bork
I've literally zero faith that you'll be able to separate it for little leading from the job of being
But I also think that's why
All that should have disqualified
And here's something though
Should Cara
In 2009 Ratcliff became a partner at the law firm of Ashcroft Sutton Ratcliffe
None other than
George W Bush's attorney general 9/11
Radcliffe is involved in the Bush Administration
Then afterwards became Partners in a law firm
Endorsing this guy to lead all the countries is essentially Alex
All the stuff he used to say
This is seriously disqualifying stuff here
Alma name trying to defend the nomination of a guy probably doesn't stand a chance
Being approved by Congress
Because already indications of the Republicans oxweld
You really hate to see this
Guy who was a partner in a law firm with John Ashcroft
Alex
Do you remember who you are
You hate John Ashcroft only covered up the Democratic party of 9/11
Conservatives
Libertarian
I have no idea
Stupid
Another name piece of Alex's
Narrative here on the 29th
Which of course Alex
Proceed to
Carry out as
Black people are not great
Goes goes pretty hard
I mean that stuff
Pretty clear oh yeah it gets worse
Ms Clipper about to listen to
Dear Alex
Who's making the argument
Talks about people attack people
People
Which is the proper
Videos
And compilations and underground articles and local news stories by police
Where games of racist black people
White people
Young people
Kill them
They just lie
Before Congress
There's a lot of
There's mountains
Supremacist
White nationalist
Motivated
Videos of black people beating up white people
Text
Sure it's
Visceral
Tons of racism
Proof of anything
It's not
Good it didn't this is what he's relying
The Knockout game
Does have we had to
Enough
And none of them has come from
Alex
Is still try to defend Trump
Comments about Baltimore and I don't
I don't know
Murder Maps
Murders a year in Baltimore
Rivals
By Chicago
So the first thing we can tell hear from Alex
The coverage of the whole Trump Elijah Cummings
Homicide
Cuz the book
Yeah obviously there's very complicated situation
Explain all of it to you or even advocate for what the rights
Solution is I'm not
Outside of my Lane
What I can tell you however is
Politely to explain to Alex
I'm going to give you a little bit of your own medicine
President do that for you there are thousands of murders a year in Baltimore
That number might be right about a place like Caracas or a couple cities in Brazil
Consider is anywhere near that level
Murder
In 2017 there were 341 murders in bulk
Alex doesn't care about reality
He cares about
Presentation of the narrative
It sure looks like there were thousands of murders in that Lawless cities there are
Alex this is shity work
You need to do better
Because these are just numbers their statistic
You can even just talking about total murders
Is it pointless
Statistics
You got to talk about things in terms of rates
And when you do you find 100,000
The numbers become less meaningful
Chicago and 27th
Highest murder rate
In the country
Only two high-end just done
But
When you
Chicago hits
300 more murders in 27
Tina Baltimore
But the murderer was much lower
Yeah why is that
How do you integrate this into your conversation
You can't
Of course their burgers when there are more people
Society
This connection to Baltimore
Hey.
Chicago
Booking by murder rate there's tons of red-state
The number one is
What is the highest murder rate
It doesn't matter this conversation blue-state red-state doesn't
F****** matter but you can create the optic
If you use statsportal it
And that's all I was doing because
He doesn't care about violence
He cares about using
2 attack
The people of the other party
Absolutely
Not care about him
Improving
No
Mainly because
Still alive
M2u
So
Lying about that are involved
Ugly
It sucks
What's Bill Gates
Yeah
He's trying to
Brainwashed brainwashed people against whites
Sure
Credible
Level
Washington
Foundation
Finding Finance to buy
Perfect
WhatsApp
Besides themselves
Anybody else were funded by
Buying products
So first of all I'm excited to hear about brainwashing
But also
If this is true
No not that part
But if it's true that Alex has had all these people
Just the American people
Alex why are you fighting so hard to like make sure that they don't get access it
Why are you creating a milakovic
Money does come from like a really sick
Supplement sale in books and water filtration business
Let's see those numbers baby
I want to I want to congratulate you on a business well-run
So secretive to the point
People like your head of HR your father
Other people I have no idea what the f***** going on why does no one know what your business
Model is why is everyone
If
It weren't
Something Shady
Please Alex
You f******
You know he has he lives
Lives in a countless resistance
I believe is
Who is it
I've been
You're Alex Chinaman on something
WhatsApp
This size hole let's storm Area 51
I'm not sure if you had I missed some days because of the move outside
I heard him talk about it in the episode
He's got to have a take on that
September
Haven't
I heard about that
Leo zagami told me about that
They were storming area
Like this is something that Alex probably
Is got to talk about
First of all
He should probably be thrilled at this cuz all it is is a joke
I didn't know what
Like how he was going to land on it
And to say that I was surprised
To hear his take on it
For being understanding
I've been watching this area 51 situation
Original
3 weeks ago
I'm sure you have the same thoughts let me just explain something I'm sure you all know this
Facebook page last year
Ronnie Bass
So long
The facebook.com
Alex
Business
Uber
Everybody knows that you got to pee
Unless you're just a private person I want
Third Estate terms of service
I have a Facebook page about a podcast about how you're an idiot
Yeah I paid a couple times like $5
Experiment with a
Not worth it
Yeah I've ever put
They have no I've never had
Play running this out
They're going to demand money
Google. Letting people Christian
University
Next hour
Because
He is struggling what about the area 50
He was right
About 3 weeks ago
As were most of you about Area 51
About Area 51 is got to pay to have a Facebook page
All the Christians
Anyone have a dog grooming salon
Anyway
This individual
Is Qatar
Michelle
Shelf
Individual
Storm
Actually
An Air Force
Weapons chemical weapons
Decommissioned
Nuclear reactors on a submarine
A giant waste dump
And Facebook
A Christian
Organize
Conservative
Congressman
Reach their members on Facebook
McKellips
Storm a military base
Question about the last and the CIA
Show us Google
They are 100%
Running
Conservative members of Congress
Are not very interesting
A joke
Event like this
Pretty funny and people have done a lot of marketing for it on their own with little
Videos and and that has led people
Promote
Joke
The CIA started it
The alternative is absolutely the truth is this is a funny people liked it
People interested in a way that they're not in your b******* bigoted
Attentive that all these other shadowbanned Republicans
F*** off
Appealing to people in your not
Jumping in on this right
Although they literally can't because his listeners
Would actually try and start
That's troublesome
I think that Alex would end up turning into Steven Kelly
The Getty Museum
Is back up later and I would play it now because then there would be
There's another comment about Area 51
Like an hour later in the show
I was thinking about this organized the episode
Chronology what are the things I think is important is to
Repetition
Of this show
Repeatedly throughout the course of the show
What he does
Back and forth from them in a way that's disorienting to your mind.
Remember this brought it up so there's already been cover
It's intentional.
The strategy of
Of never
Meeting Jeff
But still creating the appearance of
Through
Westside
Artificial familiarity
I guess it's whatever
Artificial turf similarity with the story
Oh I know that
Presenting
Presenting an angle
Without any depth
And then
Because you're bringing it up later
Yeah now that makes sense
Intentional
I think perhaps
I think I think it is on some level
Because he couldn't do it the other
He couldn't do a show where he actually got into the nuts and bolts
Do something
Because it's like a show like ours
Everything
Hey guys sorry about this this headline looked good
F***
Arden
Fans of Alex Jones
Call Safelite
I might have tried to write the show like that
Disappointment might want to try one episode a special episode 30
The performa
I don't think I have the commitment
But Alex is a committed race
And next blippi talks about how the Chinese
Because he does give an example of one specific person who is not
Mitch McConnell
That's what who are the most
Please show more
The most racist people on earth
Chop't
Wait the second
Play music
No no no no
Yeah dude just say
Just say
Like Bing Bong or some other races version of like they're all the same
What's a what Chinese country are you from Laos is that the one
Pretty overt
That really is Alex is trying to
Pretend he's not racist and other people are and then he just bodies
Racist opposition
Bright
So some Chinese people are Tracy
Congratulations on your brain work
This is a representation of the disjoint
He brought it up earlier
Drugs
And then we would have ruled the planet
Audiology
A free market
And you could have sat on top of it but you had
Needle
Ding-a-ling
Dementia
He said once as hell
Making it up that he uses that
What is that we already heard earlier in the episode Alex
Is Big main gripe with the Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation
They're brainwashing people
White
Earlier
That's part of the chickenshit dimension
Lord it over a free-market world dominated by
White people
Decided to brainwash people against whites
You saying is you guys f***** up
You guys could have been
As opposed to a really rich
I also think that after having that episode about the British is realism
Christian identity ideas
Tough to hear that sort of
You know you could have
Bad world's not here a little bit of that in there as well
That's going to keep popping
Also you know we talkin about the globalist
Bill Gates
I'd like to read to you from the protocols of the Elders of Zion
We should destroy about the importance of Education
This is followed up in this way we shall create a blind before switch will never be in a position
Removing any direction without the guidance of our agents
Leaders of the mob
The people will submit to this regime because it will know
Better leaders will depend its earnings gratification
Receipt of all kinds of
So I mean what do you describe
Destroy the family in order to make us
Less able to
Have our political directly from the protocols
It was really weird when I read those
And protocol number 11 was and will send people to the chickenshit dimension
Bright International
I mean Alex isn't making that accusation but it isn't
That's been fairly popular in
In 2012 Iranian vice president mohammad-reza Rakim
Gave a speech
For anybody
Research and find one
They do not exist
This is proof of their involvement at the drugstore
A European diplomat
This was definitely one of the worst I've ever heard in my life
Iranian hsieh hsieh clerk cleric
Dude
So like
Do you have this bike
Specific purpose direct parallels
To the protocols
They're bringing drugs in
You know that is also
Anti-semitic propaganda
Is it good to hear
Bring that up whenever
Very clearly
So I kind of think he's already got about Bill and Melinda Gates
The function of the disjointed
He himself kind of thinks he's covered it already
Daily Caller news Foundation
Found it all being funded
Black lives matter
Kill the cops
But I guess I already did
You want to hear this professor
I thought I already kind of covered it
That is pretty funny
Play music forgot exactly what it was
Was going to stay near the music
So $1,000 a pop example professors he said you want to hear this
Professor dementor
The Daily Caller
Read this article
Is basing his narrative on
Daily Caller
And I don't know if I
Literally the only connection any of this has the bill
Their Foundation
Has hired the person
50s hit piece article is about
The article discusses Robin diangelo the PHD in Multicultural education
And is what is a well-respected lecturer and author of
Banfield
She's the person who coined the term white fragility
Very specific expression of
Exactly that I was going to say
Come on guys
The worst
Literally
The entire thrust of this article he received
He charges $12,000 for a speaking appearance
Scholarship and Oliver work
Because she's
What's the rate of $12,000
Daily Caller
$12,000 for speaking engagement is not really that high rate for a purse
Particular
A simple search of talent
For instance Ben Shapiro charges between 50 and $100,000 for a speech
Jordan Peterson
402 200000 as does Sean Hannity
Alex's buddy Candace Owens charge
Between 20 and 30000
James O'Keefe is right in the same ballpark as Misty Angelo with a price range
210 to 20000 per speed
Bill O'Reilly charges 100
The 200,000
John Ashcroft requires 50000-100000
Take a break from running a law firm with Alex's Preferred Choice for
Director of National Intelligence
Alex is Buddy and noted pervert Ted Nugent charges
50 to 100 thousand dollars
I think you get the point
Not in the fields of either being an in-demand lecture or booking into lectures
Lehigh
But ultimately it's not
When you look at the larger picture of the industry
It's kind of
On the lower end of an in-demand
This is a cheap trick that propaganda
Confused about social justice or economic
Equality as a hypocrite
And then they get to feel entitled to just ignore the entire message
It's a strategy self-defense
Honestly this
Situation
It goes a long way toward proving it Robin diangelo
Deserves that speaker
Great
Because
Their Manifesto
About
Concept of white fragility founded by noted white nationalist Tucker Carlson
Crying bloody murder about her charging a reasonable rate for her services
Largely because they're afraid of the topic
Luxury
Literally
If it work
Then this is dumb how about the revulsion they have
Is way better targets Pikachu's then D'Angelo
Also
Tucker Carlson charges over $70,000
I don't understand
Like
Did you did you get
Screwed over in the Equifax breach
No I checked
I did I don't understand
Because they are going to run out of money whatever
Just going after these idiots
Steal their money Robinhood
That's what I'm saying I don't know if I'm not going to double down on your
Possession
So there's nothing
Foundation they're listed as one of the people who have
Paper service
That's the closest
And it's one of a number
Groups or organizations
This isn't about the Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation
Specifically being her Patron
Of course because he wants to
He hates the Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation
He thinks that they're brainwashing people again
He's using this article as the justification
Bulshit
It's all good
Lindsey
White fragility
Prompt
Facebook has been set up
You really had to pause there before conservative wonder where his brain was
So Alex is commercial time on the show has become
A real
Sad place
Course Diamond gusset Jeans songs everybody's having a great time
Here's a commercial
Alex Jones
Exclusive
Content
Free record City spoken low rent commercial for his
Ariane holyshit
Text I also check back in on his subscribestar
It's very sad
Gloating
Same time
I don't feel like I am
You only have 400 people
Who are donating to his
Subscribe
But it's been opened
This is a very
Dangerous looking lack of Engagement
He shows up Joe Bannister brother
He wants to talk about the Garlic Festival
He got nothing
Really no insight
Here is
What I would describe as his expert
I certainly these type of things
Take you no hours if not days
To hash out
And I do understand that the
This morning
They did
Service search warrant
At the suspects
Residence
So I'm sure they will learn as the days go by
What the
This says Shooters motivations were
No that's pretty responsive
Right that's not what Alex was probably
Boils down to
What you do if you want to kill yourself
What we needed more guns garlic
South that's weekend
So interview is real boring
We get it
Allison starts rambling
About like
The globalists need to bring in the global government
Now
For a specific reason
I think
I don't think I agree with
Is wrong
Because all these
Technologies are
Coming forward now
Controller
Where will be multiplanetary
Will be
Interstellar
So fast
Will be
You think fire was invented
Love the shifting globalist they're doing what they're doing
So much over the course of his career I love that now
In the present day
His excuses
They need to make a One World Government because we're about to go to space
They want to be in control of Mars
Or whatever
It's just like I don't understand
What are you missing
I'm missing the jump from that used to be about like creating just a dictatorship making a prison
I'm missing the time when it was a financially motivated
Of all the globalist
Plans is that all of them according to Alex are incredibly long-term
So frequently like I don't I don't know I have mixed feelings
Idiot world government
The wrong people administering it would be the worst literal worse than another guy
But I do
It's some sort of
Collaboration Global probably required
Go into faith and start calling
Parts of space
We would need a one world government
Russia other countries are going to be
What are you going to do go to war
Keep them from going to space
Literally
Able to leave the planet and still have
Tensions
Between us
Just based on where on this f****** Earth
We came from absurd
CID
All the progress you could make
Seriously
Amazing
Advance
It could all be jeopardized by China coming in with space
Ever want to make it to that next level while they're still deposit
Ability that we're going to fight with each other in ruin all of it
It's silly
Play the
Colonisation Wars
Of Europe from
I mean it wouldn't even be catastrophic
Destroy
You know like of course
Okay so we destroyed New America
Jupiter's moon
Maybe what we should have done instead of just
Destroy America
On Earth
Easier
Why would we send Rockets all the way out there glow up credibly dystopian possibility
The idea of
Branching out in colonizing
Without
Absolute collaboration
It just seems like
It seems like childish it whenever you can
Consider the Stars
Gundam
And in that situation
What
Every country
Colonizer
Places in
And then creates very race
Cheapest robots
Interesting interesting series
Fair enough
So this is
Get to the Marion Williamson video
Make fun of her but interrupting
To be presented
Tucci's
Leading these people in apologizing
Before the horrors of slavery in our country's history
Alex refuses to engage with the ideas of that the lingering effect
Economically
Sociological
Politically that have rippled
Still impact
Today about how
He shouldn't feel guilty about slavery
He didn't do it
No one did it
Almost nobody did it
Not much like him saying that the Chinese are racist except for his Korean sister
Alex starts off on this
Clip
Feel guilty
About slavery
Then says something deeply races
Margery Williams
If your great-grandfather was a
You're an independent person
Only 2% of people
Most people are European
Is that what it is
Color
Amazing
Collective guilt
Zimbabwe
No
This is so evil
Subway
Is your your example is Rhodesia bro
Yep
Example
Is
Rhodesia
Yep yep
That he's trying to argue against him feel guilty about slavery in immediately
Is
A repressive
Supremacist
Apartheid government
Brutal Colonial
System that was put in place
In modern-day Zimbabwe
That is so f***** up to me
It was a good exam
That was the headliner
We had this
Really
Stupid,
Say that first of all I'd like to say we had a stupid conversation on his part is a bucket
Play from
He said
No I think
Whites are free
Mainly because
Minorities cuz we're going to have
Whites are going to be the minority soon
They're going to do the whites
What weed
And I was like
Admirable in some way that he's able to articulate
Articulate it that way
Which kind of makes it more difficult to deal with his b*******
That guy
You'd hoped there was a possibility of a dialogue you know cuz he's
He's willing to
Express
Do this in the green room I don't have right
Is little bit more racist
Also
He points out that
Some Churches
But not the donation tray
But they're not taking my money and giving it
The god
Paula White
Hazardous Christian
Morrell loving love your brother the exploit
First Methodist Church in Austin Texas
Collection plate
Villa Monte
Myfamilypies
Show you
White devil
Wow
Wow that's why I usually
I don't know are they
Why do I know one of them did do the prayer at
Paula White Cain
I do I do I just Nash
Spiritual advisor
Pop-up video
I know I can't imagine.
Being like alright
So
We're going to take
Sims 4
One of the richest people in the world
It doesn't seem
Anyway
Based on my daily Colorado
Expensive
Bill Gates Bill Gates
Station
West is inherently evil
Trying to get white genocide
Say that we are you trying to say
Meaning the same thing
Is Western culture
Stop
I just hide behind
Terms used interchangeably
And assume the people aren't going to notice and call you out on it
Every single time
It's exactly the same thing
As with the preacher Smith
We talked about the children of Esau beat
Absolutely about Western
Civilization Western culture he's talking about white
As what he's doing
You bet he just makes up
Professor is
Mainly funded
5 Gates
$12,000
Already is a misrepresentation
Maybe one or two engagements
Such.
You Got The Touch
Got a text
He doesn't have anything to back that up he is just a starting it based on nothing to this article that doesn't
Bulshit
Used
I just saying whatever you want
It's crazy
The things
He bases his rhetoric in his narrative
It's so clear that like
Nothing can be dropped
Yeah
Could just be made up
He reports made up s***
With the same
Confidence
Betty does
Reading at
She has
Grounds for a libel
This can't be construed as deliberately lying about somebody
I think I text you probably could I also think it probably isn't worth
What are you doing
Is that
I apologize
Mistake
So earlier Alex
Pointed out
It's another teaching really on White Street
No it's not I really don't
It's not but
How he can
Conceived
How
People got rid of
This race well it was because the South Korean Chinese person told him
That could be
Got rid of tribalism
Real
Jesus Christ
If you accept
And you accept free-market ID
Is Wellfleet we come together
Be looking at now is
Theocratic government
Economia
Really weird is banana
Yeah
Choose from the New and Old Testaments in order to make their cases for what Christianity
You should be
They ascribe to Jesus
I feel like I should be able to play that game every now and again to his I'm going to have fun as long as biblical
Reintroduce the law of Jubilee 5
It's out of a different tube
Property even property sold in intervening years is to revert back to the original owner
But if you bought you were living on
To your family's original property
It's laid out that if you sell someone lands closer to the year to believe
Since a person is going to have less time on this planet
I like that
This is a law
Because there is no private property rights for humans
Explicitly expressed quote
This is God speaking
Prepare myself for that the land must not be sold permanently
Because the land is mine
If you reside in my land as foreigners and strangers
If you buy a house yet to give that house back in the Year of Jubilee
Except that houses in a walled City
If it's
Man I love good old throwing spaghetti at the wall
It's a weird setting rules
So Alex
Also she want to go do test
Jesus
Do not store up for yourselves Treasures on Earth
Where moth and rust
Destroy and where thieves break in and steal yourself Treasures in Heaven
Where moth and rust do not.
Destroy
For where your treasure is there your heart will be also
Passage in Luke 6 where Jesus
People to lend other people money with no expectation of being repaid
Merciful quote just as your father is
There's a lot of folks who try to make the argument that Jesus would have been on their side
Support their ideology if you were around
There's so much in the Bible that you can really pick and choose a lot
How to make contradictory arguments
Jesus was into free market capitalism
Yeah I can't
Biblical scholar in
The free market your
Professor
Speeches
Recorded up title
We have the exact
We have the exact is the conversation Alex refuses to have everybody is the exact same thing
Yeah people like Victor Blackwell words
Cut that part out
Cuz he doesn't want to
To open that box
He's guilty of the exact same thing
Did Victor Blackwell
Actual racing
Hordes
Text blackpink
Racist blacks
Robin diangelo
He is found
We have
Examples from earlier
City allows to play because he wants me to stand as a thing
Nonsense
He has a clip of Victor Blackwell which he has to interrupt constantly
This is stupid
Another clip
And it's
To the point where Alex
Can't allow it to
Play
It is to see oneself outside of Race To See oneself as unique special in
Individual exempt from the forces
Socialization
I think so
Woman said to him I don't see color are you going to see racing
Because I am black
I do think you know that I have a different experience than you do and you're not going to be able to understand that I do not
The parts of that experience that are really painful and problematic you refuse to acknowledge
I don't see color is
Yeah
Good people check
I want to get along
I want to hire folks off
They're fighting
The abolition of
So I'll
Alex
Pasta
Because he started
This is completely different than I have been saying
KeyBank
Clearly
About
The different experiences of people of different ethnic and racial background
Arrowhead vet
Communicated to his
Absolutely
Without just being like
Good rebuttal videos capable of that doesn't drift into like
Just outright
And that's why you have to shut
You're the shut that off
Being about affirmative action or something
There's only the races for fun
Which is not a good
Write three gathers himself
He realizes because
He's listened to part of the clip
Before the show
Any realizes that what it's about is
Knology
Different
Experiences that people in the country have Bass
Gathers himself and find his bearing
Either able to
To just be like love that
Acknowledging that there's different
Experiences
Itself is racist
Oh
No you got to see my color
No that's how you created
And then once it is about color
Walking down street
Let's go out to breakfast
Twenty-something black people come up
Embrace your eyes about your eyeball out
Because you're white
F*** that white devil
I believe that they turn that music up pretty loud
Outbreak
Do black people attack
Is it
My audience real juice
It's it's really f***** up
God
It's pretty crazy
You can't even listen
To somebody
You immediately know
Alex
That what she was saying
It makes so much sense to him that he was
So terrified
He was terrified
Yeah I know
Without like
Some
Desire to
Happy challenge
A little bit
Like I listen to Alex everyday
Why
Generally doesn't
But if he know
I don't listen to him the same way you listen
People who disagree with him.
Turn it off
This guy
Highlight of your day
I wish more that's for sure
More than we would be covering a very different
Esposo
It's it is
I don't know if I have
I don't think it's impossible
I don't
I'm ready
Everytime I dig into one of the stories opportunity to learn more
And easy always
Yep
But I still
Him spiraling out of
Control because
Is getting
Really
Frustrated
About these races
Are you pretty pissed off that he's been building up this narrative about Robin diangelo
Throughout the entire episode
He's play this clip and it didn't
Say what you want
And so
Getting more races
In the last
Segments of the episode
He's
Really
You pausing a lot
Islam Slow Down Speed
It's pretty f***** up
And they're hyper.
Minority shop
Fiendish group
Zombies
Hell-bent
And everyone
Cheer
2 billion
3 billion
4 billion
Grace Pacific
HIV was home
Each other videos
Mother and child
Crossing the tracks
White Berlin left-handed Goods
They stand
An army to kill
Kill that arm
So
F***** up
As far as I can tell Alex is completely making up huge elements
The story about that
Situation
A story about a woman and her child who were pushed in front of a train
Berlin
The child died
Alright
It is real in as much as it did
Are supported by any
Actual reporting
Another story
Also it wasn't in Berlin News
In Frankfort
Articles about the events of independent Guardian German Outlets
Less reputable source
The perpetrator was in police custody but refused to speak with authorities
And no motive has been
Established
Whatever the reality of this ends up being
Alex the report that he was racially motivated
That the man push them
The tracks because they were white
You have nothing to back that up no
No source for it no justice
Application for his claim
Other than the fact that the media reported that the man was from Eritrea
That is all Alex needs to
Confidently
Absolutely
Did this is an out-of-control minority killing white people because they were white
I can't be clear about this
It doesn't
Matter what the end result of the investigation into this case
It may very well end up being that this individual did because he hated
That could be
Alex is doing is
Completely rapist
He feels like this is a racially-motivated attack and that's enough for him to report it as that is if it is
And then
It's being proof that all whites are under attack Africans are being wound up
Civilization
Someone who wasn't interested in promoting racism and white identity would not do this
They would rely on actual facts
The guide the reporting
As opposed to
To put it simply White
Agility
I've never heard Alex ever report on any of the many instances of people pushing
People on the train tracks
There are a number of them
He could have
Alex chooses dory's in Taylors is narrative
Purpose
And that is to make his white audience
Afraid of
People unlike
Confident that they're always in the right
Even if it takes lying or just making s*** up
Crafts that narrative
There's no other way for me to put this really
Alex Jones Show in the present-day is racist trash
That is trending towards increasingly violent imagery in incitement
He has nowhere left to go
To get more extreme
I do not think that bodes well for the
These shows suck
Yep this is a bad show
Weird
To watch him
Try and create
A what about is
In real time
What you doing
Discussed at the very beginning
As far as giving people
If somebody is like
If somebody goes to one of his viewers or one of his listeners
Susan says
What about all of the
Supremacist terrorism that you're not acknowledging ignore you
They'll be like what what about a woman pushing the bus
So there you go with it
To talk about
It's up to deal with the issues
I'm scouting a lot but
Sucks
It really it really really does suck
It's really
Scary
The potential that it has
Reaction to
Does he have Alex
Squid
Has to be an Army against the West
Start my wife
Send a conveyor being an army there
Come slit his throat
GoPro
I just don't think that you
You can talk like that without
Having a reasonable expectation
It's some of your audience is not going
Deal with that
Your audience of my
A I should
View all people of African heritage
Right
It's enforcing
Encouraging racism
A violent degree
Or potentially violent
I don't know I feel like as we go through this
I certainly don't know what the law
So I don't like to comment on that too much
But I think the important
This is what
He is putting out into the world
If things
Please go bad
Yeah
Just know
He's doing this
He's a part of it
That's the only that's the only thing I see
I don't know
I can see in and talk
California Student Financial Aid
Sure
Heights
It's like that's one of the things that I thought about with
Conversation of like
I think
White people are
Afraid
What they do
No worries
And
Alex
This is afraid of
To a certain extent
She knows
And so is real anger comes from
We need to defeat them otherwise we're going to get
He knows that he deserves guilt
To feel guilt
It's
It's unfortunate because
Completely Blocks office
Entire pack of bacon
The present and the future don't have to
Tamir the path
There's a
Positive world's week
Towards
That doesn't
Involved
Curing tribalism with
Appeals to Jesus
The free market
Pictures of love so much
There's a there's a possible
Better Way Forward now
Just closed off to it
Destructive
It has to make you
Miserable
And you don't even know you can't even
Because what you think is making Wells
You can't do it on the radio on the radio so long as you ascribe it to
Yeah well the one
If you ascribe it to yourself
You can't expect
Continue to make 1/8 cup
So I don't know I think you show sucks
On Friday
That's the plan
With another
Adventure
Stupid stupid world
Website
Iran Twitter we're also
On Facebook you if you wanted to
Download r-pod
Or share it with
What you should
To do
Is downloaded onto your phone
Leave your phone unlocked
And in a very public
And have it always playing
And people will eventually
That sounds right
I think that's the best strategy
What about their absolute
Tractor people are not
That's not true
I meant the
Chimeras
Who are tractor they are not at their house
I don't think we're far less enough
They are
So I come back
$12,000
Dollars for lecture
But one guy
Is Alex Jones
Alex