Air Jordan
I have great respect for its knowledge by now I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Collegeboard.com
Dick novelty beverages little bit about Alex Jones
Then what was your first
Social media page
Probably my face
I know that I was on Facebook
Had to be College email address on it
Villas Emerald was Upper Darby
I very strongly resisted getting on it
Because
It seems like a very much like a frat
Kind of thing
World
Connection
I had that vibe
Call him for my camp
I got some
I got like 8 Mile
Like this
People look dumb
Dumb dumb
Wonderwall
A really mean about your ass kind of course
I'm instalike
No no
I wonder who this guy is
I remember my brother being like you could check if he's on
See if you can find us an inference
Motivated me to join the Facebook was to find out like
Can I install this guy
Human races
Demise
Unfortunately that's what suckered me in to Facebook
Mike my personal use face
Personally
But
All that information
It's terrible
Bears on their butt out
Terrible
Any product
Alex Jones
Tell me about any number of those things
Don't Furley or the week
Did not know that
Alex named first
Debate coverage
Special
She named after a
Vaguely anti-Semitic
He has usura
Come on
Perfect timing
But you're trying to get
Because this is a 40-hour live
He's doing money Bombs all the time it's almost like the other one was a huge 40 hours
I don't know if he was going the entire time but it was at least
Tonight
Really long live spectacular
Two days straight
I've learned
My lesson with Alex Jones
Moneyball Marathon
That is like don't even bother with
The times that Alex is gone
He's going to be
You don't
It's going to be fun and games I'm just going to sit here and listen
In 240 hours of this dumb b******* and then
Hours and hours of Harrison Smith
Phoning it in at 2 in the morning
And I'm just playing half-hour commercials to fill time
It's not worth it it's
Stupid
The only value in it is Alex Jones getting drunk
Which he's on a tightly
The show
Whenever he's doing his normal show
So in the 40 hour marathon
He still only
To show for 3 hours
Gaston song
In the evening
In our block
To do an Ama
The drunk still show up for part of the debate coverage that Robert Barnes
Waterbar
Thank you God blackmail
This is not normal this is the way he's taken over this network
Please try to kill you
Edible version of Rodger Stone
Insinuated
Themselves
Has he had
Presumptive
Access to Trump
How desperate Alex's to Kalama to some powerful personality that wants
Take him over
HR department
I wanted to look into
Debate stuff but I didn't want to watch the whole thing
Because I know that
He's not going to be there for the entire time that they're doing the debate coverage suffice is just to listen to his show
Now we're going to be going over July 31st
2019 the day after the
First night of the debate
I don't really care about the second night of the debate
Interesting
I don't I don't
I'm not
I'm not over the moon with any of it
But the larger conversation of anybody whose
Maybe me or Alex Jones
Probably going to be surrounding the first night
Cuz you had
Bernie Warren Elizabeth Warren you had everybody
Is going to make things
What are you guys
This is that much on climate change
Technically
You're right
And everybody else
Right but
Forsake
Time
Micros
Let's play map change never be solved by mixing metaphors
But I don't really care about what Alex
To take on the second night
Particularly because
Send me what you going to do about Biden
So I found
To look at the first
Episode
Just going to be going over today
First Brendan thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Next Naja
I'm positive I mispronounce that
Majah
We either way
So very much
Thank you so much and I apologize
Next. Thank you so much you are now
I'm a policy wonk spine
R politics
Megadeth
Yeah
Next
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much Static Shock.
Ump
Thank you so much
You are all now technically
Heroin
Is freakishly large
Thank you so much Kali
Thank you so much
And thank you so much Deepak
Refrigerator
These guys knew that
Does Bertha show
We would appreciate we love it
We're coming off
Debate
Night
Watch
Alex was there for the live coverage
He was only there for party
But the reason is
Because he thought it was
Heroes Reborn
Here today
On the
Bigger theory about this and that Alex realizes that
Conversation
In 4th
You can't really argue
Articulated argument for medicare-for-all like the
He's really good with these
Distractionary things like good with addressing the point of
Yes your taxes will go up but your premium and your copay okay
It's a net
Supposed to
Articulate
Boring
Because he doesn't
He's not good
We're also the one
Who were yelling at Sanders about how it's going to rain
Texas
The Republic
Parties
So I can Avatar there forever
In the form of a
Play the CNN
Complicated position
Establishment
Just alright
Yeah it's not really good for him so
Part of the reason why he ended up just like Lee
His own show in a night before
I'm going home
Broadcast
It was nauseated watching it
20 minutes at a time because I just couldn't watch it
I felt my time would be better served by Ram
Fairlake what I watched all the 26
16 presidential debates on Infowars like I watched their coverage of a
I made a point of doing that
God knows what reason
In our lives
I thought it was all fun and games
But
Really cover what's happening
Didn't have the material he wanted to work with
Barnes
OMG you got this enjoy I'm going home
But
He does have a conclusion
About
Despite not really paying attention to or watching
Any of this other than
Some select clips that people have given
He has a definitive
These candidates
There is no doubt that these individuals
Absolutely
And paint
Positions of power
Sabotaging bring
This nation down
That sounds right
Feel it
Burhan
I have to relive
I don't know
I've even have a tough time trying to unify all of those candidates
People are paid to bring down America
Such
Different philosophy
Backgrounds
Better represent
Backstage
I get them
There is a variety of
Ideology
Less interesting than the idle ideology is the practical way they
Talkin about
Warren
Detailed plans are
Twisting not just because they are very
Progressive
Forward Sanders
Willing to do what Santa's has always been willing to do for 40 years which
Might as well be f****** walk-up
Front of the White House
While he's
In protest himself
Buttigeig who is small-town mayor who's f****** up his own
You should be there
Actually no any
I think you confused he's very sad
Goes like
No you're not even a person of course you got the winner of the night
Which is Alex is Angola on
Marianne Williamson
The new Ager
Because she was the only one that was genuine
That's not what
She was genuinely wrong
She was genuinely
Thanks
Tumi
The headline Maryann William
In wonder
Debate which
Something that I read
Internet
Yeah is the reason that these debates are pointless
Ratings
Right
There's nothing
If if your headline
Zoomer dog
But there's something else going on here that's worth
There were a lot of pinion
The written about how Marianne Williamson won the first night of the second round
Clickbait headlines articles
Discuss how she
Tough question
Things surrounding reparations
In particular
Makes a lot of sense on a people
Enjoyed that everyone
Point that out
Also she use the term dark psycho
Kickforce
Which Google traffic
Fun
The Narrative its realism was the most
Google candidate name
After the debate
Support or a belief in these people that she won the debate
That's just
Proof
People thought that you was interesting and wanted to learn about this year dark psychic Force
What else is talking about
Sweetly unscientific internet polls
We're right-wing Dick's mounted
To drive people to vote for Marianne Williamson
To create the appearance
She's a far more popular candidate
With the hopes of Muddy in the water
The right
Candidate
Create the air of legitimacy as a real Contender is in their best interest
Campaigns on 4chan
Followers to spam The Drudge
Marianne Williamson craziest person up there right now
She's an unhinged Luna
Would be perfect candidate to have no chance
People responded with anybody know of any other polls
Devote besides Drudge
Looney Anne Williamson needs RC
Support do what you're supposed it posted a list of other phone
Another user put it bluntly
Call you guys are rigging The Drudge poll and that's a good thing
From their right-wing sites used as well as other easily rigged
The Blazing Breitbart
To create their new talking points
That Marianne Williamson was the winner of the first night of debate
This is a very
Write a talking point with I hope so
Boosting a could easily defeat
Questioningly picked up that talk and it is disseminate
Give literally zero standards for as long as it suits his interest
Because he is a butthole.
Propaganda
Well now
In 2015
F****** president
Because what else did people say whenever Trump was running in those first f****** debate I think that's the reason why I believe it
Vox Loretta pizza but like
Does makes
Good point
Which
She should have a column
Or maybe she could be a common to a talking head on her show that you know put her on put her on MSNBC
Maybe fits in well with her
Running for president
We have. We are we are
So far gone that this isn't it
But seriously how about we have
People who should be on reality TV shows instead of the
20 win the
That's a scary proposition
Of where we're at right now
Even though everything about her is terrible even though there are a lot of really messed up
Did for the past like that kind of narrative
Really bad
People like Alex
Is Beauty's bad
And from the right all the good stuff is
Is bad
And so that means
Bright Brigade
During the first
Masturbate the first round
Goldie's pools that don't have any kind of
Controls
Multiple voting
These are
They're very easily treatable right and when you have enough people centralized
That are willing to
Keep voting
You're able to read
These things sofa
F****** easily and that's what they're doing
Animedia that is willing to take
Take those b*******
People in
Signal boost them
Sent that almost
Create the reality
Create
Do you think one of the reasons you know nothing else about Matt Drudge
The fact that you would run a pole like that
On his site that has
Huge credibility on the right-wing
Tells you everything you need to know about how little he cares
About influencing
Narrative
Being able to be conduit
For bulshit
Marianne Williamson said during the
The debate that was that
Was hurt
Discussion
The situation
A lot of under-privileged
Communities
That. Have you think so
Wouldn't be happening in a
Large well-to-do city right isn't going to get bad water
And so Alex
Play
Her commentary
Beyblade
Misrepresented
Pretend that she's saying that Trump
Poisoning
Water
Or something
But you'll see how he uses
Keep in mind
But it's also part of
40 hour marathon
Are you doing a Moneyball
You can't trust the government
Still filter your own water yourself and the water you shower in you want to live longer
Indycar.com
Here's that you got it I'm good
Yeah I mean it's perfect
Marianne Williamson talking about the water in Flint is a perfect opportunity for his water filtration
Really
Prefix
Obvious
Foreflight
She's talking about how it's a problem this week
Existed for longer than
Have crippled
If you want to create a straw man out of her arguments
But she's saying the Trump is poisoning the water in
Implied
Yeah you can respond to that has a meaning
Things where you could
Say Trump is the direct
Originator of this awful thing that the government is doing
I better myself
Government has been doing
And Trump has exacerbated it to a level that might as well be in a don't Stratus
Explicitly refuses
Is 2
Help work towards
Worse weather or not
Most of the show
Has been
Point
Using this fake
Marion Williams
Send winning the debate
Present her is like
Whoever ones
YouTube The Last Song
Over and over and over again
Judge knew that I thought Marianne Williamson
This is very useful for him anyway
Because it first of all allows him to
To paint
So much of the people
Democrat as
Forbes
Heather when she doesn't get the nomination like Squad
Narrative over again
I get the feeling that is being set up to
Just feel that sort of a role for Alex
Somewhere maybe it won't be her baby will be Tulsi
Whatever the case is
He's trying to establish some sort of a someone else should have run but the Democrat Party so corrupt
Paradise Pine
I don't give a s*** about
His version of it
There's Nike his own
Victimhood
Is that real content
To it which makes
When he has run out of time
Discover the news
Defeat the enemy
Then you're truly strong
For their own evil
Selfishness
Their selfishness is blind
What the f*** is happening like that would be parody If if it wasn't his actual show like 80s
Rambling about how he's a big strong boy
Spark I don't have time to get to
The top story
You don't have any standard because if you did I would be
Not living up to them
Better Brew
For why you want to be your own
Isaac boss
Because if no one can stop use no one could stop you from doing
Terrible work like this
Just embarrassing
I love it
To do that no no
Fixation do that a little bit later I don't
Episode
Talking about how this is going to be like
Square Times
More importantly
I don't mention this visit
It seems like he's a
Even even in his lies he's already set up at least you had
You know just straight-up
Provide
This is one of them where he explains what do you need
Need the money for
50% off
You had this deal going
Boys have off everything is big kids
Money
So we can run
Infowars operation
Barnes like in the background of the Shadow over his right shoulder
Dracula
Another room but how much money is making off this rube
Calculator
Instagram
Workouts
Oh my God I can't believe this is
I don't know I think we're covered stuff he's talking about it probably like
Pan Kaitlin Bennett
2 gold
Places with a non Infowars microphone
Play or like some sort of a knockoff project Veritas Technologies
But I don't think that's the case
A covert stuff
You look at what Alex
For what is this world
Likely but
Like when Ross Perot hired people
Storm
Veterans
I don't remember that
Ross Perot setup
Save-A-Lot
Covert operation
Into rescue
Prisoners of War
Eddie built the fake version of a prison and then they tried to go in the prison
Don Ross
Doing that
I think he's probably just paying his lawyers
But next time we get to that
If you want to to know what the real story is I recommend you read something
I'm only going to play this clip
Because I think
Straight in Alex trying
To cover like just a normal new story which is
China's making overtures that it might
Coming to
Protesting
Hong Kong
Just that
Story
He still has to get f******
Extremely
Real blunt
Travis is going to get really really really nasty
Fast
Is a ferocious
People
Can you do this again when you don't have a boss
I guess nobody is really paying attention to him anymore otherwise
Usually
Alex murders people
Yeah I mean like that
Crazy
Yeah I'm in between him thinking that South Koreans are Chinese
You got
Express
Exact sentiments
The past being somehow
Bored genetically violent once they get violent
Kamikaze pilots
Racist
But it wasn't as
Is just blanket like
Hey anybody from Asia is
It never going to end
Yeah watch out for Asian blood
Daughter's life is South Korean or whatever
Play music like
This group of people
By there
Predisposition is Viola
Immediately just after that
Is it not
It's almost as if when you see those videos
Stoffer
To kill anybody
Maybe
Oh
Man
He's a bad human
Real bad dude
Almost like
You proud of himself for his number killing abilities
I could kill more people than an Asian who got my career Baptist 6
Clark
If I got into my Prime if I made it
To the show I'd be knocking 20 30 home runs out of the
Hammer
I just think I could I hear these
These things
Do you know his version of what he likes
To brag about
How he likes to
Anthem self up the particular ways
He does
So gross
Childish
Stupid
Do I have a surprise
He is all of those day
He does
You know I mean I don't know exactly what the actual geopolitical ramifications
If China were to
You know
Encroach
Hong Kong
I don't know what the exact consequences
Alex believes it will be a giant War
And he also thinks otherwise
Set a giant War
Could start
Particular
I'm Africa that okay
Or or the other half
Two areas
Wars in the Middle East
Another area that's happening
Are there in Asia
We can make donations
Where you can also purchase products
Computer programmer
Put together
Text messaging Michael
Chevron
Was it like 300,000
Donations
Yeah in last few days
Good
But Maurice were selling this stuff no profit
Keep pushing
Tomorrow we bring a million dollars gross sales
Infowarsstore.com
This is a bummer
This is not a jubilant
Alex
During his money bomb
Number been real in the morning I think you would be
Be pretty excited that is not where he wants to be
In terms of it money bomb
Because he also knows that there's so much Dead Space
During that 240 hours that no money is coming in
Nobody's coming in with Harrison Smith is hosting
Almost nothing is probably coming in with David Knight with all his people who are on
Amount
No one's paying any money for Shroyer's stuff cuz he's
Very little opportunity to actually hit his goal probably
Man it feels like
Jackass
Your
Bragging on air
A lament
Conair about how
You need
Revenue is
You don't
Care about the price
I don't know what I don't I don't
Yeah could be
I don't know I don't know enough about finances
Doesn't know anything
But until just
I don't feel like
What he's manifest
Doing good going great
I don't think
Anything is going great
I mean it's close to schadenfreude but it's not quite cuz I still don't rejoice and
His downfall or anything like that
Mildly amused
But I'm more interested in like
Is actual Subs
The arguments and worldviews
Like I said
I'm more excited when I find Ally than I am in him
Going out of bed
Yeah cousin
I still don't like him going out of business
Still
Affects a lot of people who are
Maybe not
Remained at their status
That's pretty
I feel a little sympathy for his employees would be out of job
Another job
And
Infowars with everybody so
I also have millions of dollars even if they got a business
Will be fine
True
But I would really worry about it there might be
Do this
Be one of the few things that's holding a lot of people back
From being involved
Qanon
So we're here to go out of business
Pores vacuum paranoia somehow
The best next best game in town is
Kind of you know jumping over to Key West
It might be more Danger
I'm not entirely sure
So people actually believe in
From where we're sitting
People pretending to believe
But
You're just a couple of dead bodies
Yeah that's actually very true
So this is not going great
The one
But it's going to
To get the donations coming in
Eating horses would be awesome
He chose
Something else
Strategically plan
How I love the first of all
All the f****** time but
It's so f****** hilarious
Covington kids
Yeah the lawsuit against
Yeah yeah that's right
Because everybody was planning on Robert Barnes
Because
Presented I'm representing the Covington kids
He'll everyone is the rough out I love that Alex's defenses like that was mis case cuz his case
Exist
So he was saying that he he was representing the coming
Key is on some
Blue Ivy
I don't I don't care about the like others of Robert Barnes at scam
I just don't have the mental space
For all of that
I just think it's funny that Alex's defenses
He couldn't have his case thrown out cuz there isn't one
Even realize
I told him
To put together
And they're still not ready
Right
Here's the f****** time
I just
Can't say enough
How
Much that is like my kind of Comedy
Is like
You guys think you're insulting him because
He's case got thrown up imaginary
Looks like not be a worse go bottle
We just bluffing
Refreshing
My firm conviction is Big he left the coverage of the Democrat debate because you realize like
His skill-set doesn't work well in
The setting of the Democrat primary
Baby Alive
He doesn't have a lot of heat
Built up characters in there didn't have it Hillary Clinton
Yell at you doesn't have
Like he could just do a Bernie voice for 45 minutes but that's exhausting on his throat and people would rightfully
Be like later
Moving on
I mean Impressions good but it's not 45 minutes cut like anything
Really on a lot of these people other than superficial complaint
Like you can do the same thing that Trump doesn't talk about Native American with Elizabeth Warren
Beacon
Call them all demons
But like I was I was just thinking that's the only one where everybody on it
Don't talk about you
It's going to come out of your mouth right
I think that really
Limit his ability
I think he's a skillset his diminished
Considerably
He has take
To take
Information about these new
People and insult them
Dismiss them correctly
What happened
But it turns out
That's not what I
I was wrong
It turns out that Alex just can't handle
Looking at Democrats anymore
So I went home
Washing watching you
Thunder shows we do ab watch Tucker Carlson
Watching or listening
I can only take information through white nationalist leading channels
I can only handle my own coverage Trump Tucker and drugs
I have become so insulated that I need a safe space to take in information I can't
Wild west of a CNN debate
How's that is this
Yeah that's hiding behind like somehow it's
Visually the Democrat
Look a certain way that makes me sick
Look
He doesn't like the idea of looking at others
Who disagree with it
A healthy democracy
That's in the Anti-Federalists
Full of s***
Absolutely
And to Mexico if we hear him
Express
Legitimately
You do it
At least white nationalist of Jason
The ideas of demographic anxiety
How Alex response
Is abortion is increasing in
Populations in the West
Oceanside
You're a smart guy
Alex is already said he wants to give Barn to Shoreline
I think bars that goes home in sounds like
Buckhead mr. Burns
Everything is going according to plan
Map of Italian.
That old first I'll get in with Owen Shroyer and I'll impress him and then now it's cool give me a show
Got to have a bunch of
Voodoo dolls
It's pretty wild
Absorb
I don't believe that these things
I think he's just referencing the idea that says 14 days
Did give some grants
You work they like Julian hux
He was doing
I looked around I can't find
He's talking about
Famous book 90
So exactly what you are afraid of
Alex tries to
Comments on mayor
No plays a little clip of
Having some commentary
And yours
With Alex
By recycling the same arguments policies and politician
I've been alive
We got this summer
The courage
Alta commercial
I don't know if I heard any other substantial commentary on
Episode
I've got to
F***
Need somebody with a
Throwing knives are Dart
Throwing them right into his leg
Every time
Where can I get back on
So in this next clip
Alex
He's still a little bent out of shape about Marianne Williamson
Comments about Trump poisoning the water that he believes
She made but you did
Bright and Sophie
But you think they said he would
It is easy
Cliff again
At the tail end of it you start spiraling out about how bad the water is in LA
Summit hygiene
Routine
Why would anybody want to be the victim
Toilet
Where they take the sewage
Tasted LA water
I'm a neat freak
Okay
Shower
What I am
Bottles of
So I guess
Donate to your shoulder
When I take a shower in LA
Place is a joke
Where's the vault
I don't know if he's been other times on Covert missions
There's a larger definition of
I come from
Just watch
To get that
It's the sex workers
Thank you very much
I apologize
To me is about
You dick or I guess
You're at your genitals
With whatever his definition
Right
Can you imagine another show seriously been like in the middle of some sort of
The primary analysis be like in LA
We're still in the show right
This is just become one
Uninterrupted
Out loud it's remarkable that
It's really crazy
It's worth taking seriously is like
He's over hatred of people unlike him
Himself
It should like it deserves to be written off
Yeah
Alex talks about at the dam
Our criminal election fraud
That doesn't sound right
Mercenaries
The people are actually supporting
The pools are all fake
Cited fake poles
That work I completely rigged by trolls
I do not trust his assessment of what is not a real poll
The power the
Conservative
Just kidding
Lying about
Voter
Fraud person
Before they before the Democrats pointed out like you guys have been doing all of this
Depression
For forever the reason that you wanted these election
Is because you
In Michigan electoral college
Should not have gone that way
Cleveland
Call me
It it it is it is
Not the how easily they own
Like if if a Republican
Yeah yeah
Critic of Mitch McConnell voters
Depression
Policy ignoring the election
Election
Security
Coming
From the right and everybody take
Turn on the left
You can look at
Voter gerrymandering and whatever say and you'll have
F****** intercept
Going
Any good on them for it
But that's why the Republicans
Sabor of the unity behind
Whatever is
Next to something that I love
I love
We know that I love and Alex Jones
Story
I love it anytime takes a vacation
And comes back with
Completely not true story
Especially
CS this is the first time I've heard of this particular story
And this has to
To do with
Ostensibly a conversation about
White people virtue signaling that they care about black
You shouldn't
But I also don't know what not to believe
Because this story in a word
Is confusing
Okay it's convoluted
Egyptian king
The Roman
Keep or whatever
We shared a dog
Fishing
16 hour
As She Goes
She does
What happened
I got a birthmark
Flip
The gypsies
Royal people
I love that
Is f******
Make molding with Alex
What the f*** are you talk
What is the point
Are you trying to talk about the Roman 8 because we don't
Fulbright
Who's the Gypsy King
Cuz that's a real person
Digging in your yard looking for Arrowhead
But you let them take it
White woman who accused you hitting your son
Why are you sure that I know who you are and your kid
What is happening what is going on
Yeah because people that lock their windows I would love to
Prefer Robert eclipse or Alex talks about gamblers
As if they are trying to murder him
The sort of person who don't know who you're sitting next to Barn
Alex's f****** story makes no sense
Barnes is killing at 5 but he says
The two of them are doing nothing but Electric
It's the same sort of I but we got on that old episode where Alex and Jerome corsi we're finishing each other's sentences
Because Barnes is bringing that like
Not only that but
He's doing improv work with Alex
Crushing it and it did
It leads them
Just like
They go down
Rabbit holes with each other very annoying
But he also means that Alex also doesn't like
Real Subs
Any of the topics he wants
The cover
And it leads him to be very
That also sounds like parody
Graham Trucking
Start the clip talking about how people don't really care about black people and there's virtue signaling
Absolutely I agree with that
My daughter said took a little star I really want
God dammit
Do you remember when
Citgo on deliver the Nightly News to the world and then be like hold on one second
I got my my little three-year-old son he's going to
Single song real quick
It's so insane just to imagine any of the behaviors that are manifested on the show existing
Anywhere else
Doing it. Feeling like
Terrible at this
Trying to do a show that people should take seriously about political topics in like
I'm presenting myself as the only one in the world who gets it but they're like
Centuries-old conspiracy to destroy the west or whatever
And you do s*** like this
Alright
The only reason that we have done over
300 episodes of our show
Is because Alex is perhaps the most unique step
Show
Sing
Deez Nuts
Success is like a one in ten billion yet
Like this from somebody who just had a
YouTube channel
Show that's like this
Nobody
Yeah it is
It's wild
Incongruity
It makes no sense
We're going to spend the rest of our lives trying to understand
Perhaps
Encapsulation of conversation with
Robert Barnes
He's thrilled with Robert Barnes
His prognosis
Skating ability
Because more people would Google Marianne Williams
Congratulations
She's on the debate again people could be curious about what she says congratulations you're a psychic
You're amazing
He also predicted Like Bernie was going to get a bump in the polls like most people probably could have predicted that
But anyway
Alex
He has
Insight
In terms of politics
Andy Bragg
Tomorrow or something and really get with them and Charlotte Michelle tomorrow okay
Activate
So how you guys actually did this
Fort Campbell
Seriously
Yeah and everything that you say is absolutely.
Storage Wars
It's worth pointing out the gambling on elections is illegal in the United States
Alex literally airfryer
Recognized as one of the greatest
Politics gamblers
He had to go to Europe to bet on the 2016 election because of the legal in the United States
So
I don't know you could work
It's one of those things that I kind
Gambling on Sports I don't really think
As long as you're not involved in the sport
It's generally I think it should be totally legal
Politics
Different
I feel like that's different
And also it's
When
You are somebody
Who is Mal
I guess a host of political show
When your political partisan I think betting on politics
Involved
And you gamble on politics
I think that's so dirty
Coming first of all you're not going
Rap
Even if it were
Legal
Baby shady as hell
Politico
How do you keep your content neutral if you're gambling for certain
Comes in politics
You don't you can't
Do everything
In your power to persuade
Towards
The outcome that pays the highest dividend
Not because
Ural make
You know the person who makes
10 bucks off of a game
When there's a s***
There's going to be a
I just I think it bears
Like really pointing this out
Will not
Talking about Barnes being apolitical
About tradition
Right it's also not good
When Barn says things like he says
Clip that indicate that maybe he doesn't know what Warlock
About a lot of the issue
Skip
What the bloodline
These two dudes are having a first of all I could just take that clip of we have a history of the blood libel and be like yes absolutely
Very accurate Alex operation
Operation has a deep history
Blood libel
Trying to present
And it goes on like the clip goes longer they're very clearly talkin about
Blake I kept blaming Jews for the crucifix
The bloodline about accusations of
Jews taking
Christian children abusing their blood
To make matzo
It's a different thing I'm not understanding and not understanding the historical
Consequences
Of the subject that they're talking about and that they embody
Bands that sound a lot like when we say global
Really really
I was strange that you use the term blood libel.
F*** you
Anyway
Good work
Infowars Isabel I would say is
A white identity operation
Primary function is to
Launder
Ideas
Represent
So it's interesting to hear
Barnes
Say that
It's just a response to think the people who say that
Define respondents
Texas
Rachel phraseology
I pulled my back out
Trying to understand that
Yeah
Right
I mean I guess it's positive Spencer the races
I mean outside of that there's not much worthwhile in that in that cliff
But this is how people
Like Alex
Somebody wants world rationalized
They're dumb political position
Like we are only doing
This because you made us do that you got your left
You know that makes
Me become but identity politics for white
It's a pathetic
Is on what you're doing
What you doing
If you guys
If you
Fallen women
If you would have just
And the loudest
Go to continue run
We wouldn't have to
To be all white
Primacy all the time. That's almost literally
I've never heard heard
Pete buttegeig say you have to do what I say because I'm gay
Shrek
The way to
Delegitimize
Already of his position
Now
I picked up that's Alex
Doing identity politics
I don't understand
He's minimizing
Mayor Pete
I'm only supposed to listen to it because he's gay in his identity
To demean and to delegitimize
A point that he doesn't want to take seriously from somebody politically disagrees with identity politics
Can only come from within and without
Somebody else do you work
Not
All this is identity politics
And then to crying
I have more respect for
If they were a little bit more
Willing to own
Going to be like in doubt this is what I feel
Care about my people
I don't care about any of you dumbasses
I don't think you should be able to vote this is
Our country
I would hate that and I would still be as opposed to it as I am to this
Is there be a moral clarity
On on Alex's party ideas
I don't do this because of their identity politics
I just like the West
Call my b*******
Trick
People who
Vino
Farless exam
Lives into believing that something they
Instinctively know
Is wrong
He's still right
Messages
You can't run the operation
In any
Marketable
Viable way
If you're on
Text about what you're doing
You will be relegated
Do the same
Dustbin
That David
That storm front is in
You will be put in that same box yet if you speak
What you believe
And the way that you wish the world to operate
So you hide behind these terms
In order to
To hide your reality
So you can
Stream of discourse
Edit
Pathetic
Uncontrolled
Very true
So if Alex yells about how he thinks for himself
Yeah that's how he knows
Robert Barnes knows what's going to happen in this debate before they happen
Because we all
Really doesn't sound right
It's not
If you know who's this
Jobs
Independence
What are we doing
Barnes is really
Really
Tongue roll
Supplicating in
In such a way as to manipulate Alex
Control the entire time
A Barnes is back
Call 1000%
We noted this on another episode
Smooth transition program
Like he's one of the most glaring problems analysis
Really forced
Transition into salesmanship
That s*** like
No much closer to like
You can trick people
Better Call Saul
Like he is
Russia
Ambulance chaser
Salesman
Yeah it's kind of scary
Kind of thought that people had
You know
With with
Pretend person who believes and acts
Seems to be a manifestation of like
A slightly better operating hours
Right which is why he'll never be
Bounce off of his show be boring as s***
Smarter Trump
Would never get elected because he would never want to be
Conceivable
Makes Alex's show listenable are watchable to anybody
Is the part that makes him
So same thing with Trump
Getting
So it is next Cliff Barnes
The Infowars is legit
Legitimately
The only Free Press
In the world
Really
The American Democratic experiment
Big swing Barn too big
Transparent
Infowars didn't start
Until like
The 90 so conceivably before that American democracy was impossible
Until 1995 or so and Alex got on air
Start immediately
I think that that
Saying only free press in the world and Free Press is necessary for American democracy
Infowars if it goes so goes democracy
Wow
Perhaps
Alex mentioned that some of his money that he's trying to raise right
Yeah it's for covert operation
Now we still don't really know what those covert operations are even in this next we're not going to find out
Apology records in the FBI
Think it's legal fees
I still think that about
Discusses the covert Ops a little more
Launch operations
Play too much should I
Let's just say
White House
This is all completely
What I think it's legal and lawful and
Occupying your lawyers
Could be true of legal fees
Yep
I don't I don't know what the fuk kind of bulshit he's trying
China pitcher butt
Whataburger
So early in the episode I
I mentioned that I got the real sense
That
Yellow
He's
Disgusting waking up in 700,000 and turns out it's really three
He's not feeling good
And when we get towards the end of the episode
He breaks it down
And it's
It's worse than
Even I thought
Rechargeable
For yourself
First of all no insertive Robert
Knowing your community that already knows who you are.
Drudge Report
Maybe a couple people there
What they don't want you to see
That's why the system is so scary
So what are you saying they're really quick before we get to the rest of the
Is that you need to spread the word about our harsh
Find
That's not true is not true
They get new people and they stay for a little while and then they leave
Which is why he's in such a desperate need for new people
Just why the bad pitch that he's doing here starts
With we need you to get the word
Which is why that's almost as important
Selling his product
You need to advertise
Because without that
I don't have
I don't have new people coming in who I can trick
Without interesting I am for a little while before they get the sense like this is impotent bulshit this is going nowhere
Making up most of the stuff probably
I would rather the
Something else
Do you know that
And that's why
You know you be my advertising
Network is
Super important
It doesn't want to
We're here
We're strong
Hilton will shut down
The problem is I don't order
Which
What
Have you bought products at Walmart or Target
Future
Just code enforcer.com make a straight donation
Ouachita
I I know that we've heard a number of times him talk about the impending doom
Infowars
That's why I don't I don't know how seriously.
Any of that
Like he's embellishing
Like
There's a resign this to it in the last couple
There has been a ramping up in a more frequent
Yeah
Might be feeling
Imminent
I think for independent businesses
While they were in the
The middle of going out of business
That sound
Very familiar
Yeah I don't like I said I've learned my lesson in the past
With
He says
Even if
Even if it's what you want
To believe is true
Sound
Sincere
It could be
That just beating another marketing tactic is using
The idea of very
The troops
And get them to give him the money that he need
I don't know
I would say
But if he is being
Insincere in anyway
This is
Should not be launching operation
Not be trying to pay Kaitlin Bennett
To go do whatever paying all of these reporters
And
Just Folk
He's mission
What he wants
He could do for Sochi
There is no reason why he can't fight the globalist
Exactly the same way he's doing
Get the same information out probably better
Torchy's
Almost
Possibly
He is overextended
Because
He doesn't care about that that's not the message
His delusion
Like it's a big party because
Village Inn
The legitimacy of his operation
Is only ever going to
Compared to
CNN Studios
He'll look at that studio
Listen to work everyday
Look at how small it is and
What am I doing
I'm never going to be
I'm so glad I disabuse myself of any Notions like that pretty early on in podcasting
Like when I was
First starting I just had a 4-track
It was terrible
What time does almond
And I do like I do
See the pictures of professional recording studios in a
That's what I mean
Like if I could get to
To the point where I have that
Everything will be great
And so I spend a ton of money
And I got like microphone arms to hold the mics on and really professional
This isn't satisfying and arms were weird
It just wasn't
Wasn't what I thought it was going to be I realized the clearance
Holding a mic and just recording
If that's all you need
Can't remember which one
Which show that we
Arm
I was like moving back I can't do I can't cuz I do
Around all the time I can't do that kind of like a weird
Experience but like I I don't have any
Conception of my mind is like
If this grows
To the point where we're making Alex Jones money
That somehow I would need to have like a TV wall behind me
Exactly right here but maybe we both have insurance
It's not to me because
We can
Do the show that we're doing
No amount of money would make
The content
Better
Island Casino
That he can't do
What he does
Without
Millions of dollars
Yeah and that is
His vanity
Right
And that is
Deceitful to his audience
Like if they really loved and Auntie globalist message
Janae really love
His analysis of the world and all that s***
Alex Jones podcast out of his garage
Steph
Owns a house
Podcasting equipment that he could get like for $1,000
Would be better than 90% of podcast
Yep
Do that oh wait he's kicked off I2
I got the cat
But even happier doing
Mega millions of dollars
While we while I was working
How how are
Dreams are so like
You got a million dollars
And you didn't have to worry about work
What would you do
You stand up for like a hundred people and not really worried about it
That's my goal
Dream job that I just use all that money
I have no
A big house
Or bladadah
Live the most creatively
Satisfying way I can a greedy stack of goo
It's the most dishonest
Most awful about it
Is the wave
Uses
What I described is understandable emotions
His audience
In order to fuel his own
Because a lot of the audience is probably feeling deprived of something in their own life
Or whether it's real or not
You know those feelings
Stem from
Actual
Problems or from
Steve ones that the
The media wolves
Work up in people's mind
I believe
He's taking those things given them an enemy
And saying he's fighting a
For them
Is it Direct
Way that you can get involved in that fight is either promote for me or give me money
It's deeply abusive
3D don't appreciate it
Are you taking the
Problems
And exploiting them
Give them a
Different
Perceived
If if people
If all the money that everybody
Is that everybody to listen game
To Infowars
Did their hands
And they used it
Figure out what
He was
The issue that is
Infowars
We might have far more well-adjusted
Yeah
Misdirected energy
You can't afford your medical bills
That's because the global
Medical Center
They're all over the hmos and they're all trying to
What train fix the medical system
I got to fix the globalist
Fixing
The globalist by funding Alex's TWRP
Keto of Truth in the Infowars
Will fix the health system
I guess I'll
Give you my money
And wait
For the results to come back
Right
He's stymies peoples
Motivation towards solving their problems
Because
Doing so
Makes him money
And it's shity
It's a real shity thing to do
It's profitable
How was it was when he had it
The inflow of people
The inflow of people is really what screwed him over
Like that disruption of the cycle
Completely devastating to his business
What we're seeing is a ramification
Can do that
You made your bed
Speak now it says daughter
We're not going to play her singing Twinkle Twinkle Little Star
I believe that you
She deserves her privacy
I would say
I don't want to
How do I turn this into a thing where we like
Turn into the judges on American Idol
But
Point out how Alex uses
The
Clip that he recorded of his daughter singing
In order to help with an error
Because I think that's all so pretty
Breakfast
I just looked at
No that's good
Future
The universe
Thought about
Future
He was 10 years old
Before we get to
Point where they
The daughter comes in
You may notice what he's doing
He's using his image of his daughter singing Twinkle Twinkle Little Star
Is an image of Innocence
To juxtaposed with the globalist
Who want to destroy the futures of the children
Blood libel
This is probably
The protocols of the Elders of Zion
Number nine
We have fooled but used in corrupted the Youth of the goyim by principles
False although
Has been inculcated
Or how about this for protocol number 16
We must introduce into their education all those principles brilliantly broken up their order
But when we are in power we shall remove every kind of
Disturbing subject from the course of Education in Jamaica
Loving loving him
Decent quiet
I have corrupted the children
These ideas of corrupting the innocence of the children as an attack setting up a one world government
Are very Central to Alex's worldview
And they trace back directly to the protocols of the Elders of Zion
This is bulshit
Alex
Representation of the globalist
Is all
Or mostly Atlee
Taken directly from archaic
Anti-semitism
Medic ideas
About these Jews were trying to take over the world
When you look at these sorts of things
You see all of these people
In his
Beer also that are
People who have been lunch about it
Young people like the David Jay Smith of the world
The people who have
The people that he looks at as a new world order icons
These people all were very clear that they think it's a Jews who run the world
So when you have Alex doing all this
All these narrative that are so Central to his ideas about the globalist
Adjust mirroring
Protocols
It's just
Lame
Just f****** lame
Also
Quit Alex order another shipment Alex
Retired Forest hook for like
Yeah that's true Barnes doesn't want to take over his sinking ship
He's better at the edge
Yeah
No, go away and then Alex can be free of this this monstrosity
Is created
Spell it as a franchise than you got Barnes Wars
You got Owens Wars
You got Rodger Wars
Tazadaqyah Imagine The Hangover a lot of these people are going to have
Like if
Infowars goes away
I imagine they all have to run
Brazil
Get taken up to the Hague convention
They're going to Boys from Brazil that's all I got interesting image to have in your head
Certainly
The world does go the worst possible Direction
I think there is an argument I think there is an argument to be made for whenever everything clears up
Responsibility
More realistically
If they go out of business
Because
Yeah you can't
What's Owen Shroyer going to
Do
He's unemployed
Pipefitters Union
I'll just go work for one America News Network
Look at a job at Breitbart
Family business
Go become a plumber
St.Louis
I think he would be happier
If it was just a goddamn plum
Will be happier if they weren't career Liars
Obviously the end of this present day episode
Debate analysis
Is then
Where was apart of it
So we learned
Centipede
Because he's gay
Marianne Williamson
Poisoning Detroit and his take on
Bernie and Warren
Absolutely kicking ass positive
You want to bring up after that debate I can't guarantee it but I don't think I even heard him do this Bernie impression
Episode
Yeah you might have that one
Pointers
Rememberable it wasn't it I don't remember it happening
Yeah I think clearer
Sensational topics
Absolutely leader in the clubhouse
He talked about the other people
Fox News
20 candidates on the
Is because
If you have
You know
With ideas
Warning
Sanders
It's going to be
Riveting
Two people slightly disagree with each other
Warren and Sanders trying
To do good and then ate moderate
Throwing bulshit bombs at them
Weather Sienna
Moderators themselves are like
Your ideas are stupid and fanciful
Do you agree what's your comment
Design to make
Warren Sanders look
Ridiculous
I guess like I mean I'm not
Super interested in Alex's
Coverage of the second
Much like Robert
I'm psychic
Absolutely
Alex made a lot of hay out of jail
Speaking Joe Biden
I would rather
Make fun of
I don't need to hear Alex duet
If I'm going to look for Joe Biden criticism
I'm going to go with people
Don't need to go to Alex for that which is just another indication of
I will be back on Monday with another episode but show is stupid
In the present day
Repeat that whenever
Video president of Sodexo sucks
But it is important
10 people
I would say a person have to die within those two minutes or can you just inflicted the damage that kills them
It doesn't count if you die like 2 days later from complications
I think you get partial credit
Six-and-a-half
Here's the issue
What kind of hammer we talkin
No.
Music
You are going to be easily deflected
I think if you could apply at a very doable
Play 30 Seconds To swing is?
Clock
Right
Still harder to kill
What's the question
In 2 minutes
Dot-com
You can you could go to I-10
You could leave a review if you wanted to
You could find your nearest
I stared directly
Intuit once you realize that it is
Back at you
You will receive a
Small comment
Fill out
Reaction to our podcast
We will send you a
You bet
Until next time I would save the imaginary people digging up arrowheads in Alex's lake house
Yard probably haven't killed anybody
I love your work