I have great respect for knowledge by now it's bright I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Just a little bit
About Alex Jones
Indeed we are. Jordan
It's good we got some flowers popping up on the Toronto and Thai chili plant
Not particular that one you're staring at there but this one's got some flowers on it I have some on my
Kitchen windowsill
Those are some flowers but no as of yet
Nicely there's no real updates to make I'm glad you're asking me about the plans a little too often
It was in this apartment
But unless the next guy is late
I'm getting excited to actually probably
I don't know what I'm going to have the time
Because we're in a little bit of a you know a crunch-time right now it's show and stuff
As soon as I have a little bit of x
Everytime I'm going to head back down
Home Depot
When I get a bunch more
But probably known vegetable play
Grow a tree
Little doors
I'm just going to buy a little a little
You see there
Thinking about expand
Hangouts
What it what is pasa
No talk about growing some wild grasses
Possible
Amaranth
Yeah that might be tough but I am going to explore some new thing
That's what
Appliance interested to know when they're done
Dino Network never done
What is that when do you play
Verified
A lot of the time will come in
Will turn red
That way but you know you just a little bit
I know enough about plants
To get by
Exactly
Jordans
To cover March 11th and 12th
The 23rd psalm
A part of the reason for that is they we record on Sundays usually
Earlier in the day to noonish
I'm still
Right now with the situation that we have in front of us
Terrible
Stuff happening
In the world
Elpaso shooting or
The shooting in Dayton
And I know a lot of people want to know what Alex
To take on it is
And so far Monday episode there might be an expectation
Can the people have of like
Oh they're going to cover this
Like we're going to react instead
I think it's wise
Thrustmaster leave
Tunis jerk
And assume what Alex's narrative is going to be although it will leave at the globalist or behind us
In the middle of the day I was hasn't done his Sunday show
Because of our schedules are really a lot of
For us to cover mature for us to try and do that for Monday
Impossible
For us to do that on Wednesday on Wednesday
So that would be that put out
But 16-minute video on his website
On Saturday spending state-sponsored terrorism
It
Waffling
It's very much like allegedly this guy
Using allegedly
Alleged shooter
I listen to that I didn't think there was really enough to
To give anything
Worthwhile
In terms of an owl
Informed yet
And we'll know like I don't know if we'll even really be all that concrete maybe it will be
But Monday Tuesday shows wolf
Definitely where he starts
Especially because when he recorded that Saturday shows before the shooting
We didn't even have that
Add to weave in tonight
Whatever you going to bring
For the table
I just think we can do a much better job
Never do that Wednesday
So I apologize if anybody was hoping we could do it today
Sorry
No no the we can't be held to that
I kind of
Time
Otherwise we just do it
Before we get to today's episode
March 11th and 12th
We
Take a little moment here Jordan say thank you
People who signed up
Northport in the show
So first
Joshua
I'm a policy wonk
Here thank you so much you are now about to walk
Tim thank you so much you and I hope all is well
Thank you so much
Yes thank you to the person
Damn joke name
Signed up on an elevator love
We appreciate it very much soap IRA
Heather
Taxable income
You are all technocrat
I'm a policy wonk
Heroin
Is freakishly large
Thank you. Thank you Heather thank you taxable income
Very much
You are all wonderful second
Thank you very much
Pizza dude
Can do that by going to our website
Dysport to show
We left off in 20
Alex was on a large vacation
He had been gone for over a week
And so we took the opportunity
To delve into
David Jason Christian identity preacher
I have been listening to for years
And so now we jump back to when Alex
Gets back from vacation
March 11th
Studio
Is
Rusty
Music
Okay he's eager for The Fray
Headlines
When I get to work I'll just pour over
Frustration
You know why you got to pause there cuz he was about to say It's A Beautiful Mind
He sits around and reads headlines and makes
Tenuous connections between things
That's what he say
You're pouring over headlines
And not
Anything else
I rid of headlines at hoping
It's a stand-in
So this this characterizes
The beginning of the show
He's a guy
I'm all over the place do I cover I am out of my mind
Here we go we get to what his headline
He is actually really interesting
Sing because
There's
A really good story he could
Tell here
But instead he tells the wrong song
Let me just try to go over the stacks
How's that sound
Images start to figure out what stops
Stop story
The.is on the road
Veterans for food
Such a touching amazing
You really tell that Alex is kind of rough
Be here because
He's back from vacation
And you know his mind is still in Barton
Springs or wherever he went
He's spinning his wheels known as a big pile of paper in front of him
Momentum carrying over from the previous day
Generally speaking what is show has like
You have these narratives that you built yesterday build upon
Or you pivot from
Being in his show but when you come from a queen break
Plus
Breakers
Hit the skids
For any narrative
He was spinning before
His big gigantic investigative report that he was
Do you realize that he's just completely forgotten about it.
Piers Morgan having Michaels
Plus he was gone
He's got to get going from a
Standstill
This is how that looks
FairPoint
I bet he doesn't just take his news is talking points
That is fair
Though it's just covers what
Multiple times
He's just reading headlines from
From drugs
In an instant
It is all too rare almost completely with Alex
It's ridiculous that this homeless man accused
And got a ticket for Scavenging for food in Accra
That is Tara
However when we start
Examine what we think about the situation
Agree with Alex
Is it this is government tyranny on display
Take on it is that when humans are eating out of trash cans
We have a problem ticket for it or not
Alex doesn't have any solutions outside of just saying the churches in
Charity should voluntarily solve
The problem
As if those groups already aren't already making large contributions
Housing and feeding those experiencing homeless
He refuses to accept that there's a better solution
Because the actual solution
It is completely against
Political beliefs
And Houston
Is actually a
In 2011 Houston reached
In terms of the homeless population
Adjectives rules
About sleeping in public
Scavenging for food we're not having the desired effect
Ultimately those rules just criminalized homeless you end up incarcerated
Most people would cost the
The taxpayers more
Giving them tickets I can't pay which can ultimately
Incarceration
Or driving them off to some other city where they could become someone else's
Problem
None of the possible outcomes of that strategy
The offers actual solution
And Houston learned that lesson
In 2010 the Department of Housing and Urban Development at chosen Houston
The priority
Based on its high rate of people living without home
They took the time to analyze the issue
To set up some infrastructure then in 2011 they began imp
And their plans have paid off
Massively
In 2019 the rate of homelessness has dropped
Houston by 54
The federal assistance
And most importantly a coordinated approach
Since 2012 Houston
Has housed approximately
Mike Nichols interim CEO the Coalition of the homeless in Houston
Harris County
Told the Texas Tribune
If you have a homeless person
Put them in
Supportive Housing
And simultaneous
Play give them social behavioral and health support serve
92% of them will be
Bi-stable in that facility
Houston represents a model of people interested in homelessness and housing issues
But learning anything
From a distance
But the federal government should
Do anything
If you're supposedly Auntie home.
Government
And you learned that Federal coordination and eight is been shown to be incredibly effective in a dress
What's the problem
You have to either drop your anti-government position or accept that you really don't have that big of a problem
Not having anywhere to live
I suspect this is the case for Alex
This isn't a story he's covering because
Because he cares about this man
He just sees it as an opportunity to use
Misfortune to attack the government
Which I think is very
Shity
Also the charger
Dropping in Savannah
Houston where made
These Parker helped Usher through repeals of laws that criminalize behaviors like
That we're kind of archaea cold overnight
To begin with
What you have here is a really into
Study that Alex
Not interested in
At all
A very successful strategy
Has been used
To effectively
Help people get back on their feet
Pennywise
So
It does seem like the cruelty is the
Forcing people you know the rich
Starve the poor in
Two doing what they were
The right Behavior
It's just so f****** stupid and
Cool because I don't think that's what's motivating Alex here at all I think he doesn't care about a
Holistic approach
Cruelty in 2013
I think it's based
His desire to demonize
Is government
But that's his priority
Maybe he would be like f*****
Especially Frozen
But it's
It's interesting to see
Did the cruelty doesn't provide nearly a
Is much kind of like
The basic
Human empathy
Come on
Diving in a dumpster for
Food
He's starving and you guys are going to
300 bucks
It's kind of an elementary level of it
And I'm sure he never got back on there and gave
Like a clarification
But like
Yeah it is still coming from a place
Close to where you'd wanted to be
Again
Surface-level on the right side effects
Explain to the people like
You cannot explain to them that it
It's cheaper
To just
How is homeless people
They didn't have to have this like
Well it's unfair because I
Pulled myself up from my
Bootstraps or whatever the
The f*** they want to do
Yeah buddy
It's just
Fuk reggae
Eclipse coming up here from
March 11th
Like the content of it
Does not matter
Don't worry
I don't know how often I am worried about the content
That's fair
These are not these are not consequential stories
But they illustrate
Something about her
His style of
That I've always wanted to kind of
Straight but
Really good
Example clips that are just like of him
Here is Alex
Reading a headline
And then Patrick himself on the back
You covered a story
This is a 20-second clip
New York New York
Adam frasch
Support.com
Basically read a headline
Sort of
Speculated about other things
Alright alright
Just reading from drugs so we're doing we're doing a lightning round of headlines and he's like
We're playing we're playing speed chess
It's pathetic
Empathetic
Like without any like he doesn't read the first
At least the first line of the paragraph
Behind it why is this interesting
Nothing
Alex
Excuse still got it
He's talking about the immortal cell line
The researchers have
Very complicated and I don't want to get in
I believe we talked about it and fast episode is Alex
His take on it is
Very stupid
But
This is another thing I wanted them
Which is
We talked a lot about how Alex
Cannot stop siding
Movies
But what's interesting is he's also often defensive the people think that he gets all of his ideas from movies
Course he is because he does
So this clip is really fascinating because
You starts off
Talk about this Immortal cell line
This Lazarus cell
I know y'all are going to think that I got this from
And then watch where this clip go
Okay
He doesn't
Well Mountaintop
Humidity
I want more
Alex
Set Blade Runner about
Legend ionotropic
I would only be better if it was like
I'm talking about the Omega Man
Also makes me question
You know what did Blade Runner come out 20 years
Before this
Like he's talking about the globals put out white papers 20 years before
What that was mid-eighties right I think so
I don't know
Too hard to say but I just
Crystallize that thought process
Movies
What are the globalist want they want more life and I'm going to cite a different movie he can't get away
I guess to be fair he's not getting it for my omelette
Insanity
So when I come back from vacation
Right
He's been out of Studio but
He got back on Sunday
I listen to that episode and we don't have any clips of it
Because it was generally
Just incredibly boring
To do with him getting into a little bit of a
The fight
The cops it's up by Southwest
So I don't really
I don't want to take too much time on it
Justify
You went up South by Southwest
And he was trying to hand out copies of his Infowars
If you believe his version of the story
The out-of-control cast
You can't have bumper stickers on his car
Which is clear evidence that we live in an out-and-out police station
Except this tyranny
And the police pack down cuz they were afraid of him comes up first
That sounds true
Most likely what actually happened is
Police told him that his car was clearly a commercial vehicle and that that he was promoting
Products and that was prohibited in the area that he was in without a permit
Aveeno different if you was a food vendor parked somewhere without proper permitting
And giving out free sample
His van didn't have to have just have a bumper sticker probably a bun
Maybe even a side.
They're probably in the back of the van
It's not like they could just be walking around carrying
Tons of magazine
I don't see the reality of the version
He's telling
But
He claims that he got into it with these guys were trying to give him a
Tikahtnu got back down
Episode Alex embellishes disturb
Even further
To the point where now he's arguing that his action
Caused a Revolt within the police department
Police revolt
Did the police chief overthrown
Canterbury impromptu / demonstration
Yeah production meetings will help us show the news
Victory over censorship it to urinate
So he's has an employee look it up and it turns out
End up covering the sxsw
Issues people getting threats for it
When they actually find the story
Enforced during sxsw
Oh
Yeah I'd certainly.
This is
The story about a singer-songwriter who is giving out flyers for a
In the area that sell pie Southwest
Like4like doesn't allow people to give out flyers
Okay and we're going to give him a ticket decided not to
The story was covered in the CBS article
That's an exciting story
0 mention of Alexander
In the news
That's kind of a problem
The little I forgot it's a little bit of it
Dick move to be like if I was running a comedy show and somebody came in
And stood outside
Gave out flyers for a
Comedy show across
It is a bit of a dick move run there
Sort of talent relations
You can find about them blacklisting people
Performing in Syracuse
In the city during the festival that aren't approved
You know there's all kinds I don't know if I 100 percent sign off on
Anahi
I think they do
The same thing there's so many bands that
Just do not play in
Chicago unless they're at Lollapalooza
Play do Lollapalooza
For the greater art
It's just that
I am four
Legos magazines else for a soul revolts if they are
Put on Alex's generally that's probably a good thing
So
Alex was on vacation may be right around this time is over to North Korea
Is pretty mad about this
One of the things that I wanted to highlight
Particularly of this episode is this
Years later he's going to be thrilled with Trump saying he loves Kim Johnson
I just think that it's really interesting
To see how much
Alex
So here is Alex talking a little bit about
Towards
Love to get my Roomba.
Power
I'm sorry
Torture and
You should stop
A person who you're going to
Define d'etat.
This is like somebody if you want your graphically fantasizing about killing with your fist
And who you know
Whether or not they soften their presence behaved in such a way in the past that you could not accept them
Is the one who you can have relations with
Yep years later
If you want that I love him
What's Lowe's give John Lu and now it's just a disposition
Different
It's so different
It's crazy
It's insane
If everything
Everything we do it's like with Trump's tweets whenever everybody's like
Trump says this and then you can go back and find
Tweet from
The Obama years wearing
Exactly what he's doing
Is 100%
It's just such
Like let's say a politician that we like
Wins and
20 a year later all of a sudden there like you know what
Fuckingawesome
It's not like we're going to then on the package be like guys Alex
But like
You know advocate for a position that were explicitly again
Ghetto Lovett Elizabeth Warren gets elected and then she's like
He's into this government going to ramp up separating children from their parents at the border there's no way I'm supporting her that's
Don't you know
Alex
Rodman for going over there which good on him
I guess
Put
Do you whatever I have a problem
Looking at
What
Oh my God
I can't handle this
No
Glycocalyx
Has has really embraced that the United States is worse than North Korea right now
The policy of separating children from their families
I'm putting them into a different crime against humanity
Good people at ice and Border Patrol
Videos and they really do have an evil demonic looking
As an assessment of people
Probably less important
Sharing a meme of
Alexandria ocasio-cortez
And there
It's it's
Actually
Shocking
Here it looks like parody
You just couldn't
It would be lazy writing if we if I was going to write a f****** SNL sketch
People would be like f*** off that's so unreal is backstory of a propagandist defending X
Yeah yelling about
In the past is just
These stores examples are are
It's so common
It's literally
It just indicative of how little he cares
So you talked a little bit more here about North Korea missiles over there
Blowing up on the pad
At this point
And Alex believe
I can play
He knows
These are not
Missile problems
Matthew McConaughey is not in
They are being shot down by lasers
Body to you
It is
Cuz this is the same sort of argument I've heard from people
But Alex knows it
He has some
Proof
Which leads to a very
Weird person
Aircraft
Armor
No school
Small particle
Burned
The front
I think your dad was lying
I'm excited for that special on lasers
Special
Dead
He's going to get to those articles
Don't know if I
Story but with
Interesting about it is I don't know who the liar is
How is his dad told him that story needs repeating it
Color to it
Because I could believe his dad when he was in high school was in
To science
Stop
Some sort of a science path
Like low-level experiments with
Not not a f****** rails on laser
Experiment to maybe one of them blew up or something
But the embellishment
Alex
You know if we hurt him
Instantly
Hero Worship in exaggerated his dad's
He's there
Second
Smartest person in the state of Texas the globalist right-hand system
Stories of websites
Experiments that he did when he was younger
Turn this into
He was working on a particle beam and it's burned his eyes
I mean it also would make sense for the father of somebody the person who created and
Alex Jones to be also a pathological liar
Sun is in the cross
In the cross
Cuz he never comes
We have very little insight
To like what he's actually like
For the HR Director to go on
Bonaire
This point I don't think I will
Accent Dental
I think so
I'm not tired Alex's little buddy about the timeline
Retired because of Obamacare
Either way
We got some more about North
Alex has
Couple of bold claim
About North Korea here the first one has to do with
Food
Another world
I don't know if
I believe that
He is saying that the
Country of North Korea is
State shoes actual cannibal
This is very reminiscent of
Sort of old timey
5 use of Colonial Country
Alex
Yeah that's
I think you've used like North Korean
Another
American
Comes over and
Carrots and that's true
Yeah I don't know I don't know how much
I believe that
So you got this
And then
You got
This last clip
Where Alex talks
Kim Jeong Hoon
And
I would say
Enforcing the idea
No matter what happens
We can't
Really rationalize
Coming to any kind of agreement
There's no way for Alex's position in 2013
So Kim Jong is possessed possibly Vice 8
Right
Probably
Absolute
Okay I don't know I don't know about this
Eunos
The North Korean people aren't
Break
Desiring to annihilate North Korea
As opposed to them I think he was mostly talking about
The people in charge he was talking about
Everybody in North Korea
Misinterpret
It's okay
Stupid
I'm about to
Not just Kim Jong-un but also the people
In the police
Resources
So you might of heard
A person that the background there Soto
Chiming in
Michelle
Kind of like that
Answer welcome
Hi Alex how you doing
I'm in this new show for about 2 years
I'm only 14
And
Absolutely loved loved your work
You do excellent job
This is when you get this person off the phone
If you listening for 2 years and loves Alex
A twelve-year-old is not equipped
To deal with
The sort of
Understand what Alex is talking about
Even from just a surface
He's not
Capable
Deciphering Alex's light
It'll probably doesn't have access to the
Like the abilities
Emotional maturity
Required to
Understand is really dangerous
Well we CRV
Honored
Now we see what happens when you
Children
Exposed to this
Kind of right-wing
Papa
And I was at
What else what else have
If a twelve-year-old told me
440 drilled
Steven told me that they liked our show
What I would do.
Yeah and I would tell them
Don't let them listen
Like if you want to listen to the show when you're older
We need listeners
I'll be around in 8 years whenever words appropriate I would prefer to have less listeners
Then the people who are not able to
Understand
Because it's
Such a Negative
Unintentionally
Probably
Maybe
Influence
This kid can't integrate this
Information
It could lead him to making
Decisions litter
Dangerous
Just for us but for others
So his whole call is about how is Utah
To channel is B
Just kind of weird
Metallica
Complains about it
Hellboy
Astoria
Something about
Posted that video of George h.w. Bush saying New World Order and got it with
Copyright claim
Try to moderate
You know you doesn't mean when you have a 40
18 year old calls in who's gung-ho for what
You need to talk them down a little bit
Bring them to irrational Center
Supposed to be like
Yeah you know they are trying to take out the little guys on YouTube
Feed into it
Hey Alex I am filled to the gills with hormones
Control or under
Understand forcing me to make
Decisions that I'm
Certainly going to regret later
As do all human beings
Especially
Teenage boys
So please tell me
Direct
Thank you I will
So we're done with the 11th now we get to the 12th
I think it's clearly indicative of Wyatt twelve-year-olds
Not be listening to this show
One of the founders of
We'll see
Percent
So Professor Griff
May or may not be on the show
I don't want
Ever
For a twelve-year-old
To hear professor
Listen to Public Enemies album by
Don't Listen to Professor Griff
Will get into later
Rear spoiler alert Professor Griff
Okay but that that's
The kind of show that we got here
Professor Griff is going to get none questioning and
Really
Celebrities who were
So marginalize that they're willing to talk to him
Professor Griff is one of the most important people in here
Which is a necessary thing for him to say because he's the person in hip-hop who will talk to Alex
Manager
Now thinking about it in the
The very beginning of the show
Every has that violin
F****** fantasy of beating up
Kim Jeong Hoon
And you think of a twelve-year-old listen
Sing to that sing this is legitimize behavior for an adult
Like it
Awful
Everything awful
The cycle
Masculinity
Never end
So in this
Alex
How is
True
Listen to it
It is. He's just misusing time
Yeah you could easily get that
To get out easily
Available
But
You want to extend
On the show because
You'll see
Sponsored
Skip Network brakes
Go back 45 hours
No
Wheels behind wheel
So this is a really interesting
Sing Clips to me
Coming up from Alex
More and more
2013 Stratus
He knows he's right about every
And he's super f****** frustrated because no one else
I think that he's right about everything
One conclusion a person that situation could reach is that they're not in fact right about everything at their feelings that they are
Alex is unwilling to consider that possibility so he goes the other route
There's just too much news
Struggles of being a radio host
Screaming
He doesn't have the time
Explain it all to people so they can be
Be free
Here's how I know he's full of s***
He's been on here for like 18 years of this
He's had plenty of time to explain the globalist plan in exhaust
Hayden Park literally all the information clear as day
I bet he is right
If you wanted to he can take an entire week of the show and just get into the weeds with it
Like really lay out the names date
Specific citation
That would be 15 hours on air
And if that isn't enough he can go into overdrive
He is literally no one stopping him
A broadcast
Exactly as long as it takes
Coherently
You're missing it Dan
The globalist
Wrinkles
You can never the plan
Timeless
The reason he doesn't do this
Is that he doesn't want to show his cards
His audience knows where he's getting
His ideas from
Some of it's just made up
Some of it's clear misrepresentation.
The things that are real comfortable with his just the protocols of the Elders of Zion
Alex knows damn well that he can just yell about Carol quickly or John P holder and then move on to another topic
Without anyone getting too suspicious
But if you were really to dive in and try to analyze those Tech
His point is argument would crumble in real-time in front of his body
The second reason he doesn't do it is that it would be painfully boring to the audience
Cities cultivator
People you talk to whoever listen
To Alex's show
I don't know if I agree with him
It's fun when you yell
Alex knows that
Keeping audio
Which allows
Continue making ad Revenue
He needs to
2 gallon distract
Jump from topic to topic
He needs to keep a steady supply of white identity fueled outrage coming in the form of misleading and over over Lisa
Simplified headline
If you really buckle down and tried to get into the details he knows damn well that have his audience
Turning the dial
And there go as planned
To buy a new boat
Market pressures dictate that in order to maintain his standard of living
Try to take the time to
Explain the quote unquote
Playbook
But he's convinced himself he understands better than anyone else on Earth
There was a time when that wasn't the case
It is early days on radio you so much for your unbeholden
These advertising
Compressors
Here's what I'm getting
He's had a radio show and a video cam
This whole career
If it any point you wanted to lay out his brufen actually do a focus
Coherent type of
Breakdown of this
He absolutely good at
And Jackie Heather
Endgame was an attempt
I guess he is completely full of s***
And fails to prove any of his
If anything in what he was saying we're true
He could have done this at any point in the
His life it's not like the global is playing is some new
You're bringing up like all there's this new thing but those are all just
Wrinkles those are all good to stretch the base of it is the same
It's always been the same
There's nothing that he's doing now that he couldn't
I'm 10 years ago
In terms of verbally laying all this stuff out
Yeah it does seem that he is
Fully aware that he is
His show is
Purely enter
Entertainment Valley
That he is
Peking
White nationalist
You can't ever say that it's an end
Because that would undercut so very proud
Very clearly aware of it
Probably a little too sensitive about this but clips
Really piss me off
Because I think they show how much of a con man
And he is possibly even more so than is gross like sales
Man clips
Explain why why is show isn't
Pretends it is
By creating fake
Excuses for why he's not doing a better job
He can't fully explain the globos Playbook to you because
He has to plug sponsor
Presumably bikes
He hasn't already fully laid out the globos Playbook because every day comes into work
The last date
18 years
He's had to plug
In reality he hasn't explained his globo's Playbook because he knows that he's making most of it up
The wheels inside wheels and plans
Inside playing these the globalist cramping
Our tenuous connection
But he imagines lurking behind completely unrelated headlines he scammed in an altered state or whatever he was describing
All that stuff is in his head
So he doesn't lay it out
If he did
Be too obvious two people
Bakon stupid evil
Continuum hair like
McHugh's he's clearly scamming
He's aware of it
He said yeah
To give you pause
The depths of evil
Could be so
Yeah like the most
Evil parts
Seems like they could just
Just be like
He doesn't he doesn't
No mental process
I swear he's like oh I can't
I can't lay out my plan because if I do have one
He believes that he can't lay out his plan because
Cuz he doesn't have enough to
Right I do think he believes
Subconsciously creates all these
Impediments in his way interview
Lynbrook soap guy
Again
Limerick
Throw the globalist plan
But
He's like maybe I should extend the show because then I can get into everything
And I'll tell you this
He goes for hours on this
We'll see how that plays out
Every production
Thought he has
24-hour Network
Don't don't do it you're overextending yourself
Bad idea
So we'll see we'll see what happens
What that final hour where are you know
He's already
Get into 12
So Alex
Has
Start sex
A little bit and
This episode
Already took
Look up
The old-timers
We held it
So
About to
Department memorandum 72
277 but it's a long it's been a long time
A little brush up
Entire back catalogue
777 was a document that was drafted by the US state department and released
In September 9th
The official title of the document was freedom from or
The United States program for generally complete disarmament in a peaceful world
It's important to read this document with two consideration
The first is that this is a cold war-era
The point was to provide a possible plan of action
To the UN
The 16th General Assembly
And hope the beginning of fruitful negotiation
With the Soviet Union
Mutually assured destruction
We've mentioned it
Legitimately on the brink
The world ending
In the span of those years
People saw it is the highest priority to avoid that pain
Possible outcome
If we live all of us if we all live in Peace by way of
Complete disarmament
Why the f*** would we do
It's better better outcome and everyone dying for no reason
I remember the guy in the Soviet Union who received
The medal for literally right
Tiger Earth
And then was
Hidden in Siberia and
Story
The f****** suppress
For as long as
Humanly possible
There's nothing dangerous about that I don't I don't I don't
Understand why when your advisor
Situation where you have Brinks
Skip going on
Two nuclear Powers sewer
At odds with each other
Explore every single possibility
To avoid that outcome
It boggles my mind
That happen
They didn't immediately go
Buy one f******
Computer area we almost destroyed the world we need let's start back up
World
The 2nd
Consideration is that when negotiations began
This plan was not what either the us nor the Soviet Union
Wanted
At the 16th General Assembly it went nowhere and wasn't
Adopted
It exists today as a historical test
To a time when International negotiations might start off on a farm or idealistic step
Do today
Zoe
The place and ultimately the meeting was
Play some important groundwork toward later negotiations like the nuclear non-proliferation
Treaty of 90
Important show of goods
Make the world a safer place
I think that
If you look at it through that historical context you
Theaters
Like a
Probably a very important document
Has life too good
But not something
Enforceable in any way or actually
Carried out
Resolutions
Involving the United
We didn't do a goddamn
It was a suggestion
Of course
It's unclear from the text of the memorandum even affect citizens weather
Pens at all
It's really mostly about disarming the US and Soviet Union
Strengthening the UN peacekeeping Force
Ideally avert future large-scale crises
Between countries
And that also does have a nucleus
States
Not pursuing nuclear weapons
This memorandum 7277 is used
Second Amendment dum-dum is proof of
International conspiracies
Get their guns
So they can create a one world government in the form of this UNP
Peacekeeping Force
None of the arguments they make
Be supported by the text of the memorandum
Rely entirely on their interpretations
Which I personally do not true
You got to read between the lines
Trust
Literally any word in those document
Cuz they all mean
The exact opposite
Of what they say they make
Which I
Happened to determine what that mean
Playbook
Let me read between a couple other lines
Alex is playing with John Birch Society and the old-timers were warning about this which is interest
Phrasing
John Birch Society brought it up before this point but the earliest definitive time I can find them talking
About memorandum 7277
Is president
Former Alex Jones guess John McManus brought it up in a John Birch Society Bulletin
Titled whose side are they on dated April 1991
I thought you were going to say
This specific the president not the president
According to John Birch Society lure Robert Welsh
Quotes
Copy of memorandum
Because they works
Publicize it
The plan behind 7277
Always
I find this particular telling of the story to be hard to
Partially because from my reading of John Birch Society materials they're pretty big.
And also their own stories
That's literally
John McManus
Uses the word somehow found a copy
That seems out of their Style
Precision of the
Timeline the McManus presents about this
To be clear I'm absolutely certain that the John Birch Society was at
Agitating about memorandum 7277
I don't have any concrete proof of exact
Italy when it started
I seen some indications that Robert Welsh was aware of 72 7790
But he wasn't the only one
I can find concrete
That another group was organizing
Specifically against memorandum 7
At the same time or earlier
I swear to God if you say the KKK I'm going to be
Furious
It's a group called
The Minuteman
They're almost worse
Yeah
Jesus Christ they're f****** crazy
The Minutemen word extremist
Anti-communist group Ran by A guy by the name of Robert Depew
If you'd been a member of the John Birch Society but decided that they weren't into action the same way he was broke off and started
That didn't stop him from a full trading the John Birch Society with his men
After the fact
This is actually a common strategy explicitly violent of the day
The Congressional Record for 1960
Record for 1963 and crew includes
Introducing into the record of passage from The Crossing
The flag
Quotes followers of mine who has access to our literature should a temperature
Society meetings in their community
Do not be aggressive it did not be offense
Did I do anything to embarrass the birth leadership but always have a pocket full of literature
And materials which
You can hand out to interest
People who might want to make a deeper study into the Communist Menace
And also always
Have a few Blow Pops
Send your pocket
The more extreme groups all the John Birch Society is fertile recruiting
Sense of humor out there enough to join to JBS
You were only a little nudge
Yeah in many ways it's like a fascist
Confuse things like gamergate men's rights activist communities
As recruiting
But drives this strategy is timeless
Yep
It should be noted as of the cross in the flag was a publication put out by Gerald l k Smith
The founder of the America first party
Which of the party that was supposedly just like the relationship
What was crawling with Nazis
And Nazi sympathizer
In 1944 the party advocated for the
Deportation of us Jews
And the sterilization of those who would not
Smith himself was an outright.
After World War
For the pardon
Nazis convicted at Nuremberg
PopularMMOs
Yeah
Popular move you got it
I'm not saying you got to give it up to the Somali pirates
A certain type of
Encouraged
Laabee4
Nazis
Courage
So you ran for president and got less than 2,000 votes in
1944 election
From the America first party you renamed it the Christian nationalist
Crusade under whose name be published across the flag
Which is what was putting the Congressional Record
The Christian nationalist Crusade also published Henry Ford
International Jew
And promoted
Protocols of the Elders of Zion
Absolutely authentic
They hated Jews
Communism immigrants
And Jazz
Presumably because
Is it had to do with black
Okay Smith wasn't.
And he was one of the main figures behind
The early days of Christian identity
Christian nationalist Crusade is also
Associated with
A 1964 news article describes minutemen's founder Robert depuy as quotes
Black-haired Missouri
Which I only mentioned important to realize that the media has always done
Everett Clinic's
Who's coming and probably already here
All around
That's the only thing to do is to organize gorilla group
To fight back
Naturally this just turned into a
Anti-government fanaticism
Terrorism
Because it always does
On January 26th and 19th
The 87 Minutemen members were arrested
Planning to blow up the city hall Police Department in power station
Redmond washing
Arresting officers found firebombs Dynamite blasting caps
Guns and mask
They plan to use in their campaign
Supposedly against communist
It came out in court this is all part of a plan to cause
Distraction and Chaos that could Rob for area
I bring in about $100,000
Robert depuy is charged with
Conspiracy since he was the group's leader
But he went into hiding only to be taught in charge tonight
Because he was the leader of the white terrorist group
Though he only ended up serving about three years
Is 11 years old
Marijuana possession
3 years war white National terrorism
2 years
Prior to that
Broken up
19 members of the Minutemen were arrested in process
Carrying out a terrorist attack on some cat
They supposedly
In the Northeast
The police been tipped off and raided their cell location
Quotes these dumbasses arsenal of mortars grenades
Machine gun semi-automatic rifles at close to a million rounds
These people were not trying to fight communism
They were extreme right-wing terrorist
Rampart's quotes that detector of the group is saying quote
After you take their five phases of training you find out do you want to overthrow the government by force
And violin
About half of the people in the United
What is allegedly started out as a defensive
Fraternal organization to fight off the coming communist
Invasion
Had to turn radical and offenses
Lynette Invasion never came
They had plans to assassinate politician
Chemical weapons attack on the UN building
Rationalize
The government was the
The same as attacking communist
Since the government was already
It's proven by everything that's happened since the New Deal
Put simply the Minutemen were Alex Jones at
Kind of guys
But he does not want people to think they were his
Guys
After their formation in 1961 and quickly became a catch-all organization
Been dead for people all over the extreme-right who wanted the possibility of violence
Their life
As well as playing members
Coordinators for the Minutemen were former Grand dragons
The clan their membership rolls also included an interesting overlap with members of the Church of Jesus Christ
Christian
Which is run by weslee
We swept The Man Who Bore left
Created the
Christian identity movement
One of his ministers wasn't
Man
Not a coincidence
Much like the John Birch Society the Minutemen distributive publication
In this case however it was
You know stuff like a handbook
The Top members how to make incendiary weapons
Vehicular buying
Recipes for Molotov cocktail
The nerve gas
Just sort of the things that the Minutemen were
They also put out a periodical called On Target
Ontarget I'm not entirely sure was the first
It is very early
The publication that was spreading
Conspiracy the number random 72
Wasn't app
Take Americans guns
Amber first 19-6
C3 issue is titled quote new Drive
Disarm America
Symposium
That was held to discuss illicit International arms to
The publication makes a specific point
That the attendees were all members of the Council on Foreign Relations
And I quote
People who spoke during
A four-day conference
Nearly all fit into one of the following categories
One known and identified comedy
Two persons who have belonged to and supported numerous, Communist front
People who have made it a habit to support and be affiliated with various ultra-liberal
Peace and disarmament group
And for individuals who are paid employees of us.
Given how loose we know their definition
Communist is those were descriptions could literally include everyone who's not a minute man
Complain about memorandum 7
How everyone getting their guns taken
No it's going to happen in the next thing you know we got a new world order going under the UN
1/4 five-and-a-half of the
And pages of that newsletter
Is just the names at home addresses of people who attended that arm
Armstreet supposed
Which leads me to another important part
Doxxing is not a new strategy of the extreme right
Important to recognize it when Alex Jones says
Things like the old-timer
This is probably who he's talking about
Probably talking about the Minutemen
A dozen tainos
Not to bring up there by name
Also back to memorandum 72
That Plan was introduced by JFK
How is it possible for Alex to argue that JFK was both the president who introduced
The globalist disarmament plan for Global government and also the guy who killed by the globalist
For being the last real president
Things like this to really highlight how ink
Alex's conspiracy
These are even
To each other
Yeah but that's never been
The point is always
It's always been
Whip people into a
Fear-based 8 so they'll join us by saying
This is coming
And then whenever it doesn't come because
It's Fantastical it's already here
That's that
So what
The entire point is
Insane
Yep and it does go to the like using
John Birch Society
As a recruitment place for more extreme groups
Like if you're in for whatever Alex
Cuz selling it really doesn't
Matter if it's
You know like you're already in the place where you are
Self-selected
Bulshit
So why
Care about this thing
Making sense
Both
Heroes killed by the globalist
For being into America and to the one who introduced
The UN plan
Disarm the entire world
Doesn't matter
I just think this is
Sing because
Things that I
Want to
Pay closer attention
And really highlight more
Is this
Prince's wear
Alex has Direct
Overlap
With these
More terrorists
Pick sides
Of the
World
In the sixties
Because there is
Very
Very strong overlap
Society is kind of
Given like
Review Loki Oliver
What's fascist
Cosmetic and was one of the founding member
Where's the John Birch Society
Like there are connection
So
At this point episode Alex
He's failing time
Professor Griff is coming
Probably malicious s*** I got to wait until Professor Griff
Signal to the militia is I've complained show
Not long enough so I can't get into the global
Not allowed
Professor Griff on the other side
.
So Alex introduces
Alterra
First things first Public Enemy was formed in 1980s
Successful group
With the 1987 release
Which is well received critical
In between the release of that album and their second album
Professor Griff interview the UK
4 days
Also quote Jews are responsible for most of the wickedness in the world
Which many people suspect
Gordon Henry Ford
He's medical application the international Jew
Took up arms when Israel and killed all the Jews it would be alright
Professor Griff unbridled bigotry got him kicked out of the group right is their way was
In the aftermath Griffith played the role of pretending to apologize we could be Public Enemy
What is Minister of Truth again
As recently as 2018 he's made public comments about Ashkenazi Jews as being in
Musically evil
And that it's just common knowledge now books about
I'm not sure if I believe you would ever sorry for any of the awful ship
Absolutely
I don't believe
Incidentally and that interview reference term 2018
The book
Common knowledge
No I don't have the time
Quote this book lifts the lid on the conspiracies
Details of how the public has been duped
It includes the complete Protocols of the Learned Elders of Zion which is
Which is a big scoop as the Jews do not want the general public to know their plans for world domination
Can we get a copyright takedown of is is
I don't know if anyone owns the copyright
Ford
Ford Probe
I looked into it a little more and what do you know what are the arguments put forth in that book is
The people alive today who call themselves
Crazy to hear Professor Griff a
Promoting
Spread by people like Pastor David jsnip
At the heart of the Christian identity
Weird
Putting up to their first album 1987 does Public Enemy in the earlier part
Hip hop history
But there are a lot of people came before them by Grandmaster Flash
Kurtis Blow
Run-dmc's first album came out 3 years before public and
Stressed out
Second wave of the evolution when the old school Aesthetics branched off into town
Subjonctif
When it takes
That was the
Cement Batman
History level about
Professor Griff
Before it was that for you
You didn't come to the surface until a couple years ago interview actually
We came out
And you got in trouble and then
Groupon
Chucky brought him back Munoz
Newsradio
Sure
Alex
The
Rock and Roll Hall of Fame
Man
So that's born in 90
1874 it would literally be impossible for him to have been falling assessor grits
Since he was 11
Considering Public Enemy didn't form until 19 a
I have a hard time believing that Alex has an eleven-year-old a super intuitive
You're a member of the nation
Islam halfway across the world
But I guess you can try to make that argument if you want
I don't know literally been following for
Also I don't think the early public
Their first album
Deeply black nationalist
Exclaims to believe in
He is super again
They explicitly endorse Farrakhan other 1987
I'm single Bring the Noise
So I don't know how Alex go pretend to know what they're about
Also it's wild
Griffith Park
The group when they got ducted
The Rock and Roll Hall of Fame
Considering he was kicked out the almost legitimately ruined all of their careers
Really interesting
The Newsradio episode in this
Because literally what goes on
Phil Hartman's character
Grails about the
I love hip hop
Alex
Exactly that is real deal
So I don't know this interview
It's mostly forgettable
There's a point when pressed
Text message and Alex tries
Presented as someone hacking
His phone and listening
It's it's Ludacris
Yeah
I think one the best
Another get into like mine
In control and music
Cific that I decided I wanted
America
You gave me a specific I'll look into that
Interview I should tell you is just Alex and Professor Griff
It's just that the powers-that-be
Feminize the black man
Through Hip Hop
His evidence
Seems to be his belief that Will Smith
Quincy Jones are gay
Would you something but is very careful not to explicitly
Which is a strategy
Chris has been forced to get pretty good at
Alex Theatre
Is a kindred spirit
The rest of it is just generalized mine
Controlling Illuminati conspiracy
Music
Interesting Lee Bruce argument about these are less rooted in his personal experience than they are in
Him hearing Alex Jones
David Icke yell about
The topic
To make his experiences mirror there near
From listening to him speak it's really hard for me to not think that this is Joe
Just basically Alex interviewing at marginal celebrity
But how they used his narrative
In their own life
One specific ripto's offer isn't clip is a book called Mind Control the United States written by Steven Jacobs
This book
And Jacobs
All of them
The argument that the problem with people
Bluetooth
True
How can we possibly navigate to world around us if everywhere return working
Confronted
That are not true being passed off as truth
I agree with you but I'm almost positive you're the one who's
Navigate to
Maybe I should check this book out
Let me start by putting this very place
Steven Jacobson is a Luna
Here's how he argues against evolution
We're already there
Man is a blend of indigenous eight forms of the celestial beings who arrived upon the planet
The primate organic body because of the greater dexterity
Baby hand song
They cohabitate was the first true man
The inheritance of animal traits spiritual being
Beastly and their temperament and behavior
Okay so if I understand correctly
Humans didn't evolve
But eight
Matt Venom and the Symbiotes
Came together and now where some of us are
Yeah
This is full of appeals to occult knowledge
Psychic abilities
Anti-communist
Quote
I received a copy of Gary Allan's none dare call it can
Conspiracy
I began to study the theory of History
He cites none dare call it conspiracy
Cleon skousen
I had the politics of the same old antique communist conspiracy bulge
The source of all of these people's worldviews
With just a little bit of fun new age horseshit added on top
I'm listen to this Professor Griff interview in already
Helium tank
Full of
Bulshit book
Any sight of them is authoritative sources
Assume that he's not a guy with a very rigorous fact-checking or critical analysis 14 and play
But it goes through before he decides to believe so
Also small point
He's been over
Anti-semite
For decades
Controlled the New World Order the Illuminati
You have to be
Complete idiot
Cannot use available context clues
There's a very high likelihood that he believes the New World Order is run by Jews
It might be a productive question for Alex to
But I suspect he's worried with the ants
He doesn't
If I hate them it's so weird I don't know how to deal with how rich hay Tire
Experiencing right
How do you
Even between
Professor Griff
The bookie
Keysight
Ends up citing none dare call it conspiracy
Skousen a ton
And also
Evolutionism
True because
Professor Griff
Define
Of course
It's very boring real deal
Call Alex
Movies on
To another guy
He's got another guy
So Alex is next guest is a lawyer who works for young
He's so insane because I'm listening to this episode and Alex says it is next guest as youngevity lawyer
Close to shock
Suppressors legal experts
I wish it was
It's not
What are more interested in here though is that Alex
Play there at the end if you get one person
Jordan
Wild
New England Journal of Medicine
Listen at least 23,000 people get sent to the emergency room every year for reasons that are directly traced back
To take an unregulated dietary
I'm glad that
Team that statistic our government has
Decided you know what it's time to regulate.
The author of the study I was a doctor at the
He was quick to point out that
Underestimate
Exaggeration
The problem
What are the main problems is that because of the dietary supplements Health in it
Education Act of 1994
From reviewing supplement
Before they're sold
They can only intervene sometimes on the supplement is shown
Dangerous
This also doesn't
This applies also to
Supplements themselves
But also to
That's
Study found that a significant number of the injuries from supplements
Children who can easily access the pills because they weren't required to be in childbirth package
2017 Business Insider article reports that the supplement industry Z37 billion-dollar Market
Would you look at that in that context it starts
That's why almost
It's almost entirely on regular
Evergreen business
These people have a whole lot to lose if
The government starts
Take the issue seriously
The big companies in
Thirty-seven billion dollar in
I just realized very well-positioned to hire all the attorneys in lobbyist
They need to make sure their business
Nastase unregulated they can
Continue to face clean
Defraud naive
And that's why we need
Keep money in
In politics
Support
Decision in the head
History of the world
There's so many problems people taking supple
If you work some of them can't hurt or kill you ain't
When people take supplements they often don't tell dr.
About them when they're asked if they're on any medication
Some people don't consider them
Medication
Unfortunate
Medications interfere with real medicine
Board for example of antibiotics
Birth control and Other Drugs
If doctors don't know you're taking it
They can prescribe you something for an infection and you'll be
Sweetly get a notary
When the antibiotics don't work people are then likely to take it as traditional
It become more drawn to supplement
As if it's actual medical care
There were plenty of deaths types of them
Using plenty more where supplements played a part in the death and it wasn't caught by doctor
Is disgrace
And the only reason he would be doing that either because he doesn't know what he's talking
Or because he's a bottom page jail for assault
I would give them both
That's possible
His own
I'm guessing that now he's kind of disabused
Himself of the notion that supplements
Can't f****** you
Exactly
Probably not over over doing the youngevity supplement
He be convinced by their propaganda two of these are actually good for you and blah blah blah
Oceans and boys living in the space words
Yeah
So anyway
But it's not just
More
Like
This morning
So I wanted to get
BMO rd.com
It is a Genesis Network
Glidden is also one of these
Spokespeople for youngevity that we talked about the pat
We have the lawyer on with the doctor
From youngevity
It's called synergy
This lawyer that Alex is interviewing here on the show's guy by the name of Jonathan
Inform everything I can tell he's basically just made a career out taking on cases that speak to Cripple government regulation of non-medical met
His claim to fame is that he's beaten the FDA in court more than anybody else
That's probably
In 2010 he won a suit against the FDA that allowed supplement companies
To make quote
Qualified Health claims about their products
They can say that their product
Might help with a certain
Air condition or reduce the risk of it
But they also have to include a disclaimer that is
Scientific evidence concerning display
Based on its review the FDA does not agree
Since most people jump
Disclaimers
I might as well have just been in
That has made a career
Helping people get murdered by unregulated Mark
He's been involved in a number of other similar laws
Because of it has become something of a hero
Format world
His litigation is genuinely allowed
But I'm all sorts of wiggle room
Townspeople totally legal
In most of his lawsuit keyboard is representing an organization called The Alliance for Natural Health USA
Cases used Peterson
Sandie Shaw as their defense
Pearson and Shaw supplement designers who make their money by license
Thunder product companies
Who sell them
Federal Trade Commission wants to enforce a rule like you can't make Health claims about your product unless you have two clinical trials.
Eboards law office will petition to Ft
FTC requirements have a chilling effect
Pearson and Shaw
Recorded their licensees not
Communicate to the public on labels and labeling
Advertising
Claim
Association
Between the products they sell
Relief of temporary irregularity 40ft
DC within the claim
Deceptive advertising
I'm using quote
Because I was reading from his 2011 petition
Into the ft's
By Framing the argument
Visalia
Free speech
Speak to the customer
By doing it that way
The supplement industry that's a win-win
Situation
You can agree with their petition and allow them
Difficulty unsupported claims
Or the FDIC could disagree
And then they can go around yelling about the ftcu suppressing their fur
Watchlist
Lasorda framing
Is one of the main Hallmarks of
Questionable organization
Quote nothing more than a ploy to 4
Persuade legislators to
The permit the marketing
Aquatic methods without legal
Another Hallmark of the use of question
Travel organization
Is it the organization opposes proven health
Measures
Like Florida
According to source
Watch The Alliance for Natural Health USA was a founding member of the fluoride action
For third strike let's just go ahead and say the Jonathan anymore it is a member of the youngevity
Which is something
Deserve to be on the youngevity Hall of Fame please do not put me on
The posterity list
Unfortunately I can't find a list of people in the Hall of Fame
Pictures of
They don't want to
Have a list out there
Recalls whenever the FDA
He's also a lawyer for youngevity but the only cases I could find of him representing them
A supplement related
It stopped there for like business
Thoughts up
I don't know
Please Don't Lie by omission
What if we just lied a bunch
But like a little bit differently than those
It's most
Is mostly Alex jumping back and forth from
Anymore
Tennessee
Who cares and you should probably buy gold
All that
Folks here
Kind of makes
Things a little too overt about what he wants
Quite frankly Alex
I couldn't be happier
If the medical system collapses because we
I mean
Is going to hell in a handbasket
Is because we've taken the wrong.
What do you think there
Is we
Western medicine
This medical system that we have
To his
Supplements and Weirdos
What we should be doing to taking ginkgo biloba
Goddamn
And I we don't need to deregulate we don't need to overhaul
We need to destroy the medical establishment
I think if you lead with that people are not going to get on board
Usually that's a bad idea
It's probably a bad opening
Vale especially when you're trying
I mean what you're doing is
It involves so many aspects of his like Health policy
So many people
It's it's
Almost shocking to imagine
Number
He actually legally can't call him
Doctor
He's a naturopath
I thought he was an actual doctor
If he's a naturopath
We got trouble for calling
A doctor
I don't want to sit around and just listen
Listen to these people talk about their
Propaganda
Industry
I just want to highlight that this is all just too young
That's what it all comes down
He says we're going
Andover Drive
With doctor
The whole fourth hour
Is all an adverb
Earlier complaining about how he doesn't have the time to get the globalist Playbook
Exactly what was going to happen
Play I do wonder I do wonder if there's craft like that gets it's hard for me to say
3 hours ago and like doing other hour
It's it's
I mean there's coordination that needs
To be involved in Oakland
Schedule
Dick
Bulshit
Could have at least dip your toe into it just read the protocols that yeah
12th Street
In 2013
Definitely
Interesting
Meet me here but Alex's
He is so far adrift
I don't even know what's going on anymore
And the past
We're talking about racing that we're in a low before
Call Nora
I think
Some people speculated about this
Text mother people have this wild that
It becomes deeply entwined with the Boston bombing
So we're in this March
Stretch right
But it does offer at these great in
Alex's
Former position on Kim Jong-kook
Nodo Alex interviewing
Professor Griff like he is one of the most important celebrities in the world
I would rather you Old-Timers There's an opportunity to learn about Allah
Stop along the way
That's a good use of our
Italian Bible
Absolutely
Everywhere
It is all over the place
And there are
Stepping parallels
Between the present
And 2013
That are
I mean it
Every time
The present we're just going back through assert
Dayton
And there's a one-to-one comparison
Well I mean
Some of that is
Because
The same things that are true but
Between
Neit communist
Extremist
In the early to mid 60s
Victor similarities are there and they haven't changed
To the present day
Of course just because a lot of these people using things like
Cultural Marxism replacement fears
A lot of it is using the same operating
Right-wing extremist
Have
Baby communism
And
The world that the people who were primarily motivated by
That paradigm
Exist throughout a ton of
Extremism
Change
Shocking because
It's also not that surprising because
What is a piece of
The continuum
Is right wing
Terrorism
Stochastic Lorax
And I think
You just have to deal with that
Why would they stop doing
Exact same
Propaganda
Text if they are
Continuing to work
Yeah course there are parallels
Between
I mean the beginning of the protocols of the Elders of Zion
So well that they
Rolling with it
And we still haven't figured out a fix for it
For this b*******
It stopped
I think if we don't figure it out
There will be
It is
Something that
It will continue to be a problem
Until
We figure it out. There's a lot we need to figure out
What is behind all of this
That's been going on
The present episode
Ray of sunshine
Is it because every question that I was thinking of
Fair enough
Natural reaction
To have right now
Island
I hope everyone is
All right be well
Website
It's knowledge freight.com
We are weary if you want to download the
Go to I-10
You could also leave a review there you could if you have a
Maple tree
Anywhere near you and growing in my apartment absolutely
This app
Contains a
Full
So that's that's
Where you can get our app
Where's my next turn
Steven Jacobs appears that erode very dumb book
Seems like he spent most of his time writing
A dumb book a dumb book
Who technically probably has
Is Alex gay
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work