I have great respect for knowledge but I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
MoneyGram
College vype.com
What is your
Tweet tweet
Completely like
Do not give a fux
Situation
While back
Peterson
Great comedian wrote one time way back
Years back
Is there a Fuddruckers is run by the bilderbergers
Bilderbergers
Remember is Murphy Lee
From St lunatics
We're going to st. Louis
To do a show
And we're driving on the way
Absolutely
We were heading to
Let's see if any st. Louis celebrities will come to the show
Of course we ended up getting into the other sink
And it was great
He was dropping
Remember was
Don't nobody love these hoes
But Everybody Loves Raymond
What is that mean I don't know
There's a show where I know a couple of tweets
And I
Good
Jordan today we were doing is we're in the present we going over the span of August 4th and 5th
29th and be covering Alex Jones is immediate coverage
Of the
Shootings in El Paso
So it won't be as awful as that sounds like it's going
Cuz I don't
I guess what I'm trying to
Spring out here is
Like I think that if you're particularly sensitive
These topics
Proceed with caution
I don't know if
As horrible as you're going to imagine
The concept
Recover will be
I don't know I could be entirely often terms
People
Experience
Think so anyway fair warning
I guess it is
That's a headline
Get into that it's interesting to
How narratives
The built
Crisis mode
And in real time
And I'm excited to go over all of that but first
Michelle so first Justin
What you are now
Helen
Ewok
Not Alex's source
Nora's
Neither
Although
This guy probably at some other great
Whataburger
Claudia The Nomad
Thank you so much right now policy walk
First of all
You so much
Mcf
Apology
Because I mispronounced their name before
First time I saw it was
Exactly
Grove
And then finally I'm just here for the Alex Jones law doleful movies
Thank you so much you're all wonderful take
Business heroin
Freakishly large
Grove
Zlatan full movie
Take all of you very very much
Appreciate it
Jordan
Interesting
I've been really
I was struck with a really into
Christina thought while I was going through a lot of
And one of the things that I wanted
Almost
Idea or thought
The Haven our minds is
As we go through this
Question
It's been taken over by
Conspiracy theorist
Then people who
Often times people down bad roads
Well
You know what is
What if
And that leads you down the road
Considering
Possibly
You know
Wise sources
He leads you down a bad Road
I want it I want it
Hold on to that idea of what if
Particularly in terms of hours
What's Jones
What if
He's wrong
You know like for himself
What is that mean he's doing
You know if we're wrong
What does that mean
That means
Well first of all Alex
Needs to show me you needs to prove any of this point
I'm willing to be wrong real world consequence does it have if we're wrong
Aaron's
Start caring about other people
And become a
Right or correct
Maybe we would be negligent
We're going to be able to do anything about that or anybody listening
So there's that
What is Alex
Is wrong
He is
I wasn't Charis
I want to hold on to that question as we go along
And just let it ruminate
Things only 2.0
Before we get started
Is that I've been noticing in the present day that Alex Jones
A f****** cat
Catchphrase
But he's working on
Did I do that
Evict Tony delivers it is kind of the same mystery
Supercut of him saying his catchphrase
From these two days up
She at work
How it works that works
So he
Condescendingly Africa
Oh my God all the time
Yeah so I'm going to keep track of them
Running
Track of the see how that works
So we can see how it works
So we start on the 4th was Sunday
You were courts in the evening time
So by that point
He has every reason to
To be aware of both shoe
He does not seem to be aware aware of
The care all that much about the date
On the 4th
Almost the entire thing
Is about a female Paso
I don't know why that's the case
I'm not entirely sure if you
Probably unwise
Speculate
But just so everyone's wherever almost everything you talk about
For this first
August 4th
He's about
I told he starts
Ready
Need to get into
Speculative
I'm going to create a can
Conspiracy mode
He needs to justify that
He needs to justify Behavior
People rightfully call him out all the time
About how what he does really f***** up
Until he does that buy a peeling
History
Starbucks
Iran air
Check 500,000 children as a good price
Toupee
Cutting off their medicine
Bill Clinton did George Herbert Walker
They would never wind up a leftist to carry out of
So
We already have the insinuation
The shooter in El Paso was the last
Which will develop is
Time goes on
Why shouldn't we question
Something
Madeleine Albright
The killed a bunch of kids were a good like a good price
Start the show has me really worried
Relying on an argument it's flimsy is Madeleine Albright said something really sucked up 23 years ago so obviously
False flag shooting
Like he's got much to go on
Is that the opening volley
Yeah well it is unimpeachable logic
Madeleine Albright
Express
That's a horrible thing
Shouldn't have said that
And it's also Madeleine Albright's position
Alex always plays that clip of her little tiny clip from the 60 Minutes interview
And guilt better comments leichter
She said in her book Madam Secretary quote
Little effort was made to explain saddam's culpability his misuse of Rocky resources
Or the fact that we were not in bargaining medicine or food
I was exasperated that our TV was showing what amounted to a rack
P propaganda
I must have been crazy I should have answered the question by reframing it and pointing out the inherent flaws in the premise behind it
Saddam Hussein could have prevented any child from suffering
I said the following
I think it's a very hard choice but the price we think
The prices worth it
As soon as I'd spoken I wish for the power to freeze time and take back my words
I replied but a terrible mistake
Hasty clumsy and wrong
Nothing matters more than the lives of Ennis
I've fallen into a trap and said something that I simply did not me
This is nobody's fault but my own
It's interesting to me
Me because take whatever you like Peter bad out of here
It's really hard for me the most apologize for incorrect
Statements
Made by politician
Can think of
Always been very clear that you didn't make
Disappointed
That she wishes she could take it back
You find so many times you criticized
Yourself like from her own book
Amy Goodman bum-rushed at the 2004 Democratic National Convention
She been very clear about
It just kind of wild to be that Alex takes
This is proof of exactly what he wants
Be proof up by depriving it of
And any of Albright's later statement or she tries to clarify what
It means what Alex
Send it meme
Because this show is about constructing a narrative
Also it's hilarious to be that I would spend so much time discussing a horrible Madeleine Albright's comments
Powerbox
What are supporting Trump sanctions on Venezuela
A legit talking about a block hate to push for regime change their
Would you be devastated
Play screen active War but
Because globalist
Yeah I'm pretty sure blockades only ever
It's it it's a real aggressive act
I mean
Right on I don't know what
You could say right
Why would
Why would you and then think that you get any mileage out of playing a clip of Madeleine Albright Mystic months
It's important that
Justify
Ahead of time what
He knows he's about to
To do
So if I'm going to get into Rec speculation about the
That have happened then I'm going to
Need to be like well do this stuff
So that's what he's doing
It is interesting to me that
Think of any
Star Wars movie where Alex
Isn't probably on the bad guy
He's already on
That's why I always play The Imperial March
So we've already got a horribly out of context
Clip of Madeleine Albright
Vacation
His narrative
It's really funny to me that this is what he say
You want us to break down
Current climate
Current system brand
You found the right
That's what you
Really
Exactly what's going on
In El Paso
But I
Dunno
That the media is using the crisis try to cause a race war in this country
Corporate media
Has been
Pushing
Massive massive massive
Cultural
Division
There's been a
Mulan
Flash
For that
Non-Stop
Continually
So it's interesting to me that he says that I don't know what's going on
I do know that
Yeah it's it's amazing
That we do this
Because that means that you can
Continued list
Point where is if it were me or a right
It'd be like
The meaning of trying to start a race war
Clips
And everybody
Fordham law
Crypto globalist
Clemente's
Jordan
That's dumb
Sarcastic
If you hear me sarcastic during Alex
Beto O'Rourke motorist album
They're totally capitalizing on Atlanta president
When you can clearly blame the Democrats if you believe the official story
About what's happened here
B foaming all of this up and making it about race war
Trump's comment about race
Color where you from
Beholder
Always sing
That is involved
But you're
Hundred thousand dead children
Trumpsta Blaine
She went on to blame their all the blame
Are all the blame
How illustrating is that
I'm really shocked you didn't and we'll see how that works
I cannot believe that it's pretty close
What he feels is justifying
Lake
He knows what he's doing
Part of me that doesn't
Like no
I guess I can't be a hundred percent certain
I've learned from studying Alex Jones make me
Very confident
He enters the studio
Producing manipulative
Narrative
About real-world events
He knows that's what he
He's doing and in order
I feel like
This is just
Dubai to make it look like that's not what he's doing
Madeleine Albright singing this
They don't care about human life because of this
Now I'm cool
I don't know if I'm
Become more mature fur I'm just old
Fire and
Hatred
In my head
Instead of screaming them
Because
Once he started talk
I swear to God
Use your the a level of neighbors that you would have to yell back at me
You've got a tough day ahead
Is it going to be
I'm listening to this and I'm gone doesn't sound like
He woke up and was super stoked
To go on
Joann
Justify
Terrorism
Word like
Good morning filled with like
Tell people a white nationalist terrorism
Not a prob
It was it's just
Disgusting
Him
Maybe he's just a little
Recorded
16 minute of media
Report
On Saturday
It already like
Worked on his day off was a little excited
Halfway expected him to pop champagne just like a
16 election
F****** laugh
Well we'll see where it goes
There's a there's another thing that he needs
To do it like
Just believe
Cloister
Himself
Blanket
About his behavior
It's clear like
Paint the globalist
He's blaming
For all of this
Heartless not caring about human life
Totally demonic
Phone do that with the Madeleine Albright
Then you have to defend
Against the idea that
This person who committed the actual crime
Could have been
Motivated by
From your conversation
And you can do that by also sort of blame
You know why I question
Mass shootings real mass shootings happen
Shooting
Superstars
In the old days it was before
Is in criminology manuals it to give it stop psychology
This is well-known information
Place within a few days
Operate
Hundreds of movies and thousands of TV reports every year and just newspaper articles
About
Suicide by cop just just
So what he's talking about is a real thing
Kind of clothes
Describing a real
Found where media coverage of notable suicides people to emulate the circumstances
No suicide
This is called the worth of
Named after a character in gurthaz book
The Sorrows of young Werther
In the book where there is rejected in love intuitive
After the book's release there were reports of young man emulating worth her
How much of that reporting is
Sensationalized
Itself
Connecting disconnected cases
The book it was the late 1700s after all
It's hard to say with certain
See how much of that
Accurate whatever the case of phenomenon was named in history has shown that
To be a bit of a connection between high-profile suicides and rise
Suicide rate
This is scene after Robin Williams took his life
Research was almost 10% increase in suicide
Over what their model would have predicted
This is something that's really almost
Is it possible to prove a causal link
There's no way that demonstrating interesting patterns
It seemed to indicate that
Suicide numbers go up after them
There's no way
Definitively say that's what's
Causing it
There's a ton of other variable that could be influencing that pattern they're impossible to
Control4 in any ethical experiment
Alex wants to take the position
The coverage of a suicide does trigger copycats
I'm not going to fight him too much on it
It's worth pointing out however that studies
Determine if this effect apply to fictionalize portray
Inconclusive
Ungrounded
TV shows where the writes favorite video game
Have any bearing on causing disorder copycat Behavior
In an article in Scientific American said that this phenomenon doesn't seem to apply to TV and movies because quote
It does appear the public-at-large are able to distinguish fact from fiction
Which we know the struggle for Alec
Is she with you though is that you
Baker supply to all phenomena
Which I don't think he's in any way Statler
If we take his accepted the high-profile suicide can have an effect on suicide rates
Maybe the aftermath of news reports about it
It doesn't follow that this phenomenon
It's for Mass shooters
It very well may but the resorts that he's using to justify his claim. Suicides
It does not extend to mass shooters
You have not earned the right to make
Is based solely on his own access
I find the evidence to be pretty overwhelming that there is a copycat phenomenon going on
But I don't believe it's appropriate
It's seen as it
Suicide
When you make that simplistic and unfounded what you're doing is attempting to whitewash all the other motivations
The shooter may have had
None of them matter because all they were doing is there's another suicidal go shoot up some place
That is nsnsn
The sort of behavior you would expect out of someone
Conducting a cover-up
Not because they were involved in the shooting or anything like that because
They put into the world
Beyond anything else I find Alex's position on this
To be absurd
And downright
If he believes that media coverage of things make them more likely to be copy catter
Why does he spend so much time salacious
Covering any crime and immigrant
Isn't he worried that
He'll call the copycat immigrant crime
Is if you still worried about this phenomenon why is he obsessed about the
Thredup
Isn't he concerned that cause copycat
We carries out his broadcast doesn't support the ark
He's absolutely fine engaging in the exact
Academica media for in every
Go other circumstance
That doesn't involve gun violence
And there's a very easy to figure out reason why
So
You got this deflection you got you got this framing with Madeleine Albright quote
You've got this
Deflection with
Misinterpretation of The copier
Affect
Experience
And then what you need to do if you need to
To minimize
Sure
But it's not
So
Uno Alex playing fast and loose here a little bit I think
Thousands of people are killed in Cancun a week
Which is completely insane
They're 540 murders
In Cancun in 2018
To be comfortable but it's far less
Thousands a week
Maybe there's thousands of murders a week in Mexico that's even absurd number
There were 30 3341 murders investigations open did Mexico in
2018 approximately 641 a week
Again that's a much higher number than we would like to
Alex's embellishment of these things is super
Thousands of murders a week in Cancun Mexico as a whole
Exaggerated image of what's going on
In that country
Ironically if he believes that there were thousands of murders a week and a city in Mexico or just Mexico
He's even more of a complete monster for opposing people they can Refugee claim
But that's a separate issue then
Furthermore
It's kind of expensive to say that the media doesn't talk about the violence
Kartel crime
From my perspective I see plenty of coverage of it
Equivalent by making exaggerated completely untrue Claim about the murders in Mexico
Is what the media should be covering
Simply is away deflecting
Sing for people having a conversation about gun violence in our country
And again it's pretty simple to see why he would do that
Oye complain about El Paso
Or whatever it is
It's a strategy
Inherently a tree
It makes it so no matter how you reply you either get bogged down into an unwinnable conversation that the person who's trying to bait you
They also do not care about that at all
Don't care about people for income
Batteries dying
Even passion
It's the only way to win
Perhaps
So I we get to the big narrative
Now in this
This is what's going to guide Alex
His belief that this is a false flag
The El Paso shooting
Was set up by the club
Another using a
Trump rally
All that good stuff
Adidas shoes
Sure could be
It will be
The underpin
I'll tell this point we've got all of the preparation that's
Needed in order to justify this sort of behavior
This is the behavior
Donald Trump
Donald Trump Alex Jones
Paul Joseph Watson
Within hours of the shooting
Social media shellylike Alex Jones and qanon
I noticed it was confirmed it
Psychologist
They were removing was a Democrat
Removing
I would say that
Alex's
Eager to be Associated remember when you said earlier than that
I really wish I got more headlines that I was involved
Stuff in the conversation Donald Trump
Nkwen on
Even if there's a loose connection between yourself
Shooter like you was your fan
There's a way to cover that with
This is not
To deny that the shooter was his
Spy
Event creating a greater
Christian top of the whole thing places
Focus squarely on himself
This is a strategy to make himself the real victim of the shooting more or less
Which is a monstrous behavior and something you should be
I really wanted to get to the bottom of this
To see if there's any truth to what Alex was saying
But I didn't buy ability to do so because there wasn't coverage of the Social Media stuff on Infowars website
Is really where you think the proof would be
If this was a conspiracy that Alex is going to put out on his show
I get there was nothing
Have you found there
It took a little bit of digging but I figured out
What was up
This is the story about the shooters
MyLife page
For those of you who don't know my life is a website that uses publicly available information about people to create profiles of them
It's super f***** up
And I hate that
Wait
It's just a
Data aggregator that creates
The profile
For you
So we can make a profile regardless of whether or not you've ever heard
I believe so
After the shooting the relegation
Did someone have gone into this political affiliation
From Democrat to Republican
They further added references to MB
Qanon believer and NRA supporter and an incel
Obviously
This was the work of left
Try to cover up that this guy was one of them
And then they're going to leave Noble the noble Donald Trump holding the bag
Sure
The problem is that the shooter didn't even have a profile on my life until after the shooting
When was made for him in the right after the first
News broke with his identity and when it was first put up there was no political affiliation listed
After that
To say that he was a Democrat
With no evidence provided
They also put his religious beliefs and ethnicity is ant
People started at it again
To say that he was a Republican and honestly from their got even Wilder
People's cab
Yeah this became a Wikipedia
Entry Beach National Heroes
Decided to stop following the edit profile
Democratic political affiliation
Action was listed as Republic
This is a case of dumb dumb
They wanted to sit
My wife is a super easily edited website and they explicitly say about the information on the site quote
We cannot fully guarantee its accuracy
The point here is that even an ideal circumstances my life is not a place where real information
Should be pulled from
Unless I can be verified elsewhere
Alex's pretending vets
Prescribed
Portray him as an
That was
He's reporting
The second part but not the
The first
Because Alex Jones
He loves narrative
It doesn't matter if they're true
It just matters if they sell
Also here's the story that Alex is spinning about the shooter's father
The father is a mental health counselor treating people with post-traumatic stress disorder
Veterans Administration
Refer to guy to his Clinic to help with his
BTSD
Which was the result of a man showing up at his door and shoot again
The father worked at the guy and it set up a GoFundMe page to help him with the immediate
Expenses that he was unable to cover on his own
This is what Alex is making sound suspicious and it is proof of a conspiracy
The fact that his father worked in the mental health field
I know you'd help one of his patients setting up
Crowdfunding so they wouldn't go bankrupt
As a consequence of a
Inshot
Legitimately Alex executive
There's no two ways about this
Chimney be in favor of veterans receiving treatment for post-traumatic stress disorder shouldn't be in favor of therapists helping them set up Crow
Crowdfunding for their bills
Delta so goddamn
To the state paying for that s***
641 second about why he would take
These bro
And just put a little tone on him and make him seem
Suspicious and proof of a
This instant
I think you're pretty easily figure out why he's operating this way
I don't know
Paramount
Cuc
Is it a narrative that Alex has to cover up that he was a Democrat
Super easily additive
Page by anybody
Republic we can do it
Before shooting
It was a propaganda it was back and forth between people
Editing his page
Propaganda
To make his spurious
So that's where we're at
Spell Alex
Explicitly
About that my life
Chrysalises
Democrat
Sears
I'm busy lying
What are they
Here's a shot
No known said you made him
Don't know where Alex is getting the this page was up for years thing from
Is that point home
He said that twice
And those weird long pauses
Definitely
I was thinking it would be a weird thing for him to make up
But if you did that it's important for him to attach
The story
The Story of My Life page appear stupid broken by Jim hoft
The Gateway pundit
It has a pretty full encapsulation with a narrative
Namely that asserts that without any proof that leftist
We're the ones were edited
Profile to hide that he was a registered Democrat
The article in its current form has a correction
At the bottom of the page
Saints
Was created after the shooting
But it's not correcting any explicit claims that I can find
Previous versions of the article
Like the previous versions didn't delay age
I bet it had been up for years the way Alex
I would really can't find claim in any of the places where Alex is known to gather is
Obviously I can't possibly know what kind of stick and cheese
Impulses drive Alex to behave the way he does
But I had to guess
He's fully aware that this
What is reporting this
That the page was made after the shoot
And that whenever whatever did it put the
It was made to make it look like the shooter was Democrat and
Alex needs the perception to be that this page has been up for years
Because the fact that it happened
Completely destroys is cause for suspicion
It also underlines how easy
For anyone to edit my flight page
Is Alex's listeners understood this
Specifics of the situation
Do know that there isn't anything
Suspicious about this
It's just trolls on the internet going back and forth the shooter has 02
Narratives are to work at all the audience
To not understand this
Specifics of the situation
It's in his best interest
That they believe misinformation
So that's what he offers.
The feel of him
Grasping
Some kind of
Something and then hitting on the like it's been up for years almost in the mower
Sprite and then I wonder if I'm being like
I know that
Or I wonder if it's someone in his ear being like Alex
Yeah but not true
Facts in your lion
You're either indicating that you don't know what you're talkin about of your life
One of the two
Alex you made him
Mistake on that
Is there a way with The Apprentice be like Alex quit
Yeah
Realize like
Alex
You're drifting into behaviors that have got you seen before
I've been up for a long time like 4 years
Quit like direct opposition to reality
But that sort of behavior if applied to other areas of this story
Could get you screwed
I think it's raining
I think there might be
Giving him that call
Because he's not
I'll tell you who isn't
Barnes Barnes
Keep on going far I got a job
Stay the f*** off are in this aftermath of a tragedy
I think he knows the
Actually happened
Fair
The people he gets
Oh boy
So talks about
This
How he talked to reporters
That he works with
Headed for work
Unfair calling reporters
He's employed yes you've spoken to his underlings
About the coverage
They were going to put out about this story and I think he says a little bit
Too much
In this next
About their intentions
F******
Fumbles the ball really hard while trying to remember
What's going on
Show I don't know who this guy is
Yesterday afternoon
Emily says to me
Well I'm going to look and see if his parents are psychologists cuz you know they're usually a psychologist
Applications
The shooter
I'm am coming up
Remember that
Colorado
Psychologist
Here's psychiatrist was the former head psychiatrist in the Air Force
Over a DARPA program
I remember that one and yes you can
First things first at the end of his narrative about the Aurora shooting
Recover the back of a 2013 investigation
But the narratives about the DARPA program in the Air Force psychologist
Are completely different lies
It's supposed to be the James Holmes isn't DARPA program and got a bunch of money from DARPA and also that his psychologist
Doctor Fenton
Was an Air Force mind control doctor
Because Alex knows that all the shity talks about is baseball
Proposed
Care about being accurate but I never
He cares so little
Also I don't remember mind control chips
Being part of the conspiracy back then so I guess it's a later development
Well-researched
Now he's adding to Manchurian Candidate
I think I was always kind of a flavor of it even about the lie about
About the jailhouse.
Like that
From a book
Have a guy who was trying to
To get like he wrote the book because
State's Attorney didn't
Flexshopper
Shorter sentence
It's all bulshit
That's not even part of the conspiracy backpack
Why are you doing this
Anything you want
Such a lack of professionalism even within the area of lion
Robin the world it's crazy
And listen to him
Don't notice
And be like
Hold on
You are sloppy we're going to go down on December 15th
2003 and then one of the date comes
The cult stays in his life
I misread
F*** what it is they're there for the excited to learn
I didn't know
Dangerous yet
I think the most important thing here is that why he's talking about
Textbook case of confirmation bias
Like before setting out to do any of the research Billy Weaver is told Alex that she feels like a lot of mass Shooters parents are psycho
She's entering the research with a
Conclusion already decided
She's not setting out to find out if Mass Shooters has icollege
Parents more often than would be expected
To setting out to find a few examples that fit her decided talking point then she's going to make a propaganda video
It means anything
I would do the milly don't even care to engage with that s*** now not even a little bit
Apparently just honest way to make an argument that
Whatever the ensuing product is its meaning what
And ultimately whatever bottle like a bank would be equally
I can point out to you tonight at Shooters whose parents work psychology
Greater Point other than Alex
Intentionally
As opposed to being the product of thorough and methodical analysis
I feel like
Climate change isn't happy
Scientist
Here is a giant bag of money
Prove to me that climate change
And isn't happen
The only reason that somebody would operate this way the way that Alex is clearly describing Billy is operating is because
Because they're trying to create a
Absolutely anything to talk about.
Anything to not talk about radicalization
All of these conversations are
Too threatening to the underpinnings of the world that they profit off of
So to defend that toxic hellscape
He has pitched the theory that all these shooters of the children therapist
Set out to find a few examples to make a video about
Sympathetic
Transparent Behavior
Lame
Yeah
You know
These people are such Psychopaths
I always wonder if
Mitch McConnell like Alex Jones goes home and looks at Rex
Singers helping to make sure that you might die in a match
I'm helping to make sure that the next Max mass shooting raise the risk
Yeah
Another mass shooting is going to
That's my job
Today today is the day that I say
At least
I don't know man
It's a
They just don't feel like it
Like what if you're like what if
You're just full of s*** about all this
What are you bringing about
What another rescue
What
Alex discusses the
V3 shooter
From the past week
He said something
About something
And then realized
Make time for this
This is
If there's a moment of levity
In this
Alex's response
To realizing what road he's almost about to go to
What
The hell's going on people
That long pause I think
Oh no no no no
I know it's not funny to laugh about
These people Alex's
Like his whole thing is so built on the ten-tails you realize he accidentally
Hold on the truth if I can if I continue to follow this thought I am going to be like
Young white man
Milly who
It's kind of like
You know
Further defend
What he's doing
His behavior
So your Appeals
I'm too
The past
Happened
It's worth of the left
To kill people
Normal question everything
MacArthur left cover this next time
Turn on all this supposed shooter social media
He was a Democrat
Call Jones
Paul Joseph Watson
So I mean that's all
My lifestyle
Lee demonstrates Alex Jones
It's pretty complex imma take this be
Piece by piece
The first element is the
Completely deceptive argument that he's just questioning
That's bulshit
He's building a case
That these shootings
False flag
Because the shoot is weak and he doesn't want to get sued he hides behind us why is it wrong to question things for a s***
Whenever all of his reporting
Guiding listeners to be clearly plant
Conclusion
But this is a false flag
And that is the work of a true coward
The second element is the basic argument
You justify the active Quest
Which again is not what he's doing
He is
Misinforming
He argues that because something in the past was deceptive it stands to reason that all future things could be
And honestly I don't have a problem with that argument it's
A basic position
Skepticism
It's probably healthy
The problem comes when he realizes Alex is not just questioning thing
He's building misinformation there
If you were questioning things
If you would approach the situation
Position of caution
And a hesitant
Instareport anything definitive
Instead what do we see
We see Alex creating a talking point that all these Mass Shooters of the kids of psychology
Just you're probably secretly working for DARPA
A misleading is audience
It's about the edits that were made to a MyLife page
The shooter had nothing to do with
This is not question
This is misinformation propaganda
Maytag I just listeners away from the aspect of the story that are threatening to his business
His worldview and is revenue stream
Now he's only able to justify is argue
Manipulation
And that is on Full display here
Complete meaninglessness of term
The examples he comes up with the babies in incubators thing and weapons of mass destruction
Who is responsible for those lies
The first was an excuse to get into the first Gulf War
And the second was a pretext for the war in Iraq
The first was George h.w. Bush Administration
The second was W bush
His administration
What was those two Republican Administration says
Yeah this is incredibly
Manipulative framing
To call the bush administration's the left
Is the give up on even the slimmest pretense that you're talkin about anything real
The wife is just another name for the globalist to the Deep state
For Alex now so whatever anybody
This is her children thing
And it's really stupid to your forty-five-year-old man carrying on like this
It's embarrassing
But here's the thing
There's no known embarrassing way for Alex
How to make the argument that he's trying to make
He has to do things like this
Move around quick enough and pray that people don't take the time to recognize what he's doing
These are tricks
He's using tricks
Letter very very
Clear
Yeah yeah they're very distracting
Cuz you almost didn't even catch that the last
Fart
Whatever it is
Like if he says the left unlike it doesn't
If he says globalist it doesn't f***
Matter it's
Feels like today is part of
Let's
Special Report is about how he predicted the
El Paso shooting
As we speak
We very much said
Fine
A mass shooting being a
Well certainly
As I understand it
The clips I had heard
But
I cannot explain that in
Entirely
And I will over the course of the
The show so I don't believe that he gets credit for being
But here is a bit of that
2 days after Alex Jones predicts that false flags are going to be carried out and blamed on the Q
Movement and American Patriots
Lone gunman Patrick crusius is arrested for the El Paso Massacre
His social media page my life with change to
And his designation as a registered Democrat
Was changed to Republican
So you can see that this my life thing is just an essential yeah yeah
Everywhere throughout the
Both of these episode
Yeah
The Bedrock of why are we questioning thing
We're misleading you about this
Right
I do not understand
And why you were
Yes you are a f******
Before this mass shooting
Send Alex Jones predict
So you didn't do that some s*** was going to happen
Stupid as a carrot
Well the reality is it Alex literally everyday
That big a deal for him to have
There was a propaganda narrative it was going around that involved antifa and El Paso
Why Alex said El Paso
False flag
So
It's just his normal there's going to be a false flag
He was in the middle of working on this other propaganda narrative
So it's it's a confluent
It creates the appearance that Alex is on
Realities
Don't boast
Normal thing
For it to expect from his show
Is there a
Has very strong for
Predictive ability
There's a
Globalist
Creative qanon I don't know if you know that
This I was going to say
Qanon
For a while
Last I remember hearing he was anti
There was some good information out of it
I don't give a clique contracts or whatever
Gotcha
Who's on 8chan
Bye-bye
Like I don't know what the status is
It's gone
Anyway Alex globalist
Created qanon
There's a real
Nope
This is
A great
Skyward like grading Alex's
Conspiracies
I'd be like
You sat down and thought about this for a minute at least
It's not good so stupid
At least like
You at least have a closet
Zanaflex here
I'm just thinking about me
Terror attacks
But they can cut out of blame
We've never taken
Do Outreach out president
Crime Boss
Show me brother with a short or whatever
That's a good conspiracy it's really what he should have been saying all along
Cuz the complete mystery
Is there something you can paint whatever you want
Before because
He was afraid of losing too much of his his audience were in 2 Q
Jerome corsi
Cuz if it ate a cheese the goal that you wanted to achieve
It creates a justification
10 for all right-wing violence
Right more or less
You can just attributed to that
Also the left
But they're doing it
Because of the mysterious Anonymous nature of it
I mean it's really
It's the greatest gift Alex could have ever had he's not I don't know why you haven't used it
I will give you
One theory on why he hasn't
Because
He just said that they they
Convince them that they are
Convert them into believing they're working
King with the Press
Osher
It's very easy to
Believe that you're working with the president while committing terrorism
About committing terrorist acts against
It's Alex's conception
Trick yourself into thinking that you were doing
Are we working with which alone is a bad
Yeah
I would
Say
Also they didn't
Like he doesn't want to attack people to imagine that their work
For the president cuz it'll
Association
Forgot
Alex's Constant Contact the White House
I'm so
I can say that with some
Some confidence
Fight you should know
That he's alright
Goodyear
Providence
Studies
No that can't be
Shelbyville weather
Come out
Ignore all
Twice
Is exploding promoting
And then I saw all the FBI reports coming out
It's coming out
And then I saw the FBI come out in
Jones
Is there going to
El Paso
Pretext
Today's weather
No I didn't see that
You literally can
Can't see things like that
What are you just at my last clip on this show where you're trying to hide behind I'm just questioning things
Defense
Conspiracy in order to maintain his absurd and dangerous world
Just not the same thing as being skeptical
Just imagine all the things that Alex needs to
Substantiate to make that clip meaning
He needs to provide real crimes
Statistics he feels the FBI is covering up he needs to Val
Date his contention that the crime statistics are fake
He needs to substantiate hello earned media coverage of Epstein matters at all
In terms of his prosecution
He needs
Promoting minority crime against
He needs a dummy
Answer to FBI director Ray of the deep
Glen's run most of the FBI what most of the FBI mean
He needs to show a citation for where the FBI
The qanon was going to launch Terror attacks with Alex Joe he needs to show
He needs to show literally
Email Paso shooting
Tifa coming to El Paso
And he can do all of those things in one second
Store hours now
Until he demonstrates our prove any of this
None of that means
Throws out in order to build his notion that the El Paso shooting was done to create a justification
This is shity work
And I need to be clear about two things
I don't need to rub but any of it
It's all ahead of a paranoid man who knows his game is running out of gas
I don't give a s*** about tried to demonstrate why this theory is stupid
Text Notes app
To this is not questioning
This is the narrative that Alex has built his own imagination and things probably signed up for
Would you now passing off as the official unofficial story what happened
I know this is probably getting repetitive but it needs to be said over and over again
Alex is not questioning things
Creating and disseminating talk
3.4 misinformation
Which is all he does
He's creating Facebook
He's creating somebody post something ironically he's not on
Exactly but somebody post something like we got to stop gun violence
Here is this daddy and out somebody goes
Pointless
Stupid
I'm doing is trying to give a little bit of
Exactly
That's all it is
So what are the things that Alex
It was already is that the idea that no Paso a Paso
Facility
Try to start a civil war
I really don't remember the official spokesperson for antifa bring that out on the counter
Especially when it comes to railing about ants
FIFA space on some random post on a message board.
As addicts unpleasant user interface
I don't want to take through and try to find
The f*** you talking about
Alright let's
See what he's talking about did Aunt Eva
Client advisor
Completely neutral and very legitimate journalist who else you will be
On July 29th Andy posted a couple pictures of Flyers but a Viagra called border resistor
Advertising their upcoming tour
Including stops in Santa Cruz Oakland Minneapolis Chicago and then their last stop in El Paso on September 4th
Eddie posted these flyers with the commentary antifa is leading a border resistance militancy training
To where they will Converge on a 10 days
El Paso
The promotional image shows border Enforcement Officers being killed
The government property Fireball
From there
The Narrative got rolling
Be able to start it to me or Randy's framing of the event
Fox News used 83 to the store so they could write a story about how it was going to start a terror campaign in El Paso
And now the narrative is on its way to Alex
According to them this wasn't buildings in El Paso
Unfortunately all of that is right-wing propaganda bulshit
The website for Border resistance clearly list the groups
Involved and none of them are known to be associated with ants
55 which is a stupid framing of the point since antifa isn't it
Centralized group
For what
What are the main groups
Vault of Hecate Society quotes
We are not offering billets
We're having educational workshops about what's happening on the border and how to work better inside a community
It's not militancy training
Anyway
Which was Andy's Frame
Well
Not reality
Pre-empting or at least
Co-opting maybe just full-on project
That that's what they're doing
Next flight
Militant
Operation
Attributed
To the left a military operation
Mission in order to justify them creating a military
Which is what Alex is doing
Cause and effect
Images of protesters shooting arrows at a nice
Cancel
Any kind of intention of violence
They were going to change it to avoid any further misunderstanding
Which I would find out is an intentional
F*** that f*** you
The reality the reality of the situation is an immigrant
Group is playing at or where they would have workshops about how to best
Respond to worsening situation
In their communities
Sit around their command
And they chose a possibly ill-advised picture
Your brother flyer
From their imaginative
Imaginative s*** heads like Andino ran with it grated
Narrative Plantera campaign
Decided to call this group antifa because it fit their pre-existing
This story was a lie
But it didn't until after the shooting in El Paso
A which point it could be incorporated into a larger
Conspiracy
It's fascinating really
It started out of
Just waited to be rattled
Construct the organizing capabilities of non-white peoples trying to protest conditions at the border and ultimately through the
He turned it to a narrative that Alex is using to argue that the El Paso
That's just Synergy Dan that's in their world a happy accident
That's
Book oh the Places You'll Go to mine
You don't know where you're going to go
See how it works
So it is next clip Alex
Does something
This is another really
Essential
Framing
For him whenever he's trying to
The Craft
The presentation
Ocean of the
Horrible event
As false flag
There's something to eat
This is
I don't know how to set this up but this is
Important
Obvious
Eminem
So what do you talk about with the prehype there is that FBI came out that was talked about
Conspiracy theory related
Stupid guy but this is one of those moments where you see how he's been pretty smart and classic world
Consequences
Cabiri contextualized as proof
Of the very
Conspiracies he talks
Alex's absolutely stochastic
Terrorist has particular groups and individuals who disagrees with in such a way
He absolutely has to have reasonable expectation that someone might be inspired to hurt
I don't
Believe in adult
Could not under
Understand the connection
Between rhetoric
Impossible inspiration
Between this strategy in the leaderless resistance organization of the right-wing
Extremist cells
It's very easy to inspire lone-wolf terrorist
Sactional while keeping any real concrete connections to a minimum
It strains my credulity to imagine Alex has been aware of this
This phenomenon for a long time
Because of the lies you told about his trip to the Bohemian Grove The Inspired Amanda show up they're heavily armed
Intending to kill Grove attendees who Alex
Were there worshiping the devil and possibly even sacrificing children
Hamalach
Thirty-seven-year-old Richard McCaslin
Call himself Patriots
Enter the Grove explicitly hoping for a shootout
He told the San Francisco Chronicle quote
I was expecting armed resistance
And I would have fired back if I was fired upon
When sheriff's deputies found if you was armed with quotes
A double-barrel shotgun assault rifle hybrid a two-foot-long scored a 45 caliber pistol a crossbow and
And a handmade bomb launcher
Handmade bomb launcher
That's just like too much
I would also guess what launcher B
Tested I imagine
He would not have been successful
Yeah
In court McCaslin testified that he was inspired to do this room watching Alex's documentary Dark Secret
About Bohemian Grove
So he quotes you're collecting weapons and staking out the Grove
He said quote
I was asking our reports
Human sacrifice
Those weren't reports he was acting
Intend
Did goal
The story is honestly if
Prosthetic tail
From this article
Cisco Chronicles
McCaslin was wearing a bulletproof vest blue fatigues with Phantom Patriots spelled out in Red Letters across the chest
And a rubber skeleton mask
Crept into the Grove
F*** you cosplaying
He quickly found himself hopelessly lost
F****** good feeling almost
Silly caught and went to sleep
The next morning mccasland said he discovered the club
And would have blown it up if he had explosives
Instead he placed an Old Testament verse from Leviticus at the base of
The statue
Alone with no enemy or anybody else
But sprinklers quickly
Extinguish the flame
What a loser
You're pathetic
It's kind of funny the mental image of him going
Go Saturday to play
Go to bed
Paul Blart
It's a
It's goof it's goofy but I mean
It it's Goofy with a murder intent behind it
Really scared
McCaslin did all that in 2002
Alex had to of known as early as then that's what he was doing was playing with fire and he does
Care
He knows the consequences of his actions who knows what could happen any knows what he's doing to people it just doesn't matter to him
Alex knows he's not the only person who has this effect on their audience
He doesn't plenty of right-wing terrorist cells exist in this country because he often interviewed people from them
He has dirt roads on from old keepers of town over the years
Is that Gavin McGinnis
The proud Boys on a ton
Even pathetically trying to debate David Duke on his
Michelle ecosystem exist
That he's a part of it
Are there people who are much more dangerous
He knows that this country has a right-wing violence broke
Problem
And he's out of his whole career
He knows that say the right law-enforcement bodies started taking their problem seriously he's completely sucked
Even forgetting about possible legal consequences of his actions
The good, I don't know how that would work but
You got to be kind of worried
Hey it's a hypothetical thing
Started having the right conversation but the nature of this form of inspiring terrorists
He knows that is but business model doesn't work anymore
So he preemptively attacks any attempt by law
Even look at the problem rational
We saw this with the miac report back in
2009 and received your again
Has the FBI has released a report discussing the connection between
Conspiracy theory in the growing terrorist threat in the
This country
He has to attack these things
And pray they go away
Because it is only shot at self-preservation
Yeah it's exactly like the gun lobby
He's getting a
Bill passed
Legal to it
Invest
Gunn vile
Enola
Huge win
But the huge win for them and a huge loss for the
Continue to exist
He can easily just say that they're trying to make us look bad
Frames that he is gorgeous
I put out this report abeka
Conspiracy theorist in terrorism shooting a little while later
Well one might look
Validates the warning of the FBI report
This is the problem
Seriously long ago Alex Goes the other direction
The FBI report was
Preheat for the shooting
So when it happened it will be blamed on people like Alex
This is self-protect
This is the man who knows that the world that he's helped create the world of paranoid anti-government extremists
Is one way more violence
I'm coming weeks and months most likely
The only way to continue to own the market space that he does as this world worth it
Is to do everything possible to make sure that law enforcement doesn't take
This issue series
And the best way to do that
Is the frame every attempt to take it seriously as a piece of the false flag shootings themselves
Honestly this is pathetic
A where I'm sitting all the signals is
2009 Alex wasn't afraid of the miac
Report
He saw it as a ratings Bonanza
It shows changed a lot
Since then though
And now report like this coming from the FBI
It seems like
And I think it's you
Cuz I take a shower
Isaac I think that's
Hi bug
Maybe in 2009 you can make an argument that FBI making a report
It's like the miac report doesn't really affect Alex
He doesn't really
Ya know what first of all is only the script
Dipper part 14 script
Anyway even if it were it wouldn't really involved and it was about actual malicious
Is about actual extremist
Spell
So like
That
Is just
Red meat
This ice field
It seems very
Like he recognizes
Is that
Alright
Is show exist
In such a way that like
He is now kind of what they're talkin
Absolutely
Goodnight my love I named it all
Bye
Either way
No I mean
Being in the wake of a what was it
Nebraska
The representative who is like hey dudes we got a
Stop with this whole leg
Let's kill immigrants
Puppy party there
Register as a Democrat you're out
It's kind of like
Wow you guys are all in on terror
In others know if you're kicking people out for saying please stop inside
Terrorism
That kind of suggests that you're a terrorist
Or at least use don't care
Least you just don't care which is
I don't know I
In some ways worse
Maybe you know
Is a little bit afraid
Of this memo
I think it's possible
I sent his tone being a little bit
But I also have a strong suspicion
Conspiracy theorist
Pedophile
Actually says that
So they're talking about you
I'm positive
The came out last week
But he's using it as a basis for saying such as whole weekends of shootings was a globalist
This report came out
Cuz Alex saying
The shooting
Conspiracy
What does elf
Decide to release the report when it did
It Was Written in May 2019
The research covers extremist factions
January 2008 to the present
The document was released when it was because that's when Yahoo news obtained it and printed it
To assert that the timing is a
Conspiracy its acclaimed it prior to the globalist knew that these three dudes
We're going to commit mass shootings
To report to Yahoo
It's a completely absurd thing to think
What do you think it'll take a second.
And think about what Alex's
I mean unless you're also including that they were already planning
And so of course
Right
Still crazy
Don't get me wrong
Still crazy but that's the only way to Belmont
First one hour
I guess that makes sense
The report came out and said there were shootings would require is insane
Alex didn't read that report lying about what's in it
Ain't no point to they say that anyone who believes in
Conspiracy that is Adam s
Doesn't mention
Clinton or Alex
If you read the report I do think that Alex has every reason
Scared by it
The FBI assesses in some cases and government political conspiracy theory
We likely encourage the targeting was
Specific people places and organizations
Thereby increasing the risk of extremist violence against Dutch Target
The FBI's mostly talkin about qanon but I think that's
Pretty much sums up how I feel about Alex in the present day
So I disagree with them
So
This report is a threat assessment has the threat posed by political
Welcome to the party as bi
It's probably too late to do anything about it I do not trust the FBI to follow through
The positive sign
I'll Reserve judgment on this until we see more about things
Play out but for now I'm going to treat this as it is
An internal memo
It doesn't necessarily change
Yeah the
Who was it the guy was like we don't want
Discouraged from
Doing anything about white matter
Terrorist
Because we don't want Trump
Feel like we're attack
Like that's a simple
Encapsulation of
That's it
Yep
So the main narrative I would say that Alex
The selling
The FBI memo the
Talk about Raiders weapons a mess
Destruction
Madeleine Albright
Stop
Defecation
The main narrative is that the MyLife profile was true
Yes that's the big thing
Democrat to Republican to cover the tracks blah blah blah
And then number two is that his dad worked in psychiatry
In psychology
Enough
Narrative now the idea of shooters
Having parents
Who were in the psych building
This is
This isn't good
Yesterday I was some of my reporters and literally were like Galaxy
The family are working
Anomaly
Here's some of these articles
Fishing shops I called you today Harvard's experiment on the Unabomber
CIA mind-control
He fails to provide
Any other examples of a mass shooter
Parents were
Psychologist or psychiatrist
Yeah but one of them was the Unabomber
Universities are
Do you know it was a summer program
MK Ultra
So you got
You got that
Which is great
Cuz he saying that there's
Multiple examples doesn't have any examples penny
Jumps over to distracting you look over here
Unabomber
I bet he's skipped from the Unabomber over to the Aurora shooter James Holmes
He's already completely f***** up his conspiracies from
Farther
For it like he really is adding a
Ton
Tobacco emergency situation
Throw everything in the kitchen six yeah
You understand the Aurora
Pewter
Call jail mates
I was drugged up
I'm in electroshock
I'm in a program
And I blacked out and I don't know what happened but please get me out of here
It turned out
He's just add runs the DARPA
Human brain interface
Which computer program
Electrodes in the brain
What
What is he talking about
Google who is Daddy
Weather Dimensions project
That wasn't part of the narrative
Depart conspiracy theories it all back in Alex's going over this day
12 years ago timeline
Workout
Cuz that
That was before
That shooting took place in
Gunman James Holmes with Robert Holmes
He testified at his son's trial and of course the investigation lot information
Became publicly available about him
He was a retired financial analyst
Working in the field of credit card
He did not work for now
Melding whatever the f*** Alex's rambling about
His mother Arlie was a nurse so that's in the healthcare field
Analyst to the Stars
I don't think that's what I like
There's a large Chasm between control and registered nurse
Okay
DARPA
I think what's going on here is really simple Acts
Might demonstrate how stupid Alex Jones
How dumb he thinks is
There's another guy named Robert Holmes who was an amateur astronomer
In two
Which is 12 years ago
Google
Yes that's the world we're living in
Grant to do it full-time job would you like to a lot of feel-good press
Around 8 because there's this guy who just was passionate about astronomy
We want you to be able to do it on your own
But as a job
Honestly this might be generous of me to assume that Alex is talking
Think about this
Like it legitimately might be
Enough details are similar to same name as his dad
There are no coincidences there too
To give you pause
Before dismissing it as a
An outright
But whatever the case
It's not true of the Aurora shooter
Just talkingshit
Financial analyst
So Alex and his next book we already heard him at the beginning of the episodes
What's going on
Repeat
And then
Get close to what might be
What do you want to call it
Flippant libel
Okay
I don't know what's going on
The shooters dad
What's PTSD
Agreement was a bunch of psychiatrist with
10 years of education
Runnings Pentagon programs in Dallas
Okay
But why is it always that why why
Why why is
Always
What
Everything's fine
Nothing to look at here
I feel like what he's heavily implying it
Some sort of alike you abused
Tucson or mine
In control
Like I think I would
Mcfucking is compared to Sandusky
Why else would
Because he's a good football coach
Looks like what are you
Evicted
Close there's no other 100
I'm saying I think Alex is real close
That line
Pier like if you continue down this path he's going to be behaving in the exact same way as he did towards the family members
Victims of Sandy Hook
And Scout
I think someone around him better stop him
Don't
Play Toronto
Ethika
So the shooters dad had a master's degree which is all his line of work requires
He apparently also practice some non-traditional medicine
Sandwiches
The calling I have a guru
All this is complete bulshit the fuk down
Pretending a veterinarian and chiropractor I pretended they were actual doctors about bought him a house
So you can take that tone and shove it right up his ass
Talk about your Computing the skies
Mental health credentials
Chiropractor
Do they even have to have there's a special degree
Yeah yeah that's
It's more legitimate
Also
Whatever the socks
Also I found the article that Alex's reading
They're Inquisitor
He just doesn't know how to read
This is really a big problem
He's saying that the father was overpass
Pentagon programs in Dallas
But the actual set
He said he was reading was quote that was quote
A facility director of dapa psychiatric program
Dallas
Joppa
Alex Alex Alex
That's too stupid
I don't know I know it's true
It is DARPA
So stupid and alcohol program advisor
Cuz he works in addiction medicine
Alex is legitimately the most embarrassing person to study in the world
You always want there to be something interesting at the root of his lies but sometimes
She just doesn't know how to cold read
This is embarrass
Alec Lane
If you are listening you are at
Cowardly
You f****** p
So in this next Cliff Alex
I haven't heard this guy on before but
Do you have got the lamest voice
I hate to pretty people for their their voices really control
I would never could take him for his voice
If it wasn't
A completely fake voice
I just wanted to bring up one thing I have yet to find a shooter and obviously we're still learning about these two nutcases from the last
24-hours
The shooter
Not on ssris or some form of brain chemicals
A brain altering chemicals shrinking grade
Are psychologists
A big name relevant
This day
I'm guessing the block was too hot
Count dankula was busy so I was got Tom pepper
To come in
It's just Dum laga retweets being spammed after was less than 400 followers
I guess he's relevant here
Because he created a Facebook page called God Emperor Trump
Which teams help
I don't like that
I would like him to be
And it's just as seen on The Alex Jones Show LOL
I'm not sure what the lol supposed to be in there but whatever
Batman
You guys got to figure out humor
Yeah the rain LOL
Copperhead
Starting your own media outlets on YouTube
I swear that vocal Cadence he's putting on his all over the place
It's like these Dum Dums don't realize the people doing the impression that they are making fun of him
Yeah I know
Cool
Stupid opens up his appearance on the show by
Shooter was not on site
You should probably shut the f****** because all you're really saying is that you've never looked into it
It's so manipulative
I don't know anything about this topic but you should probably accept my blanket assertion about it
Is showing your own
Stupidity and saying I don't know what I'm talkin
Top as for one example so I guess I can start with 15 year olds
Actually you can't start there I get to that right after he goes and straight up Fox
Himself
This level of irresponsible bullshittin misinformation particularly after a weekend
Such tragic
Is furiously Danger
No information to put it on
It make it anyway
Yeah
No I don't get one it's one thing to have a point
I guess it would be
Hard to make of this
Point
Yeah I don't know I can't defend it nevermind no I don't understand how we're not having the conversations at all
All of these people are complicit in
Well cuz no one's ever heard of
I was
He's not related to Tom Popeyes
Dr. Peter langman who run School shooters that info
High school shooting
He studied involved shooters were not on any psychiatric
At all nor have I ever been
That number dropped to 71% when you looked at College Shooters and 59%
Even if the number went down as the perpetrator got older the vast majority of cases did not involve Shooters who were on site
The high-profile cases involve people who had Histories on beds but not all of them do
For instance
Columbine Eric Harris
How does that factor into this overly simplified stupid narrative that they sell
What is looking into this
Insane thing we're like right wing
Insight
Antipsychotic meds were like
Yeah Eric Harris is on site
Like my records have never been released
Because it doesn't match the information
That's why I am not going to engage with an argument
Here's the deal
These people don't know what their talk
Never heard of a shooter wasn't.
Gwen most
In his defense he is deaf
He's only heard of them
Because there's a huge talking point the right-wing conspiracy world most likely because it's an extension of the globalist
They're trying to pass by everyone
Through the lens wires like
Alex you get the sense that
If you look at reality you see that Alex is lying to
To you and it's not hard to see why people like him are lying
Also I'm still waiting for Alex to give me one more example of a shooter
Parents are in the psychological community
I'm sure there are some
Fastly refused to give me even one
Example
Seitters at 2
Not good thing
Sucks
Little bit
I don't know I was wondering like why is he on the show
I mean I know that he doesn't God Emperor Trump account
That makes sense
Really shouldn't be that easy
It's not that easy
The rackaracka that's right on time and It's Tricky
Need to get booked on Alex Jones Show
Here's what
To do
Pro Trump
Facebook
Infowars.com
Newswars.com
He's also
The manager was a great TV stations were on
He's the manager
Complete 01
No.
Prevailing consensus
Is that
This
Shooter in El Paso
Pretty roundly as his actual name
I think the Assumption can easily be made
That is inspired by a lot of the very similar
Motivation
That are
People like soccer Carlson all over the right
So
You have that perception and that's what's being
Disgust
A lot of
Lemoore
Sensible areas
Internet
Birdman
Wasn't
He knows
You look at his LinkedIn profile he doesn't have any second amendment stuff on there
He doesn't have any Alex Jones quotes on there but somehow they managed
Fascinating
So
In order in order for him to Define somebody as a right-winger they must have second amendment stuff or Alex
Quotes
On their linked
F****** in page
I didn't see either of those men's barely on his I just saw I was on the Alex Jones Show LOL
Price this is a real stupid
Play stuff like this dude like this is stupid s***
These people are saying
If you can't yell fire in a crowded
What are we going to apply to Shooters
And you're complicit
Like there's no maybe the reporting side
There's a First Amendment argument
But the opinion side
It's it's garbage
We've got to start prosecuting
And you're like
At their two is kind of important
And that is the way we already have qualifications about free speech that have to do with mitigating
You can't do things
That caused harm to people with your speech
You can't threaten to kill people
Well you can't
Extort people
Through your words you should be able to
You yell fire in a crowded building whatever you caused a stampede you could be held responsible
For your words
Legally
Yep so there is already a precedent that
Some sorts of speech
Do cause
Kind of damage
We do not believe it is protected
So I mean it's just a conversation and I don't
These words hurt somebody therefore they're bad or there is illegal
We all need to have
I think they were going to
Help
This problem
That is that is
Priority conversation
To have so we can get the absolutists
I'll probably
And I think that maybe unsurprisingly and maybe sometimes they're absolutism
About free speech
Really belies
Other priorities
But they're trying to
Tired behind
Bright
I think that's
The case with
Absolute
Absolutely
Also really weird to me because
I kind of expected
Get in it'll be a lot of
El Paso shooter a lot of stuff about the Dayton shooter
Unexpected
Tubi
The largely focused on that
Alex
Doesn't talk
About a ton
Like he does
Absolutely
The stuff is
Related
To those things
But I think
Most interesting things
He says
Okay
F***** up
Position yeah
In this next clip
We're going to listen to
To hear
I think he's advocating
For retaining the death penalty
But his reasoning for it is Ludacris
It was was the former head of Air Force weapons development
Communist
Shameless
You see how that works
No I have no idea how that works
Important to retain
F******
Capital punishment
Because if we don't
Then the Communist agitators will know that they can commit whatever crimes blamed the nationalists
Found just go to prison and blah blah blah. Get out
Wow
Some of them
Doesn't make
God damn better
F***** are you even
Talking about
Here's the position
Told me that s*** Cheese's still
Yeah I know I don't
That's a good reason
Penalty around
I feel like there's so many problems
Castration
You might as well head in his
And you might as well be like we need to keep the death penalty or route
Because if we don't The Snorks
Are going to come to real life and they're going to attack us all
And take our shoes away
You talked to Ben Capehart
I think that all this is
Is it this conversation that's starting up about how Trump
Wants to bring back the
Federal death penalty
The defense for that
Whatever
Like I don't know this to be a hundred percent sure but everything I understand about his earlier position
I think they'll be very anti inline with his
More libertarian stances
Shouldn't be allowed to heal it
Who gives a s***
What are you doing
This is nuts
And
Then this next
Clarify
Earlier I mentioned that he needs to leave
Substantiate
Yes yes
It is like whip I'm thankful that
Rise
Sort of
Come out last week
White people are racist
Hollywood show that
Still a little statistics
Yeah 10 times chance
Actor Rob Blackburn
Got 10 times chance of your black being killed by blacks
Doesn't mean
Believes it's okay to do
But you see how they played games with the statistics
He's playing a game here
Talking about
It's almost breathtakingly unsettling
Do your Alex makes literally no differentiation
Between white supremacist groups
He hears the FBI director say that whites
Supremacist groups are committing more violent
Alex reports that is that he thinks the FBI director is saying that white people are bad enough
Fret
I don't think it's an unfair reading of that
To say that Alex Jones
Supremacist
Thanks that's a deeply disturbing
To hear from someone who's
So clearly into white identity
Yeah we
Yeah yeah
You are
What was it
Was it the crossover episode
You said he thought we were race traitors and
Yeah probably
Which is funny because just before that that's
Exactly what he was doing exactly
Crimes that were specifically motivated
Not crimes that white people do wearing on white person
Who is the victim
If a white guy robbed someone who happens to be black and in the process kills them
That's not necessarily a crime motivated by whites
Supremacy so wouldn't be included
Statistics
It's very easy to understand Elementary School
Operating on this
Completely infantile level
Peter doesn't know anything about what he's talking about
Does
It kind of makes sense why you always screams by the mainstream media thinks the public is dumb
It's really just him projecting his own feelings but haven't cultivated such a stupid
Critical audio
Yeah I imagine Stefan molyneux feel
Probably bangs head on that vent alot
The Bureau of Justice statistics released a report in 2017 that analyze connections
Between violent crime offenders and violent crimes
They found that your overwhelmingly more likely to be the victim of a violent crime perpetrated by a person of the
The same race
Then by someone of a dick
If you're white you're four times more likely to be the victim of white-on-white crime then
What is not true and it is a racist talking
Pinpoint
This is just super racist s*** that Alex is saying on its face
This is that what this is is a misuse of
The name of creative
Which is used
Deflect attention away from the very real fact
Video identified 50
Extremist related murders in
In the United States
The highest number since
When the Oklahoma City bombing happened
And this is a 35% increase
27th
Every single one of those extremists related murders
Was carried out by extremists
With links to right-wing
All of the
When FBI director Ray gets up and says they're singing
In cases involving white supremacy related violence
That's why
There are more cases
Because there are more crimes
Alex knows
That he can't have this conversation on realtor
Because reality does show that right-wing white supremacy
Motivated
It's not surprising that he chooses to move the goalposts
Listen to outright racist talk
Pinpoint like black-on-white crime
It's because he's a huge racist
Another thing I was probably doesn't want addresses a reason
Study that came after University of North
Researchers compared counties were Trump held his rallies in 20
Completely copper Full Count
With similar populations racial demographics location
Level of known active hate groups
Etcetera
They found the counties that hosted a trump rally so I quote 226
6% increase in reported hate crimes
Over similar
Not hold a rally
But that's probably a coincidence
Or maybe maybe Jordan
It's just that the globalist reported a ton of fake hate crimes in the counties were Trump held his rally so some political science professors could uncover this
62 years later
That's probably what happened that I think would happen
How works
So if you need to
I think we all at this point probably need
Need to get this out like a little bit of a pallet
We're all. Feeling great probably a little bit mad at Alex think he's doing a terrible job
So if we want some shot
Freud just a little bit
I invite you all to enjoy
What I'm going to describe as one of the least
Inspired plugs I've ever heard him
Other talk show host plug-in recycle
Everybody knows the real advertising is during the show
Whatever
Got a big sale last week its extended a few more days we got to end at it's the giant mega sale
Saving for sale
Stop the clowns
50 60% off storewide
Infowarsstore.com
Double Patriot pointer next order
That is a man circling the
The f****** drain call last episode
You might be done
Yep that's not sold out
Is that there is a new special
Easter no
He doesn't answer I don't think I have a clip of
It's the anniversary of him getting banned
A Facebook sale
Oh man it's be better versuri haha
Whatever Whenever
The ban of versuri
The same exact price
Exactly 60% off everything
List Acosta t-swizzle alike
This is ridiculous
Jesus Christ
They do not have
To be a chore
Calls
I'm playing this call because
You should
Mad cuz we should all be afraid
Very very afraid yeah
I'm afraid of this caller is it actually f****** Anders Breivik I don't know if he has
Rhythm
Although it is very nice out
But
I meant secondarily
The fact that Alex doesn't hang up on him immediately also scares
Are you doing Alex
Hey Brother
Hey man I have experienced this myself and I was ready for it
I was going to stop at Natick
Program in the army
I should say that he's talking about that the idea that these shooters are mine
Stomach
So I'd already been through something similar to what they're doing to these people
And you can YouTube targeted individual
And just look at the people that are giving their testimony there
And it'll show you how this mindheim technology
It's creating transhumanist which all of them all of the media is transgender
House at Aurora shooter
That is a misdirection I guarantee you everybody has this nanotechnology that's driving these people
These days
And if you want to
This is going back and forth
You got these different Nano mafias
And everybody tries to pin it on the other people with technology
Little details in there like that that's that people up
And it goes back and forth back and forth and nobody wants to talk
Because of fairies all level
Deal with this technology
Tried to turn me into an operative
And if you ever want somebody
View
Interview and tell you exactly how this stuff operates I'll be more than happy to do it Allison trouble
I know that's a brush-off
Jesus
That are small in context clues
Everybody's got a
Control certain people controls
Joseph using people whose
Against each other
I know you just talkin about how everybody in the media is trans
Well that's in there too
Of course of course
Sure
Is the DARPA
You know
It would have been fun
It would have been fun I want to hear that call on a show in 2009
Show the barn
Papert Superior
You showed up and he said I've never heard of a shooter who was on
Who wasn't on psych meds
And now as we
Close the interview with Tom pappert
Here's his tone
He's ever so slightly the way he's presenting
The information
It's irresponsible to not point out that every major Mass shooter again the information is not come out about these two most recent Skype
Every single Mass shooter has been on some type of
Prescription
Mind-altering chemicals in SSRI antidepressants
So the first time he was saying I've never heard of one who wasn't I don't know
Virtually all of them it's irresponsible to not point out the trash
Virtual
CC the ever so slight but it's also making it much more of a
Declarative
They'll front you you act like that to a narrative
Set it up
And then say it
With a slightly different variation
Cover-your-ass
So we got one last clip of Alex here from this day forth show August
The beginning of the show he almost doesn't bring up the Dayton shooting
At all
Really weird
I think it's a little bit weird thoughts on it
So I would do as we go over
The next episode
Closes the show
I think I don't know why
I think it's upset
Whether or not visit
This isn't the way Alex wants to present that his mind
And that to me is just
Deeply
I'm a selfish person I'll tell you
The enemy is attacking
All my family
But the monster attacking all my family
People just pray for my family that would be really good
It's just my family
Inos
Like
How to get burned up right now
My family
Because it's really painful
Temple Run
We're never going to get across the line if we don't put our family on the line does that make sense
I'm fighting for my 10 year-old that's for sure I'm fighting for my son and his future
That's really f*****
I don't I don't I really really really don't like the minds that that's being
Stat there because whether or not Alex
You're about that in terms of his family
Who knows
You could just be bluffing and talking
Braggadocious
At the end of the day there aren't real steak
He's not up against the kind of f****** New World Order One World Government
Some kind of like trying to take him out
Nothing like
Uno's
Did all this is
Entertainment in performing
So
What but that's the thing is like
I can't say with any certainty whether or not he believes his own narratives enough to actually be
Be feeling that way
Or whether it's entirely performative
Uno
Is there talking like that
He is making it okay for his audience
It's to feel like
Yeah he is normal
In this community as you are struggle
I am so
You need to get yourself to a point where you families can burn if they got it
Yeah
A plea fit in with his hole
Fighting a holy war
Situation
Like if God is involved and God knows everything and your family gets
That means that your family was meant to get taken away and you should
It's still be willing to sacrifice everything
Because God is there for you and they're going to get there
Reward in heaven which is totally not
Completely different reward and
IAAI
I don't know it's unsettling it's unsettling
It's probably one of the longest times we've spent on
Sunday episode
Because
Alex is grappling
To try and understand how to purr
After the shooting in El Paso
Because of the
The freshness of it
Because of
How you operate
It really see a lot of illuminate
Points about how this propaganda work
I think it's
I think it's worthwhile to take the time to get into
About how
Lego death
Thought that keeps coming into my head is
How many
The US
Put put on a cut
How many f******
Thanks
H2 got maybe an embargo
F*** this is so much
There's a lot to get into
Side issues
To the
I think they all decide issues
Kind of relate back a little bit
To the mindset that Alex is in
And how this is unfolding
There wasn't really a good option in front of me
But I also knew there was more news
Had to
Be aware of more of the fullness
The situation of the multiple events
It's always felt like it would be an incomplete thing
If we didn't get into the
So I was struggling with it and I thought
Okay maybe we should do two episodes
Then put them both out on
On Wednesday
Yeah and what I decided is that stupid
Let's do a long a
Yeah we're going to do two and put them out on the same day
Started getting into that I realized
It's so much of it would be relying on things we talked about
It in the coverage of the fourth it didn't make sense
So anyway
Play maybe do a couple policy
Interlude music
Gabbard
So here is Alex starting out the 5th
Monday episode
I don't know
What's going on in El Paso
Okay
His music is taking a while it's not all of it there safe
Full minute of Music at the beginning
I don't really know what's going on so I think that's a part of
Special Report
I think they just played a bunch of music
Probably Alex is like
Yeah fukin place but I don't want to do the five minutes but doesn't go out on those radio station
F*** it
Play John Brown's report
Barium
So
I just like that jam 2
It certainly no Policy of Truth
It's so pretty good
So we get back into this episode Alex comes in he's actually in studio and
I'm here where Alex once again
Needs to deflect from
The fact there is
This gun violence
He's shooting
Any does sell by point
Again
Most of the deaths were caused by firearms and Mexico has a complete
On the civilian ownership of firearms
Mexico has a crime
That is the second-highest in the world
Guatemala
It also has a
Total ban on guns
So
Alex is playing really fast and loose here again like he's really responsible with a lot of these
Sites
Anything like what is he saying
The crime rate in Mexico is the second-highest in the world is that the gun rate gun death rate
Is he saying both
It's unclear what he say
I'm not too positive that I care to compare countries by crime
I just don't know if that's a really productive
Statistics uses a measuring
Different countries have different laws
Do something at the crime in country
They might not be and Country be
Similarly different
Countries have variably functional criminal justice system
And degrees is
Systematic corrupt
And so I'm not positive the compare and crime rate
This is going to be the best use of our time
Also even if you met
Mexico's crime rate is
Second highest in the world
Guatemala number one
Did Alex forget how many countries there are in the world
He forget about all the countries in Africa and the Middle East that he loves to demonize so much
Like what is he doing
Ba specious and
Stupid
To even bring that up just be
Because that is like saying well
He's not talking about a country's talking about it
He's not saying Mexico has a crime problem
He sang Mexican
Have a prime
Contract with his other
Yeah but I mean now he's
It's off the top of the Dome I guess it's like whatever whatever is in front of my face identity
Anytime I can remember and then
Beyond that
No idea where Alex is getting his numbers from Mexico
Because he never
Dover data from NPR tons of new stories the Journal of the American Medical Association and none of
Come close to matching what he saying
I do not accept his point
Which is
Countries like under it
Chicago and it's totally legal
It doesn't matter all this is seriously
Because we don't get all bent out of shape every time someone in Mexico get
Sort of
How many people absolutely should care a lot about the violence in other countries and particularly Weezer
You should care about the ways in which our country's foreign policy
Is affecting the violence
Thanos country
I think there's a lot of credible
Credible
After speaking on this topic
And I just don't think that Alex
A guy who overtly supports bolsonaro has been vocally in favor of Venezuela
Is the sort of guy I want to listen
Bolsonaro who came out
And said that he hopes all criminals are shot dead in the sky
Every single f****** thing that Alex
Is about everything
Is America first
Everything is about our sovereignty in the rest of the world
And tell the conversation
Becomes about gun violence
So weird
Sew-ins next clip
He begins
To finally talk about
The shooting in
Of course it's just
Deflection
Trying really hard
Thai the El Paso and Dayton
Shootings together
Every case where they have social media that were able to see
These shooters are
Video games
They all basically look the same
And you're in
Occult
Almost all of them
Those another computer computer
Well guess what
Christians
Ear protection all the rest of it just like the other shooter
El Paso
Texas isn't that a
Isn't that interesting
So one thing I find very interesting about these two shooting happening in
Span of a few days was that it offered a really in
Glimpse into how
Groups of people taken in
Information
When the information was coming out in the case of the El Paso shooter that he'd been involved
Yeah there was a lot of posts on it
That he'd released a man
Manifesto clearly laying out that he was doing the shooting as a political
Against the immigrants we thought were invading the country
There was a response
He was a terrorist
Wilshire
Putting out that management is 100%
I think there's good reason to believe that
Even if it's not 100%
Concrete Lady
But it
Rihanna side
That was the conversations before I think there is it clear
Motivation that was behind it
That the rhetoric was nearly identical in Fox News
They probably would have said Alex Jones to but no one really cares too much about him anymore except us
They pointed to train two people online
Particularly on a radicalized each other friend
6 stops here unless we take
Taken seriously
People in the right-wing world worth defense
As we saw in the last episode of Power
Because of course
This is an important distinction
I don't think that anyone I saw commenting on this was really trying to
Connect the El Paso shooter to Trump in the world of right-wing propaganda based on superficial similarities
It's not like he wore a Maga hat in one picture and everyone is like a hot that's why you did
The connection was made because in that Manifesto was clearly expressed why he did the shooting
And the reason
Route for doing it
Essential talking point of all these bright Wikipedia
The demographics fear Pari propaganda of Americans
Being replaced by Eminem
Chris is the bread-and-butter of Alex Jones
Talking points
I was call turning point to talk to you outside
The important
Connection is that the guy
Isn't the guy possibly like Alex Jones or Paul Joseph Watson
He said he was motivated to commit his crime by the same erroneous and white nationalist rhetoric that they make a living off.
When the Dayton shooting happen
It was very interesting to see how these very same groups responded to a different set of circumstances
Again I'm not saying Universal claim that every person on each side of the ideological Spectrum
Certain way
But generally what I saw was one side go180
And the other side were play
What information started to come out that the shooter in Dayton wasn't the right wing
Extremists worried about the invasion in quotes of Emigrant
And his politics might have been to the left
The right-wing propaganda Steaua running interference for Trump a day earlier
Just because he loved
Is there guilty for the shooting flip the script and started saying
The surface-level details were in their favor on this one
They always do
Conversely what I saw four people on the left was the exact same level of horror and heartbreak
That they felt for the people in El Paso
But with a layer of introspection
There was an acceptance that just because this person is on your side
Sensibly politically
It doesn't mean
Also be a murderer
I saw people trying to make sense of
Throughout the day as more information became available a clear picture took shape
It became increasingly clear that the shooter was a dangerous misogynist
A classmate of his from high school told The Daily Beast
She called the police after he started she started
From him about how she was on his quote raped
She told The Daily Beast quote
I was not surprised at all when I heard his name on the news
Yesterday we all predicted you would do this
When she called the police
Back in high school he got a slap on the wrist over the threat
And because they weren't taken more seriously
And processed
Didn't go through you still able to buy guns
For the most part I saw people taking stock
Even in presumably Progressive community
There's still a lot of underdressed and under address
Problems
Misogyny is not a right left Rob Lowe and I saw many people taking note of this
And discussing
I don't know
Like you might have had an Undiscovered Manifesto about metaphor
Medicare for all
Being behind his shooting
Fear the date
Shooting was motivated by his father
Which is a big display
It's not really a productive day
Discussion just a note who did
It's important to get into the Y
It really feels.
Deeply inappropriate to make
Could be situations
Analogous
The way Alex is doing
To make them
I researched on a killing spree
Buddhist podcast
Kind of fits more into the mold of the non-political version
Which is to say that
There's a History of Violence directed towards women
From everything I can tell that
What's going on here
Yeah it's a
Truth that we've mentioned
Over and over and over again
There's usually violence
If not always it's always a very high
Yeah
Pure that this
Is more of the story
He had
Left opinion
Yeah and that's something that we all have to we have to Grapple
We have to understand that do you know
Agreeing on
Political issues
Necessarily
That means that everybody is on
The same page
Right-wing propaganda. Working hard to make these two shooting
Equivalent
I know it's not new Behavior but the way they pivoted from defense
And deflection about El Paso
Go to feigned moral outrage
For someone like me
It really seems to me that the sort of behavior only really make sense
The context of these propaganda
Fully aware
That their rhetoric and worldview that they're perpetuating
Maybe behind the El Paso shooting and they need to
To protect themselves
From that reality B
I didn't see any prominent voices on the left arguing that the Dayton shooter was a false flag because he agree to some
Some of their politics
I didn't see anyone insisted that he must be a killer who did what he did to demonize the left
We can never pass the green New Deal
Because I want to make this abundant
We clear
These people like Alex
Do not question things and come up with insanely stupid conspiracy theories
Because they're questioning
They do it because they're trying
Cover up and deny the real-world consequences
The come from having it
Rising extremist right-wing media
Without that extremist right-wing media most of these people have nothing
So they need to protect
Like like legitimately
Without this white nationalist wave that he's riding
That's an extreme example because even with Addie's nobody
Game but he's running
Who is Jacob Wohl
Who's Scott Adams
Gilbert
Granny's motherfuker
The relevance in revenues rely on the porch
Cannabis extremist
Ray with media
So they protect it no matter what
And I don't see that similar Behavior being
Engaged
As it relates to
People on the west
With a date
I see circumstances being dealt with AIDS
They are
From people like
The right-wing propaganda
Yep
I mean I don't know I don't know what else to
Stay other than
At this point
In time it's kind
Pretty cool
Obviously
The right-wing
Shootings
Maybe maybe ten years ago we could have had a different
Maybe that's a
Prince story
At this point in time there is nothing else to say but
They are complicit
It's it's
It's horrifying
Clear I think I did
You know I saw some people in the initial
Right after the
I'm shooting
That it was
Supremacist
Part of that is because
We just had a white supremacist
Shooting
6 hours before their offense
Those indicate a lot of times that is a
People
That we're making those
Speculation
Generally I saw Corrections
After it turned out that it wasn't
Steph
Other people
Part there's like let's not
Assume what motivations are there
Until there's more information
I just
I don't
I do not see that
From people who are
Associated with Infowars
Icy intention
Behind weather doing
It really bums me out but it is interesting
I'm horrified about the events
Could have happened I feel
Terribly for the people
In Dayton and El Paso and everywhere else
Been touched by the
I know that there's some listeners that we
We have to or from those places
It's just awful
I don't know
It is
Something that I have also been thing
To what
Have we
Helped create
You and me
No I mean no everyone
Constant capitulation
Of like
Okay we need to stop and think about how the right wing
He's going to take this
Process
Does to me
Has been one of the
Sleeper factors in
Creating all of this
Constantly
What do they think about sex
The problem seriously but it would be seen as being
Like every step of the way
We have enabled them by
Considering their feelings
Above there
How can we how else can we put it other than to say
We don't want to say this
Because they'll get angry about it and so now we are allowing them now we're not pushing through Duncan
Obama we don't put single help because they're going to demonize.
It's on the right to create a compromise
We want to create this compromise where one does not exist for them
They are not negotiating table
They are not negotiate
This is not a negotiation this is not something where it is an absolute
And they are holding all of us
Can't
I don't want it I don't want to go too far because we had this conversation
Although when I went too far back then I was
Perigold be fairly accurate
True but it's it's hard not to
Describe a certain amount of desire to these people
Does Viola hard not to say that mr. Connell what's another mess
But it might not know might not be
The primary thing that's
Desired unfortunately caused
It's grim
It's G
Grimchef
Alex talked about
Shooter
And Dayton's appearance
Whatever
Evil eyes
Always got that weird lazy satisfied look like
That's the look they all got sick
Enjoyable look
How much he loves Elizabeth Warren
How much he loves Bernie Sanders
I want to kill fascist and he loves antifa
I can't wait to go to hell
Ensure
Almost
Every one of them
Is it the same thing
But I thought they all were the children of psychologists
To be one of the larger overriding things about the date
Shooting and I talked about it nearly as much as you might expect
He is
Clearly on his social media accounts indicate
It has left politics what you wanted dance on
Instead heater
Turn to Jeff.
It's all about him being
But the only thing I think it's super important about that club is
How
He operates it's like when there's a right-wing guy who's into Trump and you know loved Alex or was a huge bench
Shapiro's Deli platters
The Santee. Class is Elizabeth Warren
Bet that's a behavior
And the thing that
And you can hear
That
Level of
Glee
Look at look at me I can do my voice
Yesterday when it was a right-wing terrorist I had to work
The deflection but now today I get to be like
He wanted to kill your children and he wanted to eat
You know what else do you spirals
Episode
I show up and I'm expecting like
Just nothing but dancing all Democrats
There's your boy
There's a big issue I'm going to tackle first
What's an internal
That uses USB
Hotel rooms
With the guns over 10,000
They flew in from Saudi military
Air Force
Wasabi convention are
Is in the same Hotel
Embarrassed
This is Ludacris
Fox he just say to me you never heard Alex lay out exactly what
Conspiracy theories about the Las Vegas shooting
He rarely does because that sounds
Not thousands
Are all staying in the same Hotel
Walnut
Yeah that be
Leaving the Mandalay Bay
Got to get some bumps into blowing up on these days
This is part of like a 4chan
Conspiracy theory the attempted assassination of Solomon
That was supposedly shooting was at
The distraction
To get people to
Like supposed to be
Or so he thought
To cause the
They're going to do this shooting closet
Distraction so they could have their assassin
Kill the cramp
Oh okay well
But that's what Alex is sort of cribbing from
Getting the
Assassination of MBS out of it
Embarrassing
Trump is crazy
Trump went to Saudi Arabia in May of 2017 and touch the orb
The Las Vegas shooting wasn't until October 27th
Maybe
What do we got here maybe the orb was the first attempt
Embarrass Trump
Work so I had to do Las Vegas
Maybe that's what's going on
There's a middle ground
Motivation did the Saudi government have to want to embarrass Trump
Like when he went to Saudi Arabia he and the King signed a series of letters of intent to fill Saudi 350 billion dollars
Weapons over the course of the next 10 years
Very consistent about being into Saudi Arabia
Before the Las Vegas shooting after the Las Vegas shooting after Jamal khashoggi got murdered after Congress
Blocked 8 billion dollars in weapons sales
The Saudi back in May
After Congress passed resolutions blocking him from selling arms to Saudi Arabia and concerned about their actions
Yamin back in July and then
F***
There's literally no motive for the Saudis to
Concocted an elaborate terrorist attack in the United States to embarrass Trump into doing what they want
Christmas already doing exactly what they want
This is a theory like I said there was circulating on that pole board
You just get store
Shred
Their 1,000 goals in the story not least of which
Is Stephen Paddock was a patsy arm dealer hotel rooms overlooking other music left
Why did you book rooms at hotels in
Chicago Boston another one in Las Vegas
All over looking big tourist
If you was just a guy getting
Some guns
Why was he doing that s*** for
It's not like this is even worth exploring Alex you just say that the Saudi Arabians tricked
Paper trail
To keep people from finding the real truth
Thousand Saturdays
Yeah you said 10,000 Saturdays in Prince MPS and I was like what the f*** out of here I'm not even going to listen
It's nuts
F*** you
Alright we're off track
We are off
Track 10,000 Saturdays and mbsr hanging out
I forgot the pipes
Now they're great
Any
He gets into something very interesting
Like this is I loved it
Cuz it's
He's so wrong
It is amazing
Like he's just so wrong
He couldn't be more wrong
Better chance
With a Publix been disarmed
Texas
In Detroit
Baltimore Maryland
Oh my
I think that makes
Even though it makes more sense for the opposite to be true
Because you don't have
Well there's some interesting things going on here
Absolutely no idea what he's talking about
He seems to think that burglaries are happening all the time of these blue cities or the public doesn't have guns
It's not backed up by anyperk
If you spent 10 seconds looking at realize he's a big dumbass hole
First things first as a chicagoan I feel the need to point out that Chicago doesn't even have the highest burglary rate
In terms of cities in Illinois
That honor goes to Danville
Which is 50 miles closer to Indianapolis
Chicago
Danville is in Vermillion
Which voted 64%
Just buy whatever
Do US city that has the highest rate of burglary is Bastrop Louisiana
Which is Morehouse Parish
Which voted 55% for Trump in 20
Both US senators from Louisiana Republicans in five out of the six people they send to the House of Representatives
Including Alex's Good Buddies
Scalise
We're also Republic
The city in the US has the second-highest rate of burglary is Blytheville Arkansas which is weirdly in Mississippi County
Which voted 53.4% for Trump in 2016
Arkansas are Republicans and four out of the four members of the House
Republican
It is a very red so
Fourth most burglarized cities in the country are Lumberton and Laurinburg North Carolina
North Carolina was Trump country in 2016 or Republican
Hazard eight of the 11 house members
But you were bacon
You can totally have guns in Louisiana and even get concealed carry permit you can absolutely get all the guns you wanted Arkansas
Could totally open carry your gun without a permit
You can definitely do guns and concealed carry in North Carolina
I secure life.com websites
Security company 2017 FBI statistics
You know they found
New York is the state with the least burglaries in the country
Chicago's burglary rate isn't even
10% of Bastrop
Slightly lower than Austin
Nothing Alex is saying mean
Anything he's just making s*** up it feels right to him
He's making a pretty safe bet that no one in his audience
Horsepower to realize he's full of s***
Buddy is full of
He has no idea what he's talking
More often than not he's just sit with no evidence
To support at least
As he did here
Give me very stupid
Trust this dude
He's a bluffer
He's bluffing
Like I was looking at some of the people who are experts in the
I don't know
Improve this as early
The urban areas actually have much lower
I want of the reasons is
Because there's apartment complexes
Which are much more difficult to commit burglary
Well the only thing that makes sense
Where are like the intuitive thought I had is just
There are so many people crammed in together and Abby
Tends to make just enough noise
Is to f****** everybody else's. That's probably in the suburbs or if you're in a small town
In the middle of nowhere
Between you and your floor
You're going to have to go through urine after breaking later it's much easier to break into something
It's just a single unit on a ground-floor that is
So like there's tons
Tons of like just dwelling
The super elevated or behind
Multiple walls even our houses are
Walking wall
You know there's a foot of space in between each
Buildings
Have like a entrance is there only acceptable for Courtyard
Make it like
Why would someone break in your
Completely exposed.
In the city
But the rates in these
Fink's
Yeah we're happening in these I mean let's be fair
Mostly predominantly non-white
Popular Baltimore
Chicago
Yeah
That's the perception that he has
True it's based on him just making
Things up on what he
Assumes
Which
Like
Honestly
Behaving like that
To put the
Little bit of a
Asterix
Around most of the things you say
What you can confidently deliver something you're making up
Man u r a
Suspect
Cuz he think
That
I can kind of see where he
Edomites
Feel confident when he's making
Making that up is
If you think that Chicago is
Murder City USA
Then I'm guessing he probably just assumes that if Chicago has a high rate of
Murder then it must have a high rate of every single possible crime
Available doing everything everybody
Chicago's committing crimes all the
I really love for him to say I assume the Chicago has higher crime rate
Because that would be honest
The fact is it doesn't
So go f*** yourself Alex Chicago
Yeah.
The new 6 call Q U which one the original Sears
Meet me at the Willis Tower
Doesn't exist
I don't do a good Chicago
Clips
What are we doing
Las Vegas shooting
Okay
Burglaries
Wrong okay
This mixed with blue my f******
It legitimately I was like
Alex what are you say
What are you saying
He seems
Tubi
Expressing a desire to go back to a bygone age
Out of the norm for him
What's a specific
Of the contact
Text me what you talking about
Make me
Very upset
The Village
The first time they got caught doing something weird and sick
What's up you know what the villagers
It wouldn't put up with his crap
Well with Bob go
Well nobody knows World Bob win
Shooters are show
Christians
And that
Accept the El Paso shooter
Picknsave expunged
Was
And soda
It is the accepted fact
That these supposed
Lone shooter
Paso Texas
For the Trump supporter even though we have all the screenshots
Promise social media
Within 30 minutes
Anybody anybody literally anybody anybody
Calling him out on this
Representing my life as social media is very different
To the Whitepages
Yeah yeah kind of
Profiles
Why I wanted to really drive home
So much of his
Suspicions
Anything that happens can be called into question because of this right misunderstanding but he has about the my life
Profile
Anything you can get away from any kind of
The assertion
This Manifesto is he
You can get away from any
Indications
He had similar beliefs
Misunderstanding
Almost
Almost suspiciously convenient
Let's do it Alex is so goddamn
F***** up
Every time I think I've heard his weirdest position he goes and swing for the fences
And catches me off-guard with something like that would kill people
The lottery the lottery
The part of inclined to just say a community
People breaking their local mores
I think of something at this this is so weird that it deserves a little more analysis
What Alex isn't mentioned
Is that in these Villages presumably in the early days of America
These rules were straight-up Theocratic
In the early 1600s
Edna Virginia
Twice a day
You had to attend church twice a day
If you broke that law three times
You be enslaved for 6 months
Rowing boat
Humans are stupid
These early systems of Village Justice were not at all what Alex imagines they were weather
Deals with the problem early and then everyone
Feel their lips
Like they're in La costra Nostra
La Cosa Nostra
More often than not the people who are the targets of community Justice were such because the community
Just thought they were weird
Probably because they were gay or just
Social structure that was
Woodforest at the time
The Salem Witch Trials are a great example
This is getting way out of hand
Like many of the victims
Play by the repressive rules the patriarchy
Google system in The Villages
One of the people who was killed was a woman who married a Slave
Another was a woman who just didn't want to go to church
Neither these going to post a threat
Two others in the way that a mass shooter
Today and killing them was not an active protected anything
Status quo
Many groups like The First Nations in Mowry in places
The restorative
On the community level
Involved
Secretly disappearing people
I think I might be a little different about although an interesting
Idea that they have
Yeah it is
Unfortunately Toni Morrison
She is amazing but
Quote that's going
To paraphrase
If you need to tear somebody else down
Fealty
Problem
Is that a quote
No I thought
Turn up
If you take out
Like what
Who sang as plainly as you can
I think we should go back to a system where we
We kill people were suspicious of so they don't have to becoming a problem later
And I got to say
It's an insanely big swing for someone who claims that one of his favorite parts of Western culture is due process
Sounds kind of like yeah that might just be a buzzword for him
AJ's processing
Easier to solve problems I love you
But we could do away with it
Do away with it process
F****** time like and now he's like
Yearning for the days when the mob would kill weird people
Yeah I'm confused about why their parents would get along with
Fox
Get out
About
The Monday episode as well as
Sunday
First of all the dissatisfaction with Alex not
Talkin about both shooting
Wings on Sunday
Had their issue
Silence would be aware of that
Gets a lot of his information from
Kind of bent out of shape about it
He doesn't seem nearly as mad about it as I
Obviously he's opposed to them
Not being around
The story about what happened
Cares a little
It's a weird way to put it he cares so he likes
That's an accurate weight
True but I think it is true
That story
Individual supposedly uploaded this Manifesto
Internet provider
Is beyond dangerous
Talking about taking away URL as well
This individual
To go and do this it's just proposed
Interesting conversation
Preposterous
But situation here they Channel little bit
41 is a real prophet
Getting radicalized on that site
Consistent pattern
Beyond that a ton of Alex's fake information
Unfortunate
Soap making it a little bit harder for him to find that Lohan
Fruit
Play PCS to work for it a little bit more it'll bring out that fighting spirit
Fright that old
Please inform
Or he'll quit even
What happened
Taken down
Where the government to do that I would agree that there probably be a little bit of a bad president
And I don't know how
But I don't think I'd like the
In reality would happen
What's better cloudflare
Security company decided to stop working with h
Leaving them with no protection
Packers and denial-of-service
Most websites have Security Services they can work with that they do work with
It disrupted all that off
Those websites
So if you're running a WordPress page and the Conte
Does outside what they allow
18 doesn't have really any rules
So in essence their relationship
Claire was becoming cloudflare was just protecting website recently dangerous and illegal things were going on
And no one was doing it
About it
Cloudflare has no obligation
To protect
And they decided that they had adopted sever the relationship
That's their right to decide
After the United right rally cloudflare drop their services for being used by the daily Stormer
This is something I can do and honestly should do
Is 18 or the daily Stormer existed
Entirely toxic hate-filled spaces
No company should be forced to work with them to provide services that allow them to maintain their space
As long as there are other companies in that much
Marketspace
One of the things
Yeah it's just that has nothing to do with him protecting their free speech
Motivate
This is bad
Yeah yeah
What are the only things that allows these exist in operator
Intense security
Anonymity
It's create a place where users are free to throw out racial slurs cheer on mass shootings plan mass shooting
Call for genocide
And whatever other horrible
You can imagine
A lot of it's probably in
Sincere but the single thing that makes
Is it possible is
Without a company like cloudflare providing that
Liberty protection the entire game falls apart
This, could be traced back to me being
Yeah real races pile of s***
Fright is no it's that's what protects
It's for people who can still feel
In the real world Maybe
Yeah
Pretty soon after cloudflare
But quickly fell apart when it was really just selling services from another company
Who said f*** that s***
Pulled their service
It's not coincidence that fit mitigate is also the company that came in to protect the daily Stormer after that were kicked off clouds
I'm going to guess they would say if they protecting free speech thing but I don't buy that shift
Eddie White the situation as it stands now is best as I can tell is that doesn't have solid security
Is a company that will work for them
And work with them
And that could effectively be the end of their effectiveness
As a radicalization
We'll see though
Other some other s*** come along and work with them so the company could agree to do it
Coordinates input this out
Or a whole new Hub could pop up in short order
For the time being
I think it's ineffective disruption
Turn of the process
Well that doesn't
Messerli solved
The problem
I think it's probably apposite
That's my field on it is a good first step
There's never it's never a bad idea
A
It's an action
At the very least it's
Talking some
Has nobody else is doing a goddamn thing
Bad work
Turn Alex's part so far I mean Sunday shows full
A lot of nonsense but so far
You know we seeing Alex misreporting this story we've heard him bread
It's just
Mexico's crime rate
Nonsensical Waze
Rambling in
Just making stuff up about burglary rates in America
And so it's really funny when he says.
Michelle
Sorry just put
Hundreds of Articles out here
Computers
The train stories
New story show for 25 years 25 years
You switching my couple minutes
So I don't
I've noticed that lately and its present-day episodes
Really I don't know what the deal is
There's
Hi
High-level quality problem
It's not your earphones
It's not us that's
That's on his own
Yeah it's pretty pretty
He goes on to ramble about how like people that old radio station
I'm freezing all the printer paper
Play bodies on printer
There's no way that those are not
Props
Maybe maybe
Maybe too deep on an article
In his next life Alex
Is complaining about Trump
Trumpet been talking about putting
And place where people who are red.
Gun
At this point he probably you could have told me he was trying to outlaw red flags as a way to help.
Maybe whatever
So Alex is not into that but he's also not
Nearly as mad about that is
I thought for sure that tuna this show and he be like
Nice
I don't know
Totally fine with that
War
So Alex is like this is unnecessary
Because there's already this sort of thing
He said I love Satan
Go to hell
You don't need some red flag
Look at that guy
Hail
Use a Baker Act
People try
Target
Young women who were the targets
Is harassment in high school try
I will say
On paper
Yeah
There are things in place
They can help
Any sort of situation
But the conversation is about
Work
And we need to take
This more seriously and possibly that could be done through further legislation
Maybe
But anyway
Would you would you believe
But our expenses Wheels awhile
Listen to
Ranting about him
Sure
Have that distance stair little spoiled rotten baby
Probably jerks off 50 times a day
We know the exact from them
They're creeps
And nobody ever beat his ass
I hate
Soma
Needed added ass
Royal
Origin story
People smaller than me
Beat the living hell out of people once I hit puberty
Why are you doing
Like why are you why did you start ranting about the date
Shooter
He's probably a bully
Stop making this about yourself
Everything is
18 cookbooks
It's crazy
So
This shooter
Also
Show some
Accessories
To use
During the shooting
Alex believe
Copycat
Dresses or ear protection
Everything
Because they're used to wearing the headphones when they play the shoot'em up things he was into that too
Great
F*** you
We're not we're not talking about videos
Games
If you have anybody's like video games then they're done there's no argument for not arguing this argument with saddle
Little ten-year-old
Go back and f****** time and I presented without comment
That's what Alex
But I was going to say okay or not
So earlier on Sundays episode Alex brought up the babies in incubators
Richie blames on the left
Justification
You get the question thing
And again he's not questioning
Creating misinformation
Very clear
Brings back up the babies in
Incubators
At this is
F****** fast
We have arrived
Take the baby
Desert Shield
Offensive
And they came and testified that they saw baby brother
The girl
PR firm
Control by the Sally's
Was Allah
Is Ally
We talked about the specifics of the baby
Incubators narrative in a past episode so I don't want to go all the way back
1990 testimony that was given about the Iraqi Security Forces stealing from Kuwaiti Hospital
I'm leaving children to die
Pretend that there aren't
However it's awfully simplistic that the testimony was the only reason
George h.w. Bush began the Gulf War
Hunter was a piece of
It does appear that some of that testimony was not act
All that's fine
Just got the testimony on those terms
I think you'll be a great use of it
This time
That might be something an actual skepta
I do someone likes would prefer to embellish and exaggerate things in order to
To use that example to help justify his unjustifiable position
But he deserves to have a knee-jerk reaction to Every Act
Of white people committing terrorist Acts
Assuming that there's enough
That clip we listen to right there was 31 seconds long
And in italics at 7 completely not true thing
The girls gave the testimony was named to me Aurora Elsa Bob and she had most certainly
Jessica White
To her father was not a member of
PR firm her father was soured out the box
United State
The pr firm
When was Hill & Knowlton
What does working with a group called citizens for a free Kuwait
I can find no evidence
Support the claim that
Hill & Knowlton
Was controlled by the Saudis
For there's no evidence that she was 18
No one claimed she was fourteen she was 50
Stick in her testimony near doesn't specify how many babies were taken out of incubator
But in written testimony later that wasn't under oath
She put the number 815
Just far lower than Alex's b******* about country
Nowhere in her testimony does nearest say that to the babies brains were bashed in
She just said that they took the incubators and left the children to die on the cold
Staggering amount of details to have wrong in such a short burst of words
And some of this may sound
But I really need to
Distressed
Kind of has a good point he's wrong
A pathological for him
Even when the circumstances of something are in his wheelhouse
Story should be a slam dunk
He can't resist the urge to lie about it and make it even more sensation
Part of that is just that Alex doesn't know much about the stories he
He's telling that's a big part of it
But another thing
He's like a Jesus Lizard
He's only able to stay above water and Skip from spot to spot on the surface
Because he has no
The depth of the water
If the Jesus Lizard made any use of anything other than the surface of the lake
It would sink
And the same is true of Alec
Both make a great impressive spectacle
But there's not much
I did so much more of the water that they're messing
And as I read that was high when I look at
No I was feeling it
Morning
I have fudge I get the analogy
It's
It works
He doesn't know anything about this
The case or if he does he's intentionally exaggerating and
Misleading things because it helps him make
He's claimed that it's more just
Certified for him
To quote unquote question
Flimsy
So
NSX
Alex
Man
He is all over the place
I like this go.
Hollywood movies
Bill Clinton movie so much
But Dustin Hoffman
Willie Nelson
Point of order that's not the belt
Dustin Hoffman Robert De Niro
Right maybe Denis Leary third
Iowa
Yeah
Who's who
Who's the lady Amanda Hayes
Top billing over f****** Willie Nelson get out of here just cuz you know him
Exactly that
Real-time in the same area
So if you're missing if you miss like arguing that Bill Clinton love dogs so much
He decided to do it
6 movie
Long long time
I'll be the first to admit there's a lot of similarities between situation and some of the details of the
There's also a bunch of different
Need to wrestle with you want to make this kind of argued
The first is the in the movie the war is fake
They don't bomb
If Alex is arguing that the Clinton I couldn't fake bombings because you love Wag the Dog so much even though he
You would have to know the people would say hey are you wagging the dog right now
Like legitimately Clinton Secretary of
Defense was asked about Wag the Dog under oath
Movie in 97
It's not like Clinton would see that movie in the be like
We're going to do exactly this and no one will ever put the pieces together
I would argue that the fact
There were many surface-level similarities makes it
Life likely
That the bombings were an attempt
To change the media coverage
There was a cool movie that's what you're doing
The ridiculous
The bombing at the military carried out around the time of the Winski Monica Lewinsky
He testified in front of grand jury
Why do dogs eat
Put on a steak war in Albania because they know that no one knows any
Alex says the Clinton carried out an attack in
In the same area
I should tell you that albanians
Sudan or not
In the same area Thousand Miles give or take
How to spell Mediterranean
In the Sahara Desert
Not very similar or
As Alex gets in his Studio
Doing his show
He's closer to Nicaragua
He's closer to Haiti
His studio is in the same area is Nicaragua
Nonsensical
God
Love it
You have to take those moments because everything else sucks so much
Unfiltered love
So in this next clip
He plays a reporter
From the weekend
This is Monday show but he's playing a clip from the weekend
And keep in mind from his own yes
Yes
Okay
Christian
USA
As much of that is because I want to make this abundantly f******
Clear
Alex's pretending that he's questioning
That's why the media is afraid of him exist
That is not questioning things
That is a narrative
He hasn't narrative
The Weeknd
That isn't on Mondays reaction is a form narrative
Hip has people to blame
Villain
It has a storyline and has a reason
It has a victim false narrative about this
El Paso
This is what he does
This is not questioning thing
This is business information
And propaganda
It's not
It's not good propaganda
Evil propaganda
It's bad
So
You know we got
Safari
Yes
Papr
We have that one guy who called in and he had Nano Mafia
And now we get to get four more familiar with just as much of a s******* as Tom pepper
And that is
Health Ranger
No
He's not allowed
This is this is one of Mike Adams theories
But he has
It's going about this
A man I want to say this
Before we started
Conversate after restart
This dude is f****** stupid
People were really shot and killed none of us are saying that that didn't happen
Question is
What
Person
A dispatched
To this Walmart in El Paso to carry out this shooting
Suicide mission
Hearing protection
What was he wearing ipro Ender Pro as we say in the shooting community
You only do that if you expect to survive
Which is why I don't believe that his so-called manifest it was real at all
You think you're going to a drill
In the process.
A few hours later
Galaxy watch
And I want to see this
He's a complete
Uber
Listen to this dumb f***
This is
These dudes present themselves as gunxperts
Compassionate about the gun world
Is this a expect
Get to survive
Yeah it definitely not cuz you would want to continue to be able to
Lucianne
That's part of it
Just off the top of my head I can come up with a bunch of reasons
By someone who expected I would still wear ear and eye protection
How about
Is it outside the realm of possibility that these are people who shot regular
Is that seriously not even a possibility
What do I comfort
Even if you expect to die that doesn't mean you want to risk blowing out your eardrums right before you do
Or how about the notion that these dudes knew that they would be more effective carrying out a shooting
With ear and eye protection
Kind of like kind of a kickback or powder or whatever gets into your eyes big shooting that's going to limit your efficacy
As well ringing
Your ears it's entirely possible that these guys just saw using ear and eye protection is being part of maximizing the damage they'd be able to
Because
Yeah they'll be protected from the little things
Could derail their shooting
Maturely
Absolutely for Mike Adams argue with a straight face that use an eye ear protection semi proof
The El Paso shooter expected to live is a gigantic
He hasn't proven his promises
Baby aspirin does conclude
He's just talking s***
I need those he's talkin
The reason the possible other reason
They might wear protection art discuss
Because Mike and Alex have a specific
Conclusion
Need to get to
The misinformation
It's towards a desired goal
Not to some kind of
Skeptical analysis
That's
Just a bun
Italy clear
So now they're presenting the idea that you have these guys who were like brainwash
Or something
Like the globalist have despatched
Operating
Function
And I was kind of being rushed out
To break but he he he
Makes referee
Something that has to do with it
The technique in the system that they the globalist use
Peaks my interest
Because I hadn't heard of mention
On the other side Arlington Road system
He's about to break something real I never heard this
Discussed before
Kind of disappointed me because when you came back
From the commercial break
Explained it
Here's what it's all about
All the movies on Netflix
That's terrible
Flights
Talk about
Again Arlington Road came out
15 years ago
Jeff Bridges
Okay
Here we go
And there's this weird shadowy right-wing group
Nope
Minutes
Of the end of Arlington Road movie
Arlington Road
Conservative
Euharlee Road
System
You got tricked
The same way I just I thought it sounded like maybe it's something
Goddamn
About the movie Garland
Winton Road Bridges character is not setup for a terrorist attack by the FBI or the Deep state
But his neighbors are going to do it
We're looking for someone to carry out the attack
In such a way as to make it look like it's a lone wolf attack
To protect their terrorist cell so they can continue operation
Again we run into this thing we're out
Can't offend any of those ideas except by reference in movies
It's still on for the movies
Take the points
Especially
The book that one
That's when we get into
The real trouble
Crazy
Minutes
Of this and at the end of the movie
It's weird
It is
Is he eating lunch again
I think it might be a couple times I think it's
Pretty funny
Movie and mostly scripts are written by the CIA
Operate through that but I couldn't possibly
Three Transformers movies antonucci
I can find no evidence that he is CIA
Also Arlington Road is not a good movie it's a paranoid convoluted mess of movie with tons
I've site long time ago
Refresh my memory
Universal
So
Metacritic just gives it a rating of Alex Jones
A bunch of the movie
I think he starts realizing
Supposed to be
Yeah
Hypocrite
Not good for radio
Yeah
So here is
Peace about
Eaton Road
You can see like a real problem but it's so in line with his brain
So the end of the movie involves
Jeff Bridges being setup for
A bombing
What you saw there was the explosion at the FBI building
Right
Alex is missing a vital point in the plot of this movie
And that is at the bombing of that FBI building was still definitely a terrorist
Just because Jeff Bridges got setup that doesn't mean that it wasn't still an organized coordinated attack by an anti-government Terror
Cell
It's unfortunate that Jeff Bridges good name has to be tarnished by the bombing
But whether it's
Either way it's about a right-wing
It's remarkable how Alex rewrites both reality and picture
If it is Worlds
In the movie Tim Robbins and his wife
But I was watching this movie and besides they must actually be working for the globalist and back the writers real point
I know that already subjective and we all bring a lot of real baggage
Steady BT we consume
But I'm very unsettled by the way Alex
That much
I-10
That much bag I think it's worth a try and describe the plot to the writer he be like wow
Yeah I did not say that was that was my point even want to know how Alex understands I
F******
Wheel of Fortune
Episode
Like I don't want it.
So the whole time he's playing Arlington Road Mike Adams is on
Good
Whatever as long as you're on hold your not hurting somebody else
So I started things off with a Pioneer Press
If you are moving with a long gun
Sunday are on AK you're moving and trying to shoot targets they're running
It is extremely difficult
An expert Marksman
To pull that off that's not something
21 year old with no experience
So
Some softball today
Absolutely nonsensical on
What's face
And that is the DC shooter
Targets
They weren't going into places like where they committed their crimes with the intention of shooting
Specific people
And if that were the case b Mike might have Addie's
Oh yeah yeah
Open fire people
If that's not quite as hard to pull off when you're moving
If you are aiming at something
Specific
To pretend that bike doesn't understand that it's so far beyond the realm of possibility
He absolutely knows this s*** getting pretend
That he doesn't
Can spend these f*****-up
Conspiracy narrative
Protect his precious gun
Against this isn't questioning world event
Intentionally missing
Informing people
The bill propaganda
This is the business that Infowars is in
Well that and movie reviews
That's the other business
Say they were doin too much
Reviewing
So much as like
Well I mean I guess
So
They are in the business of movie reviews you're right you're right
Yeah
When was fake
For a weird reason
He is a very strange
This whole situation is you just shot 20 times
I think it's really f***** up for a thing for Alex abusing the absence of police brutality to be a standard by which he judges
Was real or not
When does countless examples of shootings are people are taking
Dylann roof and James Holmes both come to my
I don't know.
I would never take it into their own hands just to rough people up for no reason
Even if they have just committed a crime
That seems like exactly the kind of his entire career on
Given that
It seemed so weird
Legitimately
Suggest that the El Paso shooter was
Probably not the real shooter because cops
Beat them up
Implying that the normal things
For cops to do
Sick mind this guy
Yeah I mean on the other hand the normal things are comes to do kind of seem
Seems to be beat people up
So
I get
Breakup process because cops are
I guess that means
This guy wasn't the real shooter or something
But now Alex argues that there were a bunch of shooter
Which is something that he is
Got to going off of
You know there were first
Accounts people who were saying there were
Not necessarily
Indicative of
Total truth I saw that I saw that
In the in the immediate aftermath of like it's
Possible that there may have been
And and it's like
Okay everybody is saying it's a possible and there's a high likelihood that will will get when we get more information
It would be but nobody knows of a f******
Tragedy like this
So much information
Is flying around wires crossed for anybody to have been like
There are multiple Shooters there are people who
Are there on the screen
Might have
I can be caused by
Echoing gunshot
Robin Wright
From different directions
And so I don't really care too much about those
It seems pointless to engage with
But Alex has another reason
She says according to my sources in El Paso
Walmart shooting
Otherwise
That's a real
Create outside at law enforcement
But
We are here on Monday
She peed it out clarification based on an update
It turned out the police had detained a second
Person who is armed
But they released him
It was a case of somebody passing along bad information
Based on the chaos that was unfolding
This is the sort of thing that happens during every crisis
Some tragedy to work for legitimate uncredible
Confirmed reports
When they do so it makes it easier for
Conspiracy theorist
So we've The credibility of their Outlet into the later
Conspiracies as we see
Reporting in reports
Reports of people who think that there were multiple
Bull shooters
Are not evidence
These reports are all investigated it's just
That in the immediate aftermath of an event like this
It's easy for misinformation aging
Any slip-up
How to build
Make it look like there's something
What's going on
In the past I've liked him.
Concrete bits
Not yet dry
India media. Right after an event like this Alex and Izzie
Can easily imprint their suspicions of narratives on to the story
The once the cement dries
Once the actual information starts to come out
That becomes a whole lot harder
That's why Alex made his video on Saturday on his day off about
Immediacy
Another big reason that he desperately needs to
To get back on social media
Davis Wade
Dad said if he was like a
The Jesus Lizard
Running across
Fair enough
You knew it
So Alex thinks everything's fake
And who's all set up
Good morning
He tries to argue that here is to bring a
David Hogg
One of the guys from
Parkland shooter
Particularly offensive
He's talking with
Mike Adams
The guy who made
Targeted harassment of a child
Whatever
Here's it out
When the shooting happened and got there after videos
This is based on
By the right-wing of the video where are David Hogg said after school
He came back to the
The school to shoot stuff
He was in the school
And then came back
It's very simple but because he says that he
And I would last and went back to the school and eclipse
They're able to create the appearance that his story isn't
Inconsistent
Is b******* it's been explained over and over again
Continues to use it
As some sort of way back
No you'll just
You're just good one
Yeah it's pretty clear that our current strategy
I suppose dealing with this stuff
Counter it
With either
Listen to oar
Misinformation
Is in
Just not doing the job because he's still allowed to say this
Yeah yeah something needs to stop at the route
Before we ever even get to lie
Here's what here's Snopes
We need we need Snopes
You know
I think they're just probably be civil consequences
Yeah they're really got it I don't I don't
From the government
Just think that people
I honestly think
There's a baby bear class action
Lawsuit of all the people that Alex Jones is Moline
Because it would probably be too difficult for like
One of them
Go through all the litigation
Maybe if
Tons of people who he's
Furiously
I got together
Pennywise
Alex you know he feels like he's being blamed
And he has a
Culprit
For the blind
Who's putting the blame on him
It's the splc
I want to go with me
It's qanon fault
Bostitch
Them
People going on social media
Probably will babe
Yelp
Do we get back to the my life now it is there at the end
Jordan did you know that you owe him cities
Still exist
I did not know that
Not that his
It does
God dammit
1973 by Robert Mueller a couple of Evangelical Church
Camps around the country
He had a smallish block that he gathered and they settled in the woods in Oklahoma to set up their isolated Utopia free
Government depression
Multiculturalism
Owosso they were adherence to the Christian identity
And honestly didn't feel like they're white supremacist beliefs it's just a recognition that they were white in their forecast
Keeps coming up
I had a lot of connections
To the Aryan Nation as most right-wing separate
Do
Porila he presidents were members of the Aryan Republican Army to bank robberies
For 1995
To get money to fund white supremacist group
Many believe that the 400-acre Elohim City compound provided a safe haven
Haven for a RX
To plan in
The splc was not running
They definitely
Sometime but nothing has been proven
The splc was founded two years prior to helium City
So you have to believe that his mother early projects
For twenty years or so before the Oklahoma City bombing
Or I guess you could imagine that they somehow took over the compound which is pretty unimaginable
Considering Robert Mueller was in charge until he died in 2001
John is taking over
It doesn't make sense that these Hardline
Christian identity theft
Space
8 day would shoot
The splc trying to take over
Sites they don't shoot anybody who
Wearing a shirt that says it SPL and they just assumed that it has the sea
What else is claiming requires evidence
I need a provider
Climbing roses
It's real right-wing Terror groups and then
Audiological overlap and then making them all fake
Osher the Aryan Republican Army robbed a bunch of banks as part of a plan to violently overthrow the government
Who is Christian identity compound
None of it's real now those antifa contact contract that's all.
Those are totally real
The proof that the Soros is trying to start a race war
See how that works
How is manipulation work
Now Jordan
I know we're deep into this
But I think we're about to get our second
You know why
That's a bad guy
So far
S***
Mike Adams
Terrible
But I got to go
Coming up for you
I know if you think
He's Neo
Oh no doubt of here stop it
Property of Matrix results
Leo zagami is back
These are the people who answer Alex's call
What the f*** is he doing on
It's unclear
But we do learn something
He brings up he's about to be on the show
And
Holy
We learn something
This is not a part of his backstory
Leo zagami
How much involved
Was that during operation
Feisty
So
Does my cell to bring some
It turns out not only is he the are the Illuminati throughout not only is being reincarnated Jesus
Not only is he single-handedly responsible for 911 he also apparently was involved in operation gladio
Leo zagami so full of s*** but
I really respect
Time for that
According to his own bio he was DJing in the UK and had become a fixture at a bar called Legend
When is career was disrupted when he had to return to Italy
Year of bollocks in the
That was in 1987
So allegedly Leo's in the military doing an obligatory year of bollocks
And that somehow light him to get mixed up in gladio
He was first publicly recognized by Italian authorities and 9th
So Alex is operational until 9
But this is not a
Even if you believe the widest Tire
Conspiracy version to what gladia was about it definitely was not an axe
In his latest 19
And a rave DJ doing the obligatory year of bollocks before going back to the club circuit
Would not be involved in any of the clandestine operations that were going on to begin with
So they weren't going on to begin with
He positions himself as like the Forrest Gump of stupid hundred percent
Accu
Anywhere and everywhere that even close.
I love the only thing Alex really has
Elvis narrative to his audience is that Leo's Italian
That's all you got
He might as well have a bucket
What's his name
There's literally zero other proof
Lexington being Italian
Call Trice everybody's stupid if you wasn't able to also as it relates to
Steve pieczenik what Alex is referring to is that Steve was involved in the Box
Hostage negotiation
Should have kidnapped Italian Prime Minister Aldo Moro
It's a really insane complicated story that I would love to get into right now but even to the show
Deserves its own episode
So we might do that
The tale of Steve pieczenik in Italy
Does real f*****-up stuff
Leo
Use Mio
Keith Lee
Heretostay
The profit
So he comes in here
He has a difference
About the shooter
And it's interesting because what you have to
Dislike
Even over the course the last like 3 hours that we've been talkin and listen to these clip
Multiple different explanations have been proffered
Are sort of compatible to each other in
It's some form literally
Every explanation that has been offered
Has
Ben
Far away from Occam's razor as
Building a house around that very specific razor in order to
If they don't f******
Tight even as the RZR tries to us
And tell them the very obvious
Reality
It's f****** God
Yeah
It's
Secure masculinity run-amok
Yep I'm sober
Unifying
That is behind all of the various different
Throwing out a number of different things
You know whether its brain control or their leftist
Soraya
After Next
It's still in the sort of feeling it out phase
And I guarantee that this is not what they're going to run
What Leo's galebe
To the table cuz this
Psychic
Weather
You're getting close to
Slandering this father
Dark psychic energy trigger word to activate the shooter
Okay you know I know I know a lot
I know a lot
About my impulsive
And they come from an upbringing
But God dammit
If I didn't want to f******
Slap Leo zagami after I heard him say those words
Never a good idea no violence
F*** somebody needs to slap him
I don't know I don't know I think it's
The shooter's father
I don't know how deep
It was not a sir
Substantial
Care
Who cares
Shut the f****** Leo
Rhetorical
May 13th
Where he came from
So Alex app
Rhetoric
But I actually haven't
Spiral
After
Asking this question
Not coming to a good aunt
Into
I have the sense of urgency
The ships of I'm upset at myself that there's something I need to do
I just wish
Because we know more is coming
They were so sloppy
They didn't even cover up their social media
When I said I hate God I hate Christians I hate
Replaced with fake stuff
Wayback machine
Hail Satan
Washington realty
These
Expanding this my life narrative
When he starts that he's like
What can I
Say to stop
Honestly him saying that makes me want to cry
I heard him say that
The answer is literally the opposite of everything
Can you f****** say
Cuz we all know this is going to happen again
Yep
That makes me
How to f****** cry
There's a very queer thing that he could do
Admit that he's been
Scamming people for a very long time
F****** mom
Zelda trying to take gun
He's like the US is one of the only countries
Because we got to advance give it cuz we got to get
Because not only
Was Leo zagami
In Gladiator
We find out he was also
Your Forrest Gump
Analogy so right
Elizabeth
And very easily to
Amina
So he's infiltrated
He is got some solid Improv
Because there's no way he had that in his back pocket
Before getting on the show
That's pulled from thin air not in favor of torture
So I would not do any
But I would love
To make some sort of an arrangement
Where Leo zagami wood
Answer my question
About everything
Tell the truth or just answer the question
Tell the truth
1 interview a good singer
And one where he gets to tell the truth I think I would prefer the one where he gets to lie cuz it'd be way more yet
Stories of his early DJ real crazy
You think something is pretty Lucid you said he was known as I mean just of those days
You said he was known as the guy you are not all drugs ruin your memory
That's her so
Alex makes the we're coming to the end
Eclipse
I think
You see where Alex
Stop.
No no no
19 shows up
Restart
Panicky pretty
He gets really extreme
And then he ends
The show without writing arson
Here's the first clip where you make
Is
Insane prediction
And keep in mind
Feed store
Throughout this episode
Both of these episodes
Is trying to defend himself by a question question the events
Keep in mind this is a question
This is making a prediction
We now know this is happening
This is
Questioning
Become the product of all the narratives that you created over the course of a lifetime
Today's this is the now I am experiencing the narratives that I have
I built
Along the way
This is a natural end result
If if all of this other stuff that I've said over the course
These episodes is truth
The globalist are making their move
Which I mean we hear that all the f****** time
But because of the severity of the real world
Situation
It become so much worse
But he's using real tragedy
To say
Standard
That's What It All Leads to
Just the same s***
Yeah that's really offense
Going over the past two days
Hoi
Almost
Watching a man
Some selfies
Not as okay yeah
This entire thing is him creating all of these narrow
I do and
Other people adding in narratives on top of that
All of which is to
To distract him
Self from the fact that he's a f****** murder
You know well
If you think that
Episode wraps up
Pretty
He almost seems to be expanding who he'd like to see
If you targeted
There's no war against the devil
So I mean he's calling for a holy war that he says is already here and it's a war between
His version of
Christianity I suppose
And all Satanist to include atheist or Satanist but don't know their atheist
Don't believe glitterbug
Hillary Clinton has literally been there sooner
The battle between his Christian
Beliefs
Against everybody
This is apocalyptic nonsense
And it's f****** Danger
Yeah
I don't want
I want to
Get into a war
Because
The right-wing terrorist
Committed an act
Terrorism and then blamed it on
The left
And used it to justify
Calling for a holy war
I don't like that
That seems unfair at
Least at least it seems like an escalation
Uncalled for
Here and it starts with what I would describe as kind of an Evangelical
Expect
It's super weird that a lot of people don't understand this
We don't maybe make another point of it
So often the show does just turn in
To like
Who got a weird religious
Taliban
Yeah yeah but it's very quickly veers off course
Into
What are described as Alex almost
Defining
Himself
As what you need to
Lucian here
Across the country in the world
In the time of Christ
Justice and
For freedom
Dodge Spirit
It's also time to be politically
And culturally active
It's time to spread the word about infowars.com and it was worse.
Common override the AI
Here's the name that must not be spoken
That is the future
The globalist poison
There's a sense there that's almost like it starts with him saying you got to go get
I get people to come to the globalist
I Am The Cure
That is a level of Messianic narcissism
It's coming on the heels of him talking with Leo zagami about having a holy war
Contacts of all of this
It's just
This isn't
Sanity
This whole thing is insane
Gavin riding this thing so I've been doing a bunch of research
Can do all kinds of
Let me into rereading the new
Testament actually
Earlier today
And if there is
Who is going to hell according to Jesus's rules
Alex is
Even trouble even is that clip his nails like half the Beatitudes he's gone with the sermon
Get the f*** out of here with that s*** well that's just for glitterbug
Yeah
Cowboys
He's in trouble
It's been long
I'm exhausted
Emotionally
Kind of weird that we didn't
You talk that much
About the shoes
Or anything at all
Perfect I don't know if it's weird or not
But
What we're Alex light
That's
Kind of
Weary Where We Are
Why would Alex want to go anywhere near the reality sales
Why would you want to go anywhere
You cannot
Learn anything about those shootings and not go
Oh f*** we've got a real problem
Tales of these shootings
Point two
Many very proud
The shootings themselves
Are part of
The problem
Guns
That's that
We should absolutely be talkin about
Supremacist
Terrorism
Rampant we should be talking about
Misogynist dudes who are
Man would be able to kill all these people they didn't have f****** an automatic rifle
That's true they didn't have all these f***
10 guns
Conversation that I can have on the best
Gun control measures
But they sure as f*** wouldn't have walked into a Walmart
And killed all these people if they didn't have
F******
There's a hundred other problems that they were facing them
This country
You know I don't mean to give short shrift to any of them by focusing on this
But it's what Alex is talking about Judaism
About Friday
Bless this
Website.com
Facebook you could download
ITunes
You could also leave a review
You can also just
Scour the internet for different things
Is that have both knowledge and
And fighting them
Generally speaking
Episodes of our show
You rarely see
Stay EDG
Put a little
I don't feel like our outro is particularly appropriate
This episode
I am the Jesus Lizard
Alex