Alex
We're couple dudes you like to sit around and drink red wine
News about Alex Jones
Is what we do
Then we're committed to a holy war well I am
Except
Like David does not have a slingshot
He's just running around
David has receipts
As they say on Twitter these days about Goliath pass
That's the battle were engaging in
What's up is there also a David Goliath
Dynamic
Between you and I
Alex Jones
I'm somehow you come out ahead every time
Before we get going here
Goliath if they both just got depressed
But their respective governments hey man let's just have a good time
Whatever it was
For donating a while back
Welcome aboard Jason
The ranks of the policy walk
Please help our patreon there's a link on knowledge fight, you can find
Also thank you everybody who's been downloading
Got a nice email from people
Keep it keep it up everybody listening we love it
It's very good
Today Jordan
What happened over the weekend
Now I will say that it was one of the most delightful birthday weekends I've had in a long time we went
My best friend in the world Nikki gift wasn't on him and his wife
Good to spend some time with him I close down an arcade bar
One night of the weekend and then
Alex Jones did what he did on Saturday
This is a great birthday gift that he gave me
It's
So good
He does certainly more than
I mean even for somebody with narcissistic personality
Disorder that he still thinks about you on your birthday that is very
My relatives
Alex was
He released
Special Report
Yes
Now we're briefly because it's not really worth going into and it's kind of stupid
This deal with first
Was about how
People are diagnosing
Trump with a mental illness
That's bad
Takes one to know one
It is bad
According to the rules that psychiatrist themselves
Put in place after I think everybody was like drinking water
Goldwater the Goldwater rule
Some psychiatrist
It's basically decided to impose on themselves
Because water was
A bunch of people
Psychiatrist
Psychologist interviewed in a magazine
The Aspen
The diagnosed
That seems like a bad idea it was because they gave him a bunch of diagnosis and then
Anyone
So now it's like psychologists supposed to diagnose
Public figures that they have not actually interact
However at this point there are a number of mental health professionals
We're coming out and their argument is they have a right to warn
Obligation
Shinto Warren
What's the same thing that if you're in therapy and you say you're going to kill someone
You either tell the police or the potential victim
Right they have to do that because otherwise they're being
Psychiatrist
Or arguing
5 president
Trump
Please
So you're saying that psychiatrist and psychologist
Neglectful in their duties
Because they didn't inform Afghanistan
That Trump was about to murder a bunch
Even bigger the American public
They were right to warn them of the mental illness
Little bit late on that
That's the problem with these like guidelines
I don't know how I feel about to be perfectly honest I think there is
A little bit of a
Gray area
In terms of diagnosis
Interaction with
A very clearly
You can tell the truth lies all the f***
You can't be publicly without actually having sex
What's up buddy
As of medical
Professional
You are still a human being
It is a human being
If you don't look at Trump and say
Crazy
You're an idiot
Yeah somewhat video about this
It was about narcissism
Essentially
I think
A subject
I think you might be able to guess how it goes
Firmly on the side of how narcissists should rule the world
And everyone else is
Like
Are we going to go. Cyst here where it's like
Are you in the studio right now
Shockingly close
The globalist
A boy who are using psychology almost.
Just territory right now
Defining as being a successful man
Is now narcissism
That is not a good also does we can have if you can smell this coming a mile away
Wants to talk about Trump and mental health
He talked about himself a whole lot
Play
The other first is just fun
MMS is kind of a summation of his point
Like I said
Sigmund Freud was obsessed with poo poo
And holding his crap
Smoking cigars is phallic symbol
The fact that I got me Isaac
Whiskey
Alex Jones really wrestler with his subconscious there
Believe
Maybe I can
Donut Twitter pointed out that
Great
It looks like a wiener
I'm going on the profanity-laden red
Baby language
Yeah but that's what a serial killer
Terrify like a parent
Child was listening to this I wouldn't be comforted by poo poo in now
I would be like
I'd be way more concerned about the content than the actual obscenity
So anyway the next visiting capitulation
Thesis statement about the
The psychology stuff
As I recall
He basically makes the argument that narcissism is is b******* and everybody. But then he
Displays
Broadly narcissistic tendencies
I didn't exist
Thinking you're successful
They loved
Turn off Donna
Play do
Go on show Rogan podcast
Because they are make-believe wannabe Stars
Politics
So I get why the narcissist
Gyros
Did he just say that
The narcissist
And those guys
Who want to Beast
Who are stars
They want to control everybody
And save them
They want to be the Saviour
Xavier players of a created problem
So what he did
But yeah
Exactly
Let me know
Not even metaphorically
What is like
3 more minutes long and as I realized
All that good like
Keno's
That what he's doing
Maybe criticize
All he does all the time and say how he has no ego
The other clip that he put out
On Saturday
Was
Title
New Sandy Hook information
Holyshit
There's a new Sandy Hook
Information
Oh I thought you were talking about new Sandy Hook in Maine
They just started a town
All the people just
So I was thrilled
But he posted this video just based on the title
And I could not wait
To find out what the new information
You should not be talking about
Absolutely not I was talking to you earlier and I told you my theory as to why
Decided to bring backup
Give him this custody trial
And there's a lot of people clowning on him on Twitter
Saying
Hey we should follow Alex Jones around after he loses his kids
And tell him that they were actors the whole time
So there's a lot of people making that kind of joke
To be like
F***
They're hitting the spot
I got to come out
Prove that I'm right
This was a bad idea
Because
Rrl Jones
Level blunder this is bad during the winter
More or less
That is what he did
Long clip that he put out
Because there's a lot of stuff
It's just repetitive s***
About how he's not an actor
He's totally real
Just literally verbatim the same stuff that we heard in episodes
There's a lot of other stuff that he just uses
Vaguely true instances of the media lion
Reinforce his argument Ray
I don't believe
You
When you're saying but I also don't want no skin in that game
Just because
Yes they do lie
Doesn't mean they're lying now
Yeah the possibility that where I'm at
Together
Seems like a fruitless Battlefront
At least
Pothole
Really big one
So we're on flat tire
This is multiple you busted episode
Then
I will say this just an anticipation
Alex bust himself accidentally
And then he tells one of the
Craziest
Stories from his life
I can't believe it's true
And we're going to get to all that
On this episode
Can there be more
Spoiler alert
Would there be
Discover
There's nothing
Which
And he's a f******
A****** in Monster 44 what he said about it
But even if he is right
He covered it completely just tell you what the new Sandy Hook information is
Cuz I'm not sure where it comes up
But I can just tell you one wants that
Okay so his argument of the new Sandy Hook information
Adhesive
I just realized this
If
The media has about all these other things
Why would they lie to us about that
That's the new information
That's not new
And that's not information
So wait
His new information
Is a nymph
Yep
I worry about that
Because it's and it's not even just that it's a
Speculative
Inference
If
Why not
If you consider that it is still at Savin Beach
Absolutely doesn't track the premises don't lead to the conclusion that anyway
If they did this then they want to know
Hello
That's so here's the Telltale how long is this
How long is this video
How long is this
An hour an hour
Information
That he spreads out over and
That's the new Sandy Hook
Make a meal out of talking about the media lying
Right and again it's like okay we talked about
Video of Anderson
Cooper's nose
Disappearing if you look into it there there are like video specialist as I like
River really necessarily have to be a green screen there are aspect ratios and things within a camera
That could account for that
You don't know what this
I've seen this happen before.
Inclusive
Like I said
You f****** gets into a f****** crazy story about his life
Anderson Cooper's nose is green
It's true it's one of the greenest things on the
Looks like Baltimore
To your question even further
If you have little information you'll see this is how he start
Donald Trump
General come out
Rogue
Don't get the truth out about the Democratic Party
The Republican establishment to put Donald John Trump
The office
Couple thing
About it is he saying Wikileaks is good
Yeah
Of the Trump
Yeah he talks about how loyal
So I'm assuming that Julian Assange has released
The new Sandy Hook at 4
Formation
This
The preamble to getting really into the
Of what it is Julian Assange himself
The Patriot
America at all
Who is
Not beholding to our laws
Certainly not
Is it the one
Sex.
Chip should work
So if Trump is telling
They are independent branches
Now
Let's play
Get rid of any
The Constitution
Meaningless today it's a suggestion
People are fired for disagreeing with Trump
Forest
Tears
Long series of TV
Graphics about his poll numbers
Go music
Stop
Noah's first
The second thing that I think
Is interesting
Is it Alex's
Accidentally in there I believe making an argument why you should
Prosecute
Really
Volume
Community
Classified
Illegal
Disseminated
Which would be a leg
No
Disagree
Technically
The people who leaked
Under the barest rule of the
Espionage Act
Against
Ever.
They did
Right
If you are going to
Say that Wikileaks by Distributing
Committed a crime
Then
Every single news
F******
This is a bigger argument than we have the time
To get into right now but I don't necessarily the same as a normal journalistic Outlet
Because they are doing things strategically
And they have to withhold leaks
That they have gotten
Suspicious reasons
I do
The guardian
This is going to be a longer conversation we need to get down to the new Sandy Hook
Information
My point
I think if I can put a button on it
Is there instances like
The case of Chelsea Manning
Revealed things
War crimes
A lot of the stuff that he allowed
That's another thing
Here at the Clinton emails and stuff
Documentary crime
I don't think you should treat them the same way
One of them is a horrible propaganda campaign
Against
Specific person
The other is
Legitimate whistleblowing
Interesting that's
I don't know how you
Treat them differently right and in my mind I know they're not the same thing
I think that's where we get into the
And this is the bulshit argument I do not want to make
But it is that slippery slope
I don't
Rarely ever
Gree with slippery slope argument
Sure
But in this particular instance
As well as in I think the god
But that's a whole nother
I know what you're saying and what you need to do what you need to clarify
RV
A slippery slope is a logical fallacy
Because you're saying
In the future and you have no way of knowing that
You can say it makes a press
President that's really scary
But it's not like okay now everybody is going
To go down
Sing the courts can look at this
Precedent
The only the only thing about that though
Is that
Now you expand the liability
Sure and when you do that
Makes them
Far more
That goes too far than one that
Is afraid of
I would like to aromantic
I would also
You probably should
Parking public people sex
WeeWorld
It's almost like the two of us
Can't solve this ourselves
Probably not
Life's complicated
Call The Proud boys
Outlaw censorship
There's a lot of stuff that we can't really eat as much of policy wonks as we are
It's difficult to get to the bottom of the door
Alex Jones
Is a man who loves
To get angry about that a little bit
Next
It Was Written in the early nineteen
In order to get into the right
Yeah to get to the heart of the matter and what's going on
If you are you definitely are
It's important because we're going to
As we do want every f****** episodes that you've done
He goes on after this
Again not to talk about Sandy Hook but he goes on to talk about that one time
Deception
I go on Joe Rogan's podcast
41 podcast
Or 3 hours 45 minutes
But you can see how the media
Bushcraft
Yeah moving on them like a b****
Now shows depends on Trump Hill play the clip
But on both ends. Ladies and gentlemen they will not show you
Trump is wrong
What are the quotes that he would like
Just for fun
Here is the clip of him on Joe Rogan
You can see if it matches up at all with reality
Asking about aliens
GM Joe Rogan
Leave that on the show on
Hour-long violent argument
If you want go find
This is what Alex
Himself out of
Contacts
Donald Trump racist
That is friends with him
20 years ago
It's all just completed
At the RNC speech he says Republicans
For civil rights laws
Music
To use a real
You said it not perfect
He's a man
And those kind of do their type
Hyper aggressive personality
Frank Dimitri
The big one is incontinence
Whatever you want
Talking about bushes in Whitesburg
Conversation
Locker room
Company should have said probably
What is he's really doing he's really to Italy called
Snopes
No that's the clip from Rogan
I think that anybody saying
Defending Trump
Is totally right
The only one
Defending Trump and even the stuff
Go fuc yourself
Willing
Participant
He's talking about kissing people before they even get introduced
He's moving in on people like a b****
And then they reject him
Grabs people pussies
Like that's not
What's going on
Absolutely
In that clip making excuses for him
The hidebehind
Hey look
Which is
Hey look he's
I've made mistakes
Sure
It's a it's a
That's that's the thing like
Would like
That
False
Bulshit of like
Well it's not rape
Right that doesn't make it okay
No Monsters everyday thing
Since so many women have
To deal with but your defenses
Well I mean it's not rape
A truck not a defense
The defenses like
It could have been worse
Yeah great
Look you told him my car but
I'm not going to press charges because you didn't kill me
Could have been worse
All right you're busted Alex
Today I was going to happen
Excuse to say it but if never have the you got it that's what this real that's what this episode is really
Immediate aches
Contacts
Twist
On our way to his Integrity says
What is Jomon
Never do that to somebody
Pieces of news
That we've discovered
Contacts
Please go to knowledge
If you would like to see a thing apologies for you Outdoors
You owe Hillary Clinton apology
Circuit Court
Uo uo uo all your employees
The other way
Find
What is a pizza K12 recently better than on Recycle
This is not a retraction
Right immediately detects the classic example
Do now because it made such a media splash
When he did it
Treat me like
Like I get there
It's not a retract
You have to retract it
The entire pie
Pizzagate story was wrong
And we were wrong for doing
How many did
This is not
How do you spell vet
I think I might email him
And asking for retract
Because that he is a complete liar about the
Okay
I can't overstate it
It's just
Literally
He's a liar
So in this episode there's going to be no
Lying versus
This is stupid
None
This is full-on
In full control of his back
There's no wiggle room
Lying
But he starts to introduce
The Narrative about Sandy Hook
This probably like
I would say 10 minutes
No it's because we're not
When we get
The hook information
Here today
So he introduces saying that we're going to talk about Sandy Hook by
Saying that information we come out
Right
He's going to
Acknowledge that
Was wrong information
And he is
Very remorseful about that
Forces
And just
Penske has minimized
The murders
People's children
I am traumatized parents
He doesn't need to harass them in person
To do that
But can we get into the information he goes to complain a little bit about Madeleine Albright
Is on 60 Minutes
With Leslie Stahl
15 years ago
What's a reasonable price to pay
And so much more
We've heard that half a million children of God I mean that's more
Children and I don't want open in Hiroshima
And you know is the price worth it I think this is a very hard
Choice but the price we think the price is worth it
It's a good price
Turns out Saddam was a CIA operative
Kuwait
Ambassador was okay
We don't know what are you getting
You notice he doesn't have any documentation for it
If you go to his like
You go to Infowars and try and find any documentation on it there's nothing
He said was fourteen years ago which was in 2000
Does a 1996 interview that she did on CBS
No it was Desert Storm
It was the original time in Iraq
Phantom Menace
Clone Wars
He doesn't What you talkin about
What you said
You still coming out of contact
That. Hussein invaded
Yes I did happen
Alex
He was told by the CIA
For now what we know is that he did that
I didn't respond
We put sanctions
Anorak
Weave
Serious sanctions
That ended up causing a lot of
People to die
Economic sanctions and that sort of thing
Madeleine Albright has gone on record and said we were very specific we did not put sanctions on food or medicine
Those sorts of things could still go in
You know people end up hoarding
It's not something you can really control the distribution of
That's a big problem but that's not
No problem necessarily
I don't know how you
So
Thousand children
He was talking about in that interview was is that acceptable
Try and stop someone from invading other country
That is a bad quote
And
Democracynow for COD
With Madeleine Albright
And interviewed her about that
Escorted
Secretary Albright
Do you regret having said
Do you think the price is worth
Beers Madeleine Albright
Response
I've said 5000 times that I regret it
It was a stupid statement
I never should have made it and if everybody else
That is ever made a statement they regret would stand
There'd be a lot of people
I have many many times said that
And I wish people would report that I've said that
I rotate
In my book that it was a stupid
Search eastern up and gave a retraction
Exactly
Yes
That is both
Honorable
And also
It was a stupid thing
It was
And I wish she hadn't
And I wish you'd known that when she wasn't
That's like Obama, I wish we hadn't killed
This instant isn't the media line
It's someone who made an unfortunate statement even
Stupid is that statement is
You kinda understand where it came from
Yeah like there was a war going on there was
A guy who
And it's like we talked about you end up
Siding with a force
Do takeout
Against
You make unfortunately it's f***** up
But it's not
It's not what I want to say
Global foreign politics
Pretty complicate
Just a complete map
You're pregnant totally out of context
You're not
You're not a Walkman
You're not dealing you're not dealing with not until you donate to our Patriots
Patreon he will get absolutely do that for
Donut
After this key goes on
Do I give a string of Lies
About about
The times media is
I am an
He gets into talking about the lies
They made us bomb Syria
Pretty cool
Where's the last criticizing your not there
Right here,
But yes
Where is the last
Who criticized
Right here right here
Where's the last criticizing
You're not there
Then stumble Te'o
Easy
Play the gentleman
Because there's a lot of research has to go into this
Does have to go in
A lot of research
No absolutely not
I would love to be a fly on the wall
In the war room
Infowars beer pong
They probably everybody
Turn down for the WWE
Oh man
I would not be surprised
Some overlap what's the angle on this
Whoever
Is Trump about to turn heel
The only one that I really know and mainly because
What
And that's okay
It's not but sometimes you should just go
I'll tell you what
It's real easy for me to find the truth about things Alex says
Because I would dare say eighty to ninety percent of the time it is the office
If the first link on Google
Sure
Google a thing he said
First link that comes up will disprove
Sort of lead people to do surface-level
Research
The first link
Ellicott
So Alex is going on this year review
Whole bunch already about him
August. Congratulations to everybody who did the March 4th
I hope we
All the way
God damn paid protesters man that's a bummer
Forty thousand people out there
That's God
It's like 25 bucks like jewelry
Absolutely
Ridley Scott
Is he at George Soros on Twitter
If so
Funny
Right bro
Angry boys
Haven
Yes he goes on in his Mexico update
Defend himself
It's about the new viewers
You can verify this
For yourself
You can't
Also
This is what people
This is
Not true don't like a lot of people don't want to get busted in some sort of Allah
I'm not lying this is all about truth here man
All about truth
It's it's one of the best ways to get people to
Just believe you is just a unbelievable
A lot of people are dumb
It's been terrible
It is true you're an emotion in those sorts of things
It makes people shut off cognitive
Little
Stopgap measures in their brain
Otherwise guard them from believing.
Takes over ironically lizard mask part of your brain
So that's dumb
The next clip Alex then goes on
To get into more about the media lying about him and
Text
Horse pivot
Specifically
Just like all the media is always
We're going to get
But this one is just sort of generalize lies and then
It gives
Into
Big old islamophobia
Great great I was wondering we were going to get to hating on people who believe in his
Just be a second
Is the I'm sorry Muslims worship
Apologize
The media says
Lee attacks never happened
Sandy Hook
When you can go and find myself
With both side people that sing
And former top
School security
Law enforcement folks like wolf
The truth
Have you got a government caught lying about that causes Wars
Hundreds of thousands of children from
Bill Clinton
So is his basic argument is
We know the government is willing to accept that half
7 million children
When is a
Is a reasonable loss
Is Madeleine Albright
She has
Is killing civilians is acceptable in the Rules of Engagement or whatever it's like
There's a map on it you can kill up to 30 people if you get a good
So we know that the government
Is willing to
To kill
Then kill these children
Depicting his position on Sandy Hook
Quote
Oh yeah
Snippet his his position is even more nonsense
What you just said
Because his position is
There been people on the show and we've had debates about it
But I don't know I can't prove it either way I don't know
The government clearly was and is okay with killing civilians
Do your part was only
That was the sort of like
The carrot dangling out of his
Or at least he's very inclined to believe
I can't prove it either way
Hiding behind
Do we have a
Clip of him
Static
Hold on would you say that
Perhaps
He is mischaracterizing
His own state
I don't know
You don't know I have no idea let's see how this plays out
Generally whenever I ask
Question like that you have no idea
Whataboutism
And they do this over and over again I don't want them to sit there and shake their finger at me
Compare about children being shot in mass shooting
I'm here
Cause of death
George Strait
Drowning
Is definitely
CDC
I looked into the CDC
The statistics about this
Pretty off
The cause of death
The top
Cause of death
Number 10 number 10
Suicide
Suicide Squad
Guns will not all of them but a lot of them are and then number for is just do Vegas f****** thing
Accident
Accidental gunshot
Is well-taken
In terms of heart disease and cancer number one
Into
Lower respiratory diseases is number three
I mean if you want if you want
Go down that road
I mean until we heart disease
Let's not tackle guns
Do you like
The point that people who are against
Guns generally make
Earliest
Against
Everybody having gun
Is B A lot of these deaths are really avoidable
Whereas
Heart disease
A little bit more complicated
But it also takes early detection in order for it to be
Efficient
Heart disease is a penguin
A lot of those are just like
Hey
Human being
We're not
Supposed to live
Dirt bike
That's irrelevant
The thing that people are complaining about not generally that no one should have done
Kill Everybody
All the accidental gunshot death
Exist
Couldn't
Be gone they don't have to happen
Right
Control over who had
We had better education a better education about guns
Nothing like.
Leave guns out
That sort of thing
Don't let your kids be around them leave download
All that sort of stuff would be really effective
And
Of course Alex's argument against
If you yelled at Piers Morgan
One-time famously
Sword
That
It's not 14
Closer to like
Like 10 but like
It isn't the biggest
That doesn't matter
Also well
Also we're not allowed to study it because somehow
The gun lobby
Is so strong
They got a rule in Congress that you
You can't do any research about guns
In the context that he's talking about you talk about mass shootings
Stuff like that
So much
Millions of people died from mass shootings
Is that they're all horribly traumatic
Usually involve
Incredibly Ennis
Cook children
I can't do it
Like I can't do it
Are we just all accepted that mass shootings are happy
What's what is it going to take
Not really is going to take do you want it
The only
Real way that pee
People are going to make any
Changes there
Minorities start shooting white people all the time
Is it
Or if we start
If we start utilizing our Mash
Adamantly
Sure
Don't I don't like I don't like the line you're starting to go down
If you see a mass shooter
Walking down the street on his way to imagine
Just point them toward the ridge purse
I'm not saying
That you should encourage anything
I am not encouraging violence towards anybody
Sure
Pregnant
Pointed in the right direction
There are
I'm agreeing or disagreeing with you
Are a Virgo
Suicide attempt
Definition
And no one's
You are
Cars
Islamists coming in
No one said banshee
From as usual
But this latest attack
Medium
Last year without Muslims
That sounds reasonable
Your Gator kill you
Education cancer or any number of these different
What's what's the difference
What's the different one of them is a Muslim
Stuff is not really what he's
More importantly
What people were taking a
Issue with was
The way he
Doubt about it
Before the facts were in with your response
No matter what the truth of the situation is
If it does
You know if it does come out there this into
Incident was
Is an act of terrorism
It's still wrong of him before the factor there
That sort of thing
It's Unbecoming
Just Unbecoming
It is
The president of the United
So
That's what makes
It's Unbecoming if somebody is becoming human
President tweeting this s*** out that is a
To Violet
Especially if it's a present who has the record that he has
That situation
With every other single thing that he's ever
I'm not wanted to wrestle with the details
The other thing I think
It's funny cuz he's having riots every night and like they posted a video with little while back proving
They're trying to burn down Paris
And there's riots
People shooting off fireworks in like a celebration
The holiday
What is f****** wrong with you guys that Muslims celebrate Chinese New Year
I didn't know I didn't I wasn't even been Bastille Day
I don't remember exactly which holiday
But it was something that just took wildly out they would just lie even if you were
Like that's the most
Easily disprovable thing there because even if you're exaggerating
You're resorting to hyperbole
Which as you know
I would never
Never
Every night
Implies there's a lot of riot
Regular
And even then if you're saying
Well I'm not I don't mean every night
I just mean there's a
Connor Ryan
Yeah
Okay
Joe
Show me to riots
Yeah
Cuz you know what
One riot
I will except
Sure but if you're going to say there's rides every night I want at least two
Intuit
Unrelated into
If you want to develop a pattern and then test
Yeah
Number two
Lowering my bars information
Information Wars
Out of courtesy for your a busy with all the other skirmishes in the intro of War
Formation war on like 6 front
Smokey Point
What's a custody battle
Yeah
Makes these claims that they just aren't
Ever support
So
Hooray
Great
Please demonize
Population
Based on your whims
To create a storyline
Please go ahead keep doing that
It's not going to bite you in the NFL
Never
Well
I made it
A lot of people have gotten a lot of power by doing it you've made a lot of money
Easily influenced by demagogue not making any money
Nothing is demonizing
Higher population
We're going about a backwards
We're demonizing
A guy
Are we getting
To him in Subway's way more like his rhetoric and not what he stands for as a tragic flaw.
Human beings we're being way to Fair Game Plan
Who should we
Demonized
What is there like
Aztec
Someone is not around anymore
Let's demonize him group is not now that's not even
He was chopping off somebody's head
Oh my God
These dirty Aztec
We need to do something out of our ground is
Right
Sunrise
Praise to the sun god
Which as we all know there's only one God
This isn't going to work
It's a hundred percent is not going to work it's not
An Inca
It's not thinking
Inca
Income
No it's it's own
Who cares
That's irrelevant
I'm so high
Cruising the f****** head
With your jokes
You know what
After 33 years of being alive
I finally found
The place where I belong
That's another Linkin Park song
Look look I don't know any
Linkin Park
At all
I know their name is Lincoln Park and they don't
Be forgotten
Alex's figured out where all of the stuff
About
His Sandy Hook
Position that the media is lying about coming from
Yeah
The media has made specific
Friendly's figured it out
And I'll let him speak his
0 article we found
New Yorker magazine
This is
Because I look at everything from the Associated Press
And they all
Lyft
This is the most crazy thing
I've ever seen
September 11th
They quoted it
Jones amazing reputation around his family from his high volume
I have to pause there cuz you're totally right if he was able to figure out where was coming from they attributed it
Quotes
And they said
From the New York
Hey Alex
It's like a double apostrophe importation dark journalist
Use other people's reporting at their own reporting
You can't do all of the news by yourself
It's only plagiarize if you don't
If you're able to
The patient zero anyway
Really good point I completely missed that
Shropshire
Those were
Now you know this week's here
This is Brittany
But I Noah
Just keep
Never said that
So now
Now listen
I've listened
You have
Just going to adjust
Hunch
You
May have
Audio
I just might
You might
Before we get to that
I think they're he saying that everyone saying that he's fake
Has no audio lullaby
Everyone
Responding
To your lawyer
They're not
Most people
Collaborate
With their attorneys
Client
They're saying what they've agreed is going to be there gameplay
Maybe that's wrong to make that assumption and Yukon road from your lawyer
Maybe that's the case
Going to put we're not going to put a medium Avion this we're going to put a very plausible
You're making that claim I don't know what the fuc
What is up with you
But if your lawyer
I would almost
So now you saying that article is patient zero of him saying
That
Sandy Hook
Was fake
And they don't have any don't have any audio of Hillary
No links
New Yorker did not do its due diligence
They needed to
Supposed link
To all of these things and you can do it
So that means they don't exist Dan
I rest my case
I would like to travel back to the show
On January 13th of 2015 Huron remove the strike this evidence for the record
Denied
What I'm curious about is do you think that there's a new level of sophistication with a lot of these false flag
Where
A couple of pizza
I just want to make it clear cuz it Doesn't there's no context
Is the Charlie hebdo attack
That's how they got into this
He's making the argument that
Because I think Alex does references
Charlie hebdo also false flag
Absolutely man
Islamophobia
It's the globalist doing that to make people more afraid of Muslims it's complicated
She's a very Tangled married and it also had something to do with strangling free speech
Anyway
Who's responsible scholar
Flimsy evidence that get everybody talking and serum in the wrong direction
Jamaica Jamaica
It's just that when they were funded by Western Funding
Provocateurs
Becomes a red herring
Because
All the world
Bowers
Then
Caught using blue screen
Email Bloomberg
Reselling is people get ready next 24 hours to capitalize on a shooting
Yeah show
Use a synthetic
Completely fake
Manufacturer
Clearly
Used
The evenin.
Photos of kids killed in mass shootings
The sky is now the women I appreciate your call
Hi this is
3 /
That is very that's crazy
All the stuff that he said
You said all the stuff that he said the media is making up about him
Hey Alex
F*** you seriously
F*** you
You can't pull that
You can't pull that back don't f****** put out a special report
Employment everyone's lying about you when you lie about yourself
What is wrong with you
How long did it take you to get that clip of hemline verbatim
Minutes
How do you how do you sleep
It's completely insane yeah it's kind of like
You know the criminal who wants to get caught
Kind of like he's got to be exhausted
Recent version of the zodiac I can't repeat
F*** you
You stupid son of a b****
How dare you
That's enough of that
But now I want to get into for a second
Enough for our show
I will leave the rest
Do the parents
Of that Dad the dead children who are
Really doing some good work telling a shut the fuk up
Which is correct
I like to see
Terrible for their loss
But
He referenced a bunch of things there
That are like little pieces of
Proof that Sandy Hook is fake
Yes I want to make my position clear
I think it was real
And I want to make my position.
Look you're taking
I want to make my position a little bit further clear
I am a person
Who engages conspiracy theories
I'm person who for the last years and years of my life
Has been like
What if that's true
And I've looked into things
And I remember when Sandy Hook happen
I remember seeing all of these conspiracies
Popping up about them
IWatch
Peoples
Sandy Hook is fake
Videos
Scary
Really some of it's real scary
Describes
Because it scares me just based on
No matter what
Trying
Declarative
Yeah and said that means that there
You can never trust
Annie
You can never tribute
Blame
They were making these claims
Seem to be real
There was a bunch
To stop about like police
Xclear
Stuff and all this instance of children walking around in a circle
What is the Anderson Cooper
It's really interesting
To be really scared
Right I looked into it a bit further
And found
Explanation
For literally everything
That most of it was
These videos
Post
On the internet
Really
These things are all
Lies
So why there's doctor video
As we discussed there's an innocent explanation
Entirely possible
The children walking around
You have to stay out of
Around
There's nothing we could do we can't like
We might need to question people
No
Yeah it's a small town and why would anyone go back to this place
Memories
It's insane all of the pieces of evidence
Or circumstantial is f***
And most of them are Bass
On manipulative explanation
Made by YouTuber
Why would you f****** evil
Why would you
He makes millions of dollars
Yeah people really want to disbelieve every
Over and over again makes life more interest
Yeah but I mean
That's like that kind of stuff
Seems more
You have a full-on
You have an agenda there
Where somebody's
If your doctoring video
It's not because you want to make life more
It's because you're going out there
To deceive pulling a prank
With a purpose
Will not do
Understanding of the word
Cruelty cruelty
No I don't even want to
Reference
But there are those Webb communities
That
Right there's a lot of
Message boards
Right
Secure kids come on and they're like they bully them to kill themselves Community online
You think it's funny
Videos necessarily are a product of that
Yeah get attention
Get things into the zeitgeist
Whenever it's every single time
And if you're not careful
If you don't look into things
You can fall for really dumb s***
I'm super glad that I did
Videos
And then you went
And look
Further and that's where most
Primary source or what they think
Because their primary
And then they were like well I trust them
So
Done
Or not even I trust them I trust the person who shared this
The person who shared the brewery
Yeah not ever a
Two step
So whenever whenever we're dealing with a lot of aloe
Alex Jones
Ultimately that's
Like we're the second step
Hopefully
Yeah hopefully
Again which is why weird
No
Of my own
Life
And what I can give you
I can't prove Sandy Hook happen
I can't do that
I just can't
I can't prove almost anything
In the world
Brenda Hampton
Right
I can tell you
Thorough examination that I've done
Every single piece
Zodiac was fake
Is b*******
Yeah and Alex Jones
And once again
Did land on them
Alex Jones
Being a coward
Hiding behind the I don't know when in reality
On climate
F*** you
You're killing me
You are personally responsible
For the
Of millions of people
In this case I was responsible for anyone's death
F****** dick hole
But nobody is responsible for
The pain of
You very clearly when talking to that
January 13th 2015
Set that
He doesn't
If there was all actors it was a sympathetic effect
You couldn't believe it at first
But then he
Prove it
Do himself
So clearly that is what he believed
All this other stuff is window dressing
And what store
Nope it is Howard
Is pure
Hiding
Yep
Nope
F*** you Alex
So it goes on from there
After he says all this b******* about Sandy Hook
I2
Basically where are we at just goes on from here
To play
Which is unfortunate
People out there that have never
The show
Completely
Same time
Are you crazy
No it's called a skid
High School level 1,000 devil
People
Illustrating how it's bad by playing the part of statement does not
Alex
LinkedIn LinkedIn
That is a a
Dumb person that's a
God
Are you really the devil are you really I don't understand, how could
Alex is not engaging with the truth even in that state
That this
Remember
He was being sincere when he dressed up like the devil
Right
Say everyone
They worked at in Fort Worth
So I rule
Nothing
Anything is Possible
In that
That is
Come on you're so stupid
I will also not rule out
Play Sublime he makes up plenty of people who say things
To him all the time
Both Richard linklater movies
Advisor
That with no that wasn't Scanner Darkly
Oh okay I'm sorry
Advise on the movie The Discovery movie
Boys Waking Life was the first one of the rotoscoping
What's my favorite movie
A bunch of stuff throughout this about Alex
Really still hammering home that he thinks that everyone is just talking about her
Escape
Another one
Little different isn't a
That one I do genuinely think
I agree he's very confused understand
What the people who are attacking him are up to
Here is Miss next clip he's going to
Explain what he thinks the world is doing
To him
And it's fascinating
Cuz I cut out two parts in this episode already
Works
I'm not a victim
This is Vic
No one showing
The Journal of Medicine and WebMD
But
Massive massive
And then people get Warren
45/56
Blown up
You are crazy
Advertisers let's list
You don't have any
Know your channel every major News Channel
Talk to your lawyer
Berea
Really scary stuff
I say this man is psychotic
So he thinks
That being serious.
You say Alex
Comes when you are not wearing a clown
Not at all cabal of Elites
Globalist
They're getting together
To try and take him down because it's becoming too influential
Could we use his words
Literally a whippersnapper
I'm not done sketches
So we're going to say that he's fake
I mean we don't have to do that for us
Okay
Another thing
He's gotten really angry on Arrow bunch of times
Let's
Manipulative
Let's not
Presentations of Alex is a little bit
Rocky training
People who are making memes who are pretty good at it
But like
But he doesn't understand humor
Now cuz I don't understand why you
I don't
Watch any TV news
Noodle top box
Other than like better than going at it
Cuz they're implying that the actual
Has a clip of him
Being crazy
I I don't I don't know I can't speak
Cuz I I don't have like
I don't have Google alerts for Alex
Right
I don't watch a ton of
Stevie really don't have
I can awareness of that world very much because
Much like Alex tell people to don't trust me I don't put a ton of that into my brain I look for
Sources and I have
Some aggregators that I trust and I speak out
Usually in the written form
Yeah that's mostly where I'm at I don't know I will say I don't believe
Legitimate news news
Delivered
Rick news not delivered
All of them
Sonora Leon McAdoo
Definitely not
Bigamist
I'm not guys don't take that out of contact
I do think
Places like the Washington Post
Have had articles
The fact that is lawyer
Is that the diesel performance arts
A response to that memes of him
Dressed up as
The Joker and stuff
But it's people saying
It's so stupid
Explain
Tiana mean
It cuz it's
It's something
So stupid
Hit you and your brain just kind of shuts off cuz like
Nah she's a character performance artist
Defense in
In terms of dressing up in a lizard mask
And all that stuff isn't necessary
Stop him from his children
The defense
View the character is needed
For the violent Outburst that he has
That's where he needs that depends
The comedy sketches that are funny
Those
He does not need excuse for making those any right-thinking person gets what he's doing
I don't even want talk
Any more episodes
About
Him him talking to his dad
Does dads like
What do I say
He thinks gay people give off
What do you argue about
Days are Caliente
BNA
This argument is so dumb that my my brain just does
We will not be dealing with
Will be continuing
But we will not be feeling anymore with him and his weird
Performance art
Is a performance artist
Even if he doesn't
Even if he does
All propaganda
It's
I don't want to tip my hand through hard Alex Doug quote Shakespeare.
As long as
But he doesn't understand that
Everybody plagiarize the New Yorker
Plagiarized
Also
I mean
We don't have time to get into it but
Shakespeare might not have been a person
It might have been a persona
Performance artist
In some ways
I will say I think
Christopher Marlowe
It is
He is a guy
And got a weird old head
Next
Back to Sandy Hook for a couple clips
Ostensibly
But
They guess it's not
This is
Alex claiming that the mainstream media lies about his position
He is enough himself why
He does not believe it
He doesn't believe that
Right there on two layers of Alex Jones
Does not believe
Beef Wellington of Lies
That I believe.
He goes and harasses family
He sues families
I believe kids died
That I said I see Devil's Advocate
Call Solomon
Because the media has been caught
Knowing
You can go watch the full deal
You just played it
Display the Daleks
You're not good at this
That's crazy
What he saying there is so stupid
Something like that I have no idea
I don't care
But the idea
I don't never heard anyone play me super family
Say that I do know
Big lizards
Absolutely
Have absolute
Their life
They put them threw up fresh
F****** hell
Every goddamn this is an instance where he's responsible for the
But I can't really control what your listeners due to some extent you know like
Fully responsible for their actions isn't fully responsible for every pocket
Filled with Catcher in the Rye in the sea
Espouse
What position is Alex clearly
There was a fake operation
Big conclusion that you can take from okay
If it is fake and no one died
Pretending
To keep
Alex is
Complicit
A hundred percent responsible
For the actions of his listeners
Dickhole pundits with ladies Oregon
Like you're you're saying that you never sued them and you've never been to Newtown
Doesn't mean anything
F***
You I've never been to New Town so
I'm off the hook
Guess what we got another lie about Sandy Hook coming up
Investigated all I'm saying is
You should have
Most fake shooting
We know that sat before they've been taught before
False Flags household
I'm not saying real kids didn't die because a majority of people online
So much
So that means a whole new
That's a whole new version of a Sandy Hook lie about his position
He was saying earlier that he doesn't know he can't figure it out
Now in this clip you think I'm inclined to believe that there was a patsy that got killed there was a shooting
Fake
Mass shooting
What
2 years ago
Complete actor based operation
And no real new information has come out in those two years
Can you
Point me to
Mass shooting
I can't but I mean Alex could show you plenty
There's no way there's a fake mass shooting based on what he thinks but I
I don't I don't I can't
I don't know
Again again golden moment Boston bombing
Now there you're just
Putting the seed of doubt in
Philippe over
Anything's
Any
Possible Circle
Absolutely
That's insane
Because
The
Man goes like this
The globalist
So doing this basically to push
Control
The large
One of the big narrative
To turn people against
It didn't work
I guess
Yeah
Volume
Well you're blaming the globalist you're actually doing is
Repeat it
Warmed-over and dress-up anti-semitism
So what you doing is
Brothers.
Clear slime to draw but trust me that is what's going on
Subconsciously
It is all going back to
This idea
Of a global cabal
Bankers
Jewish Elite
Who are
Controlling our destiny
So
Weird
Bandwagon anti-semitism
It's thrilling
Like how long
Hate the Jews
I don't know man
It's been a long time
Anyway
That whole thing
How many years are we going to do this
I don't know probably
22 everybody in the Middle East
Hey
Exterior
Alex
Was really trying to make the point that
He's not a victim
Although he is
Perpetrating
Incredible victory
Evans next FlipKey
Explains the D is
Thunder
Massive Attack
You might as well be tricky
Very nice thank you alright makeup for my love Lana Del Rey
Radiation is real
That is what's going on right now
I'm out
I don't know no preferences
I do know about tricky
Alright I'm sorry explained that he's under attack and it's all about
His character
Fictional character think
It's about his integrity
Understand that there is a hit
A strong man that is not me
There's an imposter
What's happening
And what's going on
And I think you're incredibly stupid
You think your audience is
I'm stupid
It's
It's crazy
It's just crazy
Like
You are protect
Goodbye a strawman
People are creating is a better person than you
Is fake is a better person than the Alex that we're looking at right now
That person at least has come
Consistency
Isn't a coward
Still work or at the very least
Is only wrong about one thing.
Unwanted
A f******
Absolute
But like
I'd like
What would I keep
Occurring in his voice is
Is pure nihilism
Like Dykes his is the destruction of
Everything
Like
That quote B
Steve Bannon
About
You know like
Destroying destroying the government
Entirely
Yay
Me listening to all of his stuff
It's almost like his main goal is to
Destroy
Any and all objects
Liked except the second
That's all we need
The Second Amendment
Obama had gone into your homes and taking your guns
I just want
If you want to live in the world of amerigeddon
Sure
I'm fine with it
Let's Groove
What's your favorite Rye
See if it's possibly better
As much
As much as people like to like Alex Jones want to say 37
1976 all over again
Those
Are often
The same power
Yeah living in that
SeaWorld
Believing themselves to
To be that when push comes to shove
I'm really going to do it
I'm really going to do that
Dude
Look
I'm a manic depressed
Okay if anybody like you got me on this one like you and I are too far as like
We don't
Necessarily disagree if you murder me
There's a part of me that's on your side good point
Exactly
Free speech
We wouldn't
Maybe kill ourselves
Absolutely all the all the visions of like zombie apocalypse like
Oh man I would be the guy running that game
F*** that if I could become a Hermit in the woods
I'll do that
Yeah but if not I'm out I don't want to fight contact
If your meds
Although maybe then I would be the leader of a roving band of cannibals possibility
We have to we have to
Deal with Alex having a little bit of a break
I got a little bit of a mental break
For the rest
Episode
How much more
We have
Five more clips
And
It's all a tree
Treatise on
The degradation of society
Great notnice first clip
What he believes is going on
Without we don't have the rights
Sioux passage anymore
Ditto
We can talk all day about that if you want
Let's all I'm saying is
Go back to a tribal Society
We're Men
Have
At the age of 13
Some sort of writer pass
Then we're good
Dude you going to say
You say that's a dumb thing to say we need to say this but it would be great if you'd like
Lay you down and make you
Take me to cut from 109
Put your hand to a nest
Quit making your apps
Get rid of one hand with bullet ants
Well
Except you love where he doesn't go
But first you look like the right to Spring I'm assuming that he does the
You know you shouldn't make predictable it's sweeping string sections
More simple than you think it's so stupid
You get to judge
Just that swell
The the violin
Violas
Let's go back to travel
Society
But you're talkin about the Arts
That's one thing but Alex I think is a little bit more worried about
Stem education
Has he complained about here
I need to go back to being human are calculators
I know how to do a lot of math
Calculator
Even though I haven't
Charge to mass in years formally
I could still do geography geometry
Text Spencer
Actually I can't do that
6 / 7
Is that bad. I don't know what the
12 point
Point or something
12.2
Some long those lines
I don't matter
When I was in school we had calculator
So one day we were talking about the Pythagorean theorem
Quadratic equation
Oh I thought that was
The quadratic is like - 4
B plus or minus
The square root of
No I don't remember
I don't remember it now but I actually proved
Each of those equations work breaking it down variable by variable
I had calculators
But I still did it cuz I was interested
There's a cop. Not even like an in-depth math guy they're people who like
Video x
Explanations of how
Pythagoras didn't think of that theorem the Wade
Like a building block
Geometry
He thought of it
Yes that's the weather
And so there's this really amazing confluence
How you see the world with
And how you find out
All of these different equation
Since back before you
Like you didn't get the
Look at how all of these squares fit together
I swear and then you keep tearing that apart and tearing that apart
And then you believe in God
Traces directly to like the
Golden ratio in the spiral of life
Comes out of
Pythagoras a rap group called The Lost Children
Milan
Fuckingawesome
It's a rap song about math
F****** great these dudes are so cool
I don't I don't support everything they're into but they're cool
Anyway
This Mexico
Alex
Is going
To really freak out
Because he remembered that one of his big points he likes to try and make is a
But no one has a memory
And that everything in the world is super important
The only thing that is super important
When you're going through life
Is having a memory
That seems like
Might be right
Considering the fact that he
He doesn't remember this
Exactly an
In this clip
He has forgotten something explaining I'll explain after
Please I enjoy listening to this
Really salient
Remembering
If you
There's information there's knowledge
You're five years old
You can interface the internet
You can speak you can do basic things but you don't know from life experience
For the memory
You know you forgot
That there's four ways to learn
He forgot that he's claimed that he was reading college-level books at age 6
What do you do at age 5
But he's saying that
You don't know how to trust information
You don't either
You dumb piece of s***, dumbass whole you stupid son of a b****
You judge yourself I don't even need to knock on the door you just busted your dumbass self
Hold on what's great you ask me in the middle of that clip is there a graph
And I'll post a screenshot of this cuz it's
F****** hilarious has taken a piece of paper
One of his Infowars
And he is flipped it over
And he is drawing a stick figure on it
That says 5
Lemon there is
Stick figure
Deidre
Bright
Goes up and then another stick figure
That's the grass
He successfully graft
Beijing
You should use a Texas
Instrument graphing calculator
Just put
5 years old and 75 years old into a text
Pornography on there has ever called
My friends
Calculator
Alex it's not a graph
You're making a dumb point
It is one of the most
Truism
When you're young
Can't really understand how to use information because you don't have the experience and maturity
The comes with being older
Also
Because
Idea of
Let's just say
If you are going to go by
Who is evaluating a
Do you think old people are
Your top
75 year old
No no no it's probably somewhere in the middle of adulthood
Probably late 20s early 30s
Probably move 144th
Variance equaling wisdom
Ace Parking
Stupid to ever talk to somebody
Don't tell me about the sixties or whatever
Because I lived
I would like listen you don't know what's going on
Right now
Don't tell me you knew what was going on then
When you are a f******
Experience
Informing
True
Is true there's exceptions
It's only true to a point
I agree and disagree with
Disagree with Alex's stupid
More more
Entirely
Fine 100% we can agree to disagree. That's totally fine
Not in my world
Let me write down a graph
I'm drawing a small stick figure looks like
Damn
Screenshot this
Oh no
Vertical
Oh my God no slope
That Alex
And then all the way down here is me giggling at me
Would you like to draw another line to the side of a William Shakespeare over there
Because it's time for the Shakespeare Library I do remember that
Context in the corner of his paper
He has drawn
Basically
Triangle
Without a bottom
Uptown
Like a parabola
Basically
Alright be like two bases of the triangle and up at the top
And he's making the argument that you are
Like that weed we always will
Trying to make the argument that
When you're young and when you're old
You're down like you're you you're not as smart and when you're in the middle of the your life.
Your Peak Avenue bring Shake
Mobility
Experience life Revelations you hit a peak
And then your brain cells begin to die
Become a child again
The child
You're only wants the man
Three Times a Lady
Once Bitten Twice Shy
Cool Alex cool cool cool cool
I'd like
He seems to know
A lot more Shakespeare than I would have expected him to do but yeah but these are all like
Generally
I've known quotes
Yeah but the definition
I would argue that that is
Sixty to seventy percent of the population
Unaware of that
If possible
All the world's a stage even if
Tampa Tribune
Shakespeare
You you have a general idea of that like you heard that from somebody in a bar you and be like
Holyshit
Here's what I would say
I don't think that Alex does any researching or is engaged
With
Substance
Now
But I'm not saying that you haven't
I believe you did do a lot of reading earlier
Seems like it he's not an idiot
He's a dumbass but he's not an idiot like you know something a lot of
We need a glossary of our
Particular definition of the
Insults that we have thought that out
Illiterate
Incapable of reading isn't capable of
Integrating Factor
But you have learned
Into a coherent system
Lip reading facts
Is what's
The issue and it's easy to have quotes
He knows he doesn't really know how to make them
Threat anyway as the Bible said
Even the devil
Scripture scripture
Is this
I know
This Is the End
My friend and
I don't even know how to describe
But he starts ranting about the Rites of Passage
And then tell the story from his life that we're going to get into
I don't even care
Here we go
But if you don't give yourself
Text
You're not involved you don't develop
In your entire life
Is a five-year-old
At 13 years of age
The shaman
You know what you go through testing into rituals
411 libertad
To see if you were an adult yet
Leave somewhere else do something else go join alcohol and other
The normal
Intersex
What the f***
Is a ground work
It's a passage
Isn't to be fair in some cultures
He's not far off
I mean
Making an overgeneralization
What he's done
Is
Explain what
Entire world knows
Tubi
The historical right
Yes
Over
Now
I want to say
I don't have time to attack
If that's
If that's where you're starting
Fine now
Let's see where he goes with it
In this next clip
I very rarely at a loss for words
So thrilled
So thrilled I'm tickled
Thrilled correct please don't yell over this
Is the new adult
Is the peak
In physical and mental overall Palace using knowledge
To this level
You're you are at your Peak
Can most men I know
I want to get the approval
Children
So that's stupid
They don't have
Children
Right
No
That's not what I was thrilled about
Live It Up
To point out like
You're dumb
You dumb. Dumb this is stupid
Where is it what is
What is the talkative mad piss people don't have kids when they're younger I guess
Right
50s world of light
If you like your life or anything like that
And you hated everybody in that timer
It doesn't matter if having those kids would ruin your life and you don't want to have them
You know you work
Able to take
Now he's going to get into
Some really
Really unfortunate
Uses of language in this neck
Section
Talking about people having
This is not a good I
Oh I mean it is what's on his mind
I couldn't imagine
Tell me any other circumstance
Be involved in his life
So
You going to play some more stuff
About people failing to reach these rights
The passage such as having
The kid
His own life
It is
One of the things he says
We're going to have to stop and talk about for maybe half an hour
Cuz it's straight up
Straight up the best thing I've ever heard in my life
Nope
Definitely not
College
The priest
Do you got to make money
I had to pause there just cuz that's so horror
That's so fucken horrible
So
So what's this
But why is he
Any of this mean
He's angry so this is about
Video supposed to be
Is this the new information
Women in the forties Oparin
That's how we know those kids were real
Better argument
This is
Wow
Seniors is whenever
One that
That presupposes
Is the cultures
Not allowed to change ever or at all
Hopefully
Even beyond that
And I want it I want to remind
Everyone
He says even by his own
Recollection
Something's wrong with him
Perfect smile
He's a great man
Isn't sales all the time
He just tells you the right things
To do doesn't give himself a God damn
So
Different Virgo let the rest of this play I don't know.
This is where he transitioned sorry
This is very transitions into his own wife
And it's nice
Then I just of a sixteen-year-old I was 16
You want to party anymore
I grew up
The fight song
Ben 10 fight with full grown man
College years old
F-16
I was a leader
So he's going to say more about his history there but let's take a second he didn't have sex with 156
He's talked to the nmac 250 x
If you're a fifteen-year-old and you're having sex with college girls
You're being statutory rape
But be that as it may
It's not that
His version of the Rites of Passage
Complaining about the people are going through
Being in fight
Yeah
I f***** a lot when I was young
I don't understand what your what Your
Definition of toxic masculinity this is the definition of ugly
Female discus portable
There are only two ways to
Whether or not
Yeah absolutely a dick
What a f****** dick
Outlook
These kids now
Not f****** everybody when they're 16
Because conservative
150 women if we apply
Ratio
Describes
His listenership
Right
So
It's 45 million
And we put it somewhere around 3
We apply that
So that would be roughly is that would be roughly
Speaking in a week
Speaking in days
Actually closer to like 1.4 million visits the website
Please send me like 10 times higher
No more than that.
/ 40
Round round
That's a lot
Let's engage
With the idea that it's 16 he's had
Sex with 150 different women
Conservatively
So if you've you finish your thing and I got an idea
Are you really excited cuz I got an idea generally reach sexual maturity
Give or take
To procreate according to the Roosevelt
150 in 3 years
It's fifty a year
10-week
He's having sex with a different woman every week for 3 years
In the time when you in 15 your age
Sophomore in high school
Right
All through High School
He's banging a new lady every week
In Austin
Yeah
Alright fair enough
Cheerleaders
Bad Girls
Crocker crocker doesn't matter really in the last couple episodes going on I like I talked
That's gross
You had a point
Siri
I like theories
Fuct 100
50 women
In one night
In in
So
He spent a week in Japan
There could be video
I don't know baby.
But
Sure
Wood
Pulisic
His behaviors
I think you'd be dead by now though
30 years later
Yeah I mean if it eroded his brain in
A developmental phase it is possible that that part of the brain wouldn't grow back
So I can't vouch for this part
You gotta assume he wasn't wrapping it up
With everybody
You're young you're stupid
You know
If Alex Jones is used a condom
He did it under duress with a gun
He's like Hey listen
I don't normally use a condom but I do respect the way you're
So here is the rest of his about
Why about
It's absurd and it's irrelevant
To the point he's trying to make
No that's too
Pure
Bullshittery bracket
It's yelling at each other
In the clarity of us not yelling at each other
Masculinity equals fighting and having sex with lots of women
Those are what make you there
Part of the big problem with Arkansas
Humanity
We are also heard by Metallica
Human race
Is hurt
Bye
The fact that we
Like this is something
That I do not
Appreciate
And he's not in
But it is
The fact that
A lot of times we forget that
That we are
Sure we're not
We're not some hyper evolved
We're still f******
We're still we're still beholden to our route
Aspire for greatness
Do your physical work
We should be all be able to detach ourselves from this
The world of the world
The world
Alright
I'd love it
The rest of this clip.
Cuz he had a radio show the local radio show in Austin
Is Bragg
23 I would send it
I have a son
I got a big Empire
I couldn't believe it
If we can't believe it
But also like
Who's on who's like 12 who works
Infowars
There's got to be another older song
He might have more than four kids
He might have more kids than he is even claimed the secret number of kids
I don't know what's going on now
He has paid for abortions in the past
Maybe that was his long toddlers like
24 I had a son
Although the pain for multiple abortions just make sense if you're banging out 150 girls at 6 p.m.
Big lot more girls than anybody would appreciate
But also like
Maybe his dad
Just practice
Had to pay out a lot
If it was during this.
Were you saying he was massively sexually active
Being sexually active
No worry about it like a f******
Mentality of
Belk Bowl
All over the place that's
I didn't care about them
Care about anybody but me
I cared about
Even if it isn't like
Just about the sex
Part of it even if it is about that being a writer
Do whatever it's still bad
If you're doing it that much
The compulsion
I don't know if that's
Things I've heard
It's possible insulation not for our show
I mean he just goes out gallon more about this
I cut the rest of it and she goes out
Cuz he just yells more about how he's real
Is that
It does have a
Looking back on my career like this
This is your life kind of element of it
The end of that is
You know like Twilight
And I'm not going to have a job in 6 months somebody please
Does the feeling of like where did I go wrong
Right maybe everywhere but
Has a feel of
I think I did every
Everything right well you know what I'll bring myself into a tiny bit
That I can definitely relate to in terms of like
Stuff I didn't stand up
I knew even when I had those feelings
That they were Petty
They were basing ego
Absent these things like when I first started stand-up I created
Successful show
In Columbia Missouri
Every week on Tuesday
Scott hundreds and hundreds of dollars for the bar
Do that sort of thing
When I'm trying to make an argument for why don't more people care about what I do
And that is just Petty
I regret that I was caught up
I knew even when I was making those arguments
I know I'm wrong to feel this way but I don't exactly know why
It's insecurity
It's a feeling of not being valued to the same level that you value what you do
Ran its natural but it is embarrassing
Out of someone who's a propaganda
Who makes millions of dollars a year selling phones
It's super embarrassing also super embarrassing
Cumin the same episode
Where you're denying your own statements
About in order to demonize the media
Like the thing I think about that that whole ego now
Is especially when it comes
Is the arena that
Most familiar with Drew
Right
There is a certain amount of that word egoism
That Wilkie
Keep you going
And
You can't think you can't think you suck if you want to
Right people to like you there is that
You know
Narcissist
Like
Alex Jones
Regardless of whether or not
He's a
Pathological
Narcissist
Bagel one
It is always about
Yeah
Has served
That's really that's really one of the traits that has served him well on his
Assent to millions of dollars so there's a certain amount of that ego where you think
A
This is a
Cancerous
Double edged sword
Is what it is can be used to help you like there's a reason that
Whenever who was John
Jon Ronson
And the psychopath test
There's a reason that when you test
Far more likely to be Psychopaths
Talk about anybody else
Your
Probably going to be more willing to do all the s***
To get you into places
Because you're taking such high risk
With your own reputation
What's wrong
Again
You might lose it all and I think that's why you my people
Cannot reset in craps you were talking about
They came up in my mind is the idea of like a weapon that's productive
Will kill you there are a lot of parasites
FedEx
Wilshire General Tso parasites
You can have that are advantageous for a while and then they
End up hurting you
Futurama reality
You can have
You can have a tapeworm
And you'll end up losing weight
You lose
Listen to the things like that
This
Narcissism and this unwillingness to deal with reality on realities term
Is a parasite
That's within Alex Jones
And not only that but he is absolutely enabled by
Unfortunately the culture for him
But but that's
One of the things that he
He can ride that wave on
Unfortunate
His toxic masculinity
Does
Engender people
Supporting him
Yeah people who sort of identify with that is ultimately that
He slept with 100
50 women
That's not going to hurt him
Listening hi-five themselves
And well and I'm sure they like
Mama exactly
Because that's that's a certain wish
Fulfillment fan
For those
Toxic masculinity
People who watch a show
Can't go back to
That's all it's all
Anyway Alex you suck
You suck
Suck real bad out I forgot
Monster I forgot also apologize
Do every
Sandy Hook family
Please
Apologize individually
Very least
Apologize
You're lying about your position and claiming that everyone says
That you never said those things
Hypocritical coward
Piece of s***
You garbage human being and I actually forgot to play the out of context
Strop
We get the Ender heino
It might be a high note
Start your own website
We have it isn't knowledge fight.com
You son of a b****
Alex
We have taken your advice you want more people entering the infowar and we have
We've heard the call and we have taken it up
Well you can check us out and we are on Twitter
Shall you be home
William Shakespeare
Twitter at knowledge underscore fight
Believer of you where we were getting
A lot of really nice
Very nice
Joining up and I appreciate all respond as well as I can to email
Immediately
Patreon
You get to join us
Like what would you describe
Well I mean
Are you saying
The same sort of thing that would describe
Our listeners are donate
Yeah I mean like there's there's a certain Siri-like
Two-word phrase
Is it
Alright
Alex