Damned important
I have great respect for knowledge but I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Alex B
Fight.com
Stop sign
Even though I started what's up
My first
First cellular phone
I have a lot of memories of my parents having one of those
Turn Wheel song
In the hole
Terrible
We are both
What they decided
Like that was a presentation
You think back on that
I don't know if I had
Some point
But I don't remember any
Specific Like A Garfield phone
Cell phone I got
Really late
He's ready to have a thumb.
I had no interest
No
I removed my parents house
Second house phone
I really enjoyed at that point in my life the ability to
To not because
Yeah I give it is all before social media
I would go out and I come home and there be
And I really enjoy
I wasn't that popular I enjoy the aspect of like there if I'm out and about I don't
Have
Like
Something
I won't be necessary
Found ya
Very fast
Don't even remember that
I can remember it I don't
It's hard for me to remember exactly what I love so much about it is dealt with time
But I remember enjoying
When I was 18
I got a cell phone I got a flip phone
And then I had
Forever
I didn't get an iPhone or any kind of
Smartphone
Maybe
It's pretty close to that
A very long time
I don't know I don't I don't I don't remember that
Sprint
Whatever for free with a plan
I had the answer I had that
And then I got a I got a smartphone just cuz I kind of gave in
The flip phone was breaking
Years overdue for an upgrade you just wanted
All right sign
Please sir
Super Lotto
Technology I am not super into the gadget
My buddy Nikki gift
Super into iPhone
Pretty early
But I didn't
Any of it
Did you have a nice
No
Holyshit
I don't think so
Home
I'm somebody else but I messed around with four
Yeah yeah buddy else's for a minute
You toss it out the window
I did when I was dry
This is how f****** stupid I am
Like I had a car in
Missouri I didn't have any of the jack
Plug
IPhone and I didn't have to be
CD player in the car
The stuff that I would think I was choosing
The radio by that blinded
I want to take my laptop
Put it in the passenger seat of my car refuse
Oh my God
Very very very dumb
Do much about tech but I do know a lot about Alex.
Can you do
What is that
Which is in my future
Probably
We're coming off here Wednesdays
Very long
Yeah
Today.
Taken in order
Episode and so today what I wanted to go
Off the reservation
Completely we're going to do Alex Jones episode
You might call it a wacky Friday episode free-for-all Friday
Something along those lines
Palate cleanser
And on top of that you are about to leave for vacation
You'll be gone for a week
Oh yeah but we recorded some episodes
In advance
And then
Get some fill info
Dorothea the time you'll be gone
Yeah it is the super
Primly supremely lucky Partners mother
Paid for
Tripped
That is good never have
Even f******
Yeah
But I look forward to you coming back and being
Restarting Roadies
Of course
So I hope you have a great trip but I didn't want to send you off with
Episode that was to
I'd like another present
Episode
Africa
I got a big luggage
Jordan today going to be
Ahead of time
So
Let's see I recommend that we should do
As we should say thank you just people who are
Sign-up and sporting show
Thank you so much you are now a policy walk
I'm a policy wonk the door
Next kit I guess I'll let you on our policy walk
Next
This name
Hid
He died
Any of the
Sure I apologize that I do not know what the correct pronunciation is but I appreciate y'all the same
You're an alcoholic
I'm a policy wonk
People donated on an elevated level we appreciate that very much
Next
Veter
Thank you so much
You are all now wonderful techno
Freakishly large
Thank you so much
All I have to add
You must need
Absolutely
Seasoning or whatever Eminem
Not stay with
This episode it
For a long time people have been asking that we get back into Jim Bakker
No
What were you people have
There have been a lot of recommendations
How did Jim Bakker stuff is one-note it's so the same
Spoiler alert tried to record an episode that we in the middle of it
This is not an episode
Episode banquet
With his family out of his remember
Oh my God look at this great pancake
If we take a day off of the Epic
We recorded
Not 99% of the time but sometimes I think I was probably one of them
Bisbee Breakfast
Hilaire amazing
Pouring a disaster
I think 20 minutes and we were doing it we realized
What are we just going to say this is stupid over Everett
This is from a bucket
Hahaha
The best parody of yourself
Absurd
So
For Jim Bakker
Much like people who eat his buckets to do
Episode
That is recent
Episodes
And I was like
I was almost
I almost fell for the siren song again
Because there was a 3
Part episode that is the clearing out the warehouse sale
3 full episodes
Exact same place
So I decided I was going to
I was going to do in a rare instance
Other media coverage
Direct me
I decided to cover an episode
That actually got a bit of
This is something a little bit
The episode where Jim Bakker
Invites
Michelle
Sure
Just got your selling a gold coin
And prayer to each other and also
Donald Trump goddamnit I
The media covered
I was making fun of
A minute-long clip of him trying to sell this coin
I want to see what else happened on that episode
Is that was best for the tree
Of course so I decided to check in on that
Episode this is as good as I can do for you
I could take somebody out something somebody else cover to be like what else is going on here
Specifically about
Well after that we can specifically
More f***** up things that a guy selling a magic coin
Well the most f*****-up thing is he
It is actually true
So here is the first clip where we get our Dancing Queen
Introduction given us the other voice over and then
When we get to meet
Lance wallnau
Welcome to the Jim Bakker Show coming to you from the village of Morningside
Beautiful Ozark Mountain today is day two with our special guest he's a director of the land
Learning group and a bestselling author welcome doctor lancewallnau.com
Today is Monday
I'm Penny to Baker and now please give a warm welcome to my parents and the host of the Jim Bakker Show
Jim and Lori Bakker
Great to have you here on Gray Street and our special guest
Today
Wow
You are on The Cutting Edge
When did God first
Call you
To be a voice
The church
It really
Electing the write-off
The right presidents the right
Senators record
So real quick first question is
Theocratic politics
Kind of going
What religion is a scam to guy politics
George conservative
Call you Tyrone
Real blunt
I personally think that
It was when I started hearing
A Frenchman like Rick Joyner and you
Talkin about
Where America was that
Because like so many Christian
I just wanted to preach spiritual
Kingdom optimistic messages are focusing revised
But I heard something in your voice
Andy and the way in which you would grounded in real concern
It was a cash register
Oh my God
I myself
And part of the problem
Because Ashley
As a as a preacher as somebody had it had an audience
I was
Ignoring
What was happening
In the controversies of my country in the world in order to focus on Solutions
That's our Christ Center
I would say that solutions that are christ-centered is what your church is about that should be what you're focusing on
I believe
Beyond
Diffuser which is always dissatisfied
I was really afraid of losing
C3 status
So what you doing okay
Thunderdome
Floor give a s***
I do love I do love the Brilliance of the
Buttering up Baker
Strategy
Waterbender
It was because of you
Jim Bakker
Actually talk about religion
It's really difficult about something like this is like
People who are
Taking in the message
Probably are doing so in
Yeah or at least without
Swimsuit
They are taking it in Macon
I want to get conned by this guy
The consequences Witcher - are precipitated
That's barely I don't believe all of them
For signing up
Specifically for the
Guile
I supposed to be the way to put it
Maybe
Think about something
But this is just proof that if there was a God these people would be
Very little research into
Episode because
Who gives a s***
Absolutely but I did want to find out a little bit about who Lance wallnau
Absolutely
Which makes sense
Seeing that either got your on the
The Jim Bakker Show
Board member for the oak
Group listed by the Council on american-islamic relations is part of the islamophobic network
In America
To combat climate
Atwork initiative the Royal Oak initiative
There are groups
August 2011 the oak initiative published a book called Islam versus the United States
Which purported to expose the quote all-conquering characters many of the followers of Islam
They were to disseminate material that
62 invalidate the idea that a mosque is a form
Church
It argues that quote even in the watered-down version
And it's clear that this religion promotes
The destruction
Or enslavement of all who do not adhere
Quote watered-down bright as though that's a
Rights
Come on guys you guys are
Someone else who sits on the board of the Oakland A's
Is Alex Jones General William
Noted islamophobe of the highest order
Name is Walnut
Driving me insane
They're going to have to
Then sort of similarities
Lagoon
It'll come up
Slant rhyme
Support
Made a video
You're back
Sorry video for initiative in Islam is not a religion
It should not be protected by the First Amendment
I believe he based on is on determined
Islamic belief that Muslim
How to destroy the United
State score
In order to bring in Sharia law
Muhammad
Eventually there's going to be a whole country
Take down
Institution that's what we got to do
The initiative is a major portion
Major player in the world of
Islamophobia
These narratives being
Perpetuated
Right wing
Conversation
But it's not
So they don't like
The oak initiative is also fiercely anti-lgbt
And in 2015 Michigan
Rainbow painted on it
Accompanied by the text
Not born this way
And homosexuality is a behavior not a civil right
This is a run-of-the-mill bigot organization to do whatever it takes to support
Straight white male Christian
Supremacy
So of course
You not be surprised to learn that their super into Trump
I basically think
Absolutely
Anyway that's about all you really need to know about Lance wallnau organization
So you know
Succession of evil convent
World
He's appearing on another grifters
Religious scam program
So you can
But I don't want to be one of these guys who goes ad hominem
Let's put that aside and let the man speak
So it is like sklep we find out when
Lance got politically involved
Apparently was after hearing
Jim Bakker
That doesn't give us
To the moment that I got called by accident to the a trump meeting
And I came out of
And
And I walked out I was supposed to be there was like
I went up to the doorman
So real quick
But
That's in the original of the audio
Like
Might have forgotten her
I'm not sure but I think you have
Yeah it's a murder his way through her dad
Gotcha
And I said
List because I thought it was a mistake made a big Ministry of something
And the guy says
That's what who are you
He said I heard you in a little meeting down there in Florida
You better say something
Oh my God
Be humble just watch
I spoke
And after I
All I knew was.
I heard the Lord say
Some people
He gets invited to a trump meeting that makes him politically motivated I suppose which is
Men on some live over you
These meetings are
As much recruitment as they are bored
Let's get the monarchs look at all these meme makers
Galvanized
And there's that there's a strata
OG doll desk
I don't believe that God said
Wrecking Ball
Correctness
Woodside
I don't know it's got
Is there a is there a First Amendment in the Bible
You get to call people all kinds of racial epithets and you have to
You don't have full free will that is really f***** up that I've never thought about but their conception of Heaven
Mustang
Include absolute
The Edward around all
Should I lose my job
No they honestly believe that it in their Heaven neighborhood if I
These people are so so
I never thought about that but that is pretty weird
Is a wrecking ball
And this is Miley Cyrus
Sure
While he was there at this
Specific
Went to there was
What he describes as a black TV channel
But it's not
And they were doing some
Put it there shooting some footage or so
The details on this or sketch
Right right right
True it might be true
If it's true
Also Jim and Lori
Love this
They think this
Unreal
One of the
It was
But it had like a hole
African American
I know they see me standing
And they said
Number to Michael Cohen
Microphone
About
Wrecking Ball
Everywhere you go
I was made out of bed maybe I don't know how I got in
I don't know how I got on I guess this is what I'm supposed to do
Supernatural problem pastor
Answered
He got a catchphrase
That's great
So I guess maybe this happened and then people
Maybe someone wrote an article of it
Crazy weirdos as sharp as a wrecking ball
I don't know
There's a couple of other instance
Taking credit for starting
I'm not positive I'm going to give him credit for any of them
Ball type language highly stressful situation
Ricky's Michael Cohen
Subconscious pulls up
You've already heard Miley Cyrus
Borderline
Back to the Future Marty McFly playing
Rock and roll
Music
Like that kind of
That kind of
Bananas
So this episode
Is largely
Contingent
Jim Bakker
Having
And about how Trump
What is here because
The divine inspiration
Thanks to the actions of the church
Have brought Trump
Into office
To save the church
From the scourges of
PC culture at the Socialist
All the other
Koenigsegg
Absolutely
So
That be really what this whole interview is about
It's really weird to hear him say this about
The Democratic Party
Has been taken over
It's not the Democratic Party
Your mom is death like my mom could be
A Kennedy.
Mcrat a Reagan Republican
Right
The left
Has a movement within it
To seize power switch
New element
That is
Taking over the party and pulling
That's for the socialism comes from switch you got is there from
They're saying
The normal Democrat
In their own parties taking over
But he's not going to be able to
He probably won't he probably won't
Insane for them to be doing this weird via Craddock propagate nonsense
Like God brought us Trump that show and then be like
Their party
It's been pulled
Extreme
He didn't realize what he was explaining
Realized
Democrat
And a Reagan Republican
Bike race
I think you might have
Been aware of that on
Subconscious
Perhaps
It's it's
Definitely
It's just because the left has gone too far it's not that
Democrat may have changed after the Civil Rights Movement
And the Republican Party may have gotten more extreme when we elected a black president
For everybody
Drip too hard right
It definitely has nothing to do with race
Doesn't feel like
Because actually what's going on is
Is the Justice Democrats have come around
So the justice
Democrats
What they're doing
Is being sneaky
Alright alright alright alright
No justice Democrats of that organization that I Grande.
Okay
Jesus
I've read some interviews with
People who are involved
Like getting it going at their whole idea was to create
Centralized fundraising
Type of thing
So they could run wouldn't have to worry about going out and doing fundraising
Taking care of a lot of that so the politician
Good Apollo
Because you can't have publicly-funded election
They were trying to do this
Maybe that's
Woefully idealistic of Us 2
Any human could actually follow through with that well
Planet Fitness
That's just another strategy
It's totally legal
These folks around the Jim Bakker Show
They got other ideas about what they're up to
Earlier about
American Idol
Election for President
Another word
You could also
For congressperson
I don't
Because
Pretty much
Congresswoman congressman
And if you were out to go get a movie role
So there's a new job
So as long as you're an activist in your community
Is you if you have the charm
You're the candidate they're going to be behind
Social media
To get to your grandkids get some people
It's a new America
Irene
Don't think
Thinks that he said something
I didn't say anything bad
No cuz all he's describing is like all right there's an organization that helps
Support activist
Who are charismatic ineluctable get elected
Isn't that pretty
That's what it is
Yeah
How is this different
Like
Corporation
These are these are
Middle
Center-right or
Center-left
Candidates
I just want everybody
Come to the middle and I'm
I'm sure that giant Corporation
Really are pushing
Center
Centrist
Democrats of is it not
Weird
The third-party has a farm
People
Next
The narrative
I think there's some pretty races
Framing going on here
Your your top 3 most
Controversial
Freshman Concord
Women all coming through
Come on
To get some
The demography
So this is how
This is how fast
Real quick easy
Three non-whites congresswomen are from Central
Demographic
Write the only reason
Possibly be elected
It is because they are now
And Justice Democrats
You can literally
Breitbart
Which means this
Acting
Your Hollywood entertainment
Your
Academia your media it's
Stage
Search for what people want
Then you have to go find the empty suit
That you could fill with a candidate who will do what you want them to match
What the market wants
The media
Outlets
With
This strategy
So is to create
Innocent
You don't think there's other Congress people with more experience and more intelligent things to say that
It's really weird that intelligent
Experience are so important
To him when he thinks
From God
Bugatti
Really
Clear
What
This is the narrative
People that like
They're empty suits
Every f******
Congressperson
Is a
It's like it's all Alexandria ocasio-cortez
Revising s*** over and over and over again
Solitary
The present
I think it's still there.
I8
Just dumb
Something up with that
How dare you you idiot the whole f******
Is there a representative
Represent
A larger group of people right
Well now
That's a fair point
You get to off the hook for all that like
Yeah okay if this person was so terrible that people would vote them out by
No it's impossible
Because all elections are rigged 3 million illegal immigrants
And then words
Nowhere to go
AOC
Tlaib Omar
But
Gio's
The stupid the mediator stalks them cuz they report after casting
Now Trump
Bike
Contract
Virginia
Either Communications genius really want to hear the Jessie
Certification for this
It's going to be disappointed
That's the amazing thing
Canby
Reelect
In spite of the fact
That all the Machinery is being worked against
Absolutely
The social media purging that's happened
But he's a smart man
So what is she been doing
What is Brad Parts Galpin
They've been collecting the data of everyone they wanted
Talk to
So that
Regardless of what social media gets shut down
They're prepared to talk to their 50 60 70 million people
Directly
The presidents got
Plans to stay in communication
He's really
Communication
He's a genius because he has 89
Innovative
Trump brings you
An email list
Shity bar comedy show
Strives to create
But you've been involved with them that's I don't use email
He's a genius
Elementary
Rules of the internet
Social media
You get an email
That's the whole trip
I
Really
Alex has been kicked off MailChimp
Those companies can still give you the boot
Single people send out an email every day they'll just
Beautiful tree
So
To my grandma
This next Club involves
His name
So much that I don't remember his
I can't wait
The argument
The church
Trump elected
Ankle support
It's it's
You know
The constituent parts
They were the one
Which is kind of part of
The mythology that keep
People on board
Businesslike while we were the one
Who made
This happened
Got a fallacy like we we did all this we can't give up now
Then
After he makes that argue
He said he explained
Like
It knocked me out of my
Okay
The church doesn't understand
What's
We were the decisive
Factor
Got Donald Trump in
Donald Trump has been
Greatest gift we have had
In terms of
A resistor
Against
The devil
And a promoter
Of a world economic prosperity
Hold on. Hold on.
Hey buddy
Is it the old one
What song is this
What are we what are we doing
What are you doing here
For somebody who's existing in this space
I cannot believe he would die
Great because he's establishing a world order of prospect
He's doing it
About George h.w. Bush about
For 30 years
Nudestix
It's so unfair
Yeah
It is
Wall now
Paul Wall now
It's Lance
Discusses
The Trump had disturbing
But
He
Baker
And Lori Bakker
I think it's hilarious
And so every please
But what time you having a Freudian slip
He said I want to make my company
I don't think my country but her
Business
It's not funny
Because
CEOs on
CEOs are in
The mentality should be very different
So the Freudian
Slip of this is my company
I think it's even f***** up
To look at running the country like a busy
Is unhealthy
Unproductive to
Public Works
Yes that's what it is
My company
Holy
Here's the here's the worst part
Understands what Freudian slip
Right
He said
Slip of the tongue would be fine
Instead he said Freudian slip
Which means that he believes
Trump literally meant
Tuesday
That he's running his company
His company
I guess that means we could be fired
Well
Very literal
Yeah
So earlier
Continue
Lance is making the argument that Trump is a gift from God he is divine intervention
And I haven't really learned that yet
We've had a face
Christian cult
That has been prophesied
Nnc
Provide
I've been feeling a burden of Prayer
Fasting
A divine
The form of a wrecking ball
That would be Donald Trump
For the sake of God's people
So get that get that cash
Came in like a wrecking ball
Divine intervention for church
So
You know that's one catchphrase
Sell his products
And we find out another catchphrase
We definitely heard Alex uses a lot
No it's not that one
Atlanta claiming to come up with as well
And then this really becomes your prophetic intercessory prayer guide
Because
Regarding Trump
Regarding who it would be what he would do
When I'm down
Bring up the fact that the media would enter a. Called Trump derangement
I was the one
Point Reyes
The right-wing media
Actually invented lockherup
But I really regret that I really like my operator equipment
But it was just for Roseanne
This this is one of the many
We have with Alex
You have
Trumpets
Divine
Trump
Prince Andrew
Cool with daneshjoo
D'Souza
Get er done
Haha
More of that before
He's got a cell
The prayer guide
Right that's part of the package
Prayer guide
90 minute lecture on DVD
Gold coin
Now we're going to learn a little bit more
Doughboy
It starts
I didn't say that I said it starts back
Now
24-karat gold-plated
Is
Set me a silver coin
Silver
And we put the 24 karat gold
Trump Cyrus image and
Isaiah 45 in the back the reason I wanted to do this
Is because
I was saying we have to have a
Prayer call
Which one
End
And what we need is a point of contact to be praying
That the spirit of God will continue
To put
Donald Trump in a position
Where they
Wrecking ball is going to exposed
Structure of the institution
Corrupt
And that every weapon
Boomerang
Edxposed
So there's a couple things that are real sucked out there
I mean
A laughing about that story
I just feel like
There's a there's a
Advantage story of
The Bible is
By Bartholomew Kayla brought him a silver coin
That was a really interesting
Things are weird story
Man I wanted I want to know
Because Jim Baker's laugh right
Audience
Spitting in their face and you'll still love me
I'm telling you that God has brought about this
President
Who demands gold
It's insane
It's really it's like Testament
2 house
Get people on board with x
Scream work you can make that framework you can mold it however you want
People on board
Ostensibly for
These like a Christian principle you can
Go whenever you want
Yep
It's not that people are not going to hold
Your feet to the fire
Astonish
It is absolutely
How they have
Same thing with
In the past he got everyone on board of his aunt's herne Anti New World Order I can specifically
You want
Because what's behind it isn't
What is a
In front isn't what you're actually operating
Jim Bakker wants your Goddamn money
You found religion
Is a really good way to get people's money
He's not allowed at now Trump is
Working real well for him and turned the grift
Something about Trump
Directly contradicts something about religion
You're going to be able to make it work
Got it because he
You don't have to worry about what God ever
The Bible yes is 100%
But Trump is a nude
No big deal and then
You have Alex
Who like
It was white
That was behind everything
Icky packaged it
In such a way
Very attractive
KSI New World Order
You know someone comes around
Even pulse
Joke
Every single one of the people in the audience
Just kidding.
Every single
Fwiw they all look like
Retirees
They're all pretty old
Slow Hands
I feel bad I don't make fun of the elderly
It made me feel even more sad
Pennywise tricking old people
If you want to know why
Is Lance
Just listen to it
This is a religious show
This is a
Jim Baker's Evangelical hour
Commercial
I mean it is.
You know it's
Supposed to be a show about Christianity
Right religiously
Focused all of this is
Quote scripture
There is a scripture on the back
Bitcoin
Help you connect with other people praying at the same time as you
Fair enough
So what about politics
It's important to also take other context clues from pigs
See if you should listen to him
This one
Strikes me is like
I really didn't have a civics
Less than in my head
Know the difference
Between the day out
I thought in education
Nope I'll watch Christian television
Then I realized
Inch of ground that we have an occupied
Is being occupied and weaponized
So what he's saying
Is that I didn't know anything
And then all of this propaganda that is
So anti deep state
Type stuff came around and I learned so much
Strongly argue that you still do not know anything about that
Number of
It's the
The exact
Play doubt by
Conservative right-wing
They are so
Effective
As
They are only effective
In terms of attack and being under threat
So as long as an office
Or there is
The presumption of democratic control of Congress
Or the presidency
Then they can
They can make all the money they want
Congress and the presidency is in the hands
Republican
They cannot function anymore and therefore has to
Create
Entirely new
Bigger bad guy
Exact same problem
Gyros
Like you got Sylar and he's like completely overpowered what are you going to do
How to create some sort of other Chick Bad Guy seriously
Has been there all along know about
It's complete b*******
This is the strategy that the right with median
Needs to use
This is what
Now I have a second layer
Bulshit
Like
He is one of the board members of the oak Institute
I do not believe that before Trump got in he didn't have any understanding of some
No kind of Civic
He's trying to pretend that he hasn't been involved in like this
Agitating islamophobic anti-lgbt
You world
Previously to Donald Trump
This is this is what he's about
Just presenting it this way
Probably because he knows a lot of other people didn't know s*** about Civic
Fix before he's validating strategy
Just like you idiots out there
It's a manipulative strategy
At best
It's evidence you shouldn't listen to him because he's just been
Suckling off the tee
Of right-wing propaganda
Let's learn
Either way
Get the f*** out
You suck
Absolutely
It is next week we get a little bit of an indication
A similarity without
Just basically repeating one of Alex's big narrative
On the debate
We are we are literally
Market adjust
Without Trump in office
Of a collapse of our entire economic sis
So we had a financier protecting us
Everything would fall apart
The globalist
Stop
Boy
Really really really want to know what Bible
Market adjustment is what you're talk about in what year
Calling us
Church
Yeah unreal
401k
And make sure that you start
What the f***
Are you guys doing
It's pretty strange
It's almost like
You know if Jesus were around he would slip over Jim Baker's desk
Smitten
These dudes be
Obviously apocalyptic
Feelings on the rise of corn
Or whatever
Yes but the Antichrist is coming
And also that means
There's got to be a false prophet
Right I mean they work together
Has done some thinking about it
It's
Seems like
Well I'll let him explain it may not be a person
1 broadcast
Price.
Is in the Earth
And we could see that
Yes yes to work with the false prophet
I no longer
The false prophet
Is originating as a purse
Heading up a religion
I think the false prophets already there
I think the false prophet is a world ruler
Just like if you see perversion it's a
World ruler it's the same spirit
In Thailand and Bangkok in the sex slave industry as it isn't what
A world ruler
What's the spirit called
The false prophet
Operating through false media
Wow
The false prophet
It's in the media
Preparing the way for the Antichrist Spirit which is a
Killer
Counterfeit angel of Light
That's going to deliver
What sounds a lot like
Wow
The media is the false prophet is bananas
Grayson Harold
The coming of the Antichrist
Video to the Antichrist
Fat
Misrepresenting everything unreal destruction
They always live in like a Harry Potter like
Everything is interpreted and it turns out to be like
What we missed was when they said false prophet we thought he meant one per
The spirit
Warmed-up Protocols of the elders
Bionicle
Logically
It's fall
They're coming to be a false prophet and he's going to convince
Like
Right
That if you're like
Everybody
When's the guy you think is not the false prophet
Beautiful
So
I don't I don't I don't know if I ever
For Trump
To be the false prophet in there
Worldview
Because none of the one
Isn't
No no cuz there's a cool smart people
F****** false prophet can be all the media those two dudes
Can be everybody
That's how you get out of this box
So we've got
Lancewallnau.com
Overtly political
Zoe knows nothing about civics
This world order
Is farming
It is next clip we hear a couple of people
This wall now he's into
We just met with the President also
And he's a Christian
His is actually
Wanting
The great strength of God
What's really funny here is a flash up the picture of the former
Excellent
The president of Brazil
Is it Christian
Who wants the strength and grace of God
Four nations unprecedented Harvest and blessing coming
So he's like he likes bolsonaro
Cool
Save-A-Lot
F*****'-a Authority
Yeah I'm surprised they didn't bring out too as well
Criminals industry
I don't think that would affect
I don't think so
Something to me
Consist
Cincy with witch
You see these right-wing
Weirdo figures
You are super cool with bolsonaro
Insane
Cyrus
Cyrus l
Matson's big thing
Is gold coin has a picture of
King Cyrus
I had to describe it
In this booklet
He argues that
70 years before
Osiris
Did what he did
There is a prophecy
Prophecy
Then Cyrus came along
Fulfill that prophecy
Trump was elected 70 years after their Israel is created and so therefore
Bada-bing bada-boom
I wish I could explain it better but
Whatever
So bolsonaro and the current president of El Salvador
AR
First president
There are sheep
Goatman
I remember this one
This isn't good
No this is this is pretty bad
What what
Is about to lay out for
To do does he have to find a way to not care about most of the world
Yes if you're going to support these
Sort of authoritarian
You have to you have to brush off
A lot of the world
Most especially the meek
Got to watch out bolsonaro
So here is Lance laying out
His philosophy about sheep and goat Nation
And who matters
And who doesn't
And ultimately comes down
Two sheep and goat Nation
Very powerful New Renaissance
A nation-state
Becoming Street Nations
Yeah New Renaissance of Nations
Okay yep careful
A global
In office
The system is stable
And these nations are starting to run
A different
The nation that
As much as you've done to the least of these
My brother
Specification
Most people think by brother
That's the key word
At least of these you done it to me
Refers to
The Jews who are his
Who are his
Is blood
Inheritance
When they knocked on the door when Jesus was teaching I said master your
Your mother and your brothers are outside
Who's my brother
Stretching for the Santos disciples
She says
Behold my mother and my brethren
Those
Who hear the word of God
Will not molest
Persecute
The right of Israel
And Christians to exist
Donations
Shut you down
And steal your property
Wow
I agree zit-like states that
Suppress
People's rights
To exercise
Their religion
That's not good they shouldn't
Human rights
That their country
Matter can kill them with no consequence
The least of these
That doesn't apply religious rights
Jesus was
All about making
I'm sure people knew
Who could be killed
Whatever they wanted
Jesus was like
You guys are cool and then let's go
I remember in the book of Bartholomew
Some real f*****-up excuses for
In order to explain
All of the
Myriad ways in which you
Justify Your Ex
Set
Thing that you can turn what you do to the least
Versus like
And what
He means by that
Is you can bomb a run
Aaron is less than the least efficient
F*** off
So now we jump back into another sales pitch
For this year gold gold coin
And the bundle
And then we find
Very strong feeling that
World Order
Nuts to babies that's it's so over
Like I don't care if you were uses language
Some context I don't really give a
If it weren't for it being the central argument of anti-communist
New World Order conspiracy theory
Which this is an extension of
All about my pay
Hey to do World Order
Fiberglass
Right so here we go
Get some salesmanship
And
Some
Well what we need to do is order this bundle right now
Bucyrus trap bundle DVD 24-karat gold-plated
Trump wine
A gift app $45 I love that
Just discover the prophetic patterns
In this
Lisa Leslie
So that the hidden
Truth in the Bible
The rice
And the Cyrus and then what
That's what
What's coming next
And that's what you're saying
Telling him and there's a
We want responsible without Nations the Devils playing for Nations to Jesus
Was promised Nations for his
No borders kind of theorist
We also have
3 for $100
Aspirus
Pandora
Firetrap coins
Jessica
Have $100 that's amazing.
And we also have the baker's dozen
For I guess
After just $450 to the
Straight
At the same thing. You're eating
And at a DVD
And the booklet
Y'all love it love it love it and I suggest
You
Get the baker's dozen
Simply because you're going to want to share this
So many people
What's the weather here
Just maybe
Blanket
I think so too
Can really and give them Clarity like
Lance has really brought clarity
Not good
That is
So Insidious
Do exactly
So we can get the Panthers
We get there
Congregation know I don't have much luck with a lot of Pastor
I think
Most
I'd actually disagree with you 100
I think there are a lot of congregation that wear their Kuechly aware of who Jim Bakker is
Because this is not but you Baker is not indicative of
By God
Majority of Christian
Text unfair
Let somebody think that we're trying
To the pain
Christianity as a whole
That is
Part of a strategy
Angling for
You like say I don't know maybe you have
A grandchild
Yeah get the baker's dozen you could send them this gold coin in booklet
If you a gift of this
It reminds me of a lot of gifts
This is still fresh
Grover Cleveland
I can't remember if it was Christmas or my birthday
That was a tour guide
It legitimately was like I was scrolling through the pages room
I was flipping through the pages at one of them was like people often ask are there actually going to be gold streets in heaven
Absolutely
Wife
Twice this grifters the Tale As Old As Time
I get shocked when I got that one
And then work out a second time
Trying out a baker's dozen
It took me a long time to realize that like
Possible they got these from their Church
Local Christian bookstore
Baker himself
Orcon
Well Christianity
To me what that's always
Church
Any word from like
That's always been what I thought of as a
3200 isn't a church
Right
The reason that it's hard to
Get that
Image
Cuz the large
AR
Churches
Franchise
So big and very public
You don't
Good
Because often they're not getting mixed up in
Stuff that the media needs to cover up things
Is
Jamaica statistic
6 Bear Outfitters
Way more than you would expect
Supportive of Evangelical Christian
Bike
Who's calling themselves
Avenger
In my life I've had a lot of negative experience
But I've also had positive
It's not
I don't know I'm trying to defend Christianity or anything
Other than
Just a like
I think there's a lot of Grey
Because a lot of this show
I will never ever defend Christianity or appreciate
I will always defend
Churches
To me the church
You can pick a religion
Whatever toss it in there but
The church is what
Is a whole difference
Community
That is very
Each unit
Whatever
Oh God I love
This clip
Is so dumb
So you know how Paul Joseph Watson
Embarrassing things
More good and better accommodate makes people nervous as earlier
This guy is killing it with Jim Bakker
Murdering
Spell just watch
Just dumped on him for
Conservatism is the new Counter Culture
In this next clip takes that
Ball and runs down court with it
Tries to dunk
Hits the rim
Falls Lexie heart breaks his neck when he falls down to the ground
What's good about this is the fact that
Young people like to be
Counter
Culture
And so now that the culture has become dominant away
It's our turn to enjoy being radical
Up until now we've been the polite people
Now we have a whole new chapter
And and college campuses are a perfect
Incendiary environment
Young Chris
Start Gathering Together
To be the radicals
So it's actually a good sign
Or totally out of time
Steamrolls
You're dumb ass questions quite reminiscent of Lake George
Lincoln Rockwell strategy of antagonize
Living on campuses
Also
This is what I really really need
In the entire time
That I have been aware of Christy
Which is to say
I was involved in an angelical Church
When I was younger
There is nothing there was a bigger part
Of the like
Keeping kids involved to argue that they were the radical
Jesus Freak
Intelius
Do not think
Okay also
Awesome
Every single time
There has also been
He's never
Like a version of it that's going to be like you know what
We should be
Conservative the counterculture is
Always going other directions
Because
Like even if
The culture at Large
Accept the premise that the culture at Large
Is degenerate
Call Kyle Fuller
The counterculture to that
Will not be
Straight lace Christian
Play more of that s*** or a refinement of absolute
Like yet I guess you could argue in some ways like ethical non-monogamy
Culture 2
Promiscuity
That is in opposition
Into whatever the prevailing cultural tide was
That is
What
The idea that anybody in their youth
Large groups
People in their youth
Are going to be like
Anti Conformity I'm going to appeal to a
Ridiculously conformist
World Co
Not how that works
It is
It is the conundrum of the youth pastor
The youth pastor
Who is
30 years old
Is hanging out with a bunch of teenagers
Those Bible verses
But what if we
Just saying some hip new Tunes
By the beach
Youth pastor insisted on
Meet Virginia
Don't understand exactly why
The crazier ones are bananas
Because it's now it's
It's the next step of that
The youth pastor who's 30 years old need
He's got
Tatted up beyond all recognition
And he's like man
All the tattoos
Heroin pass
You got a trump
Cyrus tattoos
Yeah I have to do is press it and then you can talk
Everybody has a coin
Also the other thing too is that like this idea of
Sexy
Christian Youth is going around on campuses and being a
Incendiary
That's not new
Like I was
It's cool
In college
Early 2000
Of my goddamn college experience
It's good you could get away from it was brother Jed
The Evangelist people on campus all the time
He would make the rounds
Tons of colleges around the Midwest
He wasn't the only one there were a bunch of these
I've heard from the show one time
I got a bunch of emails
Also knew brother Jed and didn't go to Mizzou
Or they had their own version
Very
Consistent strategy for a long time this isn't anything new
You're trying to
Trick kids into doing it instead of an old
But
Not new
I remember
Just come around
Grab
People who
Basalt heads
Drifted from the faith or whatever
Let's go have a cup
Yeah
Go get a cup of coffee
That's whole thing over and over and over to his house for a dinner
At least my guy wasn't that great
Maybe he knew we need to go to a neutral
A buddy of mine was almost there
What's up
I don't think you did I think I talked him out of it cuz I recalled but
Resist the siren
Clip here
Idea
Earlier
I said
Alex
Oh
Do sheep Nations that are rising up
The leaders are less about party
And they're more about
The people
And bringing in
The prosperity in the principal's that'll make a nation great
This is a popular smooth
The enemy hates that the globalist
First of the populace is what you're starting to see now globalist
Want to control by the way
If it's socialism happen
It doesn't necessarily go bad for those people that are the elites
Because
The government will tell you what you doing what you don't do
And these Diesel eats already have influence over the governor
The globalist elite
Goddamn
Michelle
Because yeah he's going to create this nationalist hellscape dystopia but I'm going to be fine cuz I already haven't
Over him
All they really want like all these people really want is to continue their Griff
And people having more
Let's say let's cleaning
Policies and regulations coming
Into favor
Jeopardizes double their Griff
I would assume that they are very aware that they want to keep
From any possibility of that ever coming to pass
Especially on this show
They want to talk
Laws in place that you can
Discriminate against people based on
They want they want to
To be able to
Just seeing if I want to
If I want to do politics
The pulpit I'm going to f****** do it if I want to try and create a political machine small town
I still want to have
Ataxia
Re-up they want to protect
The scam and they want
To move things
Closer to
Authoritarian
In line with God
And there's bruising
Is it true
Is aligned with the people
They're not in a party
All that
They're putting up
Is the same thing that they're doing with religion
Yep to protect their scam
They hide it with religion
To hide their authoritarianism
And fascism
They hide behind
The populism
We're against the globalist
Socialism will wreck everything
Again
Globalist even though we are going to bring out a new Global World world Arvin
Functioning with global World borders
We don't need borders in the global world
It's like a lot of it
Is all crib
Sing from the same notes
It's all so many parallels
The guy who if you believed it had no idea about any civics
Before Trump got elected then
Took a steady diet of religious and right-wing
Media and it's come to this conclusion that he's come
To Andy's just regurgitate
Same thing
A religious
Presentation
Yeah I know it's goes to
So I guess they're not really that different at all
But they're doing different audience
That's the thing about the right-wing media
David sober
That I think they stumbled onto probably by
Best SEO
Because they agree with each
This is for retirees
Trying to get
Like
Barbie not anymore that's early but there was
It is original
Houston the market
Was trying to co-opt some left
Wing Depot
Libertarian
It's all it it's all focused on whatever corner of the market you can do to penetrate it with
This
Exact same worldview
Algorithm has killed us all
Because you watch one of these videos from Jim Bakker in your life
Haha
Stupid I'm not a religious wacko
But YouTube is like
Well you
Watch this dumb religious wacko
Let's see what you were into Alex Jones and then now you're like well this is what I meant
I'm still I'm still getting recommendation
So
Good luck.
Speaking of Goodluck Goodluck on your vacation
Have a great time over there
Do kangaroos over there
I know kangaroos
Animal
Over there
Literally
A giraffe
Cedar Rapids
I was going to
Okay good
Episodes
Over the vacation
I'll be back with some other fun now but until then we got to website
You can also find us
Twitter
Go to bed Jordan
And we are on Facebook
Yes indeed we are also on the iTune
You could download
Leave a review you could
Well
You could buy a 24-karat
Gold plated coin with dance
The gold
Put it between your fingers
We will see you next time but until I have been the Jesus Lizard
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work