Just wanted to give you a little introduction for this episode
And I recorded before he left for vacation
Neither of us has any idea of the news that broke over the weekend
Jeffrey Epstein death
To turn around and get an episode out for Monday about
Ryobi take care of that
By the time I would have been able to make an episode out of something
The only content that was really available of Alex covering it
Is there a 2-minute video that he shot in an airport
Where people behind him
Being in the background
Are Will and now it's Jones video
About a minute about feelings about everything set
Of a commercial for his
Survival Foods at water filtration
So that's
The goods a good sign
Make for episode
So anyway
Damned important
I have great respect for knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guy
MoneyGram
College vype.com
What up Jordan
When you were
Oh boy
Not a ton
I would Satan have any but it wasn't as big a problem as
Media had led me to believe it would be
I thought for sure based on all of the teeth
Teen dramas that it would be like
The biggest crisis
Philly weather
I did feel embarrassed
When you have a big
But it wasn't sad with that
I really want was where you were going to go
Because I was watching
One of those teenage
Series with my girlfriend
And it was very much like I was trying to think back on
I didn't really have that many
Puberty really early
Earlier than a lot of
Did you literally just tell me when you got your beard
I know I also my voice
It was pretty low.
Noticeable
People around
Answer the phone.
I always assumed growing up
That it was going
Going to be like
I'm going to get
Haier pimple face cuz my little sister
I don't know
Oh man
She did the whole
You got to do the whole thing
It was brutal
I felt amazing
To struggle
Give experience but I do know a lot about Alex J
And I don't know where you are on vacation
Vacation
But you will be gone
Open this comes out
And you'll be free of any consequence
. until I get back.
Because I don't want to get on that I don't have that
Experience
All the internet just killed me I lost my job
I wanted to get together with you and recording episode in advance
The people walk
Week Plus without the two of us hanging out
Nothing about Alex
Enough course
You know we can't really do a present-day episode
As well because we
According to
Preemptively so we got to stick around or do
Wacky Wednesday
Decided we are looking at March 13th and 14th
And I think we're actually turning a bit of a quarter
Couple days
Have some pretty wild s***
Zodiac
That's not what
Happens over the span of days
Think about
This is a couple days
Very excited about this
Bulls angles about it nope
This is just a racist massive a couple days this is one of the most racist
Things I've ever heard from Alex's show this couple days is profoundly racist
No s***
It's deeply
Deeply racist
Tipo pain
Let's gets racist I think that makes perfect even up about
So we'll get to that and I will also get to the
Shoutouts
2 out of context drop
For Today Show so let's get one of them
Alright
Not too much
I know guilt only appreciation
For the people that I would like to give a shout out to now
I have a bit of guilt about anybody who's for socio-psychological mess
Appreciate everybody from the bottom of my heart
Today is lousy with joke
This first one is somebody who I was
But I'm not sure that I endorse the message
That your name implies
We do not advocate for cryptocurrencies of any swap
Next
Alex Jones dog thank you so much
So I finally like to get some chat at some people donated on an elevated level we appreciate it very much so
Thank you so much
There are no wild wolves in Chicago coyote thank you so much
And that very well might be
I'm willing to accept that
I believe it to be a wolf but if it's a coyote then so be it whatever
I will take your criticism and accepted at thank you along with Melissa and
You are all wonderful technocrat
Heroin
Freakishly large
Thank you so much Melissa
Tell me somebody that they're wrong
Well also donating some of
It really does
Leaping catch while well-supported feels familiar
Jordans
We've got this episode to go if you are listening and you like sports
Please do
Text Rob from Today Show
Hats
Alright alright can I have the most racist couple of episodes
It started off by
I think if I recalled the context of that
Outward assault on the testicles
Pharmacological
Who cares
Alex is worried about his balls
Start on the 13th
And I we get to
Big guests
Alex is going to have on
And this is continuing
Right before you went on vacation
He had like
Ted Nugent Michael Savage
Daddy's big dick
Yeah
Hoes fighting
Piers Morgan in other people's Market spaces
And now he's trying to
Continue that with that
Gigante
Presence
I've seen the numbers
Certainly
Years ago
Coasttocoastam for
Yesterday
Every show
What singers of police
I would argue that your hearing
Iran
Is there air in your show
Directed towards
Similar topic
Also
That's not a good thing
No
My ships going world 1
Is George Noory from coasttocoastam
George Noory was the first person
To give him a large platform is a perfect argument
Programs like coasttocoastam
Be pretty dang
They're usually not most of the time
More critical
George Noory
It's hard not to be
Most of the time I don't think the problem isn't a problem
Ideas
There's so far past the point of believability that they're not really threatened
However a platform like that where the host has
Cultivated an audience full of open-minded but not that critical people
Where the host has a policy of not being the Hostile interviewer and letting people speak their piece
A platform like that isn't ideal Target
For someone like Alex
It's the greatest gift you could ever give a malignant
Looking to expand
What does Coast-to-Coast the hard work needs to be done in the booking
Process
You can have a loose freewheeling non-confrontational interview
But if you do you have a responsibility to not allow people on your show
Who are only there to
Put your audience and get them into their called
If you encourage open-mindedness and
Complete naivete
And you're off
Give an obligation to
Protect them from delicious
And that's a part of the equation
If they don't book they're so very carefully what they're basically doing it
Where they can be targeted by someone with bad well
And that's
At least
Alex Jones
And for this
And many other reason
I would like to say the George Noory
Can go f******
George Noory put all that fish in the barrel and then Alex
Yeah that's
Exactly what happened I don't know if I don't know that necessarily A lot of these people are all of that
Cognizant
Engaging
But when you have a show like ghost ghost
Everything is based on a lack of evidence
Possible
Is a breeding ground
Petri dish
Of
Graduate
Well now I need to know what is
I can't keep
I can't stay open-minded and all that stuff
But you're not going to the proof or
The open-minded
Yo-yo are towards
You'll certainly be directional going
Exactly I'll be there
I don't think this is any
Statement that I'm making her like something like Coast-to-Coast shouldn't
To be censured
These people running shows like this
Or they need to be open about the fact that like
We're trying to do
People you shouldn't be able to
Pretend that your your intentions aren't in that direction
And then behave in every way
That leads towards
You need an outlet
Sure I don't know what they do but yes
Clip they're also saying that
There's a little bit of a delusion of grandeur that's in there too
Because he's not just saying that his ideas are all mainstream
He's
Convinced that he's the reason
They're mainstream
And all of these people are just following
In his wake
Might be some truth to that
This was
Without even being on Infowars it was it was not even a mean in the media
Yesterday
And when you see a chain reaction
More and more
Or something
It's not on Infowars
30 seconds later
I mean it wasn't on the website
And then also
Real dangerous mentality to have that everybody gets all there already
I think he accidentally
Most radio
No it's okay that I
Most rated most radio show
It does
So I told you this really racy
Couple of days
And it starts pretty quick
Because Alex
Is on storm like they're attacking white people
Is Big narrative on the 13th
To the bottom of what's going on here
His intentions
Become Crystal
Not manual
How could you get that wrong
The LA times has Emmanuel
Nevermind
So apparently there's an LA Times article that
Sound
Closet
Didn't know really what to go on here I wasn't quite sure it just
He could be talking about nothing
Or anything
I need more details
Until a little bit later in the episode
Details and we
Figure out what is
Jones
Who is that
I love that
It's not even
Sowega
Issue
Attention to
He wasn't right
The good thing that nobody ever listen to him
But hear what we're seeing Alex
As usual
Is leaving outside
Very important
Mark's comments were in response to a video that was put out by a Tennessee weapon
Instructor by the name of James
James Yeager
Literally say Obama put forth any gun control measures
It was time to quote start killing
Mark potok was just
Quoting James Yeager
It's really indicative
All the time
Some gun weirdo threatens to kill people
Someone who works at the splc says to kill people
And people in his community
And Alex ignores the original threatened pretends that the sblc guy is not so just saying that all white people are terrorists
This really is one of the main tricks that Alex uses on his show and the robbing a story
That would make it make
What happened here was that potok wrote an article about this threat
And provided some
Specific examples of other groups and individuals around the country were making
Similar threats
About a violent revolution that they were ready to set off
This article was published in salon on January 11th
Infotalk
To discuss the topic
Alex
Responding to
I know that he needs to make a big deal out of every procedure
You played against white people
You should know what's going on here
You should know what actually is going on
Because this is what Alex's
Turning into all whites are terrorists
But there's more
The original article at the center of this whole thing like I said
Who is Mark potok
Responding to
And once you realize who James
Everything comes in
Yeager's the CEOs tactical response
A company that sells weapons weapon parts in tactical training
They're also a sponsor of Alex's
Jagr has been on the show many times and Alex sell gun parts from his sight
His website
Or at least he definitely did in the past I'm not sure if he still does
That relationship is mysteriously undisclosed and Alex's commentary about Mark
Time
All of it
It's nonsense
No
That's not okay
How is that
How's that can happen
I feel like
There's so many things that aren't
Illegal and that
I don't know how to
Police correctly
Really shouldn't be
Possible or okay
Yeah I mean
Manipulation
And a level of
Absolutely
So park photo center who is behind
Report that the LA Times article is
The root of all of this stuff
Articles
4 salon
Extension of
Of this
This commentary
Is about James Yeager
Okay
Explicit connection
Between this all being about people explicitly threatening to kill people
You got a cart and horse
Situation
That's completely
Alex's forgetting about with actually behind
The chicken-and-egg whatever the cause and effect
He's ignoring the cause
Talk about the effect
In a vacuum
Because it's b*******
And he only does this
What is issues
White gun owners
You should be able to threaten
Kill people
Eyewitness
Terror
He's a terror
What would what's really interesting about this
Because of the LA Times article the mark potok
Because of all that
A big predict
In this next clip we will see
And it's pretty
And I think I understand
And they are
And 5 minutes
So here again this is what your talked about are on our last episode
It is coming around he's a Star Wars
Coming around
Is coming around
X
What's really interesting here is that
Within a couple weeks
The Boston bombing
So Alex is here
And people are going to interpret predicting
The boss
And when the Boston bombing happen
He's going to be able to say I predicted
He's not responding
To the LA Times
For the splc
ER mark potok
He's responding to knowing the
Did James Yeager
And people like him are threatening to do stuff like this
Yeah
This is
This is self-defense
This is preemptive Justice
Application for things that he has a very good idea that his militia buddies are going to do
That's what's going on here
Conspiracy
See even from his predictions
A terrorist
What a car
Faster route
His militia Buddies
Sing a terrorist attack
Telling him about it
Having him
Say that there's going to be one that
Going to blame on them
To be clear that's exactly what I'm saying
The weather of the world
Corners of the world
This
Fplc guy coming out
Warning
And saying hey this is
Problem
There are these white
Right-wing militias
It would be wise to pay attention to Alex knows that that's in response to things
That are people he knows people who
Sponsor his show he knows that they are the people who have made threats like that
Comments don't exist
Devoid of contact
Do you think this
Because other people have made
These threats Alex knows that
Panino's
The people who play for me
If they're protected business
To go ahead and create a pre-emptive narrative
I can create
Whole new season based on that
And then it's a perfect strategy for him
He's running interference
That's a big part of it
Motivation motivation
The terrorists because
We would we would almost certainly have done more to investigate
Are the FBI would have done more to investigate White
If there weren't a massive amount of people who are
Supporting the present
You know what the biography people like
Alex
Looking at
Broader problem than just
People from The Middle
Right
Yeah absolutely
You know there is a
There's an even
Further benefit to it
No one
Does anything
Militia guys italic
Text nose
And support
Is Cool Whip
It's still good for his business to act this way
Because where is the
Griezmann
Did he make so much money off
It's so Central to
Being the fuel for his world.
In the chance that something happens
In case it nothing happens
We're still making money
It's the perfect thing to happen
For him to have
To somebody
These guys are planning s***
What they're going to do
To do it eventually
Enter in a long enough Spanish
If you give it given enough time
And enough
Support
From
Media figures like Alex
Especially now that we live in
What is zodiac
Certainly with the context
More years of History
It does feel
I don't want to I don't want to apply that to Alex
Mentality
We can always
Speculate that
Or
Likely is just
Let's
Let's build this narrative
And also a money money money
Get around to reading some of the LA Times
Stop it
Homegrown extremists
Look who they shows extremist
What part of
With the US government
They are white
You see how easy a jump he makes there from the saying
Subway terrorism
To being like they're saying
Right
Well I mean it is
The only thing that he
Can say
Everybody who's a Muslim
Who is a terrorist
So far
But in the Attic
Why do radical Islam is because they're all secretly radical Islam
So every brown person is at
Terrorist
If he wants to maintain any kind of ideological
If you call one person
A terrorist in a group
There's probably
He's not doing that a
Probably take the larger piece
Can't argue on the merits
Are there white people who are terrorists
Because if that's the conversation that that falls apart entirely
He's going to have to go out of his way to deny Every Act
He has no awareness
How does radar work but these specific cases
Conspiracies
The argument that being
They're saying people are terrorists
Nonspecific
Stupid
You can just grandstand on that
Go ahead
The point massage
Send lose the argument that people are committing terrorist Act
Yeah I know there's nobody has more in common with ice
White crested polish
Alex
So Alex
It's around 2
Stream
Was going to happen
Because this
Shrimp
So it's going to be a false flag
It's okay
Don't want them to do cuz then they like
It was a
What he can do that
Take the parts out
I like it
Bright
His
Pressured tone about like
There's going to be there going to blow something up
But when he gets more specific
You start to under
Understand
He doesn't know what he's talking
This is such a vague idea
This is
Extreme level that
You predict it
Drudgereport.com
In 2019 when we were discussing Alex's narratives that he was building about the El Paso in
Shooting he discussed
The Arlington Road model
Arlington Road system
In 2013 here
He's talking about the government nuking a city
And then killing him presumably I guess
Kind of discussing the Arlington Road system
That movie was out before then
Eviter products
This is stupid
Did you see how the 24 seconds of a clip took a little journey
It started with you know I break down crying
Cuz I have a feeling that
I bet he said Obama and his controllers are considering using a low-yield nuke
American city
From a prediction
That tone is reporting
Obama and his controllers are considering their okay I feel like they're going
The tone of that is very much like as if he has a reason to believe that other than his stupid
Analysis of the world
That's
Even though I don't know if it's easier or harder now
Mix up those tone
Everything he says
Is a Feeling
And is based in
At bat
Hand knowledge of
The summary of somebody else's
Sure
So whenever he changes
Opinion reporting
I really
Noticing
Because I it's all
The same thing
Yeah I can see how if I didn't
Can have this level
Experience that that would be
Serious way of
Transforming
Your
Apocalypto
2 prediction
Is reporting listeners purposes
He's doing it probably
I would say
I don't know how much
Muffled
But with the hopes that people will take it more serious
Absecon
And talkingshit
Clips of George Noory interview cuz it's
Really boring
Been very bad but what does solidify
Nori f****** loves Alex Jones
The two of them are on the same page about political stuff
Would you would know if you listen to a little bit of Coast to Coast AM
Yes he does let that show a little bit more than
Someone who is presumably impartial in
Just like a guy wants
Like he's very very
Against
Circle coffee
Who cares
Good Times
Coming up on the show
That is
James O'Keefe
Project Camelot
We don't have to listen to him
You shouldn't
Broadcast
I'm coming up here in about 30 minutes
Keith Campbell.
I'm sorry I gave a Freudian slip
Easter Easter
I don't believe he's sick
I believe I don't want to do this
Seems like a hassle I don't want to make this 15-minute phone call
Busy
Beginning of the episode we get a new pope
And on the 13th of March
Smoke
The white smoke came above the chimney
Found it there was
The new pope
Here whenever we get a chance
To do that
And we will be breaking more of that down
Reporting of the fact
Commentary about the new pope
We don't know that it's Francis
Anticipation
So this is
Episodes around the time the Pope Benedict
Is Pope Goodwin off episodes
I thought the odds were pretty strong
But Alex is going to be freaking out about it
Big World News
But Alex is on vacation when that happened
That was the vacation we just passed here in 2013
Benedict resigned on February 28th 2013
On March 3rd
Alex Jones response
News
Which I would describe as
Curiosity
This is interesting
Because it tells me Alex had no idea who the new pope was going to be
But according to his own self told backstory
He should know
According to Alex nowadays Leo zagami predicted
The way Alex tells the story
It's heavily implied that Alex knew about sagami predicted in watch them play out in real-time but here we see our
Wondering
Ponte
Is going to be
I think this is
Probably because Alex didn't meet Leo zagami until 25
15 which is a bit of a problem
For that for that time
Alex has just taken his truth Leo's claimed that he predicted the Benedictine
Substantiate
I can find zero proof that Leo zagami made this prediction before Benedict resign
And knowing as much about him as I do I'm very comfortable assuming
After the fact and pretended he'd known all along
Most of the citations
To this prediction
Go back to Leo's book
Pope Francis
The last Pope question
Cinemark
Money Mason's and occultism in the decline of the Catholic Church
First of all to subtitles
But that wasn't published until April 25th
A further reason to be
Suspicious is better in October 2015
He said that he knew from high-level Vatican stores
The Francis was going to step down and resign
And that was going to happen
In 20
This didn't happen
Which calls into question the veracity
Between that
Every other piece of information in the world about Leo zagami
And the fact that literally no one seems to be able to produce evidence
The actually predicted Benedict
Resignation before it happened
I'm comfortable with my position
And it's a load of b******* that Alex believe when Leo told him about it probably again
Just because Leo's Italian Improv
To say it doesn't
The veracity of
Leo zagami
But their existence
You bet
I really clearly see here
No idea who the new pope is going to be
And he doesn't even bring up
But his good buddy Leo zagami made a very real prediction
That happens to come true
What's Alex
Freaking out
Not just about the white smoke
He should be freaking out about the whole thing
Because Leo's
World Arena events the resignation of a pope
It's crazy
We're already deep into his prediction coming true it's not like the prediction is only true
Francis's
Should have every reason to be in the middle of a
Extended freakout
No
So if you predicted that one
Even though you knew he was in
If you predicted that
Evidence of
Either
You do have good sources
You're the kind of crazy person who would make a f****** The Longshots
Headlight
And knowing what I know about inclined towards the latter
Pantheon situation where I
Could have made it but
Like real any made that prediction in a
I came true
That is not convincing
But it's enough to make me like I got to track all of his other predictions
Because you are
Right that's
Very very
Yeah.
Considering almost all of his other predict
Can push it took credit for 9/11
And said he was Jesus
And clients who created a cult based on the movie The Matrix
This is created as part of his fictional eyes backstory and Alex
Hook Line & Sinker
The present-day buddy
That does always make me think of the reality that
With the infinite number of pi
Possibilities and probabilities
In the universe
It is entirely possible
For one person
To live their entire life
Every prediction that they've ever made
And it just be a coincidence
And I think about how miserable you miserable you would be
If you are that purse
It would be the worst
Feeling in the world
Yeah
You recognized it
At some point you'll probably start trying to make really
F***** up predictions trying to ruin the street so you wouldn't have to feel like you predict
Everything is fine
You agree plagued by it
Everybody
Better luck
Let's
The things
To go there was a kind of unhappy about
Something about losing that makes you feel more in control of your
Like the exact you don't have to do that when the road is really easy
Every one of your
Directions right you won't sink
Oh I'm so brilliant
Captive
Some sort of drug
Did you know what Alex probably does
How to spell all the time
His brain is so narcissistic
He transforms
Bananas
Yeah I made it
So on this Alex get back to the
The white
Quite
Tamara
Statement
Constitutionalist
White Al-Qaeda
What a little
The loser little titty baby
Like this
Soft man
I give your that Shakin by
Either have
Just a business
Skin imaginable or you are really worried
Edgewater
I guess either you're the most sensitive person in the world who can't handle any form of credits
You are keenly aware of the world that you are surrounded by
The right-wing militia world
How volatile
Those people are
You like that
Need to defend against
It's one of the two
My gut tells me
It's both
For the ladder
Well the reason I would keep.
Where is all of the
The militias that have existed from the 70s
60s and 70s
The resurgent
You cannot not be aware of the order
Absolutely
He can't not.
Booking one of his big sponsors Larry Owners of America
Ethan said that he would like to imagine
Do you have to wear that
Get think it's all fake
Makes me agree with
The latter being
True
Nelse
Just like we talked about before with
His support of trump is
He's he was all about like all freedoms all that stuff because it could happen to
And then once you remove that Baxter
None of it
Yep it's still one
Clear
Cuz you're probably wouldn't exist
If it wasn't
Absolutely
So Alex talked about the
Completely lying about
Headlines
Inherently is Terrorism and over again
It is
That this was coming
So
I don't know what else to say about it
It's just a white fragility White
Desperation is a Feeling
Cuz they move product
Key people in this world
Do you know what he
Will never do but would reveal everything
Define
You know I would love to do that
No no no
Probably
So Alex that got stood up by James
Project Veritas called every woman who agreed to
This other guy from Project Veritas comes on and I don't respect him enough to know his name
So I don't remember what it was
Other guy from Project veritas
Matt there's even one guy
So you shows up
And a video that they put out is about going to
To Police Department
Having discussions with cops
Where you say like okay so if I call the police
They're going
How to take 3 minutes
To respond to
To do someone's brakes
To my house
Well
They want the police.
It seems like
To endorse
Here's what I'd say
I don't want the cops to ever get the message
Set like we really want you to go ahead and kill people
I haven't
I don't want to take the laundry
Now somebody who has that that is of course Sheriff David
Clark
I don't think there is anything
Like just in
Entirely wrong
With
To be able to defend yourself
It's situation
Appropriate law enforcement
If people who
Two are responsible. Having a gun at home
For protection I don't
Implicitly wrong with
I think it would be something
Dangerous
About police
On the job
Well
So I can shoot people
I think it sends the wrong message
Off the job site
They sure probably do a lot
I think
Culturally it gives the worst message
Did you say a uniform special representative
Or be a torrid implied
So they get a dog
I like have a dog
Fine for a cop to say
Whatever
That's what the
Project Veritas video is
Dog
Shity
Just enough
White gravy
The conservatives who want to believe it no matter what
Interviewing
Dum dum to from over at project veritas
And he's making that argument that like we went and we were talking
All about being able to
Defend yourself in that 2 minutes
Before the police show up
That's the entire
Defense
Videos
Existence relies on
Alex
Because he is such a fuk
Idiot
And a violin
The idea of shooting somebody keep it together
And he immediately invalidates
Their entire argument
For this video
Thomas Baxter covers I can get
I am going to dissociate and kill a man
Wow I mean like I did the whole point of the video really relies on the pretense of we are trying to do
Do everything possible
Not to kill a bag
Well it's I don't know if it's
Quiet or loud
That they project
Which I find hilarious
It's pretty nice.
Yeah
Jesus
So Alex goes into overdrive
Episode
Another half-hour this power
He doesn't and most of it is this
Which isn't
Impression
Giant her to do I don't think
Terrible neighborhood
It's a McGruff the crime dog
Nevermind
I honestly think that he's in and out of the impression
He's close to his Pennywise
Impression
It's it's not as good as I remember it I apologize for saying that
But there are moments where he hits
Just the right
Do you know what he did
A really great impression of a bad guy from like a Humphrey Bogart
Who is the closer to that
Wait
Trash
This message brought to you by
The boy that was in a word
Coherent
I would also like dogs album
Good stuff album Bud like not doing drugs
Overdrive do a minute-long impression of McGruff doing if
TSA about the terrorist
We are entering
A white identity
Season on Alex's Shelby real strong scent
We got this
The next
Couple days probably next week at least
It can be Alex going out of his way
Define any
Way to make stories about
This is going to be what it's all about
And there
Unfairly maligning us as if we were
And it'll just be like bulshit
In order to
Make these stories
And I was not surprised at all
Exactly what we got
University
Scholarship Center
Today
Hardware a
It actually says that
Because anybody who designed that
F****** exercise
Yeah this is just
Escalating
I gets crazy
Not only that LA Times story
Quotes
Now he's come across the story of white people being
Inw followed around by non-whites to yell at them but how bad they are
Darren Dyke story that Alex is basing this recording on
Initiate is weak
According to Infowars and their primary source
Cnsnews
The Wisconsin Department of Public Instruction
People in their Vista program
To take steps
Consider how their there
Being white puts them in a privileged position in
Society
What are the examples of to wear a wristband which of the conversations to happen
When people ask you why you're wearing wristband
It seems like a shity plan in the post Livestrong era
Accessory
Bananas
Vista stands for Volunteers in Service to America
It's part of America
This was involved with the Department of Public Instruction
Volunteer to help with school and Library
Cuz that's what the epi
Is about 41
Even if the b******* that Alex is saying is true there still wouldn't be forced to do any of that
Franklin
Here are some of the things that are not true
That Alex
In anyway and it's just making
He saying that universities in group that's what the Unabomber called a ricer
They're forcing people to do this to
To get their tuition
This is
Tier program
A prerequisite of getting a scholarship
Who is Delta
The PC the band
The program were too much of them
We could still get their volunteerism requirements fulfilled by taking another opportunity
Or
Volunteer coordinator supervisor
Which is strange
There's no indication that anyone who was complaining at all
The only people that were mad about it
Right-wing pundits was sketchy Histories on Race issue
So
For something that
Would fit the narrative they want
Almost
It's almost like that really close to me
The manuals were written by the splc
That's another claim that
Neither Alex nor any other reporting on his website prove this in anyway
The Bengals are written by a nonprofit called DB
Beyond diversity Resource Center
And I can find do connect
Green diamond
DLC
Oz creative is completely false narrative
About the splc running the Oklahoma City bombing
Which is helpful
To help create the appearance that all white terrorism
Is the second use for that narrow
Anytime there's a social justice type organization
Immediately neutralize whatever
By claiming they're mixed up with the splc
It doesn't matter if they are or not
None of his listeners are going
Check
What's important is to mirroring
So their ideas and information
Consider
And whatever horrible s*** you're going to make up about them
Becomes completely believable
They're mixed up with the people who tried to smear Whites by doing Oklahoma City bombing
You could just invalidate kind of social justice
That's pretty much all you have to
And also Alex claims that these are their printer
Really fast
Who's printouts
Is it America
Construction is it the splc
When you try to trace down the actual document from
Infowars
You end up on
Cnsnews
And then you'll eventually find the site where it was originally posted
Which is still hyperlinks on their website
Pediatric explained
The document previously available via this URL is no longer here
It was not a Vista document Nora Wisconsin
DPI document
Including a resource pack Vista volunteers
The document was not referenced in that train
And the training session was conducted by individuals external to-dpi and Vista
Unfortunately misconceptions and misinformation about the documentary
Spread by an out-of-state entity that has no connection
With the public schools in Wisconsin
To be absolutely clear
No DPI official has asked
Requested or encouraged any school district educator or students wear any wristband and none of our Vista volunteers event
Any children put on any wristband
Again
No DPI official nor any Vista volunteer has used Quest
Or encourage anyone in the school to use a wristband activity
As reported in quote
And shared by external
This is this is the point that I made
On the winds
In that
We are absolutely
Complicit in the rise of
Because you know what
They went out of there
F****** way bending over backwards
For these fun
Who came up with this b******* bad faith argument
To the point where they write this statement
It's still up there
6 f****** years later or whatever it is
Here's the f****** f*** you Alex
I fully support
Chittering
These bulshit
Criticize
Absolutely
Absolutely if it's summer
He's criticizing you
And they have a good point doesn't matter what side of the aisle there on consider their there
But this is
Lies and you don't need to
Come up with some like
We don't support this was all the f*** you Alex Jones should be there and here's what
Because it is
On cnsnews
Infowars
That their information now links to a page that explain
Misinformation
So it is it should say f*** you
Innovations
It probably be
That would cause
Because
Stop these people
Like Alex or
Opportunistic infection
But
Stop saying wrong
Over and over and over again
I agree I agree
An important
And I also think that it is
You make a good point
I just think there was also a qualification
Very still
Just because whatever you do they're going to pay the same way
These propaganda
The news
These folks are going to do it
Whether you give them ammunition or not.
That
Still needs to be tempered with a little bit of her like
Give car block
Just behave
However a little bit restrained
These organizations that are about like
Getting handy
Accessible ramps
Go fuc yourself out I think it would be fun to see it once
Maybe in the same way that like I don't know Arby's will tell someone to f*** off on Twitter
It might
It might be a step backwards
In terms of something
I know I don't I don't disagree with you at 100%
I agree with you
Accommodate
I absolutely want them to have that statement of like
Hey this is a complete disinformation
What they did
Is lie about us
Yeah I'm just saying that it needs to be
It needs to be
To have
People
Focusing on D propaganda Outlet
Like us
And
Institution
Protecting themselves simultaneously
Have a full spectrum of protection
Perhaps because we don't have to worry about you know if we start telling people to go f*** themselves
We're not at risk of losing State funding that will hurt libraries
So
Consequences
Is for people who are vulnerable
Disadvantage
Children in Wisconsin
To begin with
Spelling of right-wing
Trollberget to f*** off
Could fuc with your funding as opposed to a of the right-wing troll Brigade
I'm not disagree
Bring
What we would like of course
Actually 100%
Behind it which is what right-wing troll
Cannot do
Extra layer of complexity
Documents
Really wrong Beyond diversity
There was giving people as they left
Meeting seminar that wasn't even being run by DP Orvis
Some of the suggestions are a little bit
Cheesy
Corporate seminar type of document is going to be
Like I would say that some of them might not be the most productive
Suggestion
Wanted to make that kind of criticize
I really don't think there would be that big of a deal
Like if you were to make an argument of like
They're telling people to wear bracelets in order to have conversation
The bracelet about
Have a conversation
Not racist nature about how like
Does a hokie idea
Really doesn't address the problem it just seems like it might without ever actually do
What you can have a conversation
And still be on fairly Solid Ground
I think
The bigger issue though is that I used to see something
You see that how something so small localized in minor
Can be spun by Alex
Sweet government sanction
Splc run attack on white people
Which is white supremacy
Look what they're doing what's going on
Clarify the document doesn't say you have to have a minority follow you around
Can tell you how bad you are
About
The privileged status
Were YouTube
You happen to be white
His quotes find a person of color who's willing to hold you accountable for addressing
There's a slight difference there and I also think that's a bad suggestion
Accountability partner
Which
Discussing race on
Other people coming to
Do you or something about reflection
Fought
Yeah
Fox2 haven't
Explore other suggestions are like put a note on your
Computer screen
But like I think it's at suggestion
It's kind of like that
It is
Weird
To be like
I'm going to go find a person of color that I can have keep me accountable on someone out
Color who is
Willing
I don't exclude the possibility that that person biting
And not think it's insulting for me to come to them be like
Hey can you call hell yeah
I will
Yeah I don't think anybody I don't think the Southern Poverty Law Center is like usual
We take a book out of game we take a page out of Game of Thrones we have people of color follow white people run
Is the splc didn't do
Life
Somehow subcontract an organization that were not involved in it all
To make a printout
Being handed out to people at 1 seminar
It's not even being run by the Wisconsin the PPI for the program or Americorps
Also
Cnsnews is owned by the media research
Which is a conservative propaganda Outlet
Rapunzel funding
Escape Foundation
And ExxonMobil thanks
They are not a good source of information
Straight up right-wing misinformation
Campaign operator
And that's where Alex is pulling
For the beach
The story
For the Infowars article
So that's where we're at
This is just
Finished
F****** worst
Wate 6
Type bulshit
Start to see this narrative and this season
Taking shape
We are in the last season
Was before Alex been on vacation
It was all strfkr
It was all just like people on here
We're having celebrities it's going to be awesome
Mary comes back
Can I get the very strong scent
Be a lot of weight
White identity
We're getting used to
So Alex
I want to play this life and it doesn't include the part of the clip where Alex
Does explicitly say that Hitler was
Buddy.
He is also a complete
As we all just started
It's less important
Something besides
Praise for Hitler
But he does
Spend
Lamar
We really don't have to get it at up to
Adolf Hitler was a prosperous class in the first World War
It's a Nazi propaganda the painted him as a war hero when reality does not setup
What are the problems of sorting out the reality of Hitler's military history in World War II
No one knew he was going to become Hitler back then
There are records of his life as a normal run-of-the-mill Soldier
What was known as the he was a runner.
War
Two-factor accepted to me that he was the sort of message carrier
The frontlines a Dodge
Machine gun fire
To get the orders where they need
Needed to be
That is not true
There are two varieties of runners in the German military in World War 1
There were those who were on the front line
Scaring orders through dangerous
And office workers
Who delivered messages between the offices of The Wretched
Metal headquarters
Far away from the siding
Hitler was the second kind of Runner during the war
Historians have noted that it's likely that he was given the first class award
After a battle where Messengers were
Particularly important
And it was likely that his inclusion
Any award recipient
Was the result of him having close Association
What's a higher rank
Officers
Due to him being
Station
Inside the headquarters
Alex is confusing things also
About how many Iron Cross first class metals
He's thinking of the highest-ranking
Of which only night
Forever giving out
Between 1870 and 1980
5.7 billion Iron Cross first and second class metals
We're giving out
Hey well the second-class ones we're definitely more commonly awarded
The first class work some kind of super rare thing
Some numbers I've seen to put the number of recipients at about 100
Wikipedia short of 10
Of them being awarded everyday
Between 1870 and 90
Alex bacon me
These comments in the context of
But it's also
Super Brave
It's supposed to be making
I'm not actually sure what point he hope to make
But it really highlight something that I think is super
Alex Jones
Versions of History
It really like it was part of Hitler's propaganda
Videos of War
It was an essential piece of his appeal to the people
And a lot of the German public
Historians and researchers head to bump this
Still preaching to his audience about the
The positive parts of Hitler
This is a trend
It's not just
Isolated incident
Alex is very in
Inclined to believe
Between this
The stuff about the Hitler was set up the
Peace treaty
The
Waterloo him directly taking the story that was
Amplify
And put into it sort of canonical form by a gerbils film
History
Revision
Not based on reality that Alex
Except
Cool cloth is real Nets
That's disturbing
What do you say
Because we've
You say you've read 100 books on WWII 100 books on World War
30 books at least of Nazi propaganda it's
Seems like
There's there's no way that at least
Coming from
Even if he's doing his best job to to critically analyze
Which is not possible
Stories
If you're reading a
100 different books on WWII
Might see
Through
Might just
Steep in all of the correct
History up but
For some reason there's this one story that's only in this one Nazi propaganda
Exactly
Because you brought up the book
On this one because a lot of people didn't actually
Look through the records enough to figure out what
Kind of Runner Hitler was
Right until
Fairly recent
To this episode
Like it's not like it's
It's been a part of scholarship 450
The years
And Alex is just
Like that off
Yeah the books that he had read
War based on
Ink
History
Ab2 there's a chance
He had read in a book of Hitler
Heroic
To reflect
That
Possibly
But history
Add more information at 2
And people
The part of
Hitler
PR campaign
Recognize
Disposition
Is not done
When history
Yeah
Yeah it's really interesting
Furious people worth it
Pluto stop being considered a
Planet
Compare that to how much white matter
Nationalism
The idea that Hitler was
Yeah
Pitstop
I feel forum
Shout out
I got to go to the Nazis who are struggling with
Finding out their hero hero
Episode
Let's get back to this
This narrative about the
Why people need to wear bracelets
And find a minority to Yellow.
He updates
Narrative
Becky is taking the colonel that he's already established
And now he's embellishing
Theme in order to make it
For more Universal
But it actually is
The symbolize that they're badass
Americorps
Inherently
The evolution
Universities all across the
Yep are forcing an order to get their tuition
Forcing
Yep
I told you that this was very real
Deeply racist
Call absolute
It was almost shocking.
To me like the consistency with which
He's he's dipping into
That were illuminated
Yeah but it's just
Brings it all in
Almost
Like a tornado of racism
Parts of his narrative
And his
Just talkin
Then we heard a hundred time
Margaret Sanger wants to kill black people
Abortion is about killing black people
Like I just all of this stuff it all
The March 14th episode
Is just all of that
Lucky's shooting
Semi-automatic blast of
Rapist.
If you
Heard for our radio show
And you heard one of those
Things where you're like
Is that a racist
Maybe you know you can even Blow by it but if it's
Just no other kin
Conclusion you can come
All over the place in the
14th episode
I considered
I considered like
Maybe just
Taken
Overkill
Entire episode of Alex being
But I realized it wasn't a ton of value in that anybody wants to listen
Already talked about the make-out with the rapist enjoy
I thought I would focus more on
Things that are new to
Yeah live within that
Yeah it is one of those
The thing about it
That I think of
Talking about a show
Entertainment show ranoush or anything of that Valley
Naturally
We've said that Alex
This is a racist
And I can understand why it would get
Boring or white Woodfield
Repetitive
Fight
Never not be men
It has to be
Consistently mention
Over and over
Over again
Because you can't for a moment for
And I don't think we do a good enough job about that
Maybe just because it comes up
You know like when he is
Right
There's not a moment where
At least since like
Couple months into doing the podcast
I was a little resistant to call him racist
It's overwhelming
Define deposition.
That you like in terms of that thing
He gives us clues about Justice
Specific race
Christian
Dominionist ideas absolute
Pope
Like it seems like
World news
Yeah
How many Catholics are there is tons of them around the world billion
Show me Catholic Church
Affected by
Non-catholics or effect
Hell yeah
It becomes a huge political story so many angles to
That one
20 weird word redshift
Going to change the world
It's interesting as a story
It
She is compelling
It's a news comprehensible is a Cuban
Touches Alex's world
He should have known who the new pope was going to Facebook
So I was really disappointed that he doesn't really cover it much
This is most of his coverage
It's kind of dismissive
The first Latin American first
And the first world Catholics
Alex is almost dismissive
Conspiracies about the Jesuits running into the Catholic church and being involved in
New world
That'll feel the fire of Jesuits
I don't I don't I don't understand why you so dumb
He hasn't come around upgrade
That's most of it he's like yeah we got this South American Jesuit that's going to make people
The conspiracy world's freak out
Analysis Alex
Most of it
So the guy who wrote the article for
Yeah about this
Wristband
Is a Aaron dykes
One of his
Employees
Don't think you still there
I'm not sure
Lot of his ex-employees
People like him and the others
Don't think there's a lot of
Ex-employee
I'm carrying the torch
So Aaron Dykes comes on
To talk about this article.
And
Man
He is
He displays
Some
Ratably
Disposition
But I think
Excludes as to why he wrote the article that you wrote
Racism
I was really disappointed Alex cousin
I don't know what that implies
Explain
Confusion is Facebook
Expressing the globalist
Soul Sister
Urban Plates
People's butt
Inexplicably
Fei3
Sure
And also
Pushing other races but
Through things like
Civil rights
Whatever their social justice cause
Like let's say
Black people
Felicia
Stop killing us
Targeting us unjustly
Unfortunately
Sing that is making
Can be racist black people
So they are more
Nonsense
Argument
Anyway
Alex
Gets into talking about it
Is Dad
Now we know that
Listen to Alex
As much as we do
Houses that has people in Texas
Globalist
Tried to recruit absolutely took him into a meeting and they tried to recruit him
He was younger
And
Here sitting with aerondight
Okay
This is really great
Because our
Probably get
Specific
And
Figure it out
Windstone High School
A junior
So Alex no better than
Use real name
Yeah that'll get him into two
Crime
Alex is referring to doctor doctor Irwin
Spear in the botany and biology
Departments at UT Austin
1853 to 1990
Students that they were posted in the alumni magazine
And from everything I can tell about him he sounds like a great
2011 interview with someone who took his class
40 years prior
It made such an impression on it
Single visit
Irwin speedbor out as like an important
He inspired us
He was a very difficult teacher
Discuss anything we didn't understand
And his exams
I think it was the first time that I was taking exams or you had to really think
You didn't just regurgitating
Information
Dr. spear was so challenge
Stimulate
And started many of us on the right road to how to study
How to prepare for exam
And how to appreciate what we were learning
That's why I stuck with medical technology
With Organic chem
That's a great teacher
Do changes people's lives
With learning
I know from Alex's dad's Dental license that he was born in 1950
About 7
19 when this meeting allegedly happen
Right cuz he still in high school at Junior the general would be 17 or wrestling
Well I happen to find a copy of an article from the Austin Daily Texan
From March
Talk to Irwin speaker
His title is listed as associate
Professor of botany
Also from a copy of publication the alcalde
From October 19th
Also
Professor
So from 19th
For tonight
Associate professor of biology
Are outside by professors are typically professors that are on the 10-year
Working their way towards becoming full professors
Add an academic
Katusha
They've paid their dues as an assistant for
And now they're in that middle step
There's absolutely no shame in being an associate professor even if it's for a long time
Cuz the super competitive ranks
To achieve at most talk to you
Your school and ut-austin is not a bad
That's cool
I found all this out because
Dr. Irwin
Spear would have to have been in
What Alex's dad would have been the Apes
He's supposed to had this completely not
There's literally zero reason to believe that the globalist
For having us do see a professor
Working their way towards their tenure
Take a little break from their Scholastic nefarious eugenics
This story is accusing
Specific person
Of being involved in a plot against
Humanity
It's a conspiracy
And Erwin
The story I was just telling you trying to recruit people with this Pacifica
Genocide and crimes against
Humanity
I'm not sure Alex feels like he's safe
Because they're Winspear died in 2002 but still this is some
Shady s*** Alex
Is doing
This story absolutely didn't happen
There's no way
There's no way associate professor Irwin
Spirit
Hey David
Jones future dentist
I'm going to try and enlist you in life Global us Eugenics you know it's like Hitler but I'm not like Hitler I'm Jewish it's
Totally cool we're going to get everybody
You're way off on this one of course
It's him because
Such b******* if anyone cared Alex
Easily be sued for
This is slander
Yeah unfortunately
Latest episodes
Is over
Like 2013
John verea circumstance
Can be charged with
But if he was
I would f******
B-real
You get in touch with you
From now on
I will be keeping a very close ear
On the present day episode
For Alex telling this story
Because if he tells this story in the present
Yes
You will have committed a crime
You know what
I bet I can find
This story
I bet I can
I'm digging through the archives and actual
Hard crime
Attempted
Genocide
Conspiracy
You shouldn't use specific names
What a f***
So about 5 minutes on this
Maybe more
It's taken up with Alex getting a caller
Who accuses him of using
Exact
He accuses the globalist
Super defense
About it
I don't I don't know if this clip is
Is worth it
Because I think I think there's something worthwhile in it
There there there is a point
Does the point where Alex's
Defensive is minute
Before this
Actually before commercial
But I think this
This clip really highlights
Alex kind of losing it
Like this guy is making
Decent courtesy
Of him
Okay I think this is
I think this is a that you know you should know
U-save-it
All of these
The globalist do divide-and-conquer but
You and I
The group
And then further the guys other credits
You just try and like
All the time
Totally
EBenefits
Response to it
I think the biggest reason that I think it's worthwhile.
It demonstrates how
Confronting Alex
You're correct
Is not worth it
Brooke was very upset
How can we provocative
The emotion which is a human circumstance
Is out of
Are we going to
Just get it
Because our headlights
Yeah
Hang up
If you're going to take the time
And make these criticisms of Alec
You're not going to hang up when he starts
Respond to absolutely absolutely
Then
Of all the time
That's show me show me
Although I would hang up the moment somebody started
Show me why fear monger
Okay
Here's why your fear
And I'll give you some
Everything everything
What
Reclusive
Yeah he's very sensitive no other one is very very
Yeah
And that's something you don't understand
With kid gloves
But also there's no way to do that because
He has around issues that are pretty
Yeah
You can even approach without
Triggering that respond
Absolutely
It's kind of its kind of
Now for the rest of this episode
Kind of Hazzard
He's like
I'm being accused of fear monger
Which is kind of a sign that he got like
Criticism
Is it goes on
And I think it also has to
Why he's got to
But you know what he does
What to do
Goes for his
Oh no
He finds his
Security blanket
Whiskey
Ted Anderson
Resources
He comes in as a guest
Alex introduction
F****** hilarious
Gold sponsor
Better Business Bureau
That have broadcast to
By the way real quick Stormfront also had a plus rating on
There's are like the Better Business Bureau ratings are a very
Years ago
Better Business Bureau
Plus
Smash cut 22 years later today
Because of a
Systemic
History of defrauding customers
Still hasn't
Of course
Do you know
Hey to get an A+ rated you know what's really
Sing to me those like
Is this point in farts
23rd
Like this is
When
He's really shady biz
Yeah
Where is the mid
2015 when he acts
We gets his license taken away
Offense
Happened prior to that he's actually
Taking people into frogs
So what Alex is doing is like
Really
Throwing people into the ring
He's
This is abuse
Do you know what what's fun is that this is
Almost like it
Preemptive
Defensive whitener
Terrorism
You going on
Long diatribe about how
Greek and his gold sales are amazing
All the while
At least
A little bit aware that
There's no doubt he's almost 100% aware
Come on
He's committed all the crimes I wasn't clear that it was
Introduction
Pretend I thought it might
Plug-in
I didn't realize this this just turns into a
Because of that caller who asked Alex Bell
Alex is really defensive about it anyway
Here is the answer to that
Alex
Your unprofessional
Another sponsor
Really implying that this is not just a sponsor
Chiefly in business
Alex
I know we have a
Difficult Power Balance relationship
But in some ways I am your boss and at the very least
Colleague
I am not here
To make you feel good
Kowtow
To Alex
To be made feel better make me whole again after that call
Servient
You know what's really interesting
The rest of this
Interview with
Is largely
Alex
Bullying
Gold prices
I was just start screaming at
It's almost like he feels
A program directors voice in his head Buick
Pick it up
His
Like
The story of his mom
Taking a bath
So much of his relationship with Ted Anderson
It's weirdly
Mommy
As opposed to anything else like it's always like
I think it's a brotherly more than anything
Ted like a brother
Older brother kind of wise
Less than mother or father
It's more just like
Suck this guy's squirrely
You listen to 10 million more hours
Well I mean
But I do have a better assessment
So
Also I think that in that clip
Is it
Is it fear mongering for me
Need to save it you know
Gold
260 in to feet
It's like 10 years later it's at 1600
The way you sell gold
Is not saying eventually it will be worth
You sell gold by talking about financial collapse
Yes you are even though the price
Yes
That's fine
You you have
Towards
Not a terrible
Investment if they have the money to make
B
The way you sold it is fear monger
Even if the end result
Wasn't
Negative
The other stuff
Is like
Because you knew that
It's a Sound Investment if you wait
800% return
Youself
Markets about to collapse in the dollar will be worthless you'll be the king with gold
Any good fighter boggart
Gambling on Commodities in the short-term is a brilliant idea
That's what sound tell everybody
On
Short-term
Income
Advice
Absolute
Is rat.
And that comes in
Play the snake
Like everytime Ted's on
Alex
Beat up on him and not let him talk
Alex is on there
2 days
And so what he wants to Riff on is the idea that anytime you say anything people call you
Racist
And so
Lesbian Saturday
If end if you respected salesman this is a bad way to treat it
Nut
If you and I
Are we okay
If we're reenacting this conversation
We're just friends
At a bar
This conversation is
Hilarious
I was never there
I agree with you
That you and I sitting at a bar having this conversation
It goes like this
Whatever the risk
Because
That say you're the one who's yelling racist
We laugh and then we move on to the
This aggressively
Now the B ended when he went
Yeah
After the second round
Yeah right
Tries to deal with this and he's very on
Unsuccessful
Here's how Alex
It sound like
You have
Now that's fine
Really really satisfying about treated so poorly
In context of the episode when I cut the
Eclipse
That is what happened
Really sounds like
I just edited together Ted
With Alex saying things over it
You made that very self-conscious of it like I do I do
A professional call your main sponsor
But he's yelling at your right right
I get that you're passionate about that I'd love to talk up I'd love to talk about going
It's almost like I have a soundboard
That is how he treats people
That is one of
Best bits of abuse I think we've ever seen
I have no root
Did either one of those people's feelings that I hope they both
Get hurt as much as
Real sympathy for
He's a piece of s*** he hasn't come around
When you're trying to make a point that's beneficial to both of us trying to make
That will
Financially benefit
Right
Nana nana.
I got a head of steam I got this caller said I got to do this
And you're my Whipping Boy
And you know better than to.
To my abuse of every person who got f***** over by Anderson
Listening to that cliff and I'm
Like I'll man If Only They Knew
If only they could listen in here
But
For sure
Not unique
Take it all like Alex treats
Like that quite a bit
Which I cannot hilarious
Indicate to me that Alex is like cool think about I wasn't a bully when I was younger
Is probably not
Does
Traeger like what bullies like to abuse he's a bookish dork
Yeah
What's really f*** you nerd at the Alex responding like
Tatooine is kind of indicative
Maybe that is how you operate
People who have detail
And substance in like
A little bit of a nuanced position
That frustrates you you
You want more of the
Intensity
Until you take it out on
Totally if you could take it out like that on someone who is
Basically
Your meal ticket I would leave
I've also
Maybe
And
He's fine
With
Letting out on air
Difference
Maybe they are the same company
And the next clip
Kind of makes me
We feel like
Gyros
TV ad script
If you are somebody who is being sponsored by
This company
It doesn't make sense
Have to write
Different
Kind of relationship
Alex is here talking about on-air like away we wrote this for Midas
Why
I should be there at
That's them
I mean
Like
I'm not sure about this
But I think that's
Very borderline
Illegal illegal
It's just like
It's an indication
Print all intents and purpose
No I know
Babe
It's it's
Motorcycle
Revenue through Midas
Is
A lot of it is
Alex Jones based advertising
Gcn
As a radio
It's because of Alex
Even if some of them are on board Market
The none of them are nearly as huge
And the shows that they have that have grown into something
Are only possible because
Cuz of the relationship that started
Between Alex and
You can't
Disentangle
They are the same company
They've come up together through decade
Right
And that's why I went ahead lost his
To sell gold
And had a billion dollars that he had to pay off for his mouth
And Alex immediately after that.
Is not a coincidence
I'm paying off
Define
Needs to pee or else
These two companies are
For legal reasons
I think
That's why what he said that we're writing ad copy
For you
That is where legal reasons get into that's why I legal reasons
No ad copywriting
Isn't
Enough
No I know that is a favor
I know I know we presented as like
Look at
He's great with gold not good with the word bully
They can put together an invoice or whatever like that I know I know that's what I meant
He's not good at.
Extend also to the ad copy that
We're all better for it we're all
Alright
Literally literally
It's
Indicate
Such a strong
So much
Deeper then
Recognize
It makes all of the other time
So
Embarrassing
Only sells gold
So much more
Like all of the financial collapse narratives
You talk about what
Yep it it all is
It's so gross
So f****** gross
Yep say one more clip and it's about a story that had come out that Michael Moore
Is apparently trying to
Work towards getting
Photos from
Sandy Hook real
Because he has
Effuse
The other situation
It will lead you to recognize the
The severity of the situation that we're dealing
That poor naive idealist
And so Alex response
That's
Photoshop
This is looking more and more like
Nope.
I know that it seems like
There has been nothing throughout this course
Of this episode about
The main idea that we're looking at
Madden 2013
Progression
At the end of this
March 14th episode
Him saying like
Michael Moore wants these photos
Which would
Shock people into recognizing
The real tragedy
Awful
Situation
Brought about
I need to defend from that
The only way I can do that if those photos come out there Photoshop
Photos
All the way and save it
Event
They still not saying their act
Like in the last couple episodes of dirty 30
Any indication
Studies
Going in that direction
To be like a pretty out of nowhere
I don't know what that was
But I do think
Set this
This white
That he is he's deeply on
This prediction
There's going to be
False flag
Treason
Preemptively
Define encase
Some of his buddies start doing
I think a lot of it is
Is tide in
I think all of it is
Thursday
It is being woke
And I think you said
Sandy Hook
Denial
It can't be understood
Side of those other
Interested
To know
It is impossible to quantify this or or even
Fight
The
They thought that I have is
What is it
Wasn't
Michael Moore
I think you're going
It would probably be the same but the fact that it's Michael Moore
Raises that
Alex Jones has those
Hackles in
Michael Moore
Some of his
Especially his early work
Like I imagined
If it was
Somebody else not
Internet from
Impersonal
Yeah
Like his reaction to Michael Moore doing something is going
To be more exact
Stream
I8u
You would assume
Yeah we're just somebody else
Yeah yeah
Pollock like
I agree I agree and I think also Michael Moore is more of a threat
That's true
I think he'd respond similarly
Even though he hates
Michael Moore
Yeah
I think it all this
Important about it
Of relative
Cultural importance
Sayings
That is why I must
Respond
And if that is
Is what makes him
Dance closer
Like it being
Just different then
False flag
Like his before is the globalist went and killed the children
The Black Sea
Volkswagen different person
Very
So I don't know I don't know what that pretends
The future
But I should tell you I have cut out an entire hour and a half
Events
To an interview with
A grandfather
And I don't care
About that
The radio show
I don't care at all
Stupidest s***
I'd heard
Isn't the episode
And then it goes into overdrive
Overdrive for another hour
But guess what
Alex leaves
What the grandpa host
No
Does he have an honor hung painting is that why you getting the fourth hours at all anybody needs to do
Formal 4th hour at this point forth hour
I don't know why they
It might have been brokered programming
Is it to me
Alex did about a half-hour with this guy
MN
Want to talk more about any vaccine
And they can
Continue the show
And Alex doesn't give us
Alex
I have some Jameson just get out of here
So that's what happened
That's never a dick it ain't listening to this. Time
I'd not heard
Like Alex
Surrender the 4th hours
Other than one of his
Employees cuz there was right there
Think was a 2000
Tried to do for hours
He had people like
Arab dude
Like his employees
Is it due the 4th hour
But
Rogue
Fourth hour
And not good
No
So we come to the end of
I think
This is a race
This this
Gets bullied
Encapsulated by RS
The 14th
March 14th
Was
Impossible to
To get through
Hi I'll just it was just
You're digging through
Racism
The entire time
And it's triggered by the LA Times
Narrative
Started on the 30
Goodbye him
Defend
These very real murder 3
That wanted to sponsor
People in his community
Deworm a cat
So
Because we're in 2019 and I'm looking back on
So many died
He's saying if there's going
Beautiful swag
And I know why
He's doing that because Valdese
What I just described
The militia people who are threatening to do s*** like
But then the fact that a high-profile
Does
And it's not playing.
You know it
It is
And tamerlan Tsarnaev
That becomes
They're trying to blame me for the
I know that cuz
Like I just
These Dynamics happening
Really makes me
If I'm very excited about this. But also I'm so
F******
I didn't know
In March
Alex's
Predicting a terrorist attack is about to happen
No
Vet
Couple months before this one of his buddies is hurting
The shoot and kill people
All of this
Context is very new.
Ayam masak
Idea first
Your prediction that the Boston bombing
Start getting Wild
I'm really excited cuz
Starting to sound true
Everytime all in the past
Suddenly you got to give it up to the Somali pirate
It really does look
Like things are like a solid
We're getting a hanging cement mixer curveball at the goddamn belt
Because history is Prelude
What is going to happen
Is that he's going to start saying
And there were actors
Before
Exactly
Where's the Dynamics in the Boston bombing happen
He's going to lose his mind
In all things are going to come together
March 17th comes on guys I got to tell you
Eastern Buffet are confusing assholes for informing us
That
Pornos. Thank you for bringing
Probably next episode
I don't know we'll see
The show
As soon as we can
Yeah
But until then
You know what
What
Facebook we are on Facebook
Now if you wanted to download
This podcast
And you could do that by going to iTune
We're X
In the
Pass right now
So you're in the future
The other way to download
Travel to build a time machine table to download
That is if there are a bunch of episodes
That are buried in the
Rare like
200 episodes only access
If you have a time machine
And you travel back
1776 on the other hand
You could also
Founding father
And we said you protect this like you protect gun to Anti-Federalists some of it we gave it to
Machine
100 more episodes of our show are available through
You can also find them on iTunes once you get that rash.
You could travel forward however to 2100
T76 Windows episodes will be
Excavated and finally they will be by the great archaeologist
Nam's. Halsey walk the dog on Earth
Episode
I don't know why I joined
The Jesus Lizard
Alex