Hey everybody here with a little apologies lunch clarification
Alex's response to the news about Jeffrey Epstein
How about you know what they say about plans the best-laid one
Nice man all that good stuff
We ran into a little bit of a barrier in terms of following through on that plan
That on Saturday Alex release date
Which is actually just a 1-minute of him rambling an airport with a ton of nervous-looking people behind him
I meant one minute of commercials
Turns out the Alex Airport
Because he was going on vacation
It turns out he's not going to be back until Friday August 16th
You got Tom pepper that boring guy who owns the station still broadcast
Staying on the snow this week
And Alex called in to ride shotgun as he likes to put it
The stuff about Epstein was very boring and predictable
Use them to attack Trump
That sort of thing
But honestly that wasn't most of what the episode covered
It seemed to me that Alex was far more interested in complaining about his vacation
According to Alex he ran into some people in a pool
We decided we're lawyers because they had what he describes as bike rider body
There's no real explanation about having a bike rider body you're a lawyer
The Divide is leap in logic
Anyway these alleged lawyers harass Alex in his pool because the left is so evil that they can't even allow
I went to enjoy his vacation
Bicyclist
I want to hear a child
Now leaving aside how this absolutely
I'm leaving aside how badly Alex wants to be the victim in all these stories that he tells
Believing is super suspicious that Alex goes on a week-long
Warriors money bomb
What I want to focus on is how the pool is the most dangerous place where Alex debate
We all know he was accosted by globalist in that hot tub a while back he hasn't globalist mess with him
The hot springs at Barton
Barton Springs
To the water
You should have learned his lesson stay out of the water Alex the globalist come for you
Anyway what I listen to there wasn't an episode there too to go over
And I hope you'll enjoy it
The Jordan I recorded before he took off for his vacation
Is it a conspiracy that Alex and Jordan went on vacation at the same time
It's definitely probably possibly a conspiracy and please have a field day speculating about it
Until Friday
I want to just let you all know that we're not going to have an episode on Friday this week dude just a difficult
I'm trying to pull it off and farm content
To go over from like I know he's probably going to Robert Barnes hosting have his lawyer host for the week
And I'm not into listen to hours of barn stock
So we're just going to go ahead and take that day off back next week
With coverage of everything that merits discussion
But I appreciate you all
But for now
And that we will see you soon
Shredit.com
I have great respect for knowledge by now I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Stripe.com
Was there a band when you were in high school that was like
The local cool band
Yeah did you ever go to those like like open mics for bands in there.
It's hard for me to say that about high school time cuz I might have been a little disconnected there might have been some
Bands that I knew of that were
I'm not entirely sure
Alberta
Like a little bit later there was a band
It's called Warhammer 40K
They were really off
Who's a little too loud generally a little bit too bright
Buddy's his little brother Cooper
Had a bit of an association
In my circle of friends but
Some of the members of it became case
They were the ones in Europe
Making some
It's good music
It's not my son
I don't know I think yeah I think Warhammer
/ cave
It's probably the
Columbia local music scene
Not really felt Dojo account
I don't know what you tell me about
I decided
To go into project
That we
Attention
Characters
Guy with telescope
We've got a telescope we have Mark Richard
Anytime of our creatures episode comes up we got a week
Top of the list guy who wants to storm The Getty Museum
These are like characters that we've become friends with
Overarching
It becomes a sort of thing where it's difficult to listen to any episodes involve them
Right because
Texas map
And there's one other guy of course Eddie page
Palladium
That's what I decided to do initially when I said I do
Episode
Was I wanted
To check in
Because last we heard of him you'd fallen out of Kerry Cassidy
Project Camelot
Restarted it and accusations started
Come out that use passing-off screenshots from video games Mothership
Called-out he took turn for the dark
Archangel Abaddon
Good for him
I listen to a bunch of his videos cuz I felt like well he's now the angel
This is amazing
Therapy
Is very boring
He threatened to open the 7th
What's the over-under yours 2019
So weird
The aftermath
He told us
You do you think that's something that you wouldn't even know about Katie's like 7 hours warning
So now he's leading a small cult
Based on
The videos that I could
Until what time comes
Which people actually
Okay nevermind nevermind I don't know why sometimes
You have some sort of opticians
Let me tell you there's no way for me to find out if anybody is watching me or anybody cares about
I think that even
The greatest
So I went down that road I realized that maybe
It's not worth it
I can't make an episode out of
Is Eddie Pages turn
Intuit Archangel Abaddon
There's just an it's bad presentation it's bad contact
Maybe
Maybe it's time to let go
Maybe it's time to
Usher Richards comes up
Course but maybe it's time to let go
Some of these
Connections
Beehive with these other people
Steven Kelly certainly not going to cover him again
He is way too scary
Absolutely
You got to let him
I decided maybe it's time for us to
To try and find
New friends Project Camelot world
Episode
Deceit
Society
I thought
Hello
I love
I like to study
I was going to be we're going to look into and
We'll see what happens
But before we get to that
People who signed up and are supporting
Your show
And make it pop
So first
Next Luke
Thank you so much
Lux Lux me strong Loop
Not robbing our haban thank you so much
Thank you so much
Stop shut up
We got Kelsey thank you so much for joining up and
But I looked closer
There's no spaces
But it's clearly Taco in a
I think I prefer
Inspected next Eric W thank you so much
And then finally Lee Ann McAdoo is an anagram of
Almani okan.
I didn't know that
Heroin
Is freakishly large
Thank you so much thank you Eric
Anagram of amnio Contigo
To all of you
Show
We appreciate
Anytime you got the full three names were talking to Fascination or somebody who is to be looked out for
This is going to be fairly interesting
I don't know for sure if I want to save it
We found a new friend
But I've certainly learned a lot
As we go along
I v I've learned
He's capable of
What she expresses
In this
Out of context
So where are you getting
Information and why do you think it
It kind of means then
Ouch
So we're going to get there
So all this b*******
Point out that this interview was posted before the 20th
16 election
1/3 twenty-six also interviewed
Willie Windsor crack
On her show
Which is
Introduction
In
The way the only sheet
Kerry Cassidy from project and tonight we have a very interesting gas
I've actually interviewed her in the past her name is Emily Windsor Craig
And she is a fascinating woman and she has a great deal to share with us
Today about some investigations she's been doing
Inquire ancient
Human Society
More of a bio here is Gary laying out some of the important facts
Don't forget
She had her own star
Start up
In the early 90s
Call play Technologies Inc
Which failed to gain funding
I know what that's like
Let's see she was radicalized during the Clinton Administration by
Focus on globalism and the effects of HR practices
Gaslighting by Corporation
And I she wrote a small political Theory newsletter when she lived on top of
Hill
Call just now
She was Redland 1998
Spent the next seven years running from gangstalkers
Gucci gang song but not radicalized
On the run from gangstalkers
She's too busy running to to get radicalized
I suppose
Maybe a couple years into
Years which overlap with the running for gangstalkers
So
She's been doing some research
She gets here into this is where Emily jumps
She expresses what her goal is
Elvis
I don't know if I like the title of this video being
Human Society
Because I don't believe that that's disgusting
Yeah I guess on that
Still I think
Between spiritual
So I decided to try to make
Synthesize
A single timeline out of all the books
I showed you in
To explain
Where we are politically
Spiritually and physically
Put it all together
When you hear something like that
That sounds
She wants a grand unified field Theory
Grace
The only thing is
Ask the question when she
She saying all these books
What the f*** books are you talkin about that is a very important question
You could be talking about the Necronomicon
Necronomicon if you're unplugged project much higher likelihood that you're talking about books
That aren't create a grand unified field Theory
Out of imaginary books in this world because
It is tough
As soon as she said that I was like okay I need to know
I need to know what you're trying to
To bring together if I
Define off on your mission
Because
Slater
She does explain what books
She's talking about
The books that are
Fascinating to listen to
If you can keep home because she's
She twerks
Are the beginning
Story of
This planet because the Bible doesn't go down for the Rancher book doesn't go back that far
And so
That's where
The Story begins
According to
Which makes sense
Oh no
Glory
Population
You can't get Tori
Get what they wanted
Already like you're about to be super racist
Raise all the way to the certainly has the feel of this being very
Baby
Like some of this stuff could be very easy
Yeah yeah weather is conscious
So the books that she's using here are the Urantia book which we covered it past episode
Lot of bulshit
Interpretation positive about her interpretation
Who is Aviana Weaver Carrie bring her up all the f****** time
And it's just
It's the same thing
She talked about
Sean David Morton
Wrote some sci-fi book that she believes is actual truth
It's called Voyager
And she believed
I don't know.
Play science fiction
I think they are supposed to
Alternative history of the universe
Terry believes they are unveiling
They're supposed to be
She thinks it's creative nonfiction
Straight up history
Teacher or is someone called her a cult leader
Whose real name is
Savannah Hayes
Completely true
Information about the secret history
I honestly wish it was more interest
It's not
From everything I can tell
Bikers Promises of the return of these
These people that she calls the guardian Alliance
Just never seems
To come to pass
Prediction
They're coming
Money gets handed over nothing verifiable has ever said and then nothing
The reason that these things are really dangerous though it need to be taken seriously
Is there
Do the vast majority of cases where someone has
Disseminate
Pejorative
But sometimes something does
You need to look no further than Heaven's Gates
If you have a framework of UFO called can be deadly
In the hands of the wrong person
Anyone drawn to starting their own group like this is someone I considered
And that's not even
Because of anything that there's
Quality
Between different races
Is something that puts you in a category of
Dubai on
Yeah I don't know if I like what you're up to
Start my own UFO cult
Even if I agreed with everything they were saying I would like
Spiritual gurus
My hands on a copy of her book so I could better understand what you preach
These books are out of print
F****** expensive
And I can't find it
Ultimately I think I've read enough books in that
Genre
No more less it's going to be like
From what I've been able to tell odeens writings online
Cuz I have read
Breakdown
There seems like there's a big
Sisters on genetics
And her philosophy
Humans as created by the
12 strands of DNA
You're missing some of those
Which somehow help the Manifest in the third dimension
That would present to get involved in art
Get out of our Jeep
Which honestly
Kind of sounds a lot like space replacement anxiety
Kind of poetic science fiction version of white genocide propaganda
We know that Carrie believes
So like if she gets a lot of her info from ashiana Dean
I wouldn't be too so
Surprised at 2
I don't know that to be taste I haven't read enough of her material but like
If Carrie is a huge.
Disciple of asean
That's one of her beliefs
If it doesn't have Mark
Right
I got to say no thanks yeah it's a little bit like a
Beartooth
Make that assumption
At this point
Later in the episode babies I don't think there's anything necessarily wrong with
Time trying to unite like space philosophies hurting anybody whatever
Only when it becomes
Damaging or is clearly reinforcing something negative
I bet I even care
Rises to the level of being really interest
So far
I'm not sure we've reached that qualify
Gotcha
But we might in this
I can look into this
Books
Personally
I'm assume inkarnate of one of the Anunnaki bloodline
And so I have
Telepathic contact with that
Not
That everybody in that bloodline degrees together or with me but I'm part of the bloodline
NAA NAA
Who was the Anunnaki
Who died in lakes
Okay so I have access
Alright
Yeah I know that's a couple weeks ago
That's almost like one of her sword
Oh yeah
Years ago to you almost had
Which now is like our right
I'm starting to get interested now
Who's the new king
I don't know she's
Okay alright
The Kings win
Legitimately
The king release date
I am really uncomfortable now when anybody says bloodline about
Evil
Peking died in 2012
Only reason
You might
I think you missed the deadline
Now in 2007
I don't know if you seen his pictures
Who has apparently been revived
That were
Him
One had an elder gentleman who didn't make it
What's not revealed who it was
Surprisingly Carrie is not sold
Okay now let me let me slow you down one minute here so you think that an Anunnaki
Sarcophagus
Calling him I think
Was that a YouTube
And you believe it
Several references today
Video
Lot of references to that YouTube video
Sister her telepathic
Connection wooden crdc
Tagalog
Interesting story
Kind of fascinating
In 2008 excavators working on prepping
Construct
Kurdistan
Accidentally uncovered an Iron Age grave
With more than 20 and text
This is a really cool Discovery and there were indications that there were all sorts of burial Goods
Plenty for researchers to learn from the grave
According to a report co-produced by gent universe
Within a week however a hoax was create a run to this.
Discovery the game
Reports and press releases began bench
I think the discovery of 6 Corpses
Instead of five
And they became a mummified King and five of his bodyguards
The media frenzy was supported by a 36-second video fragment that was placed on YouTube and various others
It is the orchestrated discovery of a bearded mummified king with a crown
A gem encrusted gold box into gems
Encrusted gold plate
With cuneiforms inscription
The forgery was so crude that no professional archaeologist could ever be fooled by it
But
Many others were and unfortunately such a Jones style stories
Are still persistent
Circulating on the web
We hope this preliminary report May for once and all put in
Do the circulation
Conspiracy stories related to
Working out in 2012
Best as I can tell
It did not end
Speculation kill King Bernard
This happens a lot
A large section of the space weirdo Community particularly
Pyramid
Who know that nothing is ever going to prove what their argument
I'd say are true
Piggyback any real archaeological Discovery and try and co-opt
Get into their world
This Behavior manifest
Different ways
You sit here with this hoax mummy video of attempted Co-op this graveyard
You see what the insist
There's a cover-up
When Mainline archaeologists won't admit there was Anunnaki in that
They use that as proof that there was
The same sort of thinking is what's behind Carey arguing
Isis was created so that the New World Order can go rounded
Destroyed
These relationships
It's all about coop
Reality in such a
Deceptively elevate your ideas
And give mask
Going to why you can't prove any of the things
You say it's a good girl
Real archaeology
Do the hard work
Fake a little video and pretend that it's related it's almost like your job is just sitting waiting around for somebody else to do
Do stuff and then you lie about it
Morph bulshit
Here's Emily talking more about
YouTube
Somebody pinches him like
Okay so if I ran
And the guy has a beautiful red.
Cool
Love it
This is just
Like a really good
Encapsulation of how little proof people in this world require two
I've seen screenshots of this video I didn't watch
Start video
And it is
Next level
Clunky
It's the sort of thing it's like carries video or picture that you showed of Anunnaki leading human prisoner
No
Emily starts talking about the Emerald Tablet of Thoth
Which is something that's really big
It's complicated
Okay
I like to I like to add golden tablets like
The other tablet
Emerald
Look at the tablets
It's it's very big
This space
Foundational documents
I don't
I'm not sure it exists
So anyway she starts talking
Think about stuff
Saying some stuff that's a little bit weird
Carrie.
There are you are saying
Things that are different
The Zacharias it's material and some other people I've actually
Forget the investigators name off hand that I interviewed but I there's another guy who does
And he's got a whole nother group
A people that he
Serta identify
So it does get quite confusing but continue to clarify.
Resources and turn me on to other resources that question
About your love this podcast
Reality
The resource
Emerald
It tablet Elsa
To a treaty
An emerald treaty
Jordan imagination
This next
Cliff Jordan
2 minutes long
The more confusing alright let's find out
This is where I really think it becomes
Like we go from
In the Royal bloodline of the Anunnaki
They dug up a living Anunnaki in Tehran video
Sure this is okay
I think she's talking about something
So around
500000 BC
Because the Lorenz
Trusting
Basically predatory
They were unprepared
Deal with
Stole the emerald
In order to protect
The white races
Predation
Oh God
Yeah you're making
Why is that
Reptilian race
Treaty
Actually
For white races that are supposed
To be protected
From creditors
Turn out to be very.
Because what
Cultures in the galaxy
Route
Okay yeah because I'm not familiar with this
And you're making so I'm wondering where this is coming from
And there are
There are there are so many races that that are mix
I'm here
Emerald
Covenant actually covers all the races
It's not just the white one
What's the problem
Wait
The reason this is really confusing
Best reading I can take
Yeah it is
Explain white supremacy
Tens of thousands
If your old Emerald 3D
I believe
She's doing
So here's what I'm getting from her
Admittedly
Brilliant explanation
Sure
So
Reptiles in Whiteville were like let's
Make this treaty endless put it on Emerald because
Emerald last forever everybody knows
Absolutely
Every kiss begins with a
Ephemeral
Do they got slammed also
I was going with your busy at a restaurant
Ordering steak
People
So then
Because they made
The treaty specifically with four races of white people
Apparently
Galaxy was like well
Clearly
If the reptiles are making
A treaty with white
Specifically
That means white people are more special
Then the other
Non-white races
Your guys's
I don't think your far-off probably in terms of
She saying but I'm more interested in what's behind it
Because
The Galaxy thinks white people are better or
It seems that way the unfortunate result of this is white supremacist
That's what I think she thinks
This is a way of reinforcing
Space treaties
You
Make
So you can't really deal with the issues
White supremacist
Galaxies fault you got to let them
It's kind of the same thing is just like when you take away
Real world
Cause and effect
System
I've been the root to the
What you're doing is enabling them to
Perpetuate
Because you'll never deal with it.
So even if
Consequence
Of the space treaty
It's still like it's as damaging as just saying like it is what it is
Well I mean if you're going to say that it's the consequence of
Space treaty
He's been you're saying that the way to
Solve
Supremacy negotiate the emeralds
I think we're going to get me why aren't we doing that right now.
We really should
Anunnaki royalty you should be doing it
You're right she's negligent
Instead you just complaining to carry
I thought that was very can
I'm not entirely sure what the deal is
More troubling
I don't like this
Into 208,000
Engineering on the white races
Reproduce
Erase
Okay yeah I just don't know why you're a sizing White
Because he's not clear
Current day real-world consequences from
I just
Feel like whenever
Talking about white people
South
Forgot I always
I always feel like
You're on
Sort of touchy growl
And what you're saying
South Africa
This is part of the predicament that were in now does she mean
The post-apartheid South
Africa
Predicament where it now
You presume it would be something
To do
With
Issues
Surrounding White
Offering any kind of real
Critique
On that level
I don't know
And it seems like
Carrie is
Less
Offended by the whole White Fang and more like
If you're going to be racing
You better back it up
The sort of
Resent
Application
It's possible that Emily understand ashiana
Better than her
Anybody who
Pewds Mark Richards
Push back on
Or
Claim sort of authority over her source
Right
So
I thought that was weird
The emerald
To protect white people
Miners
I feel like she
Speaking in code
Mexican
Jesus teachings
He said you would be persecuted
This Is War
The Romans
No
That Christians will be persecuted
Siri
But you know where you getting that the Jesuits
Had the Quran written
This is an interesting interpretation of my hammock
I understand
Known history
History
Known history like that's a very vague term we can't
Actually band around because nothing
Right now
As as you know
Because everything are our history are lies of within lies
Fair enough
York Street I would I want more people to shout from the rooftops
Islam is a false flag operation
This isn't saying like the two things that I think are particularly notable about that clip is the first
It
It's embarrassing.
50 carry
Capable of this
Because that means it's unacceptable
I'm going through
Never any
Let's discuss how we know these things
The other part of it
That behavior
Extravagant claims wrote the Quran in order to
Victimhood for christening
Volkswagen
Walt's first does that
I meant seconds
Sushi make that claim and then it's no history
That is the same behavior that Alex Jones
He said something really f***** up nose
Yep the appeal to some sort of vague authority of like
Your jump
It's a strategy
You know that they believed
If you're going to if you're going to question me on
The fact that Islam is a false flag you might as well question me on that
Abraham Lincoln was an alien and that's why I wore that tall hat to hide his f****** Conehead
Exactly known
Episode I had this feeling of like
Bring some stuff
Pretty
And I like
Weird like
I am from Anna.
I don't know
Beating up on someone
Who just believes
Weird stuff
I believe that Islam was created in alright I don't care about your feelings
Get graduated
You are quite literally
Validate
Tons of people
Carrie wants to know where she's
Kennedy's ideas from
I prize it goes on
But it's
She wants to know where
Getting you from
Find out it's
But also
YouTube
Plenty of Muslims her going to take issue with the notion
Basically created Muhammad in some way or mine
Controlled him or something to do with it
Is that that your idea
That is
Mystery
Understand it
From
Dr. Bill Warner
Okay alright this is somebody that you
You
Okay is that right
This interview definitely should have
Let's find out
Bill water is dependent for a guy named Bill French
I have no idea this is
But I like to have fun
So I assume that after 9/11 he heard we were going with freedom fries news like s*** I better
Board program
Publishing is he your bill your first name is shorter French name
So Bill franchise the founder of the center for the study of political Islam
And he's been one of the main voices putting forth a narrative that Islam is largely political system and not a religion
So many of the propaganda
Complaints about the spread of sharia law Trace back
To him and his 20s
10 book Sharia law for non-muslims
The splc includes him in their category of Muslim hardliners
Which is a rare group to be at
Along with the likes of Pamela Geller David Horowitz
I assume all the fun
Bill has absolutely no education on the subject
He's a former physics Professor who just had some half cooked Notions about Islamic decided
Because of his designation
Will take a s*** a bit more seriously than they would coming out of the mouth of some dumb dumb on YouTube
At dusk here we are
Bill Warner's is seriously dangerous or
Information Emily say that this is where she crafted her the
Created Islam from is super f***** up
I found Emily's bitchute Channel
Choose another key off brand
YouTube fire people go in their kicks off YouTube YouTube
Videos
Fear of Muslims and immigrants
It's really important to recognize that however
Steer someone insist that their living Anunnaki
All too often these sorts of beliefs and preoccupations
Accompany
And the reason for that
Suspect is at the world
The Project Camelot existence
Trains people to accept
Claims with
Completely non-existent thresholds forever
Do something
That must be true
Define
For picking the couch
But it's not good
In terms of
Philosophies history
Concrete facts
Especially not good
Does it resonate
Field trip
Yeah
A bit of a war over
Whether or not objective reality
With so many leaf
Even within an objective reality there's still room for
Subjective experience
Considered subject
Delete rude to you and not to me exactly
That's what makes our conversation
Much more difficult
It's whatever
Become an abscess
Buddhist about
He running
Into real trouble
And I do
The problem really wanted
Distinguish years
This woman is
Presenting the
Kind of fun
Also
This is not fun
Yeah believing
Islamophobic
The entire
Religion of Islam was created in order to an
Antagonize
Christian
Being its own thing
Islamophobic
And just because you have a fun way of getting there
Pastries and Emerald Tablets
Islamophobic former physics professor
Yeah it's never like
Emerald space tree
Design to make everybody feel good like there's always a bulshit Enemy at the end
Crazy
So
She has some issue
There's some problems there too
Getting back to the life of Jesus and so on so forth
Jesus was not actually hung on the cross.
Okay still fear not
Jesus
It's not the one who
To sound the Merovingian bloodline
Okay we know that that's part of bloodline
Jesus
Important King Arthur
Pretty sure he's related to
Certainly not everybody knows that
Jesus bloodline
Is it
Was not real person that also
British is realism
Wouldn't have to be considered a certain type of British Israel ism
I don't know if we are really nonsense
Specifically here in that last question what book they're talking about
She said the gospel of Barney
But it's important today
Walk you through some of the reasons why this might be
Confusing
Number of books describe to Barnum
Federal.
There is the Epistle of Barnabas
Which is dated back to round 70 to 132
And then there's the acts of barn
Which contains language
5th Century
Neither of these were considered canonical and it's possible that the epistle could have been considered by the Council of Nicea
Actor Barnabas
Postdates
So Canta
Kicked out by the
The problem is that neither of these books contradict the crucifixion
In fact the Epistle of Barnabas
The one that would have been around
Surround
Passion and martyrdom as a rich
However there is another book of Barnabas
The gospel apart
And I suspect that this is specifically the book that tekere and Emily are discussing
The Gospel of Barnabas includes the belief
The Jesus escape crucifixion and the Jews
This place
The Gospel of Barnabas
Definitely a book that is
Not in the Bible
But here's the thing
There's no way the Council of nicaea could have kicked it out of the Bible 50 years ago
The Council of nicaea took place in
The earliest versions of the Gospel of Barnabas traced to the late
This is very reason
When you're talkin about biblical
The count of the Gospel of Barnabas includes a lot of elements
The contradict Christian doctrine
The son of God
Prophet
Many of the areas where the text
Departs from Christian belief
It's in line with the Islamic understanding
Christianity
Suggested
The text was written as an attempt
Combine the beliefs
True Religion
But that's really just a hypothesis
The world of extra biblical literature that seriously wide
When you allow a time span
I've considered books to extent
You could possibly and probably find just about any argument you want to make with any of those books
The Ghost Song
With a book like the Gospel of Barnabas
It's really easy to get there
You want to make the argument that this book proves that
Jesus wasn't crucified and that the Council of Nicea
Be a cupboard that but it just doesn't
You can make it makes
If you intentionally
Confuse people by combining the gospel of barter
That makes the argument you want
What was written in 1500
With the Epistle of Barnabas which existed in the correct time. But doesn't
The argument
It's either evidence against
Same levels
Sloppiness in research
To mislead peep
And I don't know what it
I don't know if it's just foolishness or
I don't know I could easily see it just being like
Confirmation bias
What you want to believe
Willingly
Combining the two or getting it from a bad store so that is intentionally
Any of those things are possible whatever you're doing
You are disseminating
Because it is
The Gospel of Barnabas was not kicked out
Reality I'm sure that you could
Could be like
No it was written in the discovered
Gospel of Barnabas
Paul wrote Epistles all over the place and
Some people believe
Some pieces
Gospel of Barnabas
Do traceback
Two older
There's no
Opinion about that or
Surviving
Right
Examples of
What it would be
And we don't have
Are the epistle and the ACT
The Barnabas
That are from
Closer to that time. And neither of them
Fulfill the other requirements that they need
Which is Jesus escaped crucifixion
Ratified
His place
So they're just
Trying to make
I guess I don't know
I don't know
Anyway we get to present
I don't want
How to do that
She sounds a lot like Alex
People no longer
And what is going on
Pointing out is that globalist
So that we have now had
Presidents
Because our voting system
Manipulated
The globalist
Arenal party you ugly
Yeah
Yep
This
Very
Very similar
It's annoying
It's unfair when they take
The very real
That everybody agrees
Is a very real problem
Create a
Unsolvable problem out of
It's almost like taking white supremacy and blaming on Emerald Street
It sure seems like what you're really doing maybe testifying the status quo in whatever possible way you can
Damn near impossible to get up with
I'm envious
There's a part of me like if there were a way for me to engage in this without descending
Into like
Outright islamophobia denial of people
Religious beliefs identity all that like
I wish I could do it but you'd
It doesn't seem possible
Call blister all around us and their dictator
All this political
Brew haha that's going on
She also believes that the Rothschilds are up to no good
Which is also similar to Alex
The Rothschilds
Pause
She may have Atkins
Conspiracy about the Rothschild
Different than without
Napoleon actually made the Rothschilds
Make Napoleon lose
This is for
Current
Rothschild the Waterloo
But
This one's a little
Buckwild
This week
The new constitution
North America
Which is an Islamic
Surprise surprise
Where did that come
Good
Rothschild
It has not been ratified
Noda
So it is not
Again this is a globalist
Behind the People's Bank
Control
The Rothschilds are globalist
To have
I mean very similar to Alex
The new concert
She is believed that the Rothschilds have written it actual new Constitution and that it's an Islamic State
Actually that far from Alex because I mean you know that Obama was going to get a third term
Becoming a caliphate
So it actually is a lot closer than it actually appears
Yeah I'm different
Dumber
Because it's boring beyond all reason
And the way she's putting it in the context
Because Alex is more careful not to be as / 20
Knowing something
I saw it on YouTube
Honey
He's not super
I was like. Let me know.
I just wanted to make people might hear that and not me
Yeah
Carrie
Has Google
And I don't think she believes
This constitution
Interesting
See how she at
About
This
This disbelief
Okay tonight I can I just stop you there because
You've just brought up this
So-called constitution written by a Rothschild
Information and and why
It kind of means
And do you think it'll get for today's
I see but for the purposes of the
People listening
It can you just
Paraphrase where you're getting this information another words finding a link on the Internet is all very fine and good
Can you stay
Why this this also called Constitution tours means anything
Why did it resonate
To set up a North American Union
So
Soap
Like she's asking
She's asking for it why is it red
With you
Why do cats not good
Help us get anywhere you never going to find any actual information about this f****** state constitutions
Why does this feel real to you
That's great
Presumably
Journalist
Show that the
Secret history book
I've always been like well this fact doesn't resonate with
With me so I'm just going to assume that
Eyewear I'm worried
A lot more people do that then move things
So we get off this topic cuz he's not really able to
The Defenders
Very well
It's not very interesting
Surprise so apparently Emily is writing a new book
Has to do with
Desired
Education
It's in this clip that we learned something else about her that has been sort of doing in the background
For this episode
Slavery is okay
Wrong history
Our children are being taught
Minecraft 2
Teach them footballs
According to causes and effects
Maritime admiralty law
Administrative law
Lunch along the same lines
Spoke to you the other day
There needs to be a year.
Financing
Political process
The precincts were
Cheat codes
You see people taking you survey
Video
Do you know where Thailand is
What's the name of George
The people answering the questions
I don't like any of the three things that
She said to take a year
Have to do with where Thailand is or who your local representative is geography
Almost every High School District
School districts in America require some Civic
Almost every school district
Junior High
Divorce
If they were out of her hands
Crazy
Fingers too long
People learn
Throw out the Sovereign citizen
Because
Stupid also it is a nice like
Tip of the Hat
I did like that I think that if you interpret spending it
Frisk to be economics
Sure kids should learn more about economics
Absolute books
More required as opposed to an Alexa
You're not
You have no information on how to survive understand some of that stuff
I don't know if there are School District
That do a better job
Certainly wasn't
Let me we already do that
In most schools but not expanding that and making it more
Complete
Engaging
Those two things
Are great ideas
You're not going to help you know where Tyler
How to avoid
Helpful
Don't be a cop or a lawyer that you're probably never run into the river
Adjudge
I would say it's like there's a real diminishing
What she's talking about about lot of E-Class
Education
No topic
And I know that a lot of people
Kind of poo poo on some of them
Writing
Reading is really important to be able to express your ideas
And people also s*** on math a lot
Math isn't really all that helpful but the process
The reason that it's such an important
Universal education
Is because it trains
To go through thinking process
It is a lot of science
Like the actual think I'm never going to
You need to balance a chemical equation
But learning how to do it opens up
Process of
In system
That is really important navigate in the world
It is 2 mi
Great
That I have to say this but
Learning proofs
In geometry
Like
When I was in Geometry I didn't I could do all of the math in my head
And then I could come to the right answer
But being forced to actually right down step-by-step
Ripe helped me a great deal in that just
Ability to organize
Your thoughts
How's the lodge
Eric moves
Absolutely
Applications for the real world
Answer when she's talked about this education in order to add Sovereign citizen
You're only going to be able to do that vitamin
Other
High School curriculum
Is because the more you learn the more or the less likely heart
So what's to know like how do you talk
To the Anunnaki
Talk
Question
She gets into some of the
Details here
This is the kind of part of
There's no way around this Theory gets a little bit
At this point
And it's
Where
Kind of thought like maybe we should
Couldn't cover this episode
And I think there's an argument to be made
She will say a few things
That show a deep
Humanity
In her
And I don't want to makes fun of
Any of this
Other stuff that she's saying
Is
Too f***** up to not cover billion people because
She thinks that the
Along those lines now do you believe that you're in contact
To be with a certain group of the Anunnaki
Is that right
Okay
What when you say that do you mean that you're getting downloads how are you communicate
Part of their bloodline they're checking
Orsay
What their hierarchy is
And basically what I say
What's okay
That was okay with it
Probably not
To see what I'm doing
Question
She talks to Yahweh
YouAlwaysWin
He wasn't very forthcoming
Wow that's a misunderstanding
Yahweh pear
Nothing
V of like
Volcanoes
Yeah like that perception
Yeah yeah social stuff
Joey doesn't have a Facebook page
I can't man
Come and check on me
It's a weird conception of how you communicate with aliens
Face come around asking stuff and they don't say anything
We had his interest
But she doesn't
Didn't hear them
Okay
Applebee's
Contact with them and
Art why are you seeing them in person or you just getting a soda mental pictures or what
Alright
I can hear of their alarm system when
Meteorism
Night music
Particularly
Songs that are specific to certain
Certain messages
You have a memory
In the morning
I don't know exactly who it was
What I was going to do here
But
What I sent today to you was going to be
All this stuff has been Guided by the Anunnaki means that the Anunnaki
Don't
Believe Islam is a real religion
The Anunnaki believe that
Add and Anunnaki
He dug up in a hoax
2007 in a row
I would say that if she
She's getting X
Eternal like really wise
You wouldn't perpetuate
I need a grave hope
Respect
To some extent somebody who can take tinnitus
A bad dream
And
Sentimentality and turn them into a
Write a little bit and there's a little bit of a
There's that there's an indication of
How do you spell normal
Experiences
Can be Twisted by
Exposure to ideas
Yeah and they also amplify probably allow you to
Taken
Information
Integrated it's your world music might not otherwise
Like Islam
Fake religion created by
Like
World's I believe
Can be dangerous
Even if
Absolutely
We learn about her being
Incarnated Anunnaki
I was wondering about that
But
I'll just have to
Explain
So are you aware of like the neanderthal
Bloodline
That you may be part of
Okay but you know they made human hybrids right
Alright
Really
I don't fit in
Dairy
Open relationship in terms of trading meaning and thoughts back and forth
And you always still on Tinder
Cookout
I was part of the Royal Line Royal bloodline
Windsor
Okay alright
Alright alright I feel really sad
For her on one level because
Expressing
Deeply human
You know what
She feels alienated for
From people around
She has a hard time
Connecting with her children
The way to deal with those
To create
An entire worldview that's
The rat like I'm communicating with alien
They understand me
Their line of thinking is much more in line with mine
Because it is mine
Right
Turtle
As opposed to just be and I have thoughts
And you can totally see how the the sequence of events could unfold
She starts to believe things that I know she's on YouTube all the time she's believing stuff that is
Kids about it and they're like
That's absolutely not true please stop doing that and then as they stop talking to her
She starts
Craps
Is the story that you hear
Pretty regularly now or at least
Like you see this this spiral of isolation happens
Around these
Please world and I think
Like the people who are promoting these ideas don't want people to have a robust
Healthy ecosystem of friends in relation
Because they will check
Generally
Colts find vulnerable people as you're isolated from your
A real bummer because
On one level I recognize that a lot of the stuff
That she believes is
Probably it's probably a result
Of her feeling these feelings
Becoming more and more entrenched
In this world that leads you down bad
Absolutely understand
And I don't want to
Mark Hereford
But I do think that there's a lot
Yeah I think there's a line
And I also think that it's
Weird
That
She now is
Beartooth
You know sometimes you're not paying attention
And then all the sudden you're the illegitimate daughter of the
She has
According to her she has porphyria
Which proves that
Richie's from
Novel 121
Owl is the line
That's the wife
Of the dinar
That was a nerve
Remember I believe is the wife
Of the Anunnaki who was found in a Ron
It was part of the Royal bloodline
Connected
The herd Subway is there for party
She somehow royalty on Mars
And now she is
One of the illegitimate children of Edward the 8th
Right here
As that it would make her
The
The heir to the British throne
Well there are three exactly
No she's not
I'll see you then there we go
She's not even there yet
I think
This whole thing about her there's a lot of
Controversy surrounding
I should tell you it's a little scared
So she's number 10 is trying to keep her out of the out of the government
Entire life
She has 30 there are three she's one of three of these
Illegitimate children
Brings up one of them
In this neck
Okay
She has a YouTube account
On YouTube
She doesn't like me very much
Alright
I don't know that they do
I'm not positive but that is the case anymore I believe real threat
A lot of a real threat first of all to monarchical system
2nd royal families intermarry is the
Protect
Property
I really think that there would be a very serious
Issue
The foundation
I mean
Just just
. to discover
The Royal Family
Anarchy symbol
Of the United Kingdom
Is just throwing it around
And the rightful Queen
Is somewhere here in the United States
Possibly
So Emily
That what that was
That's interesting because whenever
She was introduced as Emily Windsor Craig I was like
Is it odd that she has an a the name of a royal in her I was hopeful
So poor could be Peggy chylders Virginia
It's mostly full of videos about how she's the rightful heir to the throne
The show Victoria
Okay apparently according to her fpr is a part of the Illuminati
Destroy Peggy's father.
Edward apparently was replaced by a bunch of clones
Doubles
And apparently another one was Emily's father
So Emily Windsor Craig
The cheese the daughter of that of Edward the 8th but actually was one of the Clone
Doubles
Father so she is the rightful heir to the throne
But her mother is not
Like he didn't rely upon her last name is okay
Her mother was Georgia
No
Dissolve
Convoluted
This is convolute
A ton of her videos have to do with how Emily is a fraud
Annabelle
I'd really hoped this would be a more fun way to approach
Situation like
We could listen to a bunch of her videos about this supposed to Harrah's to the throne
Black prince versus us
Another picture
It wasn't a coincidence that you make such a point of the fact that
She believes FDR's
Doesn't surprise me
Subtly racist s*** in her YouTube Channel videos about how like white supremacist terrorism is the
Vine control
Sure
So it's really weird they have another
Pretender to the throne and Miss Piggy
Defensive
You see stuff like
A videos about Michelle Obama that include the words picking cotton in the title
You got 37
And after she brings up
Siri raps
That's what our new friend
Windsor Craig
Tell the anti-semite
Let it
Call man
It's a paraphrase
So I want to see this
Ultimately
Kind of weird
For us to have done this episode and exercising
Hey I would pay
Struggling
Especially with her comments about the alienation
I don't want
To feel like I'm beating up on her
Isidewith
Excuse for Emily
I kind of have to allow it for everybody on Saturday everybody
She's lucid
She defends her position
She has all her mental faculties
She's clearly not in some sort of a real struggle
Like I've seen a number of cases the episode the project
Why we can maybe read from Context Clues
She stopped Furious alienation from people in her life and that's allowed her to adopt some elements
The Fantasy Life
That she feels more and that doesn't make her off-limits to
Iceman
Isolating myself
I didn't have
You know I
I was out of my mind
I didn't suddenly start believing that
A billion people were
F***** over by the judge
Disseminating that information
If we made fun of
What cheese you don't get to see you
Never behaves that way but
The fact that she
Perpetuates
Stop
If you can't not eat
Just allowed because she's having a human experience
How many people in USA adopted that worldview because they felt they didn't fit in on college campuses
Is around the country
How many times have you heard the story people falling in with dangerous group because they offered them a sense of
Community which they thought they lack
This is the story of so many calls
For sure
I believe it's important to treat people fall into these ideologies with a great deal of empathy
And I still do have feelings
However I also believe that the world we see in front of us
We can't allow compassion to entirely blind us to the reality that a lot of the time people who enter ideologies beak
Cousin motivations
Empathize with
Often end up becoming too
Disseminators of the very same ideology
Which is a behavior that cannot be at the thighs
What tip the scales for me was when I was looking to see
See if I could find Emily
Books
Today we come to understand your position
A little bit better
I couldn't find any PDFs or any real reviews of her books
But I did find her blog
What particularly caught my eye was a March 27th
2015 post entitled quote what is a Jew
In the post she argues that the Israelites went to Ireland after the invasion
Conversely she argues almost all people who believe themselves to be Jews are not Jews and quote
Do not have a gift
God Yahweh
Vita Vape
She closes the post I'm sorry but you don't know your history very well
And that's why the Anunnaki
She had red hair
Sure that's why there's a red B
Perhaps
So she's espousing British British Israelite
She's perpetually these things
Even if she
He got stuck
To this stuff
I would never
Do an episode about her
If she wasn't
I don't believe that she has a huge reach
Necessarily on her own
Exercising punch
Down if we didn't episode like you Channel
But Project Camelot still has a much larger audience than
As somebody who has something interesting to say about
Defeat in human society
On that channel
She's being human societies
This is not the first time she's
She's someone who
Carrie had her back on
To a wider audience than then we have our
Traceable back
Back to
Do you like
Islamophobic
Gazelle it
Christian identity
Bulshit that's intentionally misleading about the
Gospel of Barnabas
Hopes videos about a grave
He's still important
That we talk
Absolutely
I think it's still very relevant to our worldview
I don't know baby I'm being a little bit defensive because I do
Prioritize empathy towards
People
And not wanting to beat up on people who were
Struggling
Mental illness that was driving
Her
Then I probably would feel like we shouldn't do this
Able to tell I think that she's just
Somebody
Who believes
F***** up things
And whether or not paying her life letters
She is now trying to disseminate
These beliefs
HEB
Successful
Apply for larger than ours so it's fair game today
She's absolutely fit to stand trial
So to speak
Like
The impulse
Be empathetic
Uber
Overall
Is is very good but
It has to be tempered by a
We can't let this s*** go
Like that kind of
Defensive position
Absolutely
Watching empathy
Is a guidance
When I try and operate through that it requires a lot of
Questioning
If it's appropriate
Laugh
Some of this
Process decided
Industry
It is okay
She posted on her f****** blog before she was a scary show
Yeah
CO2 mite
About that
But it is important
To go through that process office
Because if it if you don't it's too easy
Fall on the wrong side
We still respect
But I disagree
I can't I can't imagine that the end goal of empathy
That doesn't make any sense to me the idea that
We had that
Being empathetic means allowing this
S*** to go under
You know what I'm saying because we understand where you're
I understand where tons of people are coming Reno
It's you go back to
Cereal
A lot of people were abused when they were children but they
They didn't grow up to murderous
Like this
And I'm not making fun of about her
Is her feelings of alienation from other people that to her too
Decide
She is talking to you
Strange how you always agree but I would not make fun of
If this was just an episode where she was talking about feeling
You know did she now has
A bunch of
Communication with
I wouldn't think that was appropriate
It's where it extends
To really dangerous ideas
Towards Muslims and immigrant
Enforcement of that
Worldview
Very
I mean there's no other way to put it
Emeline with the world we talked about
It's it's
It what it is is like there is a version of what she
He's talking about that I would never
But unfortunately
Put the
Considered fair game
Yeah no f*** her
Walking
I want
But for now we're website
Anunnaki book
Run Facebook
Go to bed
Indeed
Also if you wanted to download our show you could go to
You can leave a review there you can also go to the other podcast app
Apps and labor reviews
There are many
Cats
Who carry a you've heard of
Plasmosis
I have
Toxoplasmosis
Sysweld also comes with an episode of Archer
So if you're feeling I have a baby but you'll get our project don't do it
So
I've never killed anybody
Is Alex gay
Alexandra Thurston color