Knowledge party.com
Dot-com
What is
The weirdest
Ever had I know you were across the world
And you have received terrible candies
Stick out in my mind
I erase them never exist
I don't want
The worst one that sticks out obviously Orange
Black rapper
Taffy's that you would get on Halloween
But something rather discuss
Butts
Pick out the most for me
Gabbar is one of the best
Fantastic
The graham crackers
It's a good texter
Great chocolate tastic work Willy
And then the other one is the the
Honeycomb
Is 1
Crunch maybe I don't know it's a honeycomb
Chocolate
So good absolutely I ran into
Like my dad would go.
Conferences
Sherwood have conferences and
Various countries
Honeycomb
Honeycomb candy
He's from some foreign
Market
We were all looking for
Like an arrow
The aerated chocolate
Has a really nice Tech
Extra
Because you've just returned from your trip
To South Africa
What looks like probably the most disgusting thing ever
Candy bar
I'm looking at it original
Original original
Basically
Gummy bears inside a white truck
Play Kodak
I have no idea how it's going to
Damn your first fight
Good opening review
If I can
The jelly tots
Have a very unhappy
First review
If you're going to make a white chocolate think I think it's
You know you're behooved to make it a little bit less overpowering flavor
I'm not into it
How about that that's my review
It's not as bad as I thought it was going to be based on V jelly thing and white
Spit this out
Bro I just
It's a bad texter
That's what I was saying
That
You are eating white chocolate
It's not a
It's not it's not
I hope you had a great time over there
Think too much about the
The song
Africa by Toto
Because of your text
Successful
Remembrance
Until you text
Multiple times
Whatever you do
Hope you'd be out enjoying
Don't worry I'm not reading your diary
Yeah I know it was
I was amazed we were actually if we weren't staying in
We were actually
Which was
Truliant credit
Even that was a was tainted because
Cuz we went out
On a drive
The park rangers
At night and as where
And I on the way back to the
He literally turns around
We're not really big
Taking care of here
I've been here for
For 23 years and they're going to
Make me retire
And there's no replacement
And so he's going on on this whole thing and I'm
Once again
It really awful unlike
Where are you now
Bolsonaro selling off the Amazon rainforest
Loggers and
Like that
Government is just
Starving this place
So I assume it'll go out of bed
It's nightmare
Spider-Man car
Did see a lot of grapes
Wildlife
Oh yeah I was I was
Unexpectedly 25 ft away for a minute
Encounters of elephants to be expected repair for
Startling elephant
We couldn't see it
That wherever
25ft.
Road
And then later on.
We heard that the elephant
Figured out
That nobody was
In the camp
Eating
All of the foods in
So the elephant
It started going into the camp during the middle of the day
Elephants are sneaking in WoW
Cuz elephant tiptoeing grab the sandwiches
Well I'm glad you had a great time
Everybody who has the
Clamoring
How to get back to work I don't
I don't like to say an apology and our friend friend
Who came and we recorded episode on Monday
Or to put out for Monday
And I had to take difficulties in terms
Get out
How to release it at some point down the line
But in order to keep moving forward with the process
Releasing
Episodes in
Keeping up with the show
Forward workload
But I do hope there will be a
Will do that and I apologize
For the inconvenience
For being so kind
Come over
Fly Pole
Looking forward to list
Honeyworks
Being up until 4 a.m. with a
Computer
Impossible to get it out on Monday
I shouldn't complain
Okay
In business and we'll be going over
The August
Episode of The Alex Jones Show
As you may know
Alex Jones went on vacation at the same time you went on vacation
Vacation was announced ahead of time.
Gone away on vacation
For all of last week on Friday
In the meantime
You'd been putting in little video reports
Hand popping in while other people were hosting the show
As he is known to say
Albert
Do a lot of his own show until Friday
When he was actually back
It will be picking up the threads there
And it'll be at
I don't think it's
Like what anybody would expect
Which is now
Expect the unexpected
There are some very very weird
Episode
People
Horse boarding Michelle
This guy what a great night
Daniel thank you so much
Text Laura
Next Erik with a K thank you so much
Deadeye Nick
Remember that
Bedtime
Dover Electric
Touche
The bone
There's a terrible song, 94 in candies
Appreciate it very much
So I did thank you so much
Lodi
Thank you so much
And thank you so much
You're all wonderful techno
Heroin
Freakishly large
We would appreciate
Probably clamoring to find out what's that Alex
Does take on.
Death of Jeffrey up
Steven is an I knew going into
It was probably
He's not going to have a good take on it
Benefit stuff from the week
Exactly what you
Everybody said that this
Speculation about
Conspiratorial
Actually make any sense
And it's reasonable to assume that this effect
Number of documents had been released
Before
His dad
Jeffrey Epstein
Please document exonerated
Jeffrey Epstein was no longer useful to the cabal and so they killed him
Basically Alex
Position
It's a it's a situation where I I just I don't have the patience
To get in
Intuit quite frankly not large part of
When he comes back
The duty on the 16th
A
Minor
Thing for him
I don't know it's just
It's not it's not
Particularly compelling
His take on it
I honestly
Auto Value Inn
And I was going over it
Which is why I'm not going to go over his little guest appearances on his own show while he was on
Vacation
Stupid
I'm kind of
I don't know
The time
Absolutely
Around to it another and there's more information
Actually be looked in
Into down the road I'm willing to
Explore this topic
But for now the recovery
See that it's barely any
SUV
Which seems like it should be
But it's not
Don't look at me if you look it up
The connection to Trump and the bless you talk about FC
Sing the less you talk about
Trump be in Ankeny
It's weird
Journalism
A little bit
Oh good love that I f****** love that just
Again
Coming up holyshit
All the truth and import
Give his opinion probably on my court date
F*** you
Yep that's fun
I like that I like that complaint
Literally
Say why you shouldn't do what we are doing
Yeah like I said sure we get things wrong all the time because we were
Journalism used to happen
That is really what
Look
Normal places it's been a long time on this
We don't really care so where's could speed through
We've not do a good job
But we walk cuz he's not really saying that they do a month
Worth of work in the day or whatever
You saying we don't work that hard or that long
So I Norma's coming in and it's actually not really
To talk about Ali
It's about another case that Norm might be represented
Ice officer this morning
Regardless of what happened
Rhode Island
No he pulls up around the corner doesn't see him
Even told
Attempted murder
Foaming at the mouth
Freaking
Screaming Alex would be if a truck almost ran over a second amendment protester
Can you f****** imagine
We're not putting
Champion of freedom
Tyranny
Wood
Died with a state employee
In any way driving a car through a line of protesters
Who were expressing their First Amendment right to free speech
Three congregation prank
Airing of grievances
This is crazy
Charlottesville one of the cops
Accidentally
Rear view window out and accidentally touched one of the Second Amendment
People
Alex
To shoot on Cops
Yeah
I I just I mean it's just so indicative of this slide
Pizzana
Pretend
A present
A piece of s***
He still deserves a day in court as a lawyer
The representative was wrong for him to whether or not he's represent
It's a great
The only real reason that I think
You can have any kind of wiggle room
He hasn't officially taken on the case
According to Alex
Presentation
Search still sort of Schrodinger's
Lawyer
If he was qualified to both work criminal defense
And
Ideas
Cuz he's representing that guy who may or may not have murdered his wife
Like he does do some criminal cases as well
For the good guys
Always
An indication that I might have been a little bit too
Quickly
The piece of s***
Just because he tried to calm Alex down when he was screaming
So if we get into what I would describe as the main
Theme of this episode
I August 16th episode
What you might expect it's not
About any major world news
It's about Vivaldi
The Rites of Spring
Interested in hearing how to take on that
It is actually
Weirdest
Defending Trump
Positions I've ever heard Alex
Purchasing
With an X
Dollars of oil
Oh you never want to buy that for a few billion bucks
Greenland
Almost
From North
Politicians
Where are you going
What is this
Tobiko
What
Tipsy
Terrible horrible purchase what the f*** is that
What the f*** out episode is he trying to rationalize
Trump wanting to buy Greenland
The first idea of a president suggested that they might want to buy another country that is completely
Bill Clinton or Obama recent George W bush
Suggested by Ireland
Do you think Alex would be like
What do I got to do to get Fortune
What do I got to pay
Second the population isn't in the hundreds of thousands
Closer to 50
Greenland is very sparsely populated because a lot of the country is uninhabitable
Partially because
The Greenland ice sheet covers approximately 81% of the island
Start a good investment to get it now
Approximately 40% of Greenland is protected land
The Northeast Greenland
National Park
Largest national park in the world
And the area around
The coast are the only place
That they can have
Permanent human resume
Outside of the coverages
Explains why they're such a low population
You can only really
But it's important to remember that just because there's a
The small number of
He doesn't make their connection to the land
Legitimate or any less of a factor when considering whether or not
I'm pretty sure we've
History books on colonialism
It works out
Lynx
Appealing to a low number of people affected by this sort of decision is really no different than just saying that their feelings don't matter
For their own good
All the other justifications
Colonialism
Existed over history
Oh yeah
About 90% of the population of Greenland are Inuit people
Parliamentary government and there have been moves made towards
Complete independence from Denmark for years but they aren't autonomy
In the way that Alex
Suggesting
Just about everything that I own
Of jumping from Denmark to the United States
Enrichment of the United States
Stalinesque
97 /
Also what the f*** did the Inuit population by saying they move their 800 years ago but that's okay
Three times.
Don't you
We've only been here for a fraction of the time that the Inuit have been in Greenland
Won't stop screaming every day about how immigrants are coming into
Do not think that a full-scale strip mining operation in Greenland would bring it
Does he not care about the address
Basically something like that might
I'm sure he doesn't
I need to make this point
It's hard to hear what I'm saying and not think that he's advocating for a return to colonialism
Pretty much every single thing he built his career on
I don't know if
He was saying there
Yeah he is
Thinks that if we somehow just
By Green
Will their time from
Groenlandia
So they'll just take a parliamentary vote on whether to sell
Yeah so it's like a housing Administration
All getting together and being like well we'll get this I don't know how has it been
And then Greenland citizens will then be allowed to vote again on whether or not
Become the 51st state
As though that is in there
Yes I assume so
I don't know if he does
American about
Specifically
Because when you really get what is Ark
Is this
Is even appeal to a little bit there by bringing up Alaska
Buy a bunch of invest
Let's talk a little bit about this purchase
Just of Alaska
Purchase Alaska in 1867
Autonomous
It was a piece of the Russian Empire
And we bought it from them
At least partially because they didn't
So do is way too hard to defend from their positions
Even if great natural resources
Discovery was so vulnerable to capture that it wasn't worth the effort it would take
Protective
Completely wiped out the otter populations they were killing
Prefer
So maintain colonies there's wasn't profitable for them in any way
We paid the Russian Empire and then without the people who lived in Alaska
It was then part of the United
Even when the Russian Empire arrive in
There were approximately 100,000 and what happened
And their auntie
Alaska native peoples are we're not allowed to citizenship until 9
1824 mean that they had no right to vote and at the time had no ability to formally on property
Bereavement file claims
Mineral deposit ask you a
Yeah
Would be something along the lines
Without
For sure
What America is
They were against it
The Bureau of Indian Affairs
Destabilize native life
I made efforts to do away with the indigenous
Cultures of the peoples whose like the United States
Concerned for the natives of Alaska
We the People
The US didn't even make Alaska a state until 1950
Benign and some progress had been made for the seeding land vaccinated population
Absolutely it was not a primary concern when we bought Alaska
My point here is that Alex Jones is a f****** monster
If you were alive in Belgium in the late 1800s Road out that he would have been going around yelling at everybody about how
It was a great idea what king Leopold
I get insane what are you saying is is is crazy
Manifest
Well I mean it's it's a little bit because he has this f****** nonsensical idea about paying
If you put it in slightly different context
He would scream but there's being bribed
Well I'd say we were trying to
Steal the land from Denmark
Right
Dollars
Amalfi's 1000% increasing profit
All the resources the tourism
The development
He's going to be in the Arctic
The first thing first
So I can purchase
Says because Alex can never used
Pacific's correct
It's going to be very bad
His plan to pay off the people of Greenland
Is f****** stupid
He's suggesting
U.s. government to pay each person in Greenland
220 million dollars
Prophet
And it's a f****** Terrain
Leave aside the fact that he thinks of the population is in the hundreds of
Global number of 15 million
If you gave that amount to each person in Greenland that would be 840 billion dollars
That is an insane amount of money
Someone advocating for 840 billion dollars
Greenland
Is not a fiscal conservative I would argue
By any stretch of the imagination
Avoid giving Americans 100
Billionaire
Stimulus
Where's Alex
He's coming from
I might ask
Does he realize
Are batshit idea for him to justify the
I was kind of s***
Physicians East
Pretended to support for the entirety of his career
Can you imagine Ron Paul advocating for 840 billion dollars to buy Greenland
Alright
Look I know this sounds like a lunatic idea
Just spent 40% of our GDP
I have three proposals all foreign aid
Get rid of OSHA
You just got yourself a standing ovation
Now that the second matter to consider and that is what he thinks there'll be thousands of percent profit
Now in order for that to be the case you need to see about a tenfold
So now we're talking about bringing like 8 trillion dollars and tourism and resources
Play 100 days of owning Greenland
Trillion-dollar bad news about his plan
Currently the GDP of Greenland is 2.7 billion dollars
If the United States were just
Steal all of that it would still take us about 3000 years to make 1000
The percent profit on the purchase Alex's
Make Moscato purchase profitable required almost unimaginable lengths time or an almost unimaginable level of
Destruction of nature
In pursuit of these resource
Oobi horrible things
To do and there's no reason to destroy every piece of
Protected wildlife
Dude end up with the kind of return on investment Alex ism
Colonialist equivalent of John Wall's NBA contract
You don't know John Walsh
The worst contract
Entirely
Pretty close
So like I said I love the idea that
Don't try to use this
Because I need to make this clear
He's talking about
The idea of perch
He sang everyone
Trump is stupid
For wanting to buy Greenville
What is going to be look at all these other times presidents have bought land
Or whatever
And it was so stupid
The argument hinges on the idea that the
These people bought the lamb
That's import
Is okay
The Louisiana Purchase
Yes of course
So let's not let him get into the Louisiana Purchase
Colonies by
Dollars
Equivalent of about
Purchase
Hundreds of trillions of dollars
That's so like
Strange
The president during The Louisiana Purchase
Because I do right now
Someone who Alex
The foundation of a tunnel
Joseph Thomas Jefferson what the f***
Whoever was President back then
Jesus
What is wrong with this guy
Liberty grown without the guarding of firearms
From a purely Financial standpoint turn out to be purchased
But other factors make it a bit more of a complicated
Situation
Again we were out buying the land from the people who actually live there
We weren't buying autonomous areas
And everybody knows that
The area that was bought in the Louisiana Purchase slaves it was colonized by the French bought it from them there was no consent
Who lived in the area there was no vote about it
It was just a negotiation between two colonizing powers
F*** about the
List of the people who lived in the areas they control
It doesn't
It's impossible to argue with the purchase wasn't a really good investment
It's for the US
But it also sent into place a lot of
Really long lasting problems
Still resonate to this day
There was the disruption destabilization of
Displacement of native peoples that we enact
There was the ensuing war of
Caused by its artifacts
Obviously
The international response to American expansionism
As well as the British
Support of Native America
With the United
Because the United States was disruptive destabilizing
Displacing
So those were factors that
Direct result
Of our expense
The British wear
So I could be made
Out of this Louisiana Purchase either be free or slave state
Which would disrupt the balance between
Compromise of 1820
That compromise likely postponed the outbreak of the Civil War but it also gave an air of legitimacy to slavery
It also made official that anti-slavery progress was not going to extend
Past that barrier remind me
You can't compromise
I'm certain issues you know you
You're compromising with
You're really just
You allowed to exist
There are a lot of serious factors that go into looking at the history of Louisa
Whether or not we made a lot of money
Unimat kind of simplistic logic
With Alex Feel-Rite
You know
Will you be all right with pretty much any kind of Oppression in the name of a good return on
Like let's imagine a super-rich Communists wanted to buy Texas
Have United States cold
Shouldn't he have to be okay with that
I get the super-rich common is paid people so they would vote to sell him Texas
How to never stop screaming but how it was rigged to vote and bribery
That's exactly what he wants.
In Greenwood
A monster like a monster thing
I just got the
His vision of both of us in a bar
Conversation
Goodbye
So
So Alex
Forgot that ghost
His next
Example
Access from the max
Know where it got a little while till we get
Is not as good
Have an example of a perch
River Valley Church
The Red River Valley purchase is not something that
We didn't buy the Red River Valley or the Red River basin
18 at the end of the war of
12th and actually the treaty involved
Eating a bunch of land
From the Louisiana Purchase
The Britain since the treaty established the northern border in that area for the
Cummins making s*** up here or reading off a hastily compiled list
Territorial expansion
United States history
Are there probably one of the interns but together we bought
Concession of land to the British
We fought the War of 1812 and at the end of it we had a treaty that negotiated this borderline Ed we lost
Poncho liner
Robert Ely
Losing the Civil War everybody knows this
So
Now we get to another one
I mean again
Very repetitive
But he's wrong about it
For $5
Present
President
You tell me
Where he's actually doesn't go
I don't think he does
It was Thomas Jefferson
Doesn't make him a great guy
The Florida purchase only happened because Spain didn't want to spend so much
Job maintaining the colony wanted to make a deal with the United States
Treaty of 80
People often misleadingly say that the u.s. paid $5000000 to Spain
A Florida at Alex
$5000000 was part of the Adams Onis
Where in the u.s. agree to pay for the legal claims of US citizens against up to the amount of 5 million
Dollars
It was more an issue of accepting bureaucratic
Responsibility for claims of the territory if the territory was ceded to the United
You realize this is
Sew-ins
Insanely like Howard profession
Call sportsworks
There was no actual payment for Florida
It was a negotiation of the resulting agreement was 1
That was not
Fun fact
Because what he's talking about
The Florida purchase
Explicitly made the US relinquish all claims had on most of Texas
USA
Steve to his Catholic Majesty that's
Renounce forever that all their rights claims of
Pretensions to text
Among other areas that would end up becoming part of the United States somehow I'm not tired
We didn't buy Florida and the agreement that brought Florida into the United States involve language
Alex's Homestay
Again his team is very very sloppy
Any idea what he's talking about
He's only reason to exist
In the present day is to justify whatever dumb s*** Trump does
An agitator
Authoritarian
White National
At this is a piece
Yeah absolutely
Also mentioned James Monroe was president
19 am.
He wasn't a great guy
It's also
Just f****** hilarious that this noted student of History nowhere of all things a reader of 1,000 books
I literally have no idea
President when these great
Expansions of the country love song
This is embarrassing
Read a lot about American history
I guess just it's B pretty he's not equipped
To have the conversation he's trying
You have absolutely no
Actually learning
VA
Haier American Education
Is built around
No one knows out
Utterly in
Completely
American hits
. ended
To create this
American Myth
A constant
Push and pull between
Stupid and
Yeah yeah that's a huge
So
Purchase
Check it off the list that helps us that makes sense rationalize
Turn on Louisiana Purchase
Just we have the non-existent Red River Valley Fair
These are not great job
Here goes now with some more example
How much did we spend
Another
So at this point I'm not sure Alex
It sure what he's even arguing anymore
Purchase involve the u.s. territory from another colonialist
Force examples of literally nothing to do with the point he started
The Red River Valley purchase isn't a thing
Florida purchase wasn't a purchase and the Texas annexation was again not us buying Texas
The territory that's now Texas was colonized by Spain
It 1821
Steve Austin's father Moses Austin
Was granted permission to
Settlement with a population
300 in Spanish
After Moses died Steve kept up his work but the number of American immigrants into Texas did not stop at
The Americans
We're in charge
Which quickly gave way to Santa Clara
And finding themselves unable to
To defend themselves
Texas asked to join the United States in the USA
Cool
Mexico albino an independent country
Texas that would mean War
The USA let's do this thing
Does the history books now get to include a little
About the Mexican-American War
6 million Lego
I don't know I mean
To from within Spanish territory
And then toward the cost thousands
Supplies
If this is what Alex is using as an example of what to expect from trying to get our hands on Greenland
I think he's making a
Terrible argument
And also by the way
We have plenty of options for 51st state already
I know Trump supposedly said something about Greenland and everyone's making fun of him so Alex just needs
The fuel doesn't need to go on the defensive but
Before we start trying to grab up parts
To Denmark maybe we should
Get our own house in order and recognized the statehood of
These territories
We've got that we've been
Then they would have rice
That is a problem
If they did
So I was really pissed off that I couldn't
Bottom line
Call Don.
There's a 300 maximum amount and that's the bottom line I was going to go there
Alex
This is really
Because in this clay College
The Louisiana Purchase
He doesn't
In this clip
He actually
Uses the word
Call vinod
When he's talking about Greenland
But
What he says about Alaska
Is
F*****'-a
Alright
Government resources in Alaska
That's
The position that they're in currently
Idaho
Alex Jones at the stupidest mother
F***** in the planet
His entire current brand is built on being opposed to socialism in any form of welfare
He hates the idea of a universal basic income because it
Well guess what
That's exactly what the Alaska Permanent Fund is
The Alaska Permanent Fund
The oil revenues
Hit a very basic said is recognizing to all residents
The state are part owners of the natural resources
And they recognize that and pay people for it
Everyone gets a check
Just by virtue of that the state is able to raise tons of people out of abject poverty
All the social welfare programs to Alex's
Children could be enrolled as soon as they're born
Heather dividend checks are placed into an account so by the time they're 18
They could easily have like
$40,000
To put towards college or trade school or whatever they want
The oil company still making same profit
But some of that has to go back to
It's a very singing model
Alex doesn't even seem to be against
Weird
What a dumb motherfuker
The more you think
Leaving anything
No I think
You're just
Making bad faith argument in order to smoke
And it's almost like the things that they actually complain about not what they care about
Jupiter something without actually
Play off quite really
In Alaska this is a state-run
And owned program
Right into Alex
B socialism run-amok
It should be something that he sees an intrinsically evil and exactly opposite to everything he staying
And yet here you seemingly endorse
Just I guess to say Alex doesn't really hate socialism as much
And here's the real kicker
Studies have shown that the dividend checks
Have had almost
Non-existing
Defect unemployed
Which is to say that given a free check has
That made them just decide to stop working and live off the state
There's some indications that it's increase
Part-time employee
Results of people having
The freedom to work Less hours and not starve
Which societally Speaking
Is it good thing
You remember
1840s
Had all those like
I mean I don't remember it ever heard of it
Keep going back
And every one of those like what the
Future is going to be like so
Scenarios
Everybody is always
Well
We won't
Have to work
Still be able to explore our interest
In a greater way
And now people have
Take a nap in the
Opposite directions
You want the future to be
You lazy
Believing
The only
Incentive
To do anything
Is
Financial
Or something along those lines
Stupid
I get it
What it is
If you don't really believe in
As much as you think
Hi Galaxy human spirit
Everyone getting
Payday basic
Survival
Vigorous an inflamed the human
Spirit would be
People create so many amazing things
Another one
Resources in Most states don't share that kind of abundance
It's been seen as a difficult challenge
The drain replicate disorder program
Dumb
Successive
Program
Could be enacted
Through taxes
And it would make everyone's life
Substantially better I would like
Something along
These lines be explored
You're not just you know
Let's throw it up and see what happened right
System we could put in place
Do my advocate for Universal basic
Competition thank you
Stupid
Call Steve
Unless there are
I think socialism is out of the program in Alaska and also drop
Papa's going to bring it to Green
Cool but not
To the 48
Not today
The contiguous 48
We just can't be trusted
You can only give it to Alaska Greenland
And I suppose Hawaii the
Because it's also.
Examples of purchases
Most of the episode
It was a tree
He does get kind
Close to that you can't exaggerate
The Oregon country was established as a dual occupied area where the United States and British settlers could freely setup
Is mostly there for the fur trade in the local species became more scarce from over
Dentistry took a downturn
In that situation in the 1840s the British weren't really all that interested in maintaining their occupation
End of The Oregon Territory
Especially considering that the US was super interested in it and there were way more
American stairs in British
The ripples of the Missouri Compromise were being felt
In Aldie
Expansionist territories the United
Every new area that was coming under our Sway With subject to the new slave state vs. free state debate
And The Oregon Territory was no different
He always has
When I go she ate again for the precise boundaries of what the US would eventually own it in terms of Northern
Slavery people wanted more territory
Because it was a in the north and if there was more territory it may become Moore's
Which of them penon slaves
The self didn't really want to fight with the British over
Expanding the Northern Battery tonight
Because they were aware that exact same Dynamic actually work
Interest
The preserving the power that slave states held
Again this is not an instance of the United States purchasing land to expand its territory
This as best as I can tell has literally nothing to do with the point Alex
Just trying to make about Greenland
Unless the only point you strike
Make it into colonialism
And existing population should just be made to submit to and
Assimilate to the culture you're bringing in with your colonization
This is really discussed
Open stuff to hear coming from the same guy who spends all his time yelling about Muslims and South American refugees coming
. so ready to celebrate the prospect of doing exactly that to someone else because he thinks it's a good investment
Because do the monster
His argument about
Colonize in Greenland
Clear he's stupid
These examples are not analogous in anyway
Except
In adding more territory to the United State
That's the only similarity that they have his only
Hey look at all these other times we've had a territory we should add more territory
Here is my main point
It doesn't justify the idea that people are making
King fun of trump for
Which is B buying it
We're so far away
And the Archimedes
Nothing to do with it
You lost the thread entirely
I don't know if it's Unique but it is
A very strong dislike overriding manaphy
You believe in
That's so many
Let's go with
Incredibly
People have I've just like
I would
Die I would
Kill everyone that I've ever met before I allow someone
How to take an inch of my life
And I will absolutely have
0 understanding of how
Similar that it would be if I was on the other
I'm going to take your land
With no consequences and no in
And your reacts
Whatsoever
But if you even come
That is just how it's so many of these guys
Without ever
Similarities
But
Arizona
Again
So we purchased it right
He's our purchases
The purchase that was taken by force you can't buy something
Cancel station is the max
High-speed land to the United States
So this isn't part of the purchaser shrewd investment
As a result of the war
Do u.s. Subs are absorbed a lot of the territory that is now the West in the Southwest
As part of the treaty Mexicans who decided
To stay were granted citizenship
Except we didn't stick
If us almost immediately began snatching Uplander was already owned by Mexican
Estimates put it around 20 million acres of land property in Mexican American
Which absolutely at a massive ripple effect through history
In terms of Capital Property and generational wealth
But I was interested in that it was a
Great Park California
California
Really
He was totally all about the annexation
Crabiel
It's very similar
There are similarities
To be like treaties that ended Wars Order
The treaties that were negotiations last
Purchases
And none of them took into account
People who are living
Already imperialism is a
An awful terrible
Interesting Lee Alex gets to another actual purse
Okay
Pro-mexico $2000000
The valley South
Arizona
Dollars
Stop
Again he doesn't know who present
The record Franklin Pierce
Was president
I know I know he was a one-term guy he was only president when the Nebraska
The Kansas active Pastor really exacerbated relations
Between slave and free states
It was an office during The Bleeding Kansas
Is Border Wars between Kansas and Missouri
That's really easy to not know much about it Beverly
You know what you've read dozens of books about the Civil War
Stepping out to the claim to read dozens of books about the Civil War should know a lot of this kind of
But I doubt his books about the
The Civil War really go into
Larger
Economic input
If I like Confederate sympathizers
Close to
They might just be about how like
The Southwest
Jefferson Terrace
Cool
So finally we have a
This laundry list of non purchased
Alex is trying to use to justify these stupid idea of buying Greenland
First things first
This has nothing to do with the
Send flag
That was designed by a guy named Christopher Guest
Sit back in the late 1700s where is this purchase is named after the chief
Negotiator of it James Gad
JK James Gadson is Pittsburgh
Grandson
So it kind of doesn't
It was a real piece of s***
President of the South Carolina Railroad
Bro company 1850 advocated for South Carolina
Secede from the Union
Because they admitted California as a free
You see
A social blessing
But of course as we know the choice to see that.
They definitely didn't put it in the
Secede
California too far south
Geographically for his taste
Because it should have been a slave state
Sure
Carolina
And up go ahead
Feedback
He decided to his new plans going to betray breakup California
And make the southern part of Italy
Giant slave colony
What are the plans for the California slave colony was to use slave labor to build a railroad
After all that was the business
It 1853 Franklin Pierce sent Gadsden to Mexico to negotiate for more land along the border
And the reason he was
Was because we wanted that land in order to build a southern
Continental Railroad
Gadsden was successful in his negotiation
Drip and now the land of the Gods
Austin purchases 12 large
Rail hubs in the car
Now I would also be remiss if I didn't tell you the James Gadsden was also involved in the negotiations
Is the u.s. made to remove native tribes from their land
This of course was during the time of Andrew Jackson and the trail of
So you know that this dude was not a very cool guy
Where do you have
Tried to start a slave colony in a live-in
Both on your resume
You really aren't replacing history of the check
Yeah that's
That's something that only
And like
Half of our president
Example of a plot of land
Kind of Follansbee exact same problem is and if the other perch
And that the move was never the will of the people who lived in the land
I like that the land that was in question
Also that ten million dollars went to
Anna who Alex knows as the villain of the story of the Alamo
Probably shouldn't be so thrilled that we gave $10 to one of his greatest
Historical art villains
His Heroes
Negotiate with a tyrant like Santa Ana
Didn't say nothing about what he's talking about
Too much about American
In history you'll hurt your
Just believe what you want to believe about
That's the best way
It's almost
We got developed a progressive colonialism
Stop
So if Alex just directly is advocating
A colonizer
Investments
Huge migraine
Incredibles
Photo of Greenland
4 something
Wow
This is
Stupid
Bums me out to hear a grown up
Although on the other hand I bet
Pompeo is talkin to Boris Johnson about something
Barry Schimmel
Whatever Scotland and Northern Ireland leaves
What if we just bought England but you got to be we used to be your Colony now you can
Full circle
Commander Dove Circle
I mean it is it is
Necessarily be within the realm of realistic
In line with the start of conversation
Box that he's opening
Suggest
Any country
Could just
Vote to become
State
And if we pay them
I do think you
Yeah
Middle Eastern
Because you'll be very
If if
Just was like
You know what we want to become a United States
States
Give us
Everyone suggesting that other states could process
Jamaica
On a very basic level what do you dipping his toe into is expansionism
It is Empire
It's not good when you have a guy who deeply deeply white supremacist
White identity
And then you add in expansionist
Interested in Empire corollary or historical parallel at
He's advocating for taking over the world yet
Not language you like to see out of that kind of guy
Have we considered invading poll
I think it might be a good way
I mean
Step one
Creek that Blitz
What kind of get into how this rhetoric is very easily molded wanted
Established
Which I think is important but we have to wait for him
To play out his
Is his thoughts
There you have it
What
They're Superior
The ideas were Superior
Over all of this stuff
Yeah I mean
So I mean
IPic
I think you get all you need
From that
Just can't go that neck
Next step of being
Blackwell
If I ride
Where is our ideas where's to
So we get to conquer
Did that
Should someone
Have ideas to
Is now
Well I mean Ben Alex and probably need
Do a lot more work and trying to refute
The yard ideas
Yeah she feels like they're trying to conquer him
To him yeah
So Alex Talk cell
About the people of
War
What
Billion dollars
So you know that is Greenland is just a bunch of shacks
Is wild impressive the 2.7 billion dollars
There's capital city has a population of about 19,000 that's a
Tanoshi
Your other airports like to call them
Flying Shack
This rhetoric is f****** insane
This is the language of colonial is
And because it's coming out of Alex's mouth and speak used to describe people that he wants to pillage resources from
This is the language of white supremacist colonialism
There's no difference between the sentiment that holds up with Alex's saying
And the notion that the people of Africa was Savage
Needed to Europeans
It's coming it's civilized
Oz talking about the people who live in Greenville
The same despain
In discussing his plans for what he wants
To do with their country expect to hear from
From some shill for the colonial powers to do back then
This is Empire ship this is exactly what I would say
Now he is also the chief propaganda
It's for the East India oil
Recognize anymore
But the reality is that at no point is Greenland
Ever been in
Interested in being bought
Greenland Market
Bensalem to f****** country
Cuz of course there
The Sydney Morning Herald interview residents of Tesla
Who were uniformly
Laughing at Trump
Once it quote I think it's a ridiculous idea I think it sounds stupid
It wasn't just the Democrats or Trump political enemies it was the people that he wanted to buy
Buck over
And here's why this conversation is half
This is a means to warm up to the idea of future Adventure
Colonialism
50 idea with Trump
But I get the very strong sense that Alex wants it
Your suggestion
He wants he wouldn't be spending so much money
Actually pursued
He is absolutely unequivocally using the language of colonialism
22c in the world
Namely that the United States becomes a
He's using dehumanizing and delegitimizing
Descriptions and imagery to
Describe the people who would be affected by
The colonization
Listeners care less about them
He's describing the wonderful outcomes that would be the result of condoms
He's implying that expanding your country
I'm gaining wealth is absolutely the thing that freedom does
This is a profoundly dangerous development now it's his rhetoric
Up to this point listen to Alex I've never heard anything
And that's probably because we never had a president stupid enough to want to buy green
But the point is still in Port
Either Alex has been waiting forever for a president to seemingly endorse American expansion
Or he's been so warped by the Trump rise to power that he no longer realizes that his primary brand for his entire career
Has been explicitly opposed to foreign intervention regime-change meddling in Affairs all that other s***
This is so essentially opposed to what he's supposed to stand for
Did it really worried
Clear I get that he's not saying we should go and invade them right now in Greenland
But what if the situation is
Slightly
What if we needed
Resource that they have and they don't want to sell
Once you've introduced the idea that it's totally great in the positive thing to buy countries to pillage the resources
How easy is it to escalate that rhetoric
Conquest
It's very easy
You can even use the preliminary rhetoric that you already done to build your
We tried to bill by this very important thing that we need from them but they want us to go without it
If you really think about it amounts to an act of war against
We basically have to invade
It's a very dangerous road to walk down and I really really don't like what it implies
About what Alex is now capable of
Is it seems like a departure
Well let's say
Greenland has as resources
Really really
Just a couple of years
Prior to this year
And you know what I found out
The green land cover
They have
That they're hiding from us all of these these weapons
And we got to save the people
Really they're already United States
Either way the yeah
It's it's really not far it's not
From Preparatory
It's Morse
During the Iraq
Did the lead up to Iraq
Exactly
Regime-change
Change over colonialism
Is that sometimes
It goes your way and then some
Sometimes it goes the other direction
Like with Iran we were like
And then it all went
Douche it real quick always goes
Of course
So f****** stupid and I think
Like a lot of those other things
That we found that invalidate
Pieces of his
Rhetoric
You know like the now being cool with camps
4 people Posse Comitatus Act
Got out the window
Pretty bad
It really damning
Dostoevsky
Geopolitical
Location
I find one
I find I find that to somehow be worse
Is it really a fact
The world
Yeah
About
Ridiculous military might that the Earth has ever seen
No that's no good we don't want to know
Imperialist cut
You know whatever
Cute drawings
Trump wants to buy Greenland
And Alex has more examples of perch
Really
There's more purchases
Trump's attorney
47.2
We already talked about Alaska
What airport what the f*** is a island
Midway Island
Literally
I mean
No one living on it when it was discovered in 1859
It was discovered by a captain who is trying to mine or Birch
Ain't playing the island for the United States which is acceptable because it was unclaimed completely on it
And before anyone gets the wrong idea about this Midway Island currently has a population of about 40
And no economy or government
It was initially used by the commercial Pacific cable company is a stop in a project to lay transatlantic
Cable lines in the early 1900s
After that point was a
Cheapest location for
For the Navy to set up radio towers
Of course as World War
Crucially important
Refueling
Sunday was halfway between the United States and
Hence the name
Midway
In the sixties and seventies there were a couple thousand people
Station bear what was the Vietnam War going on
But outside of that there's never been a relevant population permanently living on the island
And nowadays it's a bird refuge
So if you're keeping score this one wasn't ugly to be a 51st state
Whataburger
This was an uninhabited Island was claimed by the United States and no native population
This wasn't a purchase and no one is ever really lived on the island
There's no culture of the two distinct the island it's never had existed
Accepted as a US base
Unless you're a bird
This is literally nothing in common with Alex's fantasies
Trump colonize in Greenland
The stupidest a****** in the world these so terrible at making
This is almost embarrassing to listen to this
And I absolutely wouldn't care at all except for the office of
He is advocating for the return of colonialism
That is very bad
So you have to
Pieces that he's using.
Enforce
That shift
Towards that
Mentality
It's important to understand why these are terrible example
F****** Midway
The f*** out of here
So
Being without
Constant Contact
Mill
For the past
Has been
Very nice
It really has
But it gives it gave me this
Perspective Wild
August
Papa's going to buy grave
That I didn't
Of course he's not going to
Even talking about
Is pretty f*****
It's just s*** for the con
What fascinates me about that
Is that if we hadn't brought this subject
Colonial is
Were it not for a b*******
Content
Yeah and you never you never would have had a reason for it to be something he needs to do cuz he needs to defend Trump and the only way
Is joy.
So the more Trump does dumbshit the more they reveal exactly what's underneath
That is that has been there the whole time
Yeah I guess that's
You think about folks
Croissant
Less
Interesting the trumps edx
It's more interesting
How Alex
Response to
And how it makes
The people who love Trump
Yeah it's it's fascinating because you like
I would never have even expected
People to really think
Colonialism
Was still okay
A lot of people
It's troubling
So here's another example
That was the worst
How to purchase
ISO respect some years of his childhood growing up in Hawaii I can tell you firsthand there are still some. Feeling
About the process in which the island nation was brought to the United States
I love fun memories of my dad taking me out of school early so we could go to the courthouse
Apps for the Big King Kamehameha Day celebration
Legitimately some of my best memories
My time living on the island of Oahu
Taking apart in Celebration
A culture that was not my own but I was welcomed into the celebration all the same
That was not the full experience of growing up white
Hawaii there's definitely a good amount of racism thrown my way just because I was
And that's never great
But as an adult
I kind of understand it in a little bit of a larger
The early history of the Hawaiian islands is difficult to get into basically because
All the island
Have their own story
We're completely like a United thing through a lot of history conflict
Between each other from time
The time
Because getting into that is endlessly comp
Placated
I'm going to choose to start our story today in
Is that the owner of the Hawaiian pineapple company
Come Dole bought the island of Lanai
When I became almost
Entirely a pineapple
We're not allowed to go to Lanai
Because it was wholly owned by Dole
Imagine
We're Leo accidentally stumbles into a giant marijuana Farm on an island but this would be with
It wasn't
Closed off to people anymore but it might have been when I was there
Pineapple plantation operation
Until the time I lived in Honolulu
I was more like Leonardo DiCaprio in Django in
By then the library Plantation with a smaller operation
Domino's run B El Monte
Does do Landslide Hawaii
Cheaper labor
The pineapple business in Hawaii was very big
And when I posted the largest such Plantation in the world
Stole a very powerful position
The island
King Kamehameha was unite has United the islands
Is descendants rule until 1870
Was King Kamehameha
With no air chaos descended on the process of
Determining
Text ruler
When things got a little bit of Western
The force has stepped in to quell the violence
Ultimately leading to the Ascension of King Tahlequah
Although initially on friendly terms
Western interest
In time, cool
Ideas of creating a federation
In state
Each independent and Sovereign but Cooperative in there in
This was not something that the Western business
Centrist wanted
Happen
Things are all right for their business
What are interest
As it was
But if politicians States got together they could ultimately jeopardize their corporate power through export
Labor union
Yeah yeah
61887 King literally forced at gunpoint
Substitution for wife that was written by the White
Disenfranchised native population
And make it easier for their businesses
It's remembered by its appropriate name
The bayonet
The Constitution were members of a group called the Hawaiian
Which is comprised of sugar and pineapple business
Missionaries
And lawyers
This was legitimately a white secret society
The angel overthrowing the
Kingdom of Hawaii
The gay. Getting to us
XP Island
They are controlled by joining up with a local militia called the Honolulu rifle
Who are literally the one pointing the gun during the signing of the bayonet
The new constitution took much of
Power away from the Monarch and gave that power to the
Generally democratization what it's not forced at gunpoint
Is it good
But discounts
Tucson also specified
Put in place new
They were disenfranchised most of the native population of the island
Leaving only the white settlers and business owners as the ones who could elect the members of the
To get elected even one had to quote on real estate within the kingdom of clearvalue
Calicos
Some fleeing the country
And under
Feelings that they were going to be killed
Possibly
The cabinet was then replaced by members of the Hawaii
This was not democratization
This was a coup
Hello Georgia
Died
Brian Kemp
Oh yeah
Calico died in 1891 and was succeeded by his sister Queen liliuokalani
Who is recognized as the last monarch of Hawaii
Weed delivery
The throne she made it clear that was her intention
Restore power to
To the monarchy
Specifically targeting the business center
The original
That scared the s*** out of the business owners and members
Came to the committee of safety
The gold the gold the actions of the white settlers up to
Compass Pointe at always been
Name to the annexation of Hawaii
I really wanted the United
To take over one
Most of the momentum
Suppressed people whenever
Holy
Most of the momentum was coming from Americans wanted to take the island
But they also use the fear that if the British
Would rally politicians
To their side
Nationalism being used in a
Negative
I don't know
Ability to achieve their goals
Liliuokalani was clear in her position
Members of the committee for safety
Knew that they have to actually overthrow the queen
Which is what they paved the way to do
In order to help pave the way for the United States to have no reason
On January 14th night 1893 Queen liliuokalani
Indicating her intention to invalidate
She made clear she would not
Speak to quote deprive one white man
And of any legitimate right
But you quite accurately also pointed out that quote
Any newly arrived white man without interest or intention of residue
This place does a voter above the heads
The thousands of my subject
God given these islands and no other
She presented cabinet ministers with the new Khan
Constitution that you wanted to Annex
Which I refuse to sign
Before fleeing the government building
Afraid of crowds
Good gather.
Support the queen
The committee of safety held a meeting on January 16th
Where they decided to frame they're coming action
Purely amines
To protect the lives and property
Of white citizen
Noble reason for their clearance
Conspiracy
The reasons for the situation like this was because they knew that the US military would not openly support their efforts to overthrow the queen
But they would intervene.
Text US citizen
If you lose it was created what they were like that's what they were needed for you could get the military into play
Charles Burnett Wilson
The Marshal of the Kingdom
For the members of the committee
Government
But because they were all well-placed businesspeople with K'NEX
10 to the legislature
The requests were denied
What is closed at the time with
I don't think they're really
Interested in safety at all guys I think this hold of this no more
There was trouble Brewing Wilson started Gathering opossum
Protect
Queen but it was
The committee abused their narrative to bring the US military into
City of the Defenders of the throne no match for
For the forces behind
Baku
Lily okalani surrendered
Conspirators took over the government
Installing
You guessed it
Stanford ol as the Press
Who is the cousin
Plantation
Intertwine
Political business cards
It's a good thing that America
Grew out of all
Now where the champions
The Democracy abroad
Freedom free number.
These groups
Or at least was a like a big
Agitator in
These groups
His brother
Owned
Plantation impresario
With adult
Uncharged is time for the us to come in Annex
Unfortunately
Play Grover Cleveland
Set the timer.
S***
Cleveland actually advocated for Lily Alcala needs to be restored as Queen
So he was of no help to these plotters
Hey guys real quick I'm going to try and do the whole America believe the b******* that we say about ourselves
Real quick so business owners I'm sorry I'm not
Get your back on this
Please make sure that my terms Arkansas
All their coup work
Seem to be four
Not one to be discouraged old declared Hawaii an independent republic
Waited a few years until McKinley came to office who agreed
And that Jordan is Hawaii came to be part of the United
It was a sneaky brutal series
The plots carried out by white settlers a business interest
For the express purpose of disenfranchised in the native population
So their business could process
A gorgeous and Rich history and culture subjugated to the interest
The higher profit
An increased sugar
Exports
God Bless America
Before everybody
It's pretty much exactly what Alex wants for the Inuit people
On the one hand I didn't enjoy the kids at my elementary school would call me haole
Why was that
Hawaii
History a little bit better it kind of makes
King Kamehameha Queen liliuokalani
I take this opportunity
Alex Jones
Your goddamn house
You f****** a******
Go swim with the humuhumunukunukuapua'a
And I wish you a merry Kalikimaka
I come close to trying to
The state fish
Kalikimaka
Merry Christmas
Cuz there are song
Those are about all the
You know that one
It was a little bit
Boras a terrible exam
Alex
Just because of how explicit it is
And how would I can own the history
Like it's not something
Like eating legit conspiracy
Read out to overthrow the monarchy
For the explicit purpose of helping with the
Sugar
Plantation
The pineapple plantation
The missionaries
It was
It was a coup
It's something that Alex should not be in favor of it as a great example
Of American expansion
The coup already occurred
2016 election
Like
Why didn't
Is because of voter suppression
Control over who was allowed to vote
Because of voter suppression because we were electoral college system
Stupid
Buhl election
Why did George Bush
Steal election
Purchase a bunch of atoms
Terrible idea about getting that was a terrible idea cuz we bought them
From Spain
Is not true at all
We didn't buy them after the Spanish-American War
On the island
Does naturally year-long philippine-american War
Just because we were the one calling
You're really
Certainly not I really would like to hear more positive
White people brought up examples
Horrible time
10000 Filipino soldiers as well as civilians were killed in that contest
The list of war crimes committed by US forces in that war is a very long one
I don't want to get into it but it definitely did not include killing entire villages
The people
Whatever the case the war resolved that the u.s. put in a transitional government that would give way to the Philippines
The country which was achieved in 1935
This lasted a few years until they were occupied by Japan in World War II
Exile
After that the country went on to become
Then of course came the rise of the brutal dictator Ferdinand Marcos
Excuse me
I meant to say brutal us back dictator Ferdinand Marcos
I meant to say brutal usbank dictator and Rodger Stone client Ferdinand Marcos
Marco's world the country for 21 years and terrorizes people and stole a shitload of money
Alex is citing the Philippines
Citing it as some kind of example of positive u.s. involvement in
Zero idea what he's talking about
Or
Super into people like Ferdinand Marcos
And honestly these days
For the exam
They took the princess to the end of this list and I mean like I don't think he's made any cogent
But here in terms of why it's not dumb.
Chester Jeff to buy green
Most points purchase
Most of them were
Brutal
Exploitation
Native people
They did
They were profitable I don't disagree with that angle
To determine whether or not this was a good thing that happened
You are going to justify any
Let's
Not even get into
For whom were they
Say okay so you say
Just was profitable
Definitely wasn't profitable for the people who are already living
And frankly it's not even that proper profitable
Is profitable for the giant people
Owners who
So am I when I started to cover like Friday Sunday Monday
Event in Olathe
It was like
What's so crazy
Just because his hero said something
Just a defense that he has to go all the way
To advocating for colonialism
For the United States
In a in a terrifying
Can we get to just
Some dumb
Defending Trump but other stuff
Is really stoop
He said the Trump supporters are like
Lowered the flags half-staff
Kyle
Hitler
Prisoners
Really
Small group of prisoners believe that I like
That's me nicely does protest too much
Justin Smoak prisoners Alex
Right
I could get into the numerous times that
Aztecs
It's about 1488
Leave that alone for now
Was good
It's made by Franco
11th Hour
This dude the former counterintelligence guy for the FBI and he spend time researching
I'm studying extremist groups
He pointed out that lowering the flags
The flag on 8th
That would be interpreted as he
What's deliberate
What was the extremist community on the right currently it's stuck
It's something like this will likely be seeing is some indication of
Tacit support
The Loren was meant to
About the El Paso
Which were on August 3rd and 4th
Respectively
Essentially was that it would have been a wiser or safer PR move
If the flags would have been chosen
To be raised on any other day
Since it wasn't a
It wasn't a speed
It wasn't like we got it
If they understood the white supremacist movement
Country
Someone would have advised him against doing it on
Really the main criticism seems to be the drop his people seemed unaware the reality of extreme
Miss movements in the country
It doesn't seem to be criticism that Trump is racist or not senior anything
Like that's just that he's not getting good advice
They could possibly avoid
Sending the wrong message
The former deputy director of the FBI is on TV calling Trump supporters
I feel like you wouldn't
Make that kind of misleadingly
Generally unless
There's a part of you that was
Was worried about people rightly
We calling you and I
This is Adolf protest too much thing
Defensive to fat
That's when you know what you're
Actually afraid
What year was the idea that any criticism of you is your race or not
Because you know eventually valid criticism
Are you being a racist
Preemptively
You revealed that
You're just to open
Does a big part of Alex
So Alex
Has this is a little bit of an ad
Do you have and you'll see how he's trying to raise my
Because of you
Democratic Party
Because
Coming up games
The Democratic party hasn't done
Parents
Suggest that
Actually more lawsuits is a very bad
Alex
Because these parents would be filed a lawsuit
If it looked like the other ones were going to fail
The only reason
Add more lawsuits is like
Yep terrible sign Pharrell
Of course that's what he would use trying
I got bored
And that's why we got Norm pattis onto actually directly ask you for the money that I'm going to
I want to let people know that
Try to drive over people
Subway
Yay
On the show
Norm was on earlier but his
Is so boring
Broadcasting worldwide thank you so much
The sky is blue
Among which are political bias
Search results for specific websites
Google CEO Sundar pichai
And other questionable
This size
So we got this guy
Great Coppola
Future
I heard Alex was going to have this dude
Come on
Jack talk about Google is trying to crush conservatism
I was let out an exasperated
B i
I'm so tired of these Comcast M2 journalism from James O'Keefe
I just can't stand him
They're all equally bad and
Exhausting
Exhausting to get into
Yeah that's what he's
That's what he's doing
Yeah the more times you have to
Suspend react
Doing something
Right
I decided instead of even caring but Alex's interview with this guy I was going to watch the project
Guys claiming to be whistleblower
Namely that Google is trying to election metal by silencing
Conservative
I legitimately had to turn off the video long before it's done because this guy is saying
F****** nothing
He says that the way Google is censoring conservative
A small number of sources for their news category
News results
Services are quote
Vitriolically against
President Trump which I considered be interference in the American election
I decided to put this to the test by just Google and Donald Trump putting on the news Tab and seeing what comes up
The second result was
Fox News
The 3rd results
News from USA Today headlines
New haircut
A little further down the results just so you know I am rooting now for climate change
A little further down the results from the National Review the outlet founded
There's another article from Fox News Heather McDonald
Israel's are obsessed with quote white privilege
And another one there's another Fox News article declares Trump is greatest president of the century
Okay Publications that are included in Google's news
Footwear news
Sporting News
WebMD
And of course
Fish stripes
The only podcast to know about if you're saying
Miami
All of these sites and tons of others show up in Google's news
So I kind of suspected this guy just might be talking s***
If people like James O'Keefe really want to listen whether or not what you saying
I'm really not comfortable with this
Is pro Marlin
Comfortable with no I do not endorse this
Dubai every Marlins
Maybe
But their podcast shows up in the news section of Google
Great the second thing is that this dude says that 20% of all searches for Donald Trump go to an article from CNN
Jordan results do you think I found in the first page of Google News by searching
For Donald Trump
First page
15 results 7
Zero-zero-zero
There were two results from Fox News on the first page though so I do two stories
2 out of 7
Is more than 20
Nothing like the
2 out of 10 stories on the second page were about about Trump
I'm from Seattle
If it weren't for the first page because now we're up to
2 out of 17
After that point there about two stories for page
MCI
Nefarious
I looking through the search results
And where they come from
The places to put out a lot of material
Simple pop-up most frequent
Fox News Politico Washington Post
CNN De Pere orders the hill Guardian
USA Today
Some of the other folks sprinkled in
A rolling stone article National Review article
I don't really see much that
Quite honestly without what I would call proof
I think it's perfectly reasonable assessment for why there's a whole lot more content
Be naked about Trump
Is that he's doing a lot of naked
No one would write a story about it being an idiot for wanting to buy Greenland if he hadn't said he wanted to buy Greenland
There wouldn't be stories about him getting into a petty fight with the mooch
If you hadn't gotten into a petty fight with the boots
Asking for the media to cover negative things that Trump doesn't
Positive way order
Crying that they don't
You're mad.
The Press isn't controlled arm
The states
And I don't really have a lot of time for that thank you
Right as you're demanding positive coverage of things that are
Pretty good
I don't like what do you want
Is great
I wrote your CNN article next
Give me another headline I really I really didn't see anything worthwhile in this guy's comment
Couch and all of his answers questions
Instead of saying that there was bias
You think he believes
He seems actually resistant to saying anything
It's something that people could nail down
There's also one point where we actually know what Google is doing
Aubrey says but what they do do
Have any smarts at the camera almost cracking himself up cuz you said doo doo
Which is photography
This is not something I'm going to take
Help me not take him too seriously when I don't have a Smoking Gun
Putting away too strong
You don't have anything except Notions
O'Keefe basically got a guy who works at Google to say other than my own thoughts but I think all of your
Panda is totally right
It's possible that this guy is pranking
He seems really Squirrely and constantly do it looks to the camera and smiling like he's Jimmy Fallon
Trying to keep it together in an SNL sketch
Hey I don't know if there's a there's a weird vibe he's giving off but that just could be like social
Ability
It's probably not
The other possibility which is way more like
Is it this guy is just a right-wing weirdo who believes all the propaganda put out by the extreme right-wing media like Alex
Project Veritas and Tucker Carlson
Witcher 3 places I've seen him pop-up for interviews
Some of my reason
He seems to think they shouldn't because Trump is called a quote very fake news
He also suggested
It would take to skew the results
If you people working in a secret project
But he doesn't anyway indicate that he's aware that such a project exist just speculating talkingshit
In the same way that Alex does and all this other right-wing
He says quote I think the way that Google works the way the Democrats work their way out with their allies work in the meat
They don't really want a lot of question
There's want to call people names and get them to tow a certain kind of lying
Man it sounds like I've heard almost that
Word for word for
From other places where you might have
I heard that front brake
The way there
And he says that immediately after saying that at work at Google on a day-to-day basis
But everyone knew that you like Trump and no one cared said nobody's responding to
The guy isn't it up is that this is yet another project
These tech companies absolutely do need to be address
Bastard series problems
The need to be taken care of
But I know these guys well enough to know that I cannot find common cause with
They're superficial agreement with what I would
Position I would have
About what the problem is
Describe the problem
That covers up a massive disagreement underneath
About why we thinks
Another problem
So f*** all this
It bothers me
Because either they know exactly how carts
They're being because literally what they're doing
You saying okay we need content that says what we wanted to say
Can't get that con
So we'll make some content and just
Say it
Cartoonishly
That's cartoonish manipulations
To work
Yep
Planet episode
And somehow people are not realizing that
The bad guy is a guy who looks like a giant rat
Yeah that guy seems like he's got the
Good ideas about the entire
Yeah it's weird it is it is weird when you
Step back and look at it through wider prison
So I said I wasn't going to
Recover it all
This guy's interview with Alex
Because I really felt like the chances are this is
This guy just has a bunch of paranoid Notions about elaborate
Conspiracies a probably got them from Alex to begin
Alex Alex can say I was right all along
Is the feedback when
Interview I watch the project Veritas videos
Actually goes a little bit off the rails
Miami Marlins
No
Will cover it
Alex is talking to this
Because they don't have enough followers
Nothing I mean I got 9,000 followers in the first two hours and I haven't had any more
Even after I went on Tucker
Even after the President Trump retweeted me
I think they're getting
We don't have transparency so it's kind of
Hours
I don't believe that for a second baby those 9000 10010 ar-ab out the market that is interested in following
Twitter
Like maybe
There's a lot of like
Older people who read the watch Fox News Tucker Carlson on Twitter
Maybe the people who are
Yep there's there's plenty of
Maybe the
Cubot Networks
That over-inflate a lot of people
Pre-workout
For workouts maybe they have
Picked up on you
Plenty of reasons
Buy like followers for you. A project
It has like maybe two thousand likes
The project Veritas
Okay so your video got 2,000 likes from the main
Account is it put it out you ended up with 9000
Unfollowers Matt that seems
Like normal
Metric
They're being blocked
I do like that ability
To blame
Any amount of
Success or lack thereof on
Secret
Conspiracies
Eddie's really really comforting like
Could just stay at my,
The reason that I'm not on
TV is because a large group of people
I've been depressed
Yeah that's true you do your lotto Drive
Very appealing
Mindset to have
Long. Of time where no one was listening to our show
We didn't come to that sort of rationale for why
No one would listen
Honestly I think we're still coming to the opposite of conspiracy
Ourselves for a little bit
Is this a Make-A-Wish
Situation
Yeah yeah
Weird alien race
So in the next life Coppola
Absurd
I mean I honestly like being able to go viral is almost twenty-first-century so
Transparency around
Why certain things can buy some things can't
Amazed by that level of Human Rights
Argument
That argues against a lot of really basic human rights
First of all having a social media account even
And is a human right
This crazy idea that you have the right
To go viral
Is insane
That's not
Bat
That's astonishing
Yeah
This is from this Google
Wow
Where is everybody at the human rights we're going to be really inundated
With a ton of
Terrible content definition of delusions of
Isn't it it doesn't get more grandiose than like
If the only possible reason the world does not
Instantly all
Shout out to my whim at
After
Whistleblowing video
Is because somebody is suppressing
And they're destroying my
Human right
Viral viral
Wolfgang
So Alex complains about
The social media game by bragging about his appearance on Rogan
But it's
The platform
Elon Musk
What about Bernie
But because it's the biggest thing ever
Most popular now
Humans agree with
He did go back on Road
I don't
This is crazy we should be allowed to outlaw
Clearly fake
Indicted for bulshit
Shadowbanned
If you say shadowban
Get the f*** out
What does a real thing
Contended there it sounds f******
Space
Shadowbanned
This interview is largely
The project Veritas video and it is exactly that like
Character
It's not interesting it's
What year did
Alex trying
To validate is victimhood through
This guy who doesn't seem to have any real information
That's not good
And this next clip is why
It ended up
To talk about
And that's because Alex brings
Another guy
From Google
Directions to work
Put on
Or so far
Alcatraz
Voorhees
Is another Google whistleblower who project Veritas is promote
He was interviewed by James O'Keefe and almost immediately journalist
Ran into some
Unproblematic information
Someone putting back
Looking through the Zack guys Twitter account
People queuing on has been more accurate than any news Outlet
Disqualifying audits
Judgment
And discern
You look at more of a social media
You're the big
Pizzagate guy and has made numerous accusation
Immediate government are controlled by
Write 3 as an unimpeachable track record
He's even gone so far as to say that Zionist
Killed Andrew Breitbart
He accuses quote Israel and designers cabal for doing 911 which is insane since we all
Leo zagami
Dog which stands for Zionist occupied cover
Commit multiple times and that is a huge problem
Zog is not a term the Casual folks use
It hasn't.
Steak place in The Fringe worlds of anti-Semitism and white supremacy
His use of that term is a very strong indication
Mickey himself isn't outright white supremacist
Or
He takes in information
White supremacist sources so regularly
If either of those he's not good
It is
Occasionally heart
You know a lot of people when you perceive a Google
Employ youth
Somebody who's this
Brilliant
Top of their field
Level
Talent
And then you see this guy new like
If you know what you're talkin about any idiot could be
Compressor
It's probably a very good it whatever Tech
Stuffy. Also occupy the same brain
There's Azog
Yeah
Probably no
I put this down to a dichotomy of him being an anti-semite or take
White supremacy
Absorbs it
I think it's probably more the quesadillas
Parentheses
Around words that you want
Totino jewishness
Like when he put them around the globalist media
I think that's a case where
When these parts of Voorhees belief system started to come up project Veritas accused sites like The Daily Beast
Messenger instead of a message
They were engaging an ad hominem attack
Because they were scared of what Voorhees brought
To the table
That's a dad project veritas
You know his believes that nothing to do with the message
Also interests
Immediately went back and started
Scrubbing is social media to erase
Because of course
Yeah
It's not true or fair to argue the bring up the stuff is just
It's very relevant
The documents he is releasing
Publicity stunt fraud operation for Port to show that there's a grand conspiracy against conservatives in the media
Criminal fraud
It's very relevant that this guy also believes that the Jews control the media and the government
So when you tell Sookie that they're tampering with elections overthrow the government
It's important to realize he believes
The message being put out on Project Veritas is overtly anti-Semitic
Because of this guy's beliefs
We have prior context to understand what he believes
But because O'Keefe doesn't mention that aspect of his store
He's able to slightly obscure that reality
Just presenting information is unbiased
Coming from credible source
What do you might as well just be reading from a new high-tech version
The protocols of the Elders of Zion
This isn't some extraneous piece of trivia about the guy
It gives content and shows why he might be trying to go out of his way to prove his theory
To be used by project veritas
To do so
Like if it documents reported what they claimed they did
Absolutely get a platform to release them on
The intercept
Are any number of places
Other media Outlets zodiac
This kind of story
You only go to Project veritas
If what you have isn't
Great
But you want to make a splash in the right way
And also if it is your
And if it is a human right for you to go by
Absolutely
I looked over
That Voorhees release
Project bear
And
Pieces of evidence that he brought to the table is a list of blacklisted sites
Support to be included in news search
These included Google Drive
They're on Google
EBay results were exploded right make some sense
Because they have their own
The only other site that isn't one of those types
Are black
Is the daily Stormer
Then there's another sex
Which is quote
Hi user block race
User block race
Which is to say users of Google block these sites themselves
And they're noting oh there's a really high a way above average
Gotcha
Okay sounds good pressing the search result
The people are
Choosing not to see the
These results in
And possibly they're on a list because of that
Yeah this is a list of states that consumers
Missy pop-up and results
Angry Patriot movement.com
Girls Just Want to Have guns.com
Admittedly this site this list is large
Butthole is
Overtly
Choice lights to
It's not just all conservative
It also includes
Sites like liberal america.org
Or modern liberals., organization
Media Matters
Occupy Democrats
And that horrible conspiracy message board above-top-secret
The end of the document
Include sites that have been flagged because they tried to create fake version
The real news sites
Like abcnews.com. Co
Or cbsnews.com. Co
From this document I don't
Any indication
There's some kind of an internal sensor
What I see is an internal decision
The block
And the daily Stormer
And then a giant list of sites that users of blocked at above-average rate
With no indication that those sites are at all Blacklist
Said to I mean I know for a fact that above 2
Top secret shows up in search
Results since I regularly run into
The site when I'm looking at the
Camelot
So that piece of information doesn't seem
One of the big pieces of evidence
I say no
Yeah well
Is that the free market
Means they'll be allowed to
Because they're obviously the most pop
If the free market
Is saying
They don't want us
That means that Google is
Manipulating those people in
That
Because the only explanation
Is that there
Supposed to win the free market of ideas
And somebody is
So that idea of
You know user block
Versus internal blocks
Obviously users wouldn't
Lock them
Program
The coverage
What immediately jumped from this
Screenshot is very clearly says quote work-in-progress
Who knows if it was even implemented or even followed through on
The other thing that jumps out is that that there's a list of example
Screenshot contain
The Wall Street Journal tops the list at 8.53
For their rating
Indicating a low level of Fringe
You got Alex Jones down today -1.5
Which makes sense
Yeah
The Young Turks
And The Huffington Post have substantially lower rate
Then Breitbart
And Fox News
Indicating that their coverage is seen as more Fringe
This document of anything demonstrates a lack of political bias
Against conservatives
Status quo heavily skewed towards old white people
Perhaps
They're apparently thousands of documents that Voorhees release
But I'm absolutely not going to read all of
You clearly I do believe the Jews control the media and government
To promote the idea that government
Who chose to highlight those two documents that I have
Pointed out.
Preaching to the Forefront
Then they show absolutely nothing close to what being touted as what they're showing
All in all this is exactly what I've come to expect from Project veritas
Pyle of thousands of documents
John is a terrible job of presenting
Are b*******
40 sucks
Occam's razor at this point
If there is a Smoking Gun or if there is any evidence
All that
Google Facebook in all this week
People are going out of their way to
It would
Come through someplace
Even if you know some pizza
Highmark
Intercept The Intercept would totally put it
Glenn Greenwald would jerk off to the notion
He could prove that they were the only ones about
Not necessarily your CNN or whatever
Problem
Hear about it
Who believes in his dog
I'm going to hear about it from the intercepts
The Interceptor somebody like that comes through with this
I'm going to let the Zog I go
But it's important to recognize
That he has clearly demonstrated by his social media presence
Put out the world
Is disqualifying
About
I don't know
Because we already know it
It's a big
You're at you're out immediately
I don't need to read any of you
If you're also the guy who
And the Dinos rondomedia
So at this point Alex decides
He's going to let these two have a bolt-action and let them take over the
That perpetual
You guys have a discussion here
Talk to each other
I don't have
What
Hey Zach what's up
How you doing
But he keeps biting me
Because
He thinks this is some kind of like world-changing
Stop it brokered on the show
He says as much as
Who all runs during the break people's office they said
We've got
Exist
Information dominance
Stalin Churchill and spr
Is this is the
Lincoln Douglas debates
Cuz what's going on with amazing history.
Appearance on Alex Jones is f******
Stupid
Nixon
Greg
Everybody hates social media
So why aren't other ones
America's really being kind of antagonize bipartisan not happy at the same thing in every country
So
Just getting to other people if you know there really wasn't free market or others.
OK Google
I can actually tell you why this hasn't worked
It's because
The people who don't like the social media Network
I do still want
Social media networks people don't like them is like
Get off this go live my life
But the ones who leave early
And
White supremacist
I went out there on Facebook
Free from the censorship of Facebook
They generally turn into violet
Awful
Shitholes
Full of people
Survival ship in the world
But you see it you see it doesn't work
Which
You are one of those
Kind of look at that as a
The microcosm of the nation that you would create
Would you have your
It seems like you should take you have your way
It will look
Like when you have a white nationalist
That's not good it looks like a place
It's going to tear itself
Because the only people
But within your white
Are the people who want to tear everyone apart
It does seem like it'll go that direction
Pictures of loving
Have you two guys
There's not a ton of
Clips of avocados that because
Conversation
Was that interesting
But Alex pulled one of his
In the middle of the counter
Once a week whatever you want
A two-hour show to say whatever the hell you want with no strings attached
The listeners love this that level discussion
Alex just love giving people Jose
He offers everyone show he offered Barnes the show he's offering these two guys
Offered colors shows it's just insane
Where's old man house phone
Rapo
Admit
Cuz I'm Petty
How to draw montucas
Black Knight
I loved it so consistent to he says that all the time you know till we watch Monty Python
So Zack
Voorhees
Talks about how
He was part of occupied
Possibly be
Yeah you know I was I was attacked by antifa
Because
One of their events
Occupy Wall Street
And you know
TV deathreats and it's really funny
I've done more
Fascism than all of them combined
Wow
You believe in as when did
The group that we've
Consider that the
Conservatives
Considered to be
Build their own
Time machine
And go back to Occupy Wall Street
It existed for a long time
It's absurd it is absurd
Occupy Wall Street is conflating things I think of right-wing propaganda
Which is not a good sign and again
He believes in US.
Interview wraps up
Kind of
Towards the end of it he starts to get into like the spirit the spirit
He wants them to talk about how they back when they worked at Google
And YouTube
They felt like
Downtrodden and like ugly everything is bad but once they started
Speakingout
Spirit
Sure he wants to introduce a spiritual aspect of the fight
That they're in
Sure and that leads to a long esoteric ramble about
How
If you if you just get into God everything is
Is great
Which again I think highlights this thing to Alex's
Express himself
He's fit
His show is primarily Evangelical
These right-wing
In order to get people in that direction
Accepting
Jesus
Or his verse 13
Here's a little piece of that esoteric ramble that
Hilarious
There's something wrong with something wrong with beautiful women there's nothing wrong with a
Horsepower car
Doesn't come close
And promoting
Puma future
It's so rewarding to stand up
The show Force
And
Show me people singing show enslave
If they have never tasted
I have never imagined
Darla
Love you just
Watch ever touch
You'll never want anything else yet
It's not like Christians
Why why even throat
And
Universal
Something's happening here
We held the course you held the course
Researcher of God
I don't want that number to everytime Leo zagami is adjective
Leo zagami been waiting for 28 hours now to have him on in just a second there is true comedy and just
Resume playing this
Standard Alex talking about religion thing
Rambling forever in
Now let's get to him he's Mio usually do
So they are the Grammys on
Care but I just want to play this one clip
That he has
F***** up
Is it
So the Infowars
Is brought together by prayer
We already know from the last time we talked about this
Is very clearly Trace back
Do anti-semitic ideas about the
The Jews creating a demonic entity
Inspires them
Is Brian Kemp communism
You know that really makes me rethink that Jimmy James line
The new news radio
That's what I thought
Unfortunately
The great joke is
Again yui
You get Leo Leo Leo
This episode was crazy
I really wanted to cover more
I couldn't I couldn't he
Justifying trying to buy Greenland by appealing to a ton of horrible thing
Purchases
It's absolutely ludicrous
And then also this Google
Cheddar's a little bit why
It's worth at least
But there's really not a ton of
There's a little bit of life
We need to overhaul
Our education
And I'll tell you who did it
Chairman Mao
He really overturn the whole educational system
It's just it's little
Cuz of this being so
Weird
For Friday
Just a little closer up on
Other days
On this day maybe I don't know
So we'll see and will be back on Friday
We will see that but scrapes be back
Mr. Jordan miss doing this
But
People can check out the website
And we also want
Facebook if you would like
Download and listen to an episode of Archer
You could go to I
Homepage.com
That's no longer on the homepage
We have so many episodes
It's very hard for people to know where to
Start the episode
Where you interview Bob Chapman
About
I'd heard from bro
It's a good bottle episode
Spoiled it but if people are looking for I cuz I don't hear from you
Amanda Show but I don't know what episode 2
Some people said that's a good entry point
If I put that up on the homepage
Go to the iTunes or so many episode
Maybe that's a good place
That's a great idea
Listen to an episode with
Shocking twist
But also
Until 9
Next time
Ivan the Beast
Alexandra Thurston color