Damned important
I have great respect for knowledge but I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Nike.com
Little bit
Back on special request
Of my mom play what
My mom said she missed me longer but I used version on the last episode
Sims 2 full episode
The beginnings of sound when she's doing some gardening or housework or whatever
I don't think she has the patience to listen to like two and a half hours of me
I don't know I don't know if I can recover
The big revelation
WhatsApp
Go to bed Jordan
Absolutely so we can have a whole night
I have a question for you if you ever met a.
Love yourself
I mean there's
Comedian Don Friesen
And who doesn't look like me at all I've not met him
I almost did
You almost did
You always been so I don't think
Not sure I've ever
Matt
A doppelganger I have really
20 cross ties and a huge beard
It's very it's rare that I run into
I don't know I remember when I was younger I was always that I always got
You look like
Everlast
I've never liked that old wheelbarrow
I don't see Will Ferrell
Completely inaccurate
From a number of people
I don't know I don't think I have
Dilated tongs
Have you ever seen that whenever he's got the big beard.
Sure.
If I needed to look like somebody
In the acting world I would prefer it be one of those character actor
Work
About today
Sojourn
Episode the present
To just keep on going
Sunday Monday
The Times They required meat
Jumpforward
10/22
Which is Wednesday and Thursday this week
The old boy oh boy
I'm alright
OK Google
You know why I'm alright
Shoutouts
Do people who decide if we got a lot of walks
To go go through
For today to get through a Big Mac
I'm very excited to appreciate being called
Group
A gaggle
Is that what murder of walks
A Aron
Thank you so much you an apology walk
I'm a policy wonk
Mark
What's your now policy walk
I'm a policy wonk
Young
Text Peter that gives you an owl
Peter Petrelli
The main character
Alex Gregory
You think it's that Gregory Coppola there's a Google whistleblower for my life episode
Next Heather
Secret agent
Bwk
Thank you so much
CW Network
Kwk
I don't know probably some reference to something
My 500 some anime or something that you were going to be like
Alright alright
Somebody
Reached out to and wanted to bestow
A policy wonk status
Upon not someone
So Kella thank you so much on behalf of Chris
Do you want our policy walk
These guys could do that by going to a website
Sports show
We would appreciate
Here's what I'm talkin about
Episode
On Tuesday
In order to be a
While we were recording
Some things happened
After we got there was a comment about how to vote for Democrats
Disloyal
Yeah well we were recording Trump went Hitler
Trump Hitler
He made some in the present tense made some comment
Good
And then Rudy Giuliani came out and he clarified the Trump didn't mean that those Jews were disloyal to the United
But they were disloyal to Israel which actually makes a comment a bit worse
I'm confused positive
Also make matters worse was when clarified
If you are very very disloyal to Israel
Not great
7 underline dual loyalty to Israel as a classic drop of anti-Semitism at whites
Supremacist propaganda
States and has been for decades
It's very much in line with the worldview propagated by the protocols of the elders
Zion
Is dual loyalty accusation
Has been used to attack
The public figures
Pretty much forever to create the perception that there's no way that a jewish-american
Possibly
Have America's actual entry
Because they'll always secretly be looking out for Israel number one
It's a truly insane thing to hear the president and one of his closest advisers and
Possibly still lawyer
Relationship
Particular
Really cares that much
Lowe's on Tuesday evening
Boarding
Trump tweeted a thank you to a very insane right-wing radio host
Who instead of trump
He's the best president for Israel in the history of the world and the Jewish people in Israel love him like he's the king of Israel
Like he's the second coming of God
The one at the end of the the big book that everybody loves so much that Bible one
Have you ever read that last book
Boy they really sure sounded
Feel like a weird pranks
Since I was 12 years old but what if we f*** with them and make them think that the Antichrist is real
It's that strange
The dynamic
Play
I'll f****** do it for
So Trump repeated those comments that way now and rooted made about himself
To give them his stamp of approval which is
Pretty much what you'd expect from a malignant narcissist
Sister doesn't really care about what other people think or feel
Anything
So then later on Wednesday dropped decided it was time to release
Enterprise geigle he was going off on a ramble about how he was standing up
The China
I am in the middle of his comments he looked at the sky and said quote
Yep this is the sort of thing that you might be able to make an argument about it that he was
Just sent you the chosen one.
Looking up at the sky party plus
Real Jews look at him like he's the second coming of God it takes a very very f*****-up dynamic
Intuit
Doesn't exist outside of the context
The board
The day before
Eye of the truth
Is a profoundly f*****-up thing no matter what the surround
You doing it like wouldn't be f****** crazy
No in his defense this is the one thing that you said so far in this presidency that makes perfect sense
Because
Who the f*** else could get away with all this
Like at a certain point you have to start thinking
Either I'm playing with f****** house money or I am literally Harry Potter
I guess so I can that mean character shield around him he can't go to jail for committing a crime
Like nobody's doing anything
The entire world is going in his Direction
What do you say we visit
The human race
Exactly
0 people between the two of us logical extension
I could shoot someone on 5th Avenue
NovaCare
You never really thought like
What are the
Like side
If that I could say I'm the chosen one
I could
I'll be disloyal to Israel by having different political
Nope
He can do anything
Well short of that
Don
That Quest
Per se
Thoughts
On these developments
I knew that there was going to be something of a response
Couldn't guess which way it was going to break
If I had to bet money on it
Before when I first saw that news
Coming out
I would have thought like well
We just did an episode about how Trump said he wanted to buy Greenland
Mx4 stalex to defend
The idea of buying
So I kind of figured that okay
I'm just going to say this stuff Alex
A defendant is going to have to say that
Pastabilities hours
Could have all of his
Religious feelings
And be like
We are gone
Too far
Pardon the expression,
Jesus moment
So we started the 20
To Hong Kong
Which is better
Reporting on the protest
Austin Hong Kong
Some folks have asked about his position on that
Incoherent
Someone
He's in support of the protests
But there's
Mostly cuz he hates China
I guess if that's how you get there that's how you get there
This mentality of like
The West is now the
Kong is just us
See you there we go
And it's
Very strange
Not grappling with
If the situation outside of just China
He kind of thinks that everybody living in Hong Kong is white
Everybody
In China is
There's a feeling of that just based on the way he describes
Yeah
Actually takes
Their own way
The Westside
He has a supportive
Entry level
It is first clippy talks about how
He's going to cover the Spectre
He's got he's got another
Reporters
Hong Kong
First of all I love that name
Hundred percent forgot your third reporters others in this Blood
Hundreds of thousands of Chinese troops are threatening to invade
15 minutes
Cam
Within an hour
So we got troubles with the meme
Okay we'll get to that later
King allowed to post
Dank memes
Equivalencia
Presentations are on par with each other
Discussing woohoo today's gas
SAR
He has a name in there that might not immediately jump out to you but this is a person who it is very
Stop that
What is hibernation
Coming up
Support
Horsepower
As well I will be
Very exciting
So it makes them scientific name Jada frames
Doesn't ring a bell to you or
Some of our non-uk listen
But I'm probably is too well known here in the US
Be something that folks
Remember
If you were called back in 2017 Trump retweeted some little videos
Immigrant violence in Europe
With the explicit purpose
Generating about refugees
Beforeigners
Trump was widely and rightly criticised for promoting this message seeing is a traced back to the ultra-right wing
Just group Britain
First
At least one of these videos with sound
Jayda fransen is a member of Britain first and it was her tweets
The trumpet
I was really hoping she was
The lady who had
Tried to restore that
Jesus painting
Came out all weird remember that one
Craigslist
Although she might have been behind this
Was the deputy leader of Britain
Position
Explicitly called for the Islam to be banned in the UK
She took over as leader of Britain
First one
X 28 weeks
Some prison for religious harass
Every violated a court order Banning
Entering boss
Given his past history
Specific purpose of religious harassment
Right he went to jail and took over and pretended the golden was just taking a leave of absence
Since to deal with family issues
Madara cover-ups
Incident
In 2017 golden was accused of sexual assault by an underage girl
The alleged attack took place at a hotel they went to after the girl that attended one of his Britain first
Which was centered around to cry and plague of Muslim child sex
Interesting
To make matters worse before remember of written first name g boards come forward and attested that Jada Franzen
Had explicitly tried to coerce this underage girl into not telling anyone
Golden had done
Morris was in the room
Jada was saying I can
Can give you everything you need platform I'll do this for you that for you she was offering her all sorts
I'm thinking this is
He went on to say that the fransen said that the girl need
Did the quote come back to the bar and let everyone
You with Paul so it looks like
So if you're keeping score it looks like it was the deputy of an organization
Who tried to cover up an instance with our leader of varmint out of abused
Around the issue of child abuse
I really normal Alex Jones
I really just don't say
These people care is
I think they're just
I think they're just making
In order to sell a whole different
Baby
I really
Case wide open it's too bad we don't have a ton of evidence
It was formerly a member of Tommy Robinson
English Defence League
Specifically out of targeting harassing an agitating against
38 weeks in prison for religious harassment
This is the result of her golden going to a Muslim
That's where they
Pedophile in Foreigner
According to the garden guardian
We're playing in the middle of the shop
Legitimately there just terrorize
The other account she was found guilty of
This troubling habits Britain
First has of showing up at the wrong
House to harass
G.i. showed up
She got the wrong address
She thought it was the address of a
Defendant
Lee's trial
Some unrelated person
Ivanti published a video of her showing up at
Release their address
She also showed up at the
The correct address
Another defense
But that guy wasn't home
And that didn't stop Jada from yelling and banging on the door anyway
The Descendants
Girlfriend was home
As were her three-year-old and 8
18 month old children
The woman testified the transit quote
Was making racist remarks
Dirty Muslim rapist come out we're not going to leave until you're gone come out dirty scumbag
It was directed at two men because she thought he was in there but he wasn't
It made me feel very anxious
I didn't go outside for a long time
I was also pregnant at the time but happen
And two days after I started
Bleed heavily and lost my daughter
Jesus
F****** cry she was stillborn I blame Jayda fransen
She also testified that his traumatized her child do still get scared when anyone knocks
On their door
It may 2019 France and was arrested again after she gave a speech in Belfast
That was the term
Going to be a quote
General vehement attack
Back against the religious
Interspeech yelled about how there is no such thing as moderate Islam
Quote these people are begging for our blood
She told rally attendees it was time for the world to unite against
Quote the one
Common enemy
Essentially advocating
Extermination
Campaign against
I thought it was
Just her
I'm pretty sure she is our one, database bad bad person
Go to hell would be your hired
She is got a
A f****** resume
Christ
No Remorse for the possible consequences over words
She's a cold-blooded white supremacist
Islamophobe
And Alex Jones giving her platform
Is a very strong
The type of show he want
To be running
So that's not a great
Cool cool cool cool
Maybe he's not going to talk about Trump's b*******
What if he doesn't
What if you just goes the entire show and doesn't mention
This is Wednesday is it really makes the most sense for him to
I feel like that
Exactly what is a little Long Branch
0 narratives that include you calling yourself the chosen one so today is day off
Probably happened while Alex was on air or
He has no reason to know about that while he's alright the other stuff however
The Tweet disloyal
So Alex has got his people out in Hong Kong
So excited about
Other side of the world by the miracle
She talks to us
Okay well like I said
Saxons
I know that audio quality you can hear what you saying
There's literally no reason
That's crazy
So funny that is so funny like 20 seconds
Just f***
And then just be like
Oh god there a little bit
Soft
F*** it we'll get special reports out of it
Stop there and we'll put it out this interview that I'm so excited about
Live interview from around the world
I feel like she was doing a pretty good fine totally fine serviceable
Bad audio quality
Audible
Yeah you could hear what you say
You pretend the other cop
Producer
So talking to the Hong Kong
Who decides to jump
To the other
Topic of
Depression
Of course
Discount Bakula
Really don't like that we live in
Carpe donktum
In the world
Not at the White House
On Instagram
I've meme sites
With this new modern form of communication
Beyond the Emoji
Facebook.com
And within two hours
So we got it
Situation on our hands
First of all I love
I love just the obsession
Not
On this site
It does to me he was five years ago when it already started looking ridiculous when people were doing
Already gone over the past episode this b******* narrative about
Millions
Great
Presentation
Rampage
We we active on Facebook it has like 30,000
Unfollowers
Stuff I don't see any
Indication
We kicked off this idea that his meme worlds
Is somehow band on Facebook
And that's kind of Interest
To their version of
The story about it
Screenshots
Not being allowed
Up to
Be posted
Now why would that be
McKay's
What is the issue
And I think I solved the problem
When Alex
Plays
Trailer
Carpe donktum website which is what all of these links
Went to
Purchase the flavor of it it's very well done
Process
Hollis
I want YouTube
Now if I were Facebook and I had a quality
Control
I would probably band
This link just for like
Stupid
We are going to make America great again
Well what are you conservative here and I'm sure
Democratic candidates for president
Are cheerleaders
That more of that coming up
So Alex cuts it off even before the
Like this is a clear copyright violation
You're allowed to do
The links that were blocked in the screenshots that Alex is promoting is proof of car
Carpe donktum censorship are all people
Make a post that trailer
Which is a copyrighted piece of work
I have no idea whether or not this is the reasoning that Facebook used for this trailer innovative
Ancient use of copyrighted material
It deflected it to clear theft of intellectual property
The reasoning for why this link
Link is blocked then there's every reason not to allow it
Like that makes
I have no idea it honestly is Facebook enforcer actual guidelines
Then Carpe donktum shouldn't be allowed to use their platform
Thanks their authenticity rule that requires under the name they use
Real life
My larger feeling isn't difference though
I want to main World in man that place sucks
It's just a basic ass work.
With a scroll of anti-left meme
Being posted
I looked through them and there's almost no engagement
The vast majority has 0 comments barely anything has over 100 likes
All it takes
Something on theirs is press the like button
Haysite announcement
Itself only has 132
All right so the problem that I'm
Is
Web pages
Suppressed by Google and
Facebook
Carpe donktum is super lucky that Facebook blocked one of his
Otherwise the only thing you have to go on Alex's show to talk about his
Is geocities ask me page it's getting D+ traffic
Nsls I'm going to say about Carpe donktum this representative of future internet communication whose Innovations
Basically a city Tumblr
I think
Got us the right is to Good Humor
So what
Heard that
Very clear
Violation
Too long
Use of Gangnam Style
Like I said I don't know this to be the case of babies trying to get copyright violated
Have some evidence that somebody was blocking it
This Griffin runs so strongly
Uworld by censorship and oppression
Essential to
So if you're going to do something and now it's your website
It makes sense
To do something that is illegal in it
Dip that you just ignore the fact
It is against copyright laws
To be taken down and then they can't even handle the fact that you know
I get too sensitive
Possible
Because that would be a wild
Assumption for me to make win
It could just be that he's stupid
Which is Occam's razor
I will consider it
When stupidity
Completely satisfied
But I kind of thought like
That's probably would have
Happened to your right
Start stalking
He kind of makes it clear that that is
Alert you to something something new
Unless I remove the
Share a link to meme world
That mean world.com
But if you try to
Send a message
So that's clear
That's clear
The copyright-infringing content
This is
Issue this is not
Your website
It is a clear violation of size copyright
Facebook and Google and Twitter aren't censoring
Tell people that they're censoring
Gangnam Style
I think we're going to get
Before
Before they do like I said yeah
So Alex has another agreed
Narrative
About text censorship gone awry everything's terrible for Trump
And if
Because it's looking for strong women
This is a war on language
What's Alex's interpretation of a totally out of control
Doesn't run on by critical
What did you please
Actual issue
Because of course they like
Be some sort of a thing with like
Diesel
Brands people are so offended by the word
The problem actually
Is that the problem
Was there a presumed
Gender in
The Adit
Self which is against Facebook ad policy
Literally if you look at at Facebook advertising rules
The first thing you'll find is a link to the rules about personal ad
Quote
It must not contain content that assert or imply personal ads
This includes direct or indirect assertions are implications about a person
Race ethnic origin religion beliefs
Sexual orientation or practices disability medical condition
Including physical and mental health
Financial status membership in a trade
Criminal record or name
Do they allow like
We're looking
Fort Rucker
Hope you don't do that that is disallowed
Okay so you can't be like are you
Indian with a broken leg
Who is
Dabbling in Buddhism
Then you should be voting
Right right
Even if even though you can
Target
People
Still in the body of
The ad presume
Someone
Any characteristic falcon
Against their policy
This is really basic
Steamburg liver posted
The stupidest figuring out what they're doing
Whether or not
And this is where we get back to those theories that I was
Kicking around
Buckhead's
To complain about
Copycat meme page
Probably knowing that it was
Wasn't covered by fair use
Is Lincoln loud boom you got a free
These people who made this Trump ad
Post an ad on Facebook
Gender but they do it anyway
This s*** is really sad
He's dumb dumb fashion
Are so desperate
The paint themselves as victim
They have to paint
Weatherby
They're not being allowed to break the rules
It's some kind of enterprise
This is the only way that they can get attention
It's the only way they can pretend irrelevant
And it's honestly
Getting exhausting
Exhausting years ago the problem
Is that it's working
Stop working
And it seems like if you're stupid and
The cheater
Then
You are a course being oppressed
Because oh and you leaders are back
And nothing applies to you today
That might actually be
The explanation
Pulled over
Did you guys not know I can
Drive 90 miles an hour in the school zone
I'm allowed to
Travel
Cheater
In this next clip Carpe donktum was talking about the rules
Clothes for people posting
Stop on me and world
Heather is discussion
But it's not open for anyone to post
Why are obvious reasons
Posing
Nazi salute
Before he goes and shoots up school
Those are not there
Did you guys do
Good protective
Say something
Awesome
To always
Like anything that is
An indication that
People on your side of things
Seem to be causing
A lot of Iowa
Right it's good to do
Preemptively universally be like all those are actually just dance
Yeah yeah yeah
Website
I haven't seen any
We don't even have any regular people post
And it so it seems like there are far fewer people who are fake
Posting title
But there are a bunch of people who are regular people
Because I love Hitler
This is a test understanding the recognition on Alex
Parts like
A lot of
F****** love Hitler
That the media
Middleman seems to be the only people who are trying to
To keep the right from being
Fans are out right now
Like Trump is just literally going full Hitler just like I'm saying Hitler words I am enough you might as well
Stand up in front of everyone and go I am a Nazi
Everybody
And the media is trying to come up with any and all possible excuses
As for why he's not enough
Convoluted explanations
We all know
This show he has one
If you guys just
Pay me a bunch of money and buy a bunch of stuff
I will do less ads
Which I like that I like that almost like a recognition
I do too much
Stockholm Syndrome
Give me
I have been
Over and over and over again and if you just give me a few slightly
Play fewer times
It's it's very weird
But I respect
Another one that's not really an ad but of course
Like an ad for it
Infowars it's
Rambling about how great farmers
It includes this that I just think it's really fun
Americans aren't going to be bowling
Walking cruises at Hillary Clinton
We're never going to give up and all you've done is awaken the human spirit
Castro
Is the wheel on a boat there's a track on it.
It's sad that
I mean you can't even
Be bothered
To care about things he pretends
This is the Ludacris
Anybody in the control room
It'll take a 10 seconds
We can add it in let's just do another take another angle so doesn't look like
You f****** be professionals
Walking cruises the person
Lori Castro George Orwell data second
Pathetic pathetic level of professionalism
So Alex really wants to make sure that no one thinks that the Trump ad targeting
Strong women
Is an issue with Facebook
But everyone has stopped
He wants to make it seem like it's a gender issue
He's very desperate about that
And so
Here is a clip
Get you to take more
And more
And more the poison
Until you just finally
Just to come to the
I just love
I just love anyclip that ends like that
Budget misleading and stupid b*******
And then I'm going to throw it to the
That's unreal a guy who has
No real qualifications except
Edit tiny pieces of meat
We can't live in a world where
Years away from being on CNN
That's two years away from
Somebody
We might be too far down the road to avoid that
I will see
Carpenter
Dog
You want to go to the doctor
Going to be on
We all know her
If she doesn't show up
Oh no she could spot
Which is a good thing that is good this is the good news of this next clip
Although it does come with some
Your question so
Princeton on
Branson
Got online
We're just going to start a little bit
Finish this whistleblower
You imagined Edward Snowden going
To project Veritas
Seems weird
Voorhees again the the
Quote-unquote Google whistleblower who believes there's a Zionist occupation government
Run the media and all that s***
Do you think Alex asked him about that
Cuz he doesn't know what is he
Leave that part inside tire rack
What about that song
Clear hierarchy of
Who bumped
You know what I'm saying with Infowars guest I want a clear like
Olio called so he bumps this person
Heat bumps that leg
From the
Responsible for Leo
Alright okay he is
The cat's meow
Just things with his
Little hammer
Drop Voorhees for that
Get back
Voorhees
We talked about him on the last episode
And so when I heard he was on it was going to be on for the rest of the show
Yeah I was like I don't want to do this
No I don't want to go back
Save-A-Lot
Time on the show
They better get into actual evidence
Because
2 hours
Renegade program
Then I'll be
You would presume
Your evidence
I so I decided I would try it
Isolate
Any instances of actual evidence
That this guy is presenting
I'm going to go with
Freewheeling chat
God made
Alex tries to get into that a little bit but it's not really the
The predominant
It's really go on for another couple hours
It does
Jesus
And I'll tell you this
He does not seem to like
Zach Voorhees as a person
I think it's a little annoying
Triggers that like certain nerve comes out
Because he there's a couple points you can just tell he's like
F*** this guy
The Alex and Zach discussing an interview this is one of the pieces of evidence
First thing
The rabbit interview that Eric Schmidt did with Charlie Rose
We definitely not something we need a whistleblower for
In the interview
The town of answers
From a search on Google is a bug
If the search function was perfect dude always get the right answer for what you're looking for everytime
You clearly talkin about factual information
Who was president during The Louisiana Purchase
But Alex in Voorhees
Talking about applies to literally every
Probably not a fair
Assassin
What he was saying
Alex and Zach are both
It's possible
The first thing they bring up
And I
To be an incredibly weak
Especially for a guy whistleblower
You don't need to go to Charlie Rose interview available public information
It was on
Charlie Rose doesn't have the viewership that maybe
You know that talk shows of your older times.
Certainly.
So
Not going to find
Snowden just pointed to a clip of mad oh my God
We would have murdered him
Descended upon him like a
Rocks from a
Has the chance to
F****** Chris Hayes interview
Got to go
I know you guys think Larry King has been off the air for a while
Now but I've got some underground Larry King footage
The show you
The issue that I I ran into very quickly
Is the things that we know that
Has put into the world and believe
Take some of the things he's saying
That might just be like a bee
This is a stupid Alex
Jones
Territory
Anna's first one involves
George Soros
The exhilaration
Concentration camp
And what's really ironic is that
If we criticize George Soros
Call
Criticizing
The reason Alex last there
Is because he knows that he
He's talkingshit
He's admitted as much on his second Rogan
But the idea
Not an answer question
He's talking
S*** it's redic
This is not okay
To hear from first of all Alex. But then a guy who believes and I'll f****** song
This isn't okay this is
True
It's not real
Isn't something video
Exist
They're talking about
And they're demonized
Soros in this way
Because of those other beliefs that they have
He's Jewish.
Don't react World
Mythology and ideology Voorhees
Scribes to
Alex Jones is allowing essentially
A complete
Somatic
Pageant
To happen on his show under the guise of the guy have in Google Documents
Prove XYZ
It's another example where they're
Cheating
Maybe
Explode
Because here's the thing
Claiming they're claiming
While they're making a
Anti-Semitic
Right
Bulshit
And we call them out
As being anti-semite
They're trying to suppress
And
We're the ones who are
Because we all work for George Soros to work
She's medic smear
Say me where to criticize Israel
Apartheid policy
And their destruction
Apartheid
Sure
So
Is true but somehow both of them are
Driving
Yep they're not great
But first we have to have another
Gigantic red flag
Be thrown onto the field
Buy one Sack or he's
Alex
Just f****** runs
He loves it
So yeah
Call Sawa
No
I would recommend
That's
Looks like Alex's
Has dropped off
Explicit
He supports the terrorist acts committed by Anders Breivik
Refers to a saint brevik
He's a race IQ guy
He's literally called homosexuality a birth defect
And argued that
Acceptance of LGBT
Take you right to the symptom of the civilization
Collapse
He wrote on his blog quote
For most Americans the issue isn't whether Jews have divided loyalties or not it's whether they I have any loyalty
Five states at all
So I'm sure he loves Trump's,
He's advocating for horrendous war crimes against Palestinians saying quote
The Israeli government must announce to the world that unilateral ceasefire balance by the deadly promise that for every Israeli soldier
25 Palestinian police
Lodi
For every civilian 100 non-combat
Palestinian adults will be
Slain
And for every child 1000
And adults
This s*** was posted on WorldNetDaily
WorldNetDaily looks good
Yeah I think they are
Are there
Complete monster
His books
Sjw it to tell you that at all
Is Vox Dei wrote it and Milo yiannopoulos wrote the foreword for it which
She did I can tell you sight on seeing if it's a load of worthless drivel
But it's exactly the sort of book you'd probably expect to hear being promoted by a guy who believes the u.s. is under his
How's the show's become completely in a
Inundated I turn on an episode of fascism Advocates or Alex's lawyer
It shows a complete disaster and if the diminishing sound quality is any
Indication it's running on borrowed
Like I think it feels like the wheels are completely fallen off the wagon
As goes Infowars
What they say
As if
America ghosts
The right next to the knob
Conspiracies about Soros
Promotions of Vox days book
Put forth by the sky
Gibson exhaust
On Alex's show which is irrelevant
Piece of information about both of those things
About forgetting
Is that you and I are anti
They go see now he's fine the guy who's like all of us
Exterminate
He's he's good
Code
Language
Should be that's a little familiar.
That's not coach Keith speaking tube
He's signaling to anyway
Google 48 years
And and then the last everything was turning into clown world
And so I decided that
That
Understanding how
Marxist left I realized
Understand that what they're doing is appalling
And reprehensible
Andaz
Available on the internal public internet
So
Cool I've even know to hide all the Smoking Gun proof and I did grab it all up
And Rachel Maddow
Couldn't
Him using a clown World there is sick
Particular audio
That is a hundred percent
Like what's being done
Probably make
Make the same argument
I'm stupid I wanted
Supremacist
Leaning
Yeah you might as well
2.024
Only a select few prisoners know about it yet
I forgot
During this talk with Zach
I love this so much
In the span of 20 seconds
Alex plug
2 shirt
Explicitly stole the design
T-shirts by the way
That are limited edition
The shirt inspire
That shirt is almost sold out so it is the last run
I'll be space force
So those are both going
But he even says on there like isochrysis so we changed it today
Because he thought
Intellectual property theft
Personal like that
This whole thing is private property loves it so much
You do it but that does make more sense why that is why the Donkey
Would be
Confused it is
Stuff was being
Center for copyright violation
Because
They violate copyright all the time
The position that they could have ice
Is like it Electro property doesn't
Put in order for them to make that they need to change the number of the things
They also need to stop complaining
Their intellectual property theft
Arrow out of their quiver
I don't think they're willing to do that
And so there internally in
Inconsistent weather
Eagle other
People's intellectual property isn't real about
It all day
The rules do not apply to me
Milk
Short supply the people who I'm trying to
Fair enough
So we get back here to the evidence
Zach is putting
He has an odd some audio of the
Susan
Speech at
And it doesn't
Really demonstrate
Close
He's got that episode of Muppet
The speech that he has essentially boils down to like
We are going
To not
Put both
Yeah
Why would you want to company
Just allow anything
Brighten their news
It doesn't prove
You saying
Brings out addict
But he wants to highlight
It's not good
It's not a good
Despite the darkness. That was released to project veritas
They can go to Project veritas
It's on page 5
If there's this document here
And if you look
At
The second example is
Wikileaks confirms Hillary sold weapons to Isis then drops another bombshell breaking news
Okay
And
And it's worse than anyone could have imagined
What are the issues
To be addressed here is it
Serious pointing to one of the documents You released about Google to find what they can
Consider to be faked
Issue with Eric
Example Google uses about stories involving the Wikileaks release
Stories are ones that alleged that the email prove that Hillary was
Brusque
Getting to Benghazi and we talked about it a bit
In the past
For a second
The particular issues
About
Hillary selling weapons
Don't I care about Benghazi
Because
Because it's not relevant at all
To the subject
Did Zac is talkin about
And the stock
Google
What team plays in this consideration is whether or not the stories about WikiLeaks
Releasing an email to prove Hillary selling weapons to us
Whether or not those are true
That's the only determinant of factor about whether or not these stories are fake
It could very well be that Hillary was selling weapons to Isis
The Confederate States of America in
Spider leadership
0 bearing on whether or not a story about a Wikileaks email is true or not
The only factor is whether or not such an email exist
Because if it doesn't then all the stories that are saying it does are like
And fake
That email doesn't
The closest WikiLeaks
Do the theories out of email to 2014
We're Hillary indicates an awareness that the Saudi government
Headband clandestinely sporting
And that we sold
Saudi Arabia weapons
She also explicitly notes in that two females that their support of Isis was something we needed to apply pressure on
To get them to stop doing
The entire rest of the email is about stopping Isis
So I'm not sure of her intentionally selling weapons.
Also Alex probably wants
Deep conversation squarely way from Saudi Arabia let's talk about Trump
Huge weapon sale
Of light
This is a classic case of a conservative media site
Creating a sensational headline
In this case
Wikileaks confirms Hillary sold weapons to Isis
Which is just picked up and repeated like a bad game
Telephone and tell people repeating it
No idea where they got the information from
They claim that they read the Wikileaks emails
If you ask them which email
They're talking about for you
They couldn't have
Because no such email has ever been released by Wiki
You can
Make a pretty solid argument the during her time as Secretary of State a lot of places that eventually found
Other ways of Angela's
Through faster
Mishandling or some combination
Circumstance
But that's not the claim is being made by these sites
They're alleging that Hillary Clinton knowingly and intentionally sold weapons
Isis which is a false
Claim
They're further thing that this would be leaks email proves their claim
Which itself is another false
This is why Google would use this as an example of a fake news story
Because it is one
Zack the whistleblowers so entrenched in the world of right-wing
Conspiracy of propaganda has no idea what the actual conversation is
He hasn't conclusion in mine so he has zero interest in the Nuance of why
He's actually a really good case study
He's very very dumb which is why you would find a ton of innocuous documents on Google share folder
And then decided there was some kind of a Smoking Gun
I've read a number of the document
I don't have time to read all sounds
And some of them
Not even
Relevant in any way
Website that
Broke down all of the document
Assessment
Perspective was
A really good
There's nothing in there
And then here's the other issue about this
Just make it up
Something is there does matter about
The situation
When's that Voorhees release these documents a project veritas
Neither he nor James O'Keefe took the time to
To protect the identities of people who are mentioned
The documents
The personal information of people in email threads
They didn't knock
One entire folder marked partes
Is mostly screenshots of Google employees social media accounts
Exactly
Where they say things that he feels indicates there's a comfort
Citywide fire
Leaving
Stupid that
Is that the individuals having opinions indicates that the entire company has
This is a shameful Act of Docs
The massive scale and it wouldn't be unreasonable
People in danger
Is that cuz arguing these people are trying to socialize
Did your the country into a fraudulent election
He's putting a gigantic Target on
Decided to release the documents on
No legitimate journalistic Outlet would ever do some
It's really really f***** up
Incredibly
They can't do
I guess
Why did we write laws for all this s*** in retrospect
Really really obviously
It's okay
But that's why
Cuz it's so cartoonishly evil we would never have a
F****** unreal I imagine
Because it's not
You know like your social media account is Poplar all of that
That this is with malicious intent 100% the only only outcome you can really expect
It is these people being it
Harassed Breton
Police threat if not an expert
Send it doesn't demonstrate anything that helps
Make that
Text point
Now I don't know what that just gives into
But I don't know if he's too stupid to not understand that it doesn't make
I think that's entirely possible
It's possible that he
Screenshots of these people
Social media accounts in there in order to Target
Right
If project Veritas hat
Even a kernel of respectability
Then they would have gone in
And wiped out people's name
Before releasing
Every reason to understand
The possible ramp
So considering they should be in jail a few
Few times over
This is
The other piece of information that he's bringing
To the table
Hillary Isis
Email example that then what are the document
The pieces of evidence
WikiLeaks
Email proves Hillary new of
Horse Sheriff that dresses up like
Vigilante guitar
Waifu
And again
Even if B conclusion
Did Hillary did sell weapons
Even if that's true
These stories are still fake cuz it doesn't exist and just the stories are fake
It doesn't matter what the conclusion
Right
We get to another piece of information
Exact has
Approve
I really know this one is f****** into his
Documents
It's just some
Little magic trick
That you can do
You can see that Hillary killed everybody
God I hate these people so much
And so
Google was able to influence the election is that
Were deleting
The search prediction results when people were trying to find information about
Hillary Clinton a lot of people
Went on and you know
We're searching for the Clinton Body Count because there's a lot of people
In a related to Hillary
Seems to be swayed the election
Because Google didn't allow the autofill
Suggestion
What do you type in Hillary Clinton
To be Hillary Clinton
Right right out of the
Suggestion
I imagined or at least hope that Hillary Clint
Big tits was removed from the auditor Good Feet
Yeah
You can search but it pulls up pictures of Ice-T
Westside
Generally speaking today
It could be
If you get way out of hand
For Media company to hide negative stories about a particular political figure regardless of their political affiliation already
I think that's something to keep in mind
And if there's ever a serious example of that I would give it to
I'm serious thought about what size
I want to laid
My cards on
However this is not an instant
I'm perfectly fine with a company like Google eliminating basic
What's a dangerous conspiracy ship from there
Suggested search bar
It's not like you
You can't just type in Clinton Body Count get a ton of f***** up stupid results
It's a tissue typing
Quinton
Google doesn't
The Clinton Body Count meme started back in 1993
Who died under suspicious circumstances
With a heavy insinuation that they were bird
Just a desire to derail the
Probably because she was a militia lunatic
But declared herself the quote acting adjutant general of the unorganized militias of the United States
Why is
These people are winning over the rest
Before March on Washington
Sounds more like a revolution we all remember we all remember 1990s
Got arrested
Nope cuz didn't happen
Citizen's arrest even the John Birch Society decried those plans
Johnson
She also made the incredibly inaccurate film Waco the big lie
Which I know I've heard Alex bring up
Before
It's full of misrepresentation
Some of the footage has even been accused of being actually manipulated
It's part of Timothy McVeigh Lovitz
Come on
Give me more of this lunacy
Suspicious Clinton deaths to representative
Who took the ball and ran with it
Even adding a
It should be pointed out that William dannemeyer though former represented
Is it completely insane
And shity person
He wrote a post for take back all right to.org entitled quote now the government can legally kill Christians
With your grandmother's Lee
Costco Heritage
Here's some choice
Let's hear it
Your US Government Can now legally kill Christians for the crime of worshipping Jesus Christ!
To go through
Who are Utah
When you say your
When you're constructing ascent
Specifically one
Don't start with your
And then
Run-on sentence
It doesn't make any
Next one!
Novel let alone a blog post
What about that
Deception has been perpetrated on the American people by their own leaders
Your government
Suggesting you were talking to people now who are you talking to
There I don't know
Shift person
Pictures of George h.w. Bush signed a law that forces the American people to be bound by a set of monsterous rules
Who's called the noahide laws
Rules that make the believe in Jesus Christ
Exclamation
Do we even have those
If that word noahide in their worries
Hold on to those okay
The article explains that a bill called education Day USA which was
Suspicious
Weekly ad in language that recognizes birthday of Rabbi Menachem Mendel schneerson
Peterson
Stay With Me
Hidden in that bill
The head new laws that make it totally
Forgot to kill Christian
But of course
That would never pass
If it were voted on by the house
I would
Hope
I think we're about to hear
A very familiar story
On the Davis resolution with
Okay
Amadeus resolution was passed
Past and quotes
The entire membership of the House of Representatives had already been dismissed
Including the voting was over
We could all go home
It was then after virtually all the members had left that the traitor is authors of this resolution brought it up for a vote on the house floor
With only four
So
This bill eventually became Public Law 102 dashboard
There's not a vote total recorded for it
But that's just probably because it passed
Without objection
That doesn't mean that four people voted on it and they just said good enough
I mean 41 the bill had 225 Echo spot
So you'd assume that kind of Bill would never actually come to a vote
They're only 435 members of the house if it belies 225 co-sponsors it's never not going to pass
I don't understand what if there is a surprise twist
Professional
Right by our comes down to sex
Congresspeople stunners
How do I factor crazy Williams
His argument is that because Rabbi schneerson organization follows the seven noahide laws
And this resolution recognizes
Call to the world to return to the ethics promoted by
Like I should point out as a meaningless symbolic thing
I'd be in their eyes language
After us is now under these Jewish laws
Punishment for breaking any of these laws
What is the cap
Another is that no historical Source exists that
Contains an instance of a non-jew being executed
Breaking noahide laws
So it's kind of
Stupid
People just believe in
I mean I know they do
For sale just believe in
In narrative magic that makes sense so long as magic
Possibly
The government could just
Mass murder at William
Right
Or even if they did it
One time
Remember
That was legal
We're going to have to refill
It's not like Congress would be like I would say that what William
Should do is test his theory by killing a Christian for being Christian
I've seen how that goes forever
We're under noahide laws
Understand he can't do it because of course
Just needs people to kill him
No he's already dying out
Alright so if you read the 70s very similar to the ten
And William's big beef stick
Used to be that the Ten Commandments were written by God
Where is the seven were written by human
He explicitly says but that is a problem
This is an argument being made by a member of Congress in the 90s
The bar has always been low
Please go little bit off the rails
Crazy Willie
Members of Congress claim they control
Look at those six confirmed
Noah underestimate the ferocity of the commitment of the
System of the world
World government
Weird alright
Run-on sentences
Stick thing
Sometimes mr. Noah mister noahide
Dannemeyer
This is protocol
Destroy Christianity
So if you're keeping
Score of the Clinton Body Count story is the product of that guy
And a lady who declared herself a fake Universal decided she wanted to arrest Congress
Over the gears periodically people of debunked
Specific people
Included on that
But it doesn't matter
Just Dance
I'm all for Google not
Suggesting this is a serf
Result
You might be looking
Before because it's b*******
Half down a radicalizing
I think that it is a responsible thing
Society to recognize
Is like that
You can look for it
But we're not going to help you find
Algorithm people into those rabbit right
Google
Things like that are in
Points down of really bad Road
And
Don't need help
People go down this way
I don't know
Anti-free speech guy for that
I never thought that I would see this
The day that you gave up on Holocaust
Did it happen I'm not I'm not mad that like if you type in Alex Jones
The suggestion isn't killed his dog
Let's say we
Started to really try and make a move a bunch of content about it
Like a hashtag SEO.
He killed his dog we're going to eliminate that from search
Wow that's censorship
We were f****** with you the whole time
I don't know
Anyways refines his idea about this
About the elimination of the
Clinton Body Count
You make six-point a little
Catalog two people can
We're able to find it
What was happening
When people would go and try to type in like Hillary Clinton Body Count
Google
Shut off
And
Body count that search result prediction
See user but part of that is B
Because there hasn't been a 26
6 year long
Fraudulent propaganda campaign
Against Trump
Right so there
Completely on and Allegan situation
If there were
Lakewood safe for 26 years
People had been putting forth this b******* list
Of people's near Trump with died Maybe
Yes absolutely that should not be in the
Suggested search
Like in those circumstances it were and Hillary's weren't
He's got a good argument but they're completely
Different things
So
Yeah
F*** off
I don't like it I like it when we're dealing with it
Evil
On the stupid evil can
Is really stupid
So stupid
It's very very stupid
Just trying to
Text bring up his
Medium page
His blog
Sure cuz he's got the information on there
Zack this made me laugh
Pretty hard
Because I know what Alex is doing
Through this
Infowars.com
We understand what happened
Beautiful
But you can come too
Infowars
Everybody we're going to put up with you today
Infowars.com
F*** out of here Google
Douchebag that's so if it's so true
Transparent
Ridiculous
So Alex also has a sale going on
Anniversary sale was after that
And now we have the America awakens
Didn't get a clip of this I wish I had but Alex explains it
And it's just basically all this
But he's like
It's not on everything it's just on some stuff
It's not as metaphor
50 to 60% off free shipping a double
Rhys not on something
Wow
You're really selling this new special. Love it
Sing of the
Paseo
So Alex Goes to Commercial and he comes back
And they play a compilation of him talk
Think about how like
Silicon Valley
People are on drugs
Right is right next to
I don't know what they were doing.
Special Report is playing
But I have this minute-long clip here
Close attention
And recognize that I make this compilation
This sounds like a parrot
Okay
In the hell
Type of pleasure you want is plugin
White light pupils are
Hazard wirehead something's going
Cuz I'm not on drugs
This is crazy
Exactly like a guy
I'll tell you what's going on
I listen to that I was like
He's someone inside f****** with him
Somebody's f****** with
I don't know I thought that was hilarious like it's incredible it's either Alex leaning into a recognition that these
Kinds of things
Hampton for him outside of his already established audience
Rights memes that are kind of making fun of him into that
For this maybe
I'm not sure but whatever it is
It's sad
Dysplasia
Everything about
No no no 22nd
And there's not really any
Certainly no exclusives
Totally blocked
I have not cut out like
Mentioned
Sears has not brought it up
But
He doesn't declare that it's time
Start a run
Hi I'm
I started fighting Irish over 40 years ago
Great set timer
Executives arrested
However you got to get there.
Why All That Remains
I've made some
Arguments
Did that
History will bear you out
As indicated by this
You'll see a lot of politicians a lot of people like open their eyes and just continue to talk and
It's a good technique in order to right now
If I'm by then I'm going to open up my eyes were wide and I was going to talk to you and your
Trance and one of the key things that you don't want to play
So he's trying to hypnotize the audience
Spy camera
This is silly
Okay okay now what you do is you open your eyes
Mezmur
A weird angle directions for this show to go in Revit
Failed to demonstrate to critical observer in entryway
Okay
Fluoride bad for you
How to do with Google first year
Because Google is blocking like a real help
Information
Which I assume is somehow some sort of
Good defensive Mike Adams
Whatever
Mike Adams get on the real health information
Talk about brings up
Biscotti
About fluoride
Texas
Real good
And there's a lot of research
Internationally showings
Fluoride lowers
And now it's like
Pediatrics or something
Preach mg of
Fluoride found in pregnant moms
Starting to mouth
So back has not really read this study or not into it
You read it all
It sounds like you ready
From start to finish a certain amount of IQ
Or something just heard there was dead even Vault IQ fluoride
I'm guessing that's okay
So this is a study that was published in the Journal of the American Medical Association
Pediatrics in to point out that it is a it's very
Very explicit in the study.
A demonstration of a
Causal link
Between consumption
Fluoride
And lowered IQ of the child
A possible assoc
A couple problems
I don't actually problems with the study but their problems for the conclusion that Alex and Zachary Drive
The first is that only 85.2
Percent of the parent-child pairs had urine analysis down to actually solidify
What are fluoride levels
Questionnaires and made estimates based on the level of fluoride in the water in a given
City and the Stars quote
For this study we develop methods to estimating calculator
Calculate fluoride intake
That have not yet been valid
So they didn't like
Compare those
Methods result
There was some indications of
Between the urine test
Quest
Estimate
Similar
By their own language
Alignment
To cause pain
The second is that the study itself points out that fluoride has a very short half-life
Hoveround 5 hours
Tricky thing
They could be thrown off by like brushing your teeth
Teeth an hour before the test
It's not necessarily the best way to figure out what a consistent level of fluoride
The study also explicitly says quote
This observational study design could not address the possibility of other unmeasured residual
Confounding
Which is to say that there are a ton of factors they couldn't
Control4 that might have influenced the results
Listen to knock on the study and anyway
Since the conclusion is just that the observational study found a possible Association in
Shouldn't could be study for
The problem is when
People like Alex's
Take the study
Like right and over-exaggerated
Conclusion as proof that low amounts of fluoride lower IQ
State 4-H Market
And they discovered and they pray
Which is not true you can have conversations about all this.
The IQ test
For the children were given between the ages when they were between the ages of
3 + 4
Well it's certainly not unheard of as a thing to do I start a number of resources that cautioned against IQ test
Can children this young
The children may not be able to focus on the test adequately that can produce an unreliable results
Plus there are tons of examples of people's IQ fluctuating quite a bit over the years
Now they say that to test their supposed to be designed
Produce a consistent result within plus or minus five points
But that's not always the case
And the younger the child is when they're test
Did the more likely it is that they're going to get an unreliable test
This would be more compelling if the
The children were 10
But that's not disqualifying for the study
It's just a
The caveat for proof of anything
Just a study that says that more studying is required
Things that are in
Beat study yourself
Lake does their sections in these studies of limitations of the study
Issues with what we're putting forth and why we can't make it to
Affirmative conclusion
Right
We're not we're not trying to prove anything to get almost like a divining Rod out there that's going to say
This area is going to narrow down what we should be studying
As opposed to we're trying to prove that fluoride
Simply trying to
Factor in as many variables as we
We possibly can
Point2 weather
More
You know followed up on people do more studies the control for the variables that were on can
Controlled
Abso medication
There is a link
Between
Fluoride
Diminished IQ in children
Then
This is not established
We're done with
The 21st
Zach
Go to hell
Zach was Zack was a hero
Sure
So we didn't get any talk
About Trump
Being the chosen one
Which again
Is because it probably happened while I was on Erica
You didn't get any talk about being disloyal to talk about
Second coming of God kind
We got from in Hong Kong who weren't allowed to
Yeah scaccia
So we get into Thursday
22nd
Alex jumps into the show and makes up
For it
I think you realize like
Probably ignore the Jews are disloyal thing
I could probably ignore that
But what
So Alex
The truth so refreshing
Years old
Yes Trump is the chosen one
So tell our Destinies if we choose to
Is delivering the country out of the globalist bondage
To keep their entire system
In-Place right now
Jack
Pretty galaxy
Alright
I am going to give it to him
Got it
Trump saying that he's the chosen one into
It's good to finally see a Statesman and office telling it like it is
That is mental gymnastics Simone biles could never touch
It was referencing at the beginning of the show like an argument
I could be mad that
You know what you're saying I'm the truth
I want to take on
Eliminate all prior context
It looked up to the sky well
Surround to allow that kind of.
And I'm not going to allow
Sad
That's sad and hilarious
Loyalty
Ideas
And this is good
Israel
Look
Support for Israel
Upside down world
People
Leprechaun Powers Israel
And then acting like Netanyahu runs the world
Rothschild
Globalist left
Not make the shop
Describing mythical powers
The f****** Rothschild
Who are liberals
We're slowly.
Davis tomorrow
What's going on
Is that Alex
Have to paint the idea that collab
Why is advocating for the end of
To critique
Can the government
Being oppressive against Palace
Well the same time
The jangly keys so you don't stop
You need to attack her in order to cover for
Stuff we got this
He is the chosen one in the same way we are all the chosen one anyways did you know that Liberals are actually
Eating your baby faces right now
Cuz it invisible liberal is eating it right
Sure
So in order to achieve
Alex has to
To get really f****** mad about Rashida tlaib
Press conference came out and
Talked about
Not being allowed to go on their fax finding
Mission
This is real
Alex's like
Alex
Carries himself
Is
I mean I don't know
It's really really bad
Free stuff
The breakroom
What's money
Press conference with with the four horsemen
Democratic
Call my mother
Hospital she was in
Power starter my grandmother and they wouldn't let her in
Free healthcare
You want to blow the country up
Wonderful Palestinian play
So I do I watch the speech
Israel
Show up Israel I don't
People who are little bit and look directly into the camera
I have some missing time
This little experiment
Validating
Surround
Absolutely Audrey
You goes further
In this next clip
And basically invalidate
Therapist
And George
And why is that
Because every time
Rebellion
Because I don't even exist
They're just people that want to take it over
Tell me I can't
That's so childish
Incredibly
Many countries
Alex's pretending don't allow any Palestinian
He's just making s*** up to support his own xenophobic and
Racist worldview
Alex's argument the Palestinians aren't even a real thing
Is a shameful display of rhetoric that leads very easily to dehumanization
Extermination is Starkey
It's not something I've even going to
Dignify with the response
That is
Insane
That is literally
Philippa Alex
Rasheeda is fake crying
While she's talking about
This is just
Israel
See this
Because it's the left
It's like all these people attempt suicide
Attempting suicide
Parasite
We are all day and then
Fetishization
Israel doesn't let her
She whines and cries about her grandmother
And our grandmother
Microcosm
What
And there's a fight
That was the vehicles America
The fight over who controls Europe
Between
Germans and Jews
Mexicans in Russia
Between evil and good
In your family it's a fight
What interrelationships in your business in your life that you
There's a struggle in the universe
Good
You people don't agree with my crazy b******* that I'm spreading
Your eval also I mean just
All this stuff aside
There's some comedy in the fact that Alex
Is talking about
Demeaning people who struggle with suicidal
Inclination
Is describing that to being with the behavior of the Democrats are
Ownership
We have Carpe donktum on talk about his link to copyrighted material
Write this whole thing is
This is pathetic
Come Dan and we're the lived
Just trying to steal Victor
From people like carpet
The joke is
Wrong
React
I mean
I don't even I don't even know where to begin
Begin with
I'm calling these people parasites
We could do
It's almost like a lot of his stuff is I feel like presenting
With minimal,
Except where necessary
Because this is just
Horrible ship that Alex's
Is product
This is part of the people leave
It's not like you didn't know that
What combination of
Also considering 10 years ago Alex was firmly in favour of Palestinian rights
From
I think a part sides bad too
They're not even
Did you think about that
It's like that combination of his worldview being only able to see through his eyes so he
He's always
He doesn't understand a good-faith ARG
He doesn't understand that they could be real crying
You know he can only
Performative for him therefore it must be greater
And then there's also that like
This is
This Trump s*** is what
Wild I don't even know what to do other than
Invalidating
Entire people
I think I think part of it is he feels he has to do that cuz he knows he's also going to validate Trump
S***
Something
I guess this would be the equivalent
White supremacist
Sugar to help the medicine go down
Now we're recognizing Trump as God appointment
Talk
Children when I got elected
Look up
Obviously
Panchos
Of course Trump
Chosen
The phenomenon
Smell it
And the devil and the enemies
President talking about
In the chosen one
Operation
Really
Coward
Take me to
Can you imagine if during ACA
Negotiations Obama was like God chose me
To help give everyone Healthcare
How to make the same arguments he was already making but it would be
Alex Alex
Being like
Master Yoda
Crazy
But you didn't go on the chosen one but he did have the whole life
God put me in off at stew to make sure that we bombed Iraq for the rest of
Yeah
I think there was an
Acceptable
Quotes socially acceptable version of an oppressed
Total understanding of
The links that you can use that probably was on the wrong side of that line
But you know like
Put me on this Earth
This podcast acceptable Ram realm of
Cuz we're living in a metaphor as opposed to a delusion of grandeur
Right
I wouldn't
I'm the
Especially when
Cortical leader of the Free World
Singer I run a carpentry business
I'm a good father
Erotic podcast
I would not declare myself the chosen one
Even though in the cult
I would literally the chosen one
You have some experience
SquareTrade
For my whole life
Trump is just jumping on a trampoline
Alex gets back to attacking
And then you see
Talib
The leader of the Fantastic
Wolf
Claim the each one is the leader whatever it serves his purpose if so great
He's in the background for a while to Topaz Lake
Jealous
You're all f******
Also the Rat Pack where like
Groundbreaking
Inside a bill
What
And then we'll didn't grovel to them
Oh I see that's how
So Rasheeda has it she is a palestinian-american but you was born in Detroit
Wright was born in Alexandria ocasio-cortez
New York Presley was born in
A refugee to like 10 years old
Alex is explicitly invalidating the American death of these women because they are people he sees us.
Who disagree with
Just know but you can't tolerate
Three of them were born here in the others
Making their own countries better
That's exactly what they're trying to do in Congress
Don't think too hard about it
Experiences
Because there's a lot of problems with the country
The revolver on the ideas of
Power hierarchy
Which Alex will desperately cling to no matter what the cost
He's bringing up to this idea of like
They're just that they know that we have feelings we have empathy visitor
Exploit
I mean can't you easily imagine
Exact
Same thing like during
The end of slavery
Absolute
These people are whipped and beaten and work
On the fields but that's
2 mi
Good
Noble white human emotion I don't want to have you not read the Bible
To keep them where they are because that's where they
Look I have just as much of a bleeding heart is any of you what do you guys call yourself that's why I want to maintain
Slavery
Have 2nd civil rights imagines Alex being like
Oh sure you know
Friends
It's all very idea
Yeah you're showing
These pictures of people being hoes
Just a tug at my Heartstrings
Exploit my good
Empathy mechanisms in order to override
Whatever I mean this is your client
Zika bulshit
So is on
Disgusting
Italics
To go over
The press conference
It's me Christian
Show Muhammad show.
In-N-Out you killed all the Christians around the mouth
But I'm supposed to kiss your butt lady
If you
You Wicked horror
Oh no
Prostitute
A psychopath
A sociopath
Find a button
Emotion
Fat
I watched as my mother had to go
Should.you humanizing checkpoint
Proud American
I was there with my city
The terrible car accidents
And I cried
Baptist Hospital
Jerusalem
I remember shaking with fear when
Chicken neck
Children's book
So interrupted there because she's
He's getting into territory that's very close to a lot of his old red
The idea of checkpoint
Oh I don't know
Government to people
The stuff that he's railed on for years
He can't allow that
Sort of
Presented on his show
A maggot
Parasite
It's way too close to his Lane
You help you run the risk
Of listeners curing her
Breakfast
And
Then think
I think I'm against
I remember vaguely
He's exactly the sort of tyranny my hero Alex Jones
Has been screaming about
The second hold on hold on
That there was a
That was
Pressing her
A minority
Of people
Through through
Tear
Checkpoint
And
Oppression
And I'm
She's a bad guy
That's what's being
I think that Alex recognizes
But there is a danger in presenting
Without interruption without
Preev
Priming the pump
Hyperloop
How evil
Disgusting display
It's like what Somalia is like
Going through the list
6 things that your
Supposed to take
Influence
So Alex is
Screaming about how she
The maggot
Do all of the other b*******
So you
The conceive
Instead of a human being
Expressing
The very
Tyrannical government
You're supposed to be again
Acting against
Instead you see
A flaming
Demon monster
Tugging upon your hearts
Wright and his arguments to just about like
Okay
Your whole thing was the about like this tyranny that's going to come
To America if you guys are going to get targeted
Because of
A big bombing
Oklahoma City
Well those are false Flags babe white people
Sew-ins Expo of Alex
Seems to be imagining
People like
Playb
Is never done anything
Sinbad
But that's not the
Does discussion at all
He's creating a straw man version
That in order to attack that is if that's the real
Flat wide
The Muslim never heard nobody
Do you want to talk about
I'll talk about the expansion of Christian
Missionaries were very much involved in that
Lobar example
Smaller example of
The ways in which
Christianity was used
I suppose he
Also
Tacit
Agreement that Christianity did it this
Right
Skewer that
Christianity only spread Noble
And Muslims
In Islam
Spread
So OK Google
Organically throughout
Evil
Bissell Good vs Evil tank
Really
It's a monkey dichotomy
So Alex and the next cliff
It's a shame
And I'm done
Jerusalem with my dead husband
In him is Gordon Gordon off the bus
Although he was a United States citizen
Just do security forces could harass him
Don't stop again
You want to overthrow Israel
From the West
My balls grab
When I go to the store
Globalist
That's
Okay
So
Describe living in a
Police state
Right
He agreed
With
The police state
Right
Then said that he has to live in a police
Because the police state is in
Correctly
I guess
Yes
Shear Art subjects
Tyrell
They're only a problem when they're being applied towards
Quite
People
The good people of the West
Wishes for y'all's about to apply to people unlike him
Absolute
Use of these women some more
I don't know I mean I can give that as an introduction
Pretty much all of these clothes
What is granddaughter
Did the elevator voice
Fight the truth.
Detroit Public Schools teacher taught me
Oh my gosh
Oh my God
Go to Somalia
Go fix your own problems
Rompers
Isn't
Powerful
I looked it up
Muslim family
Flavors
Recall on Alex to prove that man
Words from a slaver family because
Is her skin color is a little bit later yes
That is true
Omar's father was a teacher
Is an educational forum
Slavery damage
Are the only evidence that I could find
The backs of any claim even close to this
Was a Gateway pundit article that made allegations
He was working
The government has some sort of terrorist
Sure
Didn't prove anyway didn't have any source
But I was probably going off of that situation
For evidence
Claiming that congressman
Family is entirely slavery when former president
I would request
Yeah I know it's not worth anybody's time to actually Sue in Webster
Pretty crazy
I looked it up
Responsibility to
Some sort of a sorcerer
Approve this and anyway and you failed to do so
As it is
Slander
Scorpion
Declares
Which is noga
Really
It's really not good no and then he goes back
Today
Press
But
If you've actually watch
The actual Prescott
You will know that what he's doing is intentionally mislead
They cut out something
It gives what you say
Important
An abomination
Military occupation
Just really want peace and self-determination for their Palestinian Neighbors
They could have shed light into Injustice
Lexington
Here let's continue after that
At the beginning
People Force
To engage in military
Activities
What's right before that
If you listen to her actual press
Is a description
Of how she's doing on this fact-finding mission
Where
She's going to meet with Israeli veteran
She's referring to In that clip
Alex deprives out of context Israeli veterans
Open
Done Alex deprives that clip of context
Because it runs
Entirely counter
The presentation of this press conference and there's only Muslims in Palestine
And you know what they're not in Palestine
Cuz that's not even
He's trying to present the idea that
She's going over there and only going to be
Two Palestinian people
When in reality the word bunch of different groups
Omar and others were going
To go and meet up with and if you allow that reality
Be presented
You ruin the perception
That you created
Alex is interested in the narrative
Not
Which I'm sure is also one of the read
Possibly
Associated
Israel in Oak Plaza
I would assume
So if Alex
Is to inoculate the audio
From empathy
Except these arguments
Points that are being brought up
This is primarily about the making sure no one feels
The delegation would have seen firsthand destructive
Not productive
They could have asked the people in Bethlehem
Hello cut people off of way from Economic Opportunity
To live
And you don't stop right there
Mother and The Birdcage
This is this is really really
This is all to manipulate your hearts
Is all just the Heartstrings
Mr. Gorbachev
I'm loving that wall
Keep it going
More less
We're done with the press conference
But
For this next
I want you to remember
Alex Jones
Is bigamy is the New World
Sure
That's important
Because
Persona world population
Everybody trying to get my country
There's a simple reason we got Christian
In the trees
I like the
True
Got milk
The only way
Wasn't going to force you to serve Christ
Door's always open
The way is Jesus of Nazareth
Global unification
World order under Jesus Christ
Is working
Sunbury Christian rules
I cannot
Think of anything
Knowledge
More
Then Christian
Baby
Also there's
You know
Some issues about
If that's
The case of Christianity is the only thing that made things
Workout
Is a lot of periods of history that you're going to have to come up with
Right
I'm pretty sure the Chris
It's not
I'm coming at this from
Like Christianity wasn't
Invented in the 19
Metaphor
There's a lot. A lot of a lot of Darkness
An explanation for why the Christie
Operating system
As he's describing it wasn't
They taking everyone to the Moon makes me it just makes me laugh because
The Bedrock of mathematics
It was
Bev made by his enemies
Sure as well as the technology itself necessary to go to the Moon
So
I believe his Christianity
Probably Christian
I mean like the biggest
Is
What he's saying
It is entirely just a
I want a Christian world order I want a unified One World Christian order
Also is b*******
To Deb worship Jesus
Dwell in his
Theory of it but let's say there is a Christian world that comes into power right how is
How is the experience of being a Muslim in that
Circumstance
Like is the best
Case scenario
Infor is at
Tolerance
World Order
Entirely run
By Christie
Right and that's not
Isn't
A good situation
World dictators
In his conception
Well it's not
That's that's real stupid
That's real stupid
For someone like him.
Hear that
That's a little bit too much
I think you should probably bail
I think this might also be
Be something that he
He's now having
To do because of
Yeah I think
Sure and he's already indicated that he wants to buy Greenland
Indicating a move towards expansion
And making an empire of America
He's always been against the UN but now he's talking about how a Resurgence of nationalism is
Right I mean it's it's a it's not a far jump
The exact opposite of what he's based is
Depends on
Just we're doing it
Surprise
No but yeah yeah
But now from the last year of all the invalidation
Its principles are conditional
Of course the New World Order is a conditional thing to if course it is
Nothing he doesn't believe anything else
Depending
Masculinity Christianity whiteness
And the power hierarchy that are implied within those
That is it
Skip
Anyway one last question and that is Alex taking a call
To get some calls and one of them wants to
Bring up this
Trump being the chosen
Cool twitch
I include this
To be a little bit of a taste of
How Alex
Listener
Are interacting with this develop
And it doesn't
It doesn't seem to
Education
Conversations
About the energy
At churches and black churches
None of your words mean
And and I love Jesus
Connecticut
Message to Trump chosen one comment
I haven't seen Trump yet make a comment
That
Is it stupid I guess would be the word because
Totally do after the date
Shooting
Stupid that was right on
She puts the comments out and in the West Rosewood endemic in a pool
If you can't see that Trump is doing
Christ-like things for this country in the world
You can't see the office
The side of evil out there not looking in the right place
So
By Alex's rhetoric being
So insistent
That the other side are devils and demons
He has on sublevel prepared his audience for the one who's
The second coming of God
This is not an
This is not a difficult for him to make
No no
Seems like
Probably would be
Be difficult for Alex to rationalize is hop skip and a jump
From where he already was
Do it for him
To just making this up
Keep the bike out course
Of course he's God's chosen
It's clear so far
Any point of acceptability
Is like
Is a are there a group of people who are
Trying to make everything
In the book of rap
Feels like it
Like it because
Even reading it I was like there's no way I remember I remember
Specifically reading the book of
There is no way
Unless some sort of
Godly hypnosis
That the Christian
Church whatever follows
Willingly
It must be a setup
Take Blake
Zero effort
It should be harder
It's weird
I'm not going to ascribe any kind of thing like that
Position
Encanto exist
I just
Like Alex
Recognizing is Imagine
Contagious way for the bushes
To take it
Final form
Inevitable as a
Which form of propaganda
Yeah it's it's that you know you get what you wanted
It's not what you wanted
Enter like
We got to get back to
Seems lost its way and that's the scam
He was never Republican he was never really into
The gop's
He was never into politics
Particularly into a Christian theocracy
This is achievable in his mind through Trump
So why wouldn't he encouraged the worst parts
It didn't make sense
Twisted way but only if you look at Alex through
The prism that we've come to an
Understand
Dialectic
I don't know
Stances that are going
YouTube something
Exploit
To create the car
Christian fish
Maybe
I don't know whatever it is it's not good
Very bad
I don't know what the future is going to bring for Alex but it won't be good
And I should say that
That right after that caller
Alex did say that
And the clocks day was going to be and I said no thank you
We've already got too much
Behind us
I don't care
Whatever they were going to talk about
Zoggs
No interest
So
On Monday
The most worrying
Is it will be back on Monday
No
Laughed him off
The stage the moment he said I'm the chosen one
That's hilarious
I mean we're at a place now where that's the most worrying thing
You know three years ago maybe you could laugh about Thursday
Mary's real now verifying
Laughing at it
Will be Danger
Justa
Ditto
Reminder
Is this
Lick is okay
There's really nowhere there's really nowhere that you can go out no consequences for saying
Jewish people who vote for Democrats are disloyal to Israel
Where is a lion
Where is there a line
You have a president who's regurgitating protocols s***
Where is Hawaii
Nope that's what we've learned
Underscore fighting
We are
Currently
For now
Right
You could leave a review
That would be nice
People like to say no
You could also go to your local
Cigarettes they don't sell them anymore but that's
Secret code
Absolutely I also thanks everybody who sent pictures of
The crunchy bars are the best candy bar in the world
Responded to my
Bring it up with Kim
Infusion twitches
I didn't know what it
Dad wants to put to pay
That's what we're really
Chewed strategically
Around it to the Jelly Time.
Dance around a little
I am strategy know I'm laid out by the Jesus Lizard
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work