I have great respect for knowledge but I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
MoneyGram
Stripe.com
Little bit about hours
Have you ever seen
Stressfully
Play poker quite a bit
Straight poker
Somebody off of Full House was
You bless somebody else
Poker tournament that we were throwing for a friend of ours
To give him the money
We didn't we knew that
You didn't want to be like
Hey here's a bun
Armani
How far is Pineville
Really bad about it
Cuz I you wouldn't
Accept the money
And so what I did is I threw one of my trademark party
Afterwards I don't know where I pick this up
What might have been
From movie or some
Friend
There's a bathtub full of 40
Party
A bunch of 40 your bathtub with ice
But everybody comes to the party gets there
That was a great time
Kick somebody out of the party's over because they were trying to
Multiple 40 in a bag out of my butt
There's always a battle
Yeah
Bathtub full of 40s party
I know a lot about today
Theme parties
Text Joan
That's correct
Answered to go over
Common
Structure
Natural Dog episode
Play
Before we do it
Little moments
Signed up
Sporting Michelle
So first of all Steven thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Farpoint that might be Jonathan
Craig Manning
From Degrassi original characters
He is
Jimmy Jimmy Brooks from Degrassi
I also think you too Thomas
You are now policy walk
Peerless faucet brass
Plumber
Next
Appreciate it very much
So Ian and Eric
Freakishly large
Thank you so much
Ian
You so much Eric
We appreciate it very much if you are listening and you like what we do want to show you can do that by going through a website knowledge
Mugshot.com
We are trying to do something here
I'm trying to not have any
Kind of
Colonel
Mechanism involved in that and now our show it's just the two of us sitting in a
In a room
If you all make it possible so thank you very much
Also big announcement
Was that
I finally gave in our show is now on Spotify
Click those few buttons
Butts
Have
Brexit
Step one
Mice answer back
So how many plays does it take before we get a
I don't I don't I don't forget we ever will be
And that's okay
So Jordan today we're going to be going over the span of March 5th
March 5th
Teeth to March 22nd
Yeah
And the reason
That long
Is that so
You were on vacation
Coroplast
And I decided that I'm one of the things
I get through a lot of it
A little bit little bit
There is a little bit of
Restart
Doing this the crisis actors stop
And we are just like
Wow Alex
Just
Piers Morgan s***
He is all over the place
And it's not like you can just skip ahead I mean you literally have to listen to the episode
Before you can figure out
You know you can't just not
Into an episode
One of the frustrations
If you don't listen to all of them that you don't really understand that
Development what's behind
The rhetoric which is
What I'm most interest
So we going over this stretch of a little bit about a week
Of Alex's show
And I think
We might have some big
So it's good that we went ahead
I'm also I should say
That during this time there's something that I've just I don't have it
But it does bear make
Because Alex
About it
Abmat is the 2013
Cypriot financial crisis
Okay coming to a head
So the banks in Cyprus
Are going through some trouble
And I was thinking about it like well I'm not
The best
International finance
It would take a whole lot of time and it'll be like
40 minutes
This podcast
Explain
How much of the debt was
Bad Greek
Haven status
Cypress
I mean they put out a good album but after that they really
Kind of mismanaged
Is there money
What am I thinking
I don't know what you're thinking
I was hoping you would jump there joke
I didn't want to do it in the membrane
So I just decided that
Alex's take on it is very standard for anytime
There's some sort of
The money thing
And that is the globalists are doing it is and they're trying to cause
As opposed to
Some of the lingering effects from the 2008/2009
Situations
I just decided that
In and of itself is an important Global of
But for what
Texas doing it's not that important
Except for a couple of ways
That it extends
Two other area
And I will talk about those
But I don't I just we don't have the time
Breakdown
This.
I appreciate that
From Today Show before we jump
Roccat about the Battle
How old is Imagine Alex in a fedora
Blues Man Hank
The devil that's boring
Let's go all the way with scat
Start on the 15th
And what we find here on this episode is Alex
Is
Just continuing his insistence
That basically we need to go kill Kim Jeong Hoon
Okay
Alright
Running around
Surrounded by
But when you are openly running around
North Korea
Good
That's a good Line in the Sand
Someone's house with a gun and saying you're going to shoot them
Issue no
There's a brain
I don't think North Korea is withheld by First Amendment of the US Constitution
I'm just I'm just going to say that
Only inasmuch as like Alex is on like a pretty militant Pat
Relate
North Korea
Pinterest
And the second piece of it is just a
The tacit understanding
Things that even though free
Free speech is protected in the United States
There are limitations
Which is important
Because I was pretending years later
6 minutes later
6 minutes
You know even back in 2013 as a lot of apps
Absolutist ideas about
Bedford
Incongruity
With what he understands to ask
What free speech
Pictures about now Kim jong-un's surround himself with
With people who are drunk
On the
The blood
Might be more literal than you think
Is adrenochrome
You might actually be
You talkin about them being vampires from contact
If you think they force their fellow compatriots
Get drunk
Prior to
Making their blood
So they would have a hyphen
Alcohol blood
You'd probably get lice
You think so
Well well I mean just based on how much
Alcohol there is in blood than in alcohol
Let's just a cocktail
You've just invented at the worst Bloody Mary
Alright
Okay
Kim Jeong Hoon
A bit
He's getting like the violence
He's talking about the people
To talk about his
I mean that's just to further evidence that he probably
Sometimes
REI
I think it was describing
That is
Getting help for
Like if anybody
But like when I get aggressive I turn into a caveman I can't help myself
Tenable way to existence
If you are if you are like
Completely controlled by the whims of violence
You're you're messed up man
Know if at any point
Time you have no higher order
He's describing
If you are simply
Overtaken by
Testosterone
Society
Somebody who would walk up to your door and have a gun in their hand
Helped out
Violence
Sort of Albert's bragging about his own violent end
Ranting about
Demons
Dianne Feinstein
FaceTime
Continue of it
Insult
Half an hour
Of just like
Rambo
About nothing
Nothing going
Talent if it true tell
Sing about this other thing
That has been
Developing and that is
People particularly Michael Moore
That want the
Pictures
From Sandy Hook
To be released
Because there are times people were saying
And the
Motivation behind the
Desire to release the picture
Seeing photos is
Cut that off
The
Fake
Should I go your calls
Nope
So that is what he believes he want to show pictures cuz they love it
Right
Which is a
Thrill gross
They want to show the pic
Cuz they love
And glorify the death
Yes but they also want to use that
Trick you
To letting them
Break which will inevitably lead
To a tyranny
The time
But there's so many mass shooting
It's not like they're running
Okay
Sort of thinking
Extenze
Where Alex
Discussing an instant
When gun campus
The station LEDs
The genocide
Okay 100% historically accurate
So
One quick but in Port
Points
The vast majority of both the Hutu and Tutsi Rwanda or Christian
There were religious figures who fought against the knot
Is it the Tutsi were Christians and Hutu were not is a complete lie
That is absolute nonsense
He's just talkin
Try and create
Some sort of a white Hood narrative
Christian victimhood which is
It is interesting that you can turn a
Genocide in Africa
Between
Two tribes
Black people in
I guess that
So big a piece
This is his s*** that's why my brain
Did that little cup
Identify with are actually the victim
Personalization
In the wrong way
Unfolded in Rwanda in the early 90s
Complicated
There's no one factor that led to the genocide
The answer of what we is a global Community could have done
Stop it
Answer either of these questions involves a lot of possibilities a lot of missed opportunities
Deescalate
The situation
To recognize the warnings
And ultimately when you look back you see pretty much nothing
Tragedy
I know that Alex's solution to everything literally is just everyone should have a gun
But honestly if you look seriously at the Dynamics at work
Implayer in Rwanda that's just a childish delusion
Even if every Tootsie had a gun it probably wouldn't have been able to
Stop the horror
Transpired
What are the most indelible images of the Rwandan Genocide is out of
Machete
The Hutu militia
Used machetes as their primary weapon because guns were to occur
Expensive for what they had planned
Where is bullets
Or not
There's a reason that there's no reason to assume that the victims of their violence were any more able to
Report a gun whether or not
They had access
An important consideration is that
It becomes kind of a dishonest framing today that they weren't allowed to own
Gun
Chair
But I wanted to get to the bottom of this
I want to understand where the idea that
Tootsie's had their guns before they were last
I wanted to sort this out because
Materials I've ever read about the Rwandan genocide
And get it comes up for these gun weirdo
They are implying going to happen before
Broke out
The confiscation of property that happened during
Caskers
Campaign
Isn't there talk
In about
They all of the claims online
Trace back to
On all of these
Strange
Or they can
Constructed blog
The first is reference is made to the Nairobi protocol for the prevention
Control and reduction of small arms and light weapons
The Great Lakes region
The Horn of Africa
This absolutely was a resolution that's not to limit civilian ownership
Gun
Each participating country decided was illegal civilian owner
Guns
I have to suspect this is what Alex's
Is referring to
Since he's talking about that clip which is definitely involved in
The Nairobi protocol
Teen aerobic protocol was largely targeted at the illicit trade of weapons internationally in the language is pretty clear
Got that
It does
Contains language about confiscating illegal weapons
Registering authorized firearm so I can understand why Gunn weirdos
Be pretty upset about that
The problem though
Is that when they try and Link this with the genocide in Rwanda
What is a big problem
Since the Nairobi protocol was signed in April 2004
Is actor
That doesn't sound right
I've seen folks try to link this to sit
Full gear
Before that sun I really protocol to sign
This piece of evidence
It's just doesn't check out
What was it posted by a white guy
Might as well
More concrete
Discuss online
Like the NRA is what
Knock knock
Not specifically saying that this cause
Either of the campaign
Yeah based on
Chronology
Bright
The second piece of evidence I can find is a mini documentary called
Betrayed
Which makes the argument basically that all genocide
Seated by Gunn
Control measures
Effectively saying that if you're for gun-control you knowingly or unknowingly are going
To cause agenus
If a documentary there's a section
About Rwanda
Lawson
Poverty of kept the victims
From getting weapons to the
As they're saying there's an image flash is on the screen
All the fences and
Concealable arms are prohibited
With the words
Are prohibited
Outside the
Quotation mark
I'm not
Sure
What that mean
Yeah yeah yeah
I don't know where this is coming from
Right and there's absolutely no indication of what it's sighting
In the film there's no attribution
That's fine
Flashes up on the screen
Well it was a weird choice. To have that is a thing
It is innocence what is it in Central Asia
Betrayed betrayed man
From Ron Paul and Ted Nugent
So cool
Great
Good work so those words are flashed over an image that
Seems to be presenting itself as a legal
What the heck
Which is the name of a major newspaper in Rwanda
The official Gazette of the Republic of Rwanda
However the name of it is actually eat
Which makes me a little bit
Suspicious of the graphic
Save a misspelled name of the
Because that tea
Every time we talk about the
There are always those little things
If you
Had a good point
You would have spent
Presented like you weren't happy
I stay away with this project
Alex Jones City documentary
Because people are going to believe it in
Know
Superimposed
I put over a picture of a noose
That is
Reference correct
Probably
Superimposed over this image of these pose legislation
Just the words article 50
Which is Manchester just I believe that this quote is from Article 15 presumably from the Rwandan
Petition
Rwanda Constitution is nothing
With guns it's about people having equality
Under the eyes
Velox
Think of that
The current cons
Duchenne of Rwanda was put in place in 2000
Free
So maybe Article 15 of the previous Constitution
Was about Gunn
Nope
Their 1991 Constitution did include an Article 15
Recognized within the conditions
Define by law
Expedition Shelby authorized only within the limits
Prescribed by law
There's no version of Article 15 that exists in the Rwandan law that is anything
To do with the ban on quote offensive in
Concealable AR
The 15th
Article
Of the paper
That day
Article 15
Article
Score of the headline heading of a Rwandan newspaper being used as an image
Over witches
Quote about Rwanda gun laws is being presented
Restrict
New gun laws
Preceded the outbreak of the genocide
With a cryptic reference to an Article 15 which doesn't
From everything I can tell this is a complete fabrication antibiotic it seems like a disgusting
Appropriation of one of the most
Horrific chapters in modern day
Text to serve as a prop
For this gun
Carnage
That's so good
We rarely see p
It shouldn't surprise you to learn that this film was created by Jews for the preservation of firearms ownership
Alex Jones's earliest sponsors the oldest Snapchat
Being from May 19th
9 has a link to their website
Alexander Jews for the preservation
In the Firearms ownership go
Wayback
Organization
Started by a big old gun weirdo named Aaron
Zelman has been exercising absolute extremism my behalf
Since 1989
Interesting Lee with very little time on Google I found both Larry Pratt
Associating themselves with Salman and his group as a rebuttal to accusation
Consult their anti-semite
For Pratt it was when he was fired from the 1990s
Pat Buchanan campaign
The neo-nazis
It was at the Rocky Mountain rendezvous
For Ted Nugent it was after he got in trouble for posting
An image on Facebook behind Gunn
Control with pictures of Dianne Feinstein Chuck Schumer and 10 others opposed gun-grabbers Israeli flag
Eggs on their face
We might as well have been reposting stuff from Stormfront
Bananas that you can get away with
So I'm friends with
I'm also friends with Jewish Nazis
Juju bar
Explanation
Is so laughable
This is ridiculous
In my Rush between songwriting jams and usable
Musical recording
Images of people
Brown balls
I haven't had a hit you up
And everything after that I f******
Phone in
I should point out the 12 Israeli flags are kind of them
Point of that image
They're really hard to miss
Also over the image of senator Frank Lautenberg there is
Text that says quote
Gave Russian Jew immigrants your tax money
Carryover
This image
I think it would be totally get away with it
I genuinely didn't know that was the Israeli flag
I'm Ted Nugent
I'm professionally amore
So I definitely believe there are Jewish people who are opposed to Gunn
Control measures wanted minimize
Existing
Group
Large portion of
Membership with
Even juice
For the preservation of firearms
Firearm
Ownership
I believe that
Vast number of people who are in that group are probably
Concerned citizens
Jewish or otherwise
Who wrote just have
Feelings about gun issue
It seems like people like 10 and Larry have a relationship with them that feels
Similar to
Someone saying I can't be erased
The organization
To serve as a crutch to some of these
People who have
Connections with knots
In order to minimize
Distract from
Those connection
Preservation of firearms ownership
Who's responsible for Whole Lotta Vegas Oracle propaganda
That goes around a Patriot Gun weirdo circles about gun laws
A consequence
Of their enactment
Apparently this stuff about Rolanda is Judge
Yeah they have done a lot of pushing of the
The Hitler took the gun
Before
Should I which
Implore anyone to look into cuz that's
Ridiculous
Is a little off
On
Yeah f*** for a number of reasons
That 22nd if we heard was
Completely f***** up
Call
Coastal collar
Illinois gun laws
Alex is something that I find
And troubling
Last year
Bike mid-December
The Supreme Court gave Illinois
180 days
With some sort of
The right to carry
Whoa
So
I find that troubling is that I think there's
Still a difference
Between
Saying that it was staged
And saying
That the globalist
REI
Much closer
EBay used actors
Then saying they know they used
The Patsy
Whatever
It's not
They're not saying that it was
Directed
The production is
Made up
It was all there too
Play out in front of our eyes
And none of it Act
It's not as overt as I need to be
Closer
It's the language
It appears to be heading
Sing in that direction
This is
Is it closer to the bad side of it
Terrible side
Benny has been in
I can understand
Hyperbolic
Metaphor
But
I mean when you say stage
If you're going by what words
And it also has to live in the context
Texas so many of the
Fringe online
Theories that are already going around absolutely
Like this was
It's not like
That is a 4in idea to a lot of
Conspiracy weirdos right
They will hear that
I'm saying that these were
Yeah
And that we haven't really talked about it so much
Chances are if you've been following along
With the online
And debate outside of his show the online debate
Debate the online fervor
Entirely fake
Pretty quick
So that he's coming back now and saying it
Was staged
Most likely means he's relying on more current
But you know
It's in a Memphis
It feels that way
Alex has an interview with the guy who got fired for the 1996
Buchanan campaign because it came out today
Larry Pratt
And he wants to know if you want to talk about gun laws
I think he thinks he has a really good point here but I would say
He doesn't
Feinstein get a
Wonderful,
I've been
First Amendment
The invasion of privacy
Genius point is that like there are Shades there degrees that the Second Amendment
Degrees of the first
In the first clip of this episode Alex said there are
Tons of books that have been bad US history
Cruising these right-wing morons could
See
Egg the comeback
Everything
You have to be a lunatic
Take to be like
What do you say that not everything is absolute your stupid is a good comeback free speech is protected by the
But there's limits
There's no reason
To think
That
Owning a firearm
Is protected by the 2nd of May
But there are limitations to owning a firearm
There's no it's absolutely
Lele and lied with every understanding of how societies work
It's just
Sociopath
Works
Joel skousen but
Size very boring Alex just wanted to
Say that it's good
It's good idea
I hate
Divorce but pretty
It seems like it's mostly a plug for Joel skousen book
Strategic real okay
Like nuclear war
Me and that you need to know where that bug out to got to get scales
So we get to the 17th
Cuz
The Sundays
Big big narrative
That Wilkin
Continue throughout pretty-much
The rest of our time
I don't think I have a ton of clips of it but he brings it up over and over and over again
Police station
Oh there, what is it
Prison list
Florida
Law & Order balloons special balloon
So there's an element of this case
Spitaliks
Intentionally leaving it out very
Speculative
If it's episode you just keeps going on and on about this guy was arrested because he released a bunch of balloons in a romantic gesture for his girlfriend
Which is a crime in Florida because of Environmental Protection laws
Apparently it turns out you can't release more than
10 balloons in a 24-hour.
Which is admittedly a very
Strange
Limit your know it's very weird
The story behind
I didn't know story behind that large negotiation that
What happened
For what I don't know or if you have a group of people could eat if You released 10
I don't I don't know the I have no idea
Fourth Amendment says that I can only really so many balloons
Very weird
The man in this case was Anthony breast
3D prosecutors obviously didn't file a case
Based on that
It would have been literally impossible for them
Proceed with that case and they knew it
They didn't even pursue the case
This is absolutely 100% And
Cop looking for a charge to give someone
Nothing immediately popped up a cop fell back on well you really stupid balloons
As a strategy
Exactly
The important very important variable that Alex is leaving out of this coverage
Intentionally I believe
Alex's intentionally leaving the side of the story because he wants
The angle to be the Environmental Protection laws
Trojan Horse
The last thing he wants is for his audience to consider for a second maybe was actually going on here is that this is maybe an inch
Horse over
Policing of minority
Which is probably a more
Realistic way to look at the story based on the reporting I saw on
That does seem to be what the the cases
I f****** hate
Bummer bummer story
Reality of the story be warped
By someone
McDonald's
Story that everybody's
Still pulls that b******* on where the lady with the cup
The lady with the cup
The hot coffee still that like
Oh you didn't know it was going to be hot
Can you read into it you're like
This is a story about Corporation
F****** over every
It's not a story about a woman who didn't know coffee with
Admit that I do believe
She knew coffee
Okay I will agree with you I will agree with your member looking into it a long time ago but I don't
Speak on it
But I'm going to trust your version
Corporations
Cutting costs wherever and whenever they could to the detriment
And pain of everybody around
And they'd already been warned not to do it
She's absolutely they should have been sued before they
And it's just a few infuriating thing cuz every time you look at this Visa
Like short
And you know like
Sherry
You're not mad at the right person
Yeah
Corporations are people
They are
Alex goes all frantic
The
The guy who gets arrested
Search for balloons
Going to go to prison for 5 Years cuz
Environmental cop
Is a natural transition
And for him to talk about how he got jammed up for
Giving out flyers at sxsw
Caller has a really good question
For him about that
Situation
I haven't heard you reported on
And I'm very interested in them
The number of internal affairs complaints
You and your streak thing that's filed against the various officers and be various departments
It is important to file these even if you don't think you'll get a satisfactory
Because of the very least
You're getting these reports
Record just like it should track equine
Shop by Southwest
So this is
So damn indicative of what's wrong with Alex's approach toward
These supposed tyranny he imagined
He complained that he was a victim of gestapo tactics while he's out trying to give out
The story is now becoming ballast involve not only the actual police trying to intimidate him
But also hired goons threatening
18 which is
Seriously f***** up
To happen if it were
True at all
Alex has an action prove to me that this story is most likely
Because it clearly demonstrates that
He says is the problem
Tyrannical
There's not something he's at all interested
Didn't Sullivan
You want attention out of this he wants to create the appearance that he's having his rights trampled on
Do you want the opportunity
Turn this into a sales
But what he doesn't want is
Uses of an opening to help bring about real change in the system he makes money by railing against
Because that would be bad for business
First they came for my
I lied about it
And screamed about it
Nothing
They came for minorities right
And I lied about it
And screamed about it on the radio and made a lot of money and nothing happens
And then I just made a lot of money and nothing
Because I'm not going to do any
I meant if you're only reason to exist as a business is to scream that out-of-control government and police depression why would you ever
Try to decrease the level of out-of-control government in Felicia fraction
Why would you why would you ever go through the painful and difficult process of advocating for wheelchair
Change in pursuing it through the proper channels when
This creating a fictional version of your own
Struggle and yelling about them much more profitable
How much is excuse that he has too good of a heart to file internal complaints
Howard Lee cop out
If you saw a dollar sign in it he be filing those reports
And honestly him filing internal reports really only works
If he's making all this stuff up would you almost certainly is
Trouble for filing false complaints
Conversely if he's not making it up genuine genuine departmental performance
Completely counter to his agenda
If the police start operating in ways he's all in favor of he'll have no
It's just to me I think it's so damn it
When a guy calls in is like I'd like to ask about like
Defile internal reports trouble
In trouble
Play Stan that's such b******* b*******
It's so against what he's for crack
Back in his Visage
And it just flies past
Like I'm sure most people listening
Consider for a second but like
Oh hold on
This is crazy
This is this really makes
The sex work
S*** is
Going to be number one
And you could make
81 of 10 million
Just even up pause
Somebody trying
To stop traffic I do I agree with you the reason I think
Slightly
Isn't this case Alex has standings
To file these
Complaint department
Yeah and he doesn't take action
More damning
Yeah you're right
There is
Sue the city
You could
Bring about departmental change
In the way that
You feel is in line with
Diffusion Norte
Or even you could make a little money to
Sherpa
Chicken bake motor Shut up
What if Barnes is right in 2013
TV living on an island somewhere
Sagara
Ears billions of dollars disappear Alex need to take over
So this last clip from the 17th
It's not that
Michelle Alex's at complaining
Carac
Things that work
This is true under under hr32
1521 that we all have to be chick
Obamacare
Saraga
First things for
Of course the Affordable Care Act didn't require or pay for people to get
Naturally
However there was like early house version
The Bell that really got Dum Dums on the right all worked up
Particularly ones with preoccupations about the end times
The provisions of the early draft were related
To creating a database for the Department of Health and Human
Human Services of people
Pacemaker
Replacement body
Their reasoning was that if there was a centralized database
Things I can more easily study the efficacy of
Implantable devices
And probably more important
Naked informed
Boomers way more quickly wedding
Recalls
Of medical products like that of this
Which is really important
Crazy
Implantable medical devices one gets
Recalled knowing who you need to get it out of dangerous
It's very the number
People who file complaints
The FDA
Of injuries related in plants
Device is much higher than people realize
Yeah
There are some folks unfortunately
So these are really important
For obvious reasons
However this language was taken out of the phone
Final version of ACA that eventually passed
Through Congress
He was basically just lying about things that doesn't
End up being
Event at buy this one
He has ever read
Even to know that it's not
These databases actually already
BFDI freeze instant
Which is housed under the
The DHHS
Keep the registry of people laugh and plaster
What medical devices
Because without that they'd be unable to appropriately respond to
Complained
Why was obviously benefits to expanding the data available to provide people with better care
This complaint that Alex
Does making is
The real thing
At all it got taken out of the bill Alex's just yelling
Shadows
Is caller discolored paranoid about
I'm picking Alex is like yeah
Yeah
Modeling
So
Do you know which model of pacemaker you have for sure so even if they put out a call Lovey
Replaced
You don't know for sure if that one's yours aren't I would hope that if I had a pacemaker I would know that
I don't know I would be surprised if you did I would hope
There's a ton of
Just logistical
Public Health
Wise up
Nothing like this would be very
Helpful
Important
Save lives
Did you consider that
OKC
I understand where Alex's argument
Is this
We can move on
Is built on like okay so they make it okay for you.
Keep a registry of people who have
Implantable devices in them
Then they're going to just have everybody slippers
Database of people with teeth of course
Bright
It's ridiculous
Paranoia is built on
I get the beginning stages of
People just
We get to the 18th and Alex is going on
The paranoias
We've already heard him say that there's going to be a false flag
No
The Boston bombing is less
It's been a month away right around the corner
But here's the problem was that
His predictions of very
Specific about what's going to happen
Edit not
A bombing in Boston during the
.
It's not that
Billing office Chicago
Ozzy man
Dallas
Cleveland
Chicago
Helicopters flying around
Show a movie of all Anouk in Chicago
Very clear that this is the prediction he's making
Without saying they're going to Nuke Chicago
Specifically because he knows that
And it's a chip prediction
Is real shotty
So what does happen you going to take credit for predicting it but if you look at the actual prediction
First of all Cleveland sent like a
The Chicago it's not on his radar.
He's talking about nukes
It's
It's not your Main Avenue of research for this
That was
Does the CFR like to brag
The Council on Foreign Relations
Bragging about
Can I be honest with you
I didn't think that was something worth looking into
I feel like people's definition of bracken might be different and I felt like we could get in the weeds
Pretty quickly
Also
Ecfr membership Rollies
Gigantic
Tons of this business owner
Cabela's golf scores all the time
Chicago Chicago
So I'll talk more about this
Yes here it is
Chicago
Oops
The CFR really bragged about that one
So
I mean you got really specific
Predict
Going on
It's gradually becoming more refined
923 Chicago
And I guess Alex is way around it
Once the Boston bombing does
Well they heard me say that they were going to Nuke
Chicago that's how you would get around to it
But I don't text
Naturally The Playbook that he is outline for the
Globalist to do after he's correct
Is the Playbook
Follows after
Incorrect
Yes
So the rest of this episode 18
If it's not
Cathy Cypress Bank
Situation
I don't
It's so standard
Alex Financial
Exactly the same
And
I don't
Are the people in Cypress
People around the world are dealing with financial crises
Don't mean to be insensitive about that but Alex
Version of it is not something
I'm particularly interested
So we jump to the 19th
Edit begins with an hour-long yelling about Obama being the devil
Okay it's alright
Wow
It's just
Constant
Obama
I don't hurt time
Believing that you can
It's tough It's really tough
But really listened to the whole hour
Stupid commercials
I would make it through 50 minutes
Moorhead
I think during it I just I did go a couple times
I did
The world
Pretty Goods
Glimpse in his world
I guess
Now I'm confused
Do you think he's
Actually read
The hobbes's Leviathan
No there's no way right
I don't think so
I think you seen it referenced unlike Patriot vlogs
Okay
I think most of his information
Through those doors
I information that traces back
To these groups like the Jews for the preservation of firearms ownership
Forgot owners for America
There's so much
Stop that like
We getting second
Third hand
Pretending
He's really just read skousen capitalist
If he gives himself credit for reading the original thing as opposed to
Or even jumpy Holdren's ecoscience
Yeah he claims he's read that there is no chance you've read that
No textbook
It's a textbook yeah he's read the little excerpts that are posted on that out
Their weapon attack the fluoride in the water and lava blocks
Though he's never read la vie
I'm positive it's just fun for me whenever all of a sudden
He uses some
Something like that
Is it correctly or you're like
Hey it's somebody else had to avoid another word for the devil
The term for the devil
That's the one I like
I love the other one
Alex
At this point
Because the devil
The skinny one
Just fun
Because of this Cypress
Financial
Involved
Money and Bank
Is suspicious
Yeah yeah
Around this time
Also there was
Chase Bank
Glitch that happened with their internal systems
That made some users
Accounts show a zero balance
It was resolved fairly quickly
They has been pretty
Consistent
Understatement that it wasn't
It was a malfunctioning
Internal algorithms are or whatever
Yeah I don't see any evidence
That it was a hack or anything the fairies
Astronomy
Clearing out People's Bank account
Alex
Something up
There is a local news story
Where they interviewed somebody
About
This Chase Bank
Glitch
A caller calls in
Talk about house that was the
Suspicious
This is very
Important
What's your take on this
Definitely
The fact that they did that thing with Chase and if you notice the guy in the clip said
He had faith that the government would step in
In case it was something serious
Amazing
So Alex has decided this guy who said that I believe the government will intervene
Literally
Yeah so this guy who's
In this
Local news interview Alex has decided as an actor
This is a
Massive important job
Yeah cuz it opens up the door
To be like wow
If they're using actors to shape the public opinion on
How far are we away from
We're we're ending up at night
His hit this was a
Respect
Secular example of
Yes anding turned
New Prius
Y'all y'all figured out the universe
Like that
That is such a
Coked-up like
Yeah I thought it was really weird
They're all actors
You made up this whole story about directing your
I highly doubt it
No I think it I think it's an interesting thought that he arrived on because of the colors
Suspicion in Maui
He's adding a lot of little bushes
To increase the background of this pic
You know what they're like it's
It's really interests
That's why I think it's important to point out that the Cypress
Situation is happening
Construction
How is financial lies are always the same and it's all
Hispanic
Buy gold
We've got a 300 up
I think it's important
Because it does live in the background of what's making him
Suspicious about the
Situation
And those
Efficient
Glitch make him suspicious of the news report about it
I don't know if that's an entirely what's motivating him to say that this guy in the
News story about the chase glitches an actor but it's a piece of
Part of the feedback loop
If he's watching all of the
All of these papers
Bullshiter
Coming about
Sandy Hook being staged in
Thanks
Staged and fake is in his mind all the time
Constantly so
If he gets something like this this is a perfect opportunity for his brain to go like
It's fake let's jump on it first exactly the way you was trying to
Cover shooting
Yes
Do you know what he was trying to be like
His own
This is an actor thing
Have a stake in the market
Unrelated
But still very lucrative
Kickbacks
Places maybe get some SEO
I think it's pretty interesting
Soylent
His assertion that this guy in the news report was probably an actor I think probably
The lamest way possible
Driver show
Ask him questions Cash Cab
Immediately
Everybody else
2013 comedies
Scab is an example of why
The news interview was intact
Bailey
Missouri back before I move to
Chicago I did
I don't I didn't want I didn't spend much time with him but he was nice and I think he had a bit about birds that I thought was bad
Yes
A number of people who are on the Cash Cab as contestants are also comedian
Aspiring actors
That is normal calls into your morning radio shows
Real people dab
I think that it's part of the show business at
I honestly think
If you're running a show like Cash Cab
Doing it any other way is
Impossible
The idea of
Having a completely unknown variable get in
A very
Controlled
Space where you're running again
It's
So much money on shooting
Like
Issues of people needing to fill out tax forms in
If you just pick people up off the street
Like you can't
Have them fill out the paperwork after runaway you can pay them just in cash
Like I do
I don't want to get into it
If you think reality TV it 100% real then blood get the
A produced
Keisha like
Something
If he's using that as an example of like every
Interviewee
A local news could be fake
It's it's it's
I don't use the word slippery slope it's just stupid allow your brain to
Start thinking about
Because it opens up
The Pyro diminished
Credulity
Required
And even then even within your b*******
Cuz now you're getting people
You got to pull out a cat
Casting call or you have actors
Tugonon
On retainer
Get somebody in the production crew to walk in front me like I was a baby I'm fine with it
This was
Top
Big
Because it is a departure in
Is narrative
And then he starts talking about it a little bit more interview
And
He
Expensive about this subject
Factor
Do territory that I have not heard before
This is very very very very suspicious
Deal
Found instances of movie actors
About how they survived who just so happened to be in the Aurora shooting
Moderate
I don't think it was Lee major
Never up to this point if there were crisis actor
Using your aura
He said that James Holmes of the Mind Control killer and all that s*** we've gone over in detail already but I've not heard him
Accusation that are actors
The departure
And his rhetoric
I tried to trace down the particular people he's talking about but I can't really find any
Good resources
About what's going on here
And even if I could I feel like naming the people he's accusing being actors does more harm than good at the
This point even if it's in service of deacon
Constructing is why it was weird whenever they
George Clooney interview
It was weird
There is a possibility that someone who was
In the theatre was also an actor
In that movie
But I think if I had to guess based on the distinguish
Ocean characteristics Alex provide
I think I kind of know who he's talking
Sing about
There's one African-American guy who posted a video on YouTube describing his experience being a
In the theater when the
Shooting happen
And this guy was immediately attacked by conspiracy theorist is being
I assume that this is one of the people that Alex is talking about since he fits Alex's
Description
There's no evidence whatsoever outside of unfounded accusations on conspiracy message board
The second person Isis
Suspect is a Hispanic man who was interviewed on Good Morning America after
The shooting
He survived the shooting and described his experiences
Stipulating a lot while being interviewed
Would you like to be receipts Lutz online
He was an actor
I really don't think people understand how adrenaline can really f*** with you and high-pressure
Situation
Like if anybody thinks that talking with your hands a lot is a strange behavior for someone who's being interviewed on National Television for the
The first time
I really think that they've never tried public speaker
I would predict that if they had to get up in front of a room is like 100 people
And say something
Bachelor
Possibly emotionally resonant
They would find their delivery might not be totally natural or casual either
That's as closely fit Alex's description but he's another person who survived the Aurora shooting who's a
Accused of being an actor
I've gone through a bit of this stuff
Digging around
Literally nothing
Topeka
Compelling evidence
Nothing rises above the level of an
Insinuation
And yet here we have Alex Jones
Reporting on his show that there were crazy
At the Aurora shooting
I think of his highlights and under-recognized aspect of Alberta
Is propaganda
He needs
To use crutches
You just can't say that the victims of Sandy
Hooker actor
Because
Parents
He knows that the accusations are based in reality
That level of b*******
Human level of Cruelty
In order to justify that leap he needs her to be another event where it's at
The crisis actors
Reusable shooting
Unless it's sensible to assume that they might have been
Sandy Hook as well
We saw him do this from the beginning with sand
Hook but surrounding the question of whether or not it was a false
Flag
He justified arguing that the globalist probably did say
Sandy Hook
Rahsaan constantly use that as his
He did that one that they did that it's likely they did this
He established to normalize that rhetoric and now it's perfectly acceptable
For him to apply that's
Thing is that he hasn't established in the past that actors were used in Aurora
That's new
He's trying to rewrite the narrative about Aurora to include that element in order to justify saying
The director is
Sandy Hook shooting
Which I feel he's
Very close
Yeah
This is
This is important
Like these are
Trends that are happening
And this is not
Like because we haven't listened
All these episodes
Would you say cuz to me this sounds like outside in
Changing
Yeah if that's the problem that's what it sounds like to me it sounds to me like he's
Buying his own
Conspiracy b******* from elsewhere
You know what I'm saying
Internal right
A couple of days ago I
Right now he
Co-opting yeah it's an essential limitation of how we
Can
Study Island
It in that
We can see the stuff on his show
And we can see okay there's a change
Sitting here but it doesn't necessarily allow us unless he says on his show what he's doing
Can't really Noah
Cause
This possibly behind this
And I think that's a limitation that it is appropriate for us to own up to
That
Said
He gets drunk and watches YouTube a lot
Possible
In the present day
Alex
Talking about the the crisis actor stuff
As it relates to
Sandy Hook
He will say the people like James
Tracy and Wolfgang halbig
Deemed credible
James Tracey was on the show Once
Paul Joseph Watson
Alex has not talked to him on the show
Not shown up
At all
Steve pieczenik even hasn't shown up on Alex's show
There don't appear
YouTube Vianney
Influences
Outside of Alex's own mine
Yeah on his
This road
It seems entirely organic
If you are listening to his show
Those guys as being
People who gave him
It's entirely possible where
Considering that
Giving it to him
As opposed to him just watching some
I think they were on 100%
Some bad information
It could be him taking it from watching their s***
That is false
The other possibility
Is
That there are exchanges going on
Through email
And that's one of the things that I think is really
Important about the Sandy Hook lawsuits
That are happening
Is some of that key
Can come to light
Through discovery
The parrots
People suing Alex
I have requested
I think that a lot of it information
Is best
Served being investigated
And that
Contact information is available I am going
Chop it all up
So simple as that
A quick
Find search of
Hey how do you want to lie about Sandy Hook
Slugga themes
It's very possible
Seems very
Possible plausible
I have nothing
To back it up,
Concretely
Themes
It doesn't seem that crazy to assume that something is going on
At this point
Because this is a massive
Massive change
Right I don't know if like
The day of
The
Aurora shooting
Alex said there were actors
But I'd listen to Mom
Of his show
And it is not
He has ever
Applied
In that
It's been the other stuff the DARPA right
All all the other the Mind controls Antonio Airforce doctor notebook
Ryan rental
Now been on
Conspiracies
Hasn't
So why do you have that
You have the
The Chase
Interview is now an act
You're running into a good bit of
That
Becoming a
Rhetoric
Pushed
It feels like an intentional
Push here on this March 9th
Episode
I don't know what to make of it but I guess we'll see
At the same time it could just be
Alex
Could be he was watching a movie
A week ago where there were
What movie is this
Pick a pick a false flag
Okay
But it goes through the end
Fixated
Sprain
Fazos
Everything is
But I don't think so
It feels much more intense
I don't know how much
The planned editorial decision
As much as the day is like well
Moving in
Misdirection
I don't know I don't know we'll see how it develops
Episode Alex has an interview with someone who
We've never heard
From
Before
The guy named Cody Wilson
And has really excited about
Because he is
On the Forefront of 3D printing
Particularly in the area of printing gun
Okay well there was there's the bad
He is a guy who
To tell you is an anarchy
I believe that the best way to
To deteriorate
Power of the state
Is 2
To make it so everybody
Can have gun
He even acknowledges how
So incredibly f***** up this would be
Because you have completely
Undetectable
It doesn't seem to care too much about that it's like he's into chaos
Blueprints online
Infrared
Also stuff
Discussing
Sing house
Be ubiquitous
Sure that will be the solution
To all the world's problems
Especially with the gun part since we have a printable firearm
And this is why
This is important no one can take those things
They're online forever
I don't know
Should be thrilled of Anarchy
I really think
He's
A supervillain
I'm really loving everything you're doing so far
Yeah
He just falls in love with
This dude on this episode
Cody Wilson
Wilson has been working with 3D printing and unable to print a functional gun
Which he was doing to demonstrate the gun laws are pointless
Is it now or undetectable gun
Pretty much everywhere
There be no point in the state
Trying to control their flow
Andros Island
Fantasy nightmare of everyone walking around armed to the teeth
You coming to reality
This is the Phantom
If they're put in for
He says as much in the interview and he's against
The state completely which Alex should not be on board with
Everything he loves about the quote-unquote West
Completely disappear
But Cody super indigent
Then maybe the solution to gun regulation
Alex just skips over
That part
It's probably worth mentioning that in 2017 Cody well say Wilson would go on to launch the patreon alternative
Which was specifically designed to be a place where white supremacist and kicked off patreon
Because of his platform Richard Spencer was able to pull in a monthly income
And Andrew Anglin of the daily Stormer was able to raise his income by about $8,000 a month
A mad that
Podcaster in audiobook
Media because the Gorillaz
Spectacular rankings of top earners from their early time and
Existence
Why it's denoted Justin white supremacist organization identity evropa number 9 is
The guy who hosted the show fash the nation
You would probably guess it is the worst David Letterman top 10 in
Number 13 is Christopher Cantwell the crying Nazi from the unite the right rally
Number 14 is.
The founder of Stormfront
Looking through the list I really don't
Know if you can
Can find anyone with a razor
Fascist propaganda
Polly tied to white supremacy
Violence in
Last few years
I make no mistake
Initially hatreon was a service that
Creators could only set up accounts for buy-in
Cody Wilson
Specifically
Chose these
Patreon sold itself as the censorship free version of patreon
You can easily see what that means in practice
In concept you're imagining that it'll be a place where the free exchange of ideas
Can take place and everybody could be
Be themselves
Yep and reality to send up at the place where White
Confound their operation
Cody Wilson gets to take his
Cut off the top
Naturally because this is just
Literally a conduit for people to fund hatefi
Beach Pizza terminated their involved
But with the site is payment processor
There weren't any other option
Life for them to try cuz I'm place
Extra
PayPal it already
He kicked all these other costs
List all part of that point
You see all these right-wing guys
Iran has a good model of
A little off the top
It's not that hard for me to Cota website
B o of course
It's a good graft if you are willing to just make money off funding
Advantage storage
Good morning
For being a psychopath grift
Also in December 2018 Cody Wilson was indicted by the state of Texas
And indecency with a child by exposure
Get medicine
10 year old girl on a sugar daddy website
Very illegal
That's the most illegal
What do you sound out the police were looking into me allegedly fled to Taiwan but was ultimately returned back to the
I'd state
His defense argued that the child had lied about her age and Austin Police Commander said quote
Detectives have interviewed and spoken with his victim and then their opinion of someone mistakes her age
She's younger not older than
These are all that she is this gross
Even if she had misled Cody about her age
Texas law requires the adult
To confirm that someone is above the age of
You can set and put to no legal burden on a child victim
Which I think is probably the best way for
Listen to operate as the alternate yeah that would be a really good way
So Cody ended up leading down ascend
But I was still sentence
27 years probation and had to register as a sex offender
He's not allowed to be alone with minors
Nana possible poetic irony
He's not allowed to own firearm
Anymore
So these are the sorts of people
Who's got
Hanging around
Kind of
About Cody Welch
Alex Jones
This clip takes on a
Slightly
Technology
This is from
The old way of thinking
Relishing in this idea that people think they're f*****-up dangerous people
It's one of those things like you look back at this
6 years in the past
And you have to ask the question I would love to like show that would be like
Maybe everyone was right
Absolutely
Whatever
Together in the
Jerking each other off for being
Soda
That's cuz you're not
You're living this fantasy where we like
Cody Wilson is living this weird
Super villain fan
Like he's living like if I make guns available for everyone that all power is meaningless
Is doing that all thing
So powerful in the
Realm or whatever it is
Conforth been like
You're great. You're a great because we're both so
Scary
Powerful
I'm a threat to the system
Translate more to I'm a threat to peace
Because I was not treated as one when I was nine or whatever the f***
Psychology it is
He also is a big booster of Bitcoin
And he's
Specifically trying to promote bitcoin-based
I assume he got very very very rich
I mean I bet he was pretty rich to begin with
He had a lot of people interested in the
Like it cuz a month
2 months after this
He does make you
Huge Splash by
Having a 3D printed
I recall almost
And so like there were a bunch of people funding
With with capital
Make a lot of money
But in this club by he's trying to promote bitcoin-based
Coinbase
Exactly
Whatever it is Alex is always very suspicious about
It's interesting the way you suspicious about it
It's just one of the easiest way to buy and sell Bitcoin and accessible
People that think like him people with that sounds fun mentality corporations
Companies like coins
Self
Well I mean
So
Itsfunneh do your Alex still worried about Peter Thiel back in 2013
He suspicious about Bitcoin as a free and open Marketplace
The only real specific he gives him his interviews that he believes Peter Tila
Involved
Is a bit of a red flag
In October 26th New York Times reported the team donated $1000000 to Trump's presidential campaign
And not surprisingly wasn't important advisor
After the election
By that point in continuing to the present Alex has been a strong
People advocate
Which is also
Covert
I don't think it'll happen to buy 2013
Cuz the only thing I recall, in lawsuit
This point is the first
Founder of Facebook
Cease and desist you any journalistic outlet that
Said his name
Haha
Jennifer Alex
Like those trifecta
Being
Facebook
Evil global
Alex's on that tip
I'm not sure
I'm not sure what he hate
Puppy tortilla palantir is still Bowl
Yvette's
Vets around
Right I don't know exactly Alex's
But right
Fuckum
And
What something really good
Because in 2015 when we were looking at that. Of time where Alex
Makes peace with
And besides just boarded
It was in the back
Did we discover
Was that Alex
Love Rush
Right
There
Was
Perhaps some
Suspicion or some
Feelings
When we initially started looking at it that these two things were related and so
As we learned more
Love Putin and Russia
Almost entirely disconnected
Did from his path
Supporting Trump
Yeah it just existed already before
He started as opposed to drop Ricky wheeler you tomorrow
Cunningham loving Russia
Absolutely
Indication
Of
Russo positive
Worldview
Taking Russia's line
On
Certain geopolitical issues
To question about who's is correct
What is interest
Is that in twenty
Pictures of Alex's
Positive
Russia
Angle was
That Putin kicked out the oligarch
And the poop
Putin is trying to create this wonderful Christian free-market whatever
Complete and total coincidence that that journalist died
State was murdered on the same day
Leave out of sight
Alex's video
Kicked out the oligarchs
That's one of the big
This is why
You love
Supports him
So he understands but they didn't kick out the oligarch
In 2013 no not in 2013
I don't I don't that's not even Alex's angle in 2050
Alright Alex
Interesting I wonder what
I wondered what
Between 2013
I wonder if it has anything
Things to do with Siri
I do I do wonder that
I don't believe so that was a
Except for I guess going on max
Kaiser show
I'm not sure Wilson
Because that's
Pocket incongruous
As hell yeah that's strange
Look at this clip in just for our our our dear friend Sonia
I think she will enjoy
Dumb clip
But
Hours of the north-south mountain
Europe
North America
Good stuff
We love it
Western Hemisphere
That's how you say those or something
Intersection of Alex Mack
A woman whose
Supported Obama
Gross Elliman
Bring it in I don't know why I'm
Just point out these
Shift
He's going to destroy
That is going to look
You will kill for Obama
Weather out there
Wow
Alex has many many times said that he would die for
It's
Ridiculous absolutely right
He's so smart about how people will get
Turned into an authoritarian Empire
Babe
Like almost
Gleefully
Joining it
I would be critical of anybody who says
They would die for their chosen political leader
Critical of Alexandra
Sentiment
The difference between me and Alex is Alex is not critical of his own sentiment of I would die for from
That is a problem
Very weird
Very clear that she's being
Will probably yeah or
Everybody's having it to Alex right now
Probably exaggerating
Of context
It's very
We're back to the chase glitch
Now Alex is covering that you're on the 20th
Amanda
Smells
People couldn't
This is based on
Conversations you probably never had with it people
Send one time. They said that that would probably never happen
Alex is creating this
Conspiracy surrounding this Chase glitch
In service of reinforcing
I guess
What probably is more primary is
Play become more primary
Is the idea that this guy
TV interview was an actor who was there too
Describe people from thinking it was any kind of nefarious
A map
Interesting
Incredibly impossible to hide ever
Conspiracy though that idea that
Some Bank like Chase
Wood
In a second
Flash second
Take all this money from all these
Invest it instantly
See the stock rise by one penny
And then
It take it all out after selling all those shares
And putting all of that money back
Into your
So they would make money and you wouldn't even notice cuz it all happens in a
That's a fun
Conspiracy theory that could be instantly and easily found out and would be the most illegal possible thing
That could ever f******
Alex not understand
It's work already
It's Melissa
So stupid
If you don't work all she is the lady who is super into agenda
Corrupt local meetings
Any kind of
Environmentalism any kind of Civic planning
Building Park
As being part of
Their interview is just exactly the
Same as the last time we talked about her it's
Not worth getting in
Into again
Except for this
Did she say
That Alex doesn't
Australia
It's terrible people are really dealing with it
Alex doesn't seem to be like
That's the sort of thing that should be
Like
Why would you go on that show they are explicitly
White supremacist
White nationalist show
Throws Good Morning America
Like we're in a very safe space
Speak freely Rosa
How old is
Just be like oh yeah I was also on this f****** show that is largely about identity
And it's cool
21 is a global problem
Yep great
Red Rosa
Hanover
Few days
Alex incorporate ideas of this
TV interview being an actor
We seen him
Save it some of the survivors and victims
The Aurora shooting where actors
Is
A
Three is a pattern
Here is the third
Directions
We should all that's US National Guard
Social Security authorized private security
Hung up on
Security number
I just called
Doesn't look concerned that
Reporter
22nd I apologize and clarify Alex and Mike Adams hosted
And he's coming in with this narrative
About G20
Psyop
Yeah
I don't believe Alex's story about how he got this in
Information for
Mainly that he always lies right
That is just
Unbelievable chain of events
You got your answer
Alex doesn't ever do investigative work
So the idea that you would
Track down other phone numbers
Is laughing
But like I said I'm trying to be pretty clear about the
I'm seeing a trend developing of Alex
Incorporating crisis actors it was narrative has not
Up till this point
I've been listening to every single minute of his show
I can say with no hesitation that this is not normal
We've already seen Alex at actors because
Conspiracy about the Aurora shooting
And now people arrested at the 2009 G20 meeting in Pittsburgh where actors engaged
Asiop run by the
Presumably at the behest of globalist
So they could gauge how the media would respond to
Let's leave aside for a moment how stupid this is
If you believe as Alex does that the globalist already
Control the media
What's more important is how Alex is missing out on a real in
Instance of State oppression
In service of using it
How to create a different
Pharisee
Auto rebates
Level its analysis best interest
The delegitimize
The G20 protests
He wants to yell about the G20 but the people who are actually protesting never largely anti
A capitalist
People who are willing to put their bodies on the line or not people who think three people voted in the Federal Reserve it takes
The people who want to dismantle the power of capital
That's a threat to the power struck
It's also a threat to Allie
So course you would have propaganda narrative
In order to delegitimize
Census of
That said even though it makes sense for him to undercut
Decapolis protest
I've never heard of argue this people arrested
G20 meeting
Absolutely
We're not
The specific arrest Alex's talking about was the subject of his videos at
2009 viral
It was a video of a car pulling up on protesters camo coming out and grabbing a guy and tossing them into
Immediately the internet went wild the theories of
That the arrest was fake because we Campbell outfits the men were wearing
They were like a different form of
Camos and National
Sure
What's another
A comet
That's just not part of the Infowars journalism
In process
I can count on one hand the number of times I believe they may have sent someone an email to check on a story
What Alex is probably referring to as the boilerplate response that the information center
Journalist inquiring about the arrest
Found published verbatim on both
Mediaite
10 Raw Story
Jules involved 2409 arrest which has appeared online
Enforcement officers from a multi-agency
Tactical response
It's Not Unusual for tactical team members to
Wear camouflage
The type of fatigue fatigue the officers wear designates their unit affiliate
This is pretty close to what Alex is saying the Army told so I'm going to assume he probably just read this response inside
Reached out
To them himself knowing that the response
If you did reach out to its
2 safe
They reach out to him
Sure
These weren't military members
Despite their camo they were allegedly
Observe the individual
And decided to intervene the way they did do to the quote hostile nature of the
Krowd
I think that's all kind of b*******
And the rest absolutely
I would describe is overkill in the methods
They're using
But Alex doesn't help the actual problem
To file internal complaints
Wednesday is the victim
A police over-reach dozen
And help the problem
Right
Because he wants
He wants
Terrorist
Policing
The largest year for our purposes though is that this
Was a real rat
Zero evidence
Support his claim that he was an actor who was arrested
It is part of a psyop
That's a completely unfounded belief he's decided to presentist
And I believe it's part of a growing pattern
More and more things are being called fake and alleged to be evolving Act
This is the third example in a week
Weeks worth of Alex
Does program
And I don't think it means nothing
It's important to note to like I mentioned earlier that Alex has not had Wolfgang halbig on his show up to this point
He's at James Tracy on but Alex didn't even talk to
This like if this is in fact where we jump off the hook actors narrative
Alex
Really make it
Compelling argument
You heard both sides
He's doing this him
Spell fright
Is there something behind
They convince them of that and it's Wolfgang halbig
He hasn't demonstrated that in any way
I don't know I
Because originally I was thinking that it
It was some sort of
Outside
Influence
But then
Now to put this in there for
No reason real
Like there's no point in throwing other than you giving him
Possible credit for
Setting the groundwork for being able to call
A completely
But it also sounds like
Call whenever he was just having that
That fun like
Free associative like all the sudden yeah these guys are actors to throw that in there
Excited to call everything
So smart you figured out
Fake and all this
It does feel that way and on some level
A bit of that could
Possibly be
Explained by
When he had James Tracy on
A big part of it
Was a recognition that there was 10 million views of this video that I put out there was a big Market
Right that was
Recalling things
Exactly
I don't think it's unreasonable to look at it as
In the intervening month or so they've seen that
Hasn't gone away
Yeah this is a pretty lucrative fertile
Space
Conspiracy
Growing
So I think it it's it's a
Possibility
When is the case
But it is a possibility
Is that there is Market viability in Colorado
Fake
And Alex
Is allowing himself to dip into that
Right that's
Another possibility is Alex is aware that he is working
Towards
Sandy Hook
Yeah and the day it was all actors
Because we do know that that is where he
Right and if he knows that that's the conclusion you're getting to
It makes sense
To build up to that
Have the have the groundwork laid
Incorporating it into
These other
Thing
Pretty consistent
We coming up
Accusations of things involving Act
It doesn't
Seem
Organic
Right
It did it could be explained by your
Theory that he got drunk and watched YouTube
And it's like hey it's fun to call Diggs actress
I admit that that's a possibility that's not a low possibility
Mine
Suspicions are also possibility
Absolute
Possible explanation
Oceans 41
But I'm looking at it and I I can't escape the conclusion that it is happy
Yeah I know absolutely
I'm going to go with money
Ivory
Until proven otherwise I'm going to go with some sort of
And again this comes down to the limitation of looking at it the way we do
Is it I can tell you that there is something going on
Right with the available information that I have I can't tell you
Exactly how it plays out yet
And I also may never be able to tell you the exact
I give you the possibilities
But I don't know outside of Alex
Confessing
This lawsuit revealing emails that showed machinations
Deceived
I'm not sure that I would ever be able to give you the Y
Frustrating
This does not appear to me
From my time studying Alex Jones to be a coincidence
Now we got it appears to be
Weather
Conscious
Orkin
Petition to incorporate
Crisis actors
Do a bunch of stuff
I think
I don't think it's possible for us ever to
To know because I don't
Anyway that Alex
Concrete
Concrete Lino's
Squidward eats
Cuz it's not like we could do an interview with Alex like
20 years
When he's not on the air and he's got nothing to lose
We can't trust a thing he says cuz there's no way that he lay remember it or be
Bother to tell
Some insightful person
And who used to work at Infowars
If breeds
From their non-disclosure agreement we could
Explain
The Dynamics
But would have to be a third party
Before sure
Be there for
It would I think it requires
Those
What about her email said
So because Alex
Is he's getting pretty
Extreme I mean he's already yelled about Obama's
The devil for an hour
Troubling if proven
Right
He is building up this idea that
This is
An existential battle
He wants his audience
Understand
Is
That if they lose it's all over
If they win then it
This is how he's
The function of rhetoric like that is in order to
To justify
Success
On your side
If you presented as an ex
Substantial battle where if we lose we lose everything
Advair
For it all
They're using actors to create this completely fictional reality in order to
Brainwash people
If they're going for it all we're going for it all
And that is not good
Because you're creating a fictional version of what the enemy is doing in order to justify these very real things that you are doing
The enemy is going to commit war crimes we have no choice but to fight them on their level
If they're going to burn our farms and couldn't commit to Total War
Then we have to burn their farms in theirs
Grimes
You know it is
Somewhat
Relevant
Because
As we discussed
The beginning of this episode
Alex is making predictions about what the globalist are going to do
This false flag that they're going today
Pull-off
What's the prediction
Can you do
So it's all very consist
It's a repetition of the blame the Patriot
He's listed the cities but
Are the target
Chicago primarily
Whether or not
He says there's going to be a false flag all the time
So
When there is an actual terrorist attack
As the Boston bombing
It doesn't
Lend him any more credibility
He said there was something coming
Especially when you look back
Can feel like
Specifically
Predicting
Something
Completely different
So going to be another school shooting
That's not
Local news
Would give anything
Sing for that kind of
Throw to break
Like they have to be like
Is there something in your food
Still not as bad as Alex
We'll see you in five pretty distracted
Bad so Alex
Like
There's been a lot of stuff in this episode
Like I think we're seeing this tent
C towards actor narrative
I think Alex is prediction of a nuke in Chicago is pretty important because
He's going to
Predicted the Boston bombing when it happens
I see clearly is not
Of course
LOL that's pretty important
What is about to happen is not
But I think it's
Pretty
Alex has decided
That
Coyotes
Are very picky
Not not people who smuggle people know
You know what's fun
Not for one moment did I think it was anything other than literally coyotes Alex believes that there
Coyote murder happening
Purely coyotes
People are being killed by Coyotes no
He says they're being eaten
By Coyotes
And he believes
That the globalists are trying
Train people to be attacked by coyote
By watching horror movies
Because in horror movies like in the Jason movie you know the character will run away and then trip and fall
No.
She's going to trip and fall
That's just cruel
So Alex believes that this program
People coyote
The greatest
Plan the globalist to have ever come up with
This is
Amazing
Alex's
Really
Cigarettes playing now
Rawlings fall down
Coyotes coming in in in
This is
Ridiculous
First of all I don't know if anybody watches a horror movie and thinks that the person who's being killed by Jason is having a great time
First things first
Alright you're good you're good dude
Let me make a
Real clear
People that is not a big problem
In the United States really want to believe you Dan interactions released
2017 of the phenomenon of humans being attacked by Coyotes
70 and 2015 I assume it is 100%
Shorter women
Between 1977 and 2015 there were 360
7 instances of humans being attacked by coyote
And when you eliminate rabies as a variable because any rabid animals going to text
AC3 the follow
Coyotes generally attack when they're corner
With the elimination of wildlands where they can roam free their environments that are foreign
Causing some disrupt
They have the behavioral plasticity to live in urban environments
What causes
The vast majority of attacks occurred in California
Due to Natural coyote population
The text also seem to follow a pattern where they increased around the times when
Coyotes would be either pregnant or nursing their pups
Position of foods
This isn't to say that they were attacking humans
But that over time they've lost their fear of humans
They've also begun to associate humans
With food
Environment that humans live in or resource-rich environment
Think of what camp
When you start to think about that it's
See how the very basic Association could be babe
Do the presence of humans in the availability of food
It's theorized that this Association has been made by the coyote population
Exist in more urban areas
And many of the attacks we've seen
Open out of food
They believe that attacking you
Women's up will open up
Food resource
F*** you I used to live here killed everybody
Trying to live here and you're still fighting me
Albeit
Define the phenomenon of wild animals becoming the living room
Generally when things like rabies aren't in play
Habituated and don'ts
The threat they mostly don't attack people without a reason
Like being cornered or if there's a drop-off in available food
Often as precipitated by a decreasing in the population of a species
Their prey
It's a byproduct of the interconnect
Something that we are apart of as much as Alex my one
Pretend otherwise
Also only to the 360
B7 coyote interaction
Support life
When was back in 1980
The victim was a three-year-old child
Which is incredibly tragic
But I can't guarantee that the child did not watch horror movies and then decide running away from
The coyote would be fun
44 horror movie
Three-year-old watches
I don't I don't
That it's
Dubious to suggest
The other instance was in 2009 Jose 19 year old folk singer
Who is killed by Coyotes in Nova Scotia
So that wasn't even in the United
Again this is a real tragic situation
And I'm not minimizing it at all but experts discuss the situation
The most likely situation
That you was hiking alone
And probably encountered a group of coyotes
And that they were likely protecting a deer they
Whatever the specific
Details for situation doesn't mean
Alex's b*******
Either and coyotes didn't
People came to her Aid
I'm scared off the coyotes called for help and then she
She died from her injuries At the Hop
I noticed
Might seem like a minor weird thing to focus on
But I think it's a really good example of how
Authoritatively Alex
Speaks
Tuxedos in.
Sing about
This is complete b*******
And yet he's delivering this bitumen
Information
Study the topic in depth
It's important to highlight these examples sometimes
Because they illustrate would have
Con man
Self-reflection
He's capable of
He just Rambles rants about Notions and things he's making up
Feel-Rite
70% them as if they're well-researched fat
Would you recognize the
Does this about coyotes
Is eating people regularly because the globalist have trained him not to
To fight back
It opens the door to recognizing that he does this about everything
He's never read a study on coyote attack
Like he's never read
Everything is b*******
And coyote
Murder eating people
Is such a good doorway into understanding
Swing
That's just such a swing for the fences Urban cities in America
There's
Zerorez
Cuz he's already f****** crazy
That anybody is going to
Call him out on his coyote bulshit
Some
Freak happenstance he's right about the
The coyote murders
Situation
He's the most brilliant man in the world
He's not the most brilliant man in the world
It just so people don't think that I'm just taking a little clip of this
He's actually saying that coyotes are killing
People
Here's some more
I looked through instances of coyote attacks
None of the none of the stories I could find mirror this in anyway
Bloopers of the right
Easter lunch with two coyotes
The ability to switch between coyotes
It's a different way so she's just eating their lunch
Highly populated area
Can get there cuz there's so many people missing her
Eaten by two coyotes bystander coyote
Add stuff
Anime
This is
Ludacris
Play
Native American
Restarting the train
What's up
So
So he's
He's defending wolves killing people
Because he's putting the onus upon you
The person getting eaten by the wolf
I don't know I'm with Wolves
Is very similar to
Situation with coyote
His worldview and his worldview are now roving packs of
Bucking Warriors
Coming out to murder helpless innocent women on their lunch break
In the dead of winter
He is Rehabilitation
Beautiful
Yeah it's unfair it's unfair to both animals really I mean
The target of real maligned perception
Of them based on
Perception
There there
Predators
And woke up.
Really many
I think I could find two examples
Again
Confirm people who have been killed
By wolves
In North America
Coyotes
Definitely for coyote
But then with Wolves
I could find to most of the reasons I can find
Only had two examples
Native American
Sure
Leaving the Wolves decide what we have here when you really get down to it is Alex trying to make his audience scared about it
Completely made up thing
Which is the famous plague of women being eaten by Coyotes
And then trying to make them
Scared about how the globalist
Trains
Unable to
Defend themselves
For being eaten by the coyote
Really really going to have to stop here are we
Ultimately it's all made up
But that's not what this is
Is about
Now that we've gotten to the end of this rant
See Clearly this was never about the fake woman being eaten by Coyotes
It's about I was yelling at his audience about how big
And strong of a boy
He's not afraid of coyotes
After that I guess I applaud him
Have time for his show
But he's making stuff up and all that leads to is I'm strong and brave I'm so powerful
Never fall down in the face of
Coyote
Great.
That's
That's the mark of a true leader
I mean if you fall into that that's the only thing that I need to
I would say that it's ironic that it's begin this episode Alex
Accusing to see how far
The democratic debate
F*** no
Throw a coyote in there whoever stands their ground new president
Done good
From the 22nd
And against Alex predicting
This upcoming
False flag terrorism
He names multiple cities
April talks very specifically
And
Pay close attention
None of this has to do anything with us
Atomic weapon in Chicago
Coupons for Target
Chicago Cleveland Denver
Places like that
What About Bob
Was the Sears Tower
Is a nice man
Coyotes are on a rampage
Do coyotes are on Earth
Yeah I bet he's very specifically there is you know how Alex talk what he saying is they're going to Nuke
The Willis Tower
Login Duke Sears Tower
So his production issue
None of them were Boston
Austin
Yeah I guess you could say cities like that
Include faucet in a large city
Alex
This is no good this prediction that you're making a s***
I needed to get through this large
Kerchunk of time on this
So I'm glad we were able to
He's trying to start
To develop
More fully
Trying to convince
He's going to say before I really think I do everyday
Ed every time
Accelerated or decelerate in his timeline
For saying what we all know he's going to say anything.
In the past because he knew that eventually one
Coyotes will become an actual threat so I assume in the next 6 months
Sprite and take a lunch break indoors later
Dear psychic he could see the future
And he's f****** with us a
Either this podcast was eventually going through
Only question that remains the ultimate and the road is saying that
Victims of the shooting
We're actors
The question is
Is it before the Boston
Vomiting or because of
I was at
A substantial amount of money
Before
Just a week ago I would have said it's because it's crazy
Had a fun week of saying they were actors everywhere next episode
Stripes
Fresno
Like I don't have some Advanced information that I'm like
Hey is it going to be great when it does happen I have no idea
It could be a month after
It is entirely possible that our predictions will be wrong the moment we changed
The Protector
I'm actually course I'm going to say it's not until the Boston bombing
There is that there is not an observer effect
Measure it
Alright
I'm excited to see where that goes
Maybe a better way
2013 of the investigation episode
I have such a tendency to get down into the Weeds about learning about every piece of Alex's narrative
Whereas we are trying to
Understand the Sandy Hook stuff
It may not be in our best interest
Soulard every little thing about what Alex is up to it Mr. Those details
Just as excited as a coyote when Phyllis is on her lunch
Listen I would never deprive you of finding out about I got to give it up at this mall the Pirates
At the same time
We don't need to know about Alex's troubles at sxsw
I'm going to try as best as I can
When we do these
Investigations
In the future
Cover larger
I suppose Just One Day from the past
We need to make we need to make progress
I'm interested in the occupied stuff we'd say we're going to
To that there's this other.
So
On Wednesday with new episode website
You better
We're also on Twitter at knowledge underscore fight
Go to bed
Listen to our show
Spotify
You can go to Spotify
You could also
Conversely find yourself
Small family of coyote
None of them can be pregnant coyotes
Together have a little powwow with them
Steve what's going on
See what they're doing you know what they're going to say to you
The Navajo
Oh yeah
Legend
The coyote
Knowledge fight
There's one coyote
Is the desert
New Mexico
If you find a coyote
It speaks
Is open its mouth
Absolutely
Butts
I am Leo
Holding