I have great respect for knowledge B B I'm sick of them
Monica
Knowledge vype.com
Alex Jones
Have you ever had a moment where you felt like you would be
Old
You're like disconnected from the
Slang that
Maybe when
Disconnect
Did from the DU
Every single
Powerball NY on fleek
Really made me feel old even old at this point
Now I don't know I guess I'm in the VMAs were last night as we're recording this
I saw a bunch of stuff on Twitter about that I've liked I have almost no idea who have
I'm aware of
I don't know why I
I'm so disconnected from music
Because there were a lot of like a right-wing people who are kind of like
Sad about music or whatever
A bunch of these people I've absolutely no idea who they are
Getting Awards
Baby feels a little bit out of it on Twitter people were talking about Eddie Murphy
SNL I don't care about that at all
The board
Of people who are hosting in musical act
I have no idea
Years and years ago every single person who hosted or where the musical act
Of their work who they were now's
I have no f******
Idea
Some of this was when I was 22
But I don't know judge
Do you third
Are the the culture itself for like
Being something I'm out of touch with life
I've made that decision
Do basically just listen
The fucken Alex Jones
All the time.
Alex starts yelling about Billy English I promise I'll know who she is
Good for now
Not really any idea for you to stay in contact with
Current pictures of Alex Jones reviews on with everybody
Ubuntu album agree with his taste
Real Bubblegum
Real Housewives show
Would be amazing
About to pop culture but I do know a lot about Alex Jones
Today we're going over the past 2013
24th
Through 26
The reasoning for that is
I started listening to Mondays
Show of Alex's
It was largely screaming about China
And I wasn't
Super interested in
And I wanted
2checkout
Then the second variable is another
Reason I feel very old
And that is on Monday I woke up
And I could not hear out of my right
You're right
I was pretty
Not entirely but mostly deaf in my right ear
And it led to a bit of a freak out on my part on Monday
Little bit I'll be honest
And
It's going to be interesting to talk about because this episode
What is the medication towards the
Vu Sandy Hook crisis actor narrative felt like there's a lot of momentum going
Our predictions have been completely and utterly wrong
Not yet
It didn't
But they're starting to call the number of thing
Things actor involved
Are you throwing in actors in the Aurora shooting
Talk about the
G20
Protested 2009 Meryl Streep
Performance
Okay where this thread is getting pulled
So you TuneIn
To the days after that and it's very
But before we get to that good to give a shout out to the people who
The show
So first of all Oliver thank you so much you are now policy
I'm a policy wonk
Text Erick thank you so much
We talked a lot about Luke faction
Landmarks
We are strong lately lately
Seems like we've got a lot of Eric
Frame
Murder of Eric favorite murder
Thank you so much you're an hour policy
Thank you so much
Journal
We appreciate that very much so
Thank you so much a mere and thank you so much Lionel Lionel Lionel Lionel
You're all now wonderful technocrat
I'm a policy wonk
Heroin
Is freakishly large
Thank you so much Jonathan
Thank you so much we appreciate it very much
Agreement amongst all Paula
To never let anyone
Sweetly get that song out
The moment
Is that is a different person
Bottle I know love
So
Would appreciate it
Now let's get into it
So there was no snow on the 23rd
Alex comes in
Coming in
Pretty
In bloom
Heavy beginning to an epi
Add March 2013 for teaspoon 2013 will be
And the rear view mirror as well
Welcome to the show we will all soon be dead
That's Tuff
He's in a bad headspace
Is the bedside with March
If you said we're soon going to be the end of 2013 yeah
QuickTime passed over on January 3rd
But
What's important
Cool
So I thought like oh my God
He is f***** up
It is going to be weird Eclipse show
He said we're all going to die
Directly to
There's a couple of old interviews yes
Literally a producer
We got it
It's crazy cuz he was at work he was
Because I don't think that was pretty
Recorded it doesn't have the same tone as a lot of the times
It seems like he was just there
I don't want to do the show and work on something else
Replay that other interview
Jesus a pretty wild
We go over like an interview with rose
The Quarry about Agenda 21
Do the 25th
Monday
March 25th
Alex
Portion of the show getting into some
Something I never expected
Defined
And is one of the weirdest things
I've ever heard Abby
Confer aleksandr
Of the Koch brothers
Manufactured or fake
This is weird
Are you f****** with us
Bright
Whatsoever 2013 investigator I'm not
It is very weird
Influence of the past and present
I know that I have heard clips of Alex
That's where he talks about
The Koch brothers
In one of them
That I've heard
He says that they're not
Weird weird
He had brought them up before
But not to be expected here on this 25th Avenue
He has a lot
To say
What are the things I find particularly interesting
Think about this news like
Let's imagine that the worst thing that Alex
Did find is that the Koch family broke
By helping with equipment selling
Oil refinery stuff to run
Even if that
True
Imagine is Soros
Deal if David Rockefeller it's older on equipment
In the first place is anybody who's breaking anything
Haha
Correct
It's weird
It's that it's a very weird line
That I'm seeing here and I don't know what to make of it
This for me to research
I'll tell you why
Yeah that is a good question I don't know I don't think it proves that he's being paid by the Koch brothers or anything like that but it's a
Do it again
Super weird line
This is my opinion that perhaps
As a psychic link
Influencing his own coverage post-facto in order to
Maybe that's some of the technology along with life extension
Engine technology
For being such a dutiful servant
It's possible
Yeah I don't know whatever the case was able to dig up that means he's not look
Either doesn't want to look too hard
Or he has looked into it
And realizes like
Well
Well it's just
Say that no big deal
Funneling all kinds of money into things that I am against
Climate change or regulation bone
To do with the
Seized
The thing is though that I was only getting into this
I think
Because he gets
Accused
Working for the Koch brothers
A B natural
People to make
I mean he behaves like someone who would be
Suspicious
You almost think he is stupid if he
He's not taking
Or principles which we know he's not
So Alex is responding
Into that
Into that and those thoughts and feelings
He has about those accusation
Largest private Corporation in the country
Hours of it gets released
Alex Koch Industries is like a little mom-and-pop
That's why Walmart is taking over everybody
It's been awhile
It's insane he can be putting forth the idea that it's like
Family business
I meant at the same time sewer perpetuating
Like
They're America's end
Simple things
Really occupy the same space
They're relatable it's just small business owners and the other one is
They are running the whole show
The guys in trading places if they were mixed with an anarcho-capitalist nightmare dystopia
There's nothing like that nothing
It's it's almost like that before we get too far into this
Text goes in
Phrasing the Koch brothers
Makes me think he's a not getting any
Anybody from even for somebody
Who is on their payroll
Tons and tons of money from
Like freedomworks
American prosperity
Almost
You're in the clear
Which opens up even more question
Trying to
But anyway
Is hot water.
Smartcore the founder
G in the 40s
For the night
Suspicious in his absence is any discussion of like
Fred Coquina found
Remember the John Birch Society
No we had
He should be like I didn't know anything about
12 dudes
It's
Very much especially from the 40s
50 more to say about the Koch brothers
Authorities in forties was the
Scientific
Pieces of it
Cool Power Plant
Fayetteville Texas
I don't know if it close
When he was saying it's due to close
I'm not positive that this is the exact
Same power plant in Fayetteville Texas
I would say that it is
Power plant
A cool Power Plant
In Fayetteville Texas
Still open
Because I found an interesting article in the text
From January 2019 with a headline quote
Report Texas Coal Power Plant
Pollutants into groundwater
The report found that all six
Scene of a coal-fired power plant
Texas
Redwater
And it none of them were complying with regulations about spent coal disposal
I just want to say that Fred Coke
Is a
Genius
In terms of the Fayetteville plan
Specifically to argue that the pollution wasn't fault
Just naturally occurring
But samples taken from UPS
From the plant were compared to Once Downstream
And those Downstream head quotes
Significantly higher
And therefore probably not
What can
Look
We all get it
You tried to pull one over
We caught
Like it we get it you tried to pull one over we've all been there
Polluting and destroying the planet
But now you got to fix it
Naturally occurring murdered
Plausible deniability
Oh my God
So
I don't think this is
Strong stuff
It's very weird
Keystone Pipeline
Because
Oh no he believes the opposition to the Cole
The Keystone Pipeline is just about attacking
The Koch brothers
Which is
Sincerely true
Is he like once
Step away from
It's not fair
But I don't I don't actually know his position on that but I do know he doesn't really care if they are protesting
Alex knows that it's tar sand oil
Doesn't good you should know that
Clean burning
Keystone Pipeline being built with lower energy costs
Is implying equities
Is that his feelings are loyal come to the United States
So that's a fallacious piece of propaganda largely pushed by people in
The pocket of Big Oil
In 2015 President Obama signed
Spending
Which was a necessary step to avoid
Be threatened cover
Shutdown
The GOP has lobbied hard to make sure that a provision was buried in that budget
Agreement that lifted the ban on us
Exporting crude oil
Which nearly all experts agree it's something
Us consumer
Because that ban has been lifted there's no reason to believe that the tar sand oil that comes
The US refineries will ever be sold on the US market
There's every reason to believe that if it's
Profitable for the oil companies
A good batting
Lowering the price
You're the US isn't there Prime profit
It strategy
Alex repeating this line of rhetoric
Is a good indication that he has no idea what he's talking about and is just bought the corporate propaganda
Or much
Less likely he has some oil money
I don't think we have evidence of that bit like
Like I said this Behavior mirror someone who does or what
That's what makes this really
Complicated
I'm not satisfied with his behavior being he's on a payroll
It's just like I get why someone would think that
Anyway
Another problem is supported
Keystone XL pipeline
Is the building it would require using eminent domain
To take people's property away who are the path of Pi play
Totally find a broker
Curfew sanctions
It's not that big a deal
LaRosa's
He's he's
Essential
Going to come
The private property
One of the most important
Pieces of the West
But I guess it building an oil pipeline to profit
But not a controlling dust
Of course which is weird it doesn't
It doesn't make sense
America
Can land and
That's it does
Account
So I'll talk about everything is getting shots
The energy
It's all getting shut down and take it all out
Probably cuz of the glove
But then everybody comes like
The Koch brothers are so evil
County
Open
He's on the payroll
You are some sort of
Business b w propaganda
You wouldn't
Allows that
I don't think you would allow that
Over the top
Stupid
It's too stupid its way out of line
It's it's too over
Exposed
The only like
That would be a contract that they would have to go into
Fully aware
Vets say something incredibly wrong
But even the business for himself
Business to go Rogue
You know it'll be a net gain for you so
You know that kind
Anybody who is interested in advancing a particular end
Would probably not work with Alex G
I think the idea of hiring him
Push propaganda is
Not in your best in
For two reasons
One is exactly where describing
Just go Way Off Script
Ecobee
It could either be embarrassingly over-the-top
Like this
It were this to be paid broker programming
Do you know
Not really a cheese your end result by what he's
Because of his own picadillos
The second reason is
If you approach
He's not interested
He will turn you into
His next villain
He's unreliable in that way and if you don't buy him for life
As soon as
He's free of whatever agreement you have
He now has information
That could bury you
There's no indication
He seems like someone it would be very dangerous
To try and buy off
On the off-chance
But he has
Principles or he sees a bigger payday out of
Rapping the script
Brothers
Would be
Smarter than
And to do that
Glenn Beck
Today would not be
Be smarter to do that
I am going to say however that
Billionaires are almost uniformly
Strategy do
IQ
I don't know I don't think we have many examples
You know billionaires paying off
Folk
Who is an immediate
I think you just I think you don't
It could just be that he's
Trapped in the mythology of the
Society that his dad raised him
So before I even looked into the Koch brothers
Remember
And then he's just
Barbers all over their numbers
Maybe
I think that Alex
Pretty into all of the political thing
The Koch brothers
Support
I'm into all that stuff
He doesn't want to open up
Open the door
That
Into like oh my God they have a business
Teen maze
Of foundations that they used
The fund all this stuff
Politically active
And give almost exclusively to
To GOP candidates
I don't think he wants
Too closely mirrors that
He screams about the globalist
Pens that are not political
Support of them
He's just like
Based on this
There are business
People
Industry everybody for that
Internet way he kind of just
Uses criticism
Brothers
The people might have
It is listening
They're able to
Just toss them aside as
Oh this is just cuz they're in the energy
I think it's theirs that I don't know if I don't know if it's
Strictly related
Possibly
Cursory glance
He realized
They were behaving
Exactly as the global
That he
It says are evil
But the real globalist
Who happened to agree with literally everything he believes that's the problem
The opening himself up for the globalist
On the right
It over complicates The Narrative for him
I don't think you be able to
We spend all the yards that he does
Were there to be the
The idea of
People who behave exactly like the demons that he yells about have
Exactly the same social and political goals that he
He does if he comes
It's too difficult of his own accord
Like without anybody paying
Cuz it does still serve
Hughes Internet
His world using
Explanations of Isis
But it's it's
Complicated like I don't literally no way without me
Seeing Alex's finances for me to tell you what
It would just be ranked speculation
I'm not I'm not super interested in
Creating a conspiracy of him being
Koch funded
Although the possibility
I just don't know
If anything
If any funds are involved
I would say it's more of a
Like they just they just give him some money in his like don't f*** with us
Get on out of the Wild
You do whatever you do just leave us out of it for the most
So in this next clip Alex
Is talking about like
The
Like how everybody wants to arrest
The Koch brothers
I'll allow you to do that
Spurs
Soviets
A bunch of t-shirts that are really simple
I get what you're saying and rest them all set
For me with Alex's angle on it is
Endocrinology
Arrest all by political enemies
You arrest all of Alex's political enemies
The day of arresting people on the right it's not going to come
Exactly
No we should arrest the Koch brothers
Does Iceland just held a funeral for
Glacier that was absolutely murdered by the
It's very it's very confusing
I don't know what to
It's isolated
It is
Is just
On this episode is the only time I've heard this
Kind of talk
And I do
Defensive a little bit but about his world
Like I don't
I don't know what
To draw in
I don't know why
Now
In 2013 I don't know why it's happening
Obviously
Isn't the first time
I bet the accusations
Goodnight about getting Coke money
Like I don't know what's precipitating this
I don't know why you feel the need
Spontoon
You would have expected him
Going to be going on about this a lot
Yeah
I don't know it's it's
It's
A does feel
Defensive
Straight defense
Almost
Saying that
Paid by them so much
That he's defensive about them saying that he needs their money
So he doesn't need them while at the same time
He's defensive because he
Maybe or
Knows that he might want
Orbitz
In the future buddy
From them and so he is defending them as if
Hip2Save
Look I'm not getting paid by them but even if I was there still fighting the good fight
I think about it the last
Inclined
I'm to believe that he
Like I don't think that this sort of it
Display is the actress someone who actually
It doesn't feel that way
It also doesn't really feel like an overture to them too
To get money
I I just
Just feel like
Brothers narrative which isn't really a narrative it's just a weird blip
I wonder if it's going to come back I have no idea it's very confusing
Because the next day as it is
Has nothing to do with Koch brothers
Of course
And he only he only supports the Koch brothers with the five
Polluting families
Get together and
Get rings
Bring him into
Perhaps
Next day Alex has an interview with the one
The only
He of course
Is that guy who wrote a book about where to bug out
Location to Alex's selling on his
Also
Apparently
Joel skousen
Survive the plane
And
That is big
Baby picture
All right tell the story of it and it sounds a lot like
Used
I think
It's crazy
He did survive a plane crash
Okay
Feel like I was right next to me
One of the reasons that I'm pretty sure that this is a real thing
But he did survive the plane crash
Is it Alex
Is trying to sell subscriptions
Do his website
By offering to have people watch
Joel skousen
The balance of the hour
So I want to challenge
.
That's pretty strange
It's just barely 2,000
Can imagine that instead of playing the clip of the play
Crashing
Brief moment of
Your levity
Little rickrolling
Never going to have
No I don't I don't know I don't know I don't know why
Boxes using it to
Bushes that traffic to the website
I didn't I don't want to watch that
Real and not horrify
Crash
That does not charm
Okay and he has
Pretty bad
Here's one of them
Everywhere I should point out that this is a written response to a caller
Who is that talked about how like Alex had Rosa Corey who hate the deaf
And the caller was saying like I really appreciate that
She's fighting a but she's a lesbian
Tech
To the gay agenda
Okay
It is very evil
Cannot exercise the right to vote
Whatever relationship
Force other people to accept
And it's a fundamental rights if you don't have the right
Disassociate
Then you've really lost a major fundamental right why don't you discriminated private
What can you allow interracial marriage
That is a
Wildly
Crazy thing
Crashed and burned if there's video of it on the website never got off the ground if you know it
Leash
We're losing right
Scrimmage
Cool
That was the problem with those whole civil rights
I feel like
You still have every right
Discriminate
Do you want
But State structures made
Have the right to discriminate arbitrarily
Then you could discriminate in your private life
Well you're at the job so no
Well you're right
Every right to be naked in private
But you don't have that right at the office
Argument is making
So what I'm going to
How do you spell discriminate naked at the office
Cool
So it is next clip Joel skousen
Pretty concerned with demographics
Probably before
Disease
These folks started yelling about it
Publix
Losing the battle of
More socialist economies are out producing us the American
Good
And we should be
We got to start Moore home schooling or using private schools
To generation that can
For Latinos.
Other minority groups right now
The argument against
Equal protection
Across-the-board
Is somehow being bolstered by the idea of we won't have that Minority
Gross
For the last week
We had a conversation
He literally
There
The same way that
Reverse though
He said they're going to treat us as bad as we traded
That's a translation of essentially what he described
The fear is
Is a f*****-up way to live your life
Episode
Enchilada
And I have a feeling
That we are getting close
Do Alex
Going for
The Sandy Hook crisis actor
Here on this 25th March 25th episode
Sandy Hook
I need does say that it's
Definitely stage
But
It's a little muddy what is point is
The reason that message is Muddy
Is that you think is all stage
But at the same time he's calling the murderer
It does seem like he's saying they killed they actually kill
It does seem that way with the muddiness of a message
Images
The audience
How are they going to
To hear that
And if I'm
Critically looking at these episodes
Is it going through them
And I'm not exactly sure what point
You trying to make
You've got to assume the people who are in
Is there any updated with the
Conspiracy culture that's going on at this time
They've got to be even more unsure
Like if you want to believe that their actors
Then you can hear that clip
And that reinforces your belief
If you believe that the globalist did it and kill people brain says they're all murderers that can you can hear it that
That way if you believe it they're all actors when he says they're all murderers
You can just make that's it
Additionally these are murderers
It doesn't necessarily
It fits whichever version of The Conspiracy you want it
I'm sure caught me off guard
I don't think they are unsure about what
He said
I think whatever he's saying right now
They don't need to think about like
What they wanted to hear there's a lot of utility
Audience
Consciously
Unconsciously he's behaving in such a way it's
Astronaut alien
People who believe
Tennessee
Good strategy
Seems like a good strategy
So we're done with the 25th and we jump to the 20s
I feel like when I when I listen to
25th and I heard all that Koch brothers stuff
I was like
Weird
What is going on with this
I was hoping that the 26
Give me some sort of a
A clue about that
But unfortunately
Vicky hit the eject button
It takes over pretty much the entire show
And again it's another thing I could never have predicted
Something
Watch Dogs
Individual
Jim Carrey
Why
And
Define Deadman
Off-air 1
And I've never told that story
Because that's
Was private
Over the temperature this morning
Under the jeans
Upset
Because he was very close friends with
Charlton Heston
Authoritarian
Patriots Graves
Disgusting
I would say that thing that Charlton Heston was good friend
Enzo Ted Nugent
Defaming a dead
That's speaking of a Deadman
If you see
Patriots
Dancing on a Thor attarian grave
Apocracy isn't irrelevant complaint
To make about Alex Jones as we just got the hundred times
Like there's no use
Like
You try to demonstrate how little anything
I mean but Alex says by pointing out at one thing someone else is doing
Complains about it
The worst thing in the world
Exactly the same thing
But he does all the time
Matter
I don't expect this to me
But I should tell you that
Enemies
Namely David Rockefeller is a big Newport
The only thing I think that is all in
At all about this
Is that Alex
Did the day those men
Guide
This episode we listening to us from March 20th
It seems relevant the Charlton Heston died on April 5th
Almost 5 years prior
Still
Sure
Ted Nugent
Trying
Sure
Bright
Also funny point in 2015
When I Jim Carrey was going against vaccines Alex is all about
What is Alex is a song on Spotify or
Call cold dead hands
The video is basically just making fun of people who are obsessed with guns
Messenger pretty good example
Mystery
Austin impression so
It's not really making fun of his death which again happened 5 years prior
It's really more making fun of the
Expression you can take my gun for
From my cold dead hands
Which is itself a reference to Hesston
2000 NRA convention
Are making fun of it by saying it has been couldn't get into heaven cuz the Angels couldn't get the gun out of
Cold dead hands
Alright Carey made a video that got them all butthurt about their guns so they just have to pick the cheapest
Lamest
Luzeri
Angle on it which is that
Your defaming a dead
Sekiro exact
I am like if I'm being honest
If the video with Jim Carrey
Dad and suck that guy probably at least
Bizarre decision
Strategy
Standpoint
Possibly clunky attempted social commentary and parody
Whether or not it's effective or made its point is a question I'm going to leave alone but
Here is Alex
Some Ted Nugent
Be the most sensitive gone weirdos
On the f******
Also Jim Carrey's backing band
Parody video
You know it was
Mighty Mighty Bosstones the Eagles
No I don't want
I don't want I don't want
Very personal
Better
Parody video
Making a few funny faces
And so what does it say about control
Sonic made super Bale
Years old
He's on the brink of
Can I
That cuz I was listening to that very clearly in the hog
Repair
English classes I really paying off your critical as you can stare
Yeah
How applicable data analysis
Madame Bovary
Dialysis
Approached
Parody it's it's a satire
And if you admit like I don't like people poking fun at
You look super weeks
So Alex says
Almost
Entire show
Complaining about Jim Carrey
Parody video
It is
How old
Him up so much
Restarts
Reciting the lyrics to that song
Really yeah
I assume the Johnny Cash.
Charlton Heston
Thomas Jefferson talking about the farm
Thomas Jefferson
Quote about farmers
Alex's referring to who I believe I recall it correctly
Can't
Put it in the ground
Watch it
Grow in
Croagunk
If we have to go strictly based on past history
It's not a real quote
Alex does not give me budget
To work with your but it does give me a little bit
Cuz earlier this episode
He said that you know
Charlton Heston
The night before and brought him to
Tears
So I kind of got
From there
Jefferson talking about
It makes sense attitude Beacon
In the speech has been says
That the warning smoke is always quotes
Smelled first by the farmers
Who come from their simple home
Define the fire and fight
None of the language
Seems completely inaccurate
The sentiment doesn't totally conflicted all recorded
Scholarship Jefferson
This is not a time to step
Iverson quote
A full sentence
Quote the era at the smoke in the air of our conquered bridges in Pearl Harbor's is always smelled first by the farmers
Who come from their simple home to find the fire in fight
Mystic figs in that
Good 150 before Pearl Harbor was attacked
Grave of Thomas Jefferson
Clearly the speech that Alex was talking about
Thomas Jefferson about the farmers
That's the that's the way he's rough
Farmers in that's
Thomas Jefferson
Around Monticello which houses all the collect
Did writing the time
Thomas Jefferson
See what I can find dark about his feeling
Songs about farming
But that's not the whole story
Hidden November 3rd 1807 entries of John Quincy
The Adams diary
He tells the story of going to a dinner party
Attendance
Quote there was a usual dissertation upon wine
Not very edifying
Mr. Jefferson said the
The dude I had always been extremely but do nothing about it
This seems to be a really good description
Jefferson's relationship
Farming
He was into it but he knew nothing about it and he wasn't going to bother to learn
He wrote a letter to William Brandt
Giles on April 27th 7
T95 say quote if you visit me as a farmer it must be as a conda cycle
Brian Buttle learner
Ediger won Indy but yet desperate being too old to learn a new craft
I'm not referencing this quoted all the s*** on Jefferson honestly I kind of relate to it
I'm becoming much more in
Didn't plant
An apartment
These days
But I do feel too old to learn much about the art
Much like Jefferson I'm eager to learn by doing
Also it's interesting
Reviews on farming
Beliefs of the Alex might describe as
Communist
In a letter to John Dougherty from June 27th 80
Teen Titan he said quote
I think it's the duty of farmers who are wealthier than others
To give those less so the benefit of any improvements introduced
Brought it
I assume Alex just ignores that one choosing
Instead of constantly repeat fake Jefferson
I'm close to service dumb Gunn weirdo agenda
I'm pretty sure
Thomas Jefferson
Would have been super into intellectual
But maybe you didn't rise
Incompatible super-rich bomber you have an obligation
Tim to help out the less fortunate farmers
You know if you
Builta if you created a new irrigation
Then you should share it with
Probably
It's unclear exactly
It also
The trend in
His comments about Farm
10 towards like you should just run
Small farm
It doesn't seem like he's super into the idea of like
Massive
Agricultural
Conglomerate
Which Alex
So Ted Nugent
Comes on
Alex
Pentad
Physically
This is very well
We understand that Alex believes in
Erase memory
They talked a bit about that
I know we talked about it in the past but I think it's worthwhile to hear this
Rambling
Explanation of it
Because I
I think there's something you really got to think about
Based on his under
Alex
You can feel it
Split
And in the NFL
What does genetics mean
Uterus
Worried about you
Is it related to George Washington
Thomas Jefferson
You are reaching thousands of people
Not just spiritual or psychic connection is a physical Transmissions
Okay
If Alex believes he's literally connected to his
Show me absolutely be in favor of reparation
Shouldn't he be totally apathetic toward people whose grandparents
The great-grandparents were enslaved seeing as they're literally their ancestors
Like isn't this a hole in his entire worldview
Right
Separate entities exactly the same as the founding fathers
Take a closer look at this
You also see
The except the super revealing about his
White identity belief
This idea that you are your ancestors is literally never applied to a non-white purse
When is
The way
He applies it to all of this
Forget it only has to do with his connection to Jefferson or whatever
Who were the founding
Founding fathers
If you apply this
Universally
It forces you into a very
Empathy
Field position
And because he doesn't it it makes me believe that he doesn't apply at Universal
It's just some self-aggrandizing bulshit that he uses
To give some sort of a
Otherworldly credibility
It's b*******
It's almost paradoxically
Solipsistic
In the
It makes him the center of the universe
He's also millions of people
Arrow
It's very fascinating
What kind of lunatic
Yeah I mean it is just
Expression of that white shift and that also has narcissist
Its its interests
T22
To think about that
Think about how
Minimizing he is
About the history of
Horrible
This country
To non-white
Let's say
How
If you believe the things
He believes
All of those things happened
Do the people who are alive today
He can't make the argument there like slavery was hundreds of years ago
It all is happening now
Well Trail of Tears is happening now
Bet he does
He did
Eagles picks
It's frustrating
What's even more amazing is
He's basically going outside
Because every woman is born with all the eggs
Ever have
There is an unending chain from every woman back
And back and
Forever Until
Mitochondrial DNA
He's somehow throwing the men in there as being like we're also the ones that have
No dude
Ramble a bit about how like
Sure
Yep they did it is amazing
Verifying into misogyny
It's
It's it's weird
It's weird I would like
They're very few questions I'd like to ask
Things I would really actually like to ask
About race memory stuff
Does is it a superpower that only white people have is the first question
Yes
Then he believes in White Oak
If he answers know it opens up
So many other questions about you care about the ancestral
Memory and experience of people
I better run like you
Right
I swear to you I don't know why but my
Based on all the amount of time we've spent listening
Is that his answer that question would be
White people
Like somehow he throw in a probably
Yeah
Great because he agrees to
Come on Alex
Stars
Out there
But they can't come on
Like Christopher Walken
Unless he's forced at gunpoint by the Bells
I talked to Major Rockstar
New world record
I talked to
Other
I can't come on your show
They're giving me too much heat just for going to Beer website or talking about you
So I want to go play the major venues
Major Rockstar
Financing
Steven Spielberg
Couldn't even name
So if I had to guess these major Stars Alex is talking about
Like they were trying to politely decline his invitation
Going over his work
It's at either Supercenter
Dude
If you're a big star and you tell Alex you don't want to go on a show because
Toxic in
Crazy the next thing you know Alex finds a white paper saying you're a globalist bent on depopulation
He's a paranoid a******* so the absolute best way to get out of a
Precision with him is to tell him that the
Not to lose my career
Or possibly I can imagine a situation where someone in a boat
Candor told Alex
Come on his show cuz it'd be bad for their career
And now it's right into that the globalist
Oregon
The very real possibility that Alex's
It's entirely
Rockstar
And the s*** though
I think a lot of the crazy one
Shelter
A number of them have gone on
Even some crazy ones record
Big knives what's good and bad for the brain
Going on Alex's show at buddy
A career boost
Is it toxic
Connected to
The Eurythmics where Olga
Going to go on the show I drew
It doesn't matter their big stars in the 80s
The two examples that Alex uses
Evil globalist
Hollywood most prominent Jewish
Jerry Bruckheimer is born in 90
His parents were Jewish immigrants were
From Germany so you can draw whatever conclusions
That you like
He wasn't.
Collaborated
Conclusion I can draw
Steven Spielberg was raised orthodox
Easy directed was Schindler
Gloves
I understand that these are Big Hollywood guys but
Hard not to hear this
Is a sign of something that dwells
Like at 12 down in Alex's
There other names
Secret pic
Their other big-name non-jewish people in Hollywood with far more left-wing politics
Ben Spielberg and brachii
I don't know but I don't think that this mess early concert
Does anything really damn good
Has to pull out names of the
The ones who are working with the NWO but globalist
Hollywood
The two biggest
Jewish man in Hollywood
Endive name of a
Somebody who is willing to
Fight back
I was also told otherwise Tom Selleck
Himself
Tom Selleck
Not the Indiana Jones movies
The moron complaining about China
And how Thor attarian they are at
They are witch
At least he's got consistency
He's complaining about them in 2013
Still complaining about it
I'm glad history driving
I'm so Alex
A little bit
Extreme and I
You'll see you'll see what goes on here
Infowarsstore.com
The Western journalists, I got some footage of someone getting their dick cut off and just left in the street at the other globalist
I mean
That's a pretty evolve
Developed
Alex Jones at Disneyland
There's not there's not yelling
But it does have the
That we come to
The Impreza
Emotionally evocative imagery and negative
Horrible thing
Smoothly pivot
We got water filters on sale
Plasticized into
So Ted Nugent comes in
Complain
Jim Carrey
So the first hour of the show is mostly Alex talking about Jim Carrey
An a******
Yeah the second hour of the show is Alex and Ted Nugent
Sing about
2 hours of old white men
Yep
Wolf so also Ted Nugent wants you to know
Is there a lot of people who talk s*** about it
Fat people disagree
What about the people who think that they're all sucked up
You
How long
Run amok
This is a great
To hear on a Libertarian program
Antitrust
All the critics are on drugs
Newton has going for it is like
An honest salable positive I guess I've never done drugs
F*** off
Whatever age
I'm 64 years clean and sober doesn't drink don't do drugs
So
Can trade guy in his writing songs about children
Completely sober when I wrote predator
Oh man
Drugs right cuz When You're Sober you write songs like Tango
I don't know
I think
I don't I don't think it's a virtue
To not have drank or done drugs
But he does
Uses that as a way to
Attack
KissAnime
I can't because I am smoking dope
You have smoking dope
Invalid
I have also smoke and a lot of dope
The fact that I have
Not morally
He's applying morality or at least like if you have used drugs you're not a credible person
But I don't think lines up with libertarian
Weird version of libertarianism worth
I think your invalid in your argument if you do drugs to be able to I guess that
Is possible but that's f***** up
That's just too much work
Seems weird just too much work
To believe all that
Book convention
Still criticize Ted Nugent even though
Join the NRA
That's so gross
Get the call later in the show from someone who is like made me sick
Soldier getting an RPG
To the gut
That was disgusting
Alex's take on it is to respond like how the globalist use the
Terrorist noted above above
It was responding
Into the wrong
Complaint right
No real
Criticism or
Pushback from the
The Muslim Allah puke s***
Which is the
Disgusting
Michelle and
From Ted Nugent I didn't even catch
At first I didn't
Chicken Alla game
And then
Of course
Really in
Enjoy listening
Station
That is
Purelander
Utterly
With such
Moral Authority
Sure
He says and does
Is
Nonsense s*** talk
Won't
Any meaning
Here in that clip even that it's all in service
Sign up for the NRA promoting multiple times during this interview
You can do it
Description to the NRA
You got people in your life buy them subscription Cydia
It's f***** up
It's a large portion of what they're trying to
To use this
Charlton Heston
Desecration app
As a way to get people's hands
That's what
So Ted Nugent interview cuz it's largely
Bulshit
It's really funny once it's over Alex gets really mad at his audience
He calls them pathetic
This is a weird way to turn your audience clinically
Maybe a little bit
Because you're
Nnn
Pathetic
Absolutely
Completely
It's so many levels
Earwolf
Coyotes
Responsibility
Other speaker
You don't know
I just don't understand
There is an amazing irony that Alex's
Was yelling about people caring about people laughing at them after spending two hours
Complaining about a f****** parody video on Funny or Die
That is the most projecting that you can
Can possibly do
Turn off your shoulder
He quotes Thomas Jefferson about farmers
Yeah
Yeah that's ridiculous
Crazy
Call
And I think I know what that
You will know what that mean
Into the middle
This clip
1 Warren
The other thing
I mean
Time for callers
One last thing
Armored vehicles
Seriously
Their windows
Everybody has paintball guns
And wrist Rockets
Turtle you tipped over
Look at them and look for their weaknesses and
You know you don't have a lot of weight with small-arms fire but their windows
You know I can't see that can thrive
And paintball guns are inexpensive
So Alice beatbox
Eating lunch
Does not care alright call paintball guns
Stop.
Which is good
He doesn't really mind
Is taller advocating fighting
So what you're saying is
Defeat text why we defeating text
Anyways I'll take my answer off
I mean I would assume
If you're at the point where you're shooting at tent
The problem
Are you back at you
Maybe not a live round
Probably
Generally speaking to if you're in a situation where you're shooting on a tank
It's just that
There's no one else with the time
First of all this college town
Yeah I think I've started calling me when he's hungry
Only does bunnies like
I got it
I'm so hungry I need some time off to college
I want to
I wish you would just
Farmer Audible
I want
Eat chips on Mike Wiley State Park
I want I want it so bad I want to hear at
Satisfying like the life very fragile
Alex
Fight
Alex has a new plan of how you doing
Fight back again
Explains it in the
Strategy
Particular operation
And then put them in the magazine
Bumper stickers up around the country
Earnest
So like
This million bumper sticker operation
32nd
Can clip is Sotelo
His two things are
Very clear at
One of them is at Alex's only strategy
Insurance
In terms of a battle
These two seem to also have a heavy overlap with promotion
Spell possibility
The million bumper stickers going out there
Is a amazing way for him to get the audience
It's to do his advertising for
So there's that Universal in terms of almost every
Call to action that he throws up
Are videos everywhere posted to your social media
You just got to wake people up and then everything
It's remarkable that every
Single things
To have
Alex's bottom line
Firmly in place
Like that's why when the Google whistleblower came on in 2019
Lake to your media on that we're going to show the Infowars article for it
It's the information isn't as important as the conduit that Alex
Super Motocross sticker operation
Is first and foremost
Advertise
That is
Keys under
The second thing is he's like I'm doing this if it's going to cost me a bunch of money to put these
In the
Well actually I'm going to have to charge a little more cuz of the bumper sticker
More in order for me to sacrifice
This bumper sticker operated just advertising for my website this is how this works
To make this lemonade
And I charge you $2
Now this time I'm only going to charge you $1
I am going to add ice though which is
$3
Think about this
That doesn't even include the amount of advertising
I gets crazy
Whatever cost
That you would know
Need to pay
In order to get a million
In the wild instances of his put up on stop sign
Over that Ruby
Prohibit it don't cost so much
But if you masqueraded as a lie
We're going to bring the community together with this
Like you're able to get people to do it for free it's very sneaky
Also
Think we can learn
And from that clip
Daddy was a little high
Now that he's had something to eat
He is far less
You guys are pathetic you're all week you're all doing for me
Snickers
Alright you guys
The living Snickers commercial
He really kind of is
To Alex bring it up Sandy Hook
And we get to see you a little bit more of what his thoughts
Aurora
Operation
That is a control operation out in the oven
It is just off-the-charts disgusting
So one
Illustrated
Again you're not sure what
There's provocateur there's staging
Does that mean what specifically are you saying
If you believe that are actors
Do you hear exactly what you want from that
If you believe the globalist
Set up a patsy you hear what you want from that
It's becoming much it's very muddy
I'm not saying he was ever super specific about what he believed except for in that one instance
From
Months back
Want to call her was talking about actors
Absolutely that's
The time it has been most
But now there's such
A Martinez
But it makes me very uncomfortable
Because I can't really nail down what do you mean
Provocateur could be in a hole
List of a ton of different
Fight what I can't
Is that
It's very
Did Alex talk about Sandy Hook
Without the crutch of Aurora
He needs that Solid Ground for him
Stand-on
Well he point
To Sandy
Which isn't good cuz it's arguments about a roar
Terrible
But he's established them
What is rhetoric
Two uses that as
Play kids Waypoint
To get where you need
Needs to go
If we did
Know that the
Conclusion eventually is going to be
I'm saying
It'll be very
Yeah but since we know that it does
Seem like he's using that as a way to get where he's at
Inevitably going to go
I just don't know
Why that makes sense
Likewise
Currently
He's being somewhat
Somewhat
Restrained on Sandy Hook but going
Confidently and Whole Hog
And say whatever bulshit he want
About Aurora
I'll get even ate like with
Describes a certain intention
And I don't know if
Is doing it on purpose
To set us up for the big reveal that all of Sandy Hook
It doesn't
I think it is probably a couple outfits
What Alex was targeted at call her about how horrible it is
The idea of treating a grieving father that way or thick
Insinuating that their child
Didn't die
Is a monstrous thing
Be the parent like
What that would feel like a human level
Understand that
It doesn't want to drift
Into this territory
Without some
I'm sort of a
He recognizes that is a very marketable
Right
Community
Because conspiracy
Community so obviously in terms of
Raising profit
Be more interesting being on The Cutting Edge of that
Community
That's a place you want
Bien
But knows that entering it is monster
Yeah you can rationalize away the Aurora shooting not being as monstrous
To attack in this way cuz it was
It was a dull
It wasn't a
School shoes
It wasn't
Children
Evan the second piece of it
There are a ton of things about the Aurora shoe
Shooting that are f*****
In terms of
Call suspension
Student
5 in in ways that you can misinterpret to make sense
There are a ton of things
Better
For him
About that
Yeah that make it very easy to spend
And it doesn't
Seem as monstrous
It's doing that
About the murder of children
Right so I think
Because there are so many what about swith the auroras that you know nobody ever going to have an argument and then have an answer for
For every single thing
Immediate
Emotional
Is much
Do that there
And solidify that as a talking point as
World world
And then
He can use that
To rationalize
Right
Sandy Hooks.
So you're saying this is all
Almost ending
Internal
With him
I would say I don't know I don't know
You just need a
A narrative myself
You know how much how much
Desire this to make sense
I don't know it's entirely possible this is meaningless nonsense and it just happened totally
It could be
Completely subconscious
Or any there's a possibility that it is a crass Financial
Consideration
They might like David realized it's a super
Popular
Conspiracies
Just say it's fake
Then we're going to lose a lot of people who recognize that's monstrous to
To say
Consumers
If we just jump to it
So let's do it
That alleviates
Concern
Possible
Where could it be
Lake
Blindly fumbling around
You couldn't even get out
Makes the most sense about everything
Yeah I don't get to the point Alex's at
Blindly
He just going wherever the way
I don't think you're able to make a million-dollar
Billions of dollar operation
Like he has just
Coincidentally
By being able to scream really well
That possible there's some attention
That goes behind the counter
He puts out
What exactly that intention
It is
Is very
Difficult
To nail down
Yeah
So we'll see about that
I don't know
I think
My feeling on it is very similar to where we were last time that I still feel like there's
So it is next week we get a call
And I keep this call and it's
Entirety which I rarely
Because I think it's illuminates
Very
A rare glitch
Alex's show
This is a call that Alex gets
From someone who wrote an article
That was used as a resource
And Infowars
And this caller believes
That
And Infowars misuse
Information
Is it Annie wrote the original article
Because
First of all we know he's very sensitive
Handle courtesy
And also this is very threat
2 minutes longer so
So this
This is Captain its entirety
I think we should listen to it be
Because I think it's an interesting Journey
Through Alex's
Is defensiveness sensitivity
An inability
To handle
Or
Respond
The criticism
When criticism is made
He must have left
Internet criticism
Do something
Bus create a strawman
In Tennessee you're on the air
How are you
I'm good
And a pleasure to be here and I wanted to take you out and he's working a lot of people up but I called them because I
Picwood Infowars on an article
Did I wrote last year that they used his when their Chief references Ethan up
Recorded on the show and
In memoriam Andrew word if you remember Andrew the chicken man they called him
Well but they did indeed and my point was the banality of evil in this country and and the internal
Enemy is more dangerous than the external
Answering people around me
It's
The reported you sent turned it into an agenda 21 story when it really wasn't if you listen to his friends and family it was dubbed
Banality of evil of local bureaucrats doing this
Empower more scientifically designed
Play
Yes I do
Make the correction I never got a response in that was
I'm a piece of Filth
So Alex is super defensive in
Sensitive
Turns it into field blue
A terrible mother
To try and like
Facetiously deflect
Criticism
It's like that's not
What are the guy is saying
Kind of
A nuance
Point he's trying to make about his reporting that was misused
He doesn't even substantially seem to
The disagree with Alex
On
Story about a guy who got killed by the
The state
But you just misrepresent
I reported the story
Clearly this guy is talk to
To the family members of
The guy
You talked about
Long time ago
So
Alex
To respond to that as if it
It's some sort of an attack on his character
Are you doing it all sorry I am garbage
But that's
That's a real vulnerable
Scared
Insecure
Sensitive dude
Yeah well there is absolutely the reason
Where any
Daytime
What would you ask Alex Jones Rd
There's no point
That guy didn't even say it
He didn't even like he didn't even get the chance to make his full point before I was like
F*** you
I can't do any
Okay fine then goodbye
Go away
It's it's you're never going to
To get any Headway
He's very sensitive
Any mild criticism is traded as
The
The deadly attack yes
The two-hour crying bins with Ted
Nugent
So Alex is like because you spent two hours
Charlton Heston
Jim Carrey nonsense right
Covering up the news
The news
Go to Overdrive
No no
Mafucka
The show
To a guy named Richard Reeves
Okay
Who is a shill for youngevity
They just do a
20 minute
Infomercial about getting on the Infowars
Which is the multi-level marketing scam
For youngevity products
It is
Crazy
It's just this Richard guy interviewing
A guy who
Is a distributor
Do the top-level distributaries like you know what's great about this product sells itself
All you got to do is get this cleanse and study
Compared to this study
I do know what hey
Real estate
That's great invest
But
Wow man it's disgrace
He's a con man
The highest
Level one clip of it because
Everyone else
At this
Why Alex is
Important
Of the
Like a people Buck back again
Me whenever I like
Alex has a definitive
Being used for evil is a whole different question the course again
But he has a talent
And all you need to understand that
Is listen to this
35c
Before we
He's got his own radio show he's had the longest running radio show on
Home business
The home business
Network
Chenault
I got a little bit nervous there but
Tom had
Long-running show based
And he covers
It's not good
Wow that does not Inspire confidence in me to be
Be tricked by your skin
Alex would never fumble like that
April
That was
Of a parody of somebody failing like that he repeated it I got it
I've used the stuff I listen to the show all the time
That's the sitcom Alex comes out of nowhere and tackled him
Downwards
He walked in later with a sandwich anyways bye
The cool casual
Collected
Intensity that Alex has what are you doing
Tried to convince you that your family needs
These products
How great it is for you to start your own Cottage business
Infowars
Team
S*** like
And how apocalyptic it is
For you not
Right it's so different than this
If this is bad
I would never
Fall for his scam
But I could see
Someone falling for Alex
I could not see someone falling
IPad
I don't know that guy sucks
He's terrible.
The rest of the show
It's it's weird I don't like I don't think there's a ton
Forgiveness episode
Rambling about the Koch brothers
And I got nothing
I don't know
I want to trust me I want to
He's talking about the Koch brothers
And I can tell you for sure
Alex is on the payroll I want to be able to do that but that would be dishonest
Stupid
I all all
I can say is he's acting f****** weird and a Looper defending
The Koch brothers
And that's f***** up
Is a screaming about f****** Jim Carrey from
Sometimes
You go deaf in one ear
You tune into the
Eddie confuses the s*** out of here where I'm at I don't know what he's doing
I want to tell you I know but I don't know what he's doing
Is that is the central question
Trying to make sense
Savignon
There is no body of work that will ever adequately explained what the
The fuk is he doing
Another episode
Would you like to visit a website
I what
I
There's this great website
Hold on
Okay it's a top side know it's in the business
The yellow page
Knowledge
Have you ever been there it's good I don't watch that show all the time
Twitter
Go to bed underscore fights
We are
You could
You could read a review
View
You can write a review
You could go to the office
Can of course you can
So go to your
Local home
Depot
In there
Gardening
Equipment
You will see
Those little what are they
The little shovel
Trowels
Now it's right comes
Okay I thought you were going to say that if you survive a plane crash
Virtualsc
Then are you going to have
Episode
It's best to keep that to a man
Amnio
I'm Leo
I am
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color