I have great respect for knowledge but I'm sick of them posing as if through the good guy
Stripe.com
Beverages
Doesn't talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Do you have any allergies
Peanut allergy
Or the light
So at least not
Normal allergies I believe myself to be allergic to avocados
But I'm not positive that that is
Is the truth all right there's a story behind eye
You know it's one of those things that I've never gotten
Officially tested but I got
Sick eating guacamole or avocados multiple times
When I was younger
Not get sick
Times that I ate two avocado
Trick to it but I have no confirmation on it and I haven't had any
Avocado
Like I could touch it
My girlfriend
I think there's severity levels with the allergy
I don't know
I've been
Sandblasting
For saying I might be fair
I could be I could not be
That's what we're going to get a lot of messages like avocados in the only hypoallergenic fruit there is worse.
I don't think there's anything else other than that I've had
Everyone's allergic
Victaulic poison
Maybe I don't know
But I do know a lot about Alex Jones
Theme of the show
Right
That's murder
I don't know if you get off the cuff struggling to EpiPen
We got an interesting absolute to go over will be covering
The present day of August 28th
Tuesday Wednesday and Thursday of this week
Uneventful days nothing much going on these days
There's some interesting stuff going on with Alex
But I'll be honest a i8
We care about a whole lot of
Just
Spiller
Nothing happening
In many sectors of the infowar
Or at least Alex's version of it and a lot of the stuff that you look into it
Expecting to find
Is that
You find nothing
Which is strange
Abu get into all that your involvement
Before we do
Give a shout out to
People who are
I've signed up
Turner sporting the show
So first Jacob thank you so much you are now policy walk
I'm a policy wonk
Next mosque thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk your boss config
Francis
Thank you so much
Globalist walrus
I'm a policy wonk
Wilford Brimley dead
People who signed up and elevated level
We appreciate it also very much
Watch So Adam
Nah
Or nausea
I can't remember I was corrected on this
I do not
I am a real
Thank you so much though
And this one might actually be stealthily trying to get up
Commercial in here
This might be a real thing I do today
Play some goddamn Farrelly brothers movie I've never seen
But the Palermo roads executive Search you are now
All wonderful take
Democrat
Heroin
Is freakishly large
So one of the reasons that I needed to get back to the present day
We're at the front of the the
The Syracuse
The first
Was
Lawrence O'Donnell
AIDS
They was kind of unwise
No very explicitly
Maybe too-good-to-be-true and irresponsible to get on TV
Report to put his own f****** name
You know that but I felt like this was the perfect opportunity for Alex
Seeing as
Heated the f*** off mat
Spoiler alert
Not one mention of it
It seems like just a layup
It was a gimme for Alec
Saxony didn't he does not to take that so
Me to check in on the present
Null set
All that
Now the other one was yesterday
It's on Wednesday
The the Trump
He tweeted that
Fox News
Are we need to look for a new news Outlet
Very fun
Which I expected to be Alex's Greenlight
To be like
I have been here all along
Firefighter
All the races
I kind of had a feeling of like we might end up
Alex really try
Not necessarily to Taylor's contact cuz it's already there
We might
Stewardess
I'm trying to fill that void
Pay close attention
Do that
As I think we might be
We might be at a point
Of of
Demarcation
Released
One of the things that I was
Considering
As excited like
Let's stay in the present here
Check in
Necessarily
I don't see Alex
Really
C m notice
Ricky's chicken
For real
Maybe Alex is actually
Finally in that state
Just say I don't want to work
I know if it emotionally at times it does
But I don't think it's fair or accurate thing to say that Alex is
Messerli checking
Because I think he is still
The game
Yes it's
Starting on the 28th
And Alex the begin his show
By explaining the globalist
Populate the planet
In order
To rid themselves of competition
It seems
It seems like a strange motivation but
That seems to be what he is
Bowser
Broadcast off yesterday
Cover story
Wow.
Bruschetta population
Wilmot house
The competition
Earth
Transhumanism
I looked it up
Oh boy
This is it this is a hot start to the show
So what is coverage of a new book that was written by noted futurist James Lovelock called Nova
In the book Lovelock argues that in the future
Species of being in the universe
He's being poopy so far past us in terms of intelligence probably not even be interested what we're doing
Mulatto people interact
It's all good and well to take your shoe with a few
Futuristic
But it's entirely separate to pretend that the role of a futuristic Society is to unveil the actual
As if they have some otherworldly psychic
Gift
That's how I look seems to think about future
Does it there modern-day soothsayer
Making predictions about Trends in technology and culture
But they're telling the world with ease and what will definitively be
Yeah you already has a
And we've seen how well he
Right must be able to see the future
It's
Crazy
Way too thick
Dumb
In our endgame coverage we went over a bunch of the failed predictions of Alex's other favorite futurist Ray Kurzweil
We don't need to repeat all that over again but
Suffice it to say his batting averages
Is not great
Beatrice
Batting average
Is not great
He's most famous for his 1974 Gaia hypothesis
Which stated the Earth
The Earth itself is a living organism
Itself and has for millennia
Environment suitable for life
In the years since the Gaia hypothesis
Science has come out to demonstrate how this
Barely unsupported
Or is the New Scientist put it the ideas beautiful but flawed
There are elements
With understood science
Is much as ecosystem
Systems can recover from
Some forms of damage
Ecosystems are in
Interdependence
With a larger point
Seem like
Gets grounded
This is the largest contribution Lovelock and is made to the culture
View as a fun thing to think about booking
Completely off base
Scientifically
There's no reason to not look at the predictions
How is a 100 year old man
As equally idealistic
Chicken fun to contemplate
Not that realistic
I have often said
The same thing about the
Expelliarmus
It is very fun to think about
Necessarily
I'm guessing this is a final chance
Harry Potter
Harry Potter ever
Recognize Real
Zodiac
System of his
Hypothesis was
That
When it was refined the later
He had some scientist
Criticism towards a
Then he resigned his theory to make it more in line
With the Saints
Really laid down what he was saying
People that respond to it was like
Well what's new about this isn't accurate
Accurate about this futuristic
Aspect
Relay
Scientific
Fanfic
Sure
It's just the nature of the sort of future
Twerk
These people are often
Never actually right about much
But they presented compelling a romanticized version of things
As they often still latch onto a metaphorical truth about the time
Which is easy to confuse with being right
Alex is so desperate
2% of self is correct about his
Theories that his enemies are trying to kill off the population
To tell you how
It is
Larry Flynt
Now it's important
To point out that
Other stuff used
There's more than one Albert
Einstein in
Attitude in the United
One of them is a non-profit the bills itself as being dedicated to
Supporting nonviolent resolutions of international
Crazy
Criticized by many is actually supporting efforts
For US Bank
Regime-change
I'm not a criticism without looking
Too deeply into it but whatever the case is
It exists as a foreign policy entity the folks
This is on International conflict
The other one is Albert Brooks is personal
The other is the other Albert Einstein
Institute is also known as the max
Planck Institute for gravitational physics
These are unrelated entity
Because the guy who started
Inspired by Albert Einstein
Signs
Non-filer
Yeah
Whatever
I looked into that I can't find any real concrete connections
Epstein or either of these
Nor can I find any concrete connection between Lovelock
Either of the
If I had to guess I would say that the most likely possibility
Here is the Lovelock might have given a lecture at the
Science one
And they might have donated to the political
But I can tell you with certainty
She is the Jeffrey Epstein was not the Omni budsman of either of them for the last 20 years
Partially because it's on butts
Partially because he wasn't the Ombudsman of either of us
Omni budsman
Criticize your ass
Editorial
What kind
Idiot would hire f
It's a it's a little silly
Straws
It's really really easy to believe that Alex wouldn't realize there are multiple
Albert Einstein
And you just be so desperate to
The appearance
Connections that don't exist in order to
Sports.
Do this
Until I see some actual evidence
Provide
Yeah at all
So you starting off
And when I heard that I was like
Is not good
There are no citations
Today is Alex's
Just making an argument that to this guy this futurist
Telling everybody
That humanity is going to be
Be killed off
Goes to which is
Strange
Specific
This is bad work
Alex
Kind of deals with why he's doing such a bad
That
Elsa show
Alright
You a****** 20 f******
All your life has been preparation
You should have prepared
15 years ago
Cleo I don't have the information available to make
Sit down for an hour before the show
Actually talked about the depth of the rabbit hole
That's it that's your whole
Popped out
Still
Trying to find
Prince
More preparation
Alex is really big into
Kundalini Yoga who got to do that before the show
I will accept
So this is get to the bottom of the global conspiracy
I'll just ask
I think this is demonstrable of like one of the things that I see
In the present day that makes
It's not very
And that is
Isn't that
This is a really sad display
Other person comes on air makes a bunch of
Tenuous connections that may or may not exist
And asserts them as proof
Like the globalist they're trying to kill off people to eliminate
Competition
As I promised yesterday I was going to prove shape
How sad is this
That's not good
It's it's a mess
It's exactly how you would
If you are trying to get
Fired from you
A job
Turns out you own the company
Like that
Is anybody going
That's right I Ono
At least I'll give you a
Abused Alex
I'll give it up to him like he's a smiley pirate he hasn't
And not only has two excuses for why he's unprepared no
Tomorrow
Complaining
Call me this morning
What's your problem
Security
Was he
Hookah stores around here
You're the f****** CEO and
President and head of the figurehead the face
Chief talent to this company
You got a deal.
What the f***
You don't actually saw this happen on Monday Tuesday
Steve Doocy he was going to bout to do father and friends and then they went to a remote
Chasing a guy who stole his backpack citizens arrested at Horsethief
Save it for Alex is like
Do you know all of his talk of I do six hours of prep for every show I'm in the
I'm in the studio hours before getting my articles in line
And getting everything
Straightened out doing research
If you get completely
Like how long was that call but this a not even happen
Okay but that's mental space that's at least a half-hour
And half-hour phone call completely derailed population
That you've been screaming about for over a decade go f*** yourself
I just like
I love the juxtaposition
He's like I'm about to
Reveal the entire conspiracy behind the globalist
Play we're going to go all the way
730 f****** chaos
There is one
Version of this I could see it being real
Okay
That was an important backpack
If there was something in there that Alex
Didn't want to get out
I could see that ruining
Who gives a s*** I think it was actually the coronation
What was it like a backpack full of footage of like things that invalidate his narratives or
Search supplements cam openly
I understand
The way you're presenting
It wasn't employees backpack
Also
How did that happen
You have snipers on your roof
There's guns everywhere another employee
Convenience stores
I don't understand that either
Goodbye
Also is Alex
The head of
Third person is well he would be like that security had to go get it
Security camera
I don't know
I mean
Bring out the guns
DeVore
Also
How do they trace that
Backpack to a convenience store
Accidentally took the wrong
There's no way back
There's no way that he's like somebody took a backpack from the Infowars Studio
We're going to set up a two and a half kilometer perimeter Global is drop-off points are generally
Piggly Wiggly
Send the gendarme is around 2
Anywhere that sells a twin
We're going to get to the bottom of this thing
Ridiculous
Prepared
Doesn't stop him
Which is talk
Bible
Okay you don't have a lot of preparation
It's important
The fall back on
Like the Deep Wells within you
Religion
Alex Goes to the scripture
And I
I don't think he does a great job
Because
Well
You'll see
Because
You're going to override it
Fishers
You're going to conquer all
Forms of
You will conquer the universe
Garden
Good and Evil
Action
Alright
Knowledge of evil
The spirit of the devil
So adamant
It has like
He seems to think that
When Eve ate the apple original sin was created at Original Sin
Is globalism
I'll be in a little bit
Just basic coding information
The Villa whatever
Like
It is little big live but I don't think
It's far off
Now you're absolutely right
I want to point out the one
Gigantic
Flaw in Alex's interpretation
He seems to be suggesting that the knowledge of good is the knowledge of how to setup good systems that encourage Humanity
Have a knowledge of evil is the knowledge of how to setup parasitic anti-human
Is that a thought.
God forbid Adam to
From the Tree of knowledge of evil
It was a knowledge of both good and evil that was for
Genesis 2 verse 16 clearly says
And the Lord God commanded the man you are free to eat from any tree in the garden but you must not eat from the Tree of the knowledge
Image of Good and Evil
For when you eat from that tree you will certainly die
It's been ology of both good and evil that God tells Adam he's not allowed to
Is that so
In the Bible is to hold
Explicit knowledge of how to create human empowering system
This is an inescapable conclusion
The literal text
The Bible and Alex's Express believe
Which is a problem for our
If Alex wants to say that the globalists are creating a bad answer human system which is the offshoot of possessing
The knowledge of evil
Send it
He's just as evil according to the Bible
Because he's very clear
Create a good human empowering system which relies on the knowledge of which was equally
Right
Essential problem with Alex's
Interpretation of this scriptures
His conception
God it makes
Because
The way he can
Steve God I don't think that guy has any idea how to create good social system
That makes no sense
Interpretation
For you to have but I don't think you're preaching
Biscuits
Point
Never heard of
Anybody
Literally
Who interprets Jennifer
Photo I've never heard
I feel like
I'm a little bit worried
About Alex's relationship
Kinship with scripture cuz it's so full of aces
Jesus
Which is the practice of letting your own son
Subjective beliefs and ideas
Seep into the text
Itself as opposed to a exegesis where you take
The text
And you'd approach it from an objective
Seems to really want
The text
To support his worldview
So he inject them into it at
Then interprets
Which is
Sloppy
And malicious
Much closer to militia
Doctor visit
Globalism into the world
Essentially
The argument you know well what I think
Do you say
Is that God would have been cool if you only ate from the capitalist
But then they eat with the
From the goddamn commie Apple to
And that's how we know the
Sure
Again
Even if from the capitalist Apple
Still forbidden by God
Fair enough
Still forbidden by God according to Allen
Eve is not fought through his position
Huge
Pool
It is in his lodge
Sty
Large portion of the show because he didn't prepare his I don't know
Collegiate level course on the bottom of the Rat Hole
Sure Taylor Swift I guess you got a video music award
Speech
He pointed out that a music video there's a
Petition for lgbtq
Atq right
Right
Is criticize China
Fine
Because there's repressive laws about homosexuality
That's all good and well
I guess
But
Because Alex is dumb
He slips up and
Implies something in this next clip
It's Towing
I feel like if you listen to that
Carefully
Alex's
Kind of endorsing locking up
Lgbtq
Tiki people
Because he is
They believe
That's the Chinese
They know not believe know what really
Get you there because it means that we
They know
As we know the reality which is that as there are more of those people.
Yeah absolutely that
They lock these people up
Alex
Conclusion
I think well I think what he's
She's doing is criticizing them
As like
See look they're locking people up just for their non
Informative
Whereas you're criticizing the Trump Administration
It all we want to do is make sure no more if you happen
It's it's
I think he's easy
Difference of degree that I can only describe as
The slightest
It's weird and I think the other thing
Is that he thinks he's criticizing
Policy
The Chinese Behavior
Is offering an explanation for eczema
Horribly
Support of the action
China right with the action is not something to eat
To be interested
Except
A prop
To use against John
Right
Lego
You hate
Neo-Nazi
Is there a divorce
Civilization collapsed
Hitler he would have killed them all
So
Wait are you
Pizza it's a troubling
Directions
Birkenstocks
Your intent
To listen to some of his
Commercials
Because of this
V
Listening to it on the podcast form
The audio stream
That's released you get the Genesis Communications
So you get like still water filtration companies
The sponsors that the network has
Get the cut
But when you watch them on
On the infowars.com
Stream
All you get is Alex
Bulshit
Oh really that's crazy
Some of these commercials were going to listen to you little bit later are
Absurd
But also a lot of them are just
Little shorts videos
They're not even commercials as much as they are like
We just.
Insane
Villa Rebel of non-interest for people who have money
Buying up time on Alex's program
Unheard of
If you're actually advertised
No I don't
Okay if
Kiku
If someone would pay to advertise
Count dankula Meandering
Commercial break
I can't imagine ideas.com
Even if it would be cheaper
Time to buy
50 bucks
Herb dip latest meme
During commercial break
That means that no one will pay Alex $51 advertise products
It's devastating fixer
What's going on
Okay so it didn't surprise me at all that Alex
Descended into a very desperate sales
You're on this August
28th episode
He spends a really long time outlining the new special
Which is if you
You buy some product
For 50% off you get a giant bottle of another product for free
It says
Hey kit
There's even a point
In one of these episodes where he's talking about the special and he's like we're losing money on
If people keep telling me Alex
Stop it it does sound like if his numbers are at all accurate this is
This is bad
Bad sail from the visit
This perspective
Towards the end
Trying to sell this new
New cell
He has another
But he wants to
Makes me
It makes me think of it like
The it's a tough time
Station
Call responses
Sponsor
Advertiser
Your your your your
Your laundry place
On that station cuz we have great
What
Important
When are sales
Your local TV station
It is to support the Mothership
Please
Reach Out
Local station
I've heard him say stuff like this by
Before but not with that kind of desperation
That I feel
Like
Sales pitch
New special
Ratings are not good
At the local station
No one wants to buy ads on those station
Here's Alex signaling that he's in Jeopardy of losing zody's unless people were pulling for him
Separated by ads
Not as a sound financial decision
But as an ideological move to support him
It makes sense why you would think that's a reasonable thing for people to do
The station's program director that he would buy commercial time on the show
It makes sense that he would just assume this is how things
What does this
And that's just trying to get his audience
Do you like artificially keep him afloat because no one's interested in buying ads
If no one
Buying ads
That means there's a large audience
Listening on the station
So I think
I think there's a crunch happen
And it's a little too late from
Start the 60
The movie hatched
Probably
I would say so I don't think he's going to community
Manipulate
It's the
A good plan
I've heard this
Steward of thing from him a lot over the years I can't imagine anyone actually
As ever
Stepped up in the way he's looking for a telephone by billboards
I'm just sending a $20 check
To your local
Is that what like
Care of Alex Jones
Buying those little I donated in your honor things for your birthday but it
Instead it's
Wcg on over the
Yeah it's
Ludacris
And also
Sacrilege
But also wbcr in Tennessee would be my bet for the last station that will ever abandon
So it's them
Feel
From profit or business standpoint
Strong ideological allies
Play the BCM program
Their website is just a bunch of ads for young product
And poorly formatted articles about the evils of
Fluoride
I was thinking about it as I was looking at their website
Feels like this is the future of what Alex is going
To have left
If Trends continue support will be live
Living in those
Those types of presents
If there's a part of me that feels like maybe that is all that ever really was
Behind the glitch
Overproduced
The artificial traffic
Yeah like
Maybe that's all that ever was there behind a facade of
Yeah
All the johnny-come-lately to get seduced and with
Fun conspiracies
Stick around for a little while and then
Get disenchanted need to go to the hardocore stuff or come to their senses
Like once that in and out slow
Disappears
And your left
Just went through Zack
What you doing
I think you just got a lot of buggies that Geo cities ass pages
It comes to mind is
Bottom of a rat hole
There similarities
And it's weird
Them to be eating
Call
And caller expresses
Did you share
A little bit okay
A little bit more worried about that I was
Before
Based on Alex
What is rhetoric
So is what's going to happen when Trump is not around because we know Trump's going to win in a landslide he's waking up a lot of people
Things are happening because of him
But my biggest fear Alex is
What's going to happen when we don't have
You know our commander-in-chief you know and then
What's going to happen after
That's my biggest fear
No you haven't
Aussie idea that you've
Express sometime
Is about
Fear of trump.
Stepping
Not just drop it likes
Trump supporters not accepting
I don't I still think it's a little bit
I don't know not paranoid but a little bit like
No I think there is like a part of it
Could be getting ahead of ourselves
Really Grim predictions about
But
You want to listen to tune in to Alex's show
Sitting here like it just being bandied about between Alex
I'm so if the reality that
Comes about dozen
Match that we've already decided to stolen election
Narrative and rhetoric stand for
I agree with you it's inevitable that that will be the argument Alex
Now too or Trump agrees with that
I think
Will be out of our depth food
Speculate that Alex
Alex has Kaitlin Bennett
Kent State gun girl
Who is turned
To an Alex Jones
Employee
She's on because
I guess
Are you looking today
Okay strong
Don't care
Situation
Apparently Dan Crenshaw
The
Congressperson
He is in favor red flag laws
Forgot
Right and this is a big
Problem sir Alex
Yeswelder
They respect a man who looks like a pirate
Right
A couple days before Alex was screaming about how piker didn't
Show
Crenshaw appropriate respect
Wait wait now you hate
What's going on here
And apparently
Kaitlin Bennett
Said something
And then he
Sandra DM video where she read the DMs
I don't know
Didn't look at the care
I will I will only I will only listen to this if she read it in
Alright
I just
Have a couple of clips
Because I think they're demonstrative
But more important
The first is
Alex doing what he always does
Anyone else has a story that he wants to co-op
Message me
Appreciate
He's trying to piggyback
She has it on her own channel
That's correct
He's doing this
All the f***
So awesome to see every single time
Do I got to use his terms
The attention economy that they're they're they're getting
I just
Infowars is covering it
So in this
Talks about how she
She doesn't mind being
Criticize
She did make a video of about Dan Crenshaw Santa Clara message
But she does not care
About people criticizing her listen to themselves
Certainly not for stretches longer than 30 seconds
I think it's self-contradictory
He's so deep into the
Insult somebody to like
I got silenced because trying to silence
That's cool
Clip she does David she called him a name
Father by me calling him names
Come on
Just stop it
Trying to silence me feel bad
For me
Trying to silence him
And make him feel bad
It's son
I'm not I'm not I'm not coming out in Crenshaw
Nothing but I am going to say
Her go f*** yourself
Stupid
Red flag law a little bit I want to say that I don't believe
Disposition on on
Red flag laws
Which for the most part is
We already have laws in place about like if you say you're going to kill someone they can lock you up
Yeah right I don't believe that position
I don't I don't believe it at all because
Certain things
Vicky uses as examples of like we already have laws in place
Personally don't work
Is there any circumstance
Where in Alex wouldn't
Scream about how this person was being oppressed
Until after the fact
Of them committing
Okay there is no
You like even if someone beat their wife
Are there it's domestic violence
To protect themselves
You did bulshit
Soap
Shootings happen
Trump came out
Better background checks and possibly the
Red flag laws
And Alex is like a don't worry about it
Now
He has a really interesting
Perspective on this
Now
I'll get into it after
What about it
He said
Because it wouldn't do anything
So like a
This is his position here
It's
Like Trump
Red's this bill
And then somehow was like God
We already got it covered
That's the position that you're putting forth
Here
Which seems like a
Problem
Because up till this day
August
Shooting
I was his narrative has been completely
About what Trump did
He tries to present the position
He liked what he was doing
Donald Trump
So there's a shooting and he knew the Democrats wanted to take away
So what do you do
Was he pretended that he was open
2 gun
Registration
Gun regulation
So with that
Is that the Democrats out to the open
They revealed that they wanted to take away everyone's guns and they've been caught
Is Donald Trump has exposed them
As being the gun grabbers that they are and they walk away with nothing that was his
Consistent narrative
Anytime
Trump says about being open
2 gun
Reformed
Did Trump is just trying to Rope A Dope
Position is that Trump was opened a gun reform
Read the Bells
Exact
Okay
Way more sense and also
Exist
Response
The red flag laws
Which makes it troubling
Because I'll be leaving
Himself
Alex makes both arguments on this episode
Listen to this
About
Emotional
This is a completely contradictory s***
He's trying to preserve
Impossible to narratives as to Trump
Response to this gun
Legislation
Like legitimately he is abusing the s*** out of his listener
This is this is not okay believe both
Trumped-up
Trump is
He's got he's got it all wrapped around his little finger alright
In the other scenario
He was just lying
From the jump
I think it was
Situation
And he's trying to manipulate the Democrats into overplaying their hand
In the second scenario though he's just you just read the bill
Position
Zenith
In reality
If you just lie
Sure
That's not mutually exclusive
Another call and this guy is a real real sucking weirdo
But I mean
What else can you
Weirdo
Let me go
I have body armor for your
Would like to have it
What a plot twist
Never happened before
I would love to
To give your employees body armor sound
Call Ana recent
Present-day episode
Dispatched
A team of three
Employees
1/2 to 30
Chance of snow
As far as I know yet
To cover the protest
See something is that he's employees over there but could not remember the
The third person's name
And I'm thrilled to report that he still doesn't
The other self
So rude
Where were the third person is you got to get a new job
Nobody knows your name and you can just take your resume right now and move on over you are
Get out there's time
You are
Please make sure you never learned the others
The damage has not been done
Two years I worked at
Others at Infowars
So put that on your CV
So we have one last call from the 28th and I was taking more calls
Here is really a
Spoiler alert
You get to call her
What's interesting about
Is how Alex response
Reasonably
Thanks for calling around here
Alex this is Adam with no more news. Org I've been one of your biggest fans for 10 years
And perfect topic today to talk about treason in China
Because ever since the rise of trump I really
Studied it deep and realize that all the
Accusations and rumors about you being a Zionist
Apologist
Propagandists are all right and Trump is a completely a Zionist agent
Owned by Edelson a pack.
Bailed out by the Rothschild in the early 90s for billions of dollars with Wilbur Ross
Our Commerce Secretary
He got the top Zionist award in 1983 from the jnf
The Jewish National Fund founded by Theodor herzl
Are you already getting why this is
Is weird
He's not saying anything
No
He's letting this guy talk
You might be chewing
If he's not
Is he okay
Did he stroked out is he staring off into the middle distance
This is what he does with collars like
He wants them
Able to speak their piece
Yeah I don't know why
It doesn't
Feed the need to interrupt them yell at them like he does
With other callers who have
Contentious points
Other collars
To converse about what their topic is interrupt
This is not a natural reaction that Alex has
2 calls
Totally controlled by Netanyahu and Kushner
Trump donates to Kushner who is hibachi donates to Abad
They consider Christianity idolatry
That's who got to Trump support
And you
Blaming everything on China deflecting
From who really is controlling and conquered this country
Is treason George Washington with accuse you of being a traitor and you should be ashamed of yourself
For covering up for who really consideration
I barely think about Israel
Israel
Everybody around Americana
This is just like a
Crazy to me
This is not how he responds to
It's very specifically it to Joy seems like this
I made the other situation
This is totally scripted this whole thing is a f****** fake
No I don't think so
Is b******* not ending
List of Clear Lake
He's not responding to any of Alex at all either this is not how a flute
Sick like the guy from no more news. Org
Alex Jones both of them are
Scripted
Your your conspiracy about this is not something I'm going to support
Evidence of that I'll come around to it I don't believe necessarily that needs
To be true
I could see a situation where someone who holds the believes that this guy does
Could compose himself in order to
Confront Alex in the way that he is
On that call
I don't
Received this criticism enough
That he could have a service boilerplate way he responds to it after the call is done
None of that is necessarily
Indicative to me of some sort
Scripting
What is weird to me is the way that Alex allows him to speak
For over a minute uninterrupted and then at the end
Can I talk
Can I make my point
And is a choice Alex's make
I don't know why he's made
It seems very weird
I don't think it means
He's f******
Supported by Israel or responded by Israel
A shield for the Zionist
Then he wants to deflect this criticism or whatever
I don't know what it is
My working
Siri in the past
Because I've heard this behavior from and before
It's very out of line how we interact
Active callers
My working theory is that he wants
Accusation
Shenzhen criticism
Of him
To look like this
He wants
The perception of
People who don't like him to be
The world
And I understand why that has some utility
It's very weird
Supports my theory that it's
On the other hand the only believe this like this is not a conspiracy theory
Specific
Thing is
Is is b*******
The only other ever the only thing that I would say
Possible Theory here is
How regularly
Talk shows have fake collars
About
I want to listen to I mean listen to the tone of his voice that's a terrible because they supposedly a right
Alex Jones
I don't know
Not the only other thing that I will give you though is this
It is entirely possible
The way Alex
Said
Can I talk now
In such a resigned almost childlike tone
Is that that is exactly how he was berated as a child
And for the longest time that's how his dad would
Would completely come down on how you be like
Can I
Can I talk now
I don't know
The 19th
Okay
August 29th
And Alex
Dim the show by laying out the
Full breath
Of his
Conspiracy
About immigration
He just lets that
Alex spells it out
Border crisis
Will use giant third world population
For 6 months to a year
Literal
Organize them
SMUD
The borders
Other Western Nations where
You are set up to receive
They are deployed
Welfare
And then give them ideas
Driver's license unionized and then weaponizer
Okay
Alright
So
How do I join the subs
Union
Julia local 415
Goodwill
Steal all their buddies got to be touches all of his bases of things he hates
Emigrate
Democrats
Union
Just make sure it's all melange of all that stuff
Smorgasbord
I'm going to I'm going to be brutally honest
It might be partially because I've been a little bit my sleeps
Disrupted
Construction on the building
And maybe
Baby I don't have as much patience as I usually do
Where is maybe I will try it
My response to a clip like that is
Dude that's f****** crazy
Explore the idea of refugee camps beating brainwashing centers
Go f*** yourself stupid
I know they're going to leave them on the border for a while and then they're going to be
Deploy to the left
Union
They're going to take him and give them welfare and jobs
For the
Complicated portrait
Yeah he
You might accuse me of punting
But I'm a no-go fuc yourself
So Alex unionizing sub slaves
Alex says something
Location for his ID
Conspiracy
And what do you know
This is an absolute
By 2050
Resolution
Milia
Our population
Who will be
Uncontrolled
This team's first of all
Unrealistic
Wow
First of all
Know our population
But also like even if it were
I mean
Ridiculous
Just Plumbing
Numerical stay
So what are you doing here is he's just lying about a 2000 report titled replacement migration is it a solution
Declining an aging population
If you notice you look closely
Question
Hypothetical scenarios and looking at ways migration
Problem
Swordigo report
These 600 billion figure comes from an extreme example and hypothetical scenarios raised in the report where low birth rates
Would require large numbers of migrants coming to stabilize the workforce among other population-based societal consideration
There were other scenarios with lower numbers but Alex Jose this one cuz it's the highest that it makes
Morse
Sensational
At no point is this report recommending at no point is it laying out of
Plan it's just a report looking at population-based hypothetical scenarios that goes on to look at whether or not by graichen
Could be part of a solution to a problem
In those situations
Alex is a complete liar
Image of 600 billion non-white
Pictures the story that way
The goal is to create animosity towards immigrants
Doesn't even see them as people with their own motivations anymore but his weapons of the globalist
It's trying to take down the white Western Civilization
And that way is narrative is not only deeply manipulative
Based on lies and betrayal
Presentation
This is all this is about
Sometimes I think the UN has
Contest
To see who can write
The most terrifying
To White
Conservatives
Like they've had so many great well-written like
Question is just a question that
Mirrors the
Deepest darkest
Sphere of
Should migrants replace some of our population
Very sensitive Oak
Preoccupied with
But
There's other news
That the queen
Has allowed
Shutting down of Parliament
At the request of
Boris Johnson
Which
Probably not great ones
You realize all of that is
What some
Simpsons writer wrote
Like not literally but
Pointless calendar
Eventually took over the
F****** UK government
Aynax
And successfully
Garcia
That's banana it's pretty wild
So Alex is a slightly different
Obviously that's behind
But it turns out he likes the queen
No no no
No
No no no no it's a little misleading to say that the queen suspend Parliament
It's more the case that Boris Johnson
Okay
That's kind of parole though it is ceremonial
She began to legitimately meddle in the Affairs of government directly real problem
The Monarch is rolls like appointing the Prime Minister but that doesn't mean that the queen just gets to choose whatever she wants
Does prime minister hope you f***** up
Johnson's request for probably lead to a greater likelihood of a No Deal brexit
Disastrous outcomes for the British economy
Way out of line for her to not except
Because he's the head of
Experts consulted by the BBC said quote impossible for the queen to turn down the price
Service request
Like literally for heard of rejected the request would have led to a whole different conversation about the return of monarchic rule
I would have said a horrible president
Really would have been
Like it would have been really funny
Speaking well
Because from my position
I'm looking at this and I'm seeing that in the very recent past very clearly that the queen and her in Thai
Lydia
Of a decade-long the One World Government
They're legitimately
Evil incarnate
And every single thing you said about the
British royal family
Has been over the top
And cartoonishly skating
Did he him now be like that.
It's an absurd narrative shift that you tell anyone
All of this up as he goes along the very end of her life
All of those
Blood
Fusionzone
Adventure acknowledge
And Trump
And The Patriot
Send a picture
It's so weird
I thought that might just be a throwaway like now
Talk about we're supposed to kill the queen two episodes ago
Probably
A blues track
Arrestor
But I also think that was in 2013
I thought
Your queen
But
He does get back to it a little bit later
So
He first
Needs to
Like I said the beginning resep
Alex's Behavior was
Is it all
Notable after Trump insulted Fox News
Animed
An indication
Shinto like we need a new outlet which does open up
Space for Alex
I would have thought that maybe you'd be able to
Lucy some indications
And there's not much
But Fox News does come up
Interested
In Trump's
Thick shiting on
I want that
Confronted by Fox host about criticizing the network
Except for 45 host on there
Because they're planning
You ready
Person test
Election
So are you
Sure
So I don't
See him being all that interested in the actual conversation the tap
About Fox News
Which seems to be almost
The best ploy
The smoothest play which is out of character for
Yeah
Is interest
Could you have expected you would have expected him to
Either have gone
So far in the bootlicker direction of like
Job I'm right here for you
Or two
Dancing on the grave of Fox News
This kind of situation is forever and
Right there eventually but it's
Cuz you should be
Yeah based on everything about is prior actions
Weird
Ever three people to whom he remembers their name
To Hong Kong
There's another person in Hong Kong
Others Paul Joseph Watson
Goddamnit what was he
I think
Vagina
It's a pretty consistent thing that I don't care about people's personal lives
So I have not looked into Paul Joseph Watson
Some personal life at all but I remember Alex saying
Explain
He's on
And he has a little bit of
An angle
On the
The situation
And
I think that this is really indicative of how Infowars is covering
The protest
Ridiculous partisan bickering
Societies largely United
Behind the protests
Against
Migration
Which is super sing that Society
It was a lie
He said quote
They drain our resources
Making it increasingly
With this Mass migration from the Middle East and North Africa
Is being friends
The China as a result of this Mass migration
So
Just tried to
Twist my arm into a f******
Principal pretzel with that
Stupid
Ill-informed
Nonsense Aztecs
Actually really enjoy
Really sums up Infowars
Position on the protest in Hong Kong
It's purely an attempt
The Coop the protest
Interbeing about their Marquee issues
Their number events
Instances of this throughout the episode their coverage of the Hong Kong stuff
Videos
That's just like I was getting kicked off
Do you know there's instances like that but I think that this is the clearest cut one where you can see the duplicitousness
And the manipulation
The people in Hong Kong have complained about people from mainland China coming to Hong Kong in a road in their political autonomy
Alex and Paul Joseph Watson scream all day but the UMP
Invading masses of third-world refugees
To come to the United
States in order to brainwash them
People voting against Alex's preferred political
It doesn't take too much examination
The massive
Have them between those two arguments
The close enough
Did you blur the edges
You can create a narrative that
Yeah if you know nothing about either
I mean they're basically just trying to
To take
Big similarities
And try and turn it into like
Play how they're covering it which is one of the reasons why even if
You support
Protests in Hong Kong
You still can survive without
Now.
Call
Things you agree on
Because bigger
Trying to use
They are always
Yes always
Always
So we get to we get back to the queen
Now and Alex
Has
A position on this that I
Pink is unhealthy
More
That's
I feel like that's an unhealthy
This is worse
He's trying to
To start a new world war
Bestbuy.com
McLeod
Forced labor camps
Spending
The first time
Hundred
Just happened
Signify
Biker
Constellation
Resistance
The power structure
The axis
Estates
Doughboy
And how those gruesome fight
As well
Looking now
The brakes are happening
Directions of recited
Wheels
Trump knows that
New World War this year
Military
Russia will sit on the sidelines
Alex Walter World War
Specially for like
He's running out of gas also worth noting
Appealing
United right by
I don't know why he wouldn't
Based on every other thing he's ever said in his
F****** life
He wouldn't think that another world war was also orchestrated in order to create something on the other end of it
Careers
Wyatt why is your cynicism gone now why is your skepticism gone
I was blown away
Because I had that moment while he was listening to
Is he
Sing the queen over
It's not like she
She's just that
And then I was like oh no
Is looking at boats and decided that
It was right
He's just a weird old lady with a lot of that I think he either thinks that
He knows the reality but he thinks
Narrative
We flipped the queen
Is much better for him because it's better for the
American Patriot
Subverting Parliament
Never been done in 400 years
That's not good
So the question of how long it's been
And something like this is
Define what happen
Technically Parliament is disbanded basically every year for a break
Boris Johnson is arguing that that's all of this
That's clearly a live by the pro No Deal brexit
Supporters
It's business as usual
Is the longest Parliament would have had since 90
E-40 calls at the end of World War II
What's interesting is Alex's using the brexit people's position in terms of
But he's also wrong about it being 400 years ago
Alex is referring to what happened back in 1629
When King Charles the first dismiss Parliament
They shouldn't be using that as an example of what's going on now
Since it totally works against
Does argument
Charles dismiss Parliament because he believed that he had a divine right to be the sole ruler
The bike's tension what's going on according to Alex
This should be seen as a coup
And a return to a democratic system
But oh well isn't favor brexit
It's our The Narrative WorkSource f******
Then I go to bed
Even without that historical
Go Contacts
He should see this is a COO
He's a demon
Right
This actually give him
Reason to pause and be like maybe I'm on the wrong side
What is radius
Position
Conception of this is
Vista
Creature who sucks
Blood of children
Is creating One World repressive system is all of a sudden pretty cool with me
What you're doing
Yeah I know I said a lot about it and that breakfast
Great toe
We got
The birth
This to me is why this is so important
That indicates so strongly
That none of the things he's ever said
About the queen about the monarchy
Wow bikes
Arizona
Years that I would normally wouldn't
But the only reason I am only 10 years old
But the only reason I am is because Alex made a big deal of the big
400 round
If you're going to say
He said it's a big round number means
Providence
Is not true
List of numbers
420 years
From our position Alex should believe this is
And not Democratic thing
Sure
It is
She's just doing exactly what ceremony demands that she otherwise
I'll be f***** up it would lead to better conclusion possibly
Right
The complete British government code
It would be in Simpsonville there is no good
Solutions in forest
There is a ridiculous.
Alex should be strongly against
Send
He knows
Fit what she's doing
Isn't it
There's a bunch of pedophiles
Salute
What
Just flipped her dictator switch
And so she just dropped
This is his story
All I got to say so
Going to be spectacular
The world
Structure
Two fronts
I will side with the last
Hughes
Also pitching this as a war against Islam
And all that
The
Alex fields
But there's a holy aspect
To this new world war
Right
Unhealthy
Yeah
Well we've never had people who thought that way
Forever
It's also a position you've really really don't like to hear out of a staunch isolationist
Intervention
Paul guy
Get involved in Florida
I want to World War
I don't even know what
What to say about
Someone who's
Putting forth position
Not just
Advocating
For a World War
About the prospect
Because he is
We got our side now it's just like those other world wars
No one died in
Craziest
Almost done 11
It's so callous
Yeah
It reminds me so much of a
Patton Oswalt joke about
Wouldn't you want to die
Apocalypse
You know I don't want to know how did you die over the super boring but apocalypse
That kinda
Are you really does want to die in the epochal
That's because then he's a
He's one of the final men
So in this clip
The episode
From break and really get into
The situation with the queen
Solve that Queens
Just leads me to believe
A deal with the EU
Control
We got to get Lord mantra.
Why do they
Anymore
So we can still get monster
Probably
So
I mean
The idea that this is like
Queen decree
Situation
Amanda presentation of it as they did this to have more time to negotiate
Is also
The completely out of line with every reading
I've had about this
Every person who's no one
Is presented
Results
It's a clear attempt
To sabotage
Negotiation
Cancel the part of
Boris
He is allowed to speak in public without
For lying
Straight Talk
Like what
Like everything that you said about why they're doing that
So bald-faced
Like he might as well have a
The sign that says I'm lying directly above his head while he says
You should
Try harder the
Stay out
I told you that's the last normal
Surreal
How to play I told you earlier
Amazon Play commercial
The real commercial
Episode
We've been seeing this
Trend in the
Upsetting like I want American expansionism to come back right
Buy Greenland
Who cares anyway it's on there
12 million dollars
You have
Just like real domestic problem
The way you sees the United
Red State
And now you're seeing
The Hong Kong protest
And then after
The same time
Encouraging and supporting
Phrasing the idea of Another World War
Damn you just have like
One of the most
Bucked up
Autoline dude
Episode
Like just bouncing back in
Fourth from
Firearm
Political alignment
They are co-opting
A protest against
Oppressive authoritarian regime
To prop up
Their preferred oppressive authoritarian regime
Supporting protesters
Ostensibly wallet
At the same time
Supporting
A return to a monarchy
In the UK
His perception of the ACT
It's her not
Interfering
Government inappropriately
Pushing the dictator button but what I'm saying is we're just bouncing around from different angles on oppressive
Authoritarian regime
Depending on Ultimate Lee doesn't matter to him he wants
Authoritarianism
He just wants it to be
Is China in the middle right
In order to achieve that I guess
To do with anything other than they don't look like
Don't feel like there's much more going on
So
The last we leave with that bitter pill
Still lingering on our tongue
I present to you George
A commercial that Alex has
For his new Proto
Bars
This
Is so f***** up
I mean
I honestly understand that this is an attempt to be funny
And there's a portion of me that thinks like this is kind of funny
You'll see you'll visit
Well today then poured high protein bar
I just put Ballard your cousin in 45 protein bar
I need
Walmart tires Walmart
I can't hear anything other than a response to our theme song
Either that or he's gone
No way
Pictures of problems with that
He would never buy into that b*******
Japanese
Sharp edge
The big the big joke that he has in there I guess
Is
Looking at
Your cousin
It's the bars cuz I love that so much is a complete non sequitur
In context
When I hear that
A couple times
Just goes
It was bizarre plays a couple times
The thing is like
If you really listen to it
They couldn't admit that
Put it together without some clips
Free sounds
Completely dry
So f***** up
I generally thought they were
I'd like altering the audio
I think in order to make it match whatever but like
I'm good
And then also if you watch the video of the commercial
It's the same thing with that that clip with him drinking the bone broth what he looks
Disgusted by it out of the protein bar
Like
A person enjoying approach
Kevin it's like how much protein
Todd look at it
Greens or whatever
12 to 20 g of protein
I hearing the words Infowars protein bar I'm like
You can't make a thing out of that much protein
75 G protein
All it is is a muscle muscle
It's called the constipation
Delicious vanilla
I feel little bit qualms with playing that even
Gmi2
I'm not threatening its kind of awake
Penetrate
When did that is
Little bait on the hook
But at the same time
Desperate for any memes
Promoting himself
So many Avenues are blocked off to him
He's become so inundated in this
Weird memes
Kind of sphere
This is what you
Forced to do
I know you look older
You're still 45
This is
Becoming Behavior primble 4508
Sounds exactly like a Japanese
Commercial that John Travolta would have started right
Before you baby
Is comeback in Tulsa
You know whenever is like
You're losing your hair
You're not going to make it
Go to Japan do a couple commercials get a quick cash out and then come back and
Tarantino robot
From
Don't think this is moving protein
I just put more protein in
Nice bar
Through
Exhausted
We survived in one piece
Passionate about
This
Stretch of time
I don't feel all that
Like interested in it it's not
Yeah
Alex is not into
All that much
Department
That's a part of it
He's just a razor Superior rating into like
A complete monster but I already know he's a monster
So
Much revelation
End of
Nothing
Co-op these
These protests
Pretty f*****-up
To misrepresent
Queen
It's f***** up in the sense that it reveals so much about how little is narratives mean
Change it like the Rothschilds could become good
Right
Just one day's work
1 days worth Rothschild's could be rehab
And Alex is a narrative
There's that I guess there's some value to that but
I don't know
I need a
Alex
Consider this
Editorial note
Future
But we will be back
So we have a website
Twitter is well is that knowledge underscore I was just going to roll through dojo
We're also
Groggy
We also download
You can listen
Angeles on Spotify
If you would like
How to get Spotify
I generally
Have to go to a
Fairy ring
In the forest
Show me to get the
Correct number of mush
Around you
Play VI
First
And 9 sin
Clockwise
Is Manor
Spotify
Absolutely
Good luck with
Failings at iTunes
I'm Neo I'm Leo
Jesus
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work