I have great respect for knowledge but I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
MoneyGram
Stripe.com
Fix it around Beverages and talk a little bit
About Alex
What up
What is sum
Do you know what I mean we could go with
The Evangelical form of Christianity around those Corners a little too long
How long did you stick around
Pretty deep
Bistro number
I don't know if it's a little late
Yeah probably 1516
I was involved in like a life
Other Church organization
Sermon planning
Urban Planet
I was helping with soundboards for the group sermon
I was not musically but it was on the little skit
Oh my God
Yeah I was in
Camp kanakuk
Looking back it was probably just as clunky is there
Yeah I know I think I believed in
Not that so much I don't look back on believing in the religion
Impart as negatively
MVA
Pacific Church in
The people around me
I believe
I believed in that
Dulong
For sure
And I've also
Started Alex Jones I guess that's applicable
Butter
Disturbingly similar about about religion
Back in the past
82013 I think this
That's how I will be very
Holiday
What is Labor Day
On March 28th
We'll make
Massive progress
Today I raise my eyebrows at you
Before we get to that we could take
People have signed up
Reporting show so first of all
Thank you so much you and I'll probably walk
Directions
Oh boy
Next
Senior
Persuasive
Thank you so much you are now about to walk
Quinn
And I also thank you
You are all that I got to give it up
Everyone I guess I mean
Who signed up on an elevated level appreciate it very much so
Steven thank you so much
Thank you so much you are all now wonderful technocrats
Freakishly large
Sure we would
Big Stuff head of us
Just maybe you're shorter episode cuz I don't have money clips
Bulk clips
We make up for in
Big Time stuff
Alex starts out the 27
Not that important
The other
Tremendously important
The first
Letter board
Coming up today on this Wednesday
Website.com
Streaming video ad prison planets
God TV
We are going to be taking your phone call today Professor Griff
How are the founders of Publix
Call turn our
Other systems that are used
Not important
Professor Griff comes in and talk about the 13 Bloodlines of the Illuminati
Alright it's a lot of esoteric
So that's not important
No I doubt
Now what is it for
Is Alex's other
We are also going to be
Talking to Steve pieczenik today we can get him on
Fortunate
It's taken months
Love listening to these episodes
Professor Griffin the professor of propaganda on the same show
2 of amerikaz Most Wanted the same motherfuking place at the same motherfuking time
Professor Griff dr. Steve pieczenik
Angel dat opinions that Steve pieczenik is
The reason that Alex believes
I am crisis actors narrative in Sandy Hook
He's been something that I have
Thought about probably
Right
Steve pieczenik is somebody who is Lord Alex down terrible roads repeatedly throughout his career
Makes sense
Likes
Since we do know that he is a crisis actors guy
Hurricane
Yeah you are rude
Steve pieczenik showing up on Alex's show in 2013
It seems to me you like that's where things are going to go bad
March 27th
Steve pieczenik makes his first appearance on the Brock
About the first-ever
Parents that is going
Have you
Fist up in the air going like I finally got one.
Stingrays
So episode Alex's on some narratives
His big one
Is that he's found a story
Wired about press releases
And how this is going to spiral out of control
Complete
He's Aggies game
IRobot
Square
Original
House Press Corps
You will never be
It's just a video simulations
No it's interesting
You know Trump is
Kick a lot of people out of the press the room
I just wrote down for the list
I love my authoritarian leader he's got to kick him out there making snide comments
Also this hasn't happened
Easily imagine
Scenario where Alex is like
Of course Trump sends a hologram to his rallies ass
Realistically
Say it's very close to Alex being completely
I don't know how much
Answer is to the ID
To make a holographic Obama
Time is
Does not appear to have happened
Sure
Play takeover and
Control the Earth
Otamatones will become the actual president
When they have those when they're running everything they're going to need their own
For people to walk well
A cyborg suit
Switch the Holograms
Obama's going to be in there
Call it nailed it
Alex male that's what I'm going to give it to him 100
Ze starts rambling and spiraling out
And you know like the
Holographic president
Pre-recorded
Speeches and all this stuff is
Fight back now
For these
Deserve whatever
Because if
You don't
Your dad
That's
Argument
And then relies on
What I would call Shawty
Emerge
Communication satellites
Commander
You all worship Lucifer
Okay 2001 Space Odyssey Books
All the way up to number 3 which I believe is 2003 space
Absolutely so good
Good good
Good good Eva
So far
80s movie villain
Volleyball
That's why I
Classic volleyball movie
Exactly
Freedom
Yeah
But how all of this goes
Intervallic saying something
We know this because of the revealed plan in X science fiction movie
It would get sad
Quite frankly
It never takes into account like
What about all the other things
Person wrote
Like what about
To be so clunky
That's wild
I'm really surprised that
Is it have we never
Harris
How to be a guest
Maybe a gas problem
OneStop hair
Yeah I know that I have
And it makes me think that a guest probably brought it up I don't remember Alex talking about it a lot
But
So this isn't the Project Camelot
Kerry Cassidy
Over Project Camelot
Alien
Are working for the reptilians
A little worker bees that run around people and terrifying
And all that good stuff
And the reptilians are the bad guy
Author Richard bad guys
The Big Bang
Different
Computer-assisted telepathy
And the graves are humans from the future
As far as I understand from highest-level Luminati information
What salon near today
What the f***
Aliens in movies are in Illuminati conditioning device in order to make you think that that's what we will be
In the future of boy right now
That is not real
Bright based on everything I've read
High-end the Illuminati releases
I would love for him to provide this high-level Illuminati document
Or whatever that
To be available
Actually is childhood's end
Great
Alex you know he's talking about all this
This kind of you know this 2001 Space Odyssey
Gray aliens are
You know the Illuminati believes
XYZ
He doesn't believe us
You need to give himself the video of rationality
Behind the
I don't believe in stuff
I don't necessarily believe the community
He's giving the plants that I will yell about that all the time because you believe
So he gets into a little bit of that
Is it going to achieve this
Geologist
Takashi
Force
Beautiful people
Shq Wells I just quoted
His book The New World Order
Arthur Schlessinger
Okay
Set me up
Quote that Alex misuses
From HG Wells book The New World Order it all the time
Constantly
It's almost as if you only read this one
Paragraph that book
Not understood it and decided the ideas
About the world and the misunderstanding
In discussing how he observed
The world was generally towards greater social
H.g. Wells
Nor doesn't alter the fact that even when the struggle seems to be drifting definitely towards a world social
There may still be very great valeza disappointment
Before it becomes an efficient and beneficent worlds
Countless people from Maharaja to millionaires
Is a pukka sahib
The pretty ladies
Will hate the New World Order be rendered unhappy by frustration of their passion
Vision
Through its Advent and will die protest
When we attempt to estimate its promise we have to bear in mind that the
Distress of a generation or so of malka
Many of them quite gallon
And graceful looking
The list of people who sang will be against social democracy
They are the very top of the prevailing social hierarchy
The millionaires King
Colonialist
Aristocrats
When Wells make reference
What's 2 gallon
Can people he's
Expressing the feeling that monsters are not always grotesque
And often actually beautiful
Alex seems to think
The passages about him
Self
Express in the sense that eventually Patriots would show up
The counter these nefarious playing
He's putting out
And these Patriots would be Gallant
And really hot
Legends perfect was Alex's self-design pathology but it doesn't match
Wells is making
At all
Much like Alex is interpretation.
Scripture this is an active eisegesis
And it only makes sense if you understand the Alex read the paragraph
Support for the things that
We already believe
This pattern along with tons of other behaviors
Galaxy terrible socio
Terrible anthropologist
Terrible psychologist
And terrible historian
They're all labels he has no business giving
The biggest one that was missing
Is literary
He doesn't really it's
Himself for everything
Could be applied to
I'm a sociologist
Psychologist Astorian apologist I am also illiterate
So I just fine I tried that too
Be so fascinating
Level
Hear that
Opposing forces
How to kill all of us but we have to be done
Completely out of line
With the with what wild
Also
It however him
Sing with an exactly what
He is bad
Millionaire going to die
Miserably Amy Wells wrote The Millionaire meant a lot different
They Alex's ascribing to him
Himself
Hi social
But he probably doesn't Merit like
Compared to Maharaja millionaires
He's nowhere near that level no
Beep beep beep
Himself in that conversation
Also has a
Specific connotation like high-end socialite
Aristocrat
Malcontent
Yes baby
The very thing that would improve his
That is true
To be in Avid
Some calls here on this show
To talk about how the Catholic Church
Wants his gun
If you listen carefully
He gives a citation
For some of his belief
It's deeply drop
Nobody I know of so far has
Responded to an article that
February 25th at an article
Any dirt America or Catholic America magazine
An article on the 25th of February issue
Actually have a nautical new that I read
If they are going to repeal the 2nd Amendment
I'm a nobody
Respond to
Vatican of Rome doing this or any other
Stop talking about
Vatican release
Over the over the years
Roommates the American Constitution
Proven also by failing get ahold of through baby Chick Publications called
50 years
I don't know if Alex did actually scan around on XM and find a Catholic Channel but this isn't
Like a fake thing this actually is real
Yeah it was an op-ed published in the castle
Look magazine America
Who's going to ever have sensible gun laws
If we repealed
This wasn't necessarily call to outright ban
Gunn it's more of a realization that the Second Amendment absolutely gets in the way of any conversation about
So possibly debate where people were still able to preserve
Ownership that we would also be able to fix some of the problems
Is it a come along with
The ubiquity of God
Yeah it's kind of a sensible position
Controversial
Come from a religious magazine
Definitely not something I would call
Scandalous
The writer the editorializing grappled with the reluctance of people to alter laws
Particularly ones
But ultimately those are just laws written by and passed by human
If they were passed in one Circle
Answer those circumstances
Consider changing the laws
Good Roboto
Probably more troubling to
And that call is the fact that the caller is also citing a book that is put out by chick
Publication
The business run by Jack
He's got to put those little cartoon pamphlets full of gross
Grotesque depictions of Chris
Christian fundamentalist ideas it's pretty clear
It is now it makes
Fancy I got you
It's all there
Those exist
Primarily a cc
Exclusively
To scare the s*** out of
If they strafe
From the fundamental
Chick tracts run the gamut of Christian issues
You're going to hell if you get an abortion
You're going to go to hell if you have sex drugs
All the stuff YouTube
But Jack Chick was also a
C tablet
A constantly rails on Vatican
So this article is being brought up real article making a point that will be easy for Alex
Manipulate
Church
Zippo price every articles are those
It's worth pointing out that the sewer people in
Discussing the article is
This way
From my perspective here it seems
To be someone who's also into Jack
Check which is pretty bad that is a bad sign
Now
Have you heard have you read the one about calling
Propaganda
Well it really only positive
Scares children
Wanting to call in to REI
Tower with Professor Griff
Fundamentally not worth
Going over
Mostly about a book that was written by a guy
Professor
To be former
Netflix
Confirmation of it
He has a bunch of s*** about the Illuminati
The other stuff I've heard Professor Griff's
In past appearances
I don't even want
I just let them talk
Have fun guys because
And that my bigger fish
Is the man the myth
Steve pieczenik
Most of the interview was actually pretty boring
Alex wanted to have him on to talk about how the bin Laden
Killing was fake
Right and how do thing
Rite Aid
Osama Bin Laden dead forever
You have him on
To talk about
Steve Howey
Namely that Zero Dark Thirty sucks
He's very mad about Zero Dark Thirty
And I don't think we really need to get into that either that's sort of
The film review
Fair enough
So
Purview
What do you know
Sandy Hook
Surprise
Gary speed
Put
Talking about Sandy
I told you and I didn't tell you but how you said very clearly
That is very important right there until you
I told you I didn't tell
I told you and I didn't tell you but I very clearly there's no question
My mind after I damn in Sandy Hook
Individual
Play what's a Woman by 100 million dollar contract
Call Hunger Games with post apoplectic
She didn't say a damn word
Irish Catholic
Increasing union pension
Stanchion of executive power
So that
Pretty up blonde
He is very much
The crisis actor narrative
Express tan Alex's show
It's because Susan Colin
Wrote The Hunger Games
Yang Chow
Yeah that one
Heard him say Susan
There's no reason to throw that in there and then
In the back of my mind
OSHA
That's right
Brought the Hunger Games
I know first this is what year
Yeah that's not good
So on February 12th 2013
Steve pieczenik posted a Blog
Entryway
I can say with certainty that at least by that point
February 12th
Steve is absolutely Advantix
It's rooted in the fact that he credits himself as an author of Tom Clancy's books
So he knows a bit about fiction writing
The story of Sandy Hook struck him as a poorly-written
Piece of fiction
So when he found out that Susan Collins
The author of The Hunger
This explains everything
Suffice it to say this is not convincing stuff
Tracing back to January 22nd
Steve posted on his blog
I'll be posting later tonight but here's some homework if you're interested
Something does not smell right about the Sandy Hook thing
Inconsistent
You keep nagging
Especially when I start comparing them to other events in Rio
History...
Who does that sound like
The way Alex
Constantly Compares Sandy Hook at all of his feelings about it to Aurora
Event from recent history
I don't know
Seems weird yeah
I have every reason to suspect that Alex knows with Steve
At this point has been publicly accusing V survivors and victims of Sandy Hook of being actors
I need someone Alex knows and respects
It just doesn't track the idea that Alex would think that Steve is a
Intelligence operation
Weather blog
Current affairs Alex doesn't that block
It's possible but if that's the case then it's a really good at piece of evidence that Alex doesn't do nearly the amount of preparation that he want
If you read the discovery request
In the lawsuit that Alex is facing for his recovery
A couple of things stick out
They're obvious pieces of things they're looking for like
Request for all the materials involved in Sandy Hook crisis actors anything involving Wolfgang halbig
But then when you get to item number 3
The plaintiffs request
Quote all documents and or Communications
Between you and any of the following individuals or anyone acting on their behalf concerning any of the topic
Text listed
They're only two names
James Tracey isn't on there
Wolfgang halbig isn't on that
It's only Steve pieczenik
And Jonathan Wright
Reich was a twenty-six-year-old dude got arrested for harassing Sandy Hook families as well as the County Medical
He hasn't shown up on Alex's show or had any mention
Browse I think that's because he doesn't get arrested until May
If I recall correctly
Every March
There may not be any reason for Alex
Text to Noble
There's a longer list in item number for request for communications regarding appearances on Infowars
Which includes both of those two dudes and some of the other likely
We suspect a gang
The Reich
Steve pieczenik
Are the only
Only two people
Requested all Communications
Concerning
Be covered top
Based on what I've been able to suss out for listening back to these episodes
It appears that the plaintiffs may have the same working theory that I'm coming
Namely that Steve is communicating with Alex
Behind the scenes
Leading to a shift in
His coverage
From my position but this is not nothing
When Paul Joseph Watson interview James
Tracy about the crisis actor
Ethereal little while back
They were at least
Trying to be explicit about not endorsing his ideas
Paul Joseph Watson had to list off a ton of disclaimers and caveat about how he doesn't agree with this guy
No not too much longer after this point
We have our first dance
Survivors were all actors with no pushback
And actually excitement from Alec
And that's someone
Steve
Other than like a spray collar that Alex might have gotten
No one is Express
This Theory
On the show
And anyone who has has gotten at least
Stomp performative pushback
Alex's Grill
With Steve bring this up
It almost gives him the ability
To cover this now
Steve is giving him that
And I'll say this
If you go back and you look at a bunch of
To like these
These blogs that are sort of a line
Patriot ideas and stuff
The day after this
There are tons of articles
About Steve pieczenik appearing on Alex's show and sayings
Saudi idea Alex
Had a hand in really amplifying and legitimizing
These ideas
If this
Is
The beginning of it
And the kernel of it
He presents Steve pieczenik
Like as an absolute expert in everything
He's overthrowing governments
Psyop expert
He's been olivitos everything is part of the
Lcfr but he left because he was
Disgusted
Having him on allowing this to
Be sad
Uncritically
And with no pushback and infect celebration
Steve's Kombat
Does a
Mastiff
Piece of work
In terms of legitimizing
The a crisis actors Theory
Did the role that Alex plays
Even if it is a little bit
Delayed
Inasmuch as these theories are floating around on the internet
Conspiracy forums
I mean almost
Immediately
This piece of work
Is terrible
This doesn't severe amount of
Well now
I'm kind of lost
Cuz I didn't know that
Steve pieczenik
Fiery hen
Written
4 time
Is there Ghost Rider Ghost Rider
Has ghost written one book
If that part
Is true
Then I can only assume that
Susan Collins
Cuz if if a
Then be must
Be true as well
It's Shawty stuff and one of those things that I've learned from
This
Like looking at Steve's blog is that he does not write how he
Detox
Controlled measured
There's a
Almost
I don't know
There's a
Elevation
Into the waves
Speaking
On his blog it's just full of like bold letters and all caps and like
Pictures of the Photoshop pictures of
Robin Obama in homosexual
It's ludicrous blog
The only know Steve
From his appearances on Alex's show
Rambling
Nonsensical blog post
Poorly formatted just b*******
It's very weird
It's all called
Isn't the question
How much
Of his presentation on Alex's show is a put on
To make him seem more rational or reliable as a source
As opposed to where he has full
Control over what he's putting out
He stops having a
An audience
Tinfoil hat
And we start
That was troubling
That was the trouble
And here's Alex
So you want
Come back on
About this
Thank you very much.
Is it
I would definitely say that that's
The show is going to be
Be far more hardcore
As time goes on
Consider this
Yeah I'm thinking
About this
Experiences
Surreal to me
Because with the awareness that I know that the Boston bombing
Is happening
So many of Alex's narrative
We've so perfectly into that
Confluence
Of of that
Like I just
Frames
About to run into
To each other
And I can see it
There's nothing you could do it
The past
I'm getting really
Anxious
A little bit yeah
It's troubling
No no no
Disaster
Yeah probably
Alex has Devon
For rent that you know this
Clearly articulated
Sandy Hook
Was actor
There was totally fake
And it's
You know I was really wondering is like March
28 is going to be
Floodgates open
The first hour of the show is just Alex saying he's going to
Take calls all day
The whole show
How old is Cher
Betty Rambles about
Nothing
He's just going on and on about how he's not a fear monger and all that kind of standard s*** that he yells about
I honestly kind of think he's vamping
Is it really feels like you wanted to go to calls
Because he had a
Prepared for the show but no one is calling it
Standard and uninspired
Yoox
Where he does like Bob pontificate about whatever it's honestly one of the worst episodes of the show that I've ever had to listen
Intuit just so Bland
It's so Bland
It's so petty
It's still manipulative
Just it is a very
Lame
Certainly
So the first the first flower is just
Doesn't get to Costco
I think it's if he is
Pieczenik was riding out
I imagine every line of dialogue
And ironic
Adverb
He said the fear-mongering Lee
Like that's the only way you could write that
You're going to die
Twosome race memory
In his ramble hour
Isabelle
And I think in this next clip out
Kind of admits that
He's just making
Route to Bleed It Out
Doesn't spoil you butcher it yourself
You cook it yourself
You're thinking about that
Synapses
Experience
Race memories
And just doing
Willow
After someone's written
Well
Literally communicate
I've never read any of this
It's just an idea I've got milk
Refuse
Simultaneously Alex will say that science has proven all of this stuff
Like literal connections
I don't I don't believe that
I do believe that he's just making this stuff up and it's maybe an experience
That he's had with his weird brain
Of eating
Alright I kill
Ore-Ida
Find it pretty fascinating how plans
Watching them
Seedlings
Do the almost full grown
It's pretty it's pretty wild
The tiny little ceu denial hot plant
I don't
I could see how if I had a very very weird brain
I could
Really
Turn that into
Transcendent experience
I don't think
We'll use a Dungeons & Dragons
Who's playing
Cosplay
I mean I thought about 1 but I thought about it and that means
He's written it down
Experiments self-evident
Okay
You got to you got to grow plants
What's the number to connect to your ancestors
Is true just because it
It's true
But the globalist don't want you to do that
That's why they put rules in place
Agriculture I guess
GMOs
It's not only that
And in this next clip Alex fake
Fix crying
While discussing how is
Crying is always very real
Which
Is another this is not the first time
Which makes me think he's absolutely
B b
Fastest
Social engineering
Is to break
The genetic encoding recordings
Connection
The stars in our true destiny
Hard to kill deers
Plant seeds in
Space
Spaceship
Alright Alex shut the fuk up
Gwyneth Paltrow
In literally any
Why does he not care about like tribal cultures
If you so into this like
Connection with ancestors
Shouldn't he respected in non-white populations
Also they have a vanes Lee if he was going to
Just do a bunch of
I would almost guarantee
Somewhere inside there you resent made of
Tribal popular
For having
More of a Kinect
Maybe in there somewhere
Ayahuasca
Yeah that's Ludacris
Such fake crying and then additional
You know why
People don't want
People fighting
Assault
Yeah I think you're you're infringing on people's right to not be beaten up
Outlaw
What street
Right
Ludacris
Sweetly untethered
From any kind of
Semblance of his show being a show
Like really does
I can't stress this enough
It feels like he doesn't have another
Like there aren't anybody calling in
He has no news to cover
I feel that way
Part of it was
This is me writing a story
But the day before and he is dropped
Alex
About that maybe you
Really freaked out for the rest of the day
No can't sleep
Just too excited about the possibilities
I have an expert who's apart of my shows
Wack Pack
Ready to go this MI
We could tap into this market now and I have some plausible deniability that it seems
I can point to
Credible experts
I'm just
They're saying
Just dressing
Nothing
Said this.
But this made me laugh pretty hard
Alex makes
Proclaim
That
Man just think about this
In the context of like
He's still doing
His show
6 years after that
I'd screaming
All the time
About his enemies
Those of you to see by this I I don't even hate you anymore
Friend
I'm disgusted by these people
He's trained globalist
Intermediate
Yeah I remember
Poultry songs
I'm pretty sure that
So you can get that it is a warm
I don't believe that
I don't think there's any
I think that's crazy but it's also like
I think that's funny
Just as an idea that
But that's also really funny
This is what he's doing instead of take
Call
Calls to go to what
This is 40 minutes
But he has every reason
2 knots
Pretending he's reached his Zen state is battle
It's
It's pretty crazy
This one guy
McCall's in
Interesting because Alex
What are last recent
Mi presente episode
Alex said that he was going to come in
Studio and talk about what's at the bottom of the rabbit hole
Yes
Good like what the f*** did you say you were gave us our the rabbit hole this is 6 years in the past
Losing my ability
Alex dropped the ball and fumbled on his plans to tell you about the bottom of the rabbit hole
Alex what's at the bottom of the rabbit hole us no like you talk all the time about these Horrors
These terrible things
What it what are you talkin about
Alex has no answer for
He Rambles a bit
I think he feels like well I got to do something
I got to give some answer
Eva Maddox
It's wild
This is what the bottom of the rabbit hole Georgia
Home
The rabbit hole
You see what you see in Japan
Outside of baby diapers
In the world
And and and inventing machines everywhere
Open right now
Underwear
And with the picture of the woman
End
Earthquake
Wow
Questions and then we go back to the past and get the answer
Man I wish we didn't get that at there's an interesting dialogue that's happening across the temper
Coral space
This is pretty f****** stupid
I would say
Oh you know what's at the bottom of the rabbit hole
Yep that's about
Japanese
Diapers that are
Fully loaded Reloaded
Herbie this is obviously exaggeration
His world
I read an interesting article on the website Tech in Asia where they look at the bottom
Well kind of besan racist ideas
Urban Mystic
The machines advertised quote used underwear
But the actual Japanese Tech
Kiryu
Similar to pre distressed
Arises that non-native speakers see the word used on the machine they come to their own conclusion
Where is if you actually speak Japanese you wouldn't
Make the same mistake
Which tracks neatly with Alex saying that he got this information from Mancow
Who is visiting
Speak Japanese
He probably just saw used on the machines like all my God people shiting those
Virulent
Racist man
The article determines that most of the stuff you hear about this sort of thing is based on Urban
I can also find no evidence that there are poop bars all over the United States
Is that a civil rights issue we would have to close our poop
I mean
Got it
Can have her clothes up
The issue about this sort of thing is like yes there are people who have
You know it dolgin
Some sort of a kink
That other people would find disgusting
I'm not super interested in myself but
Japan that's not
It's not reach the pandemic level
No not yet
Be an escalation towards
Blood-drinking
Zombification and
Cities Burn
Even though
The good son
Could make
It's at 5
Pressing all these
We wind up
Bleeding closer to
To the blood-drinking
And
Baby I'm not entirely sure on the literature on that but it does the
It does seem like
You know some feelings you have about it might lead you to that
Conclusion
I don't know this is crazy
First of all just because
Like the information that Alex's
Is going on is obvious
Racist
This
The 2nd
Impress
About what's at the bottom of the rabbit hole
That's what he's got
That's crazy
Japanese the top seller doesn't specify without even
Japan
Is diapers for people to s*** in because they all love
Defiling themselves and
Desecrating
Right
You here though is
Is that that was
Just a
You don't like his explanation
Alright
If you want to know
You know that
Is
Ludacris
Why are you pressing me for specifics of making me look like I don't give a specific right
View
Failing this contract
Right and then you calling you amplify the things I say
Make money
So I don't know
Absurd
Some more specifics Alex
The more you realize
Nothing is
Is based on any
Memphis's
Absurd b******* about
People
Eating poop
Meaning of civil rights
So Alex
Rambles a bit more
And he ends up telling the story of why his family moved to Austin
From Rockwall alright
Loaded baked potatoes
That's not the story
I don't believe this
Okay
Mythology really well
So he would never
Who were corrupt
I even had some of them come around
I started messing with my parents
Story
He come by
Smart young kid like you
Trophy wife
Egypt better watch what happens to you what you've been talkin
Just watch your butt boy
Our lawyer called
Are these
Absurd his lawyer got a call that the FBI agent
So are the police department put out the word we're going to go kill little Alex
City Hall
David
We just want to give you heads up
Let you know that kill yourself
Supposed to do this
I've been signed by the governor
Oh right absolutely
Get out of here
I don't believe this
I also now there's Federal involvement
But I don't think I'm going
Don't think moving to Austin would help
If they have
The lawyer said they're going to kill Alex
Moving a couple hours away doesn't seem like it's going to be are there the Federal
Bureau of Investigation for them
The germs of them murder of a child
This is Ludacris
Austin has no X
Tradition laws
Even if his story was believable on its own
As the solute it makes less.
Howard kid
Which interprets things
Like it could be the sort of story that you tell yourself
You've your parents
Like you're getting in trouble at school so they want to move
Change environments cuz you're a piece of s***
Beadery will change
All sorts outcomes
Maybe there's bad influences if that's cool
Maybe he's running with a bad crowd
You can
Maybe finesse things
In your own mind to tell yourself a different story of what Acts
Happened
Set Alex's
Decided
That this. Version of the story that
VeggieTales
Is the reality
Because it never did not happen
Probably
SAS terminal pool once
I could see that I don't know
Right
I have to believe Alex was annoying as a youth
Call Tricia
I can't imagine someone not telling him to shut up every now and again
How does Merit spiraling
Into
They were going to kill me
Probably not now
That's my feeling
This is a load of s***
Yeah it's a story like that that really May
F***** him
So but like I don't know if they did
It sounds to me like
Based on every story we've heard about him
Moving or or any
Before he would
Any control over it
His parents probably
Just lie.
Maybe maybe but so much of it is only coming
From his perspective
No is actual input from his parents as perceived
So I don't know I would be I'd be hesitant to say that they're lying
Stop when it's coming from
I don't know
It could just be a self-defense mechanism
Get some selfies the hero in all these stories
That's entirely likely
Now that he
He believes all of Alex's narrative
And all of the Worlds
Puts out
His friends don't agree with them
GoNoodle
To some extent
I don't think it Alex
Response
Appropriately
You know it's a twin like all my friends hotels like
I try to tell him about like what's going on about all the Tyranny about
It's like they don't have their own.
Everyone everyone has the iPhone now it's like it's like we're living inside of a clone tiida
Well it's
I just really feel bad for like my generation my future we don't even get to live our lives now
And I mean like
The future is
Every corner
People pooping on each other
Very obviously stupid kid I really look up to you and I hear aware
Doubt about my increasing isolation
Please tell me what the future is for my generation
Alright this is the Great
That's that that's a situation where what Alex is doing is
Mocking
The out
The friends he has that don't agree without his worldview
Thursday
Serves to insulate the Imgur
That is a part of
With Alex
And I don't
But that's healthy
Not good
I think there's some Merit to
Lake
Not necessarily a lot of bully
Generational isolation
You feel the technology over
To an extent
Feels like there's a lot of in personalization
You can talk about in a realistic way at 4
Offer solutions to
And it's not hey all of your friends are stupid they're just cheap
They're thinking like that they all have
The same thoughts not like you know they're just going to end up at
Like that
That's not good that's not that's not a healthy weight
To treat someone calling it
If you don't help them or
You're going to end up at the
Kapooclub
There's also an imp
Play Syd threat to every part of
He's out groveshire
Sure
I don't know I think
That's not cool
That's the
With what
Simply
Call them
Never
One last clip and it's from the end of this 28th episode
It's kind of a no man's land
Third in there somewhere
It's pretty it's mostly just vamping to not take calls and then taking a few calls
There's no Sandy Hook
Really
Except I guess
I think once or twice you generally
It says
It's a false flag
But that's not really any
Develop
That's just him
Throw that in there
Just a reminder it's not a development
Inasmuch as
Introduce
Acceptability of dealing with this as a crisis actor situation
False flag
It's the same thing we talked about on our last 23rd
It's the kind of thing where
If you want to hear it this way you can
If you want to hear at this other way
And it's not
It's not relevant
But we got One Last Cry.
Another caller
Alex is running out of time
To tell you he's in overdrive
So he does not have to answer to
Then he's both running out of time and
He's already
Show is over but he can just keep going as long as he wants
Yeah so he's talking to this guy
He could
Come back from this commercial break that they're their barreling into
He could cancel the commercial break he wants to
I probably wouldn't
This whole thing is sort of
There's a whole story on top of the story ends medium
Shine some light on you
I covered something the other day and I know this may sound fantastic
Hartford Connecticut
Okay Define JPMorgan and his
Why is M3 songs their graves were ransacked and bodies were sold
Is the a division
YouTube
Princess
Their bodies were stolen
Such a good boy
Morgan is buried at Cedar Hill Cemetery in Hartford Connecticut
An extra layer to the story
Feels like he's talking about Sandy Hook because it's Connecticut
But it's not explicit but that's
Disconnected
You think
I don't really know cuz I would doesn't give him enough time
Conspiracy
Connecticut
Any added layer it feels like it might be
I don't know like just from the the
Large background information
Throwing
Sandy Hook
Was a
False flag
Nobody died in
To distract
Stealing of the Apple
From Rushmore
Pictures of jpmorgan's gravesite
Easley online if you look it up there's not really any
It's just kind of granite slabs
JPMorgan was married twice
Is buried with him
Cedar Hill
Problem
Mostly because JPMorgan only had one son JPMorgan to
He had three daughters Louisa Juliet
But others for children only
And are buried at the family plot
This guy is just simple facts wrong
The little difficult to trust any of them
JPMorgan and his three sons gravesites where they stole their bodies have three sons
Got an additional element
And now I want to find out that JPMorgan had a pretty good cook
I tried to look into this I can find literally no indication the JPMorgan in his family's tubes were ransacked and their bodies were stolen
I can't even find conspiracy sites are doing that sort of thing
Maybe
Yeah it is just kind of the problem with how Alex relates to his collar
He has no time left on the show even though he's an over driving to keep going as long as he wants
Realize this guy to throw up something
Unfounded and insane
While leaving himself
No time to respond
Except for with a weird grown
You can't operate like this
Especially when Alex
Fancies himself and he talks about a lot about like
I get so much information from you callers of the Brain Trust
Stories of gun bills that I don't even know where happening
You've got a call or calling in
This JPMorgan grave robbery happened
The specifics of it
It's just left hanging there
It with no like if I were Alex I one second left and that guy said that
Nope
I cannot hang up
We've been doing this
So many years I've heard so many callers and I have never wanted to know what
Any of them had to say
And if you consider that like he's Vamps
Almost there
Entire episode if this caller it just been allowed
Some of that time
We could have maybe figured out what is the conspiracy
Obviously the conspiracy is so much better when I'm writing what he might think right
That of course is going to be better because the real conspiracy was probably going to be a method
Probably it is more fun
If it is like we need a diversion in order to pull off the Italian job on his tools or something
It is more fun
It's probably not what he was
But I want to know
Come back to the 2013 on March 29th will we find it
Probably not almost certainly not
No problem. You're all going to die wondering what happened
I think I think that is something that a mystery that will go unsolved
So I am.
Departure
Like I think
I think we have
Icy chains
First of all Steve pieczenik
Simplay
He wants to come back he'll be back very soon
Disseminate
And that is the Susan Collins
Existence proves that there crisis actors
Also I want to know how much you got for ghostwriting
I would like to know that
On is big
And then I also think that
Do you think
These things and Alex.
Push back on them is big
Because it's Alex had a moral and intellectual
Consistency
What we've seen so far is it least of version
To the actors
He scolded that caller who brought up the idea that Robbie Parker was an actor
Like you can't stay
There was a repulsion about it
Winnie had Paul Joseph Watson interview James Tracey
There wasn't
Do distance
Interview the guy about what he believed but not be
Now here on Archer
You see
Almost complete except
Partially because Alex knows Steve
He doesn't take it as just some crazy idea that
There's the gravitas of Steve
Britannic behind
Which is a mess
Hypnotize
Probably he probably has like a
The real Arrow credibility of very
Like I don't think Alex has any reason to
Pieczenik was on
Every goddamn
Fueling a lot of Alex's
Shift to Trump
With his
Narratives about the counter-coup
What have you
Loki
What happened
In the future and how quickly Alex
But I do I do think that
We could what we can see
He publicly here
It definitely feels
Like
I need those
Yeah
I very much hope
The lawsuit involved release
I don't think we have standing
Prefer something along those
Certainly.
Snow
Feels feels like this is
It feels like this is a drop-off
We'll see I'm more
Excited whenever face on like
We only have like two weeks left
Before the Boston bombing
Narrative is taken
A drastic step
Before this
How much
Is that going to come in
Play how far is he
You going to go down to
Sandy Hook crisis actors
Before the Boston bombing
And then how is that going to inform his
News coverage of the bombing
Such a disaster unfolding in front of me
Like that is unnecessary
It is based on
Haribol sourcing
It's based on
Just
I mean everything is as bad as Jeff
Poop bars
In terms of
America poop
Because they're not that
I mean grounding in reality none of this is real all of it just going to drink
Yeah
Yep
I don't know either
I'm more excited than ever to see where this goes
But then I also.
I mean isn't in this
Situation I have weights
You know what I got to do information
Sabong happens if I got Steve on you
I never said that
Expect the unexpected
Nothing ever
Turns out how it appears
The appearance of
Steve pieczenik
Being
Various
Actually related to this
I think is born
That's crucial
So Pat myself on the back
Ever-so-slightly
For that prediction correct
Today right
Yeah I will
The pattern on the back
More information comes to the
On Wednesday
Live website
Yeah it is
Ross on Twitter
Yachtworld
If you would like to
Forced tell someone else
You can go to I2
Are you could leave a review
But that is
Low
Level
Oh boy
You're going to want to do
To your nearest park bench
Underneath that park bench will be a bed
That will give you the key to our dirty Dropbox
Okay
You're going to want to download those two
Three files all of them. EXE
So if you have a Mac
You're not going to be able to listen to their label JPMorgan said 12 + 30
I didn't know that's where you were going
I felt like it was either going that way or a Japanese woman
Three files will give you the coordinates of a vending machine Japan
We've been doing we've been talking to each other for
Possibly
Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color