I have great respect for knowledge right now it's like I'm sick of them posing as if through the good guy
Monica
Stripe.com
Beverages and talk a little bit
Choking
Call a number of times
If you were putting together an American Olympics shooting team you would not come today
One that sticks out the most to me was when I was like
Let's call it
Pool
In Columbia Missouri
And
I was there with you
Somebody
I got a hot dog
Not in the water frame
Hot dogs
Into all that well swallowed I could feel like
The Ono Ono Ono
Friends were laughing
I'm going to the pool having fun a joke
Parable
Against
Chair
Memories are a little bit vague
Lack of oxygen
Self
Beautifying
Not too long ago sandwich
Is in my apartment
What what time is it last year
I had a very similar moment of like
Should Have Cheated more
And I have this
This like weird
Feeling of like
Alright I do a podcast about Alex Jones being a liar I'm going to choke on this sandwich
I'm sticking to myself like about whatever
This one mom
No matter what we're destined to die in a conspiracy theory
Dislodging that
I survived to this day on
Cheese is not I need to get you a room
Because I swear that roommate
You're no LOL
How to help myself from
Tell me about
Particularly
Care right now about the
The present day
Back to it for
For Friday
Not entirely sure I might
Do an episode about it then
Baystar Monday up
Episode where are we
Discovered the
Pieczenik back in 2013
Coming in hot
Throwing Sandy Hook crisis actor talk all over the place
Got to stick around here I got to see what
What's going on
It really feels like
Unfollowing that bread
Over March 29th
The April 1st
Development switch
Confuse me
And also bring some information
You are
Into our orbit
Did you just described our entire
I did
Confusing and fun
Informative
Frustrating
I'd like to
To create that frustrating and informative
Not the fear
A person
Your nail polish
I'm a policy wonk next Daniel thank you so much
Thank you so much
Text Chris Kelly
Next
DPAC loves Alex
Thank you so much
Journal policy wonk
Appreciate very much still first of all
Charlie thank you so much
You're both wonderful technocrat
Business heroin
Freakishly large
Charlie
If you're out there listening to the website
We appreciate
Giselle
Like I said we're back in
Alex
The 29th
In an interesting way
What we speak
Is Alex talking over the
The bumper music
Like you coming into the show
From
FEMA occupied regions
For that but I think he doesn't know his mic is on
And then he pretends that he
Is Mike
Ikeno
He pretends that he's aware of it and he's doing it on
You'll see
Batman movie
Mainstream media
My life like a Batman movie
Call my Mike
He was driving into work that day and a piece of plastic
It came off of a truck
For the day
He's thrilled to be alive if you could have died out on the highway it is
Man movie
There are similarities
Batman
There we go
So Alex has an interesting narrative
He's pitching on
You trying to
Incredibly consist
Throughout his career
Prominent
Right now
Stretch
And that is the everybody who's in
Important love
World leaders are interested in what Alex's doing everyday
Rogue world leaders are concerned about
So
Is Alex talking about that a little bit in a way that
What is
Rathe
This is about Kim Jong
Honor last episode
Kim Jong-un
Kim Jeong Hoon
Come out
Is responding to
Talking about
The world
That he's a probably watching the show
Just like your degenerate father
You little piece of trash
Austin such a military Target
Little turd
So Kim
Unbelievable
Listens to his show
And because
Yelling about how soon is a demon
Kim Jeong Hoon has made plans to bomb Austin to shut Alex
That's the only thing
That is
Legitimately what Alex
Is
Leader of North Korea
United States
Which will 8 a.m.
We have to shut about
Alex is too much of a risk
Be on fire right now if they'd Alex believes in Freedom
Kim Jeong hoon is against Freedom there for Kim Jeong Hoon Must Destroy out
Supligen
Higher half of the country would be on fire
Jesus yeah it's pretty crazy
Replacing himself is radio show
He's on the elevated pedestal
Target
I can't believe someone would listen to his show and not because
Concerned about his well-being
After saying something like
Like that like or this guy is so full of s*** is f****** around like why would you
Either you're crazy or this is completely unreliable
Post on MK news
North Korea news
With the headline quote North Korean photo reveals us mainland
Strike plan
I've read this article and I have to say that from the blurriness of the photo that's in
Included I don't even think it's a fair assessment to say that Austin is even one of the target
There is a line
On the maps
Supposedly a mistletoe
Which appears to end in Central Tech
But the problem is it
Stops there
Or that's just where the
Picture of the u.s. map is blocked by one of the North Korean soldiers
His problem
Because of this even a composite overlay appears to
To show San Diego Washington DC
KC Hawaii and possibly Austin is being primary Targets in a North Korean attack
They had to make a composite overlay where this they superimpose the map over the soldiers hat and then guess where
That line ended
His hat also cover the entire southeastern United States could have ended anywhere
But it's probably Austin because Alex has been talking s*** about you
Ninjago
That was his much of a map as they could have four
They couldn't afford the second they couldn't afford the easternmost
Don't make a composite
Sure it's operating
Information
The other thing that's important to point out is that this image was not information that North Korea released at the world to threaten
It was published in MK news image in rodong
The newspaper of the
Taqueria Workers Party
The folks that has believe that this is indicative that the message
Intended for an internal North Korean audience
Not the world
John Swenson right
Senior lecturer
East Asian
International relations
Is the University of Cambridge quotes
It seems reasonable to suppose that the target map is designs
For home consumption
Create an impression
Nerf war Readiness for
Dprk
Citizen
Part of the wider policy
This was a piece of propaganda meant for interred for an internal audience
It's a wild man Alex and
Something like that
Look and decide that the real story here is about himself
I'm sure there's no evidence that Austin was even one of their targets
This is deeply troubling
Because only two
Nations icon
CR outrageous levels
Narcissism
To the point where he actually believes the moonless
Unbelievable level of comfort
And his audience will just believe it
It's not for they'll just ignore it or it like it'll be
To me so much of this has to be like water off a duck's back
After so many of his listeners where it's like
A stroke out unless something
Applies directly to them
In the same way that Alex can't pay attention to anything without applying it directly to himself
Alexa says all this narcissist
And his listeners are like okay
But still has some sort of a residual
Even if it rolls off
Because you
Even if you're like well whatever
Status of like
Super important geopolitical
Experience of listening to it even if you don't
Take that in and fully in
Internalize it as like something important
It still gives the appearance that like well I mean it's dictators want to take out
Stupid
Have to
Amplify the
Threat to them
Specifically
Almost better and more effect
If it is that sort of thing where it is
Easy to do
Just sort of like Let It Roll Off
Yeah
Because then you don't sit and think about it too long to realize
Stupid
You're crazy
Another headline
To get into and this is another thing
Things that I believe is indicative
Of all of Alex's
Does pattern of
Saying that everybody
In very astute
Situations
This is a trend that's going running
Counter
To Alex
Hook
And this is the path where we see
I'm saving some people in the Aurora shooting were actors
The G20
Person who is arrest
Did was an actor
And now we have another exam
American Terrorist
So
Eric harroun
I was an American citizen who was arrested
Sit in a very complicated
Situation back in
There's a version that Alex is putting forth which is that he was an American soldier who decided to start saying LK it was great
Most likely because he's a paid actor and then the government had stage in the rest covers
Things up or something
Obviously the globalist paid him to protect us portal creative because he's part of a larger psyops
Which Alex would tell you is impossible
That's the only
It makes as much sense
Sandwiches
Beyond that just kind of being a dumb
Conception his version of this story
Leo burst
I routed been in the army
Bad behavioral issue
When he was in love
According to the New Yorker
Fellow-soldiers service
Which he was a passenger in a drunk driving
Which led to him suffering from
He got a medical waiver and honorable discharge that's
It's for bullfighting career in the US service
In the years that followed the New Yorker paints a picture of a really f***** up guy
Discussing is stocking in a
Ex-girlfriend which ultimately led to
Shooting himself in the abdomen
What you wouldn't take
The article also says use rest
Twice for DUI
A real trouble pass
That might to him going overseas
A meeting people
And getting into
First aid in Freedom
It all the interviews I've read including
It's abundantly clear that Eric harroun was
Not in Elkader
He was a committed
Anti-anxiety
To join up with rebels in Syria
If you wanted to help overthrow Assad
And in the process he allegedly accidentally got mixed up with a G
He joined up with
A separate group that was ostensibly aligned with the United
State but after a skirmish
In the ensuing chaos
Has he got a ride
The in-and-out knows were truck
Away from the fighting
Any ended up embedded with them for about
25 days
Which you could kind of believe is a mistake
Considering that haroun didn't know Arabic
Due to his linguistic confusion there's even some doubt that he was at
Actually ever even with Elmo's World
As opposed to
The possibility he was with a group like
And he just didn't know the difference
What is father says that you was working with the CIA as Alex
Just got this
He doesn't mean that he was in
Cheerio bee
He was working with us
CIA
With the CIA
To be able to
The United States
In the foreign policy article
Describes the CIA
When he's dealing with them about like
Trying to not get charged with
The bad cop
Map to the FBI's good cop
In their discussion
Yeah they're both
They're both
They're both good
Ensure
According to that New York
In 2008 Eric and reached out to this
CIA about a Reece
Some trippy take
Cancel Lebanon
I need a received a reply from a guy named Wayne appear to be operating a dummy
Email account
Wayne did appear to act as a bit of a
The Handler
I was trying to get Eric to
Spy on a local mosque
Perform all available information it doesn't appear that relationship
Nor did it have anything to do with a Terex later Adventure is
In the Middle East
It does seem like it explains why he would approach
The CIA
Which is exactly what
Right it makes a lot of built-up from interacting with
Giants rings
To help him get information on this
They wouldn't charge him with the war crimes that it appeared
You may have been involved down
So f******
Never not in a million years Hugo the f******
Harrison Ford Road
You Escape
You go on the Run
Until you find the real killer turn yourself in they are not your friend
They are trying to come after
Whatever the case is very motivated
Whatever the case is about whether or not he deserve to go to jail for his action
She's I can't really settle for you or the
There's no credible reason to believe that Eric harroun is in
That's just a completely insane
It fits very neatly without Alex's
Beginning to incorporate actors in so many of his narrative
Erica Reed died in April 2014 of a drug
Which I'm going to guess Alex would say is actually
Is the globalist hit
Stake him out
Play Department you wasn't useful anymore happen that way
In reality Eric had struggled with a Dick's
In his whole life
Rehab for heroin in 2011 and be hospitalized for
Before an overdose
About 4 months
Before his death
December twenty
13news found unresponsive
It's hard not to imagine that these six months
The solitary confinement he was subjected to
Which ended in September
Could have played a role
Is relapse
Describe his torture could play a role in
Drug addicts death
Which was the
Strange
Is the tragic story of a complicated person who did
Probably unwise
Is things
Possibly motivated by actually wanting to
Depressed people in Syria possibly but also
Motivated clearly by some vaguely
Somatic and anti-zionist ideas
Desire in need
Is life and the fact that in the present-day someone could just
Decide to do that
Freetress
Got
Highly possible that he
Slapstick
His way into the tower
You know
Pictures of Herbie rides
Cool we're in a war zone this guy seems nice if somebody's offering you a ride
They're nice guys they're not trying to
Truck
The Prisoner for a while then there was another battle
I don't know how much of this is
Apocryphal and whatever
This is
Complicated f****** story that a lot of people have looked into and research
Pretty well
Even their versions of ambiguity
About
Precise details about a lot of stuff
But what is
Pretty clear from everything I've read
Not an actor
And Alex would rather get rid of all that
Great.
Complicated
Reality by just writing them off as an actor
Annette's. That's not good
Early forties
You see whatever
I don't know I
Syria
Sure
Done it that way
I see that
Alex has a big special report that he's bragging
About on this episode 129
Already
He's trying to troll people
Because the title of it is Alex Jones endorses gun control
Already angry
Wolf course
The right is too good at
Of course the point of it is I don't endorse gun control I endorse gun control for that
Government taken away
Fine I'm fine
Sure here's a little
No not yet
Liberty
Evil is restrained
Cowboy
Try and quote Thomas Jefferson
This is so much of a running joke
He's f****** with
Don't think I don't know man
Just doesn't know anything
The very atmosphere of firearms anywhere and everywhere restrains
Evil interfere
We've gone over this before but again
It's essential point
Even a fake Thomas Jefferson quote Washington quote
Hunting magazine from 90
T26
It's essential to keep highlighting
Because it shows how little Alex
Cares about these supposed history claims to be an egg
Expert in
These founding fathers
You fake quotes
4patriot message board
He pulls out whenever he needs
Bratz doll
Crazy
You can't be that wrong about Thomas
There's just so many
How can you be wrong
It's very impressive
The arrival of Steve
The argument
No kid died at Sandy Hook there wasn't even a shooter it didn't happen it's all bulshit
Stevi B's coming in
And Alex push back
About it and actually sounded
Kind of excited about it
He didn't leave
A really strong impression of
Disagree
He has one
People have said stuff like that in the past
So on the 29th
With a little
Surprised
And also a little bit not surprised
Figure that
Running around
Okay
Alex
Still believe
The kids workout
It does sound like he's referring to
The people who say
There
Is that
Is that a defense
Music
I don't think so
No no you missed it I also said that they loved it
Global Aquatics
To be like one of his only reasons for holding out like
Ditto kids died
Is that like
The globalist love killing kids why wouldn't I do that
Jewelry
Kids for free
Does seem strange
But that's because I
Text is not swayed
He is not right
I still think that is
How it ends up going bad
Text board
He's on his show and Little Voices
That's Mike Adams
Adam
He still telling him
Now it's
Time
Alex
Has started
Didn't notice
Some of these
Inconsistency
About the story
Enter he starting to incorporate more
What do you think
So they're having a lot of fun
5 workshop and
Radiological
Listen to enjoy that conversation
Good time
It's like sex
Play would you rather
Can for it there like how do you want it
A couple of examples
The arguments that Alex uses
Later
In defense of the crisis actors no one died there
Guy caught in the woods Bloomberg technology
He has these
Narratives that he's putting forth
These pieces of in
Information has been consisting
Which you will later blame people like
Wolfgang halbig is in no way mentioned
He hasn't been on the show there has been no indication
Awareness of ham or interact
This appears to be
Things that Alex has learned of
News reporter
These things that will be part of the
Hook
No one died their argument
Are there now
But he still doesn't believe
Bloomberg
How big
Alex
So it's for the 29th
Adams
Just have like a
I try to be Joker
That's not
Especially Mike Adams
The Friday
We come in on the 31st
And I don't know if you know this but March 31st 2013
That was Easter
Sometimes can be
Did not know that Easter and Alex
Opens the show
In front of me
Constitutional
Terrorist murderers
Big smiles
A free Society doesn't include television
Programs like this weird argument to be made by an anti
Free Society
Would make sure that these things
Would be censored and away from visual
Devices
Sure more free than censoring my political enemies
For sure
Easter is one of the biggest holidays
Christian religion
The day off to be with his family or go to services
I don't think that's a shame I just want to point out
Does how he celebrates
Recognize
Is the day when Christians worldwide
Select on how Jesus died for their sins and opened up a possibility of living
Free from the bondage
Easter egg hunts for the neighborhood
Some people make a nice meal and commune with our loved one
And people like Alex get on a nationally syndicated radio program
Complain about fox
Drama shows
From extremist religious weirdos
The show that Alex is talking about here is the following
So at least it's an actual show that was on are unlike other times you complained about Pilots that never got picked up as if they're like
I went read the article on Infowars about this from Kurt Nimmo
But Alex is reporting on
Edit start
Week
Actually it starts up too strong I would say
Well yeah that way too strong
Quote
Fox the Entertainment Network founded by Rupert Murdoch and Barry Diller is working with the federal government at the Southern Poverty Law
Americans identified themselves as constitutional
Wow
This is a devastatingly
Terribly paragraph
I would never write this
In any website with an actual editor would never publish
And here's why
It's fighting off of way more than the article
Continue
That paragraph is explicitly saying that this article will report
The splc is working with fox
The federal government is working with socks
These groups are specifically working with Fox on issues related to
Contact
And for
The work they're doing is specifically to demonize concert
Do you have any idea how much work that dum-dum curtain if I was going to have to do to actually make this article match that lead parrot
How dare you the answer is put a. At the end of that paragraph and called
Go to lunch
He's going to have to demonstrate actual coordination or involve the splc's federal government in Fox
But guess what
Even if he somehow manages to do that
He still has
To prove that this work has anything to do with the following and the content
In that show
There's literally no way that anyone in forwards has the journalism or research
Chops to pull something like that off
Just pathetic all right so I assume that Nimoy
Immediately filed
Immediate
We need emails
Between
Producers the producers of the show
How do I get to goes all the way to the top let's just go to the president
We need it all
He didn't he didn't copy and paste
About to eat my acropora and how are play for the pilot of a comedy show on are called we hate Paul Revere
And they don't mention that it's
Was never
Actually on the show
It's just all that standard bulshit
But the bigger issue here is that this isn't about the entire series
It's just about one episode of
The following
And this gripe that he has
Walking Hilaire
Quote
Any news on Thursday to recruits are asked
Guitar ex-military
They respond by saying they were raised in a militia in our quote
Constitutional extremists
First
You got the name of their own show wrong
If the important
Mark's it's real bad
Second problem
That's it
Two characters mention that they work on
Constitutional extremists in the response
PLC federal government
I don't think there's any other explanation
Massive conspiracy because they felt that for a little
These people running around calling people snowflakes all the time for not putting up with racist
Sexist bullying
These are people who are into the
Exchange of ideas
Absolutist
And yet here Alex is legitimately saying on his show that
Free Society
A show like The Following wouldn't exist because it makes his extremist buddies feel bad
Marilee of coward liar
There's a profoundly bad take on Alex
He can't prove that the sblc in federal government is responsible for this
Probably like
10 seconds and one episode of The Following
Memo write a shity article
Pretending to demonstrate
Then Alex can get on his radio show and talked about Infowars is reporting that the sblc is demonizing Constitution
Sick loop-the-loop of live version of the 24
For our Fox
Machine where the morning show has
Monday evening news
It is but it's so much more
It's more nefarious yes
Call Alex
I don't think anyone would take the
The time
It's really an insult
Or anything
It's definitely like
Real bad
Hate to make it even worse
This is so funny
Probably only bring this up cuz I had to read
Need an actual Infowars article and like when you do you find s*** like this
Pathetic
Listen to this
Axel paragraph
Real article
Quote
Infowars.com today that the
Patriot in concert
Institutionalized narrative
Television shows
Reports of Constitution
Call the hospital in police dramas
Article
No the article is
No
Really look bad all the time so I'm just going to take
Absolutely
It does say that you were fortunate
So if you're keeping score Alex is on his radio show reporting on an article on
Infowars.com
He is one
Expert
Did they consulted about what shows his wife that is
When you start to see you
This is something vet
Basketball today
You start
Question
How rigorous
Is any process for
Strong if this is okay I really like them being able to
I really like them just like
It would make
If they had the headline and then
Just a series of a
Like that would be
It's the same thing
Patriots
We are now reporting
Alex Jones across the hall
Yeah
It's embarrassing
So on this 31st year this Sunday Easter
Joe Alex goes out to break
The first commercial break
Like that
Enterprise
It's a Sprite
And guess what
Then it just goes to
Rebroadcast
What is Coachella
Alex didn't work on
He did take Easter off
So what happened with you recorded that on Friday know what special guest
They were going to replay
What interview they're going to replay
And so he
That
Adidas recorded that like 5 minutes on Friday or whatever and they took the weekend off
F****** a******
Klipsch heresies Ted Nugent
Which is like God
Just complaining about to Jim Carrey
And then he has an interview that he did a while back with John rap
Report about how
James Holmes
Amazon mind control
So you to April 1st
Real quick
April 1st 2013 I am your host Alex Jones going to be live here
I asked him a few questions during that.
Steve pieczenik is back already
Cbp's back after a weekend a couple Days Inn
Alex
Express that he does not agree with that
Look at these back.
Talk about it for an hour
Stone cave where he was
Kept
These back to bring Salvation to Alex Jones
Perhaps
So I started to listen to this episode and I started to feel like
This is
So familiar
Has like
Heard this episode
And I knew for sure that I had heard it before it got to Alex Garden
Nutella story
About how over the weekend
He got yelled at by a global Asuna
This is it is we have covered this episode already
I got about 40 minutes into the episode
This camp
Be another time that there's a globalist in the hot tub
Salvage yard
I went back and I looked
Cover this song
Why have I already heard today
A couple years back
When I was trying to find
The topic to cover
What was
I went back and I listened to every April Fools
Cuz I thought that maybe Alex would do a joke show I heard this music
But the next episode after that found the globalist hot tub story as like we got it.
So if you want you can go back and listen to our April first and second episode
Where it's mostly about Alex running into a authoritarian globalist
Who is into white genocide
Who yelled at Alex
For 20 minutes 20 minutes
The Fantasticks
I realize that like we'd already covered
S*** what do I do
Do I just say everyone go listen to that episode I were done
Listen to that episode
And I realize they like
Play covered in that
Was the Robeson
And there's more going on here
So what
I'm going to look at the other stuff
The globalist
Hot tub stuff that's in the other episode
We will take a look at all the other stuff
It's important for our
Continuing investigation
But unfortunately involved
Republican
Globalist
Hot tub I think
Sequel to hobo with a
Do you remember that Electric Power
I think that was pretty much
The point out the Globus in a hot tub
Because it's
It puts us in a really bad
He is really depressed
And really messed up
About
Running into this authoritarian
Certainly not
So he's in a very f*****-up
Really bad position
To interact with
A psych Warfare
Man
And I love it when they're hate
So we got as we get to it
But before that
He continues are running Joe
Thomas Jefferson
What
God damn it I don't think that's an actual Thomas Jefferson quote
Literally
Never said it
Searching through sources ranging
Jeffersonian archives
This doesn't appear in any recorded
Midstate Motorsports
To off-base for something Jefferson
It's just that there's no evidence
He did say it
However
It does sound a lot like a boiled down version of someone else's words
What a people will submit to and you found out the exact amount of Injustice and wrong which will be imposed
If these will continue until their resisted with either words or blows or with both
The limits of tyrants are prescribed by the endurance of Those whom they oppress
This was set on August 4th 18th
57 by noted radical abolitionist
Frederick Douglass
Is wild to me because obviously Alex likes
Quote for some reason he doesn't know that he's reciting quotes
Specifically about the
The ending of slavery
Which is something is
Family members literally fought to maintain
You're making assumptions
The next line
In the light of these ideas Negroes will be hunted in the north and held and flog it at in the
The South so long as they submit to those devilish outrageous
And make no resistance
It's either moral or physical
Men may not get all they pay for in this world but they must certainly pay for all they go
If we ever get freedom from the oppression and Wrongs heaped upon us
We must pay for their removal
Will do this by labor by suffering by sacrifice
And if need be by our lives in the lives of others
Most of the time Alex is fake Jefferson
Quotes are just
Their examples
I'm seeing a meme on a patriot message board
It's real
Huskies field
Grocer
As if what's going on isn't it
You Frederick douglass's words
And attribute them to
Someone at school with your audience
Quotes
Maybe I'm reading too much into this maybe more than I
But whatever the case
Streak of not knowing anything
His favorite subject
Still going
Impaled
Really messed up
Ted Williams
Not knowing any
Anything about Thomas
Kind of amazed
No one will ever be 256 quote
Monovalent
Does bmore messed up to me
What black people say
Frederick Douglass
Smart guy
Going to have to go
The Thomas Jefferson everything is
F****** Jefferson
If it sounds good
Cuz there's no way you're going to say
Diseases ancestor
Relearn something without linking a little bit later
So
Text Cliff we get a server continuation of Alex
Delusions of grandeur
Beginning this episode we heard him
Arguing the Kim Jong and because Alex
Getting out of pocket
Kim Jeong Hoon
That's the only thing
Alex has another indication
Is geopolitical
Important
Different
Smells like
What we know
Is the is former CFL
We know that he's somebody talks
We know that you somebody like that
The strategy of buttering up Alex with flattery
Like something that Steve is telling Alex
I go to these high-level meetings and everyone's a huge fan but you're right on
They say that you
Dear God you're there to tell people the truth
That to me is right in line with the kind of b*******
Hotel hourly
To ingratiate himself
And you know how
Scuse me
I just choked ironically I
It's so
It's so funny to baby
Alex has
The ark
For Wyatt
Not true
On his lips
He's saying literally you guys listen to me and you're saying you don't know what to do
I'm telling you what to do what are you talkin about yourself why are you doing this
I'll tell you why I
Cuz they're not actually
You know why
I listen to this s*** this terrible showare like
Flies
Leon
Easter
Cover an article that you're the primary source for about 10 seconds and a fox show were you allege that the
Splc in the federal government of running
Drama contact
Like you running that kind of a joke of a f****** show world leaders
Skip.
They're like what
Else is Alex's wife
Realistic explanation is that Steve is telling them that it's a complete lie from somebody because he sounds
He believes it and it's not something that he
Absolutely
I heard that in a
Immediately my Steve bell went off
Pieczenik
He brought up CFR brought of talking to high-level peep
It's too it's too exactly in line with the manipulation we send
Steve Hughes on Alex
There's only one other high-level
And he's not going to show up for another
True
Rodger Stone
They didn't become friends
I did not know that
That's where they that's where their pads first
Allegedly cross
I'm so Alex would say something that
About his awareness
About his Auto
And the only reason we have any wealth or money order
Is because
Which five
They are playing the game like
Exist
Prevalent
No is it like individual teeth
Press X and all teeth are removed
Same time that's a
Shawty construction of the game
Is emission
So I found a top
100 video games
And I'm not sure
In here
The top selling game of 2013
And I can definitely see Alex taking issue with that game from like a
The puritanical standpoint
He wasn't about training
Patero Patriots
Number two on the list is FIFA
Could be as an American
Number three is Call of Duty ghosts
Phone number for is Battlefield 4 which are both pretty solidly America Centric military
Freestyle
Number 5 is assassins
Creed Black Flag which is about Pirates
Number 6
Tomb Raider number seven is the previous year's edition of
FIFA number 8 is Lego Marvel super
Heroes never die
The number 10 is lasted
None of these games come close to describing the sort of game Alex
Is imagining.
I should admit for full disclosure IM played any of the games on the top 100
Except probably Luigi
These Mansion 2 tortured people because they love to yell about private property in the freezer
Market
Sound right
This is Alex
Text being dumb and
But also knowing that is audience
Gullible
An old
Keurig I say that all the top video games are about teaching kids
Torture
All I really hear is a guy
Indicating that he
He knows that is demographic
Don't include people under 40
More I think about it the more I think there's a very good chance
Alex would have been the sort of guy
Back in the day would have been like in rock and roll
Like what are the kids doing
It's just it's just a man being out of touch
The Next Generation
Knowing that
Pressing that out of touch
Aggressive
Anybody was listening is
Like someone
Video games
What's the cost
Just taking that line
You've got like old man house phone
Yeah it's not like anything about the current state of
Modern console games
Serious
Kind of
In the Fallout game
Games where it's like
Look at where Nationals propaganda will get
That kind of thing
I could see that maybe
Baby but that doesn't mean that like
Find a real life
Example of
Yeah probably is one the video game
To be able to like
Pinpoint what you probably talk about
But even if you prove
Game that's similar to
I'm about
He still has failed to prove his thesis
That is all there's so many of these games it's all about it's in the culture
You have 10 seconds of an episode of the following you're complaining about I don't believe you
Pcgamer
What are we
Atari
The GameCube
2 time I'm noticing a lot of different
One of them is the
Heightened prevalence of Alex
Things are actor
Another one that I'm noticing
Quite a bit
The troubles
Maybe
Is a lot of colors
Seem to be calling and expressing alienation
The people around them
Because of Alex
And we've seen him respond
Pretty
Episode
But in this next clip we see another caller expressing
Pretty much
Exactly the same thing
It's like now that I've woken up
People around me don't agree with me anymore
And the hostility that Alex
Expresses towards
People in the collars life
I think it's so
Pennsylvania
Hey Alex
Huge fan I just wanted to ask you
Approach people with this information I mean
I get ridiculed I get laughed at
People think I'm crazy
Organize
Yeah it's
I just want to also tell you I'll let you know you really touched my life for the positive
Wow you can't say but you can't do both of those things back to back
Alex
No one wants to talk to me and I get made fun of all the time because of
Cuz the ideas that I repeat that you have
Next
You really made a positive influence
Know you know that is sort of indicative of Stockholm Syndrome
Yes
It does seem like there is a
Where it is possible to
Interpret
Like as long as you have the veneer of martyrdom
To whatever people are doing
To you it is still possible for someone
How to destroy your life
Can you still see it as an absolute
It's so wrong of Alex
He's not
Hurting people
If you get a bunch of calls for
From people who are saying like
What you have made me believe
Has really
Made it so no one
Communicate
Should take a look at
That's all I would
That's what I would say
Tyranny
Frederick Douglass Highway of Jefferson
Earlier I heard Alex high-level government
Alex
Confirm
Confirmation on that too
Remember that I level government
Alex
Is coming off this globalist in a hot tub
I need freedom
Because this guy
You know you really shook him
And Alex is really
And that's not good
Because Steve
Pieczenik for whatever crazy
For however
Munchies
Probably exaggerating a lot of
He definitely is
Someone who understands psychology
He has
Degrees in psychology
View psychiatry
Totino's
How to manipulate
People when they're vulnerable
Helicopter
He's not somebody that you want to talk
To win
You're not in
The good place
And so when I hear Alex
Introduce him
I feel like this is the worst
Doctor Steve
What is the psychology
They're celebrating
The Publix
Homeland Security
He's not the one
To talk about the truth but I can understand why you're feeling depressed
I am not
What we see there is a
Perfect setup for someone likes to eat
Uranus
Expert on this stuff
Depressed I'm feeling grief is a lot of real name
I'm coming
You shattered put the pieces back
Together in the way
That you see fit
And
Yeah
Cheese's here
You got the compliment in there without even without Force
Reframe
Depress
So you think about that
Allowed
The different package
That doesn't make me depressed
So if you see
You won't be depressed either either
And you don't want to feel bad anymore and the fascinating
Compliment also within the framework of
Why we've always gotten along a firm Connection in there
Mutual respect and working together
It's so
I don't know if
I don't know if this is muscle memory or if he's just
That girl
No that's okay
You are somebody who has a good amount of training
In the
Probably recognize little cues
No provide stimulus
That's it
So
Steve
Gets bright
He has some
Feelings about it
No one died there was that
The writer of the hunt
Hunger Games
Is from
The city of
In this episode he starts off with
With a slightly different
And that is
Express
That
Let me see if I can
Cuz it's dumb
In the Aurora shooting
There was a gag order
Alright I am already finding this
To be stupid
President Obama talked about the
The Sandy Hook shooting
Talkabouttd
Because there was an act
Crime
Was protecting
Because Obama talked about Sandy Hook
There wasn't a gag order to actually reinforce
There's no crime there for no before Obama didn't commit a crime
Doesn't understand
What is 1250
Not going to great
Turn the phrase midnight
I thought like this is
Weird
Yeah that's
Line of thought
It's mind-blowing
Gag order
Federal and 10th
Criminal
Sure
That's weird
But I'm very strange
I just don't like how you
So
Good
At manipulation
And then in the neck
So
I mean it's on
Real what he is saying
Is that true
It's not it doesn't
It doesn't
So nobody's going to end
Steve's argument
To be that Laura was real
That was a crazy dude
A real crime was committed
Nautical flag
City of false flag
Proven by Obama's
Something about it
Breaking a gag order
It's all
So
Alex takes issue with
Because he does believe it Aurora
A little bit of a difficulty he's like
Respond to that by just
Sort of really getting
No I'm not
You're really
Bananas
Yeah
Susan Collins
Specifically she was writing about false Flags
The Newtown Connecticut
No
His only real connection is that there are schoolchildren in
And they are fighting
Timmy is
As best I can tell
That exist
That's fine
Zero Dark Thirty
The Grind With creative
Yeah is involved with Tom Clancy
Respected enough
Not a lot of people respect to ghostwriting
Got a lot of people
This conversation
You know Steve is expressing a lot of things that are
Counter to Alex's
Stated position
First of all that you know don't worry about Aurora we'll talk about Sandy Hook
No big deal nothing happen
Alex
Position he will end up
Which is string
And also Alex
Allowing this
It happened on his show with very little pushback outside
I think Aurora is fake too
Eva
This is his other
Specific
What you're saying that tells you
So like I said earlier the biggest stumbling block that he has is like why
He's pretty f******
Smart and manipulative able to come up with a
Compelling reason for Alex
To believe it would be easier for them to not kill even though they love to kill and have fun
Then that would resolve any of the
Rebuttal
Yep
That's not a hard hurdle now
And especially in his
State of being right now
So deferential at
Like this is Daddy issue on
Display here is an older man
And who I respect and he is allowed to hold forth and whenever I push
Going to be with a
Every state in fesbian
Everything is a quest
Yeah
At all like
Eve Alex's
State is very
To hold court for long stretches
It's just
Public pontificate
Sing about a whole bunch of
Really is in
There's a lot of like
Packaging
His argument about Sandy Hook with a lot of window dressing about
Like
Return of small business
The era of false flag already
Which we know is bad prediction
Sure
No Thomas
Steve does say that Europe has never valued entrepreneurship
Are these people
Anyway it's a little bit longer but this is Steve laying out his big
I guess about Sandy Hook being
I want to allow him to speak
I asked why I was talking to doctor Steve in the break and I
Specifically
Repeat
Call Susan Collins
The first piece of evidence Susan Collins
Dash he's a writer who's written similar things
Even lives there yoga
Hunger Game movies
Who is 42 social media Emergency Management
Emergency Management Institute
Prestige community
Psychologist
Minecraft
Irish cops who I have to go in Connecticut
Wealthy community alcohol
No evidence of murder or killing
In contrast to Aurora
By the way not a psychiatric disorder
Irrelevant
Alarm for today
So you see that
Alex
Response
The Cavalcade of b*******
Is to be like
Obama is trying to
To push the Small Arms Treaty
That's him talking himself into the
Yep he's in a vulnerable position cuz globalist in a hot tub it really threw him off
Yeah I don't know is that Alex
In control of all of its back
Kobe's wouldn't behave exactly the same way
He probably would but it's it's a bad
State for him to
You can see it you can see that you starting to be
I probably wouldn't happen so obvious
Do you think
The crisis actors
Is Guild
View Inn
They have an amazing package
When do I get my
Tagine rosin is the guy who the kids
Blade
To his front yard
Overact
Not any of it
The other piece
There were
You know like
Guidelines about how to cover
Disaster
This is how we
Planned disaster
Complete misrepresent
Always
Starting about like these are Irish
Rich area
Aurelia
Can I get pension increase
He doesn't say it in this clip
But it's
It relates back to other things
Please set it in the last step
Episode we covered
Irish cops I've ever heard of
PTSD from you
Providence
That we bottle it up down inside until we
It's just phlegm
I love coming in with like a lot of things to say
But all of it is so weak
I love that
He even goes over like his all that we know is that his mom gave him guns and alcohol and there's nothing wrong with that
No no most
If not all violence
Happens when alcohol is involved
Yep
But Alex is starting to come around but I don't
His body and yet
I think you can see that
Aurora Frank
And
Episode
He's not
He's not operating well
To be resolved for Alex
To take up the
Theory
Kids
Didn't get killed
AR
Someone explaining to him better
They're not actually killing people
That's super easy
Perceived
Easy for him to resolve this other lingering
Concern
About Aurora
Play Speakers by alright yes I was
Argument
You convinced me
Galaxy
That would be perfect
At least what I see
From all of my experience of Alex's psychology
How he comports himself howdy howdy cover stuff
He's on
The edge
Teetering on the edge
All it takes
Is resolving a
A couple tiny little thoughts
But he has
In order for him to
To get on board
So Prime
Now that you have a f****** psych Warfare guy involved
You're just asking for it
If you don't that
Never talked to someone like Steve ever
You know it's it's almost one of those things where I want
A benchmark
How good are you
And also how good am I
See this is how you get this is how you end up on the rocks
Sirens do you want to hear the song boats going to crash baby
I just want to hear the song
I think I think your
Seeing Alex
Being seduced
In this direction
But refusing to be
Be pushed over the edge
Until a few lingering question
Resolve
Going to be hard
Steve
Is very capable
Of doing that
I think that's where we're going to
In the very near
I think just about anybody
Pretty capable of
Kicking him over the edge
Right but you got Prime but it's gotta be somebody likes
Older man who reminds
For sure.
Jim Fetzer who wrote no one died
Would be able to do it
Cuz he doesn't know how to work with Alex
Psychology
Steve.
Steve knows what you need to do is
You have put sugar around the pill
Rite Aid
To Sweet Malik's up
Complement
Flattering
Evoking your history together of like
You need to you need to frame any possible disagreement as just like
Well we're both really smart
That's why we disagree on things
Exactly overwhelmed with flattery and a lot of
Be able to convince
Position of like I'm correct
Let's bring it together
I just need to
Bring it out when you're
Already there I'm just
Breaking away
The Marvels
Yep
Was
Any policy will
They could take the lessons learned from the show
And convince Alex if
I definitely think that's true
Tear and it's
Just some indication
Steve is not
I think that
You see that
Obviously
Steve pieczenik is somebody who's up to no good and is meddling in Alex's life
For whatever reason.
Outside
Just convincing him
Whatever the f*** people on the
Sure
I think he likes
Don't even think of that in terms of a civil war
Abraham Lincoln
Stop president
Oh boy
You want some slaves
I don't know what greater psychic Warfare is there
Something to that
I don't know what that is but I do know that he seems to be
Northern northern
You do see a lot of Confederate sympathies
Yeah what is where is he
I mean I know you lives in Florida
But where is he
Cuba Northern
So I don't know
Betty White
Very weird
Feel like this is a bit
Pretty much
About race
No no
Know how that works
He really wants to say the word uppity on a daily basis
If you really want
To say it yeah I feel like that's just an indication of
That's some pretty late
Northern invasion
It was pretty
Pretty clear where your sympathies lie if you saved
John Wilkes Booth
Revealed
I think you can hide behind a lot of ideas about
Stuff like that with the northern invasion
But
Expressing something like this
American wars
The northern
You wouldn't have a goddamn
State Alex if it weren't for the northern
That's an interesting Theory
More convinced than ever that Alex
Being softly LED down the path
To Sandy Hook denial is
By doctor Steve
Based on
Is
That it might be a good
Cigar time
For our next episode to forgo going back to the
The present-day checking in on whatever.
Has been involved
Take a closer look
Who is this guy
Is he crazy
What what's going on
Which
Novels did he write with Tom Clancy
Interested know which one to use his belt
So I hope you have residual
I guess in effect because on Mondays episode we stumbled into
To Steve pieczenik
Showing up in the past
In-N-Out this episode we see he comes back a couple days later
And he's very clearly
Putting forth
Hey aggressive
Sandy Hook no one died there arguing
Good to know more
About him
So on Friday
With a
Steve pieczenik breakdown
Steve pieczenik
I like it
So I will see you then
We have website
Also on Twitter
Russell on
Facebook
Listen to this park
You could go to iTunes
Download there you go
You could leave a review we're also on Spotify now
But let me tell you
There is this
Brazilian steak
Mariano's
Two drinks
Even though there are four people
Sitting around the table
That's the symbol
That this it not simple
The signal then the waiter is
Going to come out
Bring to UA
Small Drive
Hand it to you
Put it on the table walk away
Leave the restaurant don't pay
Run
That is the best way to get our episodes
Galaxy color with huge fan I love your work