Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
We're couple dudes like to sit around and drink red wine
The goings-on
In the wife
Alexander Emerick Jones
His middle name is Emirate it is
This isn't news to you he's getting really blowhard he refers to himself as
Alexander
Or something like that
Well yeah he wasn't really that great of a guy
I mean you did a lot of Grey
Things great meaning like
Black
Lotto
Anyway
Valic
What has happened is there a twist
Is that I know a lot about Infowars end-user
I don't know anything about Alex
And apparently he
Twins a lot of time on it
Before we get going I want to take a little moment I got a plug
I got a plug to do I gotta plug I do yeah absolutely it's not for us
Oh wait so then it's it's
Stewardess for me
But it's also for a listener and something really cool that's going to be happening
5th and Des Plaines Illinois
There's going to be a wrestling tournament
Call Jam tournament Edition
Right going to be a situation
Resume tournament to decide the first Threat Level wrestling champion
And a whole bunch of other matches
Just ate random dudes are like red. The straight like there's a guy barking right up
Do you want to be in the rain
What is it like Spider-Man
Like the original Spider-Man the Macho Man will be there
$15 at the door
And you can find out all the information you needed facebook.com
Wrestling all one word
A friend of mine has a listener
Friend
Policy wonk have gotten around
Nobody is wild
Fuckingawesome
That's just a fact I've been through a lot of like
You know pro wrestling events in the local world number of them
Okay sing is missing from all of them
These dulcet tones are you going to be doing some
Ring announcer yeah I'm the
Michael Buffer
Oh yeah
He may eat me
Billions of dollars just saying those words
Is really good
Yeah so if you guys want to smoke
Over on that Facebook page but let's get down to business
Today's episode got a couple things to say first of all
Like to that couple of our new donators
Because I'm going out to you buddy
Another new policy wants a how you doing out there
Congratulations you're both now policy wonks
What you doing tonight
If you'd like to become a policy wonk please you can visit our patreon there's a link on
Now it's right. Just bought the show
That makes
Giving us money sounds so amazing
Yeah actually it's already
The house versus the Sun
We are false
Pokemon you can donate whatever you want doesn't matter the monthly thing to give a dollar giveaway $8000000
If you're native before Road
Do we have found out east at George Soros
Let's suspend V John Rappaport
Campaign
Start no no
No
The hill I will die on
Speaking of which that brings us to our out of context Alex Jones quote for the day
Today's episode
Should give you a sense of where things are going to go
Yep that's the seriousness that we're dealing with today
Or I will die
Current
Plant pants situation
I'm going to put my money more on the floor the ladder
Is this about
Going to get custody of his children
We are not yet
It's not about that
He's getting sick
He's getting Greek yogurt they have put a lawsuit
Actually the amount looking for
$10,000
It's almost nothing
We'll get into it
April 25th
I came out Tuesday of this week
Alex Jones
We'll get to it
Okay I'm sorry
Okay nevermind
On the 25th Tuesday of this week
Alex Jones came in early
Before he had to go to court
Cuz it's pre-taped it's not live sort of pretend that it's live
And he recorded the first hour before Paul Joseph Watson took over
Or I'm sorry I think it's actually David Knight
Took over Houston today
Regardless I didn't watch the rest but I just watched Alex's first hour
Holyshit
Do do we got a winner
This stuff
Is crazy
Curious about this lawsuit
We'll get into all this feelings about it all of his nonsense
Because it's so bad
I have to say up top
I apologize
They were rebroadcasting
To my Muslim friends out there
To all of the Islamic folk in the world
I am sorry that someone says these things
It's going to be very bad
I have cut out some stuff
Particularly gross
Cuz he makes a lot of
Breitbart
Claims
About crimes that immigrants
Right there all not true some of the ones that are
Particular
But I will say listening through this I almost threw up
So
I just got so overwhelmed and anxious about all the hate
How is the
I'm not sure
Cuz that demagoguery
I mean this teams
I think I do have it.
I think it's cuz he's hemorrhaging money
I think it's because he's bleeding money out and he knows that the end is near
David he's pulling out his most desperate moves
And
He knows the ending
On one of the only things one of the only last Trixie has in his pocket
Is outright race war
So
Going to start
Introduces
Be lawsuit introduced the idea of the lawsuit
This is about
This lawsuit is scheduled for one fall
Teen yoga
Shows your host
April 2017
Brown
In the fight for the United States
The biggest
World
Bill Clinton
Big
So this is the introduction
Because we're friends
George Soros
No I mean
Oh yeah
I mean obviously not Alex
They're coming after us
Really I don't have specific numbers on a bug Levi read that down
Milkers like Yoplait or CIA
I remember reading the line that they are just aching for 10,000.
Also irrelevant to
A little bit later but the point we need to realize right now is that Alex is being sued by
Yogurt money is coming after him
She is furious about it
In this next clip
Alex explained
And he tries to
Contextualize why he thinks this is happening
Images
Other mainstream
Independent Media articles about Idaho
We weren't even that article
Average price
Salt
Eufaula
And you have with the headline that I published fake news
Yeah yeah things were mainstream news
He was just reporting on it
Yes one of the things we need to really
Deal with right up top is that he thinks the Breitbart is mainstream
Because he's just referencing Breitbart
The only thing as rescue keeps showing either Infowars or Breitbart article
Examples of like
This is the story this is the story
The
The Chobani plant is in
Twin Falls Idaho
And in that town there was a story that came out in June of last year
About
Three kids
Who had
Attack
A young girl
In a laundry room
Awful awful more awful was all the lies that got spread on right-wing media
They said that they
Rapes this young girl at night
Point
They had videotaped it
And shown their dad and he
He congratulated them
It was all sorts of wild twisting
It's all just trying to turn Islamic culture into something
It's so foreign and evil to our mine
Of course
Encourage them for this Behavior.
Right exactly is absolutely not true
There wasn't even a race
Metokur is okay because what happened was still bad
Brett
And he's basing a lot of his quote on quote reporting
Only came out on break bar
Now there's an article here in the Idaho Statesman which is
The paper of record
And Idaho
And they are that they have an entire story about the plea bargain
These kids
I ended up having to take
Good I mean
They should have baby been punished harder but the oldest was 14 at the time
Set a reminder
Alright the other thing that we have to take into consideration is that the full details of the case
Or under wraps
Very specific identities are under wraps because they're all minors
In this case
You can't
Publish the details
About these people
And the defense attorneys have discussed
The situation that actually happened and what happened was there was a
1410 and 7 year old boy
Basically
One of them I believe the seven-year-old
I groped
A five-year-old girl
In a laundry room
Gross
Super gross
Yeah
Have nothing to do with the fact that they're immigrants
No it's f***** up kid chip
Seems like
I don't know how you make a mountain out of this I mean it's bad but it's not like
Who is who is monitoring
News
Right-wing blogs baby
What what I mean
They're just f****** racing around anywhere to find anything that
Could even remotely be at 8
Well actually there's an interesting quote that I found about this
From the prosecuting attorney
Prosecutors
Lobes
He said
Fan the Flames of anti Syrian refugee people
But suspects that false reports
Are the work of a local group opposed to refugee resettlement
Go to stir up trouble by claiming the incident involves Syrian refugees who committed a violent sexual assault
There's a small group of people in Twin Falls County whose life goal is to eliminate refugees
They have not been constrained by the truth
LoveSac
I don't expect him to be constrained by the truth in the future
Heavily publicized spread spurious rumors about it and right-wing blogs picked it up
It mean to excuse the actual truth
It is that you're making it worse
Your right-wing blogs are making it worse and you're lying about the situation whole four
With the
Express purpose
Demonizing people
Who haven't
Done anything wrong
The only reason you're demonizing them
Is because they're not you
And they're in a town where you wanted to be
I'm going to go out
And say that Idaho is not exactly
Bastion
Multiculturalism
Words to because
The reason that people are so mad about it is that the Chobani plant is in
Twin Falls Idaho
Chobani plant
Tires people who are not always
Danzig
Chobani is a notable proponent of Refugee Rights
And is a heavy donator
Two refugees
Resettlement
Okay
Focus Group
Now has their George Soros to fight
Who actually
Is going to be linked George Soros by Alex
I'm glad that well of course
Prosecutor spaces between miners aren't uncommon
This case is being exploited by the local anti-refugee to make a political point
Also
No syrians have been settled in Twin falls through the Idaho Refugee program
There been periodic website postings about hundreds of syrians coming to Idaho that have all proven
To be false in the past
And this is probably just one of those attempts to try and stir up hatred
How can you
Isn't there
You pretend they're there a guy who works in me
And hateful
Guy names
Cyrus ug Center
It breaks my heart when people in the community are divided around issues of resettling refugees
Some of the stuff that Alex Jones was reporting
These
Right-wing whites
Also describe them
I would assume that is definitely true
That
And I'm going to use their words
I hope
That God f****** murders them
Using two angels
Do they try and rape those angel
Is reporting the right-wing version of the story and he was repeating things
None of them
Play back on the podcast
Do you want it's all
Because they're in the same business
They're in the same business of demonizing other population
Have
If you wanted if you little after 4 if you want to go see though
Atrocities
You can find them
If you want to do it and I'm not
Here's how you doing
Why would you
Why would you go after this
The b******* whenever you have real things that you can
You can make a ton of money by playing on people's fears and fears about Islam are the best
Your fear is super into that community so they're playing that game
That's one thing
Secondly this guy who owns
Chobani
He is a major player in the refugee resettlement game
They're going after
Matter where he
They would try and go after
Most likely
I believe that to be
Understand what he's getting in trouble for
Cheetah
He doesn't realize he doesn't realize that he's repeating completely debunked and
Dangerous clams
Where on April 11th
He released a video
The title
Idaho yogurt maker caught importing migrant rapist
Literally slander
That can't be
Okay that was their publication that was a video they posted on their YouTube page
Rant
Call April
Is
Dead to rights slander
Well
Were they
Immigrant races
Rapist
No there was no right
The only crime that's actually
Involved with this situation
Was were they from
They're all from the same place
Sam and Sarah trash
Whatever
Aerotek
And I've been here for a while
They are still refugees you got one part right they are migrants it is in Idaho
No
Was any part of that sentence
He's an Idaho yogurt
Yeah so we got one piece yes all right
The thrust of it is.
They make Greek yogurt
They don't make Idaho yogurt
He's not an Idaho yogurt Greek style
Yogurt
So everybody's everybody's completely sucked
Based on his own nuanced than bigoted journalism
Tactic
We got so many Clips I just hope that like
He's trying to thread the needle and claim
That this guy his name is
Ulukaya
He keeps calling him
Which is a trance
But also has the dangerous.
Anyway
He's going to now in this clip trying and thread the needle in
Unclaimed
Zaxby's
Specific immigrant
Are his fault
Or somebody's fault
Here we go
So that's not going to hold up in court
Okay doesn't really explain
And we have no
Basically make his plane is super into supporting
Refugee causes has a plant in that town Ergo he's responsible for the actions of
Every immigrant
It's not and we'll get a little bit later and spelling it out
Really unfortunate
Because it kind of implies
He should be put on trial for the guy
Who went
Comet Ping Pong with a gun
But we'll get to that when we get
His logic is logic is incredibly flawed
We'll get to that when we get to it
All of those words
Blue in my brain I don't understand
Like now I don't even understand
That's all I get from that time
I think that this might be too dense
There might be too much going on and it's all lies
So it's it's crazy this next the next one
More lies
Morla fake s*** about Hamdi
Using his first name Mister ulukaya
I don't know
I'm going to call him Mambi I don't care you seem cool
$2,000 lawsuit
By the way
Local news
George Soros
Alex has a picture of a tweet
Hamdi ulukaya with
George Soros
Done
I seen it all now
They were sitting next to each other
I don't believe so
Sign up we're going to catch all these
Make a
So is Alex's playing is that like this definitively proves that the two of them are working
Against him Twitter pictures
Twitter picture is
Alex reports
From 2 years ago
And it says the caption is
It was great to refresh
George Soros
So he had met him two years ago
He didn't know him before that
Basically trying
Claimed that the only reason Chobani is anywhere in the world is cuz of evil George Soros connection
All this crazy s*** there's a conspiracy against Alex
He slandered someone
In this case
100% title
Idaho yogurt maker
Imports migrant rapist
Is it illegal
You can't prove
Can you
You don't have to in court
The proof is on the person who made the claim
Husto f***
No
He has nothing
Here's you going to lose this suitcase
So hard
And that's why you putting up this video
He knows
But he's going to lose
And so he's trying to pass out his chest
Iran threat
And intimidate
And unfortunately
Because he's really bad at this game
He says a bunch of stuff that I know will be used in that eventual court case
Cuz it's like
You're going to be able to create a pattern of bigotry
In him
And they're going to be able to use that too
Insinuate or suggest that that's why he published lizard
Stories to begin with
Wait till you hear the kind of crazy b******* that comes out of his mouth throughout the rest of this episode
For this alone possibly
No I would
It's sort of free speech
Threatening I do it walks the line
Anyway
It's appropriate that I'm wrestling with that big
Text Cliff Alex
What's playing
I don't know what you're referencing here
I'm sorry I can't play the game
Oh I'm sorry I did
And it's gotta catch em all that's all I've got
Infowars.com
Alex Jones
It's about being able to shut down
The owner
Wants me to apologize for my fake
Everything
Damages
3D World
That's petulant
Is that that's so true
That's so f****** childish
What you saying
People have hurt other people
Is a 43 year old man
He's pretending like
You want
What a f****** baby
That's who
The whole thing is
This whole thing is very pathetic anyway
Alex
Cry-Baby
We're also going to get into hobo Jones
So he goes on
To spend another bulshit story
Brags about how great this case is going to be
I have the same
Warheads
I'll talk to my lawyers
A dream
It's a dream
It's not
But I pulled up
CDC statistics in 2016 1287 do tuberculosis
This provisional count
F******
Represents the lowest numbers ustv cases on record and a 2.7% decrease
The 2016 tuberculosis incidence of 2.9 cases per 100,000 persons
Represent a slight decrease compared to 2015
The - 3.4%
In the Deep
So nice
Cool also the tuberculosis rates have been steadily declining
All over
If you ain't it like if you include
Just us born people
There's a much sharper slope downward
You include just immigrant populations
It's still trending downwards
But it's it's
It's a little slower
But it's still going down
Also I pulled up
The statistics as it relates
To the specific
Cities
However sorry states in the country
Closest rate
You really can't drive parallels
Between states that have high immigrant populations
Places like Texas and California are all on the decline
There is a bit of an up
Swing in
A percentage wise in Idaho
But there's a about five times bigger upswing in
West Virginia
The dirty
West's minors
All of them under the age of
You really can't trace
What's a kilo
Very different
It is
Migrant populations in a few are you really just trying to stretch excuses
He'll get to this later but he claims
Is that 7 active tuberculosis cases were sent to Idaho
I did a little digging into that is actually true
But
Here is a response
From
Channel 11
In Twin Falls Idaho
You might have seen an article published today by breitbart.com
The article said that seven Refugee resettlement in Idaho between 2011 and 2015
7 people in 4 years
Epidemiologist confirm that that is true however it's not the
Complete story
TV is nothing new for Idaho
Dr. Kristy Hahn
The state epidemiologist
The Idaho Department of Health and Welfare treats people both Refugee and American every year
These particular cases are not contagious
And do not pose a threat to the public
The department typically test
Centuries refugees than 90 days of them being in state
And refugees are usually good Payson
Quote from this dr. Christine Hong
We're very active
And refugees are increasingly Cooperative about wanting to be immunized
Wanted to be putting any treatment they need and getting on their way to becoming good Idaho Center
They really are very willing and eager to be treated
They do not want to pose a risk
To anybody either
Wow
You know what that's really really admirable that you would want
Interesting
These refugees are more responsible than Jenny McCarthy
Somebody followed Alex Jones kids
Tvblog
Don't do that come on man
I got them
No
Joseph middle name
I took the reality is that these stories are all just
If you do a little bit of cursory researcher all bogus they're all busted
Straw case
That have been for channel 11 news
Twin Falls Ford
Oh my God real news to report
Thank you Jesus
His f****** kitten
So now we're going to get into a little bit
I specifically about Hamdi ulukaya
Yeah and we're going to hear some of Alex's
Pronunciation
I understand that I might not be pronouncing his last name perfectly but some of Alex's pronunciation
They border on racing
Just the pronunciation generous
You're also is
Codename the Texan
Yes they have a difficulty with foreign names
I understand that
Don't want to put any effort into respecting other people
Where are we we took most of this land from the Mexicans but ends up calling
Him in Islam assist which is probably not good considering that is a code word
I also talked more about
For Alex somebody who's actively Islamic Jihad I believe it that's Alex's sort of death
Cuz whenever there is
Terror acts carried out
So I don't know
It's bad it's bad whatever he's using it is it's making up a new word in order to pretend
And that it's a different thing
That white Muslims
And you like them that's fine because they're not
So he looks like Hillary Clinton in the super predator
Right
He
He says this about Hamdi
And then he says that
Yeah the new lie
And then gets to like his feelings of being oppressed
And this is all a big conspiracy
I talked to my lawyer
I understand a lot of money
But you got a guy from Turkey
Just got here in the 90s
Runs
Is ultra Secret
Pictures of Federal Reserve George Charles Dickens better
View George Soros
Bill Clinton apologize
Muslims
Let's get into some fun
Fun
Has the Ring of like a cork board with
Push pins in it
Tying strings together
He's from Turkey
To start this Law Firm that's all nonsense and
Conjecture
Would you like to learn more about Hamdi ulukaya
Alright was born to parents small sheep goat
And cheese farm in Turkey near the Euphrates River
He does not know his actual birthdate because his parents were they lived semi-pneumatic nomadic existence
Because phlox
We're known to move around
And they moved with the flock and he was born when they were sorta on the road
They made awesome cheese
Apparently
That's what they were sort of no no
Claims that Hamdi ulukaya showed up out of nowhere in the 90s
Well
That's not fair
He's trying to create this idea of a mysterious beginning
But it's not true
Is he okay
He's not in a turkey
1994 that he moves the United States University
Then the University of Albany
Restarted a little bit of business
Africology went to work on a farm upstate
His father was like a bro
They do do some more here how about you know we got this awesome artisanal
Feta cheese going on why don't you bring some of that Stateside there cheese sucks
What do you try and sell it over there
So he convinced him to do this
He started up his own little minor cheese operation
I need it for 2 years
But event at the end of it he was only able to really break even with a business
From the world
You know
Turcotte his losses
Stabbed 1005 by chance
Hamdi ulukaya noticed an ad for a craft yogurt plant that was shutting down
His lawyers and most of the people in
Circle told him not to but he decided to buy it
And decided to start up making some yogurt
He even
Went so far as to rehire some of the craft employees who were laid off
After the
They went out of business
They were not
I don't know
Yeah I don't know it's I think
Number one
Super irrelevant
A people
Because of the craft Factory going down swings in
Anybody even Trump would admire
Absolutely
I know you would still hate it because
He paid them the same amount
He didn't
Oh no did he pay them less eventually
Trump would hate him
Money on the table
Chobani is a variation of a Turkish word for Shepherd
That's where they at that's where the name for the company came from
I am in 2017
And whereas if you're small operation you would think that you would sell to boutique stores
And Specialty operations
He decided instead
The target normal grocery stores
To make his product accessible to
Everybody supposed to just really rich
Knowing that he couldn't afford marketing
You couldn't compete on that level
He made the shape of his package distinctive
You're the Chobani comes in those bowl
As opposed to like Yoplait comes in the Triangular Go-Gurt
The Squeeze
So he made that bowl which is distinctive and he made sure that his
Packaging was bright
On top of that you set up
Frequent in-store sampling
So people could get used to this new idea this Greek yogurt
Cuz it wasn't popular at all at the time it's a thicker yogurt he is reasoning was that American yogurt was
Two sweet and didn't like his kind of gross
Wanted to bring back what you do growing up
Yeti putting so much f****** a
To get people on board
Do used
To give to stores
The president could salad make a profit
Instead of giving the money cuz he couldn't afford it
Coming up from nothing he's he's doing all the all the stuff that other people wouldn't do
In order that game Business movie
Yes so people caught on pretty quick and they really liked is Robert cuz it's very good I don't know if you were if you enjoyed your boss
Lonnie Brooks
Not all the flavors but this is not this is not the yogurt taste
So in 2009 he starts getting carried by Costco which is acute breaks
The company basically gives them
They're huge windfall and makes them asses
Hundreds of thousands of cases that end up being
Hamdi ulukaya was not satisfied with just that he kept innovating
From that point on with all kinds of crazy s*** new flavors at
Desert line at this point you
Working on
Dip
Now yogurt dips
Drinkable yogurt
These are galaxies really innovating
But all call me when he makes
Things go to create jobs they all go to create jobs in terms of innovation product testing
All of this stuff and most of it is in that Twin Falls
Idaho plants
Rectus really awesome to bring tons of jobs to Idaho to a place where otherwise
The open this large Plant in Twin Falls Idaho has been a tremendous boost to the local economy
The New York Times article in March of 2017 highlighted ulukaya
To work with colleges to offer Technical Training for workers to solve the area's labor shortage
The Chobani yogurt plant in Twin Falls
Is the largest in the world and pays its workers in the area on average
Twice minimum wage
Oh
Yeah
Percent of the profits the net profits every year to charitable causes
The offers is employees
Parental
Which is something that is not legally required to do
He gave his employees a huge mass of shares when they went public
I want to read you his quote
Because I think it's
I think it's beautiful
Here so
Here's the specifics of it
CEO and founder Hamdi ulukaya told the companies 2000
Full-time employees at its Upstate New York plant Tuesday they'll receive shares worth up to 10% of the company's value when
When it goes public
Or is sold
This isn't a gift
Ulukaya said in a letter to employees obtained by USA Today
It's a mutual promise to work together with a shared purpose and responsibility
To continue to create something special and of lasting value
Holy f******
How we built this company matters to me but how we grow it matters even more
I want you to
I want you to not only be part of the growth I want you to be the driving force of it
At the sharing our success to be rewarded by
So this guy is
Literally if
Capitalism
It would look like this guy
It would look exactly like this
He disapproves all of that b******* about companies would need to leave if they pay their workers more
All of that matters
Because it's not
I really like this guy
He is a major donate to the Children's Aid Society of the Special Olympics is on the board of the Kennedy Center for Performing
Foundation which of the refugee program
Any part of the giving pledge
You are forgiven
Fortuner whatever doesn't have to be when you die
Most of your money
Is worth about 1.2 billion he's committed to giveaway over 700 million of his own money
To charitable causes throughout the course of his life or by the time
So
He seems
Really cool
Yeah he seems like a good guy almost
Listen
I am fairly certain
That if you're a white supremacist
Used million times over
You know what's amazing to like if you really listen to that
He is a massive
Success story for refugee
Interested in giving back to the community is living proof of what
Can happen
If people he is the quintessential American 100%
People talk about the American dream house
The American dream
That's what people want to find like negative things
You got sued
Because
Yogurt wasn't technically Greek
I really can't find too much negative stuff about it superhero ready thing like that
From everything I can find you seems really cool
Seems like the kind of business leader you would want
He seems to be encouraging all sorts of really
Great thanks also Alex Jones of the New York Federal Reserve
Bored
And Alex Jones
Know what the New York Federal Reserve there's absolutely no
Something to do with the Illuminati
The f******
Call the Elders of Zion and this stupid anti-Semitic
He's claiming that first of all is a part of the New York Federal Reserve board he is not
And he never has been
No
You can but you know what he was
Cialis
Who ruled with an iron
Know what he was was he was a member of the upstate Regional Advisory Board of the Federal Reserve Bank
New York
Which was back in
Now the upstate
New York regional Advisory Board
Do you know what they do
No the name is too boring
The board meets three times a year to provide the New York leadership with ilevel financial and economic intelligence
From an Upstate New York perspective
The board is composed
The chief executive officer and president of National and international oriented
Large companies
At that are headquartered in Upstate New York
This was because at the time
Headquarters in
New York
So I would assume
Alex tries to pretend to the all this s***
It's f****** secretive
If you just Google it
Everybody who's on the board is listed right here in front of me
All of the
Whatever business the president CEO of
New York James P lorito president Central Hudson Gas & Electric Corporation in Poughkeepsie
Scott Taylor
President
West Herr Automotive Group Orchard
Park New York
So mean just goes on there's just all these people who are in business
And I'll explain to pretend its secretive is b*******
Because right below it
PDFs you can download of the minute but all of their meetings
Legitimately you can see what they were talking about it Salisbury public
There's nothing secretive going on here
Their agenda and presentations list and the minutes of their meeting
Are right here
It's literally right in front of me
If Nixon can turn off turn off his recording for 15 minutes
Sure
Maybe maybe
Luminous artist specific as Alex wants them to be
What are more specifics and Trump's read out of his phone calls
So
Suck it
Anyway
Alex
Is trying to create this entire narrative about this really awesome
Just because I happened to be some refugees that are coming in
Nuance believe in
Then Alex has
It's super important it's about Alex slandering someone who doesn't deserve it
And he's committing further slander in this video
And it's really unfortunate
Because
You going to get sued harder
His putative
Another day of detention
So in this next clip
I feel like I've been talking too long
Alex
I really tried
What's a compliment
I built this podcast from the ground up
Do Costco's on board
Get really is trying to hit hard that he knows
The hungry goat is funneling islamist
Pandora country
He goes on to
Really suck up his chances of winning a lawsuit
And then
Kind of indict himself for some others
I will get to it at
What will discuss what I mean by that at the end of this
He's really bad at the record show
A guitar mode
Call back anytime
Mustard
Will be destroyed
Chobani yogurt in the world
Kyogre
Grocery store
Call Alex thinks that he strong-armed the government basically into putting Chobani into this
School lunch mandatory programs
That's what an argument
But who cares
Alright
So we're here just because
He says something really fun
Chobani yogurt
What did he start
Alex Jones Infowars
George Soros
We know some of the time
Pilgrim
Colonist
F*** you
Doesn't doesn't
So
He's saying that because I mean Lucaya is
Involved
And donate
To Refugee causes
Because of these refugees,
And commit crime
He is therefore responsible for those crying
Now you use that logic
Alex Jones
Is responsible for the man showing at the Comet Ping Pong with gun
Cuz he didn't record say that he was inspired by listen to Infowars
Further he's responsible personally
For every time
Someone harass the Sandy Hook family member responsible for all sorts of things that are illegal
I really don't think you should be making that argument
I really I really think
You have a bad lawyer
But also you're in the middle of a custody battle
You should not be putting this video out
I don't know what
You f*** your thinking
I have no idea who's letting you do this
I think
He should be wearing a
Maybe he had a very good lawyer
That would be happening right now or you'll just have a ball all day everyday
The briefcase
Wearing a tiny little mustaches painted on
It's ridiculous like I don't know I can't imagine in good conscience a lawyer being like alright look
We're trying to save custody of your children
Now you've been
Serve as lawsuit filed against you
Don't f****** blow that lawsuit
You're going to think you're on thin ice you did slander this guy we need to pray
You're f****** an hour and screams some of the most vile filled
Embolize
That he could possibly
It's like he's trying to destroy him
It legitimately
I can't
Many other
Okay
Alright
Here is
Here's your secret
That's interesting
If he uses the insanity defense
Which admittedly
Is
Not usable in civil court
Reply to like long-drawn-out behaviors
So far lasted for twenty years on the air
This next cookie gets back to that maybe this is maybe you do
Cuz then you can really hang on your performance
Right here what kind of insane person
Wood
Unless person was a committed performance
Actually
Committed in a way that otherwise people wouldn't like being all apologetic
Let your Siri sit and marinate because there's a lot more to get through and you might change your tune
Is he gets back to that sexual assault case that we discussed already and keep in mind at any time
Brings up a headline is Breitbart article
So keep that in mind most of them
Thoroughly debunked
What's media
Confirm
Literally found the first one
None of that is true
That's true they didn't plead guilty to rape
And all of those
Details the videotaping all that stuff is
It is just from Breitbart
There was one of the kids
Allegedly did videotape
The groping
The assault
It was
No sexual
Contact
But no penetration or anything like that
Doesn't make it better
Isn't
Alex is literally lying
Yes so
This media firm PR thing is not founded by George Soros
Course not it's called economedia
Can the
I could be a kangaroo
We're going to do with that but
Alex narrative
It's going to go through the next 3 clip
Which is what do you think
Is the plan for censorship
And the first part
Phase 1
Alright
I'm a big fan of phasers
I'm a big fan of the superpower phasing
Yep phasing through doors and s***
It is already happened
Effects
Everybody
Santa Cruz radio host
Everywhere is playing
Fraud
Play habit
It's your lawyer
That's what I'm
Comedy
That's phase one
All started with his water
Who is good friends with
Who was on The Advisory Board
State New York Federal Reserve stop
Bill Clinton
Do you know what happened to their
He was
The man who put
His lawyer through law school he's called in that favor
So
He has donated to the Clinton Foundation but one of the only things that I could really find
I was a concrete thing of his involvement with them
Little speech you gave on
September 29th 2015
He spoke at the Clinton Global initiative in New York
Do more than just write checks
To help alleviate the suffering of the display
Okay
Sinister
Underground Railroad
That's why we built an underground tunnel from
Idaho.
The channel it is
Play Islamic Channel
Yes
Everybody brands
Alex
You needed that you're so
Sears Phase 2
And this is where Alex I think
Is telling some truth lying about
Natural out what's true and what's not
We call we got a letter
We can get away get away with it
What's your point out that has been forced to admit
Idaho
Turned out
Pharmacist
Oh what are they going to do is that phase 3
I thought we didn't face to face
Tourism threatening a lawsuit
But what they did I believe
From all the information I can tell from knowing Alex like I do
They sent him a message
Much like James Oliphant is dead
You can't stay this s***
You can't
We're having article opposite says Idaho yogurt maker Imports
Migrant rapist
That yes you can't do that
So what Alex Jones.
Which he thinks is a retraction
Is he changed the headline and left the video up
That's not a retraction
So they they
They were unsatisfied by that pissant
Because what a real retraction would be is him coming on there and saying
We went a little bit too far we're sorry about that this is
You know we make mistakes sometimes
Is what they do when they make mistakes when they make mistakes
They go on
Sometimes
Everybody makes
Nobody is more front than Alex Jones when he makes a mistake
Go down there anywhere
So we can only assume
He's still a lot of headlines in the past
Basically what I'm getting Coronavirus
Sunnyway
Yeah it's coming up again Phase 2 was a letter
Reborns
Could have been
The history also could rolled up
The Iowa State or the Idaho Statesman
The local paper is in on it
What do they do
So
Extremely informative
First I have a photo of myself
Last year
Escorted by police
Just left it up there to make it look like I was being arrested
Imports
Yes you said all three of us things
Literally
All three of those things
Things are true we showed on the last episode the Sandy Hook
Right though
He has made those claims
About 11
And
He a hundred percent
Betty
He said all of us
So you're in trouble Alex
Big trouble
A I didn't respond
Blue Links there
Backup backup
Riveting television
That's not
That's not our YouTube channel
They got a copy of it
Where's the original
Headline
Alex thinks he knows the law
And maybe that is the case but he didn't do the headlines
I don't believe he knows what statutorily
Keep did just straight-up say that
These links
Show the original headline
Yes
So we know that the original headlines were those horrible inflammatory
Slanderous thing
So you can't even say like
They're just making up stuff
These guys
Thursday and what we'd originally
Alex tries to play like
Chobani
Attack Chobani
Robbie cancer
WWE style promo
Or he's really getting his
Horny are we getting some energy going
And also I would like to say that in his discussion of why would I attack your body
He shows his car
At this point he can't not do it
But when I when I said
Because he's a Muslim I'm basing that on everything I know about Alex and what he's about
Enjoy
United States
People working
Goodbye
Ado About
Muslim holiday
How could you destroy that don't you
You have chosen
Let's go
What's up let's do it
Everybody
We're going
So he goes on to start making
Some f****** c***
Rittenour at 10
The best I can in this next Federal Reserve connection
You talked more about how he appeared out of nowhere
Beard in the nineties
Because he was a college student in Ankara and came here
To go to college
He transfer colleges
What other f****** business would it their beef to have important records about him before that
I don't know
I don't know how else could he amassed so much wealth
Jim
Do himself especially ironic self-serving gin
Yes
Problem
It's all just a trap
Mysterious
Which is code for Muslim
He is real
He's involved with George Soros which we can't really prove
Outside of this one picture from Twitter and the fact that they're both interested in humanitarian causes
The Federal Reserve again is this
Anti sematic bathing
Yeah trying to use that is dog whistling
The people who were like
S*** all that evil Illuminati stuff
He was involved
Someone who advise
On business issues
In Upstate New York
4 years ago which if you're looking at the Twitter picture timeline we know that two years ago is when he met George
Zoro for the first time before that
Obviously
Why can't his relationship to George Soros
Beer
Retroactively change
H22 years ago
Also frustrating because it's like
What if everything is different
I don't know
Yeah what if everything is different I don't know
What happened in October
We would never know
No we just all believed until we are we do tonight
At this point Alex Jones is not even
We're not dealing with our stupid evil continue nope
Nowhere nerd
F*****'-a Lisa
Hirsute
Straight to evil pretty quick we're going to have Alex believes is the mainstream media
Media strategy to take him down
Which is interesting
How many phases
There's only one
Victory from the jaws of defeat
Idaho
Muslim population
You don't know
Your coward Alex most power guy
Listen
A little charisma
You're going to be you're going to be better off if David night goes down
Sure but also without here is my question
He does bring up one
That I am in
I'd love to hear about it
Create these
Cuz we not cuz you said we didn't create them push that push them but did he create
Can I answer that in a slightly dismissive way
Who cares
Because that's not what he's getting sued for
Okay he's getting sued for slander
Right
Can you then claim that it's a
Breitbart it right that headline
Didn't create the content
Breitbart to
They should
I imagine that my in the word bright
I don't know
There's also being assholes before complications
Yeah he's in the site yeah that's true but it seems like
Not a lot going on this is going to get really really really really really f***** up
Just a couple quick let's do it
Actually
Starts
Right now
This next clip
ESPN
And now
We're going to show you two hours of a man break
King his leg horrible
Start
Now this is
Bucked up
This the rest of this is basically breakdown
He's losing his mind
It starts with him talking about how evil the Idaho Statesman newspaper is
Flips onto
Pictures of the Idaho
He says I just want to say this but he's about to he says to look at it and it was like it was
Islamabad
Just like he said he was really
Bigoted schematics
So you talk s*** on the paper
And then
I want like I'll give you the high sign and that means don't say anything because
Throws to break
The harshest I've ever heard
Dark ocean it's real dark
Islamabad
It's like
Article
I mean he almost caters to Muslims
Almost accidentally said population
Muslim
Yeah
Anyway
So
If you look at
Their paper a lot of it is because there is a large Muslim population there
Arab population there not enough
So
The fact that they have stories better about their issues makes sense because it's relevant to the leadership of the paper
Yeah so f*** you Alex
Trying to make some sort of weird nonsense out of nothing
He's punching down on the
Idahosa
And the population
The Islamic people in Idaho
I mean it's about punching
He's punching
Down from your Ivory Tower of Lies
Yeah that's
To me because
Thing is before use
Nationalized
He's got his boy in the White House
A lot of popularity from being the Trump guy
My contention
Now that he's the truck guy
He should go after
I think he's punching down Soros out
Or something like that I think that's what he thinks he's doing the worst
I think that's what it is psychotic mind he thinks but the media lying and then
Crazy break
Amor
In all the Sharia law
AR
Deception
Everybody
Big big deal
Bike World
Hedda basically you're taking over our society
That's a hard the hard brake
You know you know when he's in the middle of a conversation
If you're going to drop
The Islamic people are taking over society and they bought off our governments and you don't want to prove it
You just want to throw to break and then not get back
So you just
Rosetta ether just like hey they're killing all of us taking over but the Brotherhood
Sharia law
Specific
It's because the people who already agreed don't need proof and you don't have proof
Convince anyone was
Skeptical
So what's the point of giving birth
It doesn't matter
Lose lose game for you to try and provide proof
Because it's a if he starts
Actually retracting
With the pizza gate thing we all saw everybody saw it and everybody went
Just like that because the moment
It's it all crumbles
Who else is going to come after
How many more how many more letters do you apologize to them
This Landorus
He doesn't win this lawsuit
How many other goddamn
Is he coming out that's
Exactly what's about to happen that's why he's so desperate
This is where is Alamo
Red blend wine
He does not get back to it and prove that islamists are taking over our society
Whatever
He comes back from break
Jesus some news
North Korea going to Nuke us
He basically just
Sort of acts like he didn't do anything wrong
And he was being magnanimous
By giving the change of headline
Which I guess is kind of what he has to believe in order for this
Anyway
This next clip
Alex gets mad at
To comment
F****** Christ and then
Then he starts ranting
And declares
He's going to Idaho
Go to Idaho
Kamen Rider
I hope you don't talk about the 42-inch up lawsuits
Let me show you
Name of the
Company
Yeah yeah we got it
Muslims
System
Images
1580 a.m.
God
The Federal Reserve board at 44 years of age
Citizens can find out what's going on just Google it I found a lot about it I read there
Threadbare minutes
It is really insulting that he
Keeps calling him out of his name
Yes ma'am
Also Alex
Also I think he's going to go to Idaho or there's just going to be bunch of like evil Muslims getting
Stop playing at all out
No no
Of course not there landed on unsuspecting Idaho farmers
Citizens of the town
Alex doesn't he
I apologize
Don't put racist
Anti bus because they're already there
So you might actually wondered
Is this is this really what this is all about is it you might be wondering that
2017 episode
They're a bunch of Secrets of 2017 apparently cozy
I think I figured out what this is actually all about
What
The deposition
Trotter big nose
Because it's a story we can document
Absolutely incredible
20% more off
I want you to try it
3% off big ol keg Edition
Concentrated bone broth
Super healthy amazing
Walmart.com or AAA 253
The ultimate paleo formula we have other big discounts Super Bowl
Infowars.com
Billionaire cuz of a 50 million
Contract no no you don't and you're probably actually taking a bath on it
The amount of product you could be
Be selling
And if you look at his history he's not
I really don't think he's the type of
You do not seem like it this type of person is pulling us
I don't know I mean
Does Mike cernovich
Actually work
Infowars
Okay
Is going to be fun
I know he's in trouble for some other stuff
I would probably
No
Because you ended this point
Distancing yourself from Alex's or encouraging him to do things that will destroy
He's Young
He could be the air
If Alex Jones
Goes away there's a there's a vacuum
Horrifying man to scream
Anti-muslim bulshit forgotten actually when we discussed him on past episode forgotten he was also involved in
In the gamergate
I forgot to do something around back then
I think you've already said that about him and I
This is really more to
To the point what's going on I think Alex knows he's going to lose this
Bleeding money really hard
If you have a hot product
It's going to sell out
You also don't have an Easter sale that goes on a week
Can a half after Easter
And then you don't
Yeah so I mean like
He's not moved
She's not moving product
You need
Costello This
S***
Yeah
I really think this is what it's about
He's got to go
You got to get as much
Revenues
It doesn't matter
Whether or not
Prophet prophet
It got to happen
Yeah he needs is much money as he can get right now
Plug ugly it is
Do you have to pay a lot of it away
Product
Know that money is going to
Give it to charity
That might be the best choice products
Indirectly
Through the courts
That'll be the case
Anyway this next clip
He gives a really really bad synops
So the situation in the lawsuit that he's
He blame
Hamdi ulukaya for the situation
And then
You'll see
Real weird
Alex loses the thread
George Soros
Of course he's really loose
She's working with him in terms of Refuge
Tg7 Peter Sutherland
Peter Sutherland a little bit later and I don't
And the Archimedes principle
Moral responsibility
Yeah
People getting murdered by their own
Horribly
In men's
Just tragic ways
And constant
And they want to escape
Then it is your
Moral
To do everything you can to help I promise we'll get to that in a minute in Morty
But I wanted
Because if we're not going to take it
Twisted Sisters playing
He was karaoke in with it
Do you think do you think
They do that without his knowledge karaoke
In the first place I have no idea cuz it's cuz
Pre-recorded it's
He's screaming like that
It's amazing
Anyway back to the B
Europe
The fact that
Hillary Clinton lose the election
With the ogre because the few times I've eaten it taste
Recover
And yours
If you're not coming
I looked up the Starbucks
Stock
It is up
Today
Cuz almost 1% up
And if you look at it on a 1-year basis
It is up
Really high from where it was about a year ago
You look at it on just a month base
It's up almost
Let's see you're almost five points
Really well X
It's a pretty
Consistently you look at it no matter no matter what how you look at it there's a there's an upward trajectory
So your whole argument that people are sick of
People hiring
Refugees in the water that's absolutely absurd
Yeah but that's the old
Alternate reality
The right-wing protects don't back it up
It don't matter
The reality that
Is that there is
A United
Front
Against them
And if there's more of us than there are
Them exactly
Allow themselves to accept
For once a
That most people
Bar
Pretty cool
That or in the middle
Then they would have to re-evaluate
Literally
Every position
They have parcel of it have to be business
Yeah
Because that also ties into something other narrative
Absolute
Success story
He's doing well he's doing great Starbucks stock is doing well they did hire a bunch of refugees but you know what they also
So hired a bunch of that
Initiative
To hire a lot of people who are in need of
I've work so I mean
Soot all over the place
You're going after
Genuinely
Yeah
For all of his
These are genuinely
Christian Acts
I would say so
Just every
F****** reading of the new test
Estimate that I can play
Put together
I'm basically going by
Luke
I got the rest of the gospels are also kind of bulshit to
Neither here nor there
6 vets
Exactly what's going on
Charity
Like these veterans
Yeah they want to be part of this
Country
Charity Stillwater
If they want to
Good
That isn't that they wanted Alex claims they don't want
Beat f****** whites
Don't
Want to be part of this
They want to be part of their own, they want to be part of white
Exactly
You use nobody
Nobody
Hates America
They hate it
Yep really do
Big time
Like
The Muslim societies that they espouse hatred
If the Muslim societies just said oh and
It was all white Christian
Exactly the same.
Exactly what they would be happy
You know what you guys
You guys don't have some bad ideas on this whole controlling
I'm not a big fan of that have an agent
We have some Middle Ground here
Skip this next clip cuz it's just
Alex Jones
More lying about the situation he's in
Pumping is stressed out
He brings up that whole Jennifer Lopez you should go to Somali and get raped
Situation
Our Heroes
That's her
Don't be fooled by the rocks
He goes on and I have to stress
I have to stress again because next week I'm going to play is minutes
Name that YouTube, too
There's nothing I love more than I love more than whatever these guys have to go
Like a Twitter handle
Bone broth 60w tram
Twitter handle
Are we
Like I like Twitter
But
Everytime I hear like
Tweeted this morning
I want to die a little bit
Knowledge underscore fight
Kinda this next week
Like I said
Is only a couple minutes after the last salesman
Because he's about to do even more pathetic sale
This is gross
Really trying to get
Calm your family needs high-quality gravity-fed filter stainless steel sits on the counter
Your family need
Purchase our products
The funding
I really don't think you could
The scope is lost
Deposition
Also I think I think he's not using the word depose in the way that the word depose
Like
And this is the
Court deposition like he doesn't get the difference in role-play it out
Entirely like Alex Jones in court.
If he gets into that courtroom and it's a slander trial basically or defamation trial
And they're like
Alex Jones on the
Irrelevant
Okay
I hold you in contempt
How old in contempt of court
So quick has already been
You're not going to talk about that
Not a business
This court case is our business talking about it all day long
Years back
Just f******
With the custody thing we don't know the details we don't know what caused it we don't know that the ex-wife at all we don't know
And the kids
It's a tragic
Sympathetic situation
In this case we know the details
He deserves this
Damn he's going down
Anyway
Let's get to the part where he plugs
Open most sad way again
Minutes after the last
Mama
We will stand up and fight
Your Love
More fun than we ever have for this time of year
And so we need to really increase
Silver
Vitamin B12 or liver Shield Oxycontin
Dot-com
BioLife Bubblegum
And we are all in this together
Barbie
You got to stand up
Change the world
No.
I sadly kind of agree with him but I'm
Before it
National
Ilysm is rising
I was starting to think about the other day that released
Kind of stuck in my craw
And your disk
It seems really weird that people like
A lot of Donald Trump's Associates
Emeryville pain
Putin
And bronchitis
Really connected
They seem to at the very least
Strongly support each other
Which is not really what nationalistic movements would do
They would not be all that concerned with International affairs
Baby really concerned with nationalism
Kind of makes you think they seem like there is a way
White Christian supremacist operation going on globally
Yeah I don't know
It's stuck in my craw nationalistic that have no skin in the game in France is Alexa
Yeah absolutely I guess I just
Only
What what's the what's the
What's the endgame for
White Maxima
I think it's probably
Nuking countries in the Middle East
I think it's probably Mass Slaughter of Arabs
But I mean
It really does seem like everybody's
England for the holy war
Yeah
Nnh
Exactly
Isis is angling for the holy war these people are
Like well
You've you want to holy water then we're going to give you a holy war and there's because of that
Because Bates
Christianity suicide
Alarm for the hardcore religions
Islam or Christianity
Impulse that's embedded in
Fanatical religion as a whole like I mean there are Ultra Zionist
Within Judaism bright like it sits Within
And it's not
Israel while understandable is still committing
And none of that is necessarily the religions
Location of it
Whidbey yeah
It's the
The coop
By the very elements
Set the religion
Itself with
Basically started
To come back
Like the idea of people using a system that was intended for good but it's also assist
Control what call yourself a Christian
But in the side of
Jesus versus
The Pharisees
You're on the Pharisee side
If you're if you're a republican that's
What's the same s***
And this is why we need a Jesus
Because
And for them it was they were that they were the
Judaic
I might be being sacrilegious with my understanding of religion and Jesus
But one of the things that
This is really
Into was that I'm not that much
Something you
I don't understand he's the son of God
Yeah but
That was kind of a metaphor
Central synagogue
6000 years old Earth
Jesus I did say a lot of
Jesus did say a lot of things like everything I do you will do to those sorts of
If you really want to do this exist in the world that is within you
Go ahead
Bee Gees
Should be pretending you're the Son of God literally
There's a lot of things with Jesus
You can be a cool dude
Yeah
No I have plenty of experience
Do not start a cult
Scouts
Jordan look
Come out again
Yep official I have a lot of
Very strong stance
Alex Jones
Just got done with it what if is very sad sale
And now
This next clip
I requested
We say nothing over it
I think everyone needs to hear it because
Is
Damning
It's really bad
It starts
Without right paranoia
It's just something else
And then there's a
Complete breakdown
And then he starts purring
Okay it's a wild ride
Would you
Would you say that
It's okay
This
Is
Razee
This is how he finishes his report
But it goes into
A special report that we're also going to be covering
But
Because it's the same topic
But I've cut out the parts
Of the special report that are just rested
To play some of the stuff from the Special Report because
Horrible I will be silent
Here we go you know what's
Going to happen
To Alex
They're failing all these attacks
This is what they do before they kill you
Systems
Blind
Other news sites
Everybody else out there
Supportive
I need your help Yelp
Because even though we've seen a record support
In the face of all this and I want to expand I don't want to
AAA 2539
As well
Pictures of every week
Football coaches
What is talking about
We've already we've already seen him talk about how
Sports are actually draining men of their their Tomatoes vitality
FedEx
Let's use this clip cuz it's so f***** up
I feel now I feel
Superhit hypocritical
If Eddie but like
Guys
Don't donate to
Just don't donate to our podcast
Just
Bye
From us
No.
Play Infowars t-shirts about going to refugees eventually
And guess what
Woodmore Infowars t-shirt off the street
I'm telling you he's in the middle of a breakdown
It's probably fake
Football coach
Please help me be strong
So you missed it cuz you're yelling over it but he claims that there's Muslims following
Everywhere
And it's a goddamn cult
Yeah there are Muslim
Crowd stalking
No
It's a mental illness
Basically I believe that
Strangers
Or actually connected with each other
And they're all following you
And the keeping up on keeping tabs on you paranoid schizophrenia
Trout stocking is phenomenon
Is super interesting
Because people believe
That's all I can
Get huge groups
People to
It's it's
To follow you
Keep tabs on you only attentive it is to drive you crazy
Do you think
That the intent
Underwriting
Is
A lot of these
Psychotic break
Smell I think he's probably seeing a couple of Muslims
And there are probably some reporters following him around because literally anybody with a head job
Probably has them reporters that he sees regularly because they're at the court
Is custody trial because he's dumb he's conflate
That's my bestie
Does not Merit
You claiming
The ball Islam is a cult
Imn
Praying that people give you more money
Also I love I love that final prayer
Christ please let our listeners on
It's serious for him
That
That's fine
That's why he keeps
If I lose its a free-speech laws
Do anything do anything for anybody else other than
Now we're going to get to this special report
I apologize that we're keeping it in
Cut out
The stuff that is
Redundant for the most part
Wanting to
Isn't this special report
Expertly produce
By 1 Rob do
Because some of his work producer
Cameraman
On-air Talent
Lawyer on-air Talent
Let's call it let's call him on air
Start
And it is
This is already play
Only his news is available to the public
Whoops
April 24th
George Soros
I don't ever want to hear
Kindness and Alex Jones anywhere f******
Nope
Cruelty
You're mistaking my cruelty for
I don't even know
That's no
You're a boss.
Okay
You know how
Is force
To call herself
Like because by law
He should be
Calling earlier
Just because she is by law a fat
In the same way
Alex Jones
Should not be allowed to use
In regards to him
I would love
Alex Jones you have to publicly recognize that your propaganda
Every speech
Every episode you have to say
I'm interpreting
Non-factor
But
Look what I love.
Still preserve his free speech
He would still be allowed to say all the things
Again
That Cliff was essentially wrestling promo
You're not about to see Alex Jones you're about to meet
The American people
And then a blazing red fire filled Infowars logo comes up the music swell
Is just
Stanford
This guy came out of nowhere blah blah blah
A little bit of new information
He says some really really
Really hard islamophobia
In this
I want it I want to play Just
I think I'd like five clips
From the Special Report
Play the special report in this first hour on April 25th
Package together
Like
This is ugly
This is really really ugly
There's some fun lies along the way
But some of the stuff he says
Is inexcusable
And it is absolutely
Dog whistling to racist
At worst
Incitement to violence
I think
Far be it for me another legal scholar
But I sincerely think that were on the cob
Of life
Stuff that you
May not be able
To get away with
Like
I don't know
Necessarily
Fire in a crowded theater
My gut still tells me it's protected free speech
Except for the slander portions get absolutely not okay
Everything
About Hamdi ulukaya
Is absolutely not okay
Straight up making s*** up slander
But the staff about like
Does the horrible stuff he says about Muslims in general
I hate it
I'm really against it I think it's hate
Speech
But I don't know
I don't know if it's
It's tough for me to say I'll let you know
Weigh-in as it goes along
Just know
In the four months of doing the show
So far
We've been
Ron
This
And the Chris Cuomo's daughters
Thing
Chris Cuomo's children
Are the the closest I've got to like
I can't do this
Yeah it's just
So f******
Stupid
And awful
And I
Can't wait for him to lose this lawsuit
Here we go the first clip
Is not so heavy
He has some
Thoughts
About
Hamdi ulukaya
Connection to Turkey
And he has some of his facts
Islamic dictatorship
Turkey Mike Flynn
Two portions of the u.s. lunch program
He doesn't
It's a phone
Nope but the part that I think he has
A little bit wrong is that
Came to power in
20 years after
Hamdi ulukaya
I'm here
So I I don't I don't
A dream
You might be a wisp
Hearts of man
There is one swamp in Idaho
And the will-of-the-wisps
Finally games
We have a complete lunatic is our president right now
F****** monster
Is destroying the world 20 years ago
Was in office
Perfect but it was a very different world back then
Government
Change over the course of 20 years
So to save it like
First of all there's no evidence that he has any involvement with the government
Second
The government has changed a lot
Trump just congratulated
His power is it
Guys
We're in for a great
4 years
It shouldn't be
Everybody who's fun
Run for
God
Especially Oliver listening in the UK
As long as you become a citizen
Run for
But first
Starting yoga pictures
Or appear out of nowhere
Imaginary
Run for
Because
Go this isn't this isn't it
Literally what's half
Text
Is trying to cut the corporate rate
215 1st
They will a
Because that's what all the
F****** nightmare
They just
What text
Willing to
Risk
Nuclear goddamn
F******
Text
Kerasotes have President Pence
Exactly
Let's get rid of all abortion laws let's do
President
Text World bro
Even if
So this next
Clip
It starts with Alex
Fully not understanding what this lawsuit is about
Clearly
Explained
An established
It's about headline
Contact
Within articles and videos that he posted
That were slammed
Spy the
Literal definition
The trial should laugh
45 bit
It should be like
Hey Alex
You said this
Did you retract it
I think it should go a little bit longer cuz you should give Alex a chance to prove it
But he wouldn't be able to
Let him spin his wheels a little bit and then
Jokester.
Videoing
Over
So I understand what's going on with the law
Expressive
Islamophobia
We go there you might scream before we go
Because
Mentally and emotionally preparing
To survive
I hope we can only survive
Question
Which
Which path
Leads to his
Destruction
Because Alex Alex is courting
The end of his career
No matter what really
If
Apologize
Traxxas
About Tabata music
Right now
So he doesn't
He doesn't have to deal with the lawsuit
Which steaks
I think I think that at this point because they asked for retraction
I think it's happening no matter what
What if what if lamp
We
We guess
Probably correct
That if he does that for them
More of those letters
So we know that then he's got more and more
Retractions
Which
To wind up cutting in
Because they suddenly know it will erode his credibility
Perception of credibility
Yeah okay
So
To me going to be a slower like
Like death by 1000
Right
Whereas
Him
Pudding
It's f****** foot down on this
Now he's going to go
I don't know if he'll go broke cuz he is
Crazy rich
Infowars is really what
It's not him personally I assume he's personally part of it
But Infowars is going to be hit with
Punitive
Is well right right I think it'll be a big hit
Here's here's what I think
I think it's inevitable
No matter what he does
It's bad for him
How I would describe
Branch
Pam
And that decision
You have the apologize
If you go down the apologize I think you're assessing
Correctly
There will be a bunch of people who will be like
Now it's time
Farrar's
And then
Yeah it will spiral from
If you go that don't apologize root
He's going to lose
Unfortunately
The exact same results
Was going to happen
Once he loses it
Those people who wanted apology
These before will now also be
Yes it will just be a bandwagon
But
His money on the
Apologize
Like on this one
I think he wind up losing everything
I think he hears my
You think it's a better outcome for
Losing
Well that's that was my next thought was
This is his blaze of glory
Yeah this is where he gets
To go down as a martyr
Instead of as
Holy Ship
You know what just came to me
One of the songs he plays
Sometime coming in from break
If you ever heard Pancho and Lefty you are interpreting his music as
His subconscious
Pancho and Lefty
Willie Nelson Merle Haggard Dead version 2
They could have had any man
They only let him get
It's so far
Out of kindness
Rihanna and will do a
Covers album do you understand what that
Maurice's
Who got away with the you know a bunch of crimes
And the federales
They could have taken him down at any point
At any point in Alex Jones's career
Especially after he calls him a Nazi collaborator
He's the character in Pancho and Lefty
Yeah he is the guy who's gotten away with it
Out of the kindness
Or just the I don't want to deal with it of George Soros
4 out of all of the people on the ulukaya
James alefantis
All these people who have legit lawsuits
He only they only let him get so far
Kindness I suppose
Isaac said I think I might have to deal with
Petroglyphs
Alex Jones
Possibly I mean
There's some other songs that relate I met we talked about the Mike and the mechanics Saga super Alex Jones
Have to be at 8
Royal music
Who plays we're not going to take it coming out of break
Obviously there is
Bubble method
S***
Yeah I think I think
He is like
Maybe
Now we're reading it is
Subconscious way too much but I think there might be a part of himself that sees him
Self as
The Last of a Dying Breed
Like this kind of
Thank f******
The same f******
Right
Yeah he's he is part of it
Take the rest of us
With
Possible
So yeah I agree
The Blaze of Glory path I think
Strategically actually is better
Because even if you get
And Infowars goes out of existence
He can
Hold on to some thread of his credibility
He can present it as
F*** man
This is the globalists screwing me and trying to take everything I have away from me now he's wrong he's lying
But there's enough people who would believe him and pity him
And even if you get sued
Put on the bankruptcy
He can get a job
Like he can
What are you talkin about maybe you can get that f****** turn down over and over again
Like he could land somewhere if he get sued into Oblivion
No one tire
The grace to possibly do in that trial
The propaganda skills
He has at his disposal
I think you could turn it into a complete circle
Do you know what I think he's going to do
I think he's going to pull a Bill O'Reilly and when he gets kicked off the air
He's going to
Call the brain battle
Oh no
Revo clips
Parody on Colbert is brain fights catalyst
Still available
Speculation
The next thing is
He is
He's going to go broke
My theory is
Homeless
He fights all these
And thankfully he's going to lose custody
Exactly
Even if it goes
Completely broke you still go
That's how this works in our society
A cynical as I am
Golden parachute
To bulshit
He has I just
I just want to
Post 19
1920s
You see all the
Guys who use
Used to be million
Sucking broken
Broken
Coming soon to America near you cuz it's just more about the tuberculosis outbreak
React
It's not happening as we documented the people they are the album
Yeah and the people on the ground or saying
This is not that
The cases we've looked at
Contagious
Yep it's not a public health risk at all
Deal with every immigrant
Comes in within 90 days of them being
So are there
The fiction book
All the Hat I just don't think it's worth pointing out is again all the things
That he brings up our headlines
Are awful
So great
Breitbart will not hold up in court
He tries to cite that as evidence
Of his argument
Is done
That seems
To me that seems like
That puts brightburn
Oh no he's he's introducing them into the conversation
Alex
For this
Defamatory
And he introduces
Doesn't that then mean that you
Absolutely have a case
Actually you know what we can't
This next clip
But I thought of
About
I mean it's just more about Hamdi
Yeah but it is is like sort of getting into
Alex Jones
Problem
Youjizz
And then
He plays this quit
Sutherlin
Who works at
The UN in terms of
Fuji stuff any plays this clip
Any
He presented in a menacing way
But I want you to really listen to it
Tell you my perspective on it ahead of time
I think it's a great
We'll see if you agree
Just like agenda
Refugee advocate
Is also on the board of the Federal Reserve Bank of New York
Sounds a little drunk
Undertaker 1951 convention
Activator for refugees at the responsibility
Hiding behind borders and fences
We have to work together cooperatively together to make it better work
She plays that clip
Evidence
That's supposed to be
Yeah
Nefarious
Okay well no I understand first off
I want him
To narrate audiobook
Carlos L Adelman
It's beautiful the most relaxing MSR video
It's an MSR you
Where am I
ASMR the only thing that I think you could really take issue with
Especially based on Alex Jones is worldviews
You saying that like we can
Hidebehind border
Because I was pissed off about the idea that we don't have
But
What he's actually saying there is that like
Pretending the issues outside of our country don't relate to us
The old way of thinking
Now
People being brutalized
Another country
You are trying to
Leave at
Or our responsibility
And it is heart
To be like no
We're afraid you might hurt us
The Peter Sutherland
If that's the best
You've got
Against him
You failed
He sounds like he's really
Yep and I assure you our
The end is also we want Islam to take over the world
Positive
Hundred percent
We okay with that
Ulta beauty like
Okay
So
That that does seem to be the center
Conflict
OurTime
Is
The internet
Exploded
Globalization
So much faster
Human races
Everyone
Across the
Nose
Well I mean if your Kinect
Did the internet
You know what's going on
Or you can find out with
Anywhere on the play
Witches
Something that was not pause
Before 2000
Simply wasn't a real thing
So he's
When he says that
The days of borders
Ozark
Because
You-and-i friend
AR
Citizens of the world
I'd like I would say to me
The way I see myself
I am less than America
That I am
Human being
I agree with that I find I find the the idea of
America
Not just
You know not least of which to be
Like it is
B d idea of
Do United
Has
As much good as it's done
Also committed a s*** ton of genocide
Has murdered so many civilians
Is absolutely.
Destroying the protection
Things that are built in for it
Every single part of the United
Now
Is
Eating itself alive
2A
A billionaire
And that's all it is
But their strike the United States
Remind
Still uses yours
You still love the image of Dad
You still have
Your actual debt
22 my point
Fuel
Lascana
2 dni
I do too
Let me ask you a question
Is it do you think of it it's
The same way that like
You feel like less
A citizen of Illinois then you do
United States
It's the exact same thing is compartmentalization
Text Emily we live in Illinois
I live in America but we're citizens of the world
It's just
Going to the next
Level
Concept of the type ones
Civilization
Has
Gotten Mastery over its entire
Right entire galaxy
3 is
5 almost
That's to me the compass
Is it between
And and it's
It's Barry Allen Oliver
These elections here
Who want to be part of
And the people who want
Be part of
That's
The ultimate lesson of
Brexit
Is
That complex
Our next clip
What I would describe
Really sad
About turtle on
Into a ramp
But I think is based in Fanta
But I'll let you decide
We're watching a Holy War II jihad's
France
Sweden
Belgium
Urgent urgent
Run
Codenames
Asia
Took over all over the place
Holy Roman Empire
Plasma
It's Been Working lyrics
We can't bend over
Of Europe and London
Mary major
All you do is
As we're playing this I am starting to realize
You do sound a little
The report not as bad as that
March 30th
But
I mean
I'm not here
Vanderlaan Zach's
No refunds
He is
Truly
Journalist
Terrible
The only
Coup attempt that I genuinely
I'm so like
There is very little doubt in my mind that that was
A literal false
Totally and that is such a
One it's a it's a
It's a brilliant move
It's a brilliant move if no one had done it but
Before
And no one could like
Do some signs of this
Didn't really go down
Cultural revolution
In China
Whenever he wants to like come up and demonize erdewan
Ever
F****** wrestle with
The fact Mike Flynn was paid by them to the lobby on their behalf
That makes
Plan has registered as
Is a foreign agent
Turkey
And
The Heat
Constantly
Him and his son
What are retweet Infowars
And I have no doubt in my mind that the two of them have spoken
Before I don't know I don't know I just know up I mean
Based on based on comments that he's made it
Past
He's made sort of indication
Information
A phlegm
But not from erdogan himself
No connection between Alex and Alex
No
I'm shocked that he doesn't make fun of how Sebastian Gorka
No early ones name
He might not even wrote
Never brought tomorrow
We have a literal doctoral
So I was reading up on that on foreign policy
Very
Globalist
He cites Wickham
Pedia and a couple other like really on
Scholarly sources
It came out recently that he defended
His doctoral thesis
In front of not a doctoral committee
He may not actually have a doctor
Sounds like he got a mail order.
He's a literal
You know that rule of like the
When you bring up Hitler the internet rule
He's an actual
Like he's a literal
He was part of an order
It was it was
Yeah
Has a Nazi
National Security
44 whenever we had our Nazis
Develop
Science 4A
This is like
Hey
You know what genocide you guys are
Wernher von Braun coming over cuz he knows a lot about rocket
We're flippantly talkin about it we're not serious
Like I told you about this before we started recording
I had a dream last night that was about
Coming nuclear war
Just don't think the M very much like
It was at that moment where we know the we know the
The missiles are coming and they're about to hit you know It's Goin Down
And with with nuclear missiles
But in this
Particular in
You would have
Time like they would report
Few minutes are the missiles coming
It takes it takes a while
Like it takes a half hour time is a few minutes but then the actual
Yeah exactly
Are they wouldn't tell us
The point was the point that there is
Escape from
There was definitely a lot of relief and
Where am I
Well
Finally f******
Hangover like waking up now knowing that it's
Probably coming I mean we've compared it a couple times to like
Just basically
Play
Just come already
Sing about that
That kind of
Fear is
My my instinctive course is
To take that
Not going to destroy the world but the more you read about the the Cold War
We came
3 *
Minutes away from an act
Old nuclear war was largely inactive
What do like come on guys
Let's not do this
False alarm
That's like the Russians
Thought that missiles had been launched
And they they
And there was a guy who was
Sent to Siberia
For being the guy who
Defied the Russian government
He did
Personally
One man Saves the World
Exact
Because you could never reveal the
One man save the world
So it is it is that kind of thing where you're like well this fear is irrational but
I find it
Super rash
It seems on the
Yeah it really does know Jordan
Two more clips
These are ugly
Is a very ugly
I've saved
The worst for last
I didn't save them it's all in chronological order the order
No I understand I'm not blaming you I am just saying that you are the bane of my
First clip
Defend himself
Because these are so bad
I want to talk over them
By this first one
He talks about how he's going to
To act
In this court case
Talk about
Basically hopes
That the Iowa dirty are the Idaho jury is as racist
And then he just gets into what I would describe as
Straight up
Literal race
So here's that
Mike down
I'm just going to pause it there really quick because when he says all when they see all of this
Is referencing a bunch of Breitbart article
Was that he had shown before that
Just forget just to give it some contacts at all propaganda s***
Be f****** not admit
But then he applies
All your employees hate you anyway
Patty
Probably not true
Is he treats his employees hope it's not
Doesn't
Trump
Having Teddy comes
Herbalife
That's pathetic
They're so
Manny
So many
Do you know this goes down to like
Alex not knowing
VIP people are decrying the
These things and there are a bunch of
Credibly
Awesome
Wonderful people who haven't
To be Muslim
It's not because
They don't exist
It's because he doesn't
Try to find him
It's just something he doesn't know about
Exactly
If this idea that like
All of the information that I represent on this show
Elvis
About
The Idaho situation
Tuberculosis outbreak
All the stuff
Isn't information that's on accessible to him
It's like he doesn't want to engage
The fact that he has in the past that the
The Sandy Hook was fake
It was all actors
Isn't information he doesn't know
Defamation
Camp no
Review have to stop doing what he's doing
It's information
That I would
Suspect
His people
Either
Purposely
Implicitly
Keep away from
Right and what's unfortunate is
If you don't know that information
Reality
What you end up doing is
What you just did
Which is
Brutal
Hatred
Of all Muslims
Based on
Hawaii
And this is this is the other thing that we
We talked about earlier
About
Being about that
Idealized version
Of America
That idealized version
America is
One thing that I ate
Did that does
Exist
Is the way that
So many
Immigrants
Come from so many different
As with so many different
Eventually what happened
We all see ourselves
And so a lot of that
A lot of that
Cultural shift
From way back when
That
Like the genital mutilation
So many Muslim
In America
F******
Sure
Because they're Americans
Part of our values are
Turtle girls
Sure
Whatever reason why they gravitated here in the first place
And how have we like
Like how is it that we
Become
Allies with
Germany
Japan after
It wasn't by
Demonizing
It was my thing
Caesar this is Who We Are
Complicated
Rrr
Our values
Steve the idealized American values
Are far more effective
Combating
Terrorism in
Combating all of the
Anime
You know what you thought only create more terror
What did I do
You just mirrored Alex Jones
He makes the Arkham
The Americana
Is the bestest
The sexiest system
Everybody loves it
Dealer
Sister that's Americana
Not today
No we have different definition
It's not important
I agree with you
Idealized version of what
Analyzed
Aspirational versions of
The freedom and tolerance and no such a thing
Exactly
We're going to eat this last clip
I think
A couple minutes long
But it's worth it
For the roller coaster ride that it will take you
Okay it is disgusting
Are we listening to edited
In its entirety with no
Enter interruption
Possibly
I might closet at one point I don't know
It is
Disgusting
And I can't stress that enough
This is okay
I hate it
And I hate Alex for sale
Maybe you don't know what it's all about so you come out
He's talking
Directly
To Omni Hotel
Mister know-it-all
You don't know what Islam is all about
I think you might be
You're not
Ever going
Globalism
World war is Islam
If you want to support the broadcast.com
And by those products.
To knowledge for the articles
Note
This is what the global don't want you to see
Because we are still effect
Racism got Trump elected
Will be their final
George Soros
Involve this whole program
Operation
Juggernaut
The word
What's your own
We have products you
Weather
Against a bunch of authoritarian globalist third world population
World War 3
Closing all of us
The father
Owl Spirit system of globalism Islam in modern liberalism
Affected much stronger
Church's parts
Because
Used approved God
Wow
Cross the state
Crushed
I just kept pause
Jesus
They wouldn't
Would have bought some bone broth
Sure
Greenbrier
Infowars
We will fight
Weather
Jesus
Jesus would have turned
Serving of bone broth
The masses of bone broth and bring Force
Pills
Ultraman
Pathetic
Exploitation of religion
What are the things that makes it all the more pathetic
What is the heat
Arguing
A certain group is using
Islam as a weapon
In the act
Using Islam
As a promotional
Yeah he doesn't mean any of it
There is
Know if you are
Believer
Literally any
And you are sharing
You should engage would like heck
Every
Possible
Religious tax
Morality
Right
Emotional
Yeah like there's no there's no other
Dividing line
There's another problem
They never really address
We talked about the
The judeo-christian
In Tradition
There could just ask the label
I don't I don't like hearing that
I was apart of it
Do not
As long as a part of the
As we all know Islam doesn't believe that
Never reference
No no
Definitely not
That Jesus character
Even a lot of Eastern religion
Recognized
I mean a lot
There's a real cool dude
But
Degree
Jesus
So that last clip I just feel like
For a little bit burnt out on
Is hate so we're not responding
Through this entire f
Episode
As as much
You built that
Clip Up
That
Just
Parcel
Light amplification
Like I'd like on your iTunes you click the volume up one
Time and that's his race
Disagree but just be
Because of how passionate
Italy like
Exploiting
Christianity was and then
And then going out to break
Ending the report on saying our God is
The true God right across the state
Hanok god of Islam
But hold on right before that
Saying if you give us money we will do this
That's right
So over it
So clear that you
He's a con artist who's being
Because he didn't understand
F****** libel and slander laws
Andy's
Begging his audience to please give me a bunch of money so I can
Stay in this
I'm about to
Crazy
How does a guy like this become
What he is
It's for
Who is the multiple lawsuits
Using Christianity and exploited who is Connie
I got like this could never become president
Alex 2020
That is likely as f****** anything
Holyshit
That isn't like
It's f****** auntie
F****** radio show
If you have 45 million weekly listeners
That's a big built-in fan
How many votes did f****** Hillary
Get30
No I don't know
No way more than
I don't know numbers
Let's just go
Alright
Vermilion so anyway
I think we've come
To I would like to submit
By saying that Alex Jones
Shoney's cards
Really
Really angry
But doesn't really
Stand
Bad facts
Either he's really angry
He knows his
Listenership
His listeners
Really angry it is
And so he's
Explain
To get as much money
It kind of feels real though I think
I think there might be some bigotry on his part
That that is
Responsible
We've established that but how much how much does he probably not
He just he just
The money man
So he's got some custody battle he's got some lawsuits to go for
Future lawsuit
Better f******
So that's conclusion number one is that he hates Muslim
In some way
Weather
More advantageous weather is moderate or 1000%
Second conclusion
Yes
Hamdi ulukaya
Can you add a good dude
Awesome
Two other billionaires
How to do what he's doing pretty good I'm not saying he has a perfect record I'm sure there's some
The same with any human in the world
He's killing it
So far seems like it
Is going to win this loss
Alex Jones
Sweet Leaf
He has no key
He's elated out over the course of an hour
The only things he has our
He's a part of the Federal Reserve
He's not
He's connected with George Soros
Yes they're both
Global a bedroom
Picture on Twitter
Please increase Court
The judge.
Flimsiest Alex is going to lose this case
But I'd like to remind you
Alex good luck
Really is
We should start looking for another right-wing topic I've told you we got
We could do any of these episodes about that
I'm glad there's no end to right-wing propaganda terrible of that was
Seems like hateful white people having
A non-exhaustive
Multiply
Anger
Minorities
Strange
It's almost like our entire country
Almost
It's almost like our society
Is gone in the direction of recognize
And trying to work
Towards equity
And people can't get on board with really threatened by it
Cannery
Yep
Yeah anyway
Guys
Let me ask you a question
Is going to get sued
Hard
Are you just want to say that again
It's very exciting
Looking
Find out more information
Turnabout
You can do that at knowledge.com
You can do that there you could also follow us
Twitter at knowledge
Underscore
Correct if you wanted to listen to this podcast
You could go to the
You could also go to
Yep
You could search Naruto
Subscribe to our website
You can leave a review
Yeah that's a nice reviews males from
California
Big shout out to you
I know it's awesome
Getting on board 11
Thank you to everyone who has donated
All the people who have donated in the past we're not yet you will you will you will
But as long as new people
Donating
You're going to get pushed your long-time absolutely not
But I will terrible I will say this
The people who have been waiting
For the longest
It'll be that much
This is all about the ratification we're edging
To be fair those people donated
Before there was a second
Policy wonk
Title not leave this in
This is been not that fun
It's been fun but like I hate this
I really sincerely hate
I'm glad Alex
Is getting sued
You deserve it
UCF
You slander man
Who didn't deserve it
IU base
Most of your point
Listening
Cruelty
This is legitimately just
Mason Point chick
Coming home to roost
You thought no one would notice you
Been getting away with it for
For so long
Just saying whatever you want
I had a guy stepped up
Said no
I got to put up with this
And now you're suffering no
You are suffering the consequences and you don't deserve anyone to come to your house
Because you suck
Single finger
You deserve it
Now this is a f*****-up
I wonder if they'll play this video in York
Cuz it seems like
Like we said this
Just play every video every
If I were a judge
And the way I heard it
He recorded this yesterday
In the middle of it he talks about how he's not fake
He's not an actor he's not
And then
Misaligned Muslim
Why
Says he's not fake news but
Delivers fake news Wild Thing
Says that the Islamic God
Yep
Insight
People to violin
Basically
I don't understand why you would do that
I don't like
Cuz he's losing
How do I get help Alex
Until next time
Let me ask you
After all of this work
Through this
It's b******* after all of this
Just struggle
We have been on
Would you call
I know that I've donated
Get to the show through my research
And I think
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work