I'm sweating
College B
Knowledge fight
MoneyGram
Alex
College.com
A little bit about
Alex Jones
What up
What is the worst
I don't know
Anything like that but like
Did you have a high school guidance counselor
Some terrible advice
I don't know if it comes to my mind the most here is
Don't give me that gave me the
How to replace the back
Stupid
Nothing comes to mind is like you think about parents
I guess this isn't too much advice
Bad move
From from the like a good source of
Afraid of thunderstorms
When I was a wee boy
We moved to Missouri when I was
News 10
Thunderstorms
The boy had no idea what they were
Yeah there aren't
I've never seen one in the four years that I was there
And from what I know of Missouri and there are these things called tornadoes
Thunderstorm
Right it's so like I have this built up in my head that if there's a thunderstorm
Enter my mind tornadoes are almost identical to hurricanes
So I had to
Careful Terabithia read them when they were thunderstorm
And so I was a old
And I was scared in bed during a thunderstorm
And
I called out for my dad
In the middle of the night
He comes into my room and
Then don't worry the worst is over
And then as soon as he says the worst is over this
Would lightning outside the window
Basically
Loudest
Yeah yeah
As soon as the Thunder claps
Subsided
The Lights Went Out in the house
Tornado siren
Hilarious
My dumbass.
It's a good gamble to say the worst is over your right
He was way off
Very funny
And other tornado warning about it now but I know more about Alex
Tell me about Alex
A unique episode 2
How to present to the people
Last episode
Getting a bit into
PVP
I have done quite a bit of digging around trying to find some information on this
And come away from it as confused as I was when I started
Harry's
Steve Perry is
Not the same a different fairy will come up in this episode
There is a Seafarer that I will mention later
That is super bizarre
How great I feel about people who signed up and are supporting the show
Do I sharpen my skills on a tornado fields
Missouri
We got today.
To get through
And express our gratitude
First of all Matthew thank you so much
Emblem
Thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Text Brian
Journal policy wonk
Louise
I'm a policy wonk
Next Trevor thank you so much
Journal policy want
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much you are now policy wonk
I would like to believe that that's either TJ is in Tijuana
Okay
Or TJ Lavin host of the real world
I show that I no longer watch but long
Is it still on
Yeah
Then finally likes
Epoch
Thank you so much you are now
I'm a policy wonk
Absolutely
Something is that a name
It's like policy wonk but inverted
Wow wow
Poke
History all the time
Do you like sports or website now.
Here Comes
What's in front of us today
Is a profoundly complicated episode of this podcast
As we dig through past of Alex Jones Show in 2013 to learn more about how he ended up believing that no children died it's
We found it speeds
Pieczenik is absolutely the first person
To make that argument on are in a way that Alex
Considers
He thinks about it
Even says that it's blowing his mind
Hearing Steve
Pertronix
Of course
We've encountered Steve many times in the past
On Alex's show
And we've delighted and how he and Alex
As they did and I watched episode of our podcast
That's where Alex cult
Who's in the middle of trying to survive hurricane Irma
Alex wanted to talk about how Trump was being surrounded by globalist and he was under attack
But Steve wasn't having any of it cuz he had water coming in
And here is a little taste of
Call house arrest like Rapunzel
You don't need the president on house arrest punzel
He can do what he does but I am you to judge the Republic
Because I don't like many other people and like many others
Wait for dinner order maintain the Republic
Weather Trump is here
The Republic
15 years of level of selling out the country and
Trouble
Of course not
I told you that
The system that was put in by the EU
I was I was
Natalia brilliant
In the real world
2 days before
Yourself
Favorite quotes of all time
This which is just
Spectacular
Just sick of the bulshit
Respect
I find it
Endlessly hilarious that
One Clip that is so integral to our entire show
Was part of a lost episode from 2 years
Have to resort to this episode that could be
The moments like that are really fun
Jordans
There's a relationship with Alex that most guests
Don't
Alex
Really nice
Or at least he did for a very long time
Steve was a former State Department official an expert in psychological warfare
Proximity to Alexandra's professed respect for Alex's work
Made him invaluable
In terms of making Alex appear
Credible
There's no way they didn't understand that dynamic
So you can just yell at Alex a little bit here and there which is always so much fun
It upsets the normal Power Dynamic of the show where in Alex is the
King of all that he surveys
The other side effect of this
Is that Steve was pretty much able to say anything on Alex's show
And Alex had to treat it like a serious
Worth considering
Like all the time who can forget when
Donnybrook
Sandy Hook and Miss Parkland false flag
And what you looking at
Vestiges of the press trying to be relevant
So park Mendoza
Alex is smart
To be like
How many false Flags
How long are we going to
Keep calling me
It's getting thin
Steve went on
Straight up the Las Vegas shooting
Let's go straight to the shooting in Vegas
Number one why I can't get on the internet the reason is very simple I'm being here
The reason why you hearing me now it's another person bumps part of 9/11
Call Inspira sleep everything you said David
The same thing I said with him twenty-four hours of 9/11
My CIA operatives admitted that they did it I have the names of the people involved
Bush Cheney
Troodon
Giuliani
The Mossad operatives to blow up the building and then Conde and as well as
Going down
This is what happened
So what we happening
What's happening now is anyways Sandy Hook false flag
San Bernardino false flag
Yesterday in
End in Las Vegas a complete false flag
You could hear the same setup as we had in Sandy Hook
The Narrative is so predictable that no one was killed there was no shooting
And in fact what happened in the giveaway was this was the greatest
Killing Emmett Idaho kind of America that's distinctive Trump
He has to have the most in the bed
Sad artist that Trump Bell Angeles
System and co-opted by the Department of Health
CIA and FBI what we need to do an Americanized Amman
The indictment of President indictment of officials
I don't know if it'll happen but this is enough
Reasons to start a revolution
So we got to do you say Las Vegas Noah
How to say if David Knight wear any
Good as a host
Have you tried turning it off and on
Hit the switch on the back
Turning it off and
But David has ever called his response was
Yes but Sandy Hook definitely Texas
16 election
Steve
Claimed that he created Bernie Sanders as a psyop
Well Hillary's in a very serious problem and once again I want to thank you already asking you what we did wasn't
Back to do a psyops
Hillary
Which was ineffective create Bernie Sanders
Bring Em Out
Co-op Drake streamlab
Samantha bring biting in
The Coop to middle and then two breakup and fractionate her system
You know what we got to eat created Bernie Sanders
Bloomington
Doesn't know that
Leo zagami
He's working at cross-purposes Leo zagami information
To hear a guy who claims to have committed 911
Baillios job together
Things are turning off phones to this
In Florida
So we have created
Incredible thing
Who could forget
About how also
He created
Can enlisted him to run for president
Your take on Donald Trump
Thank you very much the truth of the matter is this is one of the most that one of the most phenomenal American
I've ever seen in the one we were waiting for Alex I thank you and I thank the audience
I backed the so-called alternative media which really became the mainstream media
Reality is Trump have been monitoring this mainstream media for a long time I knew it he knew it
Many of us had known that and Anna Paquin
For the next president
Basically ran with it and this is the true expression of the mineral majority
And the fact that we are so tired
The people who committed the crime at 9:11 that once Trump gets in my
Stationary
Many of them will be arrested
So what we have is him pitching this narrative to Alex
He was part of a group of Heroes
Who enlisted Trump to run as president is
The counter coup against Hillary Clinton of Court trying to pull off her own intro.
Narratives that Steve was promoting on Alex Jones Show in late 2015
Seeing as we've
Saw enter 2015 coverage
They're shockingly similar to the things
You know the idea of looking to arrest all these people after Trump gets in
Goodguys Heroes intelligence services that are working to install
I do not already become a okay
No
I'm not trying to say that Steve is cute
But I wouldn't be surprised to find out that the people who are running that scam
At least in part
Inspired by narrative
Persuade
To support Trump
With all against so many little elements
Are very similar
Maybe that's something for another episode of didn't want to get into it
That would be something we should leave to the guys over at qanon anonymous
My favorite ever convince
Salix
And that is the idea that Steve does psyops
But he isn't doing them against
Be good and Noble people who listen
We had
A lot of folks here because of the position
You should trust me
I don't
But look at what he's told us over the years
George W Bush's involved in 911 in Uno
Advising them to run Jeb Bush
Just set Jeb Bush up so they can
Please clap
And he's not doing it to this broadcast
B+
Patriotic
Level
But
What he's saying is true and has been listened to
Tennis broadcast is a format for that to happen
That's very sad
Yeah that's not good
It's always real sad
I'm so looking over the period of time that we have various stretches
Is the time it's hard not to get the impression that a lot of
Gotten
And that have gotten them in the most trouble
Trace back to school
Steve earliest appearances on Alex's show claiming the 9/11 was a false flag
Create the legitimate
Analysis content it wouldn't have been there without a purported expert Insider back
I can come up
Without being on the Vanguard of the 9/11 conspiracy movement
Never been in the position to
Become what he later became
At least some of that credit for elevating Alex above the level of
Just another weirdo yelling about s***
Was getting Steve pieczenik
To say on-air that 9/11 was fake
In 2000
That is a massively important
Piece of Alex's
Projector
Unfortunately
Their relationship soured in 2017
Ultimately breaching its breaking point on October 5th
Want to call her ask Alex his thoughts about the Las Vegas shooting
Didn't happen
They well
I mean according to Steve Burton
Caller and here is Desert
Response
Call Brenda Georgia
And talk to Paul
Thanks for calling around here worldwide
I just want to bring up a point
That came on yesterday on
David Knight show inside this whole thing didn't happen
Are you aware of that
Yeah I think it's Preposterous I watch the wrong foot
It was almost like a distant formation campaign is he still working for the CIA I mean this whole thing
Deep state
Do to provoke a response
Middle America
Turn on Schaefer said
Just like Colonel shavers
The target is the motive and the top psychiatrist everybody else of course
So Alex
Steven 27
Emptiness is working for the CIA
And he promised me
Turns out
Turtles of ambiguity
Videos of Sandy Hook actually happened
Alex wants to believe that Bernie was a biopic
Against Hillary
Because that seems fun
Auntie wants to believe that it's good guy Patriots pies
Install Trump as president
Las Vegas
That's just
Too much
Alex is already starting at that point to get blowback about his Sandy Hook coverage
And if you said that this shooting didn't happen
He had every reason to know that he was
Tacitly telling his audience that a number of people were crisis
That Route 91 Harvest Festival
Count of over 20,000
On the day of the shooting
That's a ridiculous amount of people
Encourage your audience
Potentially harass
Plus there's a high likelihood that there were multiple Alex Jones listeners at that Country Music Festival
So Alex would want to alienate them
Some sort of
I don't know what you even call it but like you would be disrespecting
Brick turning
Yeah yeah yeah
I don't know removing the whip
To put it in Breck
But
And so Alex would probably running a Alex and his audience
Of course that raises the question of what else was Steve manipulating Alex about
It would be terribly naive to imagine
Steve was straight-up with Alex about everything
Extended 2017 just decided start
Oculist
That's the worst example is a little bit above
He's more of a special attraction
She's just big
It is not good guy bad guy
Gigantic
Brick wall
Look at all the available information
We're going to discuss
If you're looking for definite answers
I don't know too many of those
Steve is way too complicated guy with way too long of a trail for me to ever pretend that I can
Definitively tell you what he's up to or why he does what he does
I can't help you
It's confusing
I don't know what he
You know it the thing about his
Argument for why
Somehow it is
It's literally the only
Impossible arguments that could
See the most Plaza
Well
Trump's crazy he wants the biggest and bag biggest of everything
So if he was going to orchestrate
Well it's a big is a piece of relatable like psychology of what we know of his narcissism
But it relies on
Just the weakest Foundation
Because
He's trying to get you to buy into the narcissism angle and then
Not not realize it what else you're
Buying with it
All I can do
Through what's known about
And see if it matches the character that we've come to know
The wacky
Frankie Gaston Alex's Joe doesn't like Batman
So
Let's jump in Jordan
That was my
Introduction
December 7th 1943
The second anniversary of the bombing of Pearl Harbor
I'm not sure
Hayward Baker
Sure I guess everything is f****** face
Gone
He was born in Havana Cuba
The Jewish Refugee parents who'd left their homes and you're up as World War
Kick him out
Right
Grants for some years then made the other way to New York City when he was 8 years old
According to his bio Steve went to Cornell and received his bachelor's
Degree in pre-med in Psychology in 19
Before
Then proceeded to get his medical degree at Cornell as well
You went on to do his residency at Harvard Medical School and simultaneously pursued a PhD in international relations
At MIT
Okay
This timeline as always
Confused me a little
If you assumed
He finished his undergrad work in 19
Tell me a sumption would be that he
Probably complete his MD at Cornell probably in nineteen
Generally just four years of med school
General you need at least
To complete
3 years of
Before you're eligible for a medical life
But that's at the low end of
The Spectrum
So the earliest possible time I could see him finishing up his Harvard rotation nineteen
That seems almost impossible though considering
Be at MIT
Don't be almost
Human workload
No
Possible
Pretty high standard
All the laws
IMDb
PHD programs
Can take between
28 years.
Complete couldn't be with Steve
International psych Warfare program
R160 to me as kind of
Fishy
Is it Steve entered the state department in 1974
And it seems unlikely that he would have been able to complete all of that coursework and residency in the time
For that
It's not impossible but if you did pull that off
He's basically super
When you add the Steve
Also claims to reach the rank of 06 in military become almost
Possible to imagine
Like generally takes twenty years of endless
Meant to reach the rank of OC
They're definitely variables that can make me
Things go quicker or slower but from everything I've read 20
Seems like a pretty average tenure of someone when they reached
A track
Listed on his 18th birthday
You have to redo that rank
Quicker than average
In order to reach that rank
MD and PhD from multiple University
Speed record
Is either
A liar
The most
Brilliant
Like I have to keep stressing
I'm not
13 years
All the information that's available about this stuff comes directly from
No idea how much of it
Believe
If any of it could be substantiated I will gladly tip my hat to hizon
Impressive early career but for now I view it with a healthy level of Sceptre
Battlefield promotion
What do you mean
He was in action
I don't think you can get all the way up there.
There is a
Consideration to of like if you're a doctor
And you join apparently you can skip a rancor to help
Steve
Describes his earlier years
Tala
And this part of his
Career when he made his first appearance on Alex's
To show it to thousand
Quote I was a very young 06
I then went on to my training and Psychiatry at the same time at Harvard
At the same time I got my PhD from MIT
International relations
That makes things a little more
Because Steve is clearly saying that you reach 06 at the age of 32
PHD programs
Got his undergrad work and MD Cornell out-of-the-way
Beginning the second part of his doctoral track
Unfortunately
That means that he would have to be at the state department while he's a resident at Harvard and studying at MIT
Because he would have been 32 in 1974
The savior he supposed to have joined up with the state
Alright
Just
Absolutely
He was just a consultant
Secretariat
Department
Completed his residency and got a PhD
If you believe his version of the story based on the age
He clearly is saying
What's up
Automatically start of hire at
The state
Then deputy
Consultant
Yeah I don't know I don't know
Consideration
Nearly even on my radar
I'm tired but
I stress
This is all part
Certainly
But if I find hard to believe
Something feels off
I'd be happy to Steve would be willing to produce his Collegiate transcripts and service record
For having probably one of the most impressive Scholastic and Military careers
Absolute
I would imagine I achieve these things
I would f****** publish all of my s***
Yeah I would I be like oh yeah oh yeah
Here's a terramite degrees here's all the
The classes absolutely
Would be a relative
Lifetime
It's not just the fact that he hasn't published his transcript
Means that they are not real they know like that that would be kind of faulty of me to accuse
Psychologically
I would do that
What's a good student
If you read any bio
What are the things that you notice is that they're all pretty much
Pretty much the same lines they all copy and paste
A lot of the stuff that you find biking is Wikipedia page
Taken directly from his bio
Which he has on his website
Which I don't recommend people go to cuz
If you Google it
It gives you a warning this site might be hacked of course of course of course
Do all of this without going to his website
Dennis Martin
But you'll find if you look at all this bios
He has been credited with devising
Successful negotiating strategies and tactics
Used in several high-profile hop
Situation
Including the night
TWA flight 355 hostage situation
And the 19
77 kidnapping
The stone of sniper
So these are
He created subtract
Right
Gotcha now he was only a consultant at the state department before 1976
Situation
So I guess in that time to years
Divisive
Yeah no that one's that one
Has anybody written
Well actually obviously
Nobody is written
The biography of
Not that I am aware of no
Murphy you would just be reading
Get to me
Questioning everything yeah
This might be as close as we're going to get to a biography
Lying about the the
He's credited with device
If that gets in his bio
And that's taken directly from an article in the LA Times
Written by Robert
Heat off
Top doesn't say who credited
Did Steve as creating these things
And if you read the article Stevens the only source cited and the only person quoted about any
This seems important
Because the articles about Steve's involvement in the dissociation
Free kidnap Italian Prime Minister Aldo Moro
And I know in that article he is not being entirely honest
What about the situation
That he was involved it
I'll get you later
But it's the only source in that article
To some extent
Makes me question if
That's where all the things
Site his bio are site that
Jailhouse Inn
You're getting paid a lot of money to save
This guy didn't murder
I don't know
Self-aggrandizing
I look at it more is the same way that Alex pays people to write articles that have been report
Reporter is clearly talking to
Steve
Steve tells him things in this article in the LA times and then Steve uses blurbs from it for his bio
It's nothing that I say
Roberts wrote articles by Steve
That are the primary source
Purses for almost every element of Steve
Eve's Bayou
There are other elements but they also come from other articles that
Yeah
It's a good thing
Robert
Too obvious is completely unrelated a year prior to him writing these two articles
Steve pieczenik Robert top was the Moscow bureau chief
For the LA Times
And he was detained by the KGB on suspicion of being a spy
Completely unrelated
If I wanted to make a conspiracy out of this
Seems like literally everything every part of
Steve's life
Is somewhat
Like there's
Some elements of life
F*** is actually going on
I don't know as much as it is like
Maybe pretend like intentionally
Cloudy
Restart to look at the specific
That are mentioned as the ones that relied on Steve strategy
Hey consider them from a hostage negotiation
Standpoint
First there's a case of the hijacking of TWA flight 355 back on September 10th 1970
The plane taking off at LaGuardia side passengers claimed to have a bomb hijack this
The bomb was fake and hijacking was mostly in extreme by Croatian Rebel
Receipt
Engine for their cause of gaining independence from Yugoslavia
That was also
Sponsored by Coca-Cola
So that was a big
Big promotional thing
They had no bomb and this wasn't a normal terrorists hijacking
A man who was on the plane related experience to the Atlantic
Quotes
We are going to pass out papers for you to read
Read them please
You should not worry
We have no intention of killing anybody
All we want is for our declaration to be published in the American News
Papers
We're not asked
A difficult thing
We want the world to recognize the Injustice is against our people
The people of Croatia
After that he said the mood became almost social on the plane
Even with the hijack
He describes it as friendly
At a certain point a passenger's engaged with one of the hijackers in a conversation
And argues with him about their political beliefs
Which is crazy
Fun
It's insane that is a picture that's painted by this guy in the Atlantic
That's crazy terrifying but at the same time all so surreal.
You know the first-person account of people there
Feels
Like friendly ish
Why is it
Pretty much convinced you probably going to die
Whiplash
We say we're hijacking this playing and then giving you homework
You be like Jesus
Love you frustrating
You know you're up there
Terrifying
At one of the stops the hijackers decided to let 30 people
They're 25 children and elderly and infirm people that they released and then they asked the rest of
The people if any of them thought they should be allowed to leave
Because of an illness
Or another problem
They let one woman go because she was on her way to get married
Many passengers began to identify with the hijackers which many people have pointed out as a
The classic case of Stockholm Syndrome
Named after Stockholm Europe
It is a discussion of other hostage situation
Steve has said a good policy is quote no Ransom note
Confessions no negotiation
Which is exactly the opposite of what resolved
The TWA
Situation
Everyone after they got exactly what they wanted
Namely people publishing their political message
The strategy employed
Beliefs nor does it match the techniques used in situations he's been directly involved in
And yet every single bio credits his Innovations
For resolving this
I'm getting never specify what Innovations they mean
Confined very curious
Giveaway
There's stuff in the pay
That was a pretty bro
It does seem so far that the strategies we talked about 4
Hostage
Have not been very
You know I'm saying not really
If you can call that is
I don't know Universal strategy
That's a good
He decided to
Situation
It's a good open
Bargaining
You show strength
Apps
Say that a good strategy
It's your willingness to negotiate because that buys you time
And that offers the possibility that the people who
Just might screw up
Escalade
Would you consider the second
Steve's methods are said to a result
That's the December 1977 kidnapping of achileas
Cipriano
The son of the president
Cypress
The kidnappers demanded the release of 25 prisoners
They didn't go they wanted they were going to send the president to Sun
Ultimately negotiation
A prisoner
Like 225 a task for
But them go Shooters did make concession
The kidnappers were allowed safe passage out of the country
In exchange for a Killian
These are situations are completely different approaches were taken too hot
Did you negotiate
And neither of the match with the way that
Operate
Based on its
Senses we definitely know about that he was directly involved in
It's it isn't like
Like hostages were never taken before 1974 when Steve supposedly after the department
He's credited with
Designing the methods used to resolve
Actually result
Pretty standard
That long predates
8 Steves involvement is at
His employment
I don't know what it is
Without anybody ever given more
I don't know what they're talkin about
Seemed to make sense
Just from
Perspective
Okay
New Theory
Steve pieczenik
Is d.b. Cooper
Any got hired by the state department
In a cat
You can kind of scenario like the only way to catch
He's with the hijack
You know I'm saying
I like that and then you can make up.
Hijacking one though
You just got up for it
Instances of real-life
But I can confirm
Steve was definitely at least somewhat involved
Great
No you're thinking you're looking up that means I know that most of them people.
I don't know that
Isn't a great strategy
Playing
Hijacking
Concocted
Leave a real bomb in New York
Stop.
At least one person
T.i. Steve also is
Been involved in
Disco people
One of these situations was the March 9th
77 Hosta
Situation in Washington
A group of hanafi Muslims
A radical group
It's splintered away from the Nation of Islam
Took over three buildings in
The b'nai b'rith center the Islamic Center of Washington in
The leader of the group come on Scala
Made a number of Demands
Four of his children have been murdered in 19/7
33 and he was demanding that the men who who are incarcerated for that crime
As well as the murderer of Malcolm X
Text be handed over to them so they can
I could deal with that
Guys
I don't know if you want to be living out some
Deadwood s*** right there like where the Bob bring out the
Converter
No.
However some of the other demands were met
41 Carlos wanted
Stemming from his disruption of the trial of
The Killers he wanted hand it over
Further he want it
You want
Okay sure you get it further he wanted the upcoming premiere of the film Muhammad messenger of God cancer
Snctm
Sacrilegious
Write any one of the new Star Wars movie
In Jeffrey David Simon
The book the terrorist America's experience of terrorism
The Avengers discuss
And according to his quotes
The incident was finally resolved with the assistance
Three Muslim diplomat
The ambassadors of Pakistan or Ron and
Who met with Carlos
And other hanafi leaders
For more than 3 hours
From the Koran
Appealing to their conscious
Wow
Fat
As
0 Seafood
Well apparently told Alex about the incident and it's 2002
Entirely
You could get that impression
I'm not entirely sure
I'ma go like Alex
Fair
He describes his involvement
2002 debut
Appearance
Infowars
Rebuilding your held hostage by fundamentalist group called the hanafi Muslims
Any New Year's being manipulated
The FBI called me in and use I use the Quran to Take Over Control
And eventually he couldn't help but follow the orders that we gave him
And he eventually release
The hostages
It was because
Steve use the Quran
Obviously
Magic
Thread
Wrote their names
To a pillow on
Absolute
This seems like a slightly different
Different version
The stories
The account
But I can find elsewhere
Does diplomat
Cereal
Appeal to their content
Because I can't escape the
The fact that I'm March 13th 19
77 article
In the Eugene Register-Guard does seem to confirm that
Was involved in a response
You would quote
And quote working side-by-side with police
Chief Maurice
Cullinane
At the same time Jeffrey David Simon
Book doesn't mention
But it does say quote
Also joining the negotiations
Were Us attorney for the District of Columbia oral silbert and Deputy attorney-general designee Peter Flaherty
The book even quotes police chief Maurice cullinane
And there's no mention
He mentions the head of the FBI and attorney-general being
Command Post
But everything we can learn about Steve's involvement comes from his own mouth
Either through his telling of the story or quotes he's provided to newspaper
I don't
But if you got
Deputies attorney attorney
Deputy Attorney General
Deputies
I'm not sure where the plan goes
And
SPI
And then you've got all these other guys
Even if
He's
Medical doctor or International
He's still not top build
It has fever running the show and he was the one using the Quran to Rihanna
Sincerely
I'm not entirely sure I don't
Discount take away from
Like he was there and involved
Buy it
I don't know I think it might be
Specifically told all of these
Don't snitch
I don't know
What it looks like to me is
Hap's
Exaggerate
Of his involved
It feels like a
High likelihood
Resign from the state
Department on November 7th
19 seven
Because he was upset with the handling of the Iranian hostage
I'm out of here
He wasn't happy that he
He wasn't called into resolve
The situation
Reporter Georgia Operation Center on my own after 72-hour
Does Huey have a guy who's revolutionize the entire world
Negotiation
Call Dan whenever there's a big crisis
Unfolding
Who's considered a genius and high-pressure situations
And no one calls him what it the big game is starting here with this a roni and Hast
Did situation
That just doesn't
Track
If the people in the state department knew that they had the king of Hostage negotiators at their disposal
There's literally no reason they wouldn't use
What a potential
Closest hostel
Situation breaks out
I'm guessing Alex might want to write this off as the state department
Secretly not wanting to cry
Has to be diffuse
So they keep Steve away
From it knowing that you
Beauty easily be able to set things
Straight
Amor real world explanation baby that they did
And that maybe that has something to do
With his most recent at that point
High-profile job
One of the few things we absolutely know Steve was involved
And that is the Boch negotiations
To free the kidnapped Italian Prime Minister
Aldo Moro
This is one of the document
Two pieces of Steve history
Ray's okay
It's legitimately
Jim sain
I can't wait
A 19-7
Compromise
Where are they
Where they would share governmental power
They were going to call
The Three-Fifths Compromise cuz it makes
Santana
Situation but then they heard about ours and they were like
It was revolutionary stuff like it was
One of the first times that communist
Parties
Involved
The government
Coincidentally
The day Morrow was kidnapped
He was on his way to Parlin
Historic first voting
Christian democrats
And the Communist Party
The kidnapping severely hurt the communist
And put this attempt operation
Completely honest
Morrow has been kidnapped by terrorists on March 6th
1970s
He was ultimately held for 55 days during which time the red brigades gave him a criminal trial
Found guilty
Because on May 9th
His body was found in the
A car
And everybody who is that
That I can fly in
Specifically points out
That the car that you was found in was
Equidistant from the Communist Party
Christian Democrat headquarters
I bet you see that written all over the place
I don't know if it
It's true but
I don't know
Every single
Report
For three weeks during this.
D-Patrick was secretly working
And meeting with the Italian authorities
Intelligence
Helping craft a strategy to negotiate the release of Aldo Moro
What if we said no
However in April
Steve left Italy and gave up
Haven't decided that Morrow was the victim of a set-up
If there wasn't anything and anyone in the government that he could really even truck
Quote given the deployment of paramilitary forces
Cuz I found it increasingly difficult to believe that they could not find
That they had no clues
Fallout
I realize that the whole situation
Was compromised
What I suspected that was why I left early was that they didn't really care to pull Morrow out alive
This is one version of the story that he's told
He's just a good guy trying to get the job done but everyone else
They were a bunch
That's not
Does he still work at the state department
There's no indication that I have that
I just think
Baby things
Didn't go as well
Yeah
Story about his involvement in the morrow Affair has changed a bit over the
In 2008 a documentary was released
Called the last days of Aldo Moro
In the film Steve admits that the decision was made to let Morrow die
And it made in the kidnappers
The killing him was the only solution available
The decision was made in the 4th week of the kidnap
Boro's letters
Became more desperate
He was about to reveal States
Hey
That's that's allowed to write letters back
Government
And what have you
And they were getting the tone.
So so
And this is not backed up
Correct
Maldives
Steve saying that the Italian government was literally like
Let's let him die
You looking at me with
Very pregnant eyes
Well many people don't believe
Which I think is a pretty healthy
In 2014 the international business times reported the prosecutors in Rome said there's a Siri there's serious evidence
Adjusting Steve pieczenik
A former state department international crisis manager
Participated in the murder that shocked
Considering he more or less admitted as much on tapes
6 years prior I don't think that's
2 shocking over-report
Both Steve and Italian interior Minister Francesca
Costa Rica
Have admitted that they released
Allstate
Attributed to the kidnap
Known as Communication number 7
Which Morrow was dead
Though he was still alive
In captivity
Steve admitted that they did this to Gabe's
The public reaction to news of morose
As well as to send a message
Switch to the red brigades care whether I lived or died
Up
No you can't do that
So he
Literally just
It sent this message
Of just like we are going to be out in front of the story
We're saying he's dead so you have the option
Killing him making him
The f******
Jesus those are your options
And Steve
This was Steve
Hey well we don't know if it's
Steve
Relishing
As a good idea
So so this is this was not known
Article comes from
Involves the Aldo Moro kidnapping it's not public
Different version of the events
What happened
So
So other people are like
International business times
Later later this information came out and both of them have admitted that they
Communication
Richard part of trying to manipulate the
Which probably led them to not believe that
They had
A bargaining chip
Speaking about the red brigades trap
We're the only thing they could do eventually was kill Aldo Moro
Steve little
Haha
Steve literally says this through a psychological operation
Asiop
Steve goal was not to free Aldo Moro
Is Goldust
Power structure
He worked to get Morrow killed
Premium wouldn't be advantageous
Morose letters indicated a feeling of being betrayed by his associates
And they worried that if you made it out alive he would use their inaction to
To save
Simultaneously
They couldn't take the risk
Of the red brigades not killing Morrow
Because if they kept him alive long enough
Well
His animosity toward the people who are not rescuing them could grow to the point where he might leak in
Information of the red Brigade
Hurt them politically
Wait because you get like this
Stockholm Syndrome
Okay
We're the Bad
Seletsky
I don't know I don't know I don't know how to describe it but I don't know if that's far off
In order to
Status quo
To paraphrase
Aldo Moro head
In that documentary the last days of Aldo Moro the filmmakers talk to a couple of former members of the red
Brigade
Here's an excerpt of that documentary where they discuss the interrogations of Morrow which is a twerp
Presents for
The first voice you hear is a woman named Adriana Ferran
And the second is a guy named Murray
Active members
Of the red Brigade
Still
And meanwhile held any style in the vmsr Cheney
The hostages interrogated Everyday by the red Brigade kidnap
Convinced that the country is politically and economically enslaved
The attempt to make him confess to Lynx exist between Italian state
American National company
The comrades who interrogated moral
We're expecting him to confirm what they had imagined about the Italian today
Existed and imperialist Multinational state
Behind
How you check daily quests
Indecent
Tomorrow talk to that reality is much more complex
How to easy to decipher
Multiple meno
Vichy France
They were being cute
Companion Care
They said the motor was deliberately not answering your questions
Trying to waste your time
Trying to gain some time
Moreta.
Our leader mobile.
Couldn't get more 02 giveaway
They have tomorrow
According to him
Models answers were partly true
But only partially
The reality was much more complex
But for a brigade members incomprehensible
Reality is much more simple
There were causes
Send a text
Complexity the complex
Overlapping
The contradictions
We couldn't understand all that
Jordan 8
After a few days the interrogation stopped
For himself
You didn't seek to convince.
Because he understood
Did we want to kill him
He knew that his negotiating partner was now the state
And no longer the red Brigade
So
Who do these red Brigade peoples.
Militant anti-government Rebels who believe in a one world government who refuse to accept
I don't know cuz it sounds like a guy with your podcast about
Yeah I was
I was just hearing that.
Just make it like it's not
That's the way of it
Do not try and
Unexplained
Situation
2 people who are alive
How is everything we want
Do not tell us the truth
Yeah
Confirm confirm for us all of our paranoid fantasies by the world
That are based on oversimplifications in black and white
It's not like that you got under
XYZ
Call God
Petersburg times from April 21st 1978
Situation worked out well I can't borrow myself because the government didn't have to resort to extreme actions
Which is a thought would threaten
The credibility and viability of
Of course like I said
In 1978 when he
He's talking to this newspaper
He was pretending
He and Christina had sent out fake
Communication numbers
Man that's f***** up supposed to happen in real life like that's a Bourne Identity
Movie plot right
Stupid
From a larger Force
Perspective
Valdemoro probably wasn't
If you're a hostage negotiator
And you're dealing your Sentinel by the state department at Jimmy Carter's behalf
To go and try and resolve
Situation where a head of state of an Allied country has been kidnapped by rebels
Yeah you don't necessarily want to come out of that with a dead prime minister in the trunk of a car
It's not a great thing
So my feeling on it
It is possible
The Deep
Punted on this
Just screwed up
Yeah and then
Wasn't involved in the Iranian hostage crisis
Because
He had just been coming off this terrible
Minister got assassinated
Jimmy Carter is like hey
Let's go save
It let's send some people to help save the prime minister
At Super chaneques like
Okay I'm going to go
No no you don't understand
We want to go save his life
Vaginas
Really loudly right now did I say that
Steve has a lot of quotes also from his past about like being a rogue and stuff like that until like
Did
I got a f****** crazy idea here at me of this work
What what is but he's like a punk
Hostage
What are cool and underground than negotiating
The opposite of what you're supposed
Talking about his life
What if we asked you to kill him
Yeah
The other big piece of Steve's resume
That's always comes up
Is the Camp David Accords
He is always cited as being
Involved in the Camp David Accords
Which took place in September 1970
Jimmy Carter brought Israeli Prime Minister Menachem bagin and Egypt
President Anwar Sadat
Card card
What if we
Without exception is repeated quote instrumental
And that's interesting
It seems entirely likely that
It was there at the time
It's in between the moro Affair and his resignation in 90
279 as a state department
The problem comes in when you try to Define what the word
Instrumental
Because no Source I can find that doesn't traced directly back to
Credited with being instrumental in the Accords
The door behind him when he
Left the room in the doors are locked from the
The outside able to leave without.
Like a lot of the sources on the Camp David Accords
Primary goal is not letting him leave without you
Instrumental
I'm not saying you wasn't there
I'm perfectly willing
To believe that he was
But I don't know if I trust his depiction of
Every other source I can find
Things to put far more
Sessanta big new brzezinski's involve
He's a major player in negotiation
Even down to that famous picture of him playing chess
Against Menachem bagin
Yeah one of one of those people is historical
Figure
The other one
Is the big new Brazil
Who even knows who that f****** guy is
Sure
Yeah man
Cbp's in there right it seems strange
Did Steve did all this stuff
When
Everybody else agrees that it
I don't know though it could be a grand conspiracy to Moline Steve can make sure that he is
His brand of roguish
Hostage negotiation never takes over I don't know
Only thing that I could say is that
Obviously the guy at that you know if you're in a
Chris Arreola
Something along those
Sure
Generally
Speaking
And the the face gets all the
Usually those guys are not listening to
Steve pieczenik
Deputy assistant
Through the secretary
Under the various
Assistant secretaries of State there a lot of those
And so like yeah it's either cool position to be in and I've never knock somebody for reaching that level of a
Achievement but it's also easy to
Say that you're doing a lot more than you are
Incredibly difficult
Definitely wasn't a position
From night
1874 when he was a consultant
The 1976
When he became a deputy assist
Secretary of State
Do 1979 when he quit over there on up
I know that to be true
From
Contemporary report
Definitive things you can trace down he was in that role
According to Steve when he's on Alex's show
According to his bio
He took a little time off
And then returned and served under Reagan and
Bush Senior
Gotcha
Is bio
Orchestrated 9/11
Resume
His bio consistently says that
You worked under four or five Administration
If they don't really get the story straight
No
Okay that's an issue
There's an inconsistency of whether it's four or five Administration
Maybe they're just not taking into account Ford
I have no idea what
The situation is but there's a lack of
Clarity there
We will get into the early 80s
After the Iranian hostage crisis
And Steve's resignation
Department
CBS and ABC talking to a number of newspapers also
He's offering his expert opinion on how things are going with us
In all instances he's credited as a psychiatrist Hellboy
In all of these appearances all of these times he's in the newspapers
He's credited as a psychiatrist
And former member of the
Then
On February 17th
Steve formally accuses the state department
The attack
Vic killed US ambassador to Afghanistan
Adolph dubs
Kidnapped by militants
And as The Story Goes
The US
Patience and negotiation
Whereas the Afghanistan government took a more rash Prout
And attacks the militant
Would you like to the ambassadors
There was tremendous Fallout 4
Incident
As the US began to
Drastically
Got back for it
Steve claims he was in the room when permission was given for the Afghan forces
Has to attack
But no evidence has ever been produced
Tobacco claim
He said he knows the name of the official gave permission
Official
Because he doesn't want the case to become an indictment of just one person but the focus the attention on the US anti-terrorist
This is shockingly similar to what he told Alex Jones about 911
Thing he knows the names of generals who were involved in the false flag but wouldn't reveal them
Seems like a pattern yeah I would also Point YouTube
Supervisor
A mighty but unfortunately
According to the United press
An article
Spokesman William dice
Said officials involved
Officials involved in the dubs kidnapping head
Consulted and Communications logs
Review
And then he said the allegations by pechenik
All concerned stress
The need for restraint
As well as
It strains credulity for me to imagine that
Steve pieczenik could be involved in the bungled morrow negotiate
Quit over not being involved in the Iranian hostage
Crisis
Then take to the media to accuse the state
Being complicit in the murder of an ambassador
Then get his job back at
That feels
It feels like this kind of attack
Making public accusations like this
Will probably disqualify someone from getting a sensitive job back
State Department jobs
I think you'll be even more disqualify
How to run disinformation campaign
On your own
I guess that would be
That'll be an interesting
Freelance resume act like
Do people play video games
Last Starfighter
His way to the secret
I don't know about that
I mean I don't know about that
In articles in the New York Times from 1980 to 1985
Has consistently credited
As a former member of
The state department
Under Reagan and Bush Senior
There's no indication from contemporary sources
Betty ever worked in the government in official capacity passed his resignation in 90
And that wouldn't
Make total sense based on his behavior in his action
Who is involved in wedding
Department stuff
And I don't give a good goddamn
How good Steve is at his job and publicly in newspapers and media accuses us of
What can I give a murder of an ambassador
That he's not getting credentials again
Yeah
Yeah cuz he would have mean
Was still in the
Maybe
To your insulation of information
If you shown himself willing so yeah like if this is true this is disqualifying
But I'm sure that in real life
The state
Mandela effect
Define resources on whether or not he was a joke
Fights
It's weird quick question
Why are so many people
Quoting him
Articles
I think so
Seems to have a tendency
Need to have someone who's this go to purse
Right right right
Talk for a minute there's a couple articles
Nike printed about Steve
And then that Georgiana
Gayer
She seems to be someone who Steve went to over and over and over
She's like wrote stuff about how he's a brilliant mind
I don't know if there's anything suspicious
Just about anybody
People likes
Steve like to have a reliable
Place where they can
Can funnel
And get positive number these stories are written
Every reason
To go to a cop
Like in the late 70s
There's every reason
To treat him like somebody who
Like he's a rising star it Department
He's involved
Electric standoff
You could paint that is like a Big Sur
So I see the process being like
Obviously
But as time goes on
I think there's much less
Useful idiot
In a certain until Alex comes along
Idiot
Useful of all seem to fit the pattern that he has of a couple of these journalists
Goes back to the well with
Ulta
That helps
Realities of him
Trying to go back to
To the state department
Or whatever I have no idea
And honestly it would be impossible for me to ever really get to
These are secretive and clandestine Waters after all
So how would it be there but everything I could bring to the table by saying like
Steve is working for the government
Address anything like that existence of space
But I can't tell you for all the sources that are available from the late 70s to early 90s bread
Until 1979
Accredited In Articles as a current deputy
Secretary of
And after
Easy privately
Psychiatrist
Who used to work in Fab
Until I see some proof to the contrary there's no reason for me to believe he was ever in the game past 19-7
Everything else could easily
Just be
Him doing his own thing
To go from
Negotiating
The murder of a
To your own
Private
Psychiatric
Would that be so weird to
Difference in
In status
Stature
Do you still like
That really really big
Pretty well respected in our culture well-respected most of them
I've never killed a prime
It's true it's true
Clear
Kill the Prime Minister kill
Percent not handled in a way that was appropriate
We get the 2,000
Two and Steve pieczenik makes his first appearance
On the Alex Jones Show
On April 24th
Audio of that first interview
At the fantastic
Fascinating.
From the very beginning
Steve with playing to Alex's narcy
Listen to this
Exchange
His credentials
Alex
We're talking
Dr. Steve pieczenik
And he's worked at the highest levels of psychological operations
44 Administration
You're talking about controlling Paradigm paradigm
Well
I've never used that word Paradigm but you clearly you must be a professor Alex
Is that
Rice
That's flattery
It's a lie
In a March 12th 1977 article in the Saint Petersburg Times
Discussing the b'nai b'rith
Standoff
This was a paradigm of unusual
Stop it
That is petty
We already saw that he was lying as f****** teeth off I mean
That is but maybe it's instinct
Or maybe Steve did his homework
Exactly how to ingratiate himself
Alex brings up the Council of foreign relations
And it really
Skeptical way
And Steve reassures him that the CFR is basically a rotary club
And he's also a member of the NRA so what do you think about that I'm a member of that
Minutes into the interview Alex's saying s*** like
Doctors info Warriors and for administration
Classic much of the policy the last 20 years
And I'm so honored to have you on the show tonight
So much
Everything I know about Alex
Harley against the policy
He's received the previous 20 to 30 years
And yet he is
.
Praising The Man He's
He's credited with crashing those policies
That makes no sense
Hearing about the
Previous journalist
Writing
Looking to see
For blurbs
Makes way more sense
You would be as
Is Polished in good
Like he's already
He's already home. His bulge
For almost 20 years
Get out like he's been gone to a lie at higher level
Absolutely
Working out at open mics
He's been working out at those guys one-nighters
Comes along he's at the height of his
Easy rum
Especially for someone who has
Like the appearance of the
Super elevator
Comedy on State
Hey
Appearances on Alex's show particularly 2011 2012 time
Time frame
He took particular that President Obama
He called him a sociopath
Unfit to be in office
I didn't fairness to Steve he'd also said some pretty horrible things about George h.w. Bush while Bush was still in office
Clinically depressed
And obviously in the midst of a serious identity
Eddievr even further fairness
He complained to the LA Times about how people were lazy
And psychoanalyzing President Carter
I personally feel it's unethical to write psychohistory about a president while he's still in office
These studies adequately into a
What's the president wears
I guess he changed his mind.
The time that I imagine that
Hwn Obama neither
We're very open
His resume
I found some interesting
Think things and that is
Respectable
Let's say
International Affair context intelligence
Okay
V-eats published two articles are very short
In the American intelligence
What is called is called Putin KGB forever
Which is really funny because
Pretty profound in 2016
But he wrote another article in volume 22 of the American intelligence
Fitzgerald's
It's called Amanda
In which he argues that the national security info
Structure in America
By gathering human
Intelligence
He describes a bit of the complaints that he has like
Unfortunately effective integration of Civilian military intelligence
Counterintelligence of psyops
Absent
From the government for well over a decade
This is like to a serious inability to predict human behavior and prevent evolve
Crisis
Crises
This is a strange position for Steve to have
When compared to
The position
Who takes on Alex
The show
In one of his appearances on the show
Steve literally tells Alex quote
It has to do with the famous technique in Warfare that we call the stand-down false-flag deception in denial
It was done during Pearl Harbor
Alex
Explain it to you yesterday was done by Hitler
It was done by LBJ during the war in Vietnam where we had the Gulf of Tonkin and he claimed we had a false flag operation we had to shoot the
Vietnamese cuz they shot it off
That was wrong
Many men died for the
Very against false flag
Deception psyops counterintelligence
When he's talking to Allie
One of these writing in the American intelligence Journal
He seems to be
Throw those things
And save the people
Gone for a well over a decade
In the United States
He sounds
Like a light
Contradict
He doesn't sound like
He's being honest with
I don't know f******
Suggestions for how to resolve the problem
Limited use of humor
Is the co-op open source
Predictive intelligence
Which is to say that he was interested in taking already public information
And using it for intelligence
Gallery
What is the culture of intelligence
Community where 90% of what's required for operations already exists an open-source event
Is newspapers magazines
TV radio and most importantly the internet
As usual American entrepreneurs have anticipated this
Is intelligence Kanojo accordingly have developed
Extremely capable software for catalog
Behavior
Greater cooperation
In between the business community and the intelligence Community is imperative
Decreed f****** Cambridge analytica what the f*** is wrong with this guy
Finishing the quote
Kudos to the CIA and defense
Department for having already created joint ventures with
Information Technology start
God dammit
That's amazing
Wow
That's
Very much against what Alex believes kudos
Angling for a Mastiff
Surveillance state
Utilizing already public information to control and manipulate the population
By the way Alex I'm against the globalist
Did you say well
Kudos to everybody else
And this wasn't a stray idea 2004
In 2001 he was the CEO of a consulting firm called strategic intelligence
And in his capacity as profiled in November 32001 Post in the National Defense magazine
Arguing that the intelligence-gathering
Should be outsourced
To the private sector
It's very strange for me than all the times I've heard Stephen Alex's show
Confirm those advocating for the creation of private spy business
And advocating for spying cooperation between the government and Tech startups
It really seems like that's something Alex would be massively against
Going back eight poll box advocating for
In his
If I were
I suppose
Looking at it from his
In that kind of
Field
That would be something that
That you say to a higher up
B y World maybe like
Genius
So that's a good idea
From his
His world
Perspective on it
Praise for that
As a position
Certain circles
Alex
This big point where I don't know what the fuc
He's going on about it would be
Irresponsible and Adeline
Of course I can't tell you why what you saying in this
The journal
Doesn't seem to match at all
With what Alex believes or what
What's to believe
Because he was like
Oh oh so I run a intelligence
Consulting business is to create a private spy company
Like I don't imagine Alex going along with 1,000
No don't
Part of his Consulting
Creating private spy age
Agencies I'm going on your show Alex it ordered
F*** it
This dude
Consulting business
This was
It was much more than just
I don't
Have any reason to believe that it was a massive Outlet
Or any
Is attack
So one of the other
Huge beasts
Association
Course it is Vios.
His writing career is generally encapsulated
Ghost wrote books
It interview with Alex Jones
The story has gone so far as to be that's
Himself
Is the inspiration for Jack Ryan
Which
What
Steve
What is marketing
No
ZabaSearch
So he told Alex or Alex multiple times
Steve never corrected him
He's both Sean Connery
Did I get one wrong there
I don't know movie
Sean Connery
My bad
The great Russian accent
Radius in a very long time I don't care about them at all and I just
Types of
Amazon Prime
Attempt at a fake version of
Isabel Amazon Prime
Washington Post in 1995
I don't know if he's a model for Jack Ryan but we're Buddies
It's that simple
Contradict
The inspiration
Right
Probably leave one
One to assume that
Orbit of
Insinuated himself into
Circle
Cooking interest
But if you were hanging out with him he would tell amazing
Story of reality
Slightly more real than
Regalo Burleson
It's literally impossible
Coy about
It's literally impossible for Jack Ryan
Eva
Steve's own words
In 1995 Stephen Clancy co-produced
TV miniseries
Let's start the great Harry Hamlin and Wilford Brimley
Oedipus peace about it in the Washington Post
Steve explains how he met
Tom Clancy
He recalled a book fair
Happened by nav
22 Prescott
Quote book with a submarine on the cover and Page through it
Based on his experience as a negotiator pieczenik thought the author display great Insight on the Soviet
And the submarine stuff was fantastic
He pointed out the book
The book was The Hunt for Red October
Steve had no idea who Tom Clancy was
Clancy had already created Jack Ryan published
Probably the most
Defining book about it
One of the most popular
The books that Steve was involved in with Tom Clancy where the books in the
Center and net force
Sure
1995 and net force in 1990
Where is the character Jack Ryan October
Annabelle the focus of six books by the time either of these spin-off series
Creative partners
These two men
Stevens Hardware the creators of the series but they didn't write any of the books in the op-center or no
Net force
Frozen wrote most of the Ops
Center books
Steve Perry
Not the guy from Journey
Wrote the net force one
They called the books
Tom Clancy's op Center
Tom Clancy's net force
Don't those people would just assume that Matt Clancy had written them
As opposed to just signifying say exist in what I'm going to call the extended
Clancy verse
What is books
I'm not sure I tried
Millions of dollars
Spin-off series paperback
He's got to get something at an airport
Unfortunately Jordan all good things have to come to an end
And the same is true for Steven Tom friendship and their business partner
In 1999 Tom Clancy got a divorce
And in the 2005 settlement his ex-wife got control over Jack Ryan limited partner
The Entity
Use the published books written by other people
Jack Ryan limited partnership was in a joint venture with S&R literary incorporate
And that's beyond feisty
With Clancy's ex-wife taking
In control of Jack Ryan
He was now in business with
Tom's ex-wife
Or
Steve without event
Right
In January 2004, declared his decision that he no longer
Beyond these books
But he didn't write
His ex-wife thought this was a breach of his fight dude
Fiduciary
Severely impact the value of this
Right of course
As did the Appeals
He couldn't take his name off these books
Nightmare
Copyright violation
His own songs
Whatever it was it's like
In good faith
You made it totally fine for someone else to write books
With your name on them now
Also in the divorce it came out that the reason for the separation was that Wanda discovered the Clancy had cheated on her with a woman
Nickname
Classic Steve pieczenik insert into
Very strange.
You divorced him when she found out that his friend
I was not
You know what everybody got to go back
Offensive story behind that I've just knocking I don't want to do it
These books
Are Jack Ryan Limited
Steve sided with the King
And testified against
Clancy
Alleging that his motivation to take his name off the books was to hurt King Financial
From everything I can tell there's no reason to give
Steve any elevated status
With Tom Clancy
Or anything like that he's not.
Forgot
I'm pretty sure Steve spawn some great Yarns
Do you know anything about the op-center or net force books
One of them
Maybe
Where in the middle is place we got to get stuff done
Net force is about
Illegal Fisheries
Really
I do like it I know the names of like for Tom Clancy books and
Things to do with Steve at all none of the books that you know
Have anything to do with
Isaac
An international Spy book
About fishery violation
But it might interest you to know that
Career as well
In 1989 came out with blood
Maximum vigilance was published in 1990
Text Pacifica
In 1995
These books as quote
Bad
And caught having no literary value
But these are just the reviews of random people online so maybe they're very Brookside
Now something I find interesting is how closely some of these books
To match up with Alex Jones
Some of them have been inspired to believe
Based on Steve
Princeton's blood he is about an evil cabal
Conspiracy to create a mutated by even more transmittable
Scary
Virus
Controlled-release
Palisades do psychiatry
Nefariously
Pax Pacifica involves
Conspiracies and power struggles in China that Ripple over it to the United States
All these vaguely intersect with major Alec
Narrative
Set Steve's 1992 book maximum vigilance
Is perhaps the best
Example of his literature having
Strange parallels
But the things that
He's pulled out
The central conflict in that book is about how is fictional eyes version of President Bush was crazy and needed to be removed from office
It's using the 25th Amendment
Interesting Lee
Around the time of the book's release
Went around
Accusing George h.w. Bush
Being crazy
50.
You would have used it as a platform
I want to spread the bushes crazy
For sure
These comments got him into
Some trouble and he was reprimanded by the American Medical Association which ultimately led to him
Leaving the American Medical Association
He said the Bush was clinically depressed
And obviously in the midst of a serious
No one else was putting forth these sorts of accusations are gossip
And it's super relevant to point out that there was a little boy
Similarity between the book he was selling at the time
And the portrait of reality he was president
Unsurprisingly the heroes maximum vigilant
Does quotes
Clark
I want to spell a name for you
DDS
Vix
Easyacc
Probably an anagram for something
This guy is a crisis manager
P6 who works his way through layers of Deceit betrayal torture and assassination
Multiple
Conspiracies a foot
Don't know why anyone
With that
Has no literary
Steve Howey
Self into his work
He's a patriot
Good for him
In the book Clark
Clearly fictionalized version
Discovers that the president who's clearly a stand-in for President Bush
Has Marfan
That's the condition
Dzx Clark need to get him out of office
That book came out 1990
When Steve started coming on Alex Jones Show
What do wavy compressed Alex
Was arguing that Osama Bin Laden had died back
Aaliyah died of Marfan
Marfan syndrome is something that would have been almost
The death sentence
In the. Of time that
Steve was coming up in the world
In the fifties and sixties the prognosis for someone with Marfan would not be good
Death from cardiovascular complications often would happen by the time
The patient was in
However modern medical science is
Big breakthrough
For the most part it's a relatively manageable
We predicted lifespan for people with Marfan syndrome general population
So I don't message
Sara Lee
With the thing that I think is that Steve knows of this thing
The most people don't know anything about
And it's a great thing
Throw in as a creative device
Especially
Book maximum as a plot device
And now he's
Clearly repurposed it as a plot device
To help convince Alex
B 911 right
And that's exactly what you would want
To tell Alec
Some disease
That
Has never heard of
It's so rare
Nobody listen cuz I was going to follow up on
And Alex is going to pretend like he already knew all
I'm an expert
Supercalifragilistic
70s
It seems interesting
To meet at this fairly
Your condition
Is used as a plot device
In both his book and in telling Alex
Now there's a
I don't I don't
Pretend to me that it definitively means
It also seems like maybe a pack
I don't know
Yeah like who Rodger Stone blames why
When he needs to get out of
Time travel
The same guys over and over and over
Socratica
Still is a little bit of
Question
That I have after all of this after looking at all the available evidence of like
It doesn't look like Steve worked at the state department past 1979
Story based on
The information that you can find make
Total sense
But your track through the State Farm
He came in
He is sort of f***** up
He got mad that he wasn't involved in the Iranian hostage crisis
Be quiet and then creative self mythology around
Himself that some people in the media that really
Certainly helps his path go forward
Sandy Hooks up with Tom Clancy
After already
Shirt now.com
He starts writing
Thrillers
And they're not getting much tracks
He meets up with Tom Clancy starts working with him
And then that
Sort of falls apart
I don't I don't know what his f****** game is without
Like I don't know some people think that upon him
Yeah I'm infiltrating the Patriot community in order to bring them down or something like that and I
Argument
Completely uncredible
Before somebody dies
Sure okay
Show me any evidence is work there
Can talk
It's not upon me to do that
If there was any evidence
Then you would know that it wasn't
Happening
That's how you would know
Because there isn't evidence
Is why you know he is
Because if there was evidence
Keep going all right I really don't believe
I don't believe that he's just
Crazy
Don't get it
Honestly
REI
Swear to you this
This is the number one
This is the thing that I say
Most yeah
I think there's a chance
Easy Living
Kill the Prime Minister and then he had to go right back to just
Now he's
He's written all these books
Maybe he's is he still practice
Nothing or whatever but he doesn't have the
Livin On The Edge
I can't prove it obvious
Is it comes up to support the argument
But he is look
Is the fact that he knows a lot
About the intelligence
He knows a lot of names
She knows a lot of dates
He talks like an expert
I believe it's some of this could be explained
It was accidentally revealed in 2012
In 2012 Wikileaks released a ton of information
From the intelligence
It's Group Stratford
Included in that dump of
Was an email chain
Where's Steve
Sonic was complaining customer service
Quote
I bought several straps for book several weeks
Have not received
Could someone inform me as to what happen
We learned that Steve is a customers
Stratford who produces intelligence
Assessment
And we also alerts
Steve's phone number
And the fact that he uses an AOL email
Would you wouldn't think someone in his position would do particularly when emailing with an intelligent Contracting Company
This weird man this is a guy
You cannot turn his phone
Sbcglobal.net
All the book Steve ordered with the works of George freed
The founder of straps
It is exchange of customer service
Rapper has his Visa number on file
Might be a regular customer and consumer
Of their product
This impression is strength
Goodbye another email
From 2009
Where Steve is responding
To a book email
Subscribers and he's responding very sniffling
It appears from his response that and automate
Getting spam
Also he would like to know why there's another email
2007 include Steve on a list of
The Stratford
I has him listed as the holder of a life
Time membership
In 2004 the following email
Happy holidays
Continue the great job
Well
Expensive bloated government agency
I would venture to Guess that someone who reads
The premium Conte
Including the Daily Intelligencer
Produced by
And release by Stratford
Pretty regularly
Interact with them to wish them a happy holiday
I wish for the downfall of government agencies
Probably person who beat
Really well-versed
Geopolitics
Edit teligent stop the Waze
Steve.
But it was
Explain how Steve is able to sound like an expert in this field
When
Probably hasn't been involved in decades
He just reads
A lot of Stratford publication
Who put out
Intelligent
Assessment
Professional
That does explain how he sounds like he does
Did not realize
Yep
Just so you can
Just get intelligence
You just do
A guy
How do you say I want
Some intelligence
Why would you ever say
Thanks for 1 sec
Because they're produced by professionals
I don't think it's evaporates off them necessarily cuz I don't think
Get that
Pretty interesting
Like it it could go a long way as to
Explaining
Steve's ability to present himself the way he does
Any other way
It's not like the only documents they've ever released for the
They're quite a few documents
They released
Involve Steve
Mostly classified cables but state
He's mentioned at that
Who got killed
Everybody was
Now what's interact
Literally every single classified
That's been released
That mention Steve
Comes from the period of 1976 to 1979
There's nothing that's been released that would tend
Kate is
Continued involvement in government
Pasta point requip
Because the Iran hostage crisis
Every other piece of information that I can find that doesn't traced directly back to
So even though the WikiLeaks
Steve
Only exist
In the time frame you would expect
In emails he sent to Stratford as a paying customer of their materials
That's f****** interest
That's very
Terry
Is true but I would say
Telling
Perhaps
Insurmountable evidence it doesn't prove anything.
If are working
Is well based on all available information that doesn't Trace back to
Or an article in the paper receive is the primary source of
Information
He left the state department in 1979
Has not worked
Officially in the government
I keep
Finding things
Supreme
The fact that every
Newspaper article after 1979 refers to him as a former
State Department
The fact that these WikiLeaks
Consistently go straight through with
Tempe Metro to the state department
During that time
It's hard for me to over overcome that
Like I said
If there's proof
I'll change my to I can't
Another email in this transfer Wikileaks collection
Involve Steve
I don't understand what
No I don't know anyway it's a 2008 email from a guy named
Dr. John neustadt
Who is
It is email he mentions that his partner is Steve pieczenik
Depace over $700 a year for his Stratford
Dr. newstead
Steve's romantic partner
Already thanks
Supplement
Putting together called nutritional biochemistry Incorporated
It's definitely not as wacky an outfit as Alex's supplement line but their overlaps
There's iron supplement sleep aid stimulant free energy supplements and all the stuff you normally
He was definitely involved with this company and was Doctor new sets partner in it at the
Co-founded the business with him
You still involved or when that ended
Nutritional biochemistry Incorporated website
They're about page
Just curious
Either way
Probably nothing super nefarious
Just another adventure
What it is
It's just further confirmation that if you scratch the surface a little bit
You always find a pill business with these weirdos every single one of them has some sort of
Supplement business
Cooking somewhere easiest to get into
Get out of
And
Scam people on
Cuz you can make up whatever it is you want to say about it
Your confirmation
Placebo effect
I give you justice
To get by on
There's no regulation of the market whatsoever
And your
Basically private labeling everybody else
So you
You get a thing and if you don't like it
You just close it all down and burn it up for insurance
It makes perfect
It works
Yeah
So I reached the end of
Where do things I've looked into
Now I intentionally didn't want to explore too much the idea that
Steve counter-coup narrative
And all that stuff is very similar to qanon
We already gone greatly in-depth podcast
In convincing Alex
To sport
It's like that would be rehashing too much territory
The image
Swept is like
We receive a pretty strong and
Navigation to Steve pieczenik
Is involved with Alex Jones
Around
Weird
I haven't seen
His involvement
In convincing Alex
To support Trump
These are two major decisions
But Alex made
Have negatively affected his
His career to a point that is almost
Unexpressed
Oh no they've destroyed
It's been done
Based on
Is it appears
The advice
And guidance
Of somebody who when I look at it all the chips are down I would never think of
Is a credible person to talk to
Even if I didn't know any of the stuff
That I've looked into for this
If you told me a psych Warfare guy wants to talk to me
I promised Warfare on me I would say I pass
No matter what information
You can give it to me in writing
I don't want to talk to me
I do not trust myself not to get completely
It's like I'm I'm one of those people who just
You know it doesn't happen so
Ono Ono
It turns out those were the words that wake me up
So I don't I don't know like I seen a lot of stuff in a red a bunch
Stuff for this
Look at a lot of indication
And to me it's
Like
Thursday
There's a clear picture of what's most likely
But the alternative is also possible just incredibly unlikely
And all the information that is
Definitive that I can
Confined
10th towards the likely explanation
The dick who record the podcast in his apartment
I am not involved in the halls of government
Or the high levels
Spy intelligence
Consulting business
I don't read Stratford
Stop
So I have no idea how any of this stuff works
Is it possible there's a world that is completely obscured and all kinds of secrecy is involved
Steve is actually actually was working with Reagan and Bush
I don't know possible
It's possible I can't tell you it's not
I think it is I think it's true
You haven't worked
So you can't
Hey you can't do Steve story
Steve's
Story
Through that lens
However
You are
As am I somebody who
Works from home
Every spend a lot of time
Writing
And staring at computer screens and a
And you get bored
You get bored
You & I we do this if we don't do this podcast
Cuz we're bored but this is an outlet
From losing our minds all too often
What do I do
To get out some of this stress
To get back
To my computer in
I'll go f*** with Alex with Alex for about an hour or so not a lot of work
I don't know
I'm bored
So after all this examination of reflection
For a bit and I really don't know what to make
I don't know how much of the story is true but I can definitely say it's not entirely
False
There's some truth
Just some of the things he's saying
Which is the best
Exactly
I come away from this with the sense that
Steve is first of all incredibly smart
And see if they have it
Singular talent for persuade
Seems to be able to
Convince people up there
Couldn't get his job back
He appears to have exactly the right amount of credentials
To be able to convince
People who are inclined to believe him
That he had been everywhere
And he has done everything
I look at all this available evidence about Steve pieczenik
What comes to mind is a line from his 19
T95 novel blood
Quote every life is exciting
Depending on how you
I think
Podcast
Incredible life for himself
It's very interesting
And he may have accidentally or intentionally or just
Capriciously torpedoed Alex Jones's life in the process
Almost
One of those like
Hitler did do something
Sing good in his life
He killed Hitler
His life he killed Alex
His career but also
For the rest of the world at least
At least we know
Well
So is this a
Play Reflections of Jordan a lot of information I don't know I don't know
I don't know what case I've proven I don't know
But what are your thoughts
I'm always amazed by those
Those guys
F*** around their way up
Do you know what I mean like
This is a guy who is
Not good at just about any
I don't know that's true
Maybe that's his only
Maybe he's really really bad at everything but
And he is
Skill into a
Weird and interesting in one
But
Wait on the single line you just read to me from his book
Fun tournament people online sent to aviary
He helps co-create without plan
He was his Mojo Harry Hamlin
You're not going to stick up for Brimley
She's fine he's got that natural money
Biggest thing
In his entire State Department
Career was
Of the death of a prime minister
Everybody agree
Really involved with
He quit because people didn't want him around most likely
Indication is that he is anything
He tries to do
Talked his way into buddy might be
Which is the correct we would have together
Talented
Might be very gifted and understanding how people's brains
Spending aren't involved
Situation
I don't know but like I said I want to be totally clear there is a
Ratably
Small possibility that a lot of his resume
Is true and the snow
The stuff he tells Alex is
Stillborn
That's one under
Even if his resume is totally true
There's no way to Las Vegas you didn't happen
So he's a f****** a
What a giant
F****** ass
Burn the world on fire
Burns the world
It's almost
He's annoyed he has to destroy the world
Consider like his arguments with Alex about manners or how he was mad when Alex was supporting
Neil Gorsuch
Spring on the Supreme Court
About to
Yeah it's it's fun when you cranky
It is
So I don't know your own conclusions about
This whole matter
I just thought it was important to as were in the 2013
Damn. Where Steve has appeared
I think it is
Essential for us to have a better understanding
Understanding of
When he comes on his like I'm a complete expert and all of these things
What is true about the
We couldn't do that within the span of an episode
Wasn't fully
No this is great I'm really glad to learn more about
Yeah
What his deal
What is your dream
Dzx Clark
Subway
That's right where you can find
Find us on Facebook and
If you would like to download
Go to I-10
Thought you could leave a review
School aisle
Target hit
Underneath
The small 3
Restart notebooks do you remember this
The small one
Like a little notebooks about
Which is why
If you open it up yet
Traded wanted I have wondering if you open it up to
Scribble a little demon star around there with the circle.
I won't but an episode of our podcast will emerge
Hand warmers
Words from the summoning
And it will give you a
The Barnacle restaurant
Flashlight
Computer
Emilio Emilio
I'm dzx Clark
Jesus Lizard
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color