I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
MoneyGram
College fight. Com
About Alex Jones
Jordan Jordan
What is the
You've ever waited
4A
Or a bar
Do you remember when we were in Austin and there's that barbecue place
You up for our way out everyday
It must be incredible
It must be incredible I would never wait for our
New York Subway call ahead for catering and then
Forgo the line
It's just a highly in demand barbecue place
I don't know I don't I can't think of anything
B released
Sticks out in my head because I don't go in for that at all.
Rather get something
Left good
Right I know that there have been times when I've waited before because I have
Play kiddo
Vague flashes of memories
Those disks
They give you that light up with Marissa
I can't I can't really think
Think of many incidents
This is right has any time that's like more than like
50-minute wait I have
No time for
So 15 minutes
Probably cuz if I want to I don't know
Some takeout place I hadn't called ahead if I just show up and
Disorder
Still might take 10 minutes
To make my food and give it
Not too bad the way
I would wait
An hour though that's
Half an hour get out of here
I think I've only ever weighed
The Pearl Restaurant
Like that's the longest I've ever
And that's because I wasn't
Control you know it was like a family gathering at once
3 people are like
I don't like food that much
A restaurant
Absolutely
Inline 4 movie
I was like
Can I just look at the people waiting.
Pittsburgh
Columbia Missouri when I was like right headlights with autonomy over decisions
I am like not a ton of bands come to
To Columbia so
Waiting for tickets ever that huge
Sing for me
City either
I bet it could have been if I had like more obscure
No I don't know I don't I don't
Not not too much
Rather get tag
I'll call you like a hundred percent
Character or the bond
That would be fantastic
Lutheranism Pakistan match by waiting in line
But I do know plenty about Alex Jones
The fun sort of present day
Episode to go over but
Before we get to that
Go to sign up
Restarting the show
I think that's a good idea so first
Annatha thank you so much
Rihanna
Taylor thank you so much you are now apology
Mister sir thank you so much
You are now policy walk
Mister sir thank you very much
Consider adding an
Sure absolutely that'll come in a little bit later
Well
I'm a policy wonk Annabelle
I'm finally
So-net
Thank you so much
Charles
And Francis Mary thank you so much
You're all that wonderful technocrat
Heroin
So good
Is freakishly large
Nick Charles
Francis Marie Mari
Thank you very much Nick Charles and Frances
Is Mary. Marino
Hey I like with these guys.
The sports show on the website
Horchow
We got a most
Present
Today
Situation going on
Because I was looking well you know what be great
Everyone seems to be interested in
They're coming out about Alex losing an appeal
Sandy Hook lawsuit
Seeing as we've
Come to the point in the 2013 investigation where it looks like things are going bad for Alex's coverage of Sandy Hook
You know we got a break in the case
In the present day
Probably wants to know what we think about that
Cuz response to breaking
And so I thought all right September 4th
So we're going over September 5th
Today although I lost my patience for this episode
And I think
You might be able to figure out why
Okay
Lost lawsuits and defensive
America and free
Free speech
Absolutely and we got a little bit of
Got plenty of bars
The show is so Barnes heavy present
How you can have a
Show that's entirely about your own legal trouble
In between in between calling for
Inviolate over
Overthrow
Just your own legal issues
Can you imagine if I can understand Cooper's all the sudden is just doing news about it so he's getting sued
Find a conceptual getting practice it's not a good show
The idea of it makes me laugh
Probably not going to work out
So talk about these legal developments
And they talked about there at the end of that clip
Vesuvius associated
And media organizations because
He believes that the Associated Press said that he wrote that book no one died at Sandy Hook
A lawsuit about that book
However as we discussed
In the past
This is
Different website
Can some content from an AP article article was not on that other website
Distributed
Thrown out of court like there's no way
But he's posturing in brain standing like next week we're going to file this week
Coercing a f****** ever
Few weeks Bhai
T's and dotting the I's
The yough
How to make it through the summer of Rage
I may have survived intact after it but there's a summer break
Yep
To talking about something by new product
But he's got
The other new products
At this product is it sounds crazy
Unveil a product that I believe
Because I'm a
Do this is product Clarity and focus through the roof
Lately
Is laser-focused on the issue season the weeds man has he want
Product
First advertisement for this specific product
IPad Focus relay back
Friendly non-combative
You worry about that
Where is
Alex is like mushrooms months away from
How close is he getting to like Soma
Does it cross over into like he's just doing
Really
Alright buddy I think you can't come by
Is wake up in the
Take some brain Forest
To get you through your morning
Then as you're coming down on that you takes
Until forced to go to bed at 9 evening
Knockout is for going to bed
Even more products in the life cycle of every moment of
Your day today
Did you think for Wars Health can heighten every experience
Is it at like trying to
The rising
CBD Market
But either way I just
Effective my outburst
Ridiculous
So Alex
Just Alex saying that he has
20 hour live a Day broadcast format
I cut that color cuz it just the same thing as the lawsuits are coming
She had over and over and over again
Liking you
Rowan a couple of new novel little pieces of bigotry here and there
Some weird defense
Open Trump.
And the rest of it is all just like it, don't worry about it down the road
We get to this point
Sentence of Alexei saying that like
He's indicating some
Desire is to get away from
But not
What it is
After the El Paso and Dayton shooting
Trump came out
Besides these red flag laws
Baby there's some
So you know his narrative on that way
That was the rope-a-dope globalist
The revealed themselves men
Give them nothing
And now it appears that that is not true
Actually be interested
And now these red flag type laws
And the Alex is saying that he will call for a
Chuck Liddell net worth
Because there's a bigger issue
Is that down with the 5th
In the first place
Course
Alright
You're never going to believe the truth
Okay
I made it depends on what you mean by Sandy Hook lost
Have you ever seen
You're wrong you haven't anything anything anything that's obviously true
You are an idiot for thinking
How do you know anything exists
Pictures of the most solipsistic lawyer that I can exist
Aperitif
It is a
Hazardous thing we are
Professionals and even then
It's dangerous to go
Commercial break
Gets into talking about the
Worcestershire about Sandy Hook
Disinformation
Is Illustrated
WyzAnt
York family destinations
Text
Pusha T
Alicia Howard
First things first Washington Post article that he's talking about is not buried
It's literally as easy to find as any other articles posted on their website
Just look for it
The media won't cover it
Washington Post article
Supreme Court that has nothing to do with Alex's Maine
In court case
Specifically about the sanctions he was hit with after he drunkenly put out a million-dollar bounty on the opposing counsel
After which he was found to have
Unknowingly sent that email containing oligo pornography is part of his discovery
From the article
Supreme Court agreed to hear it
Appeal of a lower Court's decision
Broadcaster Alex Jones
From later in the article
Last month a judge in Connecticut
She said his legal team failed to produce several documents
Despite repeated orders
And she decried what you described as a 20-minute deliberate tirade and harassment and
Intimidation
On Jones's broadcast
About about the lawsuit in one
Attorney
Alex's lawyer Zaid number of complaints about this
I was largely boil down to claim that our sanctions were a violation of Alex's free-speech right
This is all good and well but from everything is been publicly available it doesn't appear this Connecticut
Supreme Court appeal
Concluded yet
All the headlines
Better coming out
It certainly is no indication
Or bearing on the idea that the larger case
Has anything to do with
Or that he's being unfairly treated in that
Write this is
Narrowly about the sanction
That the
Anthony
The conversation is I understand it is about whether or not
Sanction Alex or something
Utah's out-of-court
With the question
Does his out-of-court behavior in as much as
Cuz he's threatening and trying to intimidate the opposing counsel right I rather
The court proceeding
I'm at 5 agree but I'm not a lawyer and I don't know
I don't know how it works with in a courtroom so I understand why someone would want to
Talk it out but this isn't the Wild West
Balloon he threatened to kill my lawyer
That's a completely different situation
The reason for this
Can I get Supreme Court
To hear it even if they didn't agree with Alakazam
It means nothing that they agreed to hear it other than like
That's kind of a novel question
What is Ruby arguments are
Is it to the Supreme Court
To deal with it Everett
Like the Connecticut Supreme Court step over here
Are there more like okay fine
The current headlines were seeing involved the defamation lawsuit he's faced
The Texas case was filed
The father of a six-year-old child who was killed at Sandy Hook
Advocates that got going outside to have the case dismissed
Twitch did not work
Even try to appeal the decision to not dismiss the case and the new stories popping up now we're all related to the Texas Court of a
Determining that the case be dismissed
And Alex has to pay all the legal fees
By the other side during the appeal
Fiesta produce all the internal documents and emails in that Discovery process
Which had been refusing
Provide
All in all what I see here is an intentional strategy being employed by Alex and his legal team of stalling inside tracking
He doesn't want to see the inside of courtroom actually having to be under oath and talking about this stuff
Cuz he knows he f***** up
Courts are really bad places work on man but the legal system is also place
Where other cons can be run
So instead of the actual case
Houston
You refused to hand over required Documents To The Judge
And before you know what you're fighting a large the unrelated battle over whether or not you should give the lawyers or email
Gone forever
You can run around pretending that the whole cases of champagne if you lose that little side
Alex dating this Texas case
You end up having a bunch of Articles written about how you lost this
And then you can
Get on your Shelby like the media signal off the case they're all f****** Liars
It's a win-win and prolonged
Reckoning when you're actually in court under up
And as far as the Costco like what is it
10 G
And for the cost of a
Plaintiffs lawyers on that
It slower
It's not Ritz kind of a negligible cost whenever you already have a large
He's going yeah how much is a
Bravado I don't know but I would assume that
If you're already in if you're in for a penny in for a pound
Analisa
If your main court case
Keeps going
Penalties
These are
Millions of dollars
Which
Very high
The very least possible
Or whatever to put day off
Another 6 months
To make sure that
Maybe that'll help
The blow would spend all of my money
Pushing the case back for the rest of my life rather than
Just losing
Still have to go
All the Paul bye-bye
Behavior is absolutely the behavior someone who really really doesn't want
Fixing to come out
Really I don't know what that thing is something about this case exposes
Something about the source of his money or some editorial decisions are made at info
Either these things
Pretty much
Incredibly Jermaine
Sandy Hook lawsuit
So I could obviously see Alex
My crazy to stop the discovery process
Anyway you can
It turns out that his only real strategy to kind of just
The pro temper tantrum
Blow up the process
Which can buy you a little time
6 months
In the case of this Texas
It's not going to work in the end
He's just delaying the inevitable and that inevitability is
Is that whatever he doesn't want people to know is going to
To come out
And how he's pretty regularly being forced to pay plaintiff's legal fees
Every reason to
Suspect that these cases proceed
You going to be bankrupt
If you thought the other half a chance to win on the merits you'd be doing all this weaselly ship to stall the case
You feel like it
Hail Mary attempt
To avoid looking easily be his
Conduit is not just from a public humiliation
Sandpoint at least
12 a possible
We going broke
I can't get away from
Not matching
Someone who wants
Like someone who wants to prove themselves innocent wouldn't play the
These sorts of games
These are the games that are played by people who need to not go to court
This is the corporate
Like this is like
Equifax
Accent s*** like that they will throw off any side the billion-dollar company
Is like Costas Costas what do everything we can and then
You always read the story
After 10 years of Appeals
Equifax finally agrees to
Everybody
Nothing we have going to have to do any
That's one of the downside says the fairness of the legal system are considered
So Alex that I don't
B
You know I'll tip my hat to him
Because he claimed
But he's not seeking money from the Sandy Hook parents
David lawsuit
Kind of contradicted
Hundred-thousand-dollar
And that's not true
Okay
Still the article is true
Okay so it's not true.
Okay
Alright
Okay whatever
When the article was written
Not Trail okay
That day after the articles
Totally
Sounds good
Hooray
So I just tried to deny
Escape the reality is
Situation
I'm not going to trial
Obviously
This is amazing
All of them
It's
It's so you know it's all just down to what you define like you're able to
Things like this
The declining of the appeal was based on a jurisdictional issue and they wasn't.
It's of the case or whatever
You can split hairs like that if you want to but
It's not if you look at the larger picture of the case as it
It's going this is not a posit
For Alex
One more loss
One more battle lost
In a long ongoing War
To appeal the non dismissal of the case
If the end result of that is
Know whatever the reason for the know is
It's still a no
You did not get the outcome you thought
So I look at that is
Comes on and they talk a whole lot of bulshit about
And Free Speech
Basquiat
If allowed to proceed
If it is even allowed to pursue
Yes
And
Not only that
That is also the goal of the people Sue
Zip some of the legal theories being pursued
Are permitted
Or allowed
Then press will no longer be free
So these cases will establish the true scope of the First Amendment
Fundamental
First Amendment cases in the country
To come
Block Rockin Beats
Mortgage
Geopolitical issues geopolitical issues with Robert f****** Barnes
This guy has some really good
I think he's
Great
Lovely nose the nitty-gritty details what's going on over there in Kashmir
Call up Barnes
And he'll tell you absolutely
It's take us out to break
Customer shal
That I thought was a
Thomas Jefferson's years ago
Close to ground close to reality
I think
I don't know that to be Thomas Jefferson quote I can't find it in anything I think he's reference suggest the
Charlton Heston
Speech that we talked about the recent episode
Is just go to jail
It's not good
Never seen anybody bungalow
Supposed
Comical
Tremendous
So they come back
And finish up Barnes
Most of it is just a flexion
You know after all that
Barnes
Gives a little bit of a plug
For something that I've been a little bit aware of for a bit now cuz of listen to these episodes
But it's becoming more public about
Deserves a little bit
It's lukewarm for Sono
If only
We Salute You
That you're amazing
Organization
It's free America Law Center ww.w
Free America lost center.com
Free America law center.com
$17 in 76
We are going to be supporting
That works
Exactly
Lawyers to bring great cases to equalize the equation
Because the left has been effectively monopolized
Interest law in this country
So do the left has taken over the ACLU entirely too
Organization
Weed
ACLU
Oh boy
So Jordan
Yeah
Robert Barnes dangerous part of his path as a scam artist
It's all good well to manipulate Alex and feast on his court Express
It's almost amusing to watch Howie's
Completely insinuated himself into the actual programming at Infowars Alex now refers to him as expert
Things like international relations
It's understandable to up on other scams
Flash react
Missionary Outlets like the Rubin report
And doing interviews with
Stefan molyneux
It is so predictable territory
Shein
However
Now he's in barking on a project
That no matter how it shakes out is a really bad song
Robert Barnes has launched
The free America Law Center which is uses the antidote
Liberal Stranglehold over the world of law
Splc in ACLU weirdest shields for the Democrat Party
So that the right-wing needs their own version of these organizations in order to
To even the playing
Yep got it would be
So much better
Free America internet
National RC
Something like that and just himself
I be great
So it is justifying the need for this organization has cases for liberals nowadays
Which is patently false
The ACLU was a non political entity that does so much goddamn work for people's rights it would take what's left of Barnes his breath away
The fair look
Here is some of the cases the ACLU was involved in right now
James Aaron McKinney was sentenced
The death for a murder but it is trial the judge didn't take
Consideration evidence related to his post-traumatic
Stress disorder
Which could have been seen as a mitigating circumstance
The terms of applying Capital punish
That case has nothing to do with liberals or conservatives
But the rights of a human being
Sounds like the left-wing, nonsense to me damn probably
Also they're defending
Based on the reasoning
Comes to life without parole as a juvenile
Does he deserve a Newsstand
Should be ruling be retroactive to minors were sentenced to life without parole prior to the Montgomery versus
Court decision
Make that an appropriate
This has nothing to do with Paula
The ACLU was on the front lines
The stuff like that
Compassion is left-wing
I guess for pulling off a f****** sniper attack
I still recognize that maybe his scent
I'm saying is invalid now because of
These are just a couple of cases they're currently involved in that
V possibly unpopular Santa
Defend individual rights
And they're plenty more examples
Of a political s*** in the work they do
They still use the American civil liberties
Here is the people like Alex and Barnes have a very specific definition of civil liberties
The ACLU believes the definition
Includes taking on cases where Refugee Rights are being trampled on where lgbtq
Thank you folks rights are being violated where women's rights are violated voting rights are being eroded
His ilk are actively interested in those rights being curtail
Organization
Pacifically exist
To defend those rights
Conservatives
Is there definition of conservatives is
Not into respecting the rights of non straight white male
Natural born citizen
Then I guess the ACLU is the enemy of
Conservative
Work outfits
This organization Works to counter the bad things I want to see
City in the world
Working everything they might do
It's almost reflexive
And that's not to say you doesn't deserve some criticism in some places it's not the valid
The type people like Barnes and
Is completely the wrong criticism invalid
It's always a a
I can't imagine
People
You can be mad
I've been mad at
ACLU
But generally speaking if you
The ACL is a bad organ
There's a lot of Green Valley criticisms you can make a lot of especially internal stuff
Now this earlier this year there's a
Real bad stuff came out of
Internal working condition
Allegation
I think it's very valid to
Be critical of Ozark
Relationship
Not in the blanket
They're run by liberals
To crush us White
That's the mentality
Yeah
2 organization
And I've always thought that
Are those crazy
Isn't that working
Conditions are
But the main goals
Of the ACLU
Splc
I have always been like
You remember all that stuff in the Constitution
We'd like to apply to every
The goal of Americas
Original goals are but just for like all p
And people
Berserk
Or out
So my big issue here is with Barnes playing to set up his own counter a course
Splc completely inaccurate portrayal of what either of those groups are or do
Proverbs Barn plan is the group's describing
Already
Throughout the ecou as an example there still so many non-political rights Focus
Advocacy groups in the United
Midstate Plumbing for fucksake in 1998 conservative started their own Americans
Union
Specifically as a response to the ACLU
This is old territory it's been done before and for these reasons you really have to ask yourself why is Barnes
Doing this
Already exist
Oh I know I know hold your hold your thoughts
One possibility
Maybe one of the more likely possibility is it
We've discussed many times that the trend of the right-wing in the scam Community is tended towards lost
Suit scam
As their ability to really make much Headway on social media spaces is diminished
And along with that their ability to pull off compelling
Improbable publicity stunts
It could make complete sense of the Barnes knows that the future of right-wing
Impotent threat
Text to file a lawsuit
We used to raise money for the person issuing
We saw Laura Loomer not too long ago
Like how long is he been saying is going to sue the Associated Press
Beginning this episode he's always just about to file this lawsuit
And until he does he has the ability to
Teases audio
You all hate the mainstream media and I'm just the guy to fight them for you to give me money I promise the lawsuit is coming any day now
Schroeder's lawsuit
If Barnes is smart that is freedom Law Center does American free America Law Center
I am setting up a corporate Entity 303
Incredible and then take a cut off
The top
Which I respect the hustle
As a 501
However Jordan
There's a possibility
Far boredness
I'd like to tell you a little story about a man named Kirk David lion
Whose footsteps Robert Barnes
Maybe
Following
Brooke Lyons grew up in text
And according to a bios
From Baylor University
From a young age Lions was confronted with the issue of racial equality
Which was realized the forced integration
Public Schools
If a write-up of your early years include
Beating black people in schools was difficult for Kirk as a child that story is not going to end well
Is it really
Very much
Sleep what they
Was actually
I think it's a diplomatic phrase
Absolutely
University of Houston that started practice
Nothing on his own
The former head of the clan and then head of the Aryan Nation
He was brought at Alliant by Mutual acquaintance
Zendaya
Anyone
Your Council
Why does mutual friend with the ground-floor they Louis beam
Legal team
I would imagine it's probably because Lions gave us that old Telltale cool with Nazis vibe
Azu preferred Alabama
Not all this is for Baylor ironically
Came from the Southern Poverty Law Center
Does white people like barns rectum
Yes so when being was arrested in 1987 left his
Gets to represent him
In the trial that's known as the Fort Smith
Sedition trial
In that trial 14
As leaders were tried on accusations plan to overthrow the government
Outside of a court of law that's a slam-dunk case
These dudes literally never stop talking about crushing occupied government
They are not very secretive
Hangouts
The courtroom
We are planning
Together
To overthrow the
Right now when they get inside of
The courtroom dad know it seems like
Free speech
Dial along with Richard smell of David Lane members of white supremacist groups
Murders
As well as the
The founder of Aryan Nation
Richard Butler
A white supremacist named Glenn Miller
Agreed to testify against the other man
Including making bombs
He served three years in prison thanks to his cooperation
In 2014 Glenn Miller carried out two shootings
The Jewish Community Center of Greater Kansas City and Village Shalom
The second of which is a retirement home
He killed three people
Ironically since his attack was clearly based on his aunt
Ism
None of the people he killed were Jewish
At the community center he killed a fourteen-year-old and his grandfather who were just there visiting
Heather retirement homie killed an occupational therapist
A Christian
Anyway that's the legacy of one of these guys now
Great good people
Prison
Three years but agreed to testify in the Fort Smith sedition trials we got a letter sent
Unfortunately his assistant
The case was pointless
All the defendants were acquitted due to lack of evidence which is exactly
It's insanely hard to prove it
Conspiracy particularly want to actually overthrow the government
When it's perfectly acceptable as a DE
To say that your constant screaming but other government has been taken over by malevolent demon
Is this criticism of the state
It's protected
So anyway all these dudes walked her clients became a big f****** deal in the world
Supremacy
He was the lawyer that saved all their leaders
From jail time
And is Lewis being put it quote Delta huge blow to the dog
Those f****** things where you're like
I get it and I know I shouldn't
But everybody knows that Colin Kaepernick
Should be in the f****** NFL and it's a goddamn conspiracy
How did the NFL but you go into courtroom and they're like well you can't prove that it's like that
That's the that's the difference between what you can
It's one thing for a lawyer to
To defend white supremacy
Justin Aziz
As we discussed
In court but it doesn't prove that
Just the fact that Lions decided to put his previous career on hold
To defeat at St Louis
Doesn't mean that he's a client's menorah.
Absolutely
And a Nazi does prove that.
Does help there is not a dearth of evidence
He marched with the Klan and Nazis in 1989 in Tennessee
He was a member of the National Alliance
What's a group run by William Luther pierce the author of The
The Turner Diaries
He was definitely definitely a member of these groups as proven by correspondence is written by Piers identifying
The lawyer within their ranks
Yeah
To give you some idea how deep in the mix Lions was
When you got married in 1990
The ceremony took place at the Aryan Nation
Compound
Wow his bride had two brothers
One was in prison
Because he was a member of the order and was involved with some of their murders member of the f****** order
Brother was
Right right
Richard Butler so he was he was marrying royalty
Richard Butler the founder of the Aryan Nation
Charges
The ceremony
Were they all wearing white
In 1988 Lions was invited to give a speech of Aryan Nations World Congress
Swear you discussed ideas about setting up a foundation where you could operate like the FPL
L
Leaders who he represented
People who he thought were just Patriots
Dissident
In quotes
District shape
Uniformity Patriots
Defense Foundation
In soliciting donations
Thanks for the PDF
William Luther Pierce told his followers in a newsletter quote
Houston member clients and attorney has organized the Patriots defense Foundation as a start towards a June for our
People what the Jews have done to RN
Before our enemies
That sure seems like a conspiracy to overthrow the government
I'm just
The PDF would change its name in 1991
Would henceforth be known as cause
Which stands for Canada Australia Us South Africa in Europe
Reflecting the areas in the world were white people were being attacked
Build themselves as quote America's only pro-white Law Firm
I put out ads and all the places you would have
Soldier of Fortune
Stormfront all the of the
Normal
Yeah we're not
Secondary Guitar Pro
From there I started recording all the right with monsters
He could take on his client
Holocaust deniers the middle of Alyssa guys who killed someone because they didn't like
Tempe of the Rocky Mountain Rendezvous the meeting held by Christian identity
Repeaters with brought together all the luminaries in the world of white bigot
He was there with Larry Pratt head of gun owners for America and early Alex Jones
Sponsor
Pratt ended up having to resign
For Pat Buchanan
Presidential campaign
Because it came out
But he was at that be
But the other reason he had to step down as it was revealed that gunownersofamerica
Had given cause
The other white supremacist organization
X 1000
The dollars
As the case was for everyone in the right-wing Patriot militia world the Oklahoma City bombing f***** everything
It came out that Kirk
Was Close Associates with Andre ostrosky
It actually introduced him
Two people are Elohim
City which looks really bad but rumors started flying around that strossmayer might have had something to do with the plant
And for the bombing
A lot of the militia Community thought that strossmayer was working for the government
So that Association
Was toxic there
Ironically it was the same white supremacist buddied up to who were now making
His life hell
As they were trying really hard to point fingers at anyone other than Timothy McVeigh
Now he's friends with that dude
Now he's on the man
Now the problem is that the same world also they saw strossmayer
A potentially a really dangerous
Streamers who played some undefined roll-o-matic terrorist
So his association with him
Fictive that World 2
Has fun with the overworked white supremacy world but it looks like it's good time was over
Not quite over
Really almost
Being involved with a
A group of
Socio
You just don't know when they're going to turn that sociopath
South Park
And you you know what I'm saying flycos
And you can't trust on their loyalty on account of them
Leaving interesting thought there
Kirk knew the block was too hot
So you decided to Rebrand
As Jennifer Lopez
No
He did so by founded
Southern legal rights
A directions
Lrc with specifically created
The defense Southern Heritage
Meeting Neil
Better
He preferred Alabama.
So he's defending Southern Heritage called quote and ethnic cleansing of Dixie
This was Proto demographic replaced
It was the early versions
He's consistently Advanced the theory that quote Confederate Southern Americans are a distinct race
And that's deserve it I deserve a distinction as a
Class under the Civil Rights
Whenever the spirit is been brought out in court
But it appears that did way better on this
Listening donation
From racists
It's a failing idiot
So here's the point
The right-wing particular tradition
Presenting their arguments
Duplicitous
I tempted to masquerade violent bigotry
Bigotry is a civil right
And plotting terrorist acts as against the government they feel is occupied
Free speech
This is a scam it's been done before
I mean it you do it maybe the Robert Barnes isn't trying
But I don't believe that
He's using very similar strategies to Kirk lion
He's using the same language about the splc only helping his enemies
And he's got his own forts
Sedition trial here in the form of Alex's
Sandy Hook
This looks like history repeating its
What are the main reasons I feel that way is because there's already
Plenty of groups that do it
Exactly
Exist
There's already the American
Civil rights
Which is very active and has filed
Defending Trump's Muslim ban
Supporting voter ID laws and trying to help with Republican
There's also the Southeastern Legal Foundation which just serves the purpose of the Legal Center for Cancer
Closet
If you want to go a little bit more libertarian with things to do with the Pacific Legal Foundation
Which has been operating since 90
Who's priorities literally
Wheatley overlap with what Alex
Pretends to care about
Private property free speech
Free association
Due process all that
If you want one that's religious in nature and pretty cool with you being anti-lgbtq you can mess around with the alliance defending freedom
Or if you want one that's super Christian and kind of unclear about whether that if they have a problem with you being anti-lgbt
You could consult these
American Center for Law and justice
There's already an organization called the American Freedom Law Center that is specifically about protecting
Judeo-christian heritage
There's so many of these f****** groups already
And many of them are very prominent
And they all address the exact issues that Robert Barnes is
Pretending no one addresses
Does his need for the America of the free America Law Center
His reason for starting the group is b*******
I have to
There are other reasons
It couldn't be a scam
You know what he's trying to fleece
Racist video
But my gut says
Is that you wouldn't take to
Take us all the way to be starting a foundation level
If that was your goal
Just pleasing peep
This feels ideological
When you look at Robert Barn
You see his past asked
Espace Client List
Particularly of light
And the way he carries
Nothing seems right
Conclude Charles Johnson
Holocaust denier who kicked off Twitter for quotes to listen
Support to take out DeRay McKesson
Who has you know is a civil rights leader
An activist
That case was thrown out of court but not before Barnes had the chance to
The frame the whole thing is
Censorship
Antisocial media and all that all those good narrative
Anti-everything
Threatens to kill a man in
Makes a detailed plan about it
You guys are all up in arms
Even though it got thrown out of court and people think
The joke
Penny represented Cassandra
A reporter at Fusion
For saying that her making the okay hamster
Signal along with Mike's
Picture taken at the White House
What's a white power sign
That case also got thrown out but not before Barnes had a chance
Is it critical First Amendment and anti-media narrative
With that
His latest hustle outside Alex is representing the Covington kids
By representing them I mean he's going around threatening to sue everyone in the media Place Elizabeth Warren and apparently a lot of
Because they smoke
White boys
Any particularly dramatic move back in January gave the people who spoke ill of the kids
48 hours
Mr. retractor slanderous words
Or face the wrath of his lawsuit
Steam to get thrown out of court a lot
After rebate is very serious and very real threat
He was the target of another very serious and totally real threat
When someone
Threat
To be clear I don't think that anyone should ever even jokingly threatened
Can someone see messages
S*** and probably should have some
Some consequences
But it's hilarious at Barnes
Decided to take
Seriously it takes
Proclaim his victimhood about that
He made a mistake by sending a screenshot of this email that he
2 media out
Oh nothing
Oh no
One is it Barnes uses Gmail
Which is weird
Form submission on his website
Barnes law
Which you runs through Squarespace
Which is a little sad for someone
Supposition
I use Squarespace for Fox Say
He's supposed to be a big-time high-end lawyer he's got a goddamn $20 a month website going the f*** out of here Barn
The reason I bring those two things up as it's Christmas is a huge comp
And this isn't the first time someone has realized
Pittsfield in
And send threatening things to people
That doesn't make them anonymous
In order to relay the message to Barnes
This email I got it incredibly unlikely that a footprint wouldn't
Be left behind
Person type
The address wasn't logged by the server that the message through
Guess what
It's coming from inside
No I don't think there's necessarily was I think this is just
Selective
Media manipulation
Epoch Times article says quote he's received thousands of messages that's picking up the case and I haven't been able to
Sister all of them
I find that weird because the subject line of that threat email is quote you're a racist piece of s***
I don't say anything
At all
But all threatened
Hey Joe it's just insulting
Free speech
Is Barnes my check
He received that message at 10:45 a.m. on January 23rd
An Epoch Times article was published on January
Fourth
I find it incredibly hard to believe that he has thousands of messages he can't get through all of them but somehow he saw this one created media blitz
I thought of it in under 24 hours
It's even harder to believe when you realize that
X was late to the game on this store
The Gateway pundit heading article up before 5 p.m. on the 23rd
She Howard
After he received this email
Breaking exclusive story for the Gateway pundit
Why it's Cassandra Fairbanks
In what is her legal publicity stunt
So weird
My God I hate
People so much suspicion
And now here with Alex he is
Barnes has the perfect opportunity to Parlay this case
Pretty much a limitless self-promotion
He's representing a guy with a media Empire that's not doing great financial
He needs a lawyer you need publicity
Perfect it works out
But publicity
Wasn't about his own
Or even getting his own show and usurping Alex's We've joked about
I suspected it was about this all along
And it looks like now the transition is beginning
Barnes is openly promoting the America free America loss center on Alex's
Tell his listeners to donate to this cause
I mean if you go to the Barnes as website Barnes law his Law Firm
In the cases
Section Alex isn't in there
You go to the free America Law Center cases
Alex is in the
He's moving this stuff over there
In order to build up a more robust
Sing it if you look at the history of a lot of these
These organization
The ones that do exist
Don't have scam history
Bright lights
Conservative or liberal Therrien
Public
Law organization
Don't have like
Ha
We're going to f****** just support these grifter assholes and their Felicity stunts and see what we can do
Start
Bye
Something like
The Patriots defense fund
Comes out of
Mentality
So I'm worried
I'm worried I'm not saying I need to be clear about that
I'm not saying that what Barnes is doing is it
Exactly the same
What Kirk Lions did
Inasmuch as like
You know Kirkland's was straight-up
Hanging out with
And defending
Real neo-nazis
Ed white supremacist
Call Alex
I don't II
There is an absolute on the radio
I think I think that you could
You could make an argument that some of the
The form and function of their
The rhetoric is maybe similar there's overlap
But in terms of what they're doing
You can't even
Come close to a
Once I started the Aryan Nation
One guy
Screams
Incredibly bigoted s*** on a radio show
But
He's finally some people into the Aryan Nation
So
I guess the other guy started
If you want to put it that way
A f****** nightmare book
Concerned
About this
Free America Law Center
Because I think that it could Bode
It could turn in
Into
A form
Where Barn
Is able
Go to
Revivalist
Cover
For a lot of these
Is that
Should had propaganda
Racial agitators
Anti-lgbt
Teq activist
Some of the more Fringe
Dangerous
People within
DirecTV
And so I wanted to get more into it but Alex hasn't talked about it all that much
Except for this plug really heard them bring it up all too much in his other appearances
Know that Barnes was starting
Started
I was like well alright
I got to go check out other things Barn
Princess.
And so I decided to listen
To his interview with Stefan molyneux you don't have any clue
Bangla Natok
Do you have a bunch
Heat have route sorry
Sorry
The rest of this episode we're going to be going over Robert Barnes
And appearing on Stefan molyneux
Because they talk a bit more about what Barnes wants to
To do
And I figure like okay if I have by theories and my ideas about what his motivations are
I need to hear them talk more about
And this is the Forum
He did have an hour to talk about
Here's my here's my
Free game
Free guy
Alright
When you file one of those bulshit lawsuit
Cassandra Fairbanks
You got to put up the money right up
And then you got to ask for donations
You got donation
Coming and going
You have a lot Center where they donate to
So you don't have to
Even put up any
Defiled
People are already donated
Then whenever you filed
You get to campaign for donation
You have just got to
Giant funnel of money off
For you without ever having to spend any of your own
It's going I don't believe that
Subscription
Are going to pay for like high-end lawsuit
Like I just don't think the subscriber base
Is generally what he's
Pretending it is
You would
Still need
High-end benefactors
That would be something that you would be able to mask
With one of these
You know non-for-profit
I have 501 c 3 Type organization
So
Gets into this interview and he starts
Describe
As Barnes
Plan
Clearly communicated prior to this
Explain what he's up to
Ivypool as well
Extraordinaire
Banana that I think it's helped with some of the challenges of
You know if you're not on the laptop if you criticize in the public eye for more than 8 to 12 minutes at a time
Then the tsunami of you like some help
Oh well I'm sure this can be easily corrected
Not good
Problems of having to prove actual malice and
So the reports in America
I think tipped a little bit more towards the First Amendment rather than
Reputational protection
I can take the approach that is very interesting.
So
Savant wait you know I'm
What's the first amendment when it comes to reputational protectant
That's tough to square with
That's bananas
Opening up
You know there is there is
Thematic similarity between
Yeah I mean
He's advocating for his Ludacris
Jenkins like your someone does lie about you you can still demand a retraction
There's no actual malice
Just like you can still do that only is about
And if you threw them you definitely should have to prove
There was
There there lie about you
So I don't worry
Approved
That's true too
Issue with a lot of those lawsuit
They're saying
Yeah later
Complaining about
Yo cuz of these these meet like these
All these big companies know good things about certain people out there
Like what
What if you're just messing with me.
Will ever be a value to the recipe
All I see is negative things tweeted at me
That's clearly because of tech center
As opposed to think bad things
Cuz there's no
Possible way
Is that everybody couldn't
Agree that I'm
I'm the greatest
I don't understand why.
Estimation the function of the narcissism
Something comes along with this world to like just no way I could be wrong is no way that anyone could just like
So you know
Is a problem because of
The need to protect my reputation
Shower something
Which
Seems silly
Gets into answering
So the goal was we needed a legal
The Southern poverty
Lawson
Southern Poverty Law
Sort of equivalent of the ACLU
For all people not to
That Just Cause 2
What's on porch
The ACLU has mostly done today
We needed something like that
People on the political right
Libertarian for Independence
People who aren't part of the
The cultural cachet
Already exist
How's it going over 100 times the framing of this presentation
Is alive
If you want to make the argument that like these things do exist
Then
You would be coming from a more honest perspective if you wanted to say
Alright I'm Robert Barnes I believe Indies libertarian
Conservatives ideas
Therefore I'm going to join up with this other existing
Public Law organization that already serves those enter
Work with like to make that better
So it can
BV
Like you're our existing framework
Better run by Lake
Very credible people
You know people who of high stature in in
In society
This reminds me so much of the
Muslim leaders to hardcore Muslim terrorist
We never hear from the leaders of Islam
Aesthetic
And then it's like
Cuz you didn't
Google it
4 / 2
You don't
Want to hear
You don't want to know that they're all ready to start exactly
Possible but I honestly
Think that it's more that what he wants
To do with differ
Yeah he doesn't really want to bring into the conversation that are real scene
And even slightly insane version of
Yeah he doesn't want to talk about that cuz he resent this is a new and novel idea
Idea that the left has been dominating and
The only people who are in that space
Public Law
Because if he doesn't what he's doing just seems like it
It's already exists
Right question why are you doing this
Because if you're trying to create an antidote on the right to the ACLU
And you're really going for it
You are going to wind up creating the ACLU
You know you're just going to do the same thing that they do
It's just because that's how that that's how that works there are some conservative-leaning
Publix
Civil rights
Liberty face
Organization
Fairly
Yeah because if you're caring about what
Absolutely actually have prints
Then
OSHA
I care more about
Doing things the right way or the legal way than I do about lying
It's very imaginable very conservative and a liberal could come together on the discussion about whether
Whether or not
The kid in the DC sniper case
Deserves a new trial based on agree or disagree
Proposition proposition
But there's no reason why a group
Interested individual right
No matter the political alignment
Integreon that
Absolutely
It's just
Shady s***
That's because
I would hazard
If you are going to ask
Billy give a s***
You going to litigate
And you want them to
If you want to go to trial
Then that means in order to win your case
You have to accept
Shared real
Both sides agree
On what the facts
And so then
You find out so much that ideology and all that
Doesn't apply
Actually not real
Grifter case
They're fundamentally imagine
Right there using public opinion
The court of public opinion versus the court of court
And that's all
Free America Law Center would be
Incredibly effective
In terms of
The the court of public opinion
It would be something that could be used as
Just
Media arm of these
I don't know I don't know what to called
Dabblers and extremism
Centers that do side with
You of course they're not going to
To draw in those
Same level of do
Because sometimes they do things that the propaganda says are wrong
Maybe they thought it would
Adventures would be more successful
Or not I think it was doomed
But it also scares me
Because I'm
It could be a very
Very day
Dangerous organization
Text Claire Barnes talks about how the left
You know
The Virtue signal
Sure we do
The second thing the left as well
It because virtue-signaling matter so much to
In ways
Generally conservative
Some value for what they give their money for
Difficult
Sprouts
We're the only value
Knowing the lawsuits going to move forward
The goal was to create a legal organization
And it serves the interest
Call people all across the
Political Spectrum
The fight the 3D
Deplatforming
Definition
Deep state
Democratize access
So we created three America
To look up find out more online about
America lost
And it's always too
Gryffindor
Distributor driven
But to make it membership
So to make it
Subscription gifts for people sign up for a month
Description at a very affordable accept
Set them up to recognize our Great American patriotic history
Organization
I feel like that price
Is virtue signaling
Absolutely
That price is not based on the free market
It certainly seems to be
Ali's left is a virtue signal with
Crowdfunding
I love
The inverted reality
People thinking
That's all the cousins
We donate to
Have no value
And yet they would donate to
F******
Because they want to get something for their money
Saying you'll see a little bit later the pitch
We're providing
Actual Direct
Driver gets
They also get weekly
Podcast
We're only members
Lawyer
Antidote into a podcast
Take it weekly book
Bill of Rights Oakley series
People that are suffocating
Yourself
You better protect their own rights
Defend their rights
Volume
The same time prank
Clyde the Mack
How f****** weird is at the idea that Barnes is like if you donate you can vote on what cases Altec
That doesn't seem like it's principles
That is absolutely ridiculous
That is
I don't have any books
That's at least like
That's something
I suppose
Pressured voice
Van Dyke
Enjoy that podcast
Is trouble
Oh no that's
I can't imagine gamify as the entire thing
Really doesn't seem like a good way to run a lot better
People learn the list
Voting
Boaty mcboatface whenever you are like
I'm going to open this up to the Internet
To make a good decision
Exactly
But you know you got to do something
The baby this is bad idea
Because there's a
Conspiracy going on
Robert Barnes is fighting against
And what's happening
A big media Ark
In ways to
Depresi sensor dissident voices
Using their Superior Lawson
Inner Superior legal
Talent on their side of the aisle be
Ceaseless
An endless retainer
This is exactly what Kirk lions
Told the Aryan Nations World Congress in 1988
They're against that guy they're against us
Dissident voices
The Patriot
It's exactly the same rhetoric
There's being used as a Justice
Application for started
Patriots defense
Similarly
What you have in the
You know Louis William Luther pierce his letter
Kirk Lyon
The weenie he's going to help us create something
To help us in the same way the Jews have done for our enemy
Sure you know the have that same thing
What's the last
Four people were against
Yeah I'm that
I get that he's not saying the same thing
But the structure is the same
The argument
And
A lot of the people that seem to be adjacent to the world's that Barnes is swimming in our f*****-up
Stefan molyneux
Can't take the context
Out of
I can't hear this without thinking
Of Kirkland
The parallels are too strong
Right
To get back to our earlier conversation though was dealing with the
Founder of the area
And Barnes is dealing with
Cassandra Fairbanks Denali
Alex Jones you know what
Absolutely more I think it might be a smarter things
To do
She gives you weigh less
But give it give it more time
And who knows what it could be
Barnes decries
The downfall of the last
Lesbian
I don't know Noble or heroic or something
Enda reputational attack
With the giant corporations intact with the giant corporations
In media against
The little guy
Capacity to push back against
Absolutely isolated
Destination
Platforming is also happy
And people with your sort of ice
Trying to enforce
Orthodoxy
Indus Elsa
The most effective
Until he can get people afraid of man if I say that I might get sued I might lose my job I might coming
Who was just ain't working as they at a gas station
And he got fired
Trump
Customer credit
Ha
I don't know who the person Barnes is because the current cases section in the free America Law Center web
Website doesn't include them
The only cases listed are the coven
Two kids of former FBI agent representing and Alex Jones
Like I said Alex
Is not listed on the current roster of cases on barnes's website
Think it means
But we'll see
I'm guessing
The barn is the guy who worked at a gas station in Naperville
Just outside of Chicago
Who was just fired
Supporting Trump
This guy was caught on video questioning the citizenship status of a cup
And then telling her that people needed
Go back to their country
He tells the woman quote you're in the wrong country and as she's leaving threatens her quote will come
Which is a real cool indication
Stormtrooper Force
Bissell course was on the Hills right after Trump's whole centre-backs thing
So I guess
Kind of argue that there's a showings
Support for Trump
Retelling that he
He's reframing that as
Expressing a pro Trump position the real incident is a blatantly racist
Inoffensive interaction that's beyond the pale regardless of a person the political beliefs
I've managed retail outlets
Gone
Even if it wasn't about race even if it wasn't about her citizenship status
You don't get into fights with customers pure and simple
If you're a clerk at a gas station
Because someone who worked at multiple gas stations in my life
You're insanely replaceable
And no business should feel any need to
Guy who likes to argue with customers on the payroll
I'm not sure if this is the case of Barnes is talking about but I would kind of bet that it is based on the details that he provides
A video of the exchange between the clerk and customer went around on sofa
Commedia three plays into that part of barnes's platform
This is not a case of someone who's fired for supporting
But that's how racism it being a shity employee are whitewashed
If this really is
The case of Barnes
Let's talk about it clearly shows what is intention
Strategy
These are you take people like this to do
Blatantly intimidating race
This thing
And then you reframe
Repackage it
Some sort of a violation of the offenders right
And by virtue that you hope to come up the process
Or intimidate people
Out of
You know dealing with the disorder outburst
Rational
Like
Vicky
The person has
To have no
That Barn
Exploiting them for
Like the person who got fired
From the gas station
Do you think so
I don't know I don't know how this work that how that works as Barnes goes to
To them
Convince
Them that they have a key
And that
If they stick with Barnes they're going to wind up with
Winning a lot of money
Wow that's a good point I have no idea but I wouldn't
Surprised
It didn't seem strange
Prefer Barnes to reach out to him but I wouldn't I wouldn't
I don't I don't know how any of this stuff works I don't know anybody's expectation
We create
You're really sweet
We try to work on creating an atmosphere
Where are bigotry
Is legally
Defensible
Defendable to the point where people will resist pushing back on it
Yeah they want to create a fear of stepping up
To entreating
Publicly abusive racist outbursts
Actually
Protected speech
Absolutely
So
I just don't understand how the guy at the ascend
Doesn't realize that
Exploiting him
Completely
Like he's going to go home at the end at the end of all of this
He's going to go home with nothing
And having a
He might have more than he would otherwise what the f***
See if we can make a couple bucks off the fair the gas station chain
Fair
Do you threaten them enough you have
Intimidating enough lawyer
You might be able to make a settlement out of it
Ivysaur
Gas station
I was pretty dumb
Customer
I don't know
Because of all the
Because of the nature of what this organization really is geared towards
Stephane knows that like this is good
This is some momentum
Well I obviously have somewhat of a personal motive in in supporting
Somebody ordered a trying to balance things like the splc which to me you know
Become a completely ideological
Battle Breakers
And me and
And other people who just
Make an argument
Any organization
Overtime
Collectivistic
Free market
Anti Freedom agenda
Having a counterweight to it
Think it's really important
Because
There are tons of counterweights already
If you think that they're not doing a good enough job
That's the conversation to have ever posted
Things don't exist
This
Is really an important distinction
To make
Because the way they framed
Is all like there is nothing
It's a wide-open Wilderness on the on the right side of public law
We need it because we
The Liberals have dominated
Their soup
Superior Locker
Did laissez-faire
Absolutely not
It's dishonest
Bremen
It means
But you're up to some
General
I've asked this question I don't know how
Does he actually believe his own bulshit
Because what he just said
With sewn on
Extensively
Just
Walmart
Everything
Except for his need for something like barnes's organization
Sentiment with gas
Well it's right
These people don't believe
So therefore it's a terrible organization taken over by globalist life dates then
Check collectivist agenda in far-left activist blah blah blah
FPL
You have like today watch out and like
They cover extremists on the right there are there one of the forces
Actually
Takes the time
And research is a lot of these people likes
Stefan molyneux don't get a pass from them
And declared himself
Like he is on the radar
It became a f****** weight National
The splc existed
Pasta
People who want
Prageru and me we're just having idea
F*** we just make argument
That's what I'm saying
So
But it's all the same
I just making arguments
It's the same
Similar to
This whole
Masquerading
What's really going on
Gas station person is just supporting Trump
It's a strategy that people like this
Right and it's essential to their ability to operate
Because Jose went around here like hey
I am going to
This guy who said a bunch of a customer
When he was working at a gas station and got fired because of it and I
Thrilled about minimum wage employees
Racist
That is the sort of thing that Society needs
No one giving money to that except for the really hardcore rapist
And that's not a big enough fool for you to run
A f****** Law Center with
Issue
You need to pretend that it's
The noble sensible Trump
Voter
Because that's a much
Larger audience
Dance from which to
Fish for donation
You masquerade thing
No one's going to be mad about Stephon just making argument
I hate him so much
You have to hide because you really do
Sincerely and honestly
Is a losing game
Which is why
Which is why they losing
Exactly
Positive
About Morris Dees
The
Founder
The Southern Poverty Law Center
Morris Dees in the time
The founder
Credit
He was originally started
Landmark
There was more money
If you suing the queen
It wasn't driven at an idiot
Anything else
What is that giving him credit for
I'll give him some credit it's still weird
Some credit goes to
Is it like
I don't understand what's being
Applauded because it could be that he was originally a client
Is that app I don't know
Is it that he's decided to start suing the clan is that what is a plot
Is it the fact that his decision
Baap Clan wasn't motivated
The clan just by a being
Financial consideration
None of the options seem good
All of them seem to be
Do you stocks
What is credit what really against the Klan uses following
Hey yeah basically what he
What he said
I think what he thought he was saying
Was that previously
He was
Non-ideological
Didn't pick
I guess
I don't know
That he was
He didn't pick
Where is Dee's is called the clan lawyer because in 1962 represented a klansman named Claude Henley
Who was on trial for attacking the Freedom Writers
He was 20
Pictures all the time and less than
For two years out of Law School
Any regrets taking that case
His subsequent legal history does
Sometime after the trial
As reflected by hit the cases that you took on
And the fact that he supported George Wallace his campaign
But by 1972 he was back in George McGovern
These objective antic Target for the right-wing because he's completely destroyed a lot of white supremacy
He's one large settlements
Against the white Aryan resistance
United klans of America and the Aryan Nation
People on the really f***** up parts of the right-wing do they can
Complain about him on the Merritt
Which is to say they can't just come out and say that they hate that he financially crippled white supremacist
This group's alternative Pro
You try to take his motive
You try to say you like
It's all an attempt
To attack without
Revealing why you're mad at him
What I think
Political work is very important
He was fired by the splc earlier this
Amedia suggested that it stems from it
Turtle harassed
Not complain
It certainly isn't from Barnes or Alex Randy's right-wing truth-tellers
It's from the f****** New York Times
The Bastion of liberal media the world
A world where the splc runs the show
Thick extensively covered the firing and all the employee
Complaints
Is the same his civil rights work is invalid
Claptrap
Don't b******* like
There are complaints about voice
Obvious plc
But the complaints that I hear out of
People is never that
Right
But at the same time they can
Talk about the legitimate
Cuz out of one side table
Look at how bad this guy is in the other side of them out there like
Employers should be able to do whatever they want that is a functional problem
Their other position
So it doesn't explicit Barnes
I think
Really sucks
90% of the people they list on their so-called hate water
Why not
They're awesome
Mainstream
Seattle
So I think the Barnes might have said be quiet
He claims that 1% of the people listed on the splc hate watch
Often within the political mainstream on the political right
Here are some of the most
Recent headlines
Saint hate watch
There's an article about the power struggle that's going on in the leadership of the anti-government militia
There's an article about women running for congress is really into calling groups
Muslim Sharia
There's a couple articles about Matthew cougarboard
Department officials active member of white nationalist group
There's an article about how many of the accelerationist elements
Sydney white supremacist community
We're responding to the El Paso shooting by emphasizing the need
To kill important people
Instead of random Folks at Walmart
There's an article about how a member of an Arkansas white nationalist group was arrested
For beating up a gay man because he
He was gay also had previous hate crime
Conviction to the Past
Legitimate
If you look at these articles and you think that's basically mainstream right-wing dissident voices
Your identifying the same problem I am
You don't think it's a problem
That's not good organization
Then you only brought up
You exam
See 90% of them are all of those
Groups are like
Americans for having a good time at places
Letter there in the political Maine
Stream right
Out of the country
Buddy there in the political
I guess Barnes could actually maybe be talkin about there
Extremist files
That section of the
Catchy name.
People remember
People listed in the extremophiles are really bad
Yeah
We could go through that list one by one and discuss how a lot of these people are either literal murders
Who killed people for white supremacy
Cicadas
Button to do is
I'd like to ask
Barnes think
Exactly are these 90% of people who are in the political mainstream on the right
That's the sort of thing that's really fun to say
Who plays really well with the right-wing persecution complex
But he's tacitly saying the mainstream of the right-wing has been overtaken by right white supremacist
In fashion
After Poland
Become a white nationalist
Really the word
Bubbled to the surface
It's probably a better way of foot
What was always there is
Just now allowed
I don't know I don't know if I wholly agree with you on that
That's an argument for another day
Barnes
Yeah the theory
About the media
The depiction
It also reminds me of what I said
Scholarships
Phenomenon
60 + 7
What particular groups tend to be demonized within the popular media
And back then
African America
Import White
Certain parts of the country
Kennedy portrayed
Fortunately
Dangerous and frightening way
Is that the beak
Take me to try to demonize those communities
Did whatever the establish
Panera
And so if you came from a community that reflected that
Popular
Cultural representation
Gifted
Whiteman
General
Also add Willy
Target even like I feel like big little lies when they
Yo would represent
Well
Other religions out there that that despite having some negative beliefs in general
Betrayed
With rapturous
Positivity like like
Somebody's either a member or a groupie
So I'm just trying to be coy with saying religious people at the fun
I didn't want to make it clear I wanted to leave a little air of vagueness that I talked about
Christian identity
Good call wink
Stefan molyneux is like
Buck
I've been through the fire and everyone knows I suck
Let's talk about f****** Christian Supremacy
Yeah that's f****** revealing too
Bb8
The idea that what he's pushing is
Glycol
Christian
I see what you doing can you imagine
Jinhao
Like imagine being able to tie Barnes
Pick 9th
I would love that
Pick out of all of those names
You give me 90% of them and wolf
Will f****** see who's in the political Maine
And if you still believe
Stefan molyneux podcast
Whatever
Snow White
The scrutiny it's just
Talk Hood narrative
He's a very
Marketable thing
No
Further down this
Slippery
Road at were on where it we learned that it's all about Christianity
White
Course
Barn starts talking about
The Covington case
But he's involved
Vicki said something
Things that aren't true
It was really a sub
Motivation
Chicken places
The Covington Chase
The message was what are these
That are successful at resisting
Sort of the elite
Entertainment and education that almost monopolize
Friday identity
Well that is place
Like really
Suppository
Independent
Establish
What's the narrative
In a widely
Catholic School
By trying to scare parents
McAfee School
Someday maybe then your time will ruin your life
Just because he really ghost
Catholic School
Affected
Time for planning on
Across the country wow
Wow writers for the New York Times
Stop
Again with her their
I'm pretty fast food fight
Education
I don't want to demonize it don't want to be one of the only places
Cuz we're like
Free thinking is is allowed
Strange
Because there's an overlay of religion
So-so
Barnes let me let me ask you a question
One of the
Strictest and most dogmatic places that you could ever get an education
Is the last Bastion for free
Sorry I completely forgot everything I've ever learned about Capo
Bookscool apologies
Not to be too blunt about this
Extremists
Presentation
Religious schools are the only place that give you a counter-narrative to the mainstream that
Trying to
Essentially trying to brainwash you and created collectivist
That dystopia where conservatives aren't allowed to say anything
Extremist
Physical kind of like
Matter-of-fact way that makes
It seemed like it
It's not as Extreme as it is this is insane
I'm still not be I'm still not able to draw this parallel that
Sorry about with lion
I don't see any similarities between that what
Whatsoever
Probably not
Barnes
It's just a lot
Dummy Jack Dorsey
Party
What is the biggest live
Because they become one of the
Forget what anybody goes to Twitter and tried to look up
Meet Barnes law
Sylvia
Unless they're already
I disappear
Saudi
I just finally they took
I did
Follow Barn
How long did it take you to find the first name that pops up to
Google Robert Barnes Barnes law
You forgot that you weren't connect
Did to Wi-Fi
Then it might take a little longer might be harder to find it that's if that's possible
Absolutely
Now what's interesting about that is the argument
It proves the opposite
Because you saying that
I can't be found on Twitter I'll maybe they're mad at me cuz I took some of your time
MSU time
That only serves to reinforce
B Twitter is not
Vindictively attacking you in anyway
I could still find it Twitter
It is not difficult
He's someone who if Jack was a petulant person news
Capriciously Rakim
Yeah you would be number one
Also he could
Sure
I do like him being like
And now I'm about to
Coppell one bigger
I don't think it's
Bigger butt like I would say how I would look at Jack statement
More like
I bet he meant that when he said it was the goal
It was not a Isaac you're starting
Start up
You probably have a really different idea of what it is
Millions of users
Isaac changed the complexion of
With Twitter like working
Speech all over the place right what's the logistics of what
How people are going to abuse
Start to become real
You can't live up to the the goals you set out for yourself
Puppy outside
Yes I'll probably
Stating an idea and then failing
To live up to
For any number of Circa
Does not
Me and you are lying about your ID
Bright Eyes
Deserves criticism
I don't think it's
Actual malice which is a problem
We're going to get rid of it
Christian paranoia here in
Sponsor
Stuff that's just
Way out of line
Why is it all the best
Deliverance your kind of redneck
Coastal Elite The General
What countries
What when you put a
Historically has stood between
Galactus collectible
And straight out of the French
Revolution posting they did was kill the priest that killed someone
So there is those who seek power
Have a great deal of
And so warm
Christian's Libertarians and so on
Anniyan and others end
Between the predators in the power AC
At people like that
Okay why do you agree with that
100% volume
Yeah the phone was on a bit of a rash was stupid
Yeah somebody tells me that Stefan molyneux is smart
I think
In some ways yes
Somebody who knows
Elvish
Is good at
You know Larry absolutely you're smart
That's
You're living in a fictitious World ice skating in Lord of the Rings world you are a f******
Genius Stephen molyneux in the real world
You're an idiot
By my earlier comments about him being really smart it is much as like he has
High level of mental processing power
Functionally
Technically smart but functionally an idiot
What kind of Elvis thing works
We don't need to spend a lot of time rehashing her Christianity
He served as an excuse and immoral rationalization for
Colonialism
Anna. Where countless indigenous peoples were massacred and had their lands taken from them and their resources
Ripple effects that still played much of the world today
I don't know how to find to find
Purity or pressure
But if it doesn't include Experian
He's talking about something else
When you look around the world and you try and figure out who some of the major not good folks are
He kind of got the sense
Stefan's notion that Christianity is somehow resistant
Just a depression is like
Complete bulshit
Nonsense
Hungarian prime minister Viktor Orban is a Christian
Religious stuff lately in the Philippines is identified
These guys complain all day about South Africa but their president
Slobodan milosevic was a Christian and that dude's face charges
Crimes against humanity
There plenty of world leaders who are up-to-no-good who are Christian
But beating up on Christianity
Isn't the point
Their leaders of all religious persuasion
To do bad things
Goleta country's downtown
Religion
When you completely ignore that this is an unrelated variable
Continue to lionize Christianity demean other religions based on that false
It really demonstrates
It's more that your soft pitching
A social theocracy
Dan
Do you know what is
Is real tyranny but the Muslims
In Jerusalem
In 1080 that was real tyranny because they wouldn't just let the British
Thousands of miles away
Have it
I think they would
Keira Knightley
The more a Christian anxiety you're coming up in
Look at the Nike
30 communist model
You're trying to rap
Which is getting bought like
Apartments apart of
Infiltrate
Appreciate people
. process
Get all of that they mostly been wildly
Ezequiel Ramos
In the United States
Almost out of them religious
Parochial School
Controller
TV and Hollywood
Major books
Elmo
With the sole exception
Really being the church
Is the last ripassa
Story of traditional beliefs
Their status
And sort of
Revolutionary mindset
It's one that attacked
Prediction
Tax ideas
Because of their Association
Warwick
Expedition
Christian religion
Because they see them as their biggest
Diesel
We could get rid of churches
Like the county
To do in the 1930s in places like Russia
Parsley
The best way to
Perceive the world
Ain't nobody trying to get rid of churches
Are we adding Catholicism is are they adding Catholicism
People who used to murder Catholics for the very active
Right there from that ideological
Willy-nilly
Growth
Used to have a great time alienated Catholic but now I still hate the Pope
Netflix
The pope is still a demon
These people are so f*****
Being stupid why is it that they get to destroy the world
I don't know
Won't work now this is
Turn now
Like this episode conversation
Stephon is having with Robert Barn
Has turned towards
Be natural
Place that it was
Okay I'm expressing that be
Are the threats
Against white identity
And Christianity that I'm going to focus on with my
All I want at least that's my guiding principles
I'm going
To be like
The guy who you go to
Whenever you
Like infringe on a gay person and you feel like you should have
Pro straight white male
Yeah
First
Prologue
And you can hear by how much this turns into a like
Christianity is the only thing that matters is the last bulwark against
Terranea
Alright man
So they get into some real stupid territory
After
But it's still within this
This dissertation that's going on about how Christianity is under attack
And tap man
Philly
Pedophilia
The Catholic Church
Hollywood
But only one
Has been sent
Recovered
Civil suit in criminal case
If in the churches in the
That's absurd
Steel focus on Hollywood
Now I would argue
They're one of the reasons that the Hollywood stuff is been a little bit more difficult
Is the people who come from the same places
Has Robert Barnes
Maybe write for similar Publications
Panic sing
There's a lot of distraction
With the pizza world that is taken away from any kind of
Real
Focus
Distraction
The create
Expectations that can't be lived up to
Yeah the creates a false version
That makes it look like real investigations recovery
That isn't the media's fault
That's your side's fault
That's Alex and his associates full
That is something that you will never be able to achieve
The idea that everybody is involved
Blood-drinking
Child sacrifice
Party
Is not something you're going to ever prove
Add because you can't you'll always look at it as like well they never really got to the bottom of
And you know what they do with the Catholic Church
The only one
Not about protecting kids
It's about attacking Christianity
Very
For especially
Cuz there's a
Griffin I mean Griff
About
The Catholic Church
Measurable number of
Is over
Comprehend
Yeah I not least of which
Because
That's not a thing that can be
Partisan
You can't do that
Directions
What are you talkin about
White religious people
Georgia
It doesn't make any sense for me
Nope
So if you wanted to make less than
Robert Barnes here has a an example of something that shows
The distinction
Between how people react
Hollywood
AMC the priest
In the Catholic Church
And I would say this is one of the more ludicrous compare
Try to reinstate
White
Death record
Appropriate
If you think
Saudi amazing dynamic
Buena Park
Revealed that their true agenda
What if God was a Catholic
Eddie took to Twitter to make horrible jokes
That's his smoking gun rights
I mean
It's a little weak
That is
Dumbo
I have ever had work Barnes
We would have been treated differently if he was a f******
Priest
Greg Barnes
Gun situation
Is kind of analogous analogous
Because
No one is ever had like a priest
Did the Catholic Church
Thing f*****-up
Right that's not been the case
You can't really draw parallels
Between them you show me that
The Catholic priest
Repeat something I really f***** up
And then we'll talk
Then we'll talk about how the reaction.
You know what also lets
Show me not just the Catholic priests who f***** up
Intuitive sense
Weird but the Catholic priest who f***** up and tweeted something 10 years ago that was Unearthed
Dubai a right-wing suck
King lunatic a****** trying to
OK Google
Control operator
Then blown out of proportion
Fair enough
Situation then we can gauge reactions and how they're different
So I born
Believes
Some interesting things about
The First Amendment
Get rid of it no
Before it but he has a slightly different interpretation of it
Most people
Big Meech
Big fat
Target certain
Really slowly because of
To suppress
Concentra
Thought
Stalking
Audience
Really all about
Protecting the audience's right
Introspective
The audience
Rational
Their morale
Capacity
It doesn't trust
The ordinary person
Ability of thought
Conscience
Processing
Information
Mick Gordon Wyatt
That's why they have
So he believes it appears
That the first time I met a titles you to an audio
Which is absurd
Crazy it's the right
You're infringing on the rights of the audience right
Which I am and of course
Entitled to right like if you use the Alex Jones example the audience
Isn't affected Alex
You can still find wherever
So even under his
Broad definition of the first appointment
Alex is not being impressed at all he has his website you can still find his s*** wherever you want
Like
Florence doesn't respect
The audience
To go out
And find it
On their own wow interesting
It don't look like barns
This is the one who disrespects his
Is audience
By saying that their apps
Absolutely incapable of Googling
Alex Jones
Infowars.com
The other problem that I have is the audience
To make a decision here these things
To make a decision
But you know the classic example of
You can't yell fire in a crowded building
Write his version of it would be
Because
If you get in trouble for yelling fire in a crowded building what you're doing is you're not trusting the other people in that building to make a sound
Moral decision about whether or not there's a fire
Capable of knowing
Instantaneously
When hearing fire
Whether or not there is or is not a fire.
Disrespect to the people in that theater
If you get the person at
Trick
Hundreds of people into doing something silly I don't
Putting on
People is absurd
Even know how to describe it it's
You're such a
Strange way to look
It is such a fascinating it doesn't matter what I do you must respond
It's such an also the fire in a crowded theater thing is a really interesting a noun
When you
Actually
In a way I don't trust
These people
Instant react
To this guy
A screaming fight
Because
That guy could be a bad actor
He could be a bad faith actor
And in
Split Second
He is
Influencing your emotional Behavior
Bypassing your rational thought process
And
In influencing you react in the weather today
Detrimental
Do your own bed
And that's what he's doing
Well it's on you to make a rational decision or whatever
Are you to disagree with me
I don't necessarily agree
Specific suit
Barnes hats
Real stupid
His main argument seems to be that this is like a
Focused attack
Using Alex as an example because what they're doing is there deplatforming
And that also defaming him
He's not able to respond because he's been to
The platform
This is
Silly
And I know it's silly because of the examples that he
He uses
But they're doing parallel
They're not only when they
Enterprise
The water right
Craziest way
Completely
Cities in California
Cities in California to lawyers totally Fallen
Instead lied about
Take me where I go Estrella Court
They were unopened
Email account
If I understand correctly
But this was not
Here's the thing
You know how Stefano's these things
Because it was f****** reported
The Lakers this is like no one was reporting the story that Alex sent these people c********* for the shitz and giggles
Get that information Insider information
If you're complaining about people misunderstanding the story that was correctly reported in New York
That I don't know what to do I don't know what to do for you your complaint is the people on Twitter dumb
Yes
Is the case
Is doing
As
Robert is presenting
They're presenting the idea that the media lied about this situated
And that does not
True I've read a bunch of Arctic
About that situation
Because we had to cover it on this show
All of them
We're clear about
They were the FBI had been involved
And had said that it does not appear that Alex was aware of it these were on open
There was no culpability that was assigned to Alex Jones
I don't even know if this isn't any of the articles are just what I took away from it
The criticism that could be launched
Is
How the f*** did he not look at what he was turning over to Discovery
Is the sort of criticism
That is
What could be taken from it
If you want to talk about the interpretations
The people could have of
DD
With whatever someone might walk away from it if they didn't read the whole article
Well then you're just talking about Alex's business model
So almost like your
Not trusting the audience
To read the
Tire art
Infringing upon their free speech
Will hear of like Alex being defamed and platform
Got the reports that I've read were very clear about the
Situation
And if you want
Need to sue those people
It doesn't matter
Anyway
I love
Like it's so stupid
For him to be like
And know if there's no way
Silence them so there's no way that that information
Okay
Let me repeat back to you exactly what I read
Quoting from the wash right
Information reporting
Sostuto stupid
So there's other lies
The media's defamed hour
Facts about sharks
Lost the lawsuit
A book that has nothing to do with
Head anti-semitic statements
He made a rap
A white shoe
Lawyer
Search lawsuit in writing the book no one died at Sandy Hook
MarketWatch
We've discussed this already
And now it should be right to
To get in touch with them
Insist they retract
Can apologize
However
The APU
And this is because they didn't write it and didn't publish it
A completely different website did
This is what I was his grandstanding about suing the Associated Press about early in the episode which is never going to fly
Knows that this is the Publix
Nice. You can tell because there's a
The clear problem they did real
And they're attacking the straw man
Yep the problem is super easy to resolve all you have to do is contact MarketWatch and if they refuse to correct it then you sue them
All you do is focus on the Associated Press
You're not interested in the correction you're not interested in the real problem
You're interested in pretending the largest news Outlet in the United States
To slandering
And the real reason to do that is to elevate and exaggerate your own Vicks
Mark my words
That lawsuit will never happen
Because any lawyer Alex could possibly have would know that if you thrown out immediately and possibly even open up
Refine
For a frivolous or malicious filing of a suit
It's absolutely ridiculous
Not if
You are a
Working for the
Free America lost
Center that lost
I don't know I still think even Barnes with no like this
Opens up
Potential
That's why I hired
You're sure
I was always against the reading of Alex's words as jewboy
But also really drunk when he say
Said that anyway
Caulking
Super unclearly in that ran
I can totally understand how someone could
Could hear jewboy in there
But I think if you're familiar
His career in style
Throw around stuff like that
He has decades under his belt walking a very fine line and even he's aware that calling someone jewboy
Is going to raise more questions about his rhetoric that he wants sex
That's one of those things where
I was
I understand why people would think him being drunk
More likely to
To throw out
But at the same time
Black performing wise
There
I don't know why I thought
Almost
Across-the-board bud
There's a certain amount of muscle memory that
Takes over even if you're
I've been
Drunk before
And then I walk up on stage
And do the same set that I normally do
It's just it's just muscle
And then you walked
Which is why I don't
Think that even if Alex is
Is really drunk
He's going to
You forget
All of those performance
Things
You know the difference between autopilot or whatever the performance
Spade
Dealing with chaos
While you're performing
Like if you started getting heckled you might end up the drunkenness might come back
Possible
I don't know if that works
As well as it might feel like it for Alex's
Drunken ranting
But I still even like in his intoxicated
It's a I still do I think he knows better
He's very used to knowing
Where approximate lines are
He test those lines before he crosses them a lot of the time
There's a lot of calling everybody else actors before he jumps in
And starts doing the actress.
That testing align
That's like telling up to it and seeing how it feels
Before he commits to
He would never just drunkenly
You got yelled this guy's a Jew boy
I just don't feel like it's in his character even if there is a ton of
Semitism
It is worldview
I just don't think it makes sense
The transcript
Plaintiff
But even critics
Like will summer
My overall feeling about this is that the transcription folks were incorrect
But I don't think it came from a place of malice
They're trying to defame out
I think Alex
Who's f****** wasted
Screaming about the plane
Million-dollar bounty on his head
Do bees eat
Mistake
In the transcription if you're not really all that familiar with Alex
Especially considering
White shoes
The super well-known
Interim
That's not a slang insult that gets thrown around by most people
So I don't know if it's on the tip of a lot of people's tongues
Yeah so you're doing transcript
He's drunk he's kind of flirting
You don't know what white shoe boy means
Cuz why would you write I still don't know what
It means like a Ivy League
Upper Crust
Kind of
Richie
So anyway we get back to Barnes
Defending the Alex
The court of public opinion
If you well on Stefan molyneux
So he is
Spear for lost
As the victim in Target of big media
Big Tech solution
To be able to
And the reason is because
Independent
Perspective
Protective
Anywhere else
Imma get information I don't hear
Should have the power in Detroit
Decide whether
Whether I like it or no
Scott to a 10-hour Montage italics
With
Yeah I love this idea that
Package Alex as this Lake
Rogue Independent Media guy who's
Get the f*** out of here
I don't like
Is is
I don't know obviously
Because I'm not in
Legal Circle
Is lawfare
Thrown around
Looking a
Cuz I'm not
Let's
That's not how you know what is the word that Barnes uses a lot and I've noticed from listening to a bit of him that he's also
One of these guys who likes to
Speaking alliteration and rhyme
He says lies and labels all the f****** time
Whatever he says either word it's
That kind of
Aggressive
Everything is okay
Fairy should be law War
Instead Infowars
Grandiose
About to Alex's struggle
I've been proud to be a car.
Try to defend Alex Jones
Legal actions of all time
To ascertain
Free speech and free
Presrite
Been behind them
The future
Free speech
Free Press in America
And that's why it's so important
City of the best represent
The best legal I can
Bates the best defense
Because ultimately
We are outside
Alex
NFL C-TEC big media
I would say okay
I would say
I don't think there's anything wrong with
Mediatek treating me like Alex drone
See how getting the consequences
If you can
If I directly inspired
Harassment to go on for years and years and years
I think I would be
If there's somebody was like
Yeah you're going to need to be punished
He's lucky that there's not a hundred more
Cuz
Hit his his style is broadcast what he does
Large
Depends on
Like he's just
Straight up constantly lying about people
That's a good boy
I guess I can try
I think it when I look at all this is a large cent
Suspicion
I don't think
It's even possible
At this point
To know what barnes's game is
But Victor strong indications
That you know
He's done some Marquee cases
In the past what year was Wesley Snipes lawyer in that tax
Yeah he's tried to
Latch onto a lot of these right-wing grifter
This case
Along with the Covington
He's trying to really make an a
Myself under the auspice
Pictures of
The free America lost
Right
It's entirely possible that
It's just
A scam
It's entirely possible
Believes
With these other
Conservative libertarian
Christian
Public Law offering
Not catered
To the specific needs that he has
Edmonton if he presented his argument as these
Things do exist but they're not
You working
In the direction I want them to
Create a run
I would find that argument a little bit more honest
Since he's not presenting
Like that in all of this is just
We don't have anything in the splc NaCl you were running over us his framing of it makes
It's me really worried
About what the realtor
Bizarre
So
All I can do
Is take the pieces of information that are available to
@ryan makes
And it's last clip
Doesn't help
Great deal.
To be interviewed by Stefan molyneux
Someone who is a creep of the highest order
And a self-described
Empiricist who supports white nationalism
So I just don't I don't
Seaway around looking at this
In the context
That Barnes is offering me
I'm not
You know
Anyway I'm looking at his actions
Compare
Somebody did very similar things in the past
You spit to publicize
His venture
He's willing to you know he promotes that on Alex's show but will Stefan molyneux and talk about it for
An hour
In a way that drift
Deeply
Enter Christian identity
White identity ideas
That to me is not
On
Important
Nah
No
So far every
Every
P0land in Iraq
Every time I've heard anything about it
Every time I've heard his voice
Barnes
Creeps me out
And he is
Running something on someone always
I don't think I've never heard him in any such
Situation where I feel like he was
On the up-and-up everything is always been like
You're running some game on somebody
Sometime right now like I just don't even know who it is is definitely
I think a lot of our invitation
Him trying to take over Infowars
Goodyear
Jack actually this
Easily explained
By him
I'm trying to set up this
Counter to the
Now that it now that we've heard about that
I'm trying
Sure people now who are like
Tech is starting
To take some of these
More seriously
There are a lot of people who have
Fascist Outlet
Francis Outlets
That are going to be needing a lawyer
And so creating
Counter splc that caters
To people who are of that ilk
Does
Seem like it could be a pretty
Prophet Levin
So that's why I don't
Exclude the idea that you just
But
It's also even if it is a scam
Dangerous
Yeah
Pat from
I understand the Freeway Rick Ross was on the show and then listen to that
But I guess
Went down this road a little bit maybe we should stay in the present for Wednesday
Either way we'll be back on
IMDb will until then
Grid website
Childsupport.com on some other social group
Yeah at go to bed Jordan at knowledge underscore fight
Unless you are not connected to the network
Croissant
Download are pocket
ITunes anywhere you can leave a review that would be lovely
To get it though
If you go to your local convenience
And I'm not going to buzz my
Specific racist yells at you
Look for the
Can we are going to see the first can of Coca-Cola and those little things
You're going to want to grab it it's not in there
Behind
You will be able to get our podcast from that
Can of Coca-Cola be a flash drive
Always
The recommendation for a future one of these
Write this down
I think that's a good one
For February
Mardi Gras February
But until then I know I'm Leo I'm dzx Clark
Holding
Alex