I have great respect for knowledge B I'm sick of them posing
MoneyGram
Alex vype.com
Jordans
What
The longest
Paper UF
Perhaps.
What was the shortest
No idea no you don't know I remembered you remember specific
Papers in college
No
I don't have a lot of memories of us like
Papers or anything
Memories of like subject
That were covered in the information but not the actual
Experience of writing paper or how long it was
25000 word paper
Of course I'm going to remember that
I forget a lot of weed
In college I wrote a lot of papers
And I always did very well with that
Very good paper writer
Especially back in college
Non-Stop
A hundred percent
Turn papers but I do know a lot about Alex Jones
Time frame of September 6th
To September 11th
Your moment
But before we do got to take a moment to say thank
So first of all thank you so much
Katie
She ran our policy walk
I'm a policy wonk
Ralph thank you so much
I apologize
Pronounce Ralph
I didn't mean to I have nothing but respect for the Nobel Ralphs
So the world's like a racket
Yes
Next
Gunks
Alright
Amapola
Appreciate that very much
So David thank you so much
And thank you so much
You're both wonderful technocrat
Heroin
Freakishly large
So we wanted to take a little quick moment before we get any further into the show 2
Give a little bit of explanation of
Some stuff
But before we do another context drop
Alex Jones
He's joking
Everybody who listens and everybody who supports
It's the show
Into this versus the reality of it and it
It's overwhelming in many ways
The creates the insecurity
Because we do essentially no promotion whatsoever the only reason
Does people
Been very very supportive
We've grown out of the point where we could pursue doing ads on
Yeah
Probably not too difficult but
Both in private conversations
Infield fairly similarly
With Epson flows perhaps daily mood
Especially on a show like are those weird experience
For listeners
Enjoying it so much you know if we
Go with somebody who gets to choose our ads
Infowars I don't want to I don't want to make fun of and Alex
Harry's razors
I like
Shrek
Is there anyways I don't know what they would be served by an advertised
Like I'm not entirely sure if anything
A+ for the audience and then also the show itself but feel weird
We're making a strong commitment
Do not taking advertising
And being entirely audience
Supported as we have been
Appreciative
Into exactly what today
It can be and should be
You everyday it would really help
Adverb
Very very
This sort of thing
So
But the average
If you look
Couple bucks
Tacoma policy walk
September 6th through the 11th
And contacts drops
I think that's putting on a
Tower I assume talking with Barnes about his
Continuing legal travel
The barn
Does make at least two appearances on this trip
Starbucks bar
So we started
Is in a bit of a weird mood and image clip heat to find leadership
But I think I only kept
B clip
Him because he pronounces some words funny
I kind of enjoyed it
Leadership
Did you know
But end up in the end
Launching
Home
Human
Whiteman
Humans
And become closer
That's leadership
Sabotaging culture
Deception
Evil
It's a virus
Manipulate system
Closet
He does not
Progenerate
It is not a
Construct
If they build or Burke
They are
Some of the similar ideas to use the tree of Good and Evil
Standing of the Garden of Eden story
I like I like that
Then this is always true
Nobody is better attic
Explaining why Ali
Alex is the worst
Then Alex
What he's talking about
What he thinks
He literally
Just laid out all of the reason
I couldn't have put it better myself
Dailymail.com
Got the show
There's a real f*****-up headspace that we're going to get into
When we get to the 11
911 911
What does startling revelation
But I think people will be very excited to hear
I know you probably already believes that's very milquetoast
So I think he's in a weird head probably because of things
Think about it later
Episodes
Knows what's going on
Comes back from break with some
Beatles
Emily gets real f****** heady about this man
Oh no
Wonder what he's talking
Drug
Greenhill
And just lay there for hours
Felicia
Universe
Gods
In the front
You don't even need to be on LSD
The good news is Chill Force works new products
I put a lot of it in this
Is a diamond lattice
Alright
So Alex gets out from there but that really trippy
College dorm
Yeah yeah this is philosophy
And what you do now today
Broadcast
If you
It's not like you're just a leg up
You're the whole shooting match
If you like
Famously today
Your Word of Mouth
Your son is
Central
Smooth they want to kill you
Both of us are like
And
There's a real feeling that I have going through this episode of preparing
Stream is s***
F****** crazy and I'm sitting here
Becomes yeah
Whether it be from a bigotry standpoint or from a disgusting
Performance-based
All of our enemies want to kill your children and I'm the one who can stop them
One of those weird
Improv
Quote unquote
Sins of what it is
In the basement I'm so dumb to it
Itsfunneh
Both of us kind of like
It was non-stop freaking out
Even though he's ramped up his rhetoric
How much further could you
And you're just like alright fine you're disgusting and gross but
Move on
So what
A lot more lately I'm not positive
Part of how he
Reframe things earlier in his
If he did it was less
Frequently but he's putting it in a lot of religious
Terms
Black people giving him money
Okay I'm done plugins
Pods for the truth I say
Post-birth abortion
Still alive
Call storytime
So
It Whatever you've been at it
Mayor Pete
Because I'm about a Buddha
Nope
Because I Got High
She's like a megachurch
Glitterbug tie
Type of guy
I don't care
I just think it's pretty interesting
If you got this framing of stuffing but much more consistently put into the terms of like
We are almost it's almost like a religious duty to give Alex 10% of your
Upsetting
Absolutely
So one of the other things It's upsetting is that there seems to be a
Trend along with Robert Barnes being on all of the
There's another guy who seems to be coming up a lot more freak
That is that guy Tom pepper
If you recall
He is a guy who runs the station at Wichita
And I don't I don't know
I mean I guess this guy ran a semi popular Trump
Facebook page the god Emperor Trump
And so that's Alex's way in or whatever but this guy
Must have blackmailed Alex
Because he is on a lot
Sorry
Jesus
So he comes on and he talks about how the Infowars audience has responded two times
They have like
His TV station has a power blackout
Interruption of service
I think that if you listen to how he died
Describes the audience
He wants
To put it in terms
Very into the programming
Kind of sounds like
Paranoid cult
They were local TV station so you got movies you've got news you've got Sports you been all kinds of stuff but let me tell you when there is a
Bump in the nights when there's a power surge when there's something bad that happened it's not
Anybody asking about the movie networking
Hundreds and hundreds of calls what happened to Alex
Completely unbelievable
They do tide
Do the TV station
They tired to Tom pappert this is gross
Because what he's described exaggerated probably
Positive sign
Is people like any service interruptions
Paranoia
That is just bizarre
Rough
Positive
Obsessive weird and
Sacrilege
Yeah there's no I have a hard time
Being the guy who is like how dare you impugn religion you're working again
What's the tenant of religion
Not my place but just feel for what I remember when I used to go to church
He found a box
My church
When I was growing up
Was not revealing post-birth abortion
They were not telling us all about all of the other b*******
But I'm pretty sure the past
Pissed off at somebody was
Iritis
That dude
So I probably wouldn't be
2 is
Tom and Allie
Describe
Ice-T
Little baby indication
New top hits
Appearances on the
Michelle
But
Kind especially on the September 6th episode
Some indication
That this dude
Surprise
I know.
I'm just completely flummoxed by this development
Multi-ethnic
I'm not sure
Surround
Of carrying out a white genocide
That's exactly right
100%
Tried-and-tested way to destroy civilization across time
Intelligent
Part of this because
Accident in trying to destroy Western countries
Lucidly in countries that were settled by high and intelligent individuals
Even more direct
The human population okay
You catch on that one Bingo metaphorically
I assumed he was including Guatemala in Western
I don't know
I'm guessing when he said they were settled by
High Intelligence individuals and I don't think he was referencing
I don't think so
Specific about who is
I feel like there's a lot of
Reinforced
And what happened what's wrong
That we're not genetically similar to the government
False
Now I don't want dissertation here
Probably
Probably the longest
Add discuss how this broadcast
And Alex Jones is worldview is explicitly anti-government
This
Is bizarre
For them to be complaining about minority groups coming
Crazy
Crazy it's almost as we all know the Roman god
Government is famous
All of it
Leaving Rome
It's almost
Like these have a very different standard for white people
It's very essential that they fight back against the oppressive government
Genetically similar to
Dumas
What else has our mentality to see on display like
It would be one thing
Do you know they weren't
All about being against
The government
AR
Poor
Yeah that's not very good and how kind of glaring a lot of these holes are
Just in their speech
The surprised they haven't thought
This all the way through
About a video that he found of some person
Being set on fire in South Africa
Okay
Decided that one of his kids is going to be like
Restarting
I mean metaphorically yeah I guess I kind of
There's a lot of rhetoric that runs
Along those lines
Starts talking about how
The black smoke in South Africa are races
List against other black people
Cigar just targets
It's complicated
Yes yes
A couple problem
Bethesda frame
Little Caesars
One-wheeler in Zulu
So this is a in the middle of tirade that Alex is on
We're horrible anti-white
Spinato's
Delivering a section of a country called
The first misconception Alex seems to have
Is that
Which is actually called kwazulu-natal
Throughout South Africa and elsewhere but if you land on a map
You might get the idea that you are
Right
When the British arrived in the late 1800s in South Africa
Cinnamon place
Surrender to British rule which these
Give it up to the British
Because they're essentially Somali pirates exist
The British eventually conquered the Zulu nation divided
Most likely because it would be much more easy to manage the
A little while after
This worried the British sense that Alliance would give the boers access to a port which could hurt British trade dominance in the region
Zulu
The most important thing to remember is that the legacy of zulu being forced to live in kwazulu-natal is not the legacy of the
It is the direct result of Apartheid
Still in place hundreds of thousands of Zulu
Had their land taken
Forcibly relocated to quads
The idea is to create a semi-autonomous state
Which was still largely controlled by the white power structure
Which would serve as a place for a lot of non-whites to go to
It's not really all that different than any other formulation of white nationalism you
Where you wanting on whites
To go somewhere but on the off-chance
Be clear that you're in charge
Do the displacement of thousands
Thousands of zulu to quads
The distribution of the population does do pretty heavily towards kwazulu
But it's not the ANC your Nelson Mandela
It was the apartheid government
Send. Completely irresponsible
He's pointing to a direct
Of the brutal apartheid system
You're in simple
This is an expression of overt white nationalism
And that is the prism through which
He's looking at
The world Okay so
Is he
Using this
In concert with their other like demographic bulshit where they're saying see look what happened in Africa
They let all these white people in and the white people destroyed the entire country
So that's why we can't let people into America
No
No he's not making that
No he's arguing that Nelson Mandela and the ANC were the people who put all the Zulu in Zoo
Zululand that's the dumbest thing anybody could say
Is unreal use a scribe
Blame for that like a geographical relocation that happened during apartheid
So what are you doing people like this look at the world
So
It's f***** up
Just went in and f*****
Everything up over and over and over again all across the world
And that was fine
Right in the
That's really really negative things that we're done during those periods
The time we're actually done by
Africa
We've covered this before in the past
Alex Reid
Understand
The genocide in Rwanda
Why why did you go somewhere like
Rwanda
Weather small Christian tribe
Years
And they killed the Christian minority
Wendy
First worship
That's really happened absolutely
Stegosaurus has proved anything
The reason that the Tootsie
Had a lot of the property was because they were deemed the
VR the bureaucratic class
By the Bell
Prior to the events
Stanford Prison Experiment
Except
I know but like
That kind of function of like
Almost
Arbitrarily the belgians were just like you so cute
See each other because you are more similar to you
And that is
What Alex's Alex's
Pretending
That you know just one
Similarly
MDF
Mr.
Crazy Bowls
White nationalist propaganda of the highest
Right
State Historical inventors
Citizen X
Just kind of dumb
You know
Could always use a little pallet
I guess
These churches
Tell you how moral they are all day
They're probably
Did he just say most
Pastors are closeted I don't know if I don't know what he's exactly saying
Sexuality
Insult
It's kind of par for the course for him but
Whatever Alex
Villa Family Show with supervisor Alex picks up this is a family show
Oh boy
Oh that's a good family
Call Larry Graf wall
Call is a guy who came out with some information about him
Supposedly infiltrating The Weather Underground
Back of the seven
And he said that they plan
Everybody's
Confirm that they were planning to put people in education camps
Who didn't give up on capitalism
And the 25 million or so people would need
Killed
And of course Alex confront Weather Underground
Volaris
About this and Bellaire the complaints
I never knew he was working for the FBI
Take that under advisement and still believe that everything is
A hundred percent true
About that a little bit
And then I think that
Tom pappert got
Trolled
Any thinks it's
Real
Vietnam
Wellness
Assertive
Thomas Wright
Yes we know how the weather underground and their remnants love to
F*** with Alex and comments on YouTube articles
Comment thread on a Yahoo article
That is
Is representative of how the entire
Nation now what
Put
People in forced labor
We're going unacceptable versions of that a little bit later
The purplest internet commentary
Another example
Real dumb dumb thing to say
Fantasizing about
Well
Toothpaste
What they're saying is the first
Form design in fruit
Thought
My only question is does Tom pappert sincerely think that these people were for real
I understand that they were f****** around this is a joke
Works for me
Right
The only question I have
Or is he aware of his
Because this is
This is a crazy attempt to launder
I guess
A f****** dumb internet joke interviewing like
These people are sincerely planning on the jobs that they're going to have
Call me to take over
Why would they have a red arm
Green army
It's f****** insane
Some of those concerns that I had about Tom password having these quite 10
We're really elevated by some comments that he makes
Sort of about countries
Might as well
This is real fast there
We basically kill ourselves
Iceland
Multiculturalism in all of these immigrants who come from completely antithetical
Call Church
Because Kim Jeong Hoon
Kendall Auto indications that West
Man's wife
Very historically Iceland
Ethnically speak
Economic upturn
In the Icelandic economy which has the effect of drawing people in who are looking for opportunity
Internet
Sensitive to welcome immigrants in
Because their economics
Success is aided by an in
Inflow of Labor
The image of Iceland in ahead of someone like Alex or Tom pappert isn't imagine it's place where everyone is white
2017 census
10.6% of the population of Iceland were first-generation
Immigrant up from 4% in 90
T90
What a great difficulty is Big Island 900 Mi away from Norway
Get indictment is a difficult feat for someone trying to
And for many years after the
2008 financial crisis
It wasn't a fight like a hugely appealing option
Native-born icelanders took that as a scientist
The country
As the economy has Diversified in the tourism sector is skyrocketed
Iceland is a place that looks a lot more
For someone trying to find a place that
Can survive
Iceland is a country with a relatively
Small population
And it was starting to replace a very low immigration
But as the economy has grown
Exactly the pattern you would expect
This isn't some globalists stronghold in the immigrants who arrived in our from all sorts of culture
Even the ones that Tom dumped her things are incompatible
With the West
Switzerland is even worse example
Over top of you
Switzerland has consistently ranked
Very high on the list of countries with the highest proportion of the population
Competing for inborn
With a number sitting at around 23%
Compared to the US at
EU countries
It's not like all the people who Tom would call Western those the only people were immigrating to
Switzerland
There's a large population of Tamil people who fled the Civil War
Sri Lanka who have resettled in
There are a large number of people from Croatia
Serbia has made Switzerland their new home
As well as Filipinos and
Pakistani population
Things that are particularly large
What time is it
Is categorically not true but it feels right
The people who yearn to live in a white f
They want it so bad that they have to pretend that their imagined enemies
Creative pure Enclave
Without immigrants
Hagen for them
Themselves because
You got to just be surrounded by your own race
They know it
They know what they're keeping it to themselves and Iceland in Switzerland
This is a gigantic red flag
From a white nationalism
The perspective is extremist
Under the guise of
Normal conversation
Also tax rates
A cross
But if you just look at the highest
Lowest tax rate brackets
United States
There doesn't appear to be too much to what he saying other than
Feels true to him
Namely that these
Is R1
Associated with whiteness
And they're better because of
Jordan
There's a name for that
I'll leave at
I just always want to be there in
Tell me what weather
And you know what
You know and I know it
Just f******
Y'all know
What was it
It was like
When the volcano erupted
And shut down travel from
Did you came to the United
Iceland
Non-Stop
The next year
Is crazy and of course
And
All of them
Missouri
Absolutely represent the reality that's been the case for a number of years
It's not a globalist plot natural occurrence
Over diversifying
Economy
Perhaps
Exploding
Alex just believe that they
Shut off valve
Looking Glass
But anything is everything
Talking about
Remember his name that's a democratic donor who would
Bring
African American dudes
To his home and then inject them
He's talking about that
Worth talking about really
Spins out
Into sort of
A claim that I don't
Sacrifice
If
Little girls
That's exactly right
Has been proven
Even like
Come on man
It's very weird
The least strange reaction to fit like that
Absolutely right Alex
Proven right
Voice
No idea what he's talking about about the Rolling Stones
It's very hard because I kind of think you can
Conflating toothache
The first thing is likely the killing of eighteen-year-old Meredith Hunter at the Rolling Stones concert Altamont
That was young black man who died in the proximity of the band I think Alex is taking that
These compliant combining it with another element
Which is the death of Rolling Stones founding member Brian Jones back in night
Jones was found dead in his pool and the circumstances surrounding the death have been the stuff of
Conspiracy theory and conjecture ever
Occam's razor tells us that he was a
Completely insane drug addict Rockstar in the late sixties
Please who was on a path of increasingly self-destructive
And him getting f***** up and drowning in his pool accidentally isn't that surprising as a possibility
Who else was doing anything like that
Literally everyone
Out of control
38 other examples of people who died at 33
Is 27
You have the fact also in this case that's a confession that they drowned
And all sorts of other side. About the ritual
Computer
Keith Richards and Mick Jagger fly around all over the place
All this fascinating stuff but ultimately it's not a story I can really just
Contango for you
Combining with Altamont turn it into a story about The Rolling Stones killing a black child at their house
There's something about the globalist
LOL so he doesn't put it that way
He says
If you almost blame-the-victim again like
They're just too appealing to the globalist at
Yikes
Yeah there's
That's that's a weird
Yeah
Exclude possibility that there is some like urban legend story about The Rolling Stones that I
Can't find but it makes too much sense
From two different stories
Because that Brian Jones story is very
Big in conspiracy theory world's ultimate aware they career
And Alex has a really big on.
South
So many death bed
There's no real
I really think that you shouldn't
Call me for like
Confusion 9/11 last words
Deals economy is going to come in
Finish you off if you do that
So
My Confession has robots
Going to take over there going to kill everyone off
Ron
Until
Billions
Worship the robots on the Bible
And it's all going to fall it 1 hour
It's like a computer was
In an hour
Irregular on every TV
Almost killed him is going to happen in our generation it will happen
How's work
People throw to like a weather of weatherman
Local news just like
In the news today
We are going to
All right damn over to you with whether it's even more brusca
So f***** up
So we have to add to that
Fun dealing with global
Wedgie
For him to prove
So much more interesting
The one I grew
Yeah
Obsolete
Nbcnews
Is to kill you
They're already killing your fertility
That's exactly right
Literally got comes in a booster
You're absolutely
Movie right
Cody it's pretty sad
Has a demonstrable effect on your IQ
You become a Christian your IQ goes up
It's time
And I know that I know that I know
I would love to see Alex
Back this up
You can't
He's just talking s***
But this is it
Shades of
Pretty white nationalist weights
Supremacist ask Uncle of
Christian Supremacy
He's indicating in Subway that there is a
Substantive difference between you've a minute before you become a Christian and after
From a
Accused
Sandpoint baptism
It's just like
Hey
Bam I'm a
Alex is an example of somebody who has done all of the
Stewart's
Is Christianity he believes in
He is absolutely someone who
Well and I don't
I see you're very very smart person here
Next Clippers game
He's going to talk about how he
You talked about Fantasy Island
Skylander dad
And after it's done
Tell me if you can guess my theory about why you talking about
Watch
Yahoo feed my Google feed on YouTube
I was talking
I'm going to say racist stuff
Phone
Recording
Do you know what my theory is
Something like that
Either that or he looked over to the side and sauce of a mare
The story
The weakest cover 2
F****** worried that I need a context for This Racist I was demonstrating what a racist
Howard Stern's on your phone when you're ready for there you go
Racist I was demonstrating racism
Ben huh
Discover 100%
Lyo him to make this cover story
For his racist outburst
Along with his wife while hiking
In Christ
That's what I
Alex starts freaking out a little bit about his court case
Which I understand why he would do that doesn't look great
On the waterfront
Exactly the direction eunuchs
I'm not scared
Wow
It's not
Well obviously it's not a depressant or at least it has a
Half-life
Religiousness a little bit earlier and I think that's in that conversation
Only afraid of God
3 second pause
And then you two can fight for
So at this point Tom pepper
Is out of the mix
Alex
Android Studio
Becomes
Incredibly disgraceful
Punching homeless
People section
It just becomes them like yelling about homeless people pooping on the
Turnabout
It's not worth talking about for the most part
Except a couple of really weird things out
And here's the first one has like he has a theory about why
People
Allow homeless people to exist
And then the city council decided to Amanda city ordinance in July
Saying it's not legal to camp out on the city sidewalk
Sleep on it
Anything you want to do it's all good
The restaurant there's eight people
This is going on but it seemingly happen
Overnight
In fact
This is a little demon
He's not kidding
That's important clarification
I'm not f****** around
Lower servant demons which you heard that and what the f*** is he talking about
I am dead serious about low-level demons being needed in order to bring
Level demon
Yikes
You know what you know what am I cute
Don't
Especially in the Butte late abusive ways that are so reductive in like blaming people
Experience
Homelessness
There've been a lot of
Studies that have
Roundabout
Systemically
That a lot of people
The situation Theory
Absolutely disgraceful and awful
To have people
I take
But take such a Target
Vulnerable population
And I think that's why they do it
And Owen does
Cool bro Ali
F******
How do you not look at that and go
This is clearly a
Structural
F*** off
Defense
Is also coming from place
The homeless have wronged
I believe this story that he tells
To be not true
I don't know that it's true
Something racist to a homeless person in the forest
It would be literally impossible for me to get to the bottom of this
But I've never written bring this up before
And it doesn't sound
Manteca came home late
$10 bill
Telluride
Cousin
I don't know about this story
It would actually be a national news story
National news
Thousand-dollar a year software developer in Seattle
Yeah absolutely it would leave
I can't find anything about it
Google various
Terms
I don't know I can't I can't figure this out
Literal zombie story with litter of course it would be national news every every meeting organization be like
Like that
A couple years later
Personal greed
Think it's not true but he is very creative
I'll give him that
He's big thing that he's pushing for towards the end of the sepa
Episode is
Look
Do you know the globalist downtown
So why don't we
To the city council members house
Now this is all good and well to sort of joke about
But what Alex described
A targeted harassed
My campaign right now
Conceptualizes this
And the fact
If he will say I'm going to pay homeless people to go to their houses in trouble
Pursues this playing
It's really disgusting the Earth
But it's also like that is legally if
I think
I think that might be illegal
Ideas
About to
Members car
No wonder you get pepper.
Down there because he's going to be like
Guessing help
Infowars
Really willing to be
We talked into it
Especially like paying
People to go harass folks
Shadier territory
I've never said this before because generally speaking
It's the worst thing that could
B Owen Shroyer definitely
Should have made a joke
Generally speaking when he jokes
It's the worst thing I've ever heard in my
My entire life to deflect this a little
So I skipped Sunday cuz I've noticed that episodes are a real
My time lately he's not even
It's just like
It's not even worth it even when he shows up he's barely there you know almost no one's listening to a show on
Sunday
Fighting lower service
Exactly
And by this point the news has broken that there was a
Potential meeting between Trump and Taliban leaders
Cancel the about that
Alex does not care about that meeting at all
The president end
Taliban leaders
I don't know
Should be you know I don't
I expected him to have a position
Because I think it's overwhelmed by the fact that John Bolton
So Alex
That is boring
To that
Search on this whole
The Taliban invited to camp
Where is this
Just why
Serious issues president
The president
I'd like to take you back
Do the day that John Bolton was named National Security
Point
We got Rodger Stone popping in
Take
On Donald Trump's New National Security advisor
Mister
A lot of people really don't like
Including myself
Because he still pushes the failed Iraq war and other things like that
The word is on Bolton
Connections
Interstate Department in the UN in the Pentagon
And that he will be
Cool
Munchkin
His words
Policies that the president wants carried out
Whoops
That's specifically the opposite of now
Episode
Absolutely
A hundred percent
Rodger Stones friends with
National Security advisor
Whiskey
30 years
He said Bolton isn't
Trump supporters will not leak
Beach
In the present day by John Bolton
Will trump brought him in today
Ministration
Allocate brought up and denied
He's like he's going to work for
Useful to leave an idiot is going to be
Exactly
Rodger Stone tricked Alex
Anza Alexander tricked his audience
Go to being okay with it now Alex
Who sang the opposite
Yeah is that you know the other really naive gullible audience
Rodger Stone exploited them through Alex
What's great about this narrative life is that now Alex gets to pretend to John Bolton for all sorts of things
The trumps done
Not really working out North Korea
Because Bolt
Frottage
It's a very boring game this
Become very routine at this point
Whatever Trump
Cast someone out
Other White House
Becomes like what was the problem
And so we get to see that all over again Alex gets to pretend
Interpretation of things
Negative things about
But he also
Overcame those bad things because of Rodger
So now he gets to pretend
Try and make it okay
The bullnose be nominated
70s cake
We learn next Trump has a temper
Which is not something that I want to talk about all that
That much
Trump is screaming
Vegetable
Aw
Composing
Mr. volcano
Peter super-slick
Nice
It is you can or he starts screaming people and telling them
Confident
That's what
Alpha male characteristics
Odyssey Fun
Really is trying
That's exactly the way you described like Hillary Clinton surprise eggs
If I don't understand
To me but he can go and like
3 years
He's been screaming about Hillary Clinton yells at people behind the scene
Like it's crazy I mean
Trump
A man
And Hillary
Is not
Christian Supremacy
If Alex knows that
Seems like you really believe
Is that story that
In her Memoir to
Maybe
It sure sounds like it fits with his
Very smooth are you screaming at you
To be around
Terrible person enter f****** rapist
So in the next clip
Alex talks about
The
Queen story time
Issues
Yeah
Something a little bit
Worth pointing out
Who talked about it
He's covered it a bunch
But I do think there's a
Slightly excited
It's important
The Wichita Kansas eagle
Is the question
Running the Houston when we're both convicted child
One register
So
Look here's the
The story that Alex is talking about is naturally being presented Wichita
Honestly
I think what he's doing kind of is close to Southern could be legally action
Story involves a possibility of specifically running background checks
After sex offense
Only on participants in the
Queen Story Hour
Now this obviously is an issue for a number free
The first is that any
Real background check that would be doing would turn up sex with
So this is kind of redundant targeted framing of the issue
By publicizing.
Specifically running background checks for sex offenders
Sentence for participants
The outcome is the people couple the idea of drag queens
The lgbtq community has beat related to sex
We have to investigate specifically
Stripes
Quickly
Geared towards committing
Is she Brave
It's my understanding from looking into there's a bunch that's Alex won't stop talking about it that most Library systems do routine back
And probably inappropriate things to do regardless of who the person is running the event
Absolute the drag queen Story Hour or a second amendment reading shooting at as long as
Selectively enforced
And used as a means of marginalization
It feels like it's the library's right
It doesn't feel like that is what the policy is about
However
This does feel like it's selective and then to target the LG
Community as evidenced by released Library minutes from a meeting
Reflecting that this proposal was brought to the table by a note Adele anti-lgbt
Thank you Pastor.
Creek Coffee
He seems to be interested in the targeting and marginalization side of this possible policy
Explode from Craig
I would like to
Target and marginalized
These certain types
How do we go
From the minutes
Quote your actions constitute child abuse
Drag queens are part of the adult entertainment
Children are much too young to be exposed to the lgbtq agenda
And their brand of immoral and unhealthy sexual
Children model with AC
Can hear perverse activities such as this used to be found only in back alleys deep or houses in dark closet
To the public in daylight
He goes on to say quote
What are the stated goals of the lgbtq
Teq agenda is to browbeat and indoctrinate the public while gaining access to our children through government schools the main
Mainstream media public libraries politics
And public policy
And any other means to promote their perversity
It is irresponsible behavior is like this to contribute to the hate and division we now see in the nation
We are indeed in a culture War
I was make
But it turns out that I should have gone
A lot further
This is not a man who's concerned with whether or not the drag queens
Stories are sex offenders are not
He wants them to be gone from
Society or at least dark closets
Either gets there exist
Particularly in public and their inclusion in a large
Society monster created
That's the motivation behind a campaign like the one he's engaged
Bunch of s*** about sex offender background check
You succeeded
Associated the story our participants as being sexy
This is really shady s*** particularly when the motivation
It's so clearly just to make members of the LGB
EQ Community not feel welcome
And be as a part of society
Coffee runs a church called the Refiner's Family Church
Derby can
Which is 12 miles outside of Witcher
Yeah
The town of over 22,000 people and has a library large enough that it
Mentioned it
Today's Wikipedia page about the time he likes that Wichita Library
Freezer is making what a library and a sidhe Dozen
Live in his business
Culture War to drive 12 miles
I don't visit
His church doesn't have its own building
They made the room they rent in the derby golf and country club which I will say from everything I can find
Polarizing golf club is
Even more literally money changers in the f******
There's a church find
They are
Another one
It strikes me as
Coffee guy talks about Allah
You know what you got is this guy who has a clear anti-lgbt
Did you stamp
Against
Put Sports this motion
In the library
From there the right-wing is more than capable to take the ball and run with it
If you read or coffee it's
Suggested to the library board agenda
Yep so it makes sense if you're on that board
Not want to go along with everything you say
It's a board is at all resistant to his message in his demand
It's so easy for the blogs and s******* websites to frame the situation is something like quote
Kansas library board divided on whether to let sex
Offenders presented
The children
Which way does a real hippo from lifesitenews
F*** yourself right
Goddamnit ultimately the reality is it this week Bible reading or second book shooting at
None of these people would even suspect or be concerned about the possibility that one of the presenters by be a sex offender
Their only concern because of their pre-existing bigotry towards the lgbtq community
Perhaps the ultimate irony is that all of these
People
Run background checks on people which
I've heard call trt1
These people so much
Because this is the
The same group of people who were like
Christian
Specifically targeted and harassed
Kill us all at the same time I would like everybody here this minority
And treat them like the awful people that they are
And so on and so forth
F*** you
Don't even don't even talk just great
You don't mean any
Confusing and knock
Yeah so we've got over this but the case in Houston that everyone relies on
To be like a sex offender
Here's a situation where background checks are already required for all people who hold events at the library
But the library didn't follow their own procedures
The only real angle of outrage that you should have is be upset that the library didn't do their job
And in this case again the publicity
Cities surrounding the event was not led by people who are concerned with whether or not these people are sex offender
He was led by a group called massresistance
Aggressively anti-lgbt
Group as a whole
And their goal wasn't to make sure that the library is a safe place
For children it's to marginalize
Community
The fact that these events have been going on all over the country for a while now
This Houston situation is really the only one these people ever
Application for the contestant there tons of pedophiles in a drag queen story hours
It is
Believe that they're wrong
You have aggressively interested parties
Black Mass resist
The tons of anti-lgbtq organization
Pouring over criminal databases
And sending out for your request
So you definitely way more stories
I found
The issue for Alex
Legal aid
Is he speaking into
Specifics that don't really match reality
He said that the two offenders in Houston where leaders of that
Because he wants to create the perception that they were running the show is it means of grooming children
Neither was a leader of the honestly I think that this could easily be construed as defamation of the action
Leaders of the group
The leaders and organizers of the Houston chapter art
And Devin will
And neither of them are sex offender
And in fact they've discussed the revelations of people who'd volunteer for their event
Hey concealed their past Act
Atkins from
Candidly
It was devastating
For them know about these conviction
And they followed the library policies
And the library where the 12
Who failed up the old they're at their end of the bargain
One important point is it when the story is covered right-wing sites don't just use pictures of the
Who were sex
Course not they used
There ever was well not necessarily
They don't breathe
But the point is they don't really
Care whether or not they're using the pic
Picture of the right person
And this is called
From an article in the houstonian mag
Asean by one of the Houston chapters Founders quotes
The most upsetting outcome is the hate BlackBerry
That's one of the drag
Because of
The controversy
She's become a canvas onto which these right-wing pundit
Projector hatred and fear
African-American with a beard
Facebook makeup
Breitbart.com Miss identified her as the direct
Sex offender in question
It isn't her
Her fault she has a clean record and is one of those prolific drag performers
In the city she's done nothing wrong
How could she have known when we invited her to read a story to a handful of children
National score
How could any of us
These are delicate issues
Being intentionally packaged as anti-lgbtq propaganda by people like out
It's disgraceful
Is bigoted and probably worst of all
It doesn't do
Anything to solve the issues that they're pretending to be
We concerned about
They don't care about appropriate background check
Even if every drag queen or King
Was thoroughly vetted
Perfectly they find some other Association and accusation to Labadee
Because it's not about background check
It's about their unwillingness to accept certain types of people being allowed to exist
Society
Give everyone background check
As long as it's universally applied
I don't see a problem
Absolutely absolutely
But also let's not forget to be very clear that people like Alex and all these people
Should go straight up f*** themselves
Further duplicitous actions
Care what you have to say
Even if it's
Applicable
If you're making a bad
Right I don't f***
And this is not entirely
Absolute
It's it's
It's crazy
The minutes for that are
So reveal
So revealing
Because here's here's what you say
If your
If you're doing this just say
I think we should have
Checks for people who
Read here
And then you get away there's no reason to rant about the lgbtq agenda
Is that strengthens your argument
Cuz it Doesn't
If you walked in there and said I think we should have
Text or everybody
I think that's a good idea
You still have to sort of understand that the only reason the conversation is even happening
Coming from this
Guy is because of his pre-existing
Feelings
Like I said most of the libraries that I've looked into that are related to any of these stories
Already have
This rule in place
If there isn't
The library that does
Absolutely fish be conversation
It should be
It's kind of gross that
The conversations being spurred by this
But I think it's probably a very small number
Library
But don't already have
Dishonest framing
Remove alarm
If it's next to a clip Alex
And you lied
Quite a bit
This critical
Report that I have
There's going to be a forced blood test
On certain people in America
Wall Street Journal
Getting in Plainview
Telling you what they're really saying article
That's hilarious
Meeting I can lie about whatever is in this article
Remember when I
Read you the article and it says the opposite of what I said.
Isaiah
I meant to say right
So
Think about a lot
My specialty is being
Particularly convincing nonsensical disconnected
So this is legitimately bulshit
What else is lying about is a new article discussing breakthroughs regarding post-traumatic
What are the difficulties with PTSD diagnosis of
Comes along
With the condition
Often patients are unwilling or resistant to
To disclose their symptoms
Fear being labeled crazy
Which really only makes
Things worse
A group of researchers set out to see if there were any indicators that they could find that would prove as an effective
Screen for physical markers are people suffering
BTS
Other findings were recently written up in the latest issue of molecular psychiatry
27 chemicals
Signatures which heart rate reading
We're bound to have an accuracy of 81%
Distinguishing weather person
Had a pre-existing diagnosis of
BTSD
They have a group
The diagnose PTSD
An asshat
Test an 81% accuracy
Distinguishing between
It's very interest
Variance
It's very clear however that the results aren't diagnostic
Someone for How likely they are to
PTSD
Which is to say that just testing positive with their set doesn't qualify as indicative of a diagnosis
Just a sign
Maybe something
They're pretty big limitation
Their study and they're clear about it like it's not a knock on the study at all it's just
Limitations of
To do
6 people
They were all male combat veteran
Chemical markers would be applicable to
People in other population
But that's something that merits further study
It'll need to be upon more studies
Before this will ever be used in a clinical
Exciting I really
Wants
The media
Unless
Do you know what I mean because this particular
Unless they have
We've proven that we can do
Tomorrow at every hop
But every other stories always
Bulshit up about
Mega potion
Or stories about this progress
Quite frankly they're covering it up
Nelly
So
Hear something like this
His first thought is Tessa going to
Used 9471
To take so they can get my gun
People who suffer from PTSD you're living in a certain
Kind of hell
Anything that can be done to get them to treat
They need to be able to live again
There's something very positive
Subject
Awesome care about alleviating the suffering of people who
Something awful
He doesn't give a f***
Because his overarching paranoia doesn't allow him
Nose monstrous
Nothing
More to say about that other than
So
Gets into
The media lies about
ShopRite
Okay well that
Yeah
Resort course in Scotland
Forsyth Audible
Spit on it
Indeed
A little bit
It's only place conservative
I can definitely understand
Just like this story about Trump Scotland Hotel
The Trump Turnberry
Resort
If you do
He's become
The issue with Trump's hotel goes like this
There was a refueling stop that could be made at the Prestwick airport which no one is claiming
Trombone
However he does have a hotel nearby it is military government Personnel or more frequently stopping at that specific
Without her other good reason
It does tend to indicate
It's something corrupt
As the president
Free
Room and board at his hotel
Not necessarily
In 2015 military stopped at this airport for refueling 95t
So far this year they've stopped their 259 time
An increased doesn't
Seem to be related to an uptick in travel that would explain the rise
Making matters more concerning
In 2015 there were only 40 overnight stays for personnel
At that location
Not the hotel like that to airport
Is that number jump
When Trump was elected
And this year there have been 200
20 overnight stays log
Which is an over 500%
Increase in overnight stays at the airport happens to be near one of Trump's proper
But it's not like dropping a business arranged
Maybe Prestwick airport cuz that would be crazy
That Donald Trump does indeed have a business arrangement with Prestwick Airport
The guardian among other news outlets
Have reported the trumpet Prestwick entered into a ranch and arranged
We're Trump's Resort offer cut-price lodging for
People flying into the airport and Trump
Both the airport and resort we're losing money previous
What do you know now they're not
This is a case where it doesn't even really matter if Trump knows what's going on or is directing the increase traffic
Victor Prestwick
It legitimately doesn't matter
Because the appearance of impropriety is strong enough that this needs to stop
The president has a pre-existing arrangement to help increase traffic to this airport and now that he's present at the military stopping their weight
Whether this is the result of
Coordinated corrupt
Activity or not it does not matter
This is the consequence of having someone in office
Who has resorts
Conflict of interest
Its exact reason why the emoluments clause
Exist
Jimmy Carter got rid of
This is in the Constitution
Professes to love so much
He knows the Trump is profiting off being present
Whether he's directing corrupt behaviour or not
And Alex doesn't
Care
He supports
He claims the media covering a story like this is him lying of other lying about Trump
Which is such a
Through the Looking-Glass authoritarian
What a f****** loser he's become
Waterford
President to be able to profit off his
Be the president
The people who loves
Most of the people
Who have a copy of it
Is very small copy in their back
Pocket at all times
Are we
The president
And they are
It's
Covered konst
It's so insane
Despondent
In the middle of the September 10th episode
Starts talking about
How wide
Before it's all over
For his peeps
Dennis gets weird remember how much I screamed about how he should have been impeached on day one cuz he was
Alex Azar
Extreme
Is that you get to recycle
Their pits
Always been but this one's pretty f****** over
Is like it's amazing to me that if you just have an authoritarian
Blitzwinger
The Senate
You can never do anything for the authoritarian white Nash
Mr. president
You don't think that's something we should be
Be surprised by course
Of course
But it's just
It's one of those things where we should probably rewrite that Constitution
If it's
So easy to s*** on it and
Enforce people that
Maybe I don't know
But either way
Alex is keenly aware that there is a approaching where he is
He will be stock
Interesting but I also think it's really interesting where he goes from there which is
She's a little bit Petty
We're done
Numbers
Unless all conservatives get up
Farms and ranches
Take a turn
Call up there
Only thing they give their money to Walmart
Ajani Oliver East Texas
Wealthy welder
Diamond skin
All you so-called Republican
I'm going to say
Back me up on
If I'm right okay choice
Maneater might be weird there
And family
Lot like what you described only because they won't give him money
Walmart hates America cuz they won't sell certain types of obvious
My family won't give me money
Yeah so that's funny
Because makes it funnier
But I think it's something really important that we need to talk about at the beginning
Alex couldn't make it more clear that is a white nationalist unless you just started screaming
What are you talkin about the idea that Democrats are going to have the numbers
I'll get it by 2024
Tomographic anxiety crowd
Most of the fears about White's becoming a minority or framed as being about the year 2045
That's weird
Constantly make up just slightly less than 50% of the US population which of course is a
A fate worse than death
Absolutely
Continue to control every
Destroyed
Some of those traces back to work put out by the Brookings
To who made this exact prediction in a report published life
September
The 2045 date is a big talking point but if you look at the graphs of their projections
2024 is also a very important point
For people who are super invested in white identity
That's the year that the white population will have an annual growth rate of 0 per
Meaning the birth
Death rate will be equipped
This isn't essentially important
Because it's the turning point after which the white population will begin to
Which again is something that they don't see as a natural phenomenon and opens
Society as much as they see it as a prominent international plan set up by evil globalist
This rant is about nothing
Except his demographic
This is white panic
Embodied
It's scary and sad on one leg
He's so afraid of white people not being the majority in the country that he completely flips out starts screaming about his Rich relatives don't give him money
It's the embodiment of
Pathetic entitled bigotry
It's not I don't know what is
It's just it's over to me
Surviving Koch brother doing
That would be
Pathetic
Financially and emotionally and clearly
Real into
So
People off and understandably
I keep the same because
You know
It's important to know what Alex believes
Even if it's like
This is terrible
Pretty terrible
Projections onto
He's talking about the beginning of psychiatric
Conditions in psychological camp
But they acted like they were new or something
Okay
Then it gets worse
It really is a thing
It's a whole bunch of
Poison
Are they
A dimensional program
So all the psychiatric conditions and all that s*** it's real
But it's probably
Poison or demon
Or some
A man f*** was that it's pretty crazy
So his
Is based off of
Telling people who are are you there poisoned
Tell me more about genetical inbreeding
Possessed by demons
3 in the same person
Right absolutely
Problem
Avakin add new names
I guess an exorcism
Massive
Amount
Which Mike
Yeah I mean it's
Just from a mental health
I think it's really disgusting
Save this way
Considering it sounds
Somebody told him he had so
Get the Frederick
And he decided that he was actually
Poisoned
I just got to do a client
Dangerous
Least believes conditions are real
It's a sad State of Affairs that you like that is like
Brightside is B
The bar has been set
Solo
Yeah you have finally jumped over it into a further middle
Morass
Yeah
Kohl's
At this point
Because of this stupid idea
Stupid idea that we've covered in
But Alex
Put out and I kind of thought maybe
He was going to let this one
No no
What would you do if I forget about buying Iceland
It sure is nice
Alex really
Does he think that's how
He just kind of think
You can just give all of Greenland buddy
And then they give you Greenland
Not
Pretty into the idea of
Expanding
Yeah cuz he couldn't just let that one go
Is what I prefer
Learn
As I said
Conversation about how
The globalist we're really just trying
Dubai time
Cuz they do they need
Steal the 2020
And all this s***
That is this
Hot b******* that leads to like one of the craziest things
That I've heard Alex
And that's why he's accelerating action now because he realizes their whole endgame was just to buy time
Manipulate
People
Six-year-old
Public School
To go with men at parks the bathroom have sex with
If Alex Jones Is On Air
No one's going to have
Well the globalist books in public school library
Training manuals of all the things I absolutely do not need to look up to tell you is not true this is probably
On the top of that
There is no public school that is teaching a book that encourages six-year-olds to go to park bathrooms with strange man and headset
I rarely drops 100% bulshit
You know and that's one of those fun things that disproved the Infiniti
Just because it is possible doesn't mean that it's going to
No I decided to look it up anyway
Such a book exist
I think I know what's going on
There's a 2015 law in California that recently went into effect their required school education curriculum
Material related to lgbtq folks
So you know the right-wing is doubly pissed off about it
You can make whatever you are argument you want for against
Curriculum board public health information
Agree with you
You can say that you'd rather teach your child that stuff at home
Your parenting none of that matters
Because the bill is very explicitly in the fact that
After children out of the car
You don't want
Problem solved
Is it on issue
I read an article about this must be talking about domestic abuse
Sex trafficking
In a book about how you shouldn't go to the bathroom with a stranger
And arguing
Secretly as a way of trying to get children curious about a condom
Remember
Specialty
He's telling you what there
Exactly
It makes no sense but if you used to listen to Alex
Kind of how his brain works
This article has some interesting comments on it
Here's a
Non bigoted
We're not fighting lgbtq people per se but their agenda
That's obviously to create more of them by infiltrating the public school
Cool stuff
The good angle on this
Wow
So I assume is what I was talking about since that complaints about the curriculum for making the rounds a little bit in the right-wing Spears
Stanford misleading headline in
Decided to report it even more misleadingly
But here's the larger point
This is the first example you can come up with for why the world needs
To be on air
If it weren't for him no one would know this completely fake about a book telling kids
Dafuq strange man in park bathroom
How is evidence of the globalists trying to steal your children
Alex is actually making a very compelling argument for why Society
To not be on the air on the other hand
We wouldn't know about this
Again
Not true thing
Alex
Everything is really smart
No
He is
Smart
Maybe conniving
About replace John Bolton
Right we got to get a guy in there
No Alex earlier was ruminating on this point
He had no idea
YouTube weird
Sort of like kicking the can down the street by doing
See who he thinks
Podcasts
Cuz it turned out I don't actually know anything
Ask Barnes
Replace the voltage is answer is not good
For someone that has
Was realistic
Realpolitik instincts
Practical strategic advice that is
Insisted
So you want
Price Barnes
Good work
That's a sad
That's disgusting
For you want to replace that
Sebastian Gorka
Is giving you
Spain reasonable advice on
Literally any
I don't want to know
I don't want a movie recommendation
Sebastian Gorka
Go to call
Caller
Colleges brings it up on his own
He's got another
Suggestion of who needs
To replace both
If this is interesting
Because it's Spyros super out of control
Alex is really excited about this idea
Today is
I think we need is a constitutionally and very strict
Sports to clear out the bad apples that are in the various
Agencies networks that we have operating
Like the present
Understands the promise software the Pegasus malware
Operate outside
Special military
The president
Walkthrough
Squad Odd Squad
Also it's
Almost parody for someone like him to not recognize
How close is what you suggested
Also William
A f****** Seth rich
Is truther an embarrassment
Even his name would be thrown around
Ludicra
So great
Trust
Infowars
F****** Benny in there
Yeah great
What up
What a load of s***
Terrible idea
So I hear from September 10th
Is an indication of a new line of business
Miscommunication
Network is getting in
Active.com
Good job guys
The Hat game
I think it would be I wouldn't be surprised if you just straight-up sold drugs on the
How many
Frozen beef
It's just not a young Japanese stuff too but
Yeah it was largely motivated clearly by TCM
The frontman for
Gcn's involved
What's your name
Gotcha based on how things shake out
Legal marijuana
Market it makes sense for them it's like a lateral move in Minnesota
But
Yeah
R Us
So we get to September 11th and I was expecting this is just going to be 11 91
Really quickly caught a theme
That was going on
And that is the Alex
Trying
To turn
911 into is abortion
Narrative
His argument seems
To be throughout this is like 9/11 was bad
Only 3,000
So many more have died from abortions
It was very weird
Encounter
We get this first clip here and I was just talking about like seeing abortion protest
And I've seen the videos that he's talking about
I know this
These are people f******
Did this is how he acts.
Weather sincerely or not
This is how he packages that to his audio
Years ago they were about to pass
Back
This is real
Who wants children
When I get the best
Followers out there
Bingo
Chrome shade going on again
Right
Negative
So I mean this is this is a lot of leads me back today
Mike with his Facebook post that he's pretending isn't people f****** around
How much is Alex aware of the fact these people are just talking with him
To pretend he doesn't understand that he actually believe
That these people were hissing and acting
I really I really would never think
True but also a rational person with a malicious
Agenda
Take that I feel like I could use this
It's f****** fake
Here's kind of my operating Theory on
Hey that you stupid V evil conundrum we often
Ourselves in
I think it
Starts out
With him knowing
That he's creating this false
He knows
He knows it's a joke
He knows that he's creating a false
And I think eventually he whines up
Convincing himself that
That could be how I always feel like this goes
He jumps into the vat of goo
Exact
That could be from
From everything that we've
The only thing the kind of
Him both being a hot
A huckster a liar
And a lunatic
Ecobee he convinces him
I'm selfish autopilot Salat
Now
The centerpiece of Alex's abortion argument
Cities make
PS2 resistance
Is a new report that Paul Joseph Watson
And put out
This is not work I think that that is either an intent like I think that was there in
It was another attempt
To find ways
To have non-band website
Right right right news would be
I think that might be what it is
I don't know it's really tough to say but
It was happening
YouTube Paul Joseph Watson
The best actor in the world
Sincerely didn't want to be around out I don't know
I don't know what to make of it I don't really care
My point gear Jordans
Is it I would
Never talked about it Paul Joseph Watson
Report if I didn't find something about it
Because they're unlistenable
This
Is amazed
Did you hear about the new sexual
Apparently he was just
So
Sure
Is reading here I is very powerful
Special Report
It's a year old post on Reddit sardasht sex
Keyboard
Weird how you manage to find this post if you wasn't specifically looking for something
Royal decision to make 9/11 about abortion
Weird the post is a year-old it only got 18 comments and was 50% down
There's no way I would ever pop-up if you were just scrolling through Reddit
He had to be actively searching for this
Yeah that's
The reply, DePaul is reading down the thread
Does the rest of the comments could be summed up as this is messed up or I'm not sure I believe this story because people on
Reddit make stuff up all the time and this would sound very
So most people generally don't think the comments on Reddit really all that indicative
What are good ways you can kind of get a sense about someone since
Charity though
If all just watching it.
I had some journalistic reservations a credible source
Around the time they post
Did this question to Paul is reading
How about their friend
If you're on birth control and let's say 45 males come inside you vaginally around
Is my likelihood of getting
Or as far as your on birth control it doesn't matter how much
I personally have a copper IUD but I'm unsure if it's a male or
So funny
This person sounds like an idiot
And most likely a kid f******
This is further indicated by another post
Around that same time
Quote me and my four friends and fun at a home party
Now I'm a bit of a kinky girl that I did find some kinky ideas the boys had
We did end up with the idea of how much loads I can hold in my mouth and well we went for it
This is
Facile
There is no reason to be laughing at this right
We are grown adults if you read the other
Post this person is written a little experience trying to write erotica
And I come from a very strong
3 f****** ashamed of
Themselves
I bet
Really kind of
Envy
Call Josie
Solo
To do the hardest part is editing and he probably doesn't do it himself
He's a real fetish
Just not the getting tons of abortion
Squats and did some deeper research on the scholarly website
You would have found it ask me anything thread from a girl purporting to have this breed
Confederation
She explains that she's on birth control which is very common
From the people who are
Pregnancy
Little bit irresponsible
For the sexual Rush they'd get out of
And people have different reasons for enjoying the fetish too if you look at the people who talk about this
Bersama Sabattus
Submissiveness
Taboo given their life circumstances
Some men just really like how pregnant women look
It's a big old world out there
Community
This is a larger group of people who indulge in the
Miss fantasy
Most part it doesn't seem like they're hard
Anybody
Is it possible there's a
Very very small segment of the population
Finally gets abortions
No
Case specifically
That goes back to 2009 ABC news story about a woman named Irene Villar
It was a self-described abortion
Who wrote a book called impossible mother
However
Did you find her is just an abortion addict
Very unfair portrait
Villar was the granddaughter of Puerto Rican nationalist Lolita LeBron who stormed the US House of Representatives with a gun back in 90
Which put her into jail
For 25 years
LeBron I was sterilized
That's just part of the program in Puerto Rico
She was 33
Her family as a ghost
Hungover
Everyone
Reproductive
Life
Her mother would go on to
Commit suicide
Velar with 8 years old
Leaving to her I going away to boarding
School
Syracuse and emotionally abusive relationship
The 50-year old professor
Who is specifically opposed to children
Sing having them kill sexual desire
Most of the abortions that you got wear during this period where she was in a relationship
With this abusive
Right
It does appear so
Describes our abortions is a form of self-harm
If you look at the larger portrait of her life
It's very easy to see
Who's the person who suffered trauma in a very specific form that took this out
It has very little to do with a larger picture picture of abortion access
But people are serial abortion
Person I can't really find any evidence
The people who get a bunch
Abortions
Compulsively
That like the idea that this is a large community of people who do nor is there anyone from Planned Parenthood or any similar organs
Advocating
This is a straw man that Paul Joseph Watson is created out of a year old Reddit post
But he's dug up and pretended is
Specifically for the purpose of attacking women's rights to control their bodies and medical
Elizabeth
Two-player journalism because
You got it was soup if you had something better he wouldn't be using an obviously fake
Year-old Reddit post
How to make a
The different women some of them didn't want to get abortion
Impact in this weird diatribe
Stupidity of
If if that was a thing
And it was
In the way that Paul Joseph Watson
Not as a
Horrible trauma
For this woman
I don't know it I don't know even gets into that
In the park
Let's Plays he doesn't even get into that it's all just this Reddit
So
Is there anyway where that is
It's all new story a Planned Parenthood employee
Steve
Same woman every month or whatever
Of course
That would be national news that you might have bronchitis
Oh you mean
Like other people that would absolutely talk to
Some journalist
We see you Louisa every 3
Does every 6 months
I'm saying it's been going on for 30 years
I don't know I just really just Gracie
.
And also
F****** hilarious
Paul Joseph Watson
All the f****** time talk about Heather the real news
And Alex's big pageant that he's putting on for this 911 abortions
Spectacular
The centerpiece of it is Paul Joseph Watson
50 primary source of
For his argument that there is this new fetish
It's coming around
It's clearly fake s*** that's a year old on Reddit
Yeah
It didn't even do this
Second of looking into this
Doing the world
Nonsensical Post-it back I don't know I don't know if I can use this
What you do is you go looking for the store you want
And when you find anything
Piece of evidence
Stop
Looking
You found it
That's fair enough
You always know he's
Intentionality
Yes
Yeah he is he's far more like
Malevolent
Peace of this abortion
Unspectacular that Alex puts on
The new story about it
Abortion procedure
Really
Doctor
So what
Circulating in the right-wing media right now because of Jill Stanek recently spoke
In defense of the born alive
In her words
Fielder campaign to get rid of women's
She described these Comfort rooms are pregnancies has been terminated usually due to complications
Genetic conditions that would would leave the child unable to survive should have been
P*** came out technically alive but not viable
What's interesting to me is at these articles about Stannis,
This incident prompted Stanek to enter employment at Christ Hospital
Which obviously gives you the impression that you saw something horrible
Because you couldn't be around it that's not true
Christ hospital after she allegedly took pictures and areas that completely violated Payson
Privacy
And then quote misrepresented the hospital until
She was fired by the hospital in
Two years after she began making public statements about these Comfort rooms
You made recently or literally the exact same thing she said
20 years ago there isn't anything new
I probably sound a bit
Flip it but that's probably because her comments kicked off a little bit of the Illinois Department of Public Health ended up doing
Navigation
And felt there was no wrongdoing on the part of the hospital
She's someone who made a fantastic
Medical claim
20 years ago
And all these guys are looking to
Inaccurate
She was fired by the hospital on the merits then she started working for WorldNetDaily
I'm not sure this is a source that I signed to have much credibility
By Alex does of course because it works into what he wants to present
This is like 20 year olds
I wonder which doctor they
Cortisone
A story saying
Well just looked out
Is all her
Yeah that's a surprise
Scout I don't surprise
Hear that in in
In the context of talking about this article about Jill Stanek
Comment
Talked about 20 years ago
There's a real
Cruelty and brutality
To what Alex
Is expressing towards the parent
The would-be parents
Crosses a line that is
Unbelievable
This time
Oh my God
For the first photo machine
Other aboard
Did you hear that
Complete with the first photo machine
Supplies
Footprint
Rocking chair
Cuz you didn't want it
Creeping death
That's really disgusting
Alex's imagine getting photos with their babies
Fish
Yeah I wonder if he thinks their Lost Child
This decision very seriously
I'm making an emotionally difficult
Choice does legitimately think that anyone would do this s*** for fun
What part of Greece
It's morning and honoring a child you never had
There's a long history of this sort of thing cross-culturally
In a religious studies class I took in College reading a book called
Fetus
About rituals some people in Taiwan would carry out to provide food and care
The fetus ghost
In Japan it's not uncommon to hold the Mizzou cocuyo ceremony
Honor and recognize the spirits of children lost a miscarriage stillbirth and abortion
These are not historically uncommon things because people need to process emotionally resonant occasion
But even if you're making good decisions
To terminate a pregnancy
That doesn't automatically mean it's
Not going to affect you
I'm sure that's not always the case
And some people don't have emotionally Paxil experience
Terminating a pregnancy
But I find the idea that of Alex mocking the idea of people grieving
To be so f******
Disgusting
They're literally proved to everything he believes about abortion
Namely the people are always going around getting them for fun
Complete bulshit
Because he can't wrestle with that he has thumakda
And act like it's the most insane
When in reality it's his callous position that is in Spanish
This is gross
Genuinely thinks
People are
Getting
Footprint
Nonviable fetus
The same way that
You get US map
That's what he
Because of you
Gross
Grosso
Yeah
They are article
Just like really ruminates in the light
Details
And when he gets to the end of reading this article
Do you say something
Like made me
My heart flutter a lil
My day
Hollywood
Looking for myself
We're going to take this country back
Children
DuQuoin legally and lawfully
What day will die
That is so f***** up
Music Choice was not income
That was
Haunting
Right on
Yeah yeah
So
I imagine that would Alex's
Describing is a faint
Mario where
I got Trump is in power forever and they outlawed abortion
Kill everyone who works at
Yeah
Anybody who has decided to get divorced because he's repented
He repented
The people whom he wants
Will not have a
Macy's
Frazee
Unlikely
S*** right there
Is not politically being opposed to women's rights
Choose
I mean we're going to legally
Excuse you
This is
Encouraging violence towards people
Who work at abortion clinics
Who are Planned Parenthood employees
Or people who
Advocate
For Women's Health
This is
Sincerely
One of them like most dangerous
Ways he could be acting 911
What are you doing
Is commemorating
The memory
Terrorist
Who inspired him to try
Can kill others
Cause 9/11
That I got through the newest episode
To prop up his abortion argue
Just makes it clear
60 million + abortions in the United States like real one
Divide 3000
White a mini
Goddamn this guy built his career on 911
He's very flippant about 911 this is not what I expected from him on 9/11
Not that big
Happy 9/11
Strange
He gets into talking about abortion doctor
Also it's more insane
It's more insane because
You could argue that
Was
The single
It was like
Flashpoint
Led to America
Cannibalized
Over the past 20 years
You could argue that
Is going to take down the entire United
Their word hasn't already
I don't know if you could draw a straight line
But I think you could make an argument that a lot of the ripple effect
That have led to the
The state we're in now
Yeah
Abortion
Are they are they are they
Probably middle management
Plumber so Alex's video of it
But he won't play it
Do it
Abortion clinics
I thought they loved it
He don't
Do you have it but it's not convincing
You got to see it
Because what he's doing is abortion clinic still see their demon
Yeah we will execute them
At some point
He makes it even more over
You know Jesus is real
What's really bad
Abortion clinics
So what we have is a show
Calling for violence
Whether it's pretend legal and lawful violence or not
Is calling for the Deaf
Of these people who are involved literal
Yeah
He's enlisting his audience
To go to abortion clinic
He's literally saying go today and see the demons
What did he expect some of his audience to do
When they see demons
No weed
No
From history that
Abortion protest
Is always very
Call
Respect
No one
It has
I don't know
Summit abortion
Doctor in the head
No never happened nobody's bombed Arleta
An abortion clinic
Bonfire
I'm not saying that like this is going
To cause that
But it's Behavior
Is trying to get that to have
This is there is no other way
This doesn't advance
Your discourse
This doesn't Advance the point you're trying to make
This exists
To Hope
One of your listeners goes and shoots up in divorce
There's literally no other way to operate like this
This is unacceptable
Levels that I can't even really describe and this is purposeful
Not
Continue sucking juice
Johnson
Give a f*** about this
He doesn't think that this is really doesn't he doesn't
Care about it
It doesn't matter and yet on 9/11
NetSpend
Fire show
So you'll pay attention to him
Fox up
And that is
Money
Wow
It might be past that
Oh no
This is one of the
We're already pretty deep into this episode
And there was a large part of me that as I was listening to the 10th I was like
Well
That's probably an episode
I heard that Paul Joseph Watson report
I heard how disgusting you was I
Heard this
Call for his audience
Go to abortion clinics to
For themselves
I was like that's f****** like that I can't leave alone
And then this
And I was like well
Is huge
Hollywood is complete
Tonight the dishes, the time to go ahead and just be
And it's really hard to
A lot of
Different ways
I can basically
To describe it
Talk about the future of Infowars
So I heard that
I have a lot of work
I have conflicting feelings about it at all
A feeling of sincerity
Be a difficulty talking about
Are you struggling with words
It feels like whether or not he's exaggerating something definitely something behind
Some existential fear that he has about like
Can't really do any
So when he comes back he doesn't he's not bluffing
Do you make some very specific
Frame
But might be sincere might not
I don't know
Free for March
Finish Line
Selling product
Filipino money
For just merchants
24-hour security up here
You're the one who chose to hire Blackwater
I don't know what to think about
Conflicted because it is definitely an
With a trans
Constantly talks about wanting to quit wanted to be a farmer s*** like that
Checked out
His legal fees
Gotta be exorbitant
Like there's no way
Keep up with
Like just all of the expensive
Stop
Toby heard
I don't know it was a couple weeks ago maybe he's talking about having to have a decision about whether or not to order more product
And this time
Specifically
It does sound like that
I don't know I don't know if he's being clear enough
Really to say like
What you saying is there are not ordering any more product
It sounds like he's given up
Yeah it does sound like that
55 days
Is a long
Year where you
Can order product
Any one of those
Yeah
Yeah it was literally like
After a month
His fans go
Shadonna is
You know what everybody loves this so much we're going to reorder is that
Why has a marathon diminishing returns to
I have to assume that that's part of the calculation that they say
Is like okay yes
This amount of money that you can get from selling all the stuff in the warehouse
Will get you so far but
Because you don't have the money now to reorder you have the money for either
You can do one of them
So basically
He's in a position where let's a cost
$5000000 to run the operation free gear and also cost $5 to order the product
He could spend $10 now for the product and hope that more sales will come
He's running on nothing
For the the show and
He is all that other legal
Or you could
Afford that $5000000 to run free year
At that point he has nothing left
In order to reorder supplies
That I see it is kind of being
Where
He's at
I don't know if that's accurate he could be full of s*** but
Well if I've not heard him speak this specifically
Morosely
Yeah it does it does sound
Real
That I goes back to I think
For money
He doesn't
Need it and
So
It's totally fine with
He's a narcissist
But now that he actually needs it
And he's coming from
Replaceable
That's why he
So resist
To talk about it
And and
Possibility
Pretty strong possibility
I think there's also a part of it that's like expectation building
Rosati's
Psyqui tiered probably suck
We don't want to disappear overnight
Yeah you should I have
Emotionally f***** you guys all up real bad
Comfify
Disappeared out of nowhere
Swan song where I ruined it
Tire NBA franchise for a year
And then we'll figure it
We talked more about in this just feels like you saying
Anymore
I don't want to sit here
I'm just going to tell this Thursday
I'm not going to dolphins back I'm going to a bunch of people off
I'm just going to go 170 election
On the front
Americana
Disposable
Populism worldwide
Just fizzle out
Trout year
I'm going to go out with a B
Bros
But also a year isn't going to get you
Point of order
Yeah
Wonderful
Product
Operation
Do you understand
Fuel
I'm On Target
Because we're going into Crossroads
27 years
See that's why I don't necessarily believe this it goes right to an ad
Right there
I still think he has some sort of semblance of a hope that he can pull this one off
Feel good.
I kind of sounds like he's
Is directly appealing to
Republican
Please I'm going to go all-in for Trump in the election
Trump
Please
Please give me your
News
Really mad at the people who are giving him money because he
Like on the six
Even before that
He's aware of
He knows that he's
Living in a situation where he's got to figure out something
And all of these really rich people
Give Pam lip service or whatever
Exist
The only way you're going to
Find like a billionaire donor is probably
Yeah like that's that's
I think the patron that was
Explicitly interested in a tangle of discovery
And I don't I don't think that they would pay top dollar for him
I don't I don't think I would be able to operate
Even some kind of a benefactor
He just doesn't have the utility
Anymore
It's kind of sad
It's kind of sad because I think
I think he's living in the space
It feels to me Italy
That he's like
I still got a good season in me
I still I'm relevant
And all evidence is to the contrary that like you have
You have played out your career
This is
This is it
I don't know
Tickets going on like you simultaneously giving up
Still trying to be like I need money
Which is weird
Embodied
We got in the position
We've been a self-funded media operations done
You found it
What's a billion
Over 100 million dollars you have
Think that's a bad reference
They were happy forever
I don't know I don't know what to make
To see how things play out
Cuz you such a liar
Especially around bunnies
Stop
Like this is such a perfect
For him to do in order for people to
The cover it and be like
Alex is going out of business and they don't come back better than ever
That possible
You want this to keep calling you
Sell these great products for cheap
But there is a manipulative is making it the audience's
His fault that he's going to go out
It is which could just be a ploy to get them to buy more
I don't know I've never heard him talk like that
Prettymuchit
That I'm delighted
Man I can't imagine being a new hire
Arthur's
Yeah the one who went to other
Probably gone by now if I work there
If I were working at it for that I heard Alex talking like this on Eric
Oh yeah
I was unemployed for years
Find myself
I was in Tibet
If this is
People be
End up seeing it out
Flow
Of employees
I'm cautious
Yeah I'm cautious about this
His mobile
He talked about the
I really just talked about white
It's kind of cleared
What what did you do
Unreal wow so Alex
It's just so racist
And that's it
It's very clear the West End
I got his phone turned on it started broadcasting
So that's pretty
Yeah
That
The wife is the West
Jesus
Rice
On Who is the
Right guy the man whose name could not be
Liar man
Little bit about
Complaints
About that manual
Mccrone
Just a little bit white National
A little bit little bit
Yes
Okay well there's feces everywhere and homeless people
Why the hell would they be doing that
In cities like Paris Stockholm London
And tourism is popped in other countries where things are much safer and where there aren't that many migrants
Cities like Dubrovnik Croatia Split Croatia a crocodile
These places are at
The cities are more beautiful they're cleaner they're safer
Everyone I know is
Selection bias there
Twisting macrons words
Just a little bit from what I can tell he said that Africa is the continent
Which is a little different from what
It also makes sense for French president
To say something like this because a large portion of Africa was part of what's known as lamole francophone
Or the front speaker
World
Places like Cote de voir
There's 18 other African countries were France French as the official language
Hey it's a small Point compared to
Far more
The things that Alex and Dan Lyman or saying here are not
True
According to the local out of France April 2019
History quotes
Francis just enjoyed a record year for visitor
The record without 80%
Paris draws in over 30 million tourists a year which makes sense given its large number of monuments and attractions Owen
The f****** Disneyland
The Francis variant
Climate so you can go to
You can do
Ski slope they got everything
The very appealing country to visit unless all you do is listen to Infowars
Connection France article from August 28th
Disgusting alfrancis World in tourism
There's some truth that terrorism took a little bit of a dip in 2015 in the wake of those two high-profile terrorist
Attack right but that was just a temporary setback in the tourism
For now
The Eukarya seems like different tourism numbers something around 3% this year compared to last year
But there's no reason to say that immigrants
That number is low
If you ask tourism organization to visit Britain
As they told the independent
Quote we've seen a Slowdown from Europe with our research showing
The impact of the uncertainty of brexit
Is having visitors from the EU
Storms of the
Incompetent
Sand
Pure evil of brexit has made people not want to
That doesn't sound particularly place where their tourism numbers are down in visitors from other EU countries
It's causing that
Is that accurate
I don't know but I think probably trust the director of a British tourism board on British tourism-related issues over Alex
Talkingshit
As for sweet
Stockholm I'll call you from the local quote
Tristan Sweden spent 370
Billion kronor in 2017
Enough to make it to top year for tourism of all time
But that was just a
You people owe 100 million
Nope according to macro-trends is part of an upward trend
12.89% increase
Continue that Trend with an 11.29
Anchor
In numbers
Feelings
How many immigrants are in them
Which is undeniably race
You can tell that by the examples that Dan list of cities where tourism is up
Poland doesn't example that white nationalist to use all the time
Declare yourself away
Set the destination to gets brought up by people in that
Sector about how great a country
They don't allow anybody
Croatia
2019 article in total Croatia news
Quote after several years of growth at unrealistically high rates caused by external factors the Croatian tourist season
2019 has so far seen a slight stagnation and decline
We have to prepare ourselves well for these new circumstances
Be prepared to fight for each and every guest
Said Franco Palmer the Croatian
Chamber of Commerce
It's just make abundantly clear that Dan is not having a conversation based on reality
Like maybe a friend of his recently what does that grab and had a really good time there
Because he knows the Croatia as a largely homogeneous population with relatively few not brown people
Who knows
Oh yeah
The argument these guys are trying to make an immigrant a trust
France Sweden in UK tourism
In places like Poland Croatia are on the rise because
They're further asserting that the people in charge
A reason probably because they wanted
The cross the Torah
The economy
Look at the numbers
It's easy to see the both of these arguments are based on anything other than
Namely that they hate
I don't
It's fine with her
It's not fine
It's awful
Straight up lie
Write what
Sting's the most
Because I feel like it's a microcosm of that
National
Is when
They say things
Things that are not
But
Demonstrable
The office
Could you just lie about
Like
Jordan eats
Spaghetti sauce every morning
Find you made that up
But if I ate the opposite of spaghetti sauce every morning
Yourself into a real hole or something
Before careful
The same thing is always true with with
Brexit
Like that
10 million dollars
Apple Health System
And then they do the numbers and with x
Stick it wind up losing 10 million
Just
Applying fake
Don't say the opposite we can't actually live in nice
Two are just completely absorbed within this year's
Where their perceptions about
These countries are
Completely
Molded by the
Sensational Videos
Post-dated taken out of context
And reporting for people like Paul Joseph Watson
Year-old Reddit post
Artist Community College
So they're already
That
Audience
So when you talk like this
You can lie about whatever the f*** you want
And it's better for you to
How to use your feeling
Paris
Literal
F******
Budget crisis for France
All we would read all day France burning
Like it
And I understand a lot of the numbers I was looking at were France
As opposed to Paris
But you got understand
Most of the tourism
80%
The country would be
Numbers would be down
So hard
London
Hertz.com
Make up the majority of
Travel affected
In any meaningful way
The country could not possibly be setting a record
Tourism
That's
Kind of
What's so funny
It is
Because I have to reference
And that cliche because we're actually living it
And we're living
Boring
It is a little bit
Immigrant
Commissioner for refugees report for 2015
But Alex is still being completely unfair
Majority of the refugees except
Did China from Vietnam
However that year they also let in 182 Somalian
86 Nigerian
52 Iraq
45 Liberian
On 306
52 people
From unspecified cont
These numbers are very low
That is a lie
I know Alex is really pushing hard for Trump to have an immigration policy
Top Fin
Is designed to let's say quotes
Promote economic development in National Security while maintaining social
Stability
Do you avoid
Really sounds like
Words for what you
Keep white people
What's the weather
Government
Multi-position on it
Immigration
It's really super ironic
To be more like them
When I hear him say the China doesn't like
Easy to hear him saying that
He thinks it's bad that they talk
In reality it's a baby throwing a tantrum so China can do it why can't we
That's when you say that
Exactly what he
Yeah you would you hear it
And you're a human
Cigarette lighter
We all agree
Accepting refugees
It's a good thing
That's not what I said
Other people
They don't let people in
Probably
Why can't I
So I get the bad news
Things in a forest without accidentally leaving my phone onto everybody knows how racist or not realizing someone walked up
He upgraded
Baltimore Barn checks
So does donkey
I don't give a f*** about the butt
I do have one
Because
It's a piece of information about our
You know hearing Alex giving up
Yeah
Weird
So now
He enlist Barn
To do an adverb
Recently confirmed
Between
Back between dinner and a late snack
Medicine
You are weird unaffected by a wide range of thing
Over the years
Bora
Was because of work
Weather
I only got people cuz I was on
Stimulants
Holyshit Dallas's product
That I took back when I was in college I've never found anything
For rainforest
Unbecoming as hell for a lawyer understand how he didn't have his law license revoked after reading
Various
Insane
Mercedes not reading it
This is extemporaneous
I believe
One he is good
If he's making that up off the top of his head
Late night snack
That's true
Is it okay
Actress Lola
The crimes you committed to become a lawyer and I'm not
Ripon College
I did
Speed drugs in college
And now frame forces just like it
That's a very weird way to solve it
Product
I understand that
It's almost as good as speakers
Not having
The single moment
Of clarity
That you should have had which
Turns out
I was take
That I didn't know what was
Inside of it
And it was
And I looked
Which
I don't know what to
Makes me feel exactly like those pills
That I didn't know what was inside of them
Speed it also puts into question like that pressured speech
Like amphetamines
Or some byproduct of his chemistry and brain Force together
Apparently
Tidewater
Scam lawyer
Scam lawyers there Amarillo
Yeah you know all those booty coffee shops that serve
Infowars coffee
Highest and
Copy
Used to work for like legit roasters
Distribute
Artisanal roast
Coffee
But it's ludicrous
To think that in the conversation of these coffees
Infowars wakeupamerica blend
Ridiculous
Wow what they do is
Personally goes to
South America.
Coffee beans
If ever there's an argument for like
Him not being allowed to be a lawyer
Yeah just
You're lying
Do people dab
11th episode
7:49
Please play the clip of trump being interviewed on TV
Mysteriously
Because that shows how great the
And I want to bring that part of the interview at
Play the conversation
Because it makes the mantown solace
Like
Psychopath who should be kept
Just far away from the rest of
The human race
Well I don't care about the little bit that Alex talked about 911 because
It's kind of a standard bulshit you always here to talk about
Specific of stupid
What is
Someone trying to sound like an egg
Expert but who's forgotten
All of his curriculum done
911 s*** in a long time.
He's dusting off the old man
Material in a dozen
He doesn't have the chops
Dino's produce loose change
You probably remember some of the stuff at that
Bye
It's not worth while it's really kind
The takeaway of the
This clip perfectly describes
I think he's describing it
As a wave
People look at
Is
Protection of all the other stuff
Stupid
Enough to sit
With the adults
Also shut up
None of that stuff is happening
He would start throwing food at people like you wouldn't be able to have a conversation if he was sitting at the adults table
You're at the Kids Table Alex
Right you can't possibly act the way he does
Like when he was on that BBC show and just as going infowars.com over people to act like
Publican expected anyone is going
You got to sit with us
Coliseum
A f****** Shulman cloud
You're very successful
You're very president
Sing like a f******
Very successful at the kids table and I applaud you for it
But
You're welcome off that
You know
Interesting portrait that we
I think that
Game Theory the problem is solving
They
Free market of ideas is rejected
No he would not say that the
The free market advice
Has rejected
Well he's at the kids
So he can
Well the problem is
The Kids Table in everybody added
Guns pointed at
The adult table
It's not a pleasant
We'll see what happens I'm excited for the possibility of Alex going broke
Fun
It would be nice to have
Schadenfreude
And the fact that even if Infowars goes under you could still do a podcast
Black eyed pea soup
Dynamic
Like him go to like
Are you never do this cuz he couldn't take the money
It'd be interesting to see what he would do
If like
Just like I got nothing
I'm just going to sit here with a mic
Hopefully become a farmer
Disappeared
I'll just talk about their show
Go see what happens with the present cuz
I want to see I want to see where this I'm going broke Naruto
Barnes
Deep down I can tell you a hundred percent hate listening bar
Prelate
I'm interested
Arrow 30
You can go to iTunes the best way to listen
Is goat
To your local
The one that
The one that is going to find out that
All of them will turn on
And Alex Jones will appear
And out of each of those screen shall come at hand
Holding a
Like the rain
I'm Leo I'm dzx Clark
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color