SMS
Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge but I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Monica
Aliexpress.com
About Alex Jones
Jordan
Obviously we didn't talk about it
Okay because of course
What happened last weekend Fleet Lee forgot about it
I woke up on the table
Oh that's a real thing that can happen
My favorite horror movie is there
Situation in real life where you were at
Actually like
You know like I thought I was going to die
Yeah man I got robbed at gunpoint when I worked at a gas station
Didn't think that there was any reason
But this would turn into a murder but that didn't mean I didn't still go into shock
Cars get off the road
Black ice
Those moments
Terrifying
I don't know moments in the car driving
Really bad driver
And I have never been
Situation
Chicago for a car
I moved here I haven't really explored the possibility of
Getting my driver's
Distractible
I'm not I'm not good at defensive driving
Not exciting
Forgot to close call
Freeway Ford
Missouri
Carson City
Small town in Missouri for fun or something
Terrified
Merging onto
Incoming traffic on the highway I'm dead
Corset never did but
That would make
Subway
Bike take Access Road
I'll just to avoid merging absolutely
Expound more on this than getting robbed at gunpoint
Discussed on the show and enjoy
How many episode
Story
I only have a few
Question
Right
So I can
Struggling
Glad you didn't ask about scary movies
Because I hate
And
A little bit about 1
I know the last episode
The present and find out what's going on with Alex
Watch him as whatever his story is goes the direct
It's going
Continue his Crusade against abortion
Listen to it again
For our show
And then he did his debate night coverage of the democratic debate
Just stupid
F****** dumb as s***
What is I don't know
I think
I'm still sticking with Avatar Aang
The only thing that I thought was really in
Interesting at all is being brought on and it's really
Disgust
Quite a bit Howie's
The political gambler
And it really seems like he's
He's trying to hand
Handicap the field so the audience can bet on the election
Very weird
Infowars to Their audience like political analysis
Blind bat
Amazon the show
Expert in political
Tell you which democratic
Primary candidates of baton
That's hilarious you can only do it outside of the United States
There are places that like pennies audio
It's not gambling
Predictive
Cavity
Me for basically like you could wait 50 Cent
You better go.
Very weird
But I was a makeup
Episode
Over
April 3rd through April 8th
Man I have a
Point where it's becoming harder and harder for me
To deny certain
Things about Alex Jones
And one of them is
I think we were dumb
To ever consider him
Shopping
I think it we were foolish
That we ever thought that stupid was a possibility
Consider the possibility
That the appearance of stupidity is cover for the
Okay crazy thing
Just say with no
Real definitive evidence totally surprised
If Alex's whole like
Being dumb
Is an act
At this point
Trends that are happening
Is that are like
Wood
This wouldn't happen by accident
Look weird
Take a moment
People
Spartacus show
So first of all thank you so much
Text Brad
From Real World Road Rules challenge
I hope so he lives in the Chicagoland area
Chanel policy walk
Halle
Thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
David clayton-thomas
Lead singer of Blood Sweat and
Oh yeah
Fictional character
Next
Next thank you so much
I'm finally
What's wrong with a special
I feel like I have to let them
Special name
By the time
Would get to their shout-out this might be completely
Acronym stick name
Okay
This person donated on elevated we appreciate it very much
So bored as bad as Donald why the f*** is the UK being affected by memes
Heroin
So good
Freakishly large
Boris is just as bad as Donald why the f*** is the UK being affected by memes
You may not be long for office you never know
We don't have the time comes
A terrible president
If you're up there listening
You can support our work and the
Continued existence
Send.
To the fair
In the form that it exists
We would appreciate it
How much longer
Everybody will we will all be meme
Forget that become Incorporated
It's never going to happen
April 3rd through 8th I just want to play
Beside this time
To the present day episodes in
September
From my one of these
Drake
Is celebrated
PewDiePie taking back his $50,000 donation to The
Anti-Defamation League
You don't have
To go that far
You're f****** crazy like
Seriously
Go back twenty years until somebody that someday a sentence like that will exist and they will punch you in
The guy who makes
Yeah billions of deaths
So Alex is telling of the story is that
The ADL
Right
Some Fruity Pie made this offer of this donation
And then the 80s
Cuz I'm mad at him
Brookhaven
22 Jewish
Realized
In fact
Text Alex has been on a reality is closer to
Got a lot of bad tweets from racist
Year on April 3rd and it's
Like
During these times when I'm listening
To Alex's show
Keep socks and there's a lot of stuff throughout a lot of it
But then there's other times
When I'm like oh boy
Here we go
I like
This beginning
It doesn't last long but I really like
Education
And I heard last week
Eyebrow razor
I was just talking to a senior Secret Service Personnel today
Amazing
Yesterday afternoon
Coming up
And
Features
My fingers for about 20 minutes
What
Guess what
And
Is my favorite kind of
I want Alex to live there
Look there's people and they're putting out this video about houses
Okay
You guys know that
Guy who spoke out the globalist
I love it
That's pretty good
Yeah that's pretty good
I'm not going to I'm not going to take that and end
I don't have time
Bulshit
Right
I looked at it and I was like a dog
I'm going to need it
Talk about their bowls
But
It's not your b*******
This is because
Big
I feel like I could pick you back in a little bit
Haunted
A crucial element of the story
This was a video of a secret service agent to be a reptilian
But that was
The central focus of a lot of the framing
When the videos were posted on YouTube
Here's a description
Went along with the video
A shape-shifter alien humanoid working for the powers that be taught in high-definition video
Zionist cabal
President Obama during a speech he gave to a pack for the American Israel public affairs committee
Conspiracy it was at The Reptilian shapeshifter was highly important
Zog Affair government
With that part of it
Is why a lot of these internet dub dubs were interested in the first place
The the
A package Interstellar involvement
What are the reasons that Alex
Is that like
Forced his hand on
But because Glenn Beck
Offense
Opportunity
Lot of f****** time yelling about
Episode
That's a complaint
Kinda funny
It's not about the aliens that's about the Alex's narratives about the billions of bullets
I don't want to hear that because we were just talking about
But that's what the pronoun reference
Who is George Soros
So he takes issue with putting such a sharp focus on that George Soros
You just can't
Entire body
Act one bag calling
Small part of it
Because once you start looking at all directions you find out this guy doesn't believe
1 Police
That's one of the most important
Of doing the show
Separating the real from the facade
Intrinsic
And there are very few things
Volume
Is kind of a good
Wait for me
Read that sentence
Masculinity
Apollo his version of masculinity
Glenn Beck
Is it
Alex
Says the guy who starts
I did get plenty of men who like real
But leaving that aside this is so ridiculous
A laundry list of right-wing
Yours to call each other
You trollop you trollops
The challenge
My friend
Like this is not the only
Glenn Beck light in the loafers
Doesn't like eat beets or two
Throughout this episode but I think that's a pretty good
Example of it
Joey also is convinced going back is just afraid cuz I would
Just went on
Yeah like everybody
Glenn Beck is f******
He makes another claim here in the
It is also
Incongruous with his bowels
Does presentation
Because I
I just don't even know what to say
Biggest frog
I like
Alex's version of Glenn Beck
I'm not sure if it's accurate portrait
Hey keeps calling me a fascist
Alex has been bought off by Peter 2
I thought it was
Campaigning
Computer tail was
Just a few years back Alex is a beast
He should remember the things he thinks
Opposite
Liberty Movement
Who else what else
Conclusion
It's weird he's really really mad
Glenn Beck a spends an inordinate amount of time
Episode
I just want you to like me
So we're starting up the
Where can I get into a little
And then we're going to
Come together I'm going to
Bravo
Yeah I will call it it does kind of feel like the possibility of a fight
And then coming to Daytona
It works for everybody to price out of it
With architect
Say horrible things about each other
Okay if David Summit
Big developments
Vagina coming up later
He insinuates himself into the show and one of the most amazing ways I've ever heard
Alright I'm so excited to tell you all about it
Before we get to that
Alex has to make
Oh really weird
For years and years one of the most consistent
Just like me
Then telling his audience
That's at the globalist
Homeland Security all of them have decided that white people are terrorists
Yeah right
So against that
You make
Stunning claim
Wheelman head screwed on straight
That is not good
Because sometimes
They are
You know it's either that or
Coming out as pro-terrorist
I think he is
Right right
The Weeknd
Maybe he just really actually loves he's covering for the 9/11
He's actually disappointed cuz they weren't real terrorists
Terrorist
Are real men
Patriots
FleetPride
Like revolutionaries in Central and South America
Like
Any communist
That would be labeled a terrorist
Yeah okay I guess he likes assert
Okay
Sort of a couple a couple of
Narrative
News stories
That he's throwing out on
Episode that
I think our
Search clearing
Indications of Hattiesburg
I can't stress enough like how this
Is a
Print of
How is processor
This is work it's pretty impressive
Cops and prosecutors
So what's going on here he doesn't explain the story at all there were likes
Some murderers
So District
I guess
Maybe he covered this on like the Nightly News or something he hasn't brought it up on the actual show yeah
I guess he's relying on his audience
Be aware of the story is very strange
But
The story he's talking about the actual news story about
Security is out of the local Dallas Outlet
Discussing Vista idea of whether or not
Areas where they have to go from the building to parking at unprotected area
Murders in the
The area of gesture
Officials
I'm still on the Run
We should not
Target
Yeah so 3 like I said
Because in early 2013
There were string of murders
In Kaufman County Texas
And two of the victims
Chief assistant just
Search attorney and the criminal District
Attorney in the county
And the third victim was the latter's wife
It was its cleared there was targeting
The pattern
There was some conversations in the media that the culprits were members of the Aryan Brotherhood
And there were some reasons to suspect that was a possibility
4134 members of the Aryan Brotherhood had just been indicted I believe was
Houston right around the
The chapter in the area is described as
The splc
Most important
The beginning of the burden
Murder spree
The Texas Department of Public Safety released a warning that the Aryan Brotherhood hit made
Threats of retaliation that the department found credible
There's plenty of reason
To think that these guys were definitely
Considering the possible
Does the Kaufman County
Attorney's office also was involved
There's a bunch of organization
In the case that ended up getting these 34 members
Indicted
But like they were one of them
Yeah so it makes sense if there
Threatening retaliation
We are one of the groups that was involved in that
People have been murdered and heard it's it
They're suspicious
It makes noise
Who murdered those guys
Was it those guys who
He said they wanted to murder guys like that
Could be those guys
It's worth considering
Fears that his gut instinct
Based on zero information is to defend
Supremacist group and say it's more likely it was Mex
Cartel gang
Yeah he literally has no reason to say
You have one violent white organization wants violent Mexican organization
High-profile Boston it threatened
Retaliate
Lead him to do
That's what he does
But if you were a media figure and
You said I think this is why
You would have reason to say that based on information
Ultimately you be wrong
As a reason for suspicion
No reason for that suspicion
Jeff Pickett
I can't prove anything yet
It suggests that our main suspects
Is it going to be the
Aryan Brotherhood
Waterford
I think you might not be into Japanese people
The Aryans nor the cartel
The guilty party was Eric Lyle Williams
And his wife Kim
Eric was a former attorney and Justice of the Peace
You said Kaufman County but even caught on camera stealing $600 worth of
Computers which ultimately led to him being
Convicted by the justice system in golf
County
According to his wife he immediately came home and began plotting his revenge
Kim says that Eric kept her high on morphine through the. While he was plotting the murders so she didn't really experience the
Clearly
And now that she's a
Prison
She's seriously regrets.
But you didn't do anything
Stop him
The crime though it wasn't the Aryan Brotherhood the police had very good reasons
Respect them as they're being involved
Though it wasn't the Mexican cartel
Alex had absolutely
This isn't
Incredible display of his races
And I think it's a really good example how that stuff penetrates so much of his coverage
This is a seemingly innocuous unrelated story
His gut
Is to deflect criticism of the white supremacist gang
Even though you know what history of murdering police
It didn't the abstract
I give it a 20
I don't know what that mean
Get somebody on here
Scott abetting
Situation
White supremacist
What you have is a pretty clear-cut
Example of a place where he is
For the perception
That area Nations Aryan Brotherhood were involved
And pointing the finger
A Mexican cartel
A notary
But I kind of.
But it's a bad
Mexican Mafia
What do you mean
56 different versions of the
Oh boy
I've got the Ninja
No
Probably
Some got killed
Prosecutor
Okay
District
Right
His Joseph
For assume
With no evidence
Dad was a cartel
People
Enable other state
Right
Haha
Chicken cartel
Previously
I hate I hate to put it this way
But you perfectly understand that's not know that is exactly what it is
The story Alex's is referencing to strengthen his assertion that the Kaufman County killings are Mexican gang
I'm is about the chief Deputy district attorney out of Colorado with Heather Stein
Who along with her husband killed an intruder who is breaking
Scuffle
They all hit him
Pretty spectacular
Wow about to have no connection
To the couple
He tested positive for
Cartoon
You tested positive for meth Oxycontin morphine and his autopsy
I cut quite a cocktail
I wouldn't even know where to
Begin
No one suspected the Aryan Brotherhood because the circumstances that lighted
Suspicion
To this case
No threat
To kill legal employees really know
Joshua Stevens
Assume that Alex is wrong on this one
Hey guess what is David been released by April 2nd
The day before this episode recorded
So Alex has every reason to know that against Mexican cartel gang
Got it
So good
This stupidity is cover
For the evilness that he's actually
The actual case is really weird and I'm not sure anyone knows what happened
It could have been an attempted burglary but it also could have been a horrible misunderstanding was fueled by the
These drugs I was on
The stockings home is actually a converted Hotel
So there's a decent chance that when Steven thought it was a place you could rent a room
From there because he was so f***** up on these
These drugs the situation escalated in a fight broke
The DA's report does reflect circumstances that are not
Really what you'd expect your son was trying to break
Question definitely link
Doesn't look like
Breaking entering
But also because he was so f***** up
It could be a really weird
He could have looked up
He could get
Very very well
Yeah with that number
Variety
Severity of dragon
If
Nobody is capable of telling
What he thought
He would say
Right even have
Whatever the case is the DNA found at this time today
Completely within the law and their actions were
Artifact
Because he's prejudiced piece of s***
Why are you doing
I mean we know why
That's that's just really
Really bad
It's really really bad
8-bit
This is such a good
Example
Of how this bigotry in the
Is prejudice
Infest
The show he's talking about race issues
It involves all of these the way he
Covers a lot of stories
X
I skip over stuff
Kind of like this but this was so egregious
Do spiders like
This is a great
Case in point case study
The tentacles of prejudice
Just are every
Yeah it's not like
It's that literally everything
To do with a white
Eventually
Post office
If it's negative
Who is a veteran who apparently had his guns taken away
Oh no Tales
What will get into some of the details of Alex
Sturtevant Howie's
Like it's real
So
First thing about that clip is that
Alex Azar
Yeah he does that repeatedly because he will reframe everything that this guy says
Your language
And Then trailer
And he's he's not like one of Alex's normal gas to someone who has experience
Trudy's trying to relate
Contextualizing
I'm seem like
I keep telling a pecan
Disjointed
Too clunky interview but by the end of Alex has gotten
And this guy
More into the Rhythm of the Night
There is apparently he got put on like a 72-hour hold
For his own
I'm not sure about that I can't really find any information other than
His own telling of the story
But I looked a little bit
Apparently
The way the story is told that this guy was a veteran was dishonorably
Discharged honorably discharged
Presages what the globalist
Want to do to all the brave Patriots
Out there in the world
The story is that schmecker went to a doctor to try and get pain meds
What a veteran who gets their Healthcare through the VA shows up at a doctor's office looking
A pain pills
They're required to get a psych evaluation
In from the VA
In an effort to screen out drug-seeking Behavior
Jamaica refuse to get that evaluate
Referred him back to the VA for the evaluation
Call Debora follow-up Macker wasn't home
He called dude wasn't
And apparently the answering machine message that he got was enough to worry him for smackers well-being
The doctor recommended wellness check and the police showed up and
I'm not sure what to make of the story primarily because the only information I can find on it comes directly from him
And even by his telling of the story his act
Created the situation he found himself
This wasn't an instance of tyranny,
To follow the va's guidelines
Disturbing
Who acted in red flags to mental health care providers
Like there's no way to say this for sure
Almost $0 just shown up for the VA psych evaluation
It wouldn't
Formality
It would have been fine as long as he didn't use it as an opportunity to rant about the government track
How to use psych evaluations
Stick control
Do people in society
If you just go
I'm almost certain of that
So overworked
If he had gone
Hyundai
Psych eval
Maybe
Yeah maybe
Baby
Would be a behavior that you would be looking
Paranoid
Baby has the mother issues
And if you recognize that
You're probably failing
A little bit from the mental health perspective
I want to hear this dude
This to himself
Just didn't
Follow the steps that are appropriate
Required
Holiday
It's just something that is
64 Alex to manipulate
Oh yeah oh yeah you know you
You just have guns
If you don't want to submit to the
Would you go to the DA you're going to go to the VA you're going in there and it's
Just for them
To get your gut
So you refused to do that so they took your guns and
Retaliation
Going to the VA
But I thought it was there so when I went
Acting a little bit
Overreacted a little bit
Over-aggressive
All those guns
I don't have enough information about this situation
To say this with any
Absolute search
But from the pieces of information that are publicly available
This is the situation
Where
This guy
Could have avoided all this
Very easily gotten his gun
That retained no harm no foul his behavior is exactly the reason
Things went the way they did
Sure
Personal responsibility is a very high priority
For the right
So Alex
Like all guns
Or being taken from veteran
It's happening
Really
Really freaks
All guns
One story where the guy
Getting all the reasons
Does it feel to like other people he's talked to.
Is a bunch of
Snitches
The VA is a bunch of snitches
Wow
The wave at the
Functions for our vets
Let alone with an a
Assholes
Hate and fear everyone at the
That's good where it's good it's good
Perception of what's going on
Now which is based on faulty
Information of misrepresentation
But he's really worried
Because
The present
Really matches
Miss representation
Right that's trouble take the predictions based on those lies
It's Dawning on me
They said they
Blood thinners
He's got a letter
Exquisite
Now I'm going to
Misrepresent various things
In order to prevent exit
I was right all along
It's crazy
It's just
To self
Fulfilling
The guy
If you got a letter L
I've never heard anybody he asks actually
One of those letters
So this clip
What where he's at a little bit
It's just so crazy how they
6 years ago
Nothing changed
Google set offshore
He just it's always the same
Never
Never changes there's the intensity of this right now another never f******
Exact
Spell for this
And I think it's
Funny
Considering Alex's
So shocking
Mariah to take pictures of hookers
Sex workers
Whatever it is it's not healthy it's not it's not healthy
No but I'm more interested in the other advice because this guy you know the police came and took his gun so that's why Alex is Target
The police in this equation
Cuz they're collaborate
But like
Alex recently
Was it sxsw
And he thinks that's the biggest
Superiority that is his life in a very long time
He refused to file a
White about how you're not going to
Complain about you don't tell the guy to overthrow city council get the police chief fired
Just working there
He wants his listeners because he knows that it won't work out it'll be a waste of time for them it'll
Personalized
But Alex will be able to report on it
He'll be able to create
Attention for himself and himself out of their action
He knows that's not in it for him if he reports this b*******
Did the Austin Police or whatever
It's it's going to be filing a false complaint going to go nowhere whatever the case is
It's going to be a drag on his own time and resources
The the carnival
The parasite you know like
Our leaders
Just sucking off of
For your money
That's what I do that's what I do
I'm a f****** parasite
What do you want
As we find out
Like he's really against
These Mexican cartel gang
Imagines are on a rampage
Wow
Sure I prefer the real things they do as opposed to the imaginary line
Prosecutor
Just took out.
This is stupid
This is so stupid
They don't want to say who
And again
This isn't stupid
This is racist by stupid Behavior
Yeah that's that's where it where at
So as Alex that call with
He gets into
Right because he's decided that this guy was tortured in a North Korean
Powfu
Alex has an epiphany
I just realized this
4 years
Right now
Serious
And
Washington
You know what the feeling I get with
Stuff like that is
I don't know if you ever experienced
Go to church a lot
They're like small group meeting
Preacher of the alike
Heading to peponi the other day
God loves us
101 s*** already to Civil War
All the time
The same thing with that you
Which is like
I'm telling you this because I know
This is the one time that I think I'm telling you the truth
Sort of
Does
I don't think Alex musically
You don't you don't believe it
You have an epiphany like that emotions and then you believe it
As opposed to
You viscerally felt
What you want to talk about it like you you had
Epiphany
Mooresville
Experience
Lights U2
Experience this in Moore
Real way
Tim self
Like this guy was in a p o w camp
Tiffany of a realization
He's already had plenty of times before
I think that Alex is
He's far more performative in the youth pass
Because what he's doing
He's trying to be
Like this is real
This is this is absolutely real
F****** know it
This is tyranny
It is arrived
I don't think he wants
Call Dale
During the last
Thomas Jefferson
Call godchild
Especially one charismatic
What
Trying to read
Just added
Text Brooke a definition for Lake
Literally knows
Nothing about Thomas Jefferson
Clifford little Snippets of qualities red in Malaysia newsletter
I will say that this one at least is a real quote but you have no idea what the quote is about
The words Alex always repeats are quote I've sworn upon the altar of God Eternal hostility against
Every form
Tyranny over the mind of man
And that sounds
Especially when you're Alex like about the New World Order and globalist
Reply back to religion I would like everything I own no idea where
It's from a September 1800 letter to Benjamin
Rush know what that letter is about like you said
Here's the quote in Kanto
The Clause the Constitution which
Secure the freedom of press
Covered also the freedom of religion
An establishment
Particular form of Christianity
Through the United States
Does every sect believes its own form is
Everyone
Perhaps hope for its own
But especially the episcopalians and congregational
They're returning to their house
Position
Power confided
Tumi will be exerted in opposition to their
And they believe truly
Upon the altar of God eternal
Hostility against every form of tyranny
Over the minds
Is a man but this is all they have
This is a quote about swearing Eternal hostility
Against all forms of tyranny but specifically
United States I don't know I don't know why Alex
Diametric opposition with Alex's b******* about the nation
And yet Alex pretends the world's number one
Some scholar and follower of his tradition
This is getting a bit redundant
But rest assured
I'm going to keep up
Keep bring up the mirror is Alex knows nothing about his hair out
Because it's important to reiterate over and over again Alex knows comes from extremist
Anti-communist propaganda sources
All of the historical ship that
Recite every time he drops
These quotes
Out of context
He has no idea what their actual
We talkin about
You think you knew that was about religious
Nonsense I don't like the way you said that
Outback
Now gets back to his
Man
Baby it's just
Can't stress how weird is Jay
Just for people to be like I've epiphany
Last night
It just dawned on me
Alex isn't cool
Problem
Drama
Top movies
Surreality
Can we hear that
I can't imagine
That we've had a
A full week on
It's one of those
I can't imagine that it ever is at
I can't I can't even do this for years I don't think there is
Is one where were you not heard Alexei almost
Exactly
Because I've not thought
Double Wacky Wednesday
They're all
Is happening up
Too close to the problem I didn't see it
But it's not just the media
Not just the globalist everybody
Despise
School counselors
So he calls
Vision while preparing us
Episode
I always prefer to show not tell when it comes to how bad Alex's but I kind of felt like doing that would be
No one special
It's very clear with Alex's doing
Puritans
There's no way around it
Like you can hear it through his framing of the schmecker guys interview
You can hear it and Howie's
Demonizing the VA
Ranting about how everyone's a global is spy and he's realized the Civil War
That's performative in order to allow this escalation
Rhetoric
All of its aim specifically a veteran
Constant
Globalist
Know that they need to take out Military in order to take over everything
It's what all resumes do they take out the Old Guard
Authoritarian
Some of the examples that uses our kind of
I mean
Yeah but also has more specific to it then like
Hitler Purge
ROM
It wasn't like
He wasn't killing
Rank-and-file of veteran
Power grab that was a leadership
The base of the militia
Leadership of the militia by killing The Regular Guy
Mmbn like hey
Bosses of the militia can I run now that Alex is using which is
Kind of absurd like he's using these historical examples of times that Armed Forces
Units have been
Have been purged like that
Typically
They haven't been done
From the ground up
Right that doesn't seem like a good strategy but either way that's the way it's raining
Leaderless
The phone lines for military folks have had bad run-ins with
VA
It's just Alex
Plus props
One guy calls and who claims
In a way but the story it's very clear that there's more to the story
He keeps bringing up how his family is who keeps trying to get him help
How he gets into altercation with his doctors
Clearly someone who's
Having a really hard time and needs
Instead of treating the situation
Stickley Alex use this guy to prove his point that the globalist
Not only want your gun
They also want
Your kids
Completely disgusting diatribe
About how the CPS people are having
I just couldn't bring myself to include that clip
Like before and it's really nothing
At the same
Time I couldn't not bring this up
Because it's so indicative of an oz
Clearly doing on this episode
He's absolutely trying to radicalize these met military folks in his audience
By lying about everything and convincing him
The people who say they want to help them like people
VA like
Psychiatrist
Psychologist counselors
There really is globalist
Your kids and then have sex with them
Listen to this episode I really don't think
Just that I don't think this is just how we talk sometime
Feel like this isn't
It definitely feels like he's trying to rile up mentally unstable people
Turn them against
Anybody who
Possibly
Help them your turn them away professionals who can help
I just hoping one of them does something horrific so you can claim it's a false why
Might be a little bit out there for me to say but it's death
Currently how it felt this
Like he's trying to Target
This
Group the middle military veterans
He's trying to radicalize them
Through exaggeration
Trying to take away
Any appeal to support structures and then also preemptively creating
Civil War and the globalists are going to create false Flags inflamed about us
It
Exactly what you would do if you wanted them
I'm to do this
Wow keeping your hands
According to prove
Wanted to
Perform a cool during
Ftr's
They got
Is the guy
Exactly
Basically said
Get all the veterans together and then perform a soft
And it's just
It's just rile up a bunch of people who are
Actively trying
Help
That's more of a coon
Cuckoo
This this feels like inspiration
Stochastic
It feels like he knows
What he's doing
Because there isn't an appeal to
Solving the actual problem
There anyone have anything
There isn't an appeal to like let's say
Greater oversight of the child protect
Active Services there isn't an appeal to
A bill introduced
In order to
Pueblo CO
These
Those are the things that you would
Probably or
You care more about these colors
And not use them just as ways to prop up your narrative
It seems to me
Very clearly
He's up to he's up to no good
You have to be a psychopath
Listen to so
Play story
Very clear
All of that
Girl spies
Advice to give
It's probably not
Walmart advertisements
I'm telling you
Honestly break is what I say as a parody of
What he saying there is
Advocating for his audience to Target
And harass people
Because
The application of
ASO
Nebulous
It's so vague
So the people at the VA
Despise and snitches
The police
Loratadine
Collaborators
Anybody you suspect of being a globalist
Now let's say someone is in the false flag terrorism event
Cartels
But you have to understand how this
Rhetoric
And like okay you know what happened
They got hammered
You know what happened
Victims of things
Who you
Text suspicion on
They got exactly
You're telling your audience that all of these people who are
I do know this nefarious s***
Define they do evil stuff
Just always be following
This is definitively on
No it's
It's about to be
I already be asleep might already be applying
Specifically the Sandy Hook because he's still
Not going full bore on that but God who has
Expert in his elevator
The platform
So
These things living in concert with each other are absolutely relevant
Like
Lumos
April 3rd episode by talking about how
Is a secret service agent
Shrek
The Dad episode
Sicilian
Hello
Pixel
From the Fantastic Four
Superhero
So I know who bit damp know is
Shape-shifting
Secret Service that alien guy is absolutely 100%
Not that bongino
Oh no
Their heads are totally different shapes their facial features don't look anything alike
There's the fact that you left the Secret Service in 2011 to unsuccessfully run for a senate
That's a problem since
Video of the supposed alien was shot on March 4th 2013
Stop
Ratigan unsuccessful a couple more times for Congress
He had a show on nr8
TV
Through his career he's been
He's been followed by
From his former Secret Service
Cohorts
That is brand is being built on
Information from
Time on the job kind of betrayal
Supposed to uphold
Pretty much
What's going on here is trying to associate bongino with this story because
Outspoken
And Alex has to claim that all such people are under attack
Immediately Globus can't handle dealing with bongino's actual arguments
For the accused
Paranoid bowls
So clear but Alex is doing at this point
Is it
The medical community VA the media Glenn Beck
And how isolating Alex's being
Also escalating is rhetoric
Around the same time.
Very nice
There's a very sincere feelings
His feelings and rage up
Suspicious of anyone
Just a recipe
Reefer trouble
He thought I'd describe it as
Trains running
Get through each other you know it
He's going to happen
It's it's
Verite
Makes me very
Decided this is Dan bongino it's rotten
Demonstrable
It's not him
Deciding vote him
Is the same thing as proving
Okay
What
No
Know you can
You can't just say
We found out who he is
My memory did that's breaking to prove it breaking news
Alex has proven the Dan bongino is an alien
It lazy
Pretty sloppy
To get bongino on the show to talk about it so you offer the bounty
For him to become a
Disintegration of 11
And it's a disturbing pattern
The offers a $500 interview
Pupate
The Obama phone
What is that what is that mean
Does it mean anything
What is what is
It means nothing
Mike Adams
April 4th
Because Alex
This is working on like some
Studio renovations
Studio
Tool belt
Fixtures
Victoria
Mike is covering is that North Korea threatening to start a nuclear war
Play again to that a little bit a little severe about it
We just kind of interesting
Considering the way the rest
Episodes going to play out
So are we get to the fence cuz who gives a f*** about Mike Adams
And Alex
He's continuing his severity but however one wants to take your kids to globalstar going to kidnap
Your children
Here's
The tone
That means
Secession
What is that
So
So rather than smoke
Which is how they going to take your guns
Cuz it's more illegal now in 2013 than it ever has which is
Pretty funny
I don't know
Tone is like
Everything is against you you have to we have to
Completely separate
So he has some ideas about tyrant
How you make them go away
Sure
Call wife
Thomas Jefferson
Come on man
Installment of our favorite segment
I thought I was kidding when I said I wasn't going to stop correct
Literally I would never stop
Sort of
I use at least using some of the words of a real quote that gets passed around in the most common version of this quote is
And people generally at the dawn of
You can already tell that this is really have anything to do with the context Alex's
Is using the Cloud app
Princeton's when Jefferson says Enlighten the people generally
I have to assume that means I have something to do with that
Education
Republic Republic
And it does have some
This line comes
Bambara letter Jefferson
Consent to pierce
A French expat
One of the largest companies
U.s. history
Anatomy of taking climate change seriously
I won't hold that against
Pierre though
You probably have no idea
Thomas Jefferson go for it
This letter in April 1860
And it's mostly about how much Jefferson likes the u.s. form of Albert
I would argue that he's a little biased on the subject so
I don't know
Disproportionate comes from is specifically about discussing a
Constitution that have been proposed in
Which would require also
Citizenship to be contingent on a person
Ability to read and write
Something
Speaks of posit
It was Jefferson spilling that tyranny
And all those negative things in society
Your body
We'll just disappear
The population was
Which is probably very naive position
Yeah
Got the British
Back off your f***
Let's go to work
It's better than the alternative but it's not a cure-all.
Nothing to do with standing up against
Tyranny of them disappearing like Mist in the morning
Important
I'm having a literate and educated
Population since the masses are where the power resides
In theory it's absolutely
Crucial that the masses have the wisdom
Them to appropriately use that power
This is about education and literacy which as we've learned over and over
Not one of Alec
Strong suit
There's a delicious irony
That Alex is misusing a quote about literacy
That he would understand
If you took the time to read the things
He pretends to Everette
Every every f******
Time he meant
And he embarrassed
Himself
But him not reading the quote that specifically like about literacy and misrepresenting that
Is just
Amazing
Over how many years
Embarrassing
You look incredible
Credible
Innovated
The speaker someone else is really impressed
On the April 5th episode
Alex has deep
Pieczenik back
Sure put this
Narrative
Takes
F******
Swan Dive
Okay this is not about that
But it absolutely
To be related
In some way
I just
I love it
I love this
Cuz it's
Something that only a crazy
Easy person brings in
Silk
No one else would do something like that
Korea
Motion Pictures
Has multiple degrees from
Here in front of me
Operation
Great great stuff
Here's what it is
Has gone to the DMZ to report
There's no way
I will say his phone quality is almost always pretty bad
Right call this coming from
South Korea
I don't know there's no
Without telling anyone
And I bet Ali
Well of course I was
Well you know Alex is the kind of guy who's really easy
To run
Key is to butter him up a little bit
And here is house
Steve present
His trip to Korea
Opportunity in the unique one and the reason I've done is to really be able to
The only media that I can get the real truth
Sing it now
Real to the only real need ESO I had to go to Korea in order to make sure
That the real truth gets out
Just on vacation
If you just went on
Listen to South Korea
His wife was literally
Oh my God
You do realize
You could do right now
I'm way ahead of you managed to ignore her rolling her eyes like
Leave Alex alone
I have literally no idea Steve was actually in
Korea
Mostly because I was drunk
In order to see what I can find I went checked out
These blogs
First you posted about Sandy Hook being a false flag
Then he made another post about how he was going to be on Alex's show that
On April 4th you returns claiming that he'd headed out to the DMZ to sniff out what is large-scale psych Warfare
He claims a quote
Isaac transition from a military leadership to civilian political system
Add later in this episode when he's talked to Alex he's going
Which claim more less responsibility
So he saying he was in South Korea
At the end of this
48 which one is 5 years old
Actually there at all
Alright okay
I have no f****** idea
The Korean War
Probably
I guess
Could have been in the country like
The 80s
As a tourist
Is any kind of a player in any situation
It doesn't make sense
His claim that he was there and in the mixed follows it
Certain pattern of taking credit for
For everything that's ever have
The evidence that accompanies his pose
Is 3 pictures
What is a legend
Steve
Tourist spots
In Korea
I say allegedly because at this point
Steve was still refusing to reveal himself publicly
So he blurted out his face of these tickets
It might not even be him
Might just be someone interest pictures with the word face
Blur don't say that
They don't show anything that could actually just be a retired guy visiting South Korea to see the fight
Which are now being Rica
Contextualize
Is proof that he's there.
On April 5th
Steve posted a picture of himself with a group of Korean
Fatigue which group of soldiers on Leisure Time
Is analysis is fairly
North Korea knows that second South Korea would mean at the end of any real military or political exist
For both the North and the South
Incredibly unlikely
You just seems
To be mad at media Outlets are escalating the story and hyping up the possibility of a strike from North Korea which is weird
Exactly what
Has been doing
The analysis of it isn't
Escalation is
Sensational
It seems pretty clear
Seems to be
Deceitful
To be advocating for
I'm not really again
Claiming to be in all different places
Accused
But what if he was doing that to give
Clear-eyed foreign policy advice
Clear-eyed foreign policy
That's not analysis been anyone needs
Let's go to Korea to have
Publications put out by the intelligence company stratfor
Steve is
Exit trip goes on he offers no evidence
You saying other than more tourist photos which I find
He also complains on April 7th that he's being denied access to the US Embassy any military base and any other official
Areas which is unacceptable
Deputy assistant Secretary of State for East Asia
This is a new title that I've never seen him
You have an any other article or any
In every other source he's at the title of deputies
Assistant Secretary of State for management
Which is
Completely different wing of the state department organizational chart for this new title that he's giving himself
Also if that was his position
You would know that it's actually called the deputy assistant
Secretary of Defense
Legitimately this would be an entirely separate career from anything he's going to happen
There is zero chance he was ever the deputy assistant secretary for it's just not possible
Until there's more proof of this
There's no way I can really even
The evidence
Tourist pictures
And Analysis that anyone could have if they just read some
Some s*** and it Daddy blurt
We blurred the picture
I kind of understand that
Like it makes sense
If he's legit
It also makes sense if he's coming
Sure I don't think that that very active trying to Maine
Maintain your private
I don't think
Dammit
Although it does make it much more difficult for you to
Use tourist pictures as evidence of you being on a clandestine mission to South Korea in order to
Tell Alex
The truth makes it almost
Infinitely
Easier to claim that you weren't holding back
Now unfortunately
And all that stuff
Some things that are real problems
And actually make his timeline
Timeline even more impossible
Like we discussed in the episode all about
Like what
We didn't know other things
Episode
His timeline
Literally a
Okay
But I know what I was trapped in I was 24 25 with Alex
Mandatory two-year service
Look there's just no way that's your story makes it impossible
He claims he made the rank of 06 at age 32 which be pretty much unbelievable
18th birthday
He was drafted at 24 25 years of age
Bentley's claimed he reached 06 and a Mac
Maximum of eight
Which is just
I'm close to pop
Yep after I last episode about Steve I got some messages from enlisted persons
Veterans
And their perspective was very
Bayside
There is no way
Hey Steve could have reached 06 by 32
It's just an insane
Shorten that time frame
Even further with
More impossible for me to believe
It's something he could have done
Beyond
At the time he was drafted
He should have been in medical school
You could get out of draft
While he was doing his
Residency
As well
And simultaneously he was getting
HD from MIT
Absolutely
Position of believing
People about their credentials
Especially about military stuff cuz it's really serious
To like impune someone
Syrup
Really just
Respectful
Screwy as something that doesn't make sense about this
And I would I would like clarification for it
Because I don't want to be
Be forced to call someone service
Listen to question
I'm rapidly being pushed down that road to take care of this for you I am not going
However I do not necessarily reflect
I'll join you at the photoshoot
This is crazy it's absolute
So on this episode
Alex been talking to Steve about it Korea report
Which is an Oculus for the most part except for the
Alex
Talks
Two two pastors Chuck Baldwin
Strippers Pastor Chuck Baldwin
And
And for the most part
It's just about
Foreign
Globalists are taking over the church
Because their argument
Churches are 501 c 3 and that's made them puppets of the state
Shut your f****** taxes
Organization
Tax exempt
If you don't want the requirements that exist with 501 c 3 entity
Cool
Pay your taxes
Big do whatever you want
I don't care I don't care about this
Bye
That's what a lot of
And now they're tools
I thought about it
About this too though is this interview
It's just about the globalist
Take overall
All the churches
And all that s***
In the same way
Vet on
The 3rd
Alex was targeting
These veterans
With this extremist radicalizing rhetoric
He's now doing that too
The Christian
Thor 2
Hitting up his
Version of cry
He sent the globalist
Are an existential threat to
The church they're going to
Takeout everybody's
Got it
It's it's
Exactly
Is isolate
And using
Whatever hardship they may be experiencing
A prop
And a pedestal upon which
To promote his narrative
Erratic
8 intentions
It's like he's doing those themed episodes of
F****** Maury
A week before his Christian who's been wronged by this
Episode where we try and radicalize all of you
Well it would be that is Maury's goal was to overthrow the government
Alright
Beyond that Alex
Episode this is one of my
Mother
Barrel maker
A lot of family on the Mayflower
The strong theory that Alex is
He's trying to tie his lineage back to the Mayflower because
Who was the first
Pilgrims that came over
And because Alex
Subscribed
To this Christian identity
The first pilgrims
Is it came over we're really were amuli
The Promised Land
So he's
Being the descendant of the like
From the original
It makes him the purest
Like it's almost like he's a Chosen One
I really believe that that's the rhetoric or the point behind the rhetoric
I was like
There's no
When he started saying
My dad's family has Iowa.
Had both of his
Parents on there
Click the British Israel
That clicked right there was like
Genuinely think that you're one of the f****** 144,000
Like that's what behind
The Mayflower arrived in America on November 9th
1820s
Considering
They're only about 130 people on board
Yeah.
Right it was a bit of a cat
The odds are staggeringly
True American royalty
Confederate Rose
Is blood
Anna's country from day one
Except for when it was out of this country for roughly 4 years
Punitive
Directions.
Let's leave his mother's side of the family out of the equation.
Zillow the difficult to sort out
Complicated
Denis just saying his mom side goes back to the barrel maker and famous lady
I know who is talk about
Descriptions I would say
However on his dad side he says the line goes back to the camp
And that's something I
Definitely looking
Alex is making the claim because the captain of the Mayflower his name
Christopher Jones
And honestly must be related
Goddamn
These people so much
I hate silver
It makes sense
About it heroic Libra
Pilgrim versus the world that made a home here where his ancestors became intertwined with the growth of this land from the very start
And you're like well clearly I started China also
Also there's a huge hole
The story
There's a lot of information about Christopher Jones
This is that he was bringing the pilgrims to America because they paid him
He had nothing to do with their Vision you could say you would people wear on
And his family
Including his children
Didn't come along
His wife Josie and Clark stayed behind in their home town of Harwich
But
After delivering delivering the pilgrims across the Atlantic Ocean
Look out the rest of his life there
Which was not long
Is he died at 6
T22
He didn't stay in America and he's not one of the founding members of this country very unlikely that he's actually related to Alex
I think it's just a thought which is amazingly
Child
Toddler f******
Use the world
Oh my God
Are you related
Larry home
Larry Holmes Larry
So rare
Literally
Maybe we could have a
I do have a lot of
Like distant weird relatives among like
Communities
Is there a reason is fairly common
Reasonably common name
Some weird distant relatives
Found a few that work on
But
I don't believe that Alex is related to
The people who were on the Mayflower because this is an area that people have studied
The original North America is pretty well research
And none of the resources I can find indicate in any way that Alec says descendants among the pilgrims
But you know who does
Movies
As well as
How about noted Avril Lavigne
The cheese Canadian or what do you think about
Relatives
What time is it okay that is but that's not what we want to say any
Can't see me
Is that for the list for The Listener at home
Antenna Concord
Sakura song
He gave England the Five Knuckle Shuffle
Stfd
Documented relatives
All I can say is that he's related to the bear
It's weeks.
Some politically biased list
That would ignore don't conservatives have Pilgrim ancestry
I know this because list also includes Sarah Palin
Alex is no different than Sarah Palin in terms of public disgust
The thing you have to consider is that the pilgrims were very much unprepared
What they found when they arrive
45 of the 180 passengers on that ship died in
The first winter
With 10 more dying within the first year
From when they land
On top of that eight of them returned to England
All the people Alex is claiming his mother's side where John Alden was a barrel maker and Priscilla Mullins
Should I get
Daily shirt
Reference to
Decide to stay in North America as opposed to returning with Christopher Jones
Right back
He married Bowen
Because Mullins
Hire family died
First winter
They're gigantic databases of John Alden
Descendants because spoiler alert
That dude like to have kids
Carol Jones
Actually a number of Carol Jones
Descendants of Alden
Caroline
Which is close enough
Unfortunately all of them were born in the early
So I doubt we are our ancestors
I couldn't be her anyway
Because
Carol hammer
The database of the Alden family tree
Hammond
Exist what
It's nice
Included as part of the genetic lineage
Or the I guess
Genetically
You call that
Play trelaney into whatever
Hilarious
Post
Yahoo answers
Quest
I re-posted like a day after the episode that we're going
Why does Alex Jones forget details about his family history on the Mayflower it's making this stuff up
YouTube
Very likely making this stuff up
Because corporate gets to feel like he has a greater claim on being a true American
Since being an opportunistic conman is all he really needs
To make him as American as
Apple pies
People who on the Mayflower far-less pate
Patriotic in America
Gaming other America
Number one
I can't stress this
Like people who have
Families go back
To the Mayflower
Know about it
They document
Like it's it's it's a very common thing people have like certificates
And like you're involved in
An organization might even know a bunch of other
It clubs
April Alex
Claimed that his family goes back
Back to the Mayflower
And him care so much about these sorts of ideas and you think
Not know the name
Of the people just the barrel maker in the famous lady unbelievable
Absolutely if Alex was
Truly related back to people who are the Mayflower
He would know their name
You know so much about them
Not forget their name
It doesn't make sense it's not true
It look
True
And everybody is family like
Important but they don't really get together about those made
Flower people
Royal
I think some of that
I think that's the thing I think that is
Also the country
I know that
Pretty hilarious
Really doesn't feel like a nose
The pilgrims was a
He didn't realize that you
Tire Guy
In the context of this interview with Baldwin
And a great day
Boring
There's also meant to
Jessica Rupp
The religion
It's kind of indicative
Talking about
They're trying to wipe out the
On Earth
Local church on Earth
Christianity
Exactly
That is a parody of what I would
Do if I were back
Confido
Weird
I would just say that
And be like it seems like
Yeah it's coming back I just saw
It sounds like
The tenor of what they're talking about
Do you win is bacon boobs now literally all churches
Is being used to do
Take over there
What what's going on is day-by-day Lorazepam
Turn on Alex's show in order to alienate
And radicalized
Segments of his audience
Segment on one day about
There's now that segment on this episode
About the church
And it's
Upsetting
You wouldn't do this
Unless
You were trying
To do something
That's almost it's almost like a
Regular it sounds like a scheduled B
That has been as overt
Right scaling
In this
Beginning of
Which is
Very trouble
So are we get to the seven
And I keep this clip-ins
Because I always talk about how bad his job
And there's no greater indication
Then how you figure
On the 7th
Prescription
Thomson Reuters subscription
What the f*** is going on
This is on the show this is like some hidden camera video this is him on the show say
What do
Research tools we should have been a long time
Subscription to Reuters what the f*** are you doing
Please God
It shows what are you researching
You're just reading support
Whatever you talk about this with hard work
But you do in like I spend hours
Google the couple play WorldNetDaily holiday sayings
See what's up
The 7th Alex Spencer
Most
Of this show
Talking about Melissa harris-perry
Because that video has just been
If you'll recall it was a woman on MSNBC
You see who she talked about how
For a long time we've looked at kids as being just
The responsibility of their parents
So we need to take a more communal approach and not look at it as children belonging to their parents
Everybody
Sat with thought about
Realized
Fairly reasonable holyshit
How we normally view the family but
We live in an in
Society
Cotuit
Charcoal
Cam
Hey sassy on that red link
From a Drudge
We talked about this narrative before when Alex has brought it up when he encountered it
Commercial said the children don't just block their parents they belong to
It's really obvious from surrounding context that she met the word belong in relation to the community and its definition that means
Being a part of
But that didn't stop literally all of the right-wing media from freaking out and screaming about creeping communism
Sarah Palin Rush Limbaugh Glenn Beck all made sport out of yelling about this s*** now it says no difference
He spends almost
I would say most of this episode talk about this clip and have proved exactly what he said about the globalist
Harris-perry responded to the backlash in a blog saying quote
Those of you who are alarmed by this ad can relax
I have no designs on taking your children
Please keep your kid
Everyone
I should know full well that my messages my dad was a call to see ourselves as connected to a larger hole
I don't want your kids but I want them to live in safe neighbor
I want them to learn Dynamic class
I want them to be healthy and well and Free From Fear
What you meant was totally clear that added self
Clarify that further
Matter
This means nothing
But there's another funny
Thomas episode Alex
Keep going on and on
About how
Nazis and Soviets
Want your kids
And this is proof of that
What bring the kids
It's weird McDonald's
I don't think
That Alex
Is is
Arguing
A lot of it
My good faith
Thinking through
This guy
Is just throwing doesn't really care I don't know
Kids throwing shade at the walk
Oh no I mean like
Whatever it is
Just like
Bright
Yeah yeah
System
There's
Felix
Tough time getting away from
Attention
Always there which is
Is that
A complete and utter opposites
A willingness
Opposition
Willingness to
Twist and distort anything
Into something that might
Fit Within
Save it
What he's saying
But there is apps
Absolutely
It's all built
In the beginning
You know he wouldn't even have the opportunity to
Something that stupid
Melissa harris-perry
For most of the show but thanks
Another segment
Show
North Korea
Psych Warfare specialist
Another
F****** North Korea
Really into
Extenuating himself into the show
You coming on very regularly
Is a Xanax
Alex is presented with all of these huge credentials
And he's going to South Korea because he helped us blush the
Be there
Deeply credible it's going there and he's telling Alex
Consistently I went so I could give only you the real truth
When you present him like that
It's really hard to not believe everything
So
Is actors
Which he already has
It really is tough
To disconnect that
From The credibility that you're giving him
By having him on concert
Play to talk about North Korea
It's it's it's
It's a setup for real
Trouble
It is kind of interesting out of all of this
I haven't heard anything about Alex
Blaming
Nothing
Williams like Wolfgang halbig
But not go through
There's no other way to look at it other than a man
F****** with Alec
If you don't see or not whether it's
Like
Or not
He is f****** with Alex
He's not in Korea but by saying the reason Korea
I will believe literally anything you say you went to South Korea and
Tell me on your own time to be a field reporter for me
I didn't even do anything
If he didn't go you have to look at this as an intentional effort
In order to make himself a fixture on a Leticia
100% this is a Hail Mary
It's crazy if he did go
It's even crazier
I don't I don't know what's going on
Just was like I can kill two
Two birds with one stone
Steve's going to be coming up
Complaining about the Melissa harris-perry
Clip
Department of Education
North Korea
Quote
Thomas
Temperature
Fight back
So it's the same Thomas Jefferson quote I know we already discussed that misuse quote earlier but
But I have to bring it up again because it's f****** hilarious to me
It's about the need for education
And here Alex is engaged targeted
To campaign against someone who's just trying to encourage greater communal responsibility for the education of children
If he knew what he was doing I would say this must be satire
But as it is
Who's memorized a couple quotes and pics
Like he's using a quote about the importance of Education
Great
Eddie's using it in such a way as to
Change it
Original me
Not
We should all educate ourselves
Serenade
Do the Department of Education
She's a political science professor
In that cuz it's
Be officially Obama's attack
Tampa take over the school
Wants her in the media to get you
Used to the idea
That's a really she
Official anyway
Unofficial
Does Steve and Steve tells him about what's going on in North Korea
Not Sensational analysis
He gets down to talking about the situation it's very much
Like okay
I don't know if I agree with him that North Korea is completely controlled by China
Prescriptive is all just about like we need
Need to calm down
Yeah yeah yeah
Now you also said something
That is
Absolute ball
What
Steve created
Delta Force
911 are you
Admission 1970
He started Delta
Just kicked off in November so he might have created Delta Force before the hostages were taken
Definitely call in for that
Search crisis
Something is doesn't make sense
Knows that he can make up whatever he wants about Delta Force because be superseded
Secret unit
It's really easy to lie about
Unfortunately for
The Army released
Bunch of documents
For the first time
Delta Force was created
And it does not my
Story
The initial plans were formulated after the bombing at
The Munich Olympics in 19
There were already at least 150
Delta Force
So the timeline of him creating it 1979
Absolutely
Jump force was officially created in 90
1077 by army colonel Charles Beckwith
And Steve's name is literally nowhere to be found
Did any of the information
I mean this
Sincerely if this isn't true
This claim is an outrageous
Spectrolite
I'm not going to go about troops or any of that stuff
But
I don't believe
Particularly about founding Delta Force
This is the only only associate
This is outrageous
I'm starting to come to a conclusion that
Might be
Severely matted
Like
After we did that episode on the show and I'm maybe I'm
Ridiculous and everybody else saw this
Little Easter eggs
You is stupid
As a crank
Right
Manipulative can I say that I still agree with those three catheterization
But then after we did the
Claims on his bio I'm like
Okay I might be out for
Fun to like this might just I'm also
You at this
When he doesn't
He doesn't need to call Alex he has no obligation
Even if
Stay
Really feels like device out of his mind
A part of it just because I'm very too
Detached from all this and I'm looking at it
The past
Like there is a part of it that I kind of appreciate
Even if he's that crazy
Because it is
So weird it's so outside the norm
That look at it
Cindy created Delta Force
Democratized South Korea
Interesting why are you doing
The guys who suddenly have this like
Weird
Forrest Gump
Lifestyle
Forrest Gump guy
Include
Like
Forrest Gump and then just throw a little bit
Over and over and over again until you have a
I'm long Forrest Gump
Steve is Freddy has
Shooting framing about why he went to
Which again dr. I believe but this framing
Interview with you which was so grateful that down Sandy Hook where I told you was the phones black I knew
That Obama and his white house quireboys but start another false flag
In Korea
I could see it
The next day without anybody's permission
Came here and I wanted to report directly to you and Jean and other parts in North Korea
.
Oee nude blown the case wide open with telling Alex B
Did Obama was going to hear his appearance on Alex's show
And he's going to have to shift gears and start a false wagon
North Korea
So he went over there to get to the bottom of that at
Crazy
Deeply
Conspiratorial think
Type of thinking that has people
And I told to have a seat
So that's good
Of course
Not
Text the different approach you and I
Tell me what you're actually doing
So great I got to have you back on tomorrow
How long are you in Korean
I will be here a few more days to serve you and I
Crispix
Individual
My friend
Relation to earlier the episode Alex got about someone
Bring up Plato's allegory of the
The cave because also in the Republic Plato and courage
Philosopher-king
Democracy
Play-Doh Daddy
Support everything
Even bring that up to flatter Alex
That was that was later.
This point
Like if you understand it
In the preparation for this episode I listen to
Thursday's last Friday's up
So that's it
6 something hours
Gone through the
Third
Fourth fifth
+ 7
Is a Sunday
That's four more episode
This is the episode he said Steve on a couple time
Signing off and saying I have you want tomorrow you got to find out how
You're not going to know what Revenge of the Sith
The prequels
Revenge of the Sith
Resistant
Cuz
Air Force 1
Kirsch
So
What's really particularly jarring about that is that when he sang the people look and act like actors
They specifically talking about Robbie Parker
The news conference that he gave
Where
He appeared
2 Chainz tune at home
This is the exact same
Something that the caller
A couple months back
Ask Alex about
I took this sort of thing about someone who lost their child
This is a 180 split
He is now making
Fun of this guy
And using it to suggest
Fifties people look and act like act
You still creating it in the form of a disjunction
Where he says
Either exploited or associate with all these people
Act like actors
That is a massive
It doesn't
Scream
Like a
Elf on the show
And Alex is presented as an expert he's going to South Korea to report for Alex
If you take that seriously you have to take the other things you bring to
To the table series
Is it Noah
I think that this is
This music by product of
Giving Steve credibility
It's insane
Telling you
How credible Steve is that you being like
Well obviously Steve told me he's credibility
He does mention that they're like talking
It's very likely that Steve
Add stop
You know we talked a lot about other things that were
That would factor into
Switch
The fact that Obama talked to them
Specifically
Would have course be one of those
Alex is like clicks and there's no way the present
Talk to her real father
Does he know that it's a false flag so he would have had to
Kill the guys
Is it there are no Vic
Zachary
Sure
He always presents himself as being against
The actor idea he has for good B
Resistance
Crazy about
This next clip
Eerily
Is in contradiction
Between saying we all need to get into this and saying the Public's not ready for it
Publix not ready for it isn't indicative of you believe this
But you don't think you can get away with it
Adan Salazar came up with his report calling
Let's run it by legal and then legal said I don't know
Everyone calling the Sandy Hook people actors
You got Steve
You got all that you got
You got James
Yeah Wolfgang halbig still hasn't appeared at all
If any of this I don't know I don't know what what's going on there
But you have this this rising acceptability of this rhetoric
The public
Also now is probably the time I could just reveal this cuz I don't really give a f***
Everybody always asks whether or not Alex is aware of our
And for the longest time I said I don't know
I do know that he is aware of
Because
That guy who created report on the actors
His longtime producer follows me on Twitter
I don't know why you do that
I told him about this hot new show and Heat
When they tweeted out there
Right so
Good job
Coming up with theories about the Aurora victims being actor
In the lawsuit
Yeah that is house
Subway
It's too late for him I think the Aurora victims
I'm sorry I act
So there we go
It's a hop skip and a jump
From here if you're saying this about people who survived the Aurora shooting
Makes literally no difference for you to bridge the gap
To Sandy Hook
It doesn't ease. He's there he's arrived at least by the beginning of April
It's before
We didn't even get all the way to the bombing
It's about a week before the bombing
Accelerating his
Rhetoric
In terms of
The existential threat that the globalist he's encouraging people to harass
The globalist
At the same time
Scaling who
Rhetoric around these false flag
2 now incorporates so much talk of them being actors
If you combine all that stuff together he's whipping his audience into a frenzy
He's advising people
Go and document.
Including grieving families as members of the people who are involved with the globalist plot
If you include all three
Very definitely happened around the same time you have everything he's being sued for
Absolutely correct
He is doing
He is
Absolutely do it.
The defense
Of like other people were saying the stuff online is absolutely true
It is
But I don't think it's a
Exculpatory because
The level of credibility he gave these arguments
By his own show
Lake at the prevalence of the high-profile of his own show
And by associating them with Steve
And elevating
Steve and his theories
With his show
I don't think anybody in the world
Would have been in a position
To do what he did
It's not
I don't know if that makes it any more
Likely
He'll be found guilty I don't know if that makes what
He did
Somehow legally worse
But I can't think of any
Person who could have done the damage
He is doing
He was in a unique position
And he did
Exactly the wrong
Yeah
I'm seeing that
It's abundantly clear.
I guess the I guess the issue
Is
Going to
Turn out to be that
We have proven
Everything
To be proven
In terms of
This is a wrong
Bad and awful thing that led to
I don't know if that means
It's one of those things where the biggest issue that we run into
There's absolutely
No way
You can come away
With the information that we have laid out and think
With doing great
McDowell
A f****** dick
He's doing this and he's using
He's destroying every
And
The law
Well
Two points that are really interests
Alex's defense
I barely talked about Sandy Hook after it happened
It's kind of true
True
He tells himself to let himself off the hook
Is like I can see why he's bought his own bulshit
Evans
He could probably fall back behind some
Version of this
You could tell himself
I wasn't aware of the consequences
Is it my accent
I think a little bit later in this episode we will
Clear evidence that can
Episode
I'm just going to get a check
Big World News
So what's going on is this is
Play pimps
Steve's coming up
This is what I look
Criminal activity there are
Thousands of private intelligence
To everything
A battery
Mercenary Bridge
You know it's hilarious
He's waiting to talk to Steve
Someone who's been advocating for eggs
Exactly
Putting out papers and journal
About the knee
For private intelligence companies to take over
For the government
He's been
A customer of Stratford
3 years
Email you'll be the ones who will take care of all this so we could get rid of
All the government agencies
Alex
Doesn't have no idea that he was on the phone with someone who advocates for
Stands for in Provo
The very thing
Sitting here complaining about
That's hilarious
That is
Man there's a
This word
Touches on a couple issues here and there
Define what the globalist
Zorgo
Running wild
Destroying normal
Complete
Stud
Weirdos
Globalist want to destroy
What you have to do is
Consider Alex
Define normalcy
That's an important piece of the equation
I think we've got a pretty good job over the course of the
The show
Define ingin
Chicken okay
Let's just pull back like let's just do like you know those composite sketches where they have
Inputted
10 million
Exactly
Mathematic
Average
If you could
Like in your head
But he thinks that a normal
What characteristic
Steven Terry looks a lot like Alex
Maybe when he was younger
Alex
Suggesting that him and all of his right
Doing dumb Dumb Friends
Repeating things from chain email
When they really are just
Spirit Amy
And then
The narrative
Here we go
He says he just told us
Oh no
South Korea
Listen and fellow retirees
So I got to go out of the country
FX Clippers just Steve like
Going
The fence is flattering out
Or more
I'm being facetious here for more historically reference
Play don t reference that I was taking it back and I had to go read some
What you were saying
Holder of multiple
Big reuse International hostage negotiator extraordinaire
Is never read Plato or Nietzsche
Level level
Look I don't even want to release
These shows anymore
Because if people just acted as likes
They could rule the world
Every one of our listeners little tricks
The CEO of a company or perhaps
Information
Requires the recipient of
Kind of
Vaguely narcissistic and
Probably not
Plate
Blue Lotus South Korea
List of complaints about that though they might be racist
I go to TSA I got to go twice
That's
Not a good look
Your problem
Smart enough for you
It seems to be as main issue
That's not good
You can just steal the old man racist
Cuz we had a president we were all like
Anyways
Minorities
Old man house phone
Over the course of the time that we've been looking at Steve pieczenik these last couple weeks as he's shown up on aisle
Alexa show more frequently
Become clearly
Drift towards what will ultimately
Destroy his life
Is like I created Delta
For example right side
I don't know about that
I was 0632 right
Stop and cause
Those are instances of
Like this guy being
I think you're full of s***
But I wouldn't call them
Fuk up
Yeah because I bet there's some way he could talk his way around
Bring up these problems to this timeline and like
Create Bells
But I was around
His way out of that
This next clip
Keith f*****-up
Okay
Hahaha
Steve really f***** up
Are you single
He really really f***** up
Everyone who's ever been on the floor.
It's literally impossible friendship out the board that gave Bill Clinton the Fulbright scholarship mostly because Bill Clinton ever
Got a Fulbright scholarship
He was a Rhodes Scholar
But you also worked as a
The clerk for Senator J William Fulbright while he was in college
And I think that's what he's
Before 1967 the Bill Clinton was a clerk
And since Steve was born in 1943 21 years
How old is that point
If he's mixing up like I got him a scholarship at the clerk office or whatever
Anytime the Bill Clinton was formally involved with
Fulbright
Steve would have been 21 years old
Yeah it's impossible that he was a
Member of any board
Been drafted yet
This is legitimately
Dick f******
41 on the board of the Fulbright program
It's a completely different
For part of the state department that he was ever involved
If the Bureau of educational and cultural
He presently this world who touched on this already they gallivanting around the state
Dissection like an interoffice Forest
Scump getting mixed up in whatever historically important
Happen in any Department
Acceptance
Describing something
Didn't have
Namely Bill Clinton
Getting a Fulbright
Set foot in the state department in 1970
Before
Like an intern
As a consult
Bill Clinton had already gotten his law degree from Yale
He'd met Hillary and he moved
To Texas with her to campaign for Georgia
McGovern
There's literally zero chance that what he saying is
Is true and Alex except
To the s*** on question
This is not a small slip-up received Fulbright
If that were the case then Steve whatever
Be claimed that he was on the board of the Rhodes trust in 90
68 which is completely unbelievable
Particularly because according to its full brightness
The state department is involved in the Fulbright program
Eddie knows Alex is stupid enough to know that Bill Clinton got a Rhodes scholarship to go to Oxford
Not a Fulbright
This guy is a pathological liar
Naked did you try and pull something like this off
Your
Help yourself
No you didn't need to add that the little expert
Forever
Senior at
You're an expert
Doesn't do anything and somehow he's in
Do you know why
He can get away with it
Oh well and that is important to me because while I was the premier of China
I led the assault on
What
The f*** out of here
Independence
Call Travis
Little known facts almost to me kind of feels like he's doing this for
Fort Lakeline
Just trying to see how far he can
Can push things I mean
However far you walk
It's crazy to me that he
You tried to sell this on Alex's show
He's on the board of the Fulbright program to Bill and
Alex
Maybe five years
Like we're done
What do you have In the Heat of the Moment you're not able to pull out the resources like Alex doesn't even
But he doesn't know the Bill Clinton did get a Fulbright
He doesn't know these things
Even after the fact
Alex isn't like
I had a check-up on some of this information
The Fulbright program
Good point
Also address one
And it's not clear that Steve is saying that they gave bill
Fulbright
If my criticism is
You gave him this
Or whatever
The timeline is still a huge problem involved in anything
Before the point that Bill had already graduated from Law School
The time it Oxford was well behind
The timeline does not work out
It just does not
There's literally zero chance you would have been involved
If any of this s***
Anyway
This is a complete lie
History does not back this up
It's Steve flippantly throws it out
In order to insinuate himself greater in
These big events that Alex's interested in
CIA plant
It's that b******* it's crazy
Yeah it's it's almost on the level of like
I went back
Can I was reading
Some Play-Doh
You know when were writing about
Uberman
I was
Really reminded
How great
Looking in
I just thought
I'm going to work with Alex
I'm going to give him a chance to look at this I got going
Particular word
Dim
He says it a bunch
Alex Jones
Spooky
Stop it
Is your Show haunted
Talk about things that are spooky
Coast to Coast
I got
Allege
So earlier that Alex has every reason
To know what the consequences of his actions are
I wish I got
I was talking about this
Play up
I have a shower back there
And
Comment
That's a pretty spooky f****** thing to do
Has every if this isn't made up
Like I know right FBI is calling
I don't really believe
Natural
Of the things
Things that are happening
It's completely believable that authorities showed up
Because people have been making death threats
Cialix
Not being aware of the connection between the rhetoric he's been using
We're going over
This direct targeting of the veterans in the Christians is like
You got to follow these demons are you all this stuff
The consequence of that
People on his mask
Message board
Things are going to go after these p
That is a natural reaction
I don't know who the person that this person was targeting is good
Bring it up
B
This is what you would expect to see
Alex can't be naive
Of that
The Secret Service f****** showed up
Even then
They would do it at
It's not like there
We're here because you are the reason
Get your records
These people went on
John Deere website
And he's like oh cool I wasn't
Batman on
Michelle
Increasing the likelihood
Will continue to pray
As he's presenting this There is almost like a
A naive
Disconnect
She's trying to have
Between his actions
And the result of someone posting threats towards
No authorities would show up if it was something the vague
It's a specific threat
And it's a specific threat that someone reported to them
Specific was worth their time to look into
Which means that it's pretty
This is a direct consequence of the rhetoric
He use it
He's trying to pretend that he doesn't understand that in that
That's not the case
Fights
As he's talking about how he's not worried about the Secret Service
Launch is directly into the exact Behavior
It's deathreats from his body
For the children
Alfred
And I feel guilty
Is going to collapse
That's all
What do you think
Expressing in nightclub
I mean what you hear is a guy who think he feels guilty for not
Not kicking down these people's doors
If you are someone who is so inclined to believe the things that Alex says
Add someone who's susceptible to the way he manipulates people's emotions
It wouldn't be hard to hear that be like this is Alex saying that I should be doing
Because Alex
He wishes he was doing those things
This is
Okay
This is absolutely
I think over the course of this episode
Pieczenik
Manipulating Alex and having him around his finger
With this pageant of going to South Korea
And then more importantly
You see this escalation of rhetoric towards Direct
Targeting of
The people who are
Sequences of that
Secret Service shows up about one of his commenters
His response to that is not to take a look in the mirror and say is it possible that the
The things that I'm doing or eliciting this reaction
It's to say
F*** it I'm doubling down I'm going to make it worse
Engage in the exact behaviors that Elizabeth and I'm going to do it so
Does CPS
Sex with your kids
Christine and I feel guilty that I'm not killing them myself
This is unacceptable
This is
I don't think it's accidental
Visit intention
Not be aware of the consequences of Zach
Not understand how this works
He's doing this
For a reason
Yeah
And I can't get away from the phone
That the reason is because
Wendy's like
These things happen he profits
I can't think that he wants
To hurt innocent people
What bison
Crazy people after
I just don't think he's that much of a
Yeah I ate
Possible but it's
So unlike
The only other explanation I can come up with is a business motivation
Yeah that makes sense
He doesn't care that
Right but he does
What mode is the money
He gets
And if they get hurt from the furthering of his narrative
Because if one of his listeners goes out and commit some sort of egregious
Motivated by the things that
Convinces them about
When it comes out
It also confirms all of his marriage is about Heather going to do false Flags
Right there is a
You going to come
It appears that it is you could see it as a comfortable spot
Because people are like giving him a pass at this point
All I all I can see is just
Craft
Crap
There's motivation
And it's
No matter what it is
For me to say what it is
It would be way beyond my paygrade I have no f******
An idea but I do know it's not
Whatever it is is it will
And and just Monster
When I look at
It's stuff like this
I can't escape from
Feeling like
Holyshit even our show
Doesn't
Really capture hub.
Yeah yeah
3 years going over
And to look at this
In the aftermath of
Of Sandy Hook
AMC
How this is
Progressed to the point that it's got to now
Like I do let him off the hook a tiny bit because of how much
Steve is manipulating him obviously
Like
Is Dopey
But it doesn't excuse
Like the other stuff that's going on isn't
The stuff that is actually leading them towards telling people to her
Harass innocent
Folk right is not
Now that's the reason
Joseph
Disgusted
Escalating
Towards
Like intentional radicalization of subgroups
Is not Steve
The part where he is
Coming into accepting the
Hook stop
Is almost certain
Splaturry that went to only one area where this behavior is manifest
Like he's
He's trying to get people to
Go follow VA doctors abortion doctors
People who are
Pastors at churches there globally
There's a lot of people
That he's trying to
To get that treat
Applied to
That was applied
Sandy Hook
Like you said it's a far more Universal thing
Then probably we even
Expected when we set out
Like he's he's legitimately
Presenting the idea that they're in the middle of a civil war already and the answer to that is targeted arrest
People that I
Determined our enemy
Escalating
It's not something that's been
A large portion of
This investigation
As we've gotten into April 8th
Really really
Take a note
Weird
Because that
Far as
Stupid versus
Evil
Kind of
Obviously the motive
The operating
Prophet and
Little bit
Belief
Ghetto
Useful fiction and
Greater real along the way
A means to the end of process
I agree with him is only useful as
Transmitted or transmuted into
They put up bumper stickers they spread the word about the show by my product
You sign up youngevity
I think a bit of it like
I don't think he believes the severity of it
Almost makes me go the opposite direction
The way that he doesn't
Give a f***
Almost to the end
Engaging in literal
Terrorism
It's almost more like
Genuinely believe
Is that we are in the Civil War
And that
There's only one way here
Come out on top
No I don't like that kind of love
Smaller
Kind of stuff
Cultural Marxism white people are the best like I think he believes
Those things
But I don't
Becky believes
This severity of this
Situation that he's
I think he's keenly aware that a lot of that is
Is just a fuse
Hyping up for the explicit purpose
Weather
Drawing in more people
Interesting
Keeping people who are on board
More scared radicalizing the groups that he's already got on board
Like I think those are the goals
To have to know that he's
Just full of s***
About about the scale
But that's just
That I get I have
No idea
Twista
Radicalizing groups
That could also
So let's
Maverick
But it's so dangerous like
Hey we have a great message
Like to really focus on the
The church issues about the church
Here's some of the things you
When you talk to your pastor
About the scripture
There
There is a responsible way to do it and it's not this it's not create the appearance of existential
Threat that's coming to
Wipeout all churches
In America in feet
That's not the way to do it
People
Deal with the
VA issues isn't
To say they're all snitches and never talked to them
But that's not how you do that
People in unhealthy spaces
But keep them in yours
So I don't have any respect
For any of this Behavior
It's just
Service showing up
Is so addictive of how he's aware of the car
Like it's
It's damning stuff
I guess all that's all I can
That's all I can say
See here
I should tell you that about an hour of this episode interviewing this basketball player who's a
Infowars
Representative
No it's not a board it's just a product
Interesting
Any any good videos
No restaurant
No Rex Chapman
Are episode today began on April 3rd
Began
With Alex
Finding out that there was a secret service
Agent who is she
Shifting reptilia
The shape-shifting Reptilian shows up on the show
Hiragana turns out
He's very available
Because he shows up on the 8th
Alex talks about having him
Well damn
Ossuary
That conspiracy isn't about him
You have made that about him
I'm sure they were laughing about it there when I wasn't
It's just Alex
Prove it
In all in all the corners of the world
Except
Now interesting Lee in the interview Alex doesn't bring this up because he knows that if he does Daniel say that
For that it can't be him.
Of course he knows
Because it's still elevates that narrative
Of everybody who supports guns is being targeted
So it's again
F*** this guy
Right
God this timeframe is just
So
Anxiety-provoking
Think it's just
It's so terrifying to look at
Because you know the consequences you know what's coming
I like you see the behavior
That if any of it was
If any of it was more sane
If you just behave like a responsible human being
Didn't lie to people did manipulate people
Ask himself or one f****** second is it possible that Steve is making this s*** up
If you did any of those things
Crises could have been averted
People's lives could have been way better
Like
It's it's Unsinkable like how every single decision had to be bad
For Alex to end up in the position
He's in
And
Against
He
Made every wrong decision
Two times in a row
Nope
You flipped it over every time you were
Every time you hit head
You just flipped it over here like
Two interesting Tales
Another
Pilot
Website
Also on Twitter
We are on Twitter Facebook
You can also go if you wanted to listen
Download
Riverview could do all
But the best
The best way to get
You're going to want to go to the Ravenswood Metra
Okay no
Against going to the Metra I don't take a measurement never
I don't mean that at all
Very nice suburbs
The mattress
Safe deposit
The 13
Select Tire
13 very important number
Chip that open
Pull that up
Hand will reach
The ground giving
Open up alright alright
Stick Drive
Of course
Absolutely
Until then I'm Nido
I'm dzx Clark
Avenidas weather
Holding
Alex