Respectful
Knowledge fight
Money
So Alex
Dot-com
What is the word on the street
You
Everson oppression
In public
Oh man back when I used to work
Groupon
All the way from my
To work
Groupon office
Down down Halsted
Chicago Avenue from my place up in
Exactly where I was living
I did get
Terminal stop of the Halsted bus
Is it intersects with Broadway
Who cares for everybody outside Chicago that nobody what I'm talking about anyway
Bus trip and I would almost fall asleep literally every morning
And every
Return home
Like I feel myself fading
Fall asleep while asleep
You already look like YouTube
Expect you to be on this bus
Let him have it
Have you ever missed Mr stop
I've missed stops
Gorgeous
Strong like negligence
Feels like sometimes it's not that bad
Looks like I got to backtrack a block
20 really weird place at the next time I like half a mile
Yeah it's
I don't know in terms of falling asleep
Public though actually
Church
Public then
Here's a little church story
12 ish
Put in that ballpark
I discovered how cool it is
Lean back in your
Like I realized it non reclining chairs
The church
Service
I went to this like megachurch
Pretty big
The congregation
I was in the back row
It was all like
Stationary chairs
The perfect opportunity
You try out this whole leaning back in my chair thing
It's so I did it and I'll be back
I lose control I just fall backwards
Bright
Everybody is like
400 people in this room.
Athletic
Smooth rolled out of the fall and ran out of the room
I don't know I don't know if anybody as a whole
Open do it with me
Service
Later
That day
I'm talking to my brother
And my brother is like oh my God
Is it could you see that guy couldn't tell if it was me
Famous falling asleep
Pretty embarrassed
And I only know what you tell me about both that's correct
I'm thrilled to get into some of this
Just people have signed up and are supporting the show
Daniel
Ewok
Colin
Thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
But you are now a policy wonk
Garage Dubois
I would I would say that the rhyme doesn't quite work yet I wear that to be the case
Also I think it involves
Salad dressing
We really appreciate that
, wizard of
You are both wonderful technocrat
Heroin
Freakishly large
Thank you so much
Oz, Wizard of
Absolutely
Click the button that says appreciate it
So Jordan I hope to do a wacky one
Episode for today but I regret to inform you that
Has not gone back to Vacaville prison to talk to Mark Richards
Yet
Cheapies that it's going to happen
And then the rest of the episodes are like
I can't do it
She interviewed like a former guitarist of the
Steve Miller Band
About happy life
It's surprisingly not that good it was not something I could really think my
I teach him to let's say
Did he also get into
Aliens
It has to do with like twins have
Telepathic
Connections
I don't know I didn't
I couldn't handle it
Not allowed who don't like a suspicious person
Handle
I can't do it it's so boring I know that people enjoy it and I wish that we could do more of it
If it is so boring
He is the worst for the purposes of making fun of him he's the worst
Yeah
Either f****** desire
I don't
Alex
Is present day
Is developing
Either
Like
The trend of present-day episode
Continuing
I'm in any way that
Compelling of course
And here we're going to be going over April 9th 10
Because
Very important
G happening on our last 2013
Episode
Where they go
I'll say that I found a couple of really wild thing
In this stretch of time
Value
Supposed to like let's say talking about
Abracadabra by the Steve
Steve Miller Band
Alright
Is that a Steve Miller reference
You said I found a couple of wild things okay
I thought you thought that went okay
I apologize sincerely thought that was a joke
It's the Alex
News item
It's been covering in the prior day
Japan and the West Coast in Austin
So
Alex has
Write being in allegedly in South Korea
I keep calling into Alex's show is to be like the media needs
To deescalate this rhetoric it's a load of b*******
This is a psyop
Stupid
North Korea's going to fire missiles tomorrow
But even if you got a psych Warfare expert has been coming on your show telling
Stupid
Complete
Ridiculous
Those reactors
It's so much more of a complicated situation than Alex
He's selling the version
North Korea
Real very serious non-proliferation talks withdrawal
Nonproliferation treaty
Had we had some reason they already had
Better react
Is the light Water Reactor
You can cuz they're much
Harder to make weapon
Great blue Tony
Agreement of selling them
Deactivate
I'd like demolish
Their other reactors
And allow weapons in
So a complicated deal
Image
To be with you
Isn't real
There are similarities in North Korea
Clearly f****** rap
Will you understand
I would possibly make it
Decision that looks
Little bit weird given Global Circle
Stances that surround
But the Optics
And they did
Sell light-water reactor
There's two
North Korea at the
Time
But it's also before the agreed framework completely collapse
Pakistan like was a 2002
The world is different
Sets of circumstances that were in place then
The change
Fairly quickly
That's a good one even though it appears that selling reactors
Is
Nuclear reservation
It was an attempt at
Nonproliferation
And it just
Alex doesn't care
50 old
Peace with our enemies
Until when
Give up something otherwise
You're not negotiating your
You're just sweet already given Aid
Like terms of
To get them to stay Within
The framework
Tibet
I don't know it's just
The subtlety use
What does not really
I think more importantly though like he has this dude who's telling him
Back
In the pharmacy
China candies like what
Strange
Next Club Alex has
Another news item that is
Continuing another trend
That we saw on our last episode
And I think you really steps
In a big old puddle
Shooting facility
So what's interesting here is that Alex has been dancing around actor ideas in terms of
Yeah doesn't believe he's not
Delivering the
Message to his audience that they're actors
But he's blaming the parents
This is worst
It's their fault
Makes perfect sense if they're fall into the only way to solve this problem is to harass them
Send forever until they die
Simultaneously dancing around the actor ideas
Missions there are dead children involved in this
Possibly know what you trying to make
Cuz it's all over the place
In his acknowledgement that they were children that are dead
He's pointing the finger at school
That's the only way I can
Gun control that's against the rules
Whatever it is like even if he believes there or or if it's
It Whatever message
Marketing
It's victimizing another
Wild how bad this is
You expect us to just jump down the road
Is like
Guess what
F*** you
You took the kids to school
Golf course in Lancaster what are you doing golf
That's your fault
You know that that's a weather disarmament Zone
It's insane but he's transmitter seeing her
I completely stocked up
It's weirder than I expected
Is waffling position is
Just as much
Him like
Forgetting whether or not he's lying at this point in time
He might accidentally acknowledge that
It wasn't a false flag the kids actually died
But if you thinking about it
Clear everything was a false flag bulshit
Possible like just like the most cynical approach is
This is Mark
To war
If you're looking at
A perspective that could easily explain
This sort of disjointed Behavior wherever
And then also it's real but it's the government answer parents fault
I don't I don't know what he's doing but
Like if it's accidental it's still manipulative
Gazelle
Baby I'm saying to expect his audience to figure out what the point is
Until the audience
Determines which one they believe in both exist at the same time and then the waveform collapses and guess what
False flag
Alright
So
And the last episode
I mean
Proxy extension
To be like a giant editorial move on his part
CPS is coming
They're also having sex with the kids and they want to deliver the back to you dead or something
So Alex is
Dovetails into that
Narrative
And he decides to go Whole Hog with it
He was a very bad idea for him to do that
Incredibles
Surveillance footage from the dock in Tampa Florida
Michael haykin Anaheim
Play the Air Force veteran engineer's wife
No criminal record
I was just watching
Point well-taken about drugs
Related
I'm with you actually Joshua hate
Isaac
Decided intentionally wrong to make it harder for people to find story about
So what's going on here
Your kids needs to push that
Close to be sort of element
And that's the end up making Heroes out of this Florida couple who kidnapped their own two children and tried to flee to Cuba
So Alex
Music as the state
But I don't make the
Quick snap judge
I need to know more about the
The case before I made it
The decision about what I thought
More information
And before you
Throw out a
So my first red flag was from an NBC Miami article about the couple being found trying to
Philippe specifically part where the children grandfather who had permanent
The police
This wasn't a case where the kids were adopted after strangers or something
He was family members and they were in agreement the Joshua shouldn't have custody of those kids
That's a pretty relevant piece of information cuz your family knows you pretty well
They're all globalist
They're all in on it
The second I found particularly interesting was that
The first time Joshua tried to kidnap his children
Short amount of time after the state has taken away his parental rights
He showed up at that foster home to try and remove them from custody
At gunpoint
You're not some kind of noble KIRO you are you are crazy
Do father-in-law who has custody of the children
Just showing up
To somebody's house
With a gun
Me and you should have your kids taken away
Even if it's trying to get back
That's a different discussion but I don't disagree
Normally when a regular person here's a story like this about a parent who's kidnapped their child
Well I won't disagree is a very strong one
Cases where people kidnap their own children are generally ones that involved
Deeply Disturbed individual
So it's usually best to get a little more information before you
Support a particular person in that kind of situation
Alex doesn't play that s***
He's got parental paranoia to stir up so he paints Joshua hakken is a hero in man that is a horrible decision that he
Reporting is Joshua lost his kids because he was arrested with a bowl of marijuana in a hotel room
Sugar bulshit charge
Well then
Is giant fish bowl filled with weed pipe
Asian one of those
I can't even talk credibly about weed anymore it's been way too long for me
Little bit of weed
The government evil
These kids way
In reality
I'm going to read you hear from the Tampa Bay Times
Slidell police were called to the Holiday Inn where the Higgins were saying on the afternoon of June 17th
After receiving calls about a woman knocking on doors
They found Sharon Hagen 34 years old with quote
Multiple bruises on her body and bumps on her head where it looks like she would be
I heard a child crying through the door of the family's hotel room
Entering they found Joshua hakken sprawled on a bed with his children next to him a heavy odor of marijuana
Smoke hung in the air
Joshua told officers that he would beat his wife Sharon
To quote bring her back to reality
He believed that she was possessed by spirits
Unconsciousness multiple times to rid her of those
Gotcha
Play the biblical literalism
In interviews with authorities the children
Hit her up their mother in their presence
You may have got arrested for marijuana possession
Initially but the reason the situation escalated to the point where he lost
Very serious domestic problems
As a result of their initial call to the hotel room
Which didn't have to do
They got there and found drugs a battered woman crying children
I would have been completely negligent
Find
Also according to the Tampa Bay Times article the police found a large knife
In the hotel room which Josh asked them not to
To take because quote I needed to complete the ultimate objective of my journey
Okay
To complete the ultimate adult large
You better either be going through the jungle
F******
Returning that knife to the f****** princess
So she can
Survivor you better not be hanging out with the wife you admit that you assault
In a hotel room with
No big deal but for people who have other problems it's very bad
Recent murder possibilities
So that you can just allow
360 what happened now this is murder-suicide written all over absolutely
In discussions with the authorities Joshua laid out his
Completely insane theories about how he was subjected to attacks by microwave weapon
And how he was a victim of MK Ultra
You convinced of literally every anti-government conspiracy theory UK
Can think of it was ultimately
Ultimately
To 15 years in prison for kidnapping
His children opportunity
Which resulted in him ranting about.
That's for about 30 minutes
They gave him the opportunity to speak
I mean nobody Oscars
I honestly think also if
We're looking at this from
What's best
I kind of agree with his defense attorney that is like going to prison is not going to help him at all
The hospital said he got 15 years in
Prison yeah I was like
Well that's a bad idea
It seems to confirm a lot of his anti-government paranoia and stuff
I think one of the reasons that he did end up
Pizza
Prison was because there was some dissent
Voices about
His legal insanity
Some people who talk to him said that he was
Competency
Sam trial because of
Agreement there's Xbox
If I were the judge probably would be like
I don't know I would honestly think
Especially after this
Diatribe you probably help him
Might be
Cuz clearly drugs are involved
I don't know I don't know
If he was if he was a school shooter Alex might have a thing that he was on
Maybe he refused all drugs
Whenever he was
Holding
Another reason of
Be pointless to put in
Prison is busy
He's not going to
No no no not going to take
I don't know if that's part of the reason for why they wanted to go to hospital
Air on the side of like
Put him in a federal
Yeah I said where I doubt prison guards are going to
You take your meds today
I have no idea
What you have here is very
Violent
But I understand
I'll reach you from the Tampa Bay Times article
Twice
Survive attempts on his life
Can foxes Bow Down
He said okay
Icarus
Muhammad to the Shiite Muslims
I am the Joshua of the tribe of Judah I am the pahana the white friend of the Hopi
I am the one written about in prophecies
Okay
So all right
This guy's a little out there
This is the story of a heroic father who wanted to reclaim his children from the evil stage
Confront him
Abuser kemetic insane levels of domestic
It's staggering to imagine what those kids were going through in that household
And what they went through when they were kidnapped
We just consider
In order to kidnap the children Joshua actually
Tied up their grandmother
To get away with
And when the kids were rescued they were badly sunburned
For being out on that boat that was headed to Cuba
This is a seriously traumatic event
Talking to them about this is like
What we're doing is pretending it was a vacation
2 + 4
Make this not be evident experience as a trauma
And I think that's great
But even so I don't think there's going to be a fingerprint of like
For sure there's going to be some
Yeah but the reality doesn't matter.
It's all about sex
And here we have a story that he can turn into being about the
The evil government taking
Give a f*** about what he's actually doing this guy
It's important domestic violence
I like I like how he has all of that with
But just so that he was tired of it
And so we went and got him
The end of the story for him
That doesn't sound right no because also prior today
Yeah but still
I would totally understand that
If you were absent from his coverage of the story
Would be like
And I understand the appeal of that line of thinking a
And that rhetoric
Inseparability of Perinton
The child is archetype
I'm like let's say if some
Gang of
The mafia
If it's cool
Like proper recourse
In terms of like systems
Where
You can get
Your parental rights back with the mafia they don't have those
Because Noster do you have hearing
Once a year to see if they can give competency hearings with
The dawn or whatever
What's the date
I realize that
Like it really is just it's a part of the Alexs
Continuing coverage of the globalist want
This
Weaves perfectly into it so you don't care about that
Details
For me to like be okay that's why I
Recovering
For the more he kept talking
The more I realized there was another reason
There we go
Joshua hakken was an info Warriors
A reporter who showed up at his house
Infowars bumper sticker on the guys mailbox
So Alex
As every reason
I'm to protect protect the brand
What's interesting about this
Cuz like if Alex ran into this guy on the street
This fan
I got to go I like you I think
Cool wall
Pink and painted a mural on the wall of us
Going to be in prison
And his story can be manipulated and used
To support whatever narratives Alex has
He's already Niro
What sticker on the mailbox was the mail person
And I walk to that
Mailbox every
Because there's no way on Google
I think that might be illegal or a bomb or something
Pop out. Don't tread on me
Is a secret any disruption of the mail service regardless of who does it
I believe that
McKay's
It's one of those things I get technically
As I recalled a felony to like
Smash mailboxes
Like petty larceny
They didn't have weather rain nor sleet nor hail nor Infowars
I think Infowars bumper
Still open
Little bit more about this situation
This is really interesting
Because he's tries to read an article about it
Listen very carefully because there is a
Certain point
Were you stopped reading
And I know where that point is
Maternal grandparents
Michael Hagan
Goes on from there
You know what is Elijah's
What kind of a f*** you f*** you Alex from 2013
He tied the grandmother up
But he shouldn't have it
Listen to this and see how in the middle of us
Because he interferes with the narrative
Beat up the grandmother maternal grandparents
Michael Hagan
Goes on from there
Run
AR
Theory that he is 100
Reading comprehension elac bigger picture
Text Gil
In terms of read
He has a f*****-up version of literacy
Just the actual words make out
There is no preparation
But he doesn't know the story at all before he starts reporting it
Because
You would have known that like
This paragraph
Send to the fact that this dude tied up a grandma
It's not great
God that was really f****** about
If my God he accidentally told right back at ya
I do like a good
Real-time pun
You know like
Nope not going to win that battle
It said it's pretty impressive like those editorial skills
Like not this is gasolinera
So we get back to a little bit
Sandy Hook talk here
Alex is pretty much like spinning his wheels
Trying to find ways to attack
The mainstream media story about
Without going to
Too far with it
And you find something that he thinks
Is
Like indicative of
A connection
Between so many of these school shooting
That lends it
Self
Maybe it's all
Event
Ant-Man
This is crazy
This is a type of
Harrison
So is argument here is relying
Conspiracy theory that Adam Lanza's mother work
Work for DARPA I remember that one
Now I have no idea about the Creed
To tell you
I want to give you that qualification and I we can take
Camaro allow you and the audience
To make their own conclusion
So like I said
Noxitril
Nancy was unemployed haven't been awarded a nothing alimony for her divorce to live without a job
I can find no sources
That I find credible arguing the Fancy works for DARPA
But I can't find one that I don't
Define credible
Conspiracy sites the claim Nancy move to New Town in order to work for DARPA
And without exception they all basements on One Source
But some of the post you'll find out message boards will just cut off the attribution and make
Acclaimed but it all Tracy
Is back to 1
Flights
This source is an alleged report distributed to the crib light by the FSB
Russia's intelligence
Sure
Vine of course
What would be the Russian intelligence
Okay
The earliest reporting and I can
Confined on this is dated December 15th 20
12 just act
There's no leaks
I can find it there's no substantiation
And for this outside of it just being asserted
On a website
Called what does it mean.
In order to gauge that's lights
Check out their front reporting
And here are some of their headline
Michael Hagan
Russia mobilizes 12,000 troops after a snake like alien craft communicating with mysterious Interstellar
Object attacks
Norway
I remember when the right now right now
Top headlines
All right there's one from a little while back
US army takes over Pentagon after unus Navy smuggles Isis snipers into America 2
Kill Trump
Okay
The type of ridiculous world I want to live
Cuz I'll tell you right now
If the Army and the Navy are currently in a
Death battle
Controls the Pentagon a high-profile football game
Why are you
Cuz you're the Navy
I'll tell you what we don't have time to talk
Talk about Sean Spicer
That's what I'm saying
That's what I want
This is full of b*******
Yes it is
If you look through the content is posted on that site it really feels like almost all of the stories are over
Berleypro Russia
And seemed to start by citing unseen
Report allegedly circulated
In the Kremlin
And this is suspicious
Now in the ensuing days after this
Report was published on September
12 the information made its way onto message
Sports website
And sites with seemingly non insane name
But are insane
EU time
Dotnet
There's absolutely zero doubt that Alex either
Information he's repeating
From this site or someone
Reposting this sites
It's absolutely the route of the theory
From which all the branches grow
Is relying on real Russian until
Reports to make their site really remind me
It's possible but it also seems super unlikely to me
Is run by a real weirdo conspiracy theorist to relies on
Claiming
Ffsb reports
That you know no one can confirm or deny or anything like that in order to
Create the validity and The credibility
Of whatever bulshit you're putting out
Decided alleged to be run by a person named Sue
Faal
Whose actual name is Sister Maria Theresa
What is he
All is a title that's given to a person after they're elected to this
A position of leadership in a group known as the order of sorts of fall
This woman is the
Maria Teresa is the
The lion of sort of Falls
After her election in 2007
I don't know I couldn't I couldn't get that information
I think it's b*******
That is truth behind
Many folks on message boards believe this to be a cover and that's a real author of the site is a guy named
David Booth
Little people
It's a lot of bulshit
Is genius hell and this is not a good source of information
If you're relying on this you are in bad shape
Love it
Get bored
So you like to write fanfic
He's got all these secret intelligence reports from the Kremlin
So why not
I love it
See I don't think it's a Russian intelligence
I don't I don't think so
They would do a much better job with the site which looks like
Disaster
This is really important to me though
Is true
I'm legitimately the only place attic
Becoming from is this website
We can see it when we look at this April 2013
. Alex is the processor
So changing his mind and his coverage about
Information put out by the 73rd sorcha fall
This is nuts
No one is convincing him of this
No one is come on the show and told him this piece of information
Introducing it to the show
Himself
Incredible
That's really fun
Locked up
The only two possibilities
Here I think this covers all possible realities
Once he got the information directly or second-hand for the site himself
I thought it was cool 42
Someone told
Before repeating it on air
Yeah
Dispute is embarrassing
But this lack of any kind
Standard for disseminating
Information is also
Really
And we're seeing
Right here was like
This lack of editorial
Standard in any way
Just really
What he's he's
Because he wants to save the Globus want to take kids he's defending this
Completely
Insane domestic
Violent
Weirdo
Mailbox
Only because he wants
The cast was fishing about
Sandy Hook
And claimed that Adam Lanza's mom works there.
From a fake
The Russian intelligence report on a
Completely insane website
Write it almost
Having
A thing that you want
And then
Searching the internet
Scouring for
Any
Possible proof
Say wrong
Evil dumb
As I like to call it
Right wing
That's one of the reasons that I started out this show with a like
Openness
Do Alex being right about something
To prove him wrong
About
It just
F****** stupid
I think now it's just become habit
Two black guy
It's like it's Soca
Consistent
He's just wrong about all this s***
I'm setting out to debunk it right
Not
Just that situation
If you are
Doing any
And you have already decided
What the
Endgame
And you will ignore literally
Anything else
Along the way in order
You're you're just
The pointless
Like any study any study that paid for by the Koch brothers
Edinburg
Is all built around the idea that we saw this little weird bit of data
So recontextualizing so we can
That's all we want to do we don't want to find out any
Anything that we don't want
The small version of that is Alex
Having a story about a guy
Cuba
Has the kids of honorable
There's a few years so that mean
The entire f***
Can government
Science established
Is trying to lie to us in order to get
So Alex is really mad
About Obama
Meeting with the Sandy Hook families
Thinks that they're using them
Crops in order to
Achieve their gun-control agenda
Taking the gun
Richard now
Check my watch it
How we doing
Now
So here is Alex talking about how Obama uses
Jamaica's arguments
University poll government-funded poll
Registration for car
Cool
If you get a really interesting
Glimpse into how Alex
Twist things on multiple
Levels
Multiple
If you will
The first movie saying that the stats Obama cited are from a government
Pole
Even further impugns the numbers by saying that they're out of line with every other Pole
Contextualize
Actually just registration
Application
These are all things he's doing without providing any evidence or support
Nothing
He's just attacking
Statistic not doing any work he needs
To do in order to receive it
As for calling the polo government poll that's amazing
Attack the polls that Obama were using workout
Is just controlled by the government in full-scale war
Shared reality
Its measured by statistical analysis
Just found that support for all of Obama's planned initiatives to deal with gun violence was overwhelmingly pause
91% would vote for criminal background checks on all gun sales
82% would vote for increased government
Spending for mental health programs for the Youth
75% would vote for an increase criminal penalties for people who buy guns for people who couldn't
Casa background check
60% result for the reinstatement
These are specifically neutrally
By not connecting to plan
To Obama in there question
They probably drop it I don't know I haven't I didn't see any poll
But every time
Calling it Obamacare versus APA where there was differ
User to neutralize that effect is
Is vitae
Just saying hi to you
You support this position as opposed to do Sports Obama's position
And that's overwhelming score for all of it
That's very hard for Alex to deal with
Extreme outlier
Answer the question of whether or not this result is in line with other poultry
I don't know what he's talking about
Pulling huge support
A couple of things to discuss
Galloped
Historical trend
And one question I've asked him.
1990s quote
In general do you feel that laws cover
Bring the sale of firearms should be made more strict less strict or kept as they are now
In the entire history question 2%
Has never been more than 14
And is regularly less than
More strict has only been under 50% 7 times
The entire history of Poland
That's never been lower than
143 Percy
Their pulses
Support for background checks
Universally over a long span of
We live in a
So it seems like a very large majority of people
Support something
We live in a republic
Corrupt
I mean
I don't know
It was just a raw vote of the public
Easily compare those results
Pagalpan
Historically the other polls you see that it's not an outlier at all
Quinnipiac's June 27th
Study found 94% approval
For background check
Washington University's July 20th
84%
There's literally nothing I can find to support the idea that Alex's
Namely that there's credible polls showing lower support for background checks for gun purchases
Which is why you needs the last
The reframing of background checks just to be about regulation
Occasion
And honestly I can't do anything with that kind of paranoia
You guys run wild with that s*** if you want to
Like you shouldn't have to do a background check when I apply for a job that's just letting the government know where I work
Me fired
You shouldn't do a background check when I try to rent an apartment that's just a government where I live
In life there are times when submitting to a background check are pretty understandable and necessary
If your real problem is that you think it is it some kind of registration that you should be politically moving to help shape
That the background checks take
Replacing
You should be pushing for background checks that are not
Kept on file
You should be advocating for the background checks to be as anonymized as possible with no data retention
What you shouldn't do
If you're thinking person
Is pretended background checks of the same thing as confiscation
Because ultimately what you're doing then
Is actively supporting people who can't pass background checks getting guns
If that's what you're all about
Cool
But don't in favor of responsible gun owner
Worship then because you're not
You're lying you're literally in favor of irresponsible
Nihilist
But also
So why try and knock
Get shot that doesn't make any sense
Also I'm saying like
Like don't try to pretend you're in favor of law-abiding honest
Good people only
Guns you're a roading a system where there could
B Jackson Control
You can't
Possession there are less than 10% of the rest of the country
You have to lie
And pretend that you're in the majority in order
Enough of those
Idiots into following along with you
It's just
Like a good bit of Alec
It's kind of like a
About various
L audio
Games to believe the Joshua
Hero
Particularly
No lying about things
Passing along the idea that
He worked for DARPA based on
Dumb blog
So this clip
Welfare people
One of those
Is more important
Men should have more power than the
Also I wandered for Kerry Cassidy conference is the name of her country
Stop one always brings up is this idea that it's
It's been proven that gun
Reduce crime
Which we have established
Previously in multiple episodes
Pacific
A statistic that
You always say
He brings that up in this club and then I want to talk about it a little
Stupid know what they're doing
That's one of Alex's favorite talking points
That's what I've heard him Scream by pretty consistently in anytime. Of the show that I've listened to
That idea 9% drop in violent crime
Cause
People having more gun
When it comes to Houston
The part of this is true is the time span of 1993 to 2013
Private gun ownership numbers wife
I thought violent crime rate went down
Both of these are correct
There's no reason to believe that just because two things happened around the same time as each other or even at the same time as each other
They're somehow related
Correlation equals causation
There's a whole website dedicated to really weird Cole related phenomena that
Guy named Tyler vision
And something's like
There's a 99.26% correlation
In the divorce rate in Maine
And the per capita consumption of margarine
That's a very strong correlation
There's also a 95% correlation
Super 1999 to 2010 marriage rate in Kentucky
And the number of people who drowned after
For falling out of the fishing boat
Yeah no
When you get married in
Sooner or later you're going to drown
Robert sooner or later wouldn't make it so immediate the time will match them animal
Go on honeymoons
You wrote a book about this called spurious correlation
Which if nothing else is Dumont
Two numbers run similar
Or appearing we correlated
You're passing it doesn't mean anything
To do with each other
People who study the gun
Violence drop
Gun
Prime drop in gun ownership
I'll be point to other variables that
Explain the drop-in possible post 1993 which was
What major factor is at
The post-world War II Baby Boom generation had just passed
The age brackets
Marimo statistically likely to be high crime
Right the Baby Boomers just stop killing
Alorica practice partially attributable to block of population
Aging out of the high crime
. whatever is 16 to 40
Like that
Passport
When you're older
Less likely to
Commit violent crime
Just hired another element is at the
Economy was in
A natural byproduct of that is a dropping
Cry
Other folks have theories By the Drop is partially fueled by increased access to abortion
People were able to control their families
I also touched on that
Exposure to lead
Is another big factor that be
People going to
They are proven
The people that put forth with x
Study these numbers
Other not-so-great factors
Like the soaring rates of incarceration for non-violent offenders
Like that's just a huge population of people who are now in a controlled environment
You have another telephone
No it's terrible you have a net less population
So what else has failed to do in anyways take these other factors into account
Preferring instead to just take this to
Statistically crime drop 49%
And appeared that gun ownership has risen
Side of the guns with a reason that the rate
This is how serious people approach stats
If they have
Looked at the issue
Conclusion for Metallica
To come up with
Most notably in that 27
19 Stanford study that showed that states
The pass right to carry laws
Experience 8:30
18% increase
Recent violent crime
So I don't I just
Addicting
Essential piece
Is this
Is when you look at what Alex is doing
He's taking the correlation in applying cause a
And he does know work it anyway
To establish that
He doesn't have any study
To show like
So it is true that you know
Morgan equals less crime
People who looked at it
Trump
The relationship between
Morgan
And less crime
They look at it from the standpoint of
Rising crime
Makes people buy more
Right
They look at it from almost like
Their analysis
6 shows almost
The opposite with Alex
Is the crime motivates people to buy gun
As opposed to
Gun buying leads people to do less crime
Right
So
All I'm saying is Alex's
Just being fast and loose
Dodging around
Being shipped
It just it just flies in the face
Of the one
Truth that I don't
I don't see ever changed
Which is that
The more
Like
If you make
The means by which
To do something more prevalent
It makes it more like
If you give people more guns
More like
That gun violence
Is going to have
That's that
Forever
That is human
Reality
And to argue
Do the opposite of that goes against
Something that's
Dental in Bayside
Inhumans and I will never trust any
Okay it's just not
Drawing your Line in the Sand
So Alex Theory and that is that Obama
Staple gun
Yeah cuz Alex
Arby's
Send it
The world
They needs to disarm them
Because they're winning
Hi Galaxy
Not yet
That's why Obama needs
New World Order
So
I mean
Throughout time
Just be like
This is at
Kind of
Mentality
Very consistent
This time.
Especially recited
The election season
I think
Consistently afterwards
Like you've been very regularly like
Like we are on the
Best all the f****** time
You're seeing massive ramp-up of that
I like those of the Battle of the Bulge
It's happening this is the full of salt
That's the clip I want to
Or anybody
Who buys into
No we should reach across the aisle at once we return to normalcy will be able to
Listen to that clip
No one's region
That's the weakest link
They're not
Listening
Listen to Obama.
Vicky
Belle yellow brick column of Liberator
Maybe if you were kids
Call Ray
That's the reality of it
Maybe
Maybe it'll change
Corn Pops
Story was pretty good
So Alex
Singled out
That's because I I know
Probably pretty difficult and I don't know if I could actually even
Convey this in
Like even if I played you a hundred clips
I'm not sure that I could fully expressed to you
The ramping up as a
Extremist
It's going on in this April time
Maybe even a little bit in
To the end of March
But it's very specifically happened
Right here in the time frame that we're talk
It is
Very easy to hear the clip like the last one we played we're like we're Rising we're the best
Obama is not my president collaborator
You could be like
Stop Alex's
Reliant
But I have
I have to stress
If you listen to me
These episodes
In their entirety you do notice
That this is getting much more extreme
There isn't a application
And Alex
Even
Explicit
About the fact
That he is getting bored
In this neck
Equip one of the things that I think is really important
Is
The Alex
Hi
That growing
Extreme now
I need to come up another word for it but
That growing radical he has on his show
With
Sales
Which is one of the contention that
The people in the same
Sandy Hook lawsuits are making is the profit off of this sort of cover
If you listen to the
Text Cliff you get some indication
Because there's no
He's also set another times like
He is going more like
He's getting more intense
He's saying you got to pay me
You got it
Gotta Buy my shoes
If you was my ability to go 100
10% in this
No Holds Barred
I think there's
It's interesting
To me because
The
Presenting
Episode
It doesn't justify
That's the one that's the one area that is light to legalize
But if there were like
VA doctors or
Ministers who were harassed by Alex Jones
Just fans
I could see them soon
Him for what he did
At this. Just as easy
Yeah I like it
It's a broader Behavior that's going on
And it just so happened that maybe
Caught on
Yeah it's people who wanted to harass in Target
Don't
Any way to get around
The fact that he's
That Ram pickup
Controls of
That's one thing that I
Thought about what
With the lawsuit
Because when we're talkin
Sing about Zach
That's where we getting
Correlation cause a
I don't know how you can
Can prove that
Specifically the
The Sandy Hook stuff
Increased his
Prophet right I agree
Like obviously
Talking about Sandy Hook
2 sails
In the same way that
Talking about
Joshua
Athleta sale
You know part of a concerted strategy
They were one of the victim
One of the targets
Of this broader
Right thing that's going on
With his bucket we're at the Battle of the Bulge
Roxanne
Rapper in the middle of the Civil War
Yeah I don't I don't know how you sort of differentiate
Other than
To take it as a
Totality
I I suppose that means
But not only do
Doctors in
VA officials
Morally imperative for them to join the class action
Yeah
From what I understand
This is the only reason that
Extends the statute of limitations is that Alex brought up
These things
Her people are able to
Vesuvio
Using
Stuff from Beyond the statute of limitations to inform things that he said within the
Positive that all of that applies
To the
Myriad group
If that Alex's
Working with you right
That you could make an argument complains about the glitterbug mainstream globalist churches all the time
And all the like there I don't know if specific
VA doctors
Legally literate people I think
Be tough for us to know what concert
Fat bike
It's important
You look at this and it's very clear
They are on the level
He is he is
Trying to benefit
From
The behavior that led
To the
Treatment of Sandy Hook
For this Behavior
Profit-based
So
You know
You can make an argument that
Internal documents
Yeah
Despite the fact that it is a more Universal behavior that we're talkin about it is also still
Specifically
Focused
And
Alex plays video of Sandy Hook
Victims talking about their
And
Because
It's just family members
Saying this is horrifying
We don't
But here's Alex's response after
This video
So first of all Peter Parker Spider-Man
You talk about Robbie Parker
Continuation of now it's okay for him to
To make fun of this grieving father
As opposed to call or calls
Suggested
Coach
Is right that's the your toe into the water of the actor shed
He's he's
Teasing
He's getting around that
Logically
To be coaching
If they are coach
You have a reason until
An escalation
This cruelty
Making it okay
To look at these people as not victims
Make it look make it look at
Okay for the audience
Them as people Worthy
People worthy of
Making fun of
There
Implying that they're fake
Emoji
Like that is
Exactly what we're talkin to
That's exactly the behavior
That's the early stages of the we've been looking for
Entire time
Absolutely it's happening right in front of our eyes
I know he seems like the things
Seem to be leading to it are
Obama talk to them
Steve pieczenik is coming around
He read
A dumb blog they claimed it had a Russian intelligence report
By sorcha faal
It's very sad
It's a really shity soup
Super villain
It's really hard
But one thing you would expect for
Right I mean
He studies all the time
Vino's the globalist
Playing backwards
Forward
Upside down
All of it
Do you expect that you would know exactly what he's talking
He'd remember all of his talking
Remember his narrative
He knows the books he's read
But
Unfortunately
Hundreds of shots they want to give kids
This is a good demonstration of how little Alex cares about his own bulshit
He's claiming the John P Holdren's book ecoscience
Discusses diet injections and injunctions
Control the public
And I really honestly think this is a result of him never reading the things here Aunt by reading all the time
He's talking about isn't a reference to Eco science
The textbook
Jean-p holdren Road
That's a line that I was always misuses from Bertrand Russell in his book the impact
Society
We talked about there's a bunch of times like
Alex is just taking that line entirely out of town to
Russell was talking about the really bad stuff that could come up if for instance
The Nazis have been more scientifically Advanced as a dictatorship
He's not advocating for the
But because he's discussing them Alex's decided
Gridley actually saying
F****** stupid
I guess what I didn't have to look any of this up to
Remember I heard him talk about it
Do you miss match references body
Even care about getting things right
Doesn't care either
Bucket
Yeah
If you have like this
Really
You like
Revolutionary
World-shaking
Information that you've uncovered
But a plant
Depopulate
Planet and kill off everybody
Seems like you know what you're talkin about.
Keep your ducks in a row
I need.
Communication
Easier to get away with
His listeners
General
Looking for like
Emotional
They have no interest in the intellect
They just want to understand
And have their anger in
Fear and paranoia
Mirror
As opposed to being like
I need to think about what this guy
No I just need to get the general Vibe of how he's
That's what I really
I don't need
I'm not going to I'm not going to do homework for Infowars
Yeah it is
Interview with
How about the evils of exit
He's not the one know the faces
Sisters the one who look
Yeah right
Is another guy album recording
Elbow
Forgot I'm really glad Anthrax came up
Thursday
Tickets still available
Probably
Is not a good interview it's pointless I don't want to I don't want to
Listen to any of it
It's just the standard.
But also they're not
Extreme masala
About the vaccination evils of the
Depopulation
Silence
I don't know especially from candy or what
Also I don't want to bring this up
Because
I looked into them a little bit
And
They might
Might be a really bad dude you don't want to get into it
Look that up yourself and feel like
Specifically shooting to be having on his show
Maybe other things
So out starts ranting about school shooting
Again this goes back to what I was talking about about
Tying
Height
Extremism with the
Desales
There is a very
Queer things happen
And it wasn't happening
Before but this is kind of new to this April 9th episode
Easter
Trying to take
The
Heightened elevated
Nature of what he's doing
Push it toward
Marketing Opera
Countries
Well guess what we're onto you this is boomerang
Health Challenge
World Order
Saying
Third Kind of juxtaposition
Of what he's doing
Yeah normally like
Also I'm trying to get everybody healthy
Buy our product
I will do anything for people to buy more
Please
Clearpath
These ideas
Also you can see that it's at
No but they're coming coming into the modern form
Census of
What would you call a modern Alex pivot covid-19
Now we have these
Teacher salary
50%
I forgot
Pretend like
My adverb
Okay I understand
That is
Wisely
For you to do
Didn't quite work on April 9th Alex has Mike
Come in
Health Ranger
Again
Yeah
Normal transfer the health Ranger detriment on
I don't think it's really that
Pinterest
Conversation
The number of points
Which
Clip
I think it exposes
So much about Alex Jones
That's so revealing
Oh yeah
Is a completely unrelated field
Sabine on medicine
Then by God I'm going to be well-versed in don't know why
Got coming in as an expert
Amazing arrange Alex's guest tab so long as the subjects are all weird and
Completely speculative
Yeah
Eddie Izzard
Disagree with too much
Coin may be a good thing and they support
Decentralized currency
But they're skeptic
In the clip where you can hear Alex speculating that the central bank
Some Federal Reserve there in the pups
Pump-and-dump with Bitcoin
How's life is fun with it
But I think it's important
His reason for his
Expiry I think like the enemy
If I was the enemy I do
That's so fucken reveal
The sport is conjecture that the FED is artificially inflating Bitcoin to bring up Adventure crash
But he feels like that's the
It's because he's decided what the enemy is how they think
How they operate
I need the sided
But that's what he would do
He was them
When you take into account that is enemies are imaginary
And all his primary sources don't say what he thinks they do
You really have to consider
Comes up with his ideas about the globalist
Shear imagination
He's imagined a villain
And you just as what would I do if I were them
I really felt like this was what he was doing for a long time but I've never heard him so clearly
Express that mentality as in that life clip
Like the global don't want to depopulate the planet
The Alex would if he were there
But Alex would if he were them
All the shoes Alex
Projecting
Everything is in his head
Dance is all nonsense
Welyn
But that's
Few times in the past.
How revealing it is
Say what the enemy
Doing
Because like
Like how many times
Do right-wing people are
Are there like
The Democrats are
Stealing boats in there right
Steel Alexa
None of that actually
But every voter suppression
An effort every attempt
Original
Crisco box
Continue tags
Like all of that
You see
Oh well
Describe
To us in order to just
Defy why they do with it
Because I just
Honored tradition
Two boys I like hitting yourself
It's pathetic
Probably
So we get to the there's not much going on here cuz I'll be honest with you
About
2 hours
Of this show
Is David Knight
Jakari Jackson
Coming in
Like to co-host with Alec
Because they do a gun control rally
Okay
You're going to try and take my gun
Type sign
Councilman Mike Martinez
Of Austin
Got on the mic
Attention
There is no gun,
Station going on
I keep that side cuz you're going to need it later
That's a good move
I guess right
He's showing his cards
Is aiming for eventual
Is about
Took a little bit
Unearned
They try and create a victim out of this guy who's older
Messiaen the train say that he wasn't trying
To get attention
Victim of
For poking him
I don't know it's a long time to talk about
It's Mike martini
In a weird way that I
I've never heard his f******
Before I have no idea
This guy is now just like he's one of the one of the leaders of this movement
Attention by the media given to any the local news story
Actually I've known forever 100
F***
It's just
Laborious
Getting through it would be no good
David Knight is boring
What do you think he's doing
Jakari Jackson
He's on board with Infowars s*** like
Q
Is amazing
Jakaria's voice
Radio voice
Fantastic also fairly boring
Still a kind of young
So he can handle the Nightly News
And s*** but being on Alex's show itself or this clearly way more listeners
Right
You seem to be a little bit like
This is the big leagues right
And that's very weird
Enjoy Alex
That much
Kind of
Like they don't seem to cut into his bulshit which is
How this episode is going to end
But it doesn't make
We're like really into
Justin Conte
It was
F****** top
So much David night talk
Can't believe
Like 25
Still see him being
Monotone
Understand everybody
Call because there's a strategy
It's trying to penetrate other markets that Alex doesn't really have access
You're exempt
To get old pee
Your attempt
To get people who don't like how Alex gals all the time okay
You filter your content through David night in a boring prom
Loud
Somebody's somebody's like I want I want to racist as the presentation
Milquetoast
Destroyer in the mix
Because you needs
Somebody was kind of
Theoretically interesting to the youth younger set
That's
Alex
And Alex
As we start up here with
I just want to give you a little bit of a
Atone
Alex
Chester
If you want
Okay
Threatening
Glenn Beck
But love it
But the waves
You got to listen to every every word okay
It
So
Stupid
Call Des Moines
And
He's talking about
Infowars.com
Newport.com
So all the time but Alex
Who's crazy
Play no reason to assume that
Gwen didn't say this every 100 press
Glenn Beck
Is plagiarizing my material and he's not
Absolutely not 100%
I don't know
Cuz I haven't listened to the show actually said that Source but I guarantee you 100%
Riverview
Also he Alex like his whole business model on infowars.com is like
Using other people's articles he does like where the article came from
He doesn't have permission
Post in hole these articles that came out
Not too long ago
Tubac he was
I'm trouble for it but it was like
Entirely
Instantly does that
From various
NewsHour
Without
But I don't know I don't care I feel like
If Glenn Beck said
Who cares
If he's
Also
Covering the story
As reported by another outlet and Alex
Just thinks it's
I'm covering Infowars
I don't care
If he's ripping off before
Also don't care right
I'm struggling to find an angle with
The only angle is Alex being like he ripped me off I know this
Maybe
Reset it and I didn't
Is the overconfidence the admission of
I don't know
Guitar ER in studio for like
Most of the time
Boring
The only things that I really think are in
You staying are this clip
Where Alex
David Knight
What he think
About Sandy
Okay
Aurora
False flag
Suspicious
Exactly
Okay
What
What is this
All right what is this Alex
What is he saying
Which actor
It's one week before the UN votes
So you want an
Bright
You know you got to have somebody that Appeals
Benicio del Toro
Usual Suspects
I would
Say this isn't
Good
This is an indication of a bad mindset
I would agree
David Knight says it was a false flag
Event unprompted Alex's they should have got better actor
Now
It is my
Gallatin life
In my
Steak in this whole thing
Overleaf air-to-air
Because it is unfair to everybody
When I hear this
There's two problems
In fairness
Is that the better actors
They should have chosen victim
Family members who had better Act
Skills in order for them to convey the gun-control message
That could be what he's trying
To stay
Give him
If
In this time.
Clarified immediately I would even
When are on the side of life
Fine still not good
Not good
They should have got
Better actors
That one
Balanced
Hard because again you could
You could fall back behind like I've never heard Alex
A defend his position by saying like
Father probably victims family members who were better actors
That's what I was trying to say
I've never heard him use that defense
Ruby Tuesday
An interpretation that could be made of
But
No one was the interpretation
Know if you're listening
You hear him say it's a false flag
Entirely
There were actors are all after actors means they were all
Whether or not
Yeah I think it's far less mature
Absolutely
To nail down
Thoroughly
No
Also
Court of law isn't
Nesterly best place to
Try and parse
The experience
Listening
Listen to all of this I can
I can tell you the experience of it
Jointed
It's
Confusing
Trying to figure out what point
He's exactly trying
If you were someone who bought
Hearing that would be very
Clear what he is
Trying to say
Where is other times there's there's so much like ambiguity
Fourth
Of whatever
Map of
The Carlton
He's directing towards
These people it's your fault you took
It's the school
Mocking Robbie Parker
And his friends
Conference
You can just see the trend going there
Directions to die
Fuel
Give the benefit of the doubt
Easy
Expressing their
I'm at the court of law is the worst Park
You can't be like
Your honor I submit
27 Hunter
Turn hours of Alex
Content from multiple arrows
So you can have a
Full Count
Text on what if
Exactly this means
As opposed to what it is that you
Think it means an illegal
Definition
There is two
Contact around
.
Where is b*******
And he be like
Write it down
So Alex
I think
More fun having
Dakari
Studio then
Either of them are happy
Is the most
Clip
Where Alex says they're actors which is substantiv Lee important
And then
Spiritually important
I think Alex is employed
Do not like her much
More fun than anyone that has to interact with Alex
Cesium save experiencing life in a way that no one around him in
Kind of indicative of that vibe
Shawn and Aaron Paul and Alex guest Pelletier
A day-long woman
Stop it
I'm stuck in Folsom Prison
What the f*** is going on
Potato salad
And he doesn't f****** Star Wars impressions
Fat is the most
That is the most like
Interesting
Yeah it's been in
Completely unfounded and I think the two of them guitari both have
3 * 2 wanting to
To do better
Feel like they want to actually
Do something
It does feel like they
They're trying to build up almost like a real
Can go to
I don't know if
Or just like trying
Have have actual like waves
We are actually reporting something
Even with the if it's within the context
Infowars
Narrative propaganda right still like we're respectable
Alex knows where the money is
Nathan is Goofy
Well that's what I'm saying if you're working it into info
And your aspiring to do real Journal
You are not working
You're not looking
To retire in
You know what I mean
Do you think you can
God bless everybody who thinks
Good for you I wish I had your level
I really do
Gorgeously you might heard from Alex
Play come back from break
And the vibe
Darth Vader
So surprised
Is the Diplomatic ship
Actually really not bad
That's really not bad
Haha
Blood pressure
It's not bad
300 times out really not that I've heard Alex do Impressions 300 time
Service
Yeah that was that was
Twice as good as burn
I would say at least twice as good as we're on a f******
Show that are actors
He's these laying out this b******* about the Josh
Nonsense like
This is Don sentmanat it like this
Existing in the same spaces
Is it surreal
You guys have some bro downtime are you doing impressions and goofing around like
And
Now we're going to do a great bit from The Wedding Crashers
I already I received
We have one last clip
And it's Alex
Quoting
But not Thomas Jefferson
Okay
So I wanted to
And it's also pretty extreme
The Wayans the April 10th episode
So I can you shouldn't you should know what year it is
You at half
You would think
Because you're a civil war illusionary war historian
It is kind of big
Literally
102 bus
From the Revolutionary War here
We know his batting average with Jefferson quotes
Parable
From the early days of
How did you fare with those
Over
Waldo's are Jefferson
Yes I believe he did not
68th and Landing
Ground don't fire unless fired upon
It's attributed to Minutemen Commander John
John Parker
These words spoken on April 9th
Since 1775
So there's a reason to believe it
It's a real quotes
Probably the Quotev
There's no actual solid historical basis for
No reliable source who was there put it down into writing until a lot later
The quote was spread initially by Parker's grandson
Who was not present at the
The time of being said
Yeah probably
Trying to mythologize is family
These heroic
Figures within the revolution
The jump park
Survive
Terrier something
Everybody
War dies of
In the middle of the Revolutionary War
He died of some
So they wouldn't even know
His grandfather.
Right
He wasn't from what I understand he was alive but not present
Theodore claims that Sergeant William Monroe
Back when he was a kid
August grandfather's great quote
But weirdly
Some forty years later Theodore is remembered it and if he comes
The part of American lore
Temporary accounts of John Parker's actions that day from people who were there
Don't really square with this quote presumably would have
Heard that
Dope quotes
Better write that s***
Shut down for pasta
Ebenezer monroes
Captain Parker ordered his men to stand their ground and not molest the regulars unless they were unless they meddled with us
He was later visited
Pre Civil War
Hahaha
Almost
Is Paul Revere's account of that day
You can see similarities
Difference
The similarities of the sentiment like
Don't f*** with those people and less than self-defense
But the difference is
Cluedupp are cats saying if they want war
The bravado is gone
Veneers
Last nerve
Those differences of the only thing that Alex is interested in about
Office quote
To glorify his grandpa
Looks like once again
Firmly on the side of law Rover
History
Really believe
Anything about the country unless it matches up with whatever
Feeling whatever he wants
You might have recognized that the ends are used
Yes the war has already begun
Alex is close enough on that pic for me to give it
The quote is actually
The war is actually
It is probably a very accurate assessment of March 23rd
Scene 75 speed
Did the second Virginia convention
Honestly
To be a great thing for Alex to actually quote
It really closely matches
Vybes
Throwing out lately but I think there's a problem with him actually
Quoting the speech
Paraphrasing it
And that is a Patrick Henry's legitimately calling for war
Not an Infowars
In fact
Patrick Henry speech
To oppose them
Shall we try argument
Sir we've been trying that for the last 10 years
Have we anything new to offer upon the subject nothing
We have held the subject up in every light of which it is capable but it is all been in vain
Shall we resort to entreaty and humble supplications
What term she'll be fine which we have not already
Exhausted
Let us not I beseech you sir to Steve ourselves any longer
Paraphrasing
Alex believe that Warhead
I truly already started
Patrick Henry would think
Coward
And helping the enemy with his infowar.
Engaged
It's crazy
Accurately
Woodlake
The Civil War has already started
Patrick Henry would hate you
Yeah he would think that you're a Redcoat absolutely
Or at least like someone who's collaborating through their inaction
Weak-willed callow
I don't know we come to the end of this and
I don't know
It's just like
Trains
Foreboding
Listen to this April beginning of April
I mean part of it is knowing the Boston bombing is coming
Even not knowing that
You just see these elements that are enter
Texting
Liquor
Going on dates
Not on the show
Like the way that Alex is rhetoric is asked
So severe light the way
Kind of
Shifting towards
Directly Target
There is something going on that is
But you can tell from listening to
I don't know what it is but
I texted you yesterday
It was yesterday
There's a big fog
Coming off the light.
It feels like that
If you would like looking at Lake Michigan and just seeing
Nicholas Sparks
Every time you've used that trade metaphor I have had that heavy
Did you ever see The Addams Family Values
I see, but I don't remember
Starring Raul Julia being f******
Amazing with Angelica
Anjelica
Absolutely
He's down in the base
And he's playing with his
And
The entire Addams Family
And they're all
Oh no its
Running around Dead Man's Curve
They all know that this is going to result
Destructive
He knows it
They know it everybody's involved in watching
And it's still so enough
You know everybody anybody
Everybody included could have
Stop it I don't
Framed
Another putting Addams Family Values
It is just like a
Zebit
80s
You everybody knows what
Going to have
Everybody knows it's inevitable
And yet anyone could stop
We are to consider the idea that people were listening
Maybe
Pick up on me
People were onboard fully as this was happening
Yeah
The trends are
Really clearly
I wasn't
All of these episodes
And I can
Fuel the entire
10:30 right
Like I can steal
Did he's in his rhetoric and the
He's laying out these episodes
The story
Choosing to cover the ways covering.
It's coming in
Into like a
Bottleneck
It it's weird to imagine
Someone
Like who loves Alex
Experiencing
Like as a real reporting
Respond
Be taken on
Hard to figure out exactly what this guy you look up to is actually
We saying aw of time
Bruschetta
That's terrifying
Not to not to go too overboard
We cannot listen
Send to all of these
Because
So the only the only evidence that most
Rhetoric is
More troubling is we
Is what
But also you really have
Have presented it
Where I feel
I really do feel like
Even though I haven't listened to this
Spanish preterite
Israel
There's a lot of
You can put him to listen to that and then we could have a conversation about your
Different interpretation
But this is problem
And we're getting days away
Boston bombing
Honestly I don't want to know what
Rhino the Richard Belzer's involve
Sonic
Bring in
The story of a
What's the name
John Parker
Telling that whole quote and everything
That is 100% Christopher Walken
Pope sick
Showing up at
Your grandfather
And
Christopher Walken in the bells were both on
Cooking
It's a big pool
Home Depot
To find out more about that in the future and we will see you all on Friday
I already website
Just a jumping real quick again
Tomorrow night Thursday night at Two Brothers roundhouse at 8 p.m.
Can album I'll be open
Inform come out Mike Wiley is
One of my favorite
King of the puns
King of the world
Right sweetheart
It's at knowledge under
Underscore fighting
At go to bed Gyros on Facebook and we are also on
If you would like to listen
Riley's first album
Oh boy here we go
Jesus
Wow that why how could I not have a sense of dread I know it disembodied hand
Go ahead
You can also go
Spotify
Oh that's it
For both our show and
Alexandra Thurston color