I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Stripe.com
Alex
Jordan Jordan
Have you ever quit
Erase
Have I ever
I don't
Like physically or metaphorically I'll
Camp Marathon
Thought
About
Times in my life when I was going to the gym more
Never got around to it
They ever get healthy again
Anime
But
Is physical
Do the mile run
Matter it all solved
Just walk it
Gym teacher did not like that
Tell the track
Impressment
Is cranky Vietnam vet
Gym teacher.
Rat that was a bad race
Junior High
Uncle Junior
Class
Central racism
I thought that was all silly stuff
Well I decided I was going to run for school Pope
That brand of dumbass
That is
Haha
I was but I'm already bored with it
Now that's like a ride but see what happens
Nothing happened
Good luck with the races of any kind
What race or political race
That you've made that very clear
Much about
I don't know anything about
Little moment here
First of all
Amapola
I'm a policy wonk
Next-gen
Jennifer
Next
Generic otter thank you so much
You are now
I refuse to accept
And special in their own way
Unlike people
Thank you so much and made money off the Iraq War
You are both wonderful technocrat
Heroin
Freakishly large
Money off the Iraq War
So elephant Jordans coming out a little bit late and I apologize for that to the good people of the world
You
Schedule in whatever
Sick all day yesterday and
That I had a slight or a light bungling
Of the schedule
In California for the better part of this
2013 episodes in a week and Wacky Wednesday possibilities were all dead ends
Alex's in California
And that means that I got to be ready to do that episode at the drop of a hat or a fireman
And that situation has guys in football field
Running in place when you do a push-up
Do ghost live with Alex man I got to drop a
Doterra animal
Yeah
So by the time Alex got back
From California it was already
Cutting it real tight for us to be able to slip out
And get this out
The next best thing to Alex
2019 episodes
Is Thursday of the
This week
You not too long ago
Said he was going to
Politically murdered
I want to get into some Joe Rogan stuff here
Physically
Metaphysically two bottles of tequila at
I'm sorry I'm sorry
Literally two bottles of tequila
What takes action Eddie Bravo
Along with his co-hosts from
Podcast
Comedian
Guy
See how this plays out there on for most of the show
The show Alice
He has a big special report that he wants
Premier agent keeps
To go viral
Well everything he does
To go viral for him
Keep going that's true I'm here to do my part
Enjoy a little bit of it
No special report
Explosively on infowars.com
Gore.com
Video Communist Party
Robert
Just submit
Honest about this
And so here is the dictator
Communist China
Know what
This is insanity
I have a couple thoughts about that
Jessica
The first is even as a racist impression this is bad
Do the quality
I have a strong suspicion
Shane Gillis
Yeah yeah yeah
If I can do that maybe I can pick it back up
Oh my God created by
What a train
Pterodactyl
Goes even
Further
What's a 6
These are nice.
Hi Galaxy
Play around in the mud
God
Ridiculously desperate Ploy for attention
This is this is this episode of Scooby-Doo
Walmart
Maybe yeah yeah I mean
I mean what what it what is more Punk
In 2019
Great so I was listening to this on audio
A video that Alex in Disguise or something like that
Go for some kind of like a defensive
Right
Trudeau's Styles radar weather
No
Did you wear the hat
Okie dokie
However
It is anime
Why not
Didn't have wings
I think so I can't confirm or deny whether it had wings but I can't
This is all just a really sad.
Getting people
It's just racism
Specifically
I can't see it any other lines other than like
Hey it's cool now
Some blowback of attention that I get from
Maybe translate into
Yeah and he's going to try and call it a day
Right right
Clearly clearly
Parody
Yeah yeah
. that is
I'm not sure but it's
As a sign whenever you perform a piece of satire
That was that. I know that you
Probably pick that was actually it was not
Proposal
Jonathan Swift went through a long diatribe of why and how people should react to it
And then he said that he did actually do want
It's the mark of great
Commentary great satire when you have to like
New jerk make sure people know every f****** around here
Because otherwise it's going to look really f***** up
I think this is a really lame and I think
It's really interesting
Kicks off because I feel like every
Desperate Ploy for attention
Much like having Eddie Bravo
I could get some of their
InFocus
Go on Rogan while he was in California
Bigger
Monroe County
And I can't imagine I have no idea what he's presenting
Being bigger is
Go on
I don't know, we are not very thorough G family that would be amazing
Read him on
Marin
5 years
It's somehow
More offense
How pathetic
You know like
It's not you know it's
That is terrible
And it's awful
Right but
Because it
It's so desperately
Fake like it's not you
He's not eating
It's just such b*******
Makes me feel really sad
No
Minecraft
Some kind of satire
I think that's awful.
A bummer
Absolutely
That's that's like how I would feel with
In a perfect world like that
The last living race
Feeling you know where you're like
Really dude
So weird Twilight Zone episode
Racist
Episode of one of those Disco.
So you talking about
His equally off
4000 +
Set that is
Exactly what he was
Literally no way for Alex to have the information
Deciding
Statistics on that access
Immigration status
The only thing basing this on is like super unreliable
He's most likely getting this information from
Speech that Trump gave earlier this year where he planted in the past
2 years I sat arrested
Criminal records included 4000
Quotes violence killing
Yeah he's
Alex is claiming this as a statistic of crimes per year by a certain population
Even if words were correct
He's just saying the people taken in by Tyson
Committed that many crimes total
It could be over a span of 30 years
No f****** idea
Another similar claim Trump made last year was
Thousand America
Cancel been killed by immigrants
Weather
PolitiFact most likely got this from a noted
Yeah he's
Yeah that's on Brandt the larger problem is that consist
Studies have shown the Immigrant population
Regardless of documentation
Status are less likely to commit crimes
Alex knows that
She can even remember
Side of Katy
In the past it's not worth
That deeply again to remind everyone that was accidentally
We fired a gun in the bullet ricocheted off the ground
Ultimately hitting
He didn't Murder In Cold Blood until what happened in absolutely tragedy
The murderer is literally only useful to escalate
Demonization of
That's literally the only reason to go
Yeah absolutely that's that's not the problem
Jose Garcia Zarate
And he was at his trial because it was clear with an axe
He was however charged with being a felon in possession of a gun
This is a charge that was a
Yosemite
The decision came down on that
Late that that was overturned
The reason that convicted of
Conviction of a gun charges overturned
Was because his attorney
Successfully argued that he didn't know that the thing he was picking up was
Is a gun
He found a gun wrapped in a rag picked it up
And it fired and he immediately dropped it
He wasn't knowingly in possession of the gun
An appeals court found that the prior trials judged
Construction on the legal standards for dealing with what's known as momentary possession
Yeah
So this is the reality that Alex is yelling about
Which is bad
He answered turn to an appeal to emotion
Word immigrant killed this precious White Lady In Cold Blood
When that's not at all the reality
What else is doing is lying about this
Quite frankly
Virtue signaling
We stopped at the gun was it was
More
New information that they established in
I think it was part of the first trial but it wasn't
Reading up on the appeal for everyone
How could it be
Suck so hard
Enter the country illegally
That doesn't mean that he
He committed that
Open murder
No is there any bearing on the event
God that is very sad involved
Up for no good reason
Other than that there are
Infinite number of
It's very
So Alex did go to l.a.
California
Probably a lie
You just said
But
I thought he was going on Rogan
I was wrong about that
But my reason that I thought he was going to go to l.a. unless there's a big
Press opportunity
We're someone else's audience
Can sort of vulture rental
Like I said unknown podcast that he went on
It's bigger than Rogue
Pod save America they're really driving
F*** these are really trying to reach across the aisle
Bigots in Richmond
But it wouldn't be an Alex Jones
Trip
If
It didn't have a story that's
Something happened to him on the plane
So he's out of control
I know you do it all for money
What you want to bet that was one of Alex's fan
Water
Christ
I guess
Security Now
Which kind of pie
Super paranoid dude
Unhinged
I mean
Smart time to preemptively assume that they're going to turn on him
Well I mean is it just be like
And I am
Very visible so they're probably going to come after me
If you create an environment group
That is so true
I would say defined by
Just accepting things with
Being
Incredibly paranoid
I just
Pull up suspicions about literally everything
Was the only lesson really that the French Revolution
Needs to do things like go to LA to be on podcast
Because
Now that he does
Have his social media doesn't
YouTube algorithm
Exploit he has no intake
This is why
His business model is falling apart eventually the people that get indoctrinated into does
Become suspicious of him and go away forever
That's low hasn't
But the inflow has
That's why it's falling apart
That's why
For someone like Alex is like
Valuable
Sharper fall because he had less groundwork live
Lessov Foundation
To build upon
Abyss
All the gears to completely stopped working but passed
Milo didn't actually create anything
20 semi deer
And that's it
And I mean obviously Alex is aware of that
If he's ever read it
Email from any of his listeners or
Actually experience
Public
Nose
Yeah
Comes back
And others undertale
Yeah
Alex
At this point brings in Eddie and Sam
Cool Veyron for the better part of two hours
How can I show coming back on Friday episode
Whatever
It's either Friday or Thursday night I can't remember
They do a podcast together and then I guess they do alive
S***
This is very
This
In the past
Weave
Experienced Eddie Bravo and Alex
As
Joe Rogan
Alex
Ready to be there
To be like sort of a pressure release valve
If something's going
Too bad for Alex
He can just yell at Eddie about Flat Earth
Everything is
How this would work on Alex's
Infowars
Just one
Sort of unknown variable exam Triple 8
Going to go
We'll find out
Necessary
Just told you that the two that were on
Anyway
Do you always have to backup everything you say right
That is true you do need to provide evidence for every
Double.
Sheetz
Why do people get
Itsfunneh
Trudeau
Situation
Comparing it to Tropic Thunder
Okay but
Do we have an actual
These guys
Conversation is a lot of yelling
It is
Not coherent
Right in most
Talk about Jeffrey Epstein
Also what Alex
Next segment
Where is involved
Tried to Blackmail
It's more important
That
They get into
To the bigger issue
Well then
Is that
Humanism
ShopRite
Tripoli know is why
What you do
Hang out with the guy
Wow
It's good is there a sad is that part of a Alex's kozma
Version of Chris
Christianity
Weirdos
Crazy yeah it's kind of weird
We run into like an essential problem that I have that I really don't like
About episodes
It's really difficult
Two different big you ate like what is
Trying to be funny
And what is actually like
Deposition
They don't want to come back as a one-eyed woodchuck
Yeah
To get a little bit of a
Being funny in there
Tell him it's in the middle of expressing an idea that I think you probably believe
Create robots never have to die in face VR cost
Where is you actually believe
And what's a joke
It's always hard to figure out site I try to err on the side of like
He's probably f****** around
Fox around
For a living
When you're on a show with
Alex f****** Jew
That is most humorless person
Try and get humor in
The show
I mean
If you're a professional
Obviously easiest way is
Make poop jokes
If you make poop don't you have destroyed
When you read the room
You say poop jokes are going to work
Actual comic
Trying to be
Actually funny everything sales over his head
Of course
Course
That's big news
Break
To fight
Never been more fun with somebody just beating up
Open old man after that Revelation comes out Alex
Reveal some information of his own
About John Bolton
All money goes to charity
Hardcore gay p*** stats
I'd like to remind you that this is a family show
Alex the libertarian
Where at
Right
Family Show
Opening
Call Mike
Verbally and
Vocally
Sounds almost
Identical to Owen Benjamin
Very similar
I don't know I don't know
Kushner's
He's a f******
Slumlord exploit
Racist
Bullshitters who's married to the worst woman in the world
Dad is the worst man in the world
F*** off
Yeah
Making a joke
That's making the joke
Is it
He's trying but he's
He's it's at
The joke
Fletcher sucks
Well I'm not saying he's a good, kind of a joke is there
In fact you know what I'll be honest with you like please
Delivery is so similar to
You have something
Piano sound
Similar to seven
I had to go check
Yeah
They got a clip of Owen Benjamin video of this episode
I'm not positive this isn't Owen Benjamin pretending
Tower on Infowars
Alex would know
Although I imagine
Sam Tripoli would be with a horrible child
Probably
Very similar like this
Which is like
Understand
Comedian
Blurring of the lines
What do you think
What are you joking about
Is that mean is that proved the Rothschild
I just don't understand I don't know what
Are you like goofing around Hitler was a Jewish Stone
When you continue the point keep trying to argue
You're making an argument
I don't
Genuinely just like really
Committing to
I don't know
There's no possible way that
He could be
It's just not
I mean I guess the podcast with Eddie Bravo
He's making any
F****** ration exact
It's got to be him being like if I'm going to go on Infowars
I am going to
Conspiracy theory
I don't know that's the only thing that makes
To me it really makes me wish that I had
You know unlimited time
Just listened to hundreds of hours of Sam Tripoli
SNL ever hires
F****** with
Yeah I don't think it's
Making a g
Joke out of being on Infowars
But at the same time
Be funny in his own yeah
I can't say that he's wrong about a lot of stuff
Like this
Across that segment
Trainwreck
It's it's really all things all things being equal
It's not good
No
It made it so like
Eddie Bravo and
AAA
Two days in a row this going to be
I'm definitely not listening
Friday
It's surprising how out there
Same time being
Incredibly boring
Would you rather Alex cover cookie
Crap like
UFOs
Alex
Does not cover
Cookie Craft
But UFOs
So Alex is kooky crap like UFOs interdimensional demons
Tricky bunch of human
Entropy and collaborators
They destroy the environment in some such way that makes the demons
Physically materialize
And then everybody dies
Because it's
Look at all of those things are the only possible
Sherlock Sherlock
Bright
Once you eliminate
Impossible
All the
Just left no matter how improbable
Is done by the f****** global
Remember that
So
I do enjoy
Like Alex has such
Shabbat
Such a skewed towards his own
Ideas
Vet like
He impunes UFO ology
Crazy
This
Strategy
Project Camelot
You think the Raptors are bad
I beg your pardon
I know Mark Richards
Yeah it's these worlds that happens a lot
Kick you out of it
Everything is kind of make believe
To be aggressive
So
What's the wrestling with whether or not I believe same tripoli's f****** around
Dismay
Text quick really kind of help put it into Focus for me
Where I'm leaning towards
Not
I'll let you decide what you think
Whatever they like
Flights
On some level
That he's really into this stuff
He believes
At least the good part
Google phrase to social score rice in China so scared of Google
Poison permanent kits
So
What are you talkin about
Words to it and that is the Eric Schmidt did take his daughter Sophia long
When he went to North
Conspiracy theory based on an anonymous source who talked to a group called anonymous
Claiming to be a former lover of Eric's
All of this completely unsubstantiated
It comes from a post on a Blog could have been written by anyone
Down to the claims that the trip to North Korea was about getting
Antidote
The daughter
Anonymous Patriots
Either be a part of or the same thing as a group called American and
Intelligent
Who does best as I can tell is a group of retirees
To talking to the webcams about Trump
Write one of the three of them
Interesting
With the digital no heat
They're also really big into these 432 Hertz
Which I assure you will be at the road
I like the evil globalist
Whatever
Change the vibration
Music
In order to put bad vibes into the public
But all of these artists that died young to go with the 4:30
Right
Nativity back into music
Alright
Debunked studies
Alright you showed up on Project Camelot
On Infowars
Super into those
Conspiracies
I promise we'll cover it
Down the road
These
They post a bunch of videos
432 Hertz
Music
10 years programming hearing aids
432 Hertz
Not anymore
Special event
Any other
Z-man you drank the Kool-Aid
Just a group of old people political power of memes
The demonstrator
Alex
To be the Alex
Spell colloidal silver
Where is America
Intelligence media
Just gives out of recipe
Before it
Well I mean you're going to need a little bit of
Sure
Sure and then you get some silver and you're good to go
People who originally posted
The image of the
The judge in Rodger stones
Which Rodger retweeted
And that got him back out
That's what that's what you're telling me
Originate
Have your argument basically goes to China is poison
I'm not an expert on these matters
Actually sure they're real Poison
That work that way outside of movies
Given the lack of any specifics in this person's Anonymous post I find it convincing and impossible to look
I don't care
Red Sky
Gentleman bastards
Series and that way
Are there
Did they just give you and then like if you don't keep taking
No word from the biological standpoint
It goes against most of what we know about
I'm not a biologist I could be wrong but that seems like
What's the name of that
One thing that's a red flag but the way the stories
Being told is also
Chronology
I have expressed by Sam
The theorist
Start a tithe other daughter
Strengthen their clients
So they killed his other daughter
I didn't desperation he took his survival
North Korea
Do to save her
The problem isn't that trip to North Korea took place
His other daughter passed away it's
What does confuse things a little bit from
Chronology standpoint
It doesn't matter though theories like this are based on nothing
Accommodate new information
Over the course of my time doing this podcast
Even before that in
Recreation
In old times
I've read a whole lot of dumb blogs
The purported
This is one of
And this is the
People get this
Information
This is
Something you know about unless
You looked into these worlds
Involved
Indomican
Conspiracies
Read stupid s*** A Lot in Belize
Cuz you wouldn't know this one
Wright's doesn't even talk about that right
Good this is this is a revealing
Conspiracy
Because I thought it was all just made up
What's on a rip keeping the risk
But if this is an actual
Conspiracy theory
Yeah you totally
Pastor
Otherwise
What the f*** are you doing the only other possibility I guess if you want to keep up the idea
Around is what it's like
LARP or whatever like
Eat like
Goes into the stupid conspiracy sites and find things in order.
And I find
Unlikely
Yeah it was just something I couldn't
Trace back to
Kind of
Kind of obscure
Right then
I would probably agree with you that it's just riffing
But this is absolutely
Conspiracy
Subterranean
This world
That's why I was
Confusing it first
Because
Could totally seem like if I start on
Like that
You know it's like weather
Closing little bit about the the stick driving how to get
That's just rapping and rest
I could wind up anyway
I have no idea
So
Claims that the Chinese government tried to murder Eric Smith family
Forward to that
So Alex insists on playing the
Video of him
Pretending to be easy
For Eddie and Sam really wants to impress them
Anti Eddie's response
Is
Amazing
Voice hours
Obama age
I have no evidence that Alex has done any voicemail
What's up cuz every time you've heard of
Turn on the radio
I guess
He could save it is like his own documentaries
When he does the narration
Take that away
I can't hire it
I don't see any reality
How does he could say that rotoscope of
Waking Life
That could be going to work with him anymore
Problem
Alex
God
God that would be so good to be other man
The next Before Sunrise
I don't think linklater has a place for you outside of crazy galleon rotoscope
Here at midnight
That Alex Jones voice
I don't I don't know what you talk about you also was on Like Jesse Ventura
And I guess the other one
Decoded
Meltzer show
Mangrove episode
They tried to sneak into book
They made a big production
I don't
What he's talking about if I were politically
PolitiFact
I would rate this claim Dubai
Dubious probably not
Local commercials
I do I do for a little while
Crazy stuff
Betty White
Before I get it to buy
Real bitter
Brandt
Let's move right along
If you'll recall in the past
Alex
That you know Trump's got to get green one
We got to get it
We need to get it
Alex has decided to move on
Okay good
It's that bhugaon
Never
First place
The Moon
I saw one of your notes Here
Real thrill
The movie
I do love how Eddie ruined the reveal their though
Wait a wait a second run the bed Eddie comes off the bus
It really frustrates me that that really
That high-pitched
Really was not where I was coming from
You're still doing the Chinese that's pretty nice
You're going to Annex the Moon
Pretension
None of this means anything
What I hear I would say something like I started apposite
Petition to make the moon the 51st state
It's something that's hard to ignore cuz it's stupid
Painfully obvious does a desperate cry for attention
You can almost hear Alex off are talking to Rob.
It's going to come from Media Matters
Post making fun of Alex
Competition
You can almost see the intention behind it
It's all about trying to
To use other media Outlets to give him
Free press that he doesn't have access to himself
The Moon is the Furious
Suggestion to make even
For Alex
He knows damn well very serious breach of international law and probably grounds for war
All countries that are capable of space travel assignment 19
67 outer space
It explicitly make space the property of everyone
Ever B
Outer space
Absolutely break that treaty
Which would
Probably pissed off literally every other country on Spotify
Breathe a long
Write me a weird situation
We have to go to war over this
Dumbledore
I don't want to do that
You know who generally make
Claims on Outer Space theme
Martis
There's a pretty rich tradition of con men claim they own parts of space in order to sell them
Spiritually continuing
This isn't it just makes me sad you see this like a racist rolling with the
Zvideo and you like
Get you and get your name in the media
You starting to change. Org petition to Annex the moon and pretend
I was taking it seriously in order to get
Press media
It really is
Stephen Moore
He would
Get
More people
Supporting him
Just
As
Saying something
Stupid and then
People will
Actively
Circle
Tenzin be like
Care about Alex Jones
Whatsoever until
You
Sent this message but now I know you're lying
And I love Alex
News
To even more so
Because that goes into
Attractive
First
Who's crazy
Like you get some
Runoff
From big ass from
People
Covering
But you'll get more people who are like this
Into paranormal spaceship
Probably
What do you need
PetSmart
Revere
Hardback in
Yeah yeah
But he's not smart
Even more land because
Like he came up with the idea
Like they were having
Hearings on.
DCU become a
Estate
Right now so it's like
And he's already done the Greenland
Play doubt
A little bit about
The guy who got fired from SNL
Civista Bank
Complaining about the idea that you can't do anything
All these moralists are going to
Come down on you if you
And so
I think that he makes a really so late
Allegiance
Let It Go
Alex spent so much time complaining about the view like he's
So much
I'm yelling about Joy Behar in the past like
I understand that might be
Like
Don't try to pretend like this is an exclusive behavior of people on the left
Or upset about places I guess the complain about Louis c.k.
That's what's up
PK
Most people had was a create an unsafe working environment for potential
That might be uncomfortable being around him
That was more than conversation then like Louise going to say something offensive
I get that I understand wanting to push back on
You're not a guest on the show The Dudley
Ridiculous
Listen
Because what if you live in I don't think it's that dumb position is wholly like
Leave everybody alone if you do that yourself
I don't know if it's not going to argue with you I'm not going to
Right
The universe
We're not
However
Kind of frame and sexual acts
Yep how crazy is the Unabomber in the next clip was
Because his argument is
Black guy at a party man
That's a Drew Michaels bit all over
Don't read the Unabomber Manifesto I don't want to be the guy who's like
Actually if you read the manifesto there's a few
You don't need to be that guy there's no point
I'm not sure that that might be
It's
Alright
I don't
I don't care
This is a rambler
Kind of weird
Some of the claims he'll repeat come from
Muhfucka
No
Embody the guy I don't want to talk
Just just
Perfectly crystallized as
Yelling the Unabomber was right
Conclusions
Was the man right
Look you got to wake people up somehow
70 Savage
That's a normal things
Sure
But
Yeah if somebody if somebody
Seriously said the Unabomber was right
Extrapolate all the other
That you don't like about
Yeah it's it's kind of a towel
That's all people at parties like you think the Unabomber was right
And I think we kind of figure out what it is
Pushing for
The 51st state of the United States
51st state
Making a White House petition
Never happen
He's advocating an
Lake Hughes
To do something
That is
It would be an insult
This is crazy I know that the mooninites a dick
So I would say we don't even want them
Not positive
The in the time I've listened to the show Alex
Advocated
For an international
Uno
Buying
Greenland I don't know if that would be an international crime Uber ride
We're possible
Completely again
International law
Country
Annexing the
Well and then we have to Annex slaves
Offset
Alright
I don't know what
The deal is
You know what I mean like
I don't know if this is the same as like Alex trying to advocate for Trump
Commit a different International
What
Yeah
Goofy it's stupid
He's advocating for
Nope
But
Infowars.com
Tom
None of those other countries are going to claim the Moon
He's acting like we've got to do it before they do
Do well we're in a new space race
Apparently
This paper is to just say the Moon is
Right that was a lot harder than the whole
Then ask not what your country
The Moon
The shirts are being printed
Lost Hills
Play Symphony first
Newswars
But the shirt
It's going to be a $30 shirt
Yeah marketing for the shirt
People signed it
Drum up like
Possible coverage
For it in order to drive sales for the stupid shirt
But also the fact that he's putting out more shirts than
How is that B has been more of a
Versailles
Abilene closer to that direction than it being a
Your existential
Yeah it was more like
The products
That we have a year left
Supplement
It's not
The show is going to
Maybe I don't I don't know
35% off or something
Claiming I don't know if it's
He's claiming some of it is
Like below
Talked like he's losing
I don't know how much of that is
Is true it could just be all
Bravado and
Sales but like
It doesn't feel
Like
It doesn't feel like
That was some
Is what I meant
He's responsive
To be like you know you should do
You change the name of that
Operation
He's doing a play on
Alex's
Not quite
Picking up on what he's talkin about
Eddie keeps being like
A b
Is what it is
It's not that in
Pinterest
Is it
Idea for Eddie
He wrote the Declaration of Independence
No no no he has an idea about how the UFC
A very successful
Can get a double
Okay idea is
Routine
Karate
The biggest
Ask them pitbulls
I think Eddie is dismissive
There
Great idea
Humans fighting
That is fine Eddie Bravo is
Stupid everywhere but if you step
His f****** room
He's going to
He's going to put you down
He's maybe
Matured a little bit
I get I don't know this is probably no other contacts
I would say that it sounds more like Eddie is hip to Alex more than he has been in
Haha and he's
Is less willing to believe
Things
He might have been
50 years ago
It seems like
It seems like he's putting up with him more where is Sam is the
The Eddy of the show
Hasn't been burned
It's possible
This is like
He feels over it
And kind of like
Whatever
And Sam's
He's eager
To impress Alex
Chasm of the various
Situation that were talk
Alex's
Ebon flow of liquor
You know they
For a while
Listen to what Alex has
They get burned
Internet go
I meant Sam Izzard
Send what he has to say
Stay for awhile
Probably
I realize that Alex has no idea what he's talking about
Yeah yeah
The good partnership
But whenever the caveman's about to host the fourth hour a lot
But
Say that again
I know we don't do that
I like hot chicks
Family Show
Call Dad
He was even trying to be funny with that
Eddie's
Oh man
Talking about
A little bit
This clip is really into
Because
Think it really highlights
How Alex
Get his story straight
About whether or not Trump was elected by the people
Or buy
I think
Square that they're mutually exclusive
Cynthia
Intelligent
So I don't I don't think you could
Make the argument that good guys in the intelligence
Community installed Trump
It was a ragtag band of
Gyros
We got we got our Bruce Willis
We got our
Call Marcin patrzalek
Cher
See what was happening is
The will of the people was but then
CIA people
Say we didn't
So then.
Gyros came in
Frey
Legitimately on his show the people only person I really know for sure
Tell him about that
Steve anymore
And we've gone back in
See why you should never have believed
It's crazy that you held onto that piece of information
The clearly is from
Like you need to
Reconsider
When the source of something is shown to be a liar
No no that's that's only going for
You can't
Ignore what
Steve said
Ex post facto
Well I mean I guess if it means
Like if you completely changed everything you do
To accommodate the bad info
Information difficult
You claim to be right 99% of the time
And then you have to go back and go through your archives
Oh my God
It's a problem 88% always correct
Certainly nowhere near that
On the show is to
To play a deepfake video that's
Kyle Dunnigan
About Jeffrey
Death wear like Bill Quinn
Donald Trump
Epstein
Auto-erotic lyrics
Himself
It's not great,
The two of them talk
Popcorn
It's it's also not
It is what it is I don't care
What's more interesting
Is it after the video
Alex
Give me the real Tramp
He's trying to
Impress them
Trying to like
This is this is so
Perfectly encapsulated
Kyle Dunnigan amazing comedians
Instagram
Yeah just go on Instagram and look up Kyle Dunnigan and he's got a whole bunch of videos like that
Hysterical
I was told by somebody
Whatever
He'll just be
Just throws popcorn
Disconnected
Call Mike
So
To act like he knows the secret
Hey man
You know I know things that only friends would know
You know what's more likely
We either that or we elected Howard Hughes
No I don't begrudge anyone for hanging out in a robe watching
Falmer whatever for yourself
Throw it in the air tank I took your mouth everybody likes to have fun
It would have been
It could have been any details
Oh man I know people who said that
You could be drinking through a straw I'd like to know the Trump all the way to the floor all no matter what
It could be
B complex
I got impressed you guys like
Stop
I'm in it
To get us.
Complaining
Glass clipart because
It's all over the place
Whatever it's really worthwhile to go over
Was yelling about how companies
A lot of songs go
Alex Epstein stuff I really don't find it
Hang it all
But Alex
The gas
Are complaining about the
Young Turks
Whatever
I'm sick of them right
I don't know
Mixed feelings on some of this
And then also Sam Tripoli says
The end of this
That is a strong indication
It's some of his beliefs
Might be much worse
Then even
He's pretty
Kazarian but you know that's another store
So what is zero interest in going to bat for
And The Young Turks
Particular
Really f****** terrible pain
Respond to criticism
And all that s***
That's probably not the case for all the things
But I know these absolutely address the horrible things
Written on his blog
Denying of the Armenian
Oh s*** yeah
Tipton Iowa
Okay
Yeah there's a streak on his credibility but assisted in the Maurice
In the more recent past but no one else back then
You shouldn't have commented on the issue
But many believe the genocide is
I don't know they let him off the hook or anyone's
To trust his Judgment at all I don't know that's a choice everyone's got to make for themselves and I don't really have a strong position
I don't think
Genocide denialism is something that you can take lightly even if someone correct their position
Pretty out there
But at the same time
Learning more yeah I don't think it's impossible to change
I give the benefit
Is
Progression of them
Like
Apologizing and coming around
I had terrible information I didn't know enough I never should have said those things
Really typical
Of people who are dyed-in-the-wool
Denial
I don't know exactly what to make of Jank
His position
I have a strong position on it I guess
Iona
Think it's a
Prince to the militia that was involved
Did The Armenian Genocide
Is Alex and Steve
Original shows just called
The Young Turk
Because he's young age
Turkish
What are the problems with Alex
I'm Tripoli deciding that The Young Turks as reference
Ignore all the other time
Groups of use the name Young
It's a pretty common name
Typically the name that's been taken on by people who are trying to change
Change the direction of their own party from within
Princeton's group of New Zealand politicians
The National Party were trying to push for reform in the
The same is true of group of Republicans who work together after Barry Goldwater Law
Really embarrassingly
These groups all take their name from the Turkish nationalist
Young Turks who were involved
True
And based on that these groups should have used that name
Rod Stewart shouldn't have made the song called Young Turks
Different names for all of it
He should have
You should have left
Sure
That's said I think it's far more plausible just term
Young Turks
It's taken on a completely different
Contacts by the time
Started the show
And the colloquial meaning of the word complete
Wanted to change the
It also fit the description
Young
It makes sense
Use of the name
Yeah in political world
Urban South I don't
That he was trying
Named himself after the turkey
Militia
As much as he was using
If you want to argue about whether any of these
Is the term like I said maybe
Not right
Just because something
Has been
Laundered
I don't know very very negative
Threw a bunch
Iterations of
Positive
You still don't want
Just because
You still not going to call you
You know
Just don't just don't
Stormtroopers
Star Wars Universe version
It's not
Whatever
I'm not going to defend Jay
Aggressively
Whatever whatever the situation is
Appositive
Far more complicated
He named his group after this
Militia
But what
For sure
Is it dropped an unfortunate bomb
At the end of his
Alex is saying that it was Muslim
Chris
But that's another story
Definitely another story
It's a strong indication that Sam Tripoli might be one of these guys who thinks
The most Jewish people are actually Jewish
And actually are the descendants of Kazarian
That's the same
Yeah
God
Maybe maybe maybe unknowingly is pushing for this
Conspiracy theories maybe or is it
Possible surrounded contacts
That conclusion
Why did that rebuttal come up when Alex said it was Muslims killing Christian
I actually was the Jews hid behind a little code that most people want
Don't even realize
Right
Free dump
Since you read online
You show up on the Alex Jones Show and make Eddie Bravo
Super rational
The point you're trying to make would you bring up Kazarian
It's a gigantic buzzword
Devore anti-semitic areas
And this
Inform to douche
Hosta show called
So just go ahead and
This is
This is a red flag
You get somebody who hates
No I'm not
Believe that you'd understand that yeah man
The New World Order is not really really actually
Turkish people
Take over the world
You get the birthright back
Esau lost
Man
Compari Lansing
It makes me worried
It makes me worried that
Yeah that
You can't really definitively say what he means because nothing
Another story
The way that Alex
Doesn't respond and leaves it hanging Lakes
Alex's maybe you'll wear that like
If this do talk some more
It's troubling
So I know I guess
Sam Tripoli on
Alex
Jasper Ephrata
Obvious
Bait people into
Covering it
Just do it
Let's take over the moon
You jump back and forth from
Past to present
Used in the past
He's terrible but
Remove the president
You see why he's doing
You like
He's the character from Glengarry Glen Ross
He's what
Lemons character
Yeah yeah yeah
Realizing that
He doesn't have it anymore any
Did his desperation
Reek so bad that
Whatever it was
That he was trying to do
So turned off by
Are you out Baldwin
Are there extra
There's got to be somebody in the background or like
Might be like a bartender
Husband
I'll be the husband
Most venomous place in an office I think Nana restaurant booth
I really sincerely think they're babies
Okay
Define it's like he's past his prime
Absolutely
In order for him to pull
Needs immediate attention
Pretty heart
Is it
People post
Think about this
The video where he's a dragon
Just over
Racist Asian voice
And that's good I think that
Yeah I wish we didn't talk about it cuz I think
Is it more attention
But this contacts
Really help
Promote him
It's okay on
On some level for us
Disgusted
This is just a desperate cry for look at
Yeah look at the saddest man in the world
I don't know
Yeah
If this isn't going to
Covering
Damn drunk
Cover those things
In order to spread the message
It's further than he has the
Ability to
So resistant that impulse seems to be what people are doing
I know I don't know we're going to do for Monday
What time to listen to another episode with Eddie and Sam
You are yelling over each other
Trying to get to this
Same benefits
Everybody's listening and responding appropriately
In the moment they crushed
All the sex
Crush
Back on Monday with the new episode for y'all's
Sorry
But
If we're not going to take the website down on Tuesday
You could visit that way might
Tuesday is knowledge fight.
Azurite Roswell
At go to bed Jordan if you want to
Go to ice
Download
You could leave a review
You but let me tell you some
Not the best way to
You're going to want to do
Is take
You
And your family
To a vacation
Cabo
Okay
You go about four feet into the ocean
Knapheide
Tide you're going to want to do it at low tide because
Just doesn't seem this by
But high tide
Reach down directly underneath
Eat that there will be a c
Seashell
I'm going to tell you something
I was really hoping you were somehow getting a weave David Lee Roth
Cabo Wabo Van Halen
I don't care
Whoever has that tequila
I respect the seashell
Metaphysical
So anyway we'll be back but until then
I am Vegeta
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color