Damn important I sweat it
I have great respect for knowledge B I'm sick of them
Monica
Knowledge buy.com
About
Alex Jones
Jordan Jordan
Have you ever fought
Fulfilled
Childhood
Grow up little do you know
I want to talk about Alex Jones
Little did you know I was a wee nine-year-old boy in Honolulu
Of years old when I first started Broadcasting
I got an update about it and
I don't know 25 years from now I'm going to have to take care of this
I started listening to the final Edition or whatever the f*** is
You know what no one's going to
Address
This is going to be
No I don't know I don't like
Full fillable childhood
Flying
You have playing at parasailing
I've jumped off a cliff
I've never jumped I'm terrified
I would never jump
It's not something that I probably would do again
Stanford
A bunch of people go off already
And
Odds of me getting hurt are Slim
You could see the water
Crocs
Butts
I would probably wouldn't do it again
Especially a contact
Fuel
Like
Are people who do that are crazy
If I guess where I am actively fulfilling my child
Radio
Right that's what I was
That's one of the things I was thinking
Thinking about the question
Beaches
Adjacent to a dream
Cuz we've talked in the past
How you've always wanted
Radio
I've done a lot of things
Things that are at Jays
Goals that I've had
Comedy is a kid but I don't know if there's a
Any like
The only one
Genuinely
Had some
6 years old
Is writing
I like that's the only childhood dream that I'm
I'm close to achieving
I'm really
Or just that means a reason not to do
Absolutely.
But I do know a lot about Alex
But I don't know
Podcast
Today and we've got an eighth
Interesting episode to go over April 11th to 14th
Texas coverage
Hook we've now reached
The day before the Boston Bomber
So weird
The next episode will probably be
Incredibly busy
What's going on here
People who show
So first of all Sean
Thank you so much you are now policy walk
Tyler thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
What you are now
Next
You're now a policy walk
You are now a policy wonk
Ranger guy
Click the button that says
Very special shout-out
Nursery today
We're so thrilled for them
Congratulations on your your anniversary
I hope you're having the best day of your life
Perhaps
But anyway enjoy your day
I want is a kind of wanted
Background of the present
Because the Eddie Bravo and we're still in
Studio on Friday
They were on the war room with Owen Shroyer
Eddie Bravo contact
Look I'm not busy but I'm still too busy to do
Waiting for worship all over that the network
Everybody
To hear some Eddie Bravo.
Severe backlash
From our audience
Unexpected and Universal sentiment
Don't cover the sky anymore it was awful
From the present day
Get back into
The past year 2013
Let's do it
From April 11th
Alex make
You get a glimpse into how his brain works
And how he experiences
Has his own
Situation
This is just
The real bulshit
And this program is
When accelerated timetable
Several reasons behind
What are projections
Their operations sale
Corporate reservation
Beat
Bert was talking about
Present
The globalist
Who created like Iceland
Is like a placement immigrant
I don't know what he's talking about but also evidence
Yeah so proven so on record is just ludicrous
I am a big fan
Suddenly somehow
10 years Bhai
We have not sent we have not talked about this
Yesterday
Or the day before that
That they are behind
Behind them too
Alex still says in the president after 10 years behind
Because the paper a push back on them
Grounded coming up the works
Because they look
Their projections
Yeah I think
He's twisting comments people have made about like
High-Speed Rail
Sure like that
Cable monorail is modernization
Countries
Behind
People had hope
Alex
Real
EZ's consist
Keeps pushing forward on this
Mentality
They're accelerating we should be accelerating
And you're just creating
The perception that they are what you're doing is
Justifying and rationalizing your own acceleration
And that's kind of all the sky
Kind of like
We've got ten years behind on killing all of us
So we
Physically got tenure
Years to kill all
That's really what I'm say
Or else
Or else what
They would already
Have killed you said
Basically
So Alex
Keeping that sort of vibe alive
Fatal
Situation
News report
Getaway today
Hank is a little over-the-top
Chilling information that we
Broadcast
Publicly available
So the most chilling information ever of all time
Every time he
We got the hammer tonight
Guess we've ever had it
The guy who hit
A pretty fun interview
Alex's guest
That guy was pretty fun he paid his rent cameras
We can spend all day trying to guess what this
Infowars.com
President
Italian Supreme Court
Has now come out and said that the government has all the documentation
Terror attacks are
Documents
So what's going on here is Alex's saying that this is in the present
Like that this guy is a document that shows that the Bilderberg Group whenever people metal in
Globalist plans or whatever
And that's not really fair but that's the presentation he is absolutely trying
To create
Ferdinando I
Italian soup
Is often credited
Of the Supreme Court
But I can't find any evidence of an actual judge I honestly have no idea what that title
And I've looked into it a little bit and I still don't really understand
From what I can tell the front like looking at Italian School website
Honorary judges are sometimes the point
Courts on various matters
What is usually a temporary
Depending on the person
So he might have a sister
Did the Civil Supreme Court
On subjugated honorary
Judge Consulting
Yeah it. He's a legitimate person who's had a career in public service
I don't think honorary president of the Italian Supreme Court is a bulshit credential
The way Alex is presenting it is a little bit
It's not as though
Chief Supreme Court judge
Roberts
Steve pieczenik working at
Sure have enough information
Whether or not this guy is lying
About his involvement
Is framing at Asda
Gotcha
18 mm possemato published a book called The Republic of unpunished Mass
Checkers
Which sounds better in
In the book
He claims that he found a document to prove that the Bilderberg Group was behind terrorist attacks in Italy in the seventies and eighties
Nor has imposimato even claim Tucson
Authenticated it
He just believes it to be genuine
Wow I mean that's
Hello bar
Simpler ice
Sure Alex himself has the document
And it proves that whatever Italy and the present day
They did it with folks like terrorist attack
Which is ludicrous even if you believe all the authors
Being baited
He was only talking about activity that took place in the days of operation gladio which
Continue to the present day
It was a product of Cold War stupidity
And by the time anything related to involved actual attack
It was because of groups that it
It's splintered from their original purpose
Gone Rogue
Now is that in itself a good argument against
Gladio
You bet
Does it prove that the people behind glad you're actually trying to create Terror cells blowout false flag attack
I think I need more evidence.
Ankeny Bark Avenue
Before we going to be able to
Substantiate that one
That's claiming to be actual evidence that the Bilderberg Group was involved in operation gladio outside
Mysterious document that deposit auto claim to Sabah.
Anywhere to be
The most chilling
News in the world
Okay so the most chilling news in the world it is
For a while
Maybe
Probably not
Right
No
I'm pretty fine with
I wasn't even born
What about
Alex to change the narrative
He's still
Kind of
They're beating the drums
Of attacking them
Use that you still saying that like they're going to attack or threatening to attack.
Japan and what-have-you
But now he is put a slight twist in it
And that is that the globalist
Are paying him
Kim Jeong Hoon
To threaten people in order to create this strategic tension
As a related
To this this
Italian Supreme Court guy
Sure I am chill. Nothing other than assumption
Send like this is how I read the tea leaves perhaps
Perhaps
11th is kind of a ghost town
In terms of anything in
Continuation of all the same
Gun paranoia they're coming to take your kids
Trends continue
It's kind of
Boring to keep
Keep going over it
Ghost town is
Dino lacoco's
I think he's trying to overblow
His own
Important
Impactfulness
Alex yeah I know it very odd character
But in doing so I think he accidentally said some
Quite true
Talking about right now
Jellyfish
Your ancestors
Of course through your spirit
Problem on their hands
You know even jellyfish listening
Are going to be
Pull up defenses because of Alex
I think if you passively don't believe him
If you actively don't believe him
Doesn't have much of a
If you're just casually listening to him
He is going to have an effect on you
But he's recognizing and and
Sort of
Pointing to the fact that like
What is it positive
Even if you don't believe me
This is going to f*** with your subconscious
What are the reason
His style of broadcast particular
Right
Really trying to
It lets you ignore it
As a whole or you come in with us
Guard up
It can be very dangerous
He's like a
I think so much
About
Update iOS
7.1
Because hackers
And there's this one little thing
I don't want you
Fix it it's all closed
Possibly walking by
And you have an update
Then out
Begin
Ocean hijacking
Find it possible that he's not aware of that like
He's perfectly describing it here just in heroic language
I think it makes them all the worse
Also on this episode
Who's got a real
Bee in his bonnet
About how everyone's ripping him off
That's cool how many times
Stolen people's ideas
Put him on a shirt
The more presents
Makai
But
Complaining about Glenn Beck
Goodnight to everybody
Are ripping them off
And I can actually explain that I also fail to believe
I refuse to believe
But he's not aware of what's really going on
Add
Rush Limbaugh
You know what's going on
What all of them were reading Drudge
You know I
I think
I don't know if he's
Expressing this
But nothing
He says where he says within
That makes me
I think that
Bless
Like they're just all reading the same I mean they were all
Laundry like Alex has something fun
Right
Is like
Distill this down to something that we can act
Right
Right is that is definitely process
Crazyshit and because he runs this Infowars website
He has articles that end up getting linked on drugs
Do a couple of days after he started yelling about that he read on drugs
Story will be on the right-wing media
Spirits
Whatever the case is all roads lead back to drive
That's the reason that Alex feels like everyone
That's just because you all have the same news source
You rely on for your careers
Bring up a buyer report a lot
Is this
Episode
Take our guns
Exhaust
Alex is lying
So hard I've listened to song
I've listened to so many of the shows and almost without fail callers do not confirmed
Bill generally try and be polite like we talked about
Veterans getting that letter f
I'm pretty sure my
Classica I haven't checked the mail today
We'll take that as confirmation of something that is absolutely not the case
IC
Very low rate
Galaxy colors
Offering anything substantial
To confirm
That seems to be pretty rare
So you getting really exist
There's a
Dick taking the guns taking the kids
Globalist want to take over all this s***
I'll bet there's a real singular focus on
Thomas episode
Regarding
Dumbing people down
Something that is very interest
Sit in on this
He's
For Oregon music yet
But his career with
Yeah and this clip where he's talking about it
Plan I suppose is at the globalist want to dumb people they can't fight back
These Invasion plan
Because
He provides for this
Is that
We're entering a.
Downhill
So Alex is figured that there's enough dumb people
Provides no video that shows that people are dumb
I think
I think that
What he think
Is going on
Is Mark Dice
Imitating what the
The globalist
Actuaries
So the globalist
Getting people to sign those petitions they're like
We know now we've got 100,000 signatures
And Mark
Proves that the globalists are doing
No no no no. This is a prank video
This is the Flop elevated man on the street video
Music
Approved
What a f****** a******
On this episode
He is going on and on about how these are great
Demonstrate these grapes
Lee Ann McAdoo has been hired
I think this might be one of the first first
Instances of Alex bring up Lee Ann McAdoo has been hired and
She goes out on the street
Ask people to sign the petition Banning
Dihydrogen monoxide
A real interest of his
On this April 12th
It's it's not following a trend
For the prior week Survivor
Just can't
Send anybody that
Any of those
For anything
Other than the
Individual
Because you're
Give me a steady
Have you out there
4 hours
99 Savage
F*** you
Undercut are clearly just like
We all signed at 3
Anytime that's
Extrapolate
Real people are like
The majority from those video
Right right so if you want
This argument
He needs to show the other stuff the globalist actuaries and what-have-you
Mark Dice
Better than that
That's something that only would be convincing to a dumptown audience
Probably
Odd
So are the Democrats
Apparently
Great job
Focusing on that I sure
Interesting for that
Standard stuff
To keep track of
We are not we are not
Robert's Rules parliamentary procedure
OK Google
Larry Harmon
Hey
Either way
Audience would believe
I understand that you love Ron Paul and his brothers got to be cool by association or maybe even Ron Paul told him to
Like this is not
Something that's acceptable for you to be someone
Epsom salt
And actually believe that
Like this this is recorded
This is very easy to
Show to be false
I have an even greater
WhatsApp follow Robert's Rules
I didn't know that
Search
Over the course of the time doing this podcast
I think we have
Seeing Alex
Pretty hurtful to
A lot of group
Groups of people minorities women
I've never heard him be shity to this specific group
Alex is almost devoid of
Being the same kind of assholes used to everybody about folks
Disability
It shouldn't surprise me but it's
Kind of
Weird
With certain
Rice
Unbelievable
Brights
What
Crazy
Party because I think I know what that means right
Nothing is the everybody has endowed with some gifts
Disability
Are there a hard time for you
I swear I'm running a horrible
Everyone is given gif
Great
And the gift given to the handicapped
Is the knowledge that they are making someone else
Supplyforce which is a growth opportunity airborne
They are things
Everyone giving gifts
Wow
But they don't know
I don't know
Insane that's it
Next level
Yeah it's treating people who I happened
To have some disability status
There
As a as a side quest
Or whatever it's yours
To you
Handicap
Being emotional barbell
For other people to work
Yep that's it
Good guess that's shity
Episode
Guy by the name of benzos
And that one of the reasons is that
Is leaving
Hi Fox affiliate works at I believe in Alex
And try to make a real sucker
Because he's libertarian
So obviously the globalist
They're forcing him out of
PlayStation
So I assume he
No no no no
Isn't this point I don't think it's anything nefarious
Explain
I think it is probably think
8fit floor online media
I think it
Perfectly Plaza
Later
Maybe not
Here like
Alex wants to be the narrative because that's the narrative Alex has about himself in his early days of radio
Shut up about the clintons
And that's why you got fired from
KLBJ or kjfk whichever one
Can rubber
You wanted to be a mirror of his
So he can yell about his own
That's basically what goes on
So Alex
Discredit
You learn something
Did you know that there are at least five different awards called the Edward armor award
Now that's what I was
And it does get better than that and it's called the Pulitzer
That's one of them
Like s*** or whatever do I get time
Digital news Association
This was for quote continuing coverage about Alexandra Flores
Who was a five-year-old girl have been abducted
And eventually murder
So their news coverage
About that story
I was what ended up winning them
The art
The thing is though is website awards at that swans name
Is there anywhere on it
That's because the continuing coverage Ward is not given to an individual but instead of to a station
In this case
KFOX
TV El Paso
This version of the Edward armor award the one that's giving out by The Archies
2 station
Reflecting a recognition
The collaborative effort
The go into creating a complete news broke
So what you're saying is he
T1d Edward armor
Inocencia
And I'm sure he worked on the coverage
But I feel like saying that
He won this award
Dishonest framing
More accurate way to say that like the station you worked at 1
That doesn't sound good on a bayou
I like Isaac that reminds
Hannibal's
I was just on the right
Team with the right
Time like I haven't
The same way to Juan Howard has
Okay
I got you Alex doesn't know that there are multiple different Awards named after Edward amuro
It's possible that by the corporation
Public Broadcasting
They don't even give them out some beer
Observe
Okay
But you might notice something similar about those two people and that is that they working Public Broadcasting
The public broadcaster
There's also the Edward armor awards given out by Washington
State University which is Everett Alvarez alma mater
I bought a whole bunch of people that Alex
Pics of one that broke off Helen Thomas Ted Koppel
That one is basically the lifetime
Lifetime Achievement Award you talking about
On that list are super relevant if you're imagining events 111
This is the problem with the words that have the same name as other Awards
It's really easy to get the idea that Ben Swann is being honored in the same way that Walter Cronkite pay
Is part of a team to put together
Quality continuing coverage of local news about a kidnapped child
I'm not for that I think you should be super proud of the work is done
I'm just saying I suspected this might be an attempt to willfully deceived people about the nature of this award or at least a willing
Famous let other people make the assumption that they make
Correct
If we gave out of scholarship
And names
The Fulbright
Scholarship
It would be a little bit
Going to be like
Yeah it would be
I got you but you know I understand multiple Awards named after luminary
Fielder
TV news
So also because of this I didn't cut a clip of it but Alex
Feels the need to brag about his own accomplishments
And so he says that a couple years back he won an award
From stalkers Maga
The top award
From stalkers magazine
Aiden
2011 Nubia seminar
Guess who open forum
Dana Gould Lionel
Yep
2011 things looked a lot different with a lot different
So stalkers didn't even put out a list
It's called The Heavy hundred
Which is the top
Radio
Go figure
Never been number one on that list
Absolutely not
ID 2019 Alex's number 49
That's not bad
It's Not Butter
Call Curtis and Juliet is number 36
Okay well then they're doing great I have never heard of them ever
And the picture was a younger blog
So Alex is Thirteenth Floor on the lift FM
Did you say red
The Dude Looks real weird text Curtis
To be fair though Alex
Gorka
Dorcas number 27
Absolutely
Giving Nazis radio she was looking right
Alright
26 /
Last year 2017
Heavy hundred list
Bad sign about the State of Affairs for Alex's career
That drop from 26
249 is a bay
Slide for him
Biggby makeup that list based on Consulting with a big group
Radio industry figures
How to ground to terms
Is Radio imp
The industry doesn't seem to see him as relevant
Is raiding the probably
Plummeting
It's not like they hate conservatives or people who are like Alex
That list is mostly just right-wing talk show host
Only right
How much larger the number 14 the last
2 years on it so it's not liberal bias
Hey Glenn Beck is beat Alex ever
I want to know who
Brutal with that feel
I scroll through it and like once you get down into like
The 70s and 80s
It's kind of
Real
I don't know who any of these people are I didn't know this was a show
Doesn't exist
Just because I thought it was really lame
His keynote speech
From stalkers
The convention in 2011
And it's f****** insane video
Well
Every now and again you'll hear a voice in the crowd be like wow
It's.
Conference attendees about the globalist that's awful like a round of applause a couple tie
One of them was like
He's talking about how in his early days
He had to edit video from taped
To table to take forever
3 night 3 hours of sleep a night for these years and he was coming up
Turn me into what I am today
Feels like they're laughing
Crazy knowledge
God I will I would
Do anything
To have
To go back in time
Should be amazing
I would
It'll be very inspirational
It would probably go long a float
If you want to know what it's like it's basically
Episode
It's what I felt was
Worth going over
But he said one
That I thought is absolute
Because he's talking to a group of
The media Insider Folk
And probably he's unaware that they're recording it
Do you love like we all know
I'm here
From Alex
He talks about his process
And I think this is
Kind of revealing
My way up in every meeting at every system
He's describing being a fabulous
Describing like I have an instinct for sensationalizing
Traffic
I know you will say that like I give it an accurate headline
I'm sure that's what he likes to believe it's probably better presentation
I ate some patient lies the s*** out of things I understand
Clickbait in my bones
Exactly like
A lot of the criticisms I would level at his journalistic style
Packard proving anything in flamboyant
Things that are
Horrifying
Going on so what we do
Nothing going on in Spanish
Yep
That's b******* it's
Because it also indicates an awareness
However much of it
Instinctual
It's like when you're aware of
And you're misleading
Yeah my real ancestor
Cesar William Randolph
Haha
That's black
So Alex gets to talk to Ben Swann
The station that he was working
Alex
Excited to see what Ben Swann does next
Oh yeah
I don't know exactly what he did
I got fired
Okay
Okay that's that's the flavor that he's fishing out
Boarding Alex Jones
On a segment that he ran on the CBS station
He was doing these
Reports
You got to stop
That
No
No.
Rated
It's okay let the show go doormat
But apparently he was going to
To try and bring it back
And then they fired
If you're going to be pushed
So local news broadcast
We've got a remote report
God can you imagine just watching WGN
News at 5 and then all the sudden they're like
These are murdering children underneath
I might watch the news more honest loose I think it would be cool
Grocery 2 News
Also worked at RT for a little bit but I don't know
Suspicious
His career has
I had a trajectory that seems to reflect
Someone who believes
Wacky nonsensical b*******
To be a part of that team that won these Edward our probe before it's because everything else he's done in his career
Award-worthy
I mean how well was it
Like the segments are well-produced
The direction is perfect
The cinematography is Grace I saw any different than most local news
Nevermind
But
The story to be the Ben is leaving the station because
He was told he couldn't cover things like gun grab
Ron Paul
But yes
He's trying to push that need to sign off on it in order to authenticate this
That's what he told us he's being silenced
You can't trust any news
But then
This isn't
That narrative
Turn off
These guys
Totally believable at this point in his career was like I want to look at a bigger thing
Then at a local news station
Probably allows
Like you got a bunch of attention from the like
Patriot
Right wing
Media
Beer liquor online
He was covering Ron Paul stuff
And I bet that really felt like this is a direction I should go in
Butting heads
With a local station
Outside
So obviously that would be like we should go separate ways
No
Go for it until then and tell them that's not what I
So I can see that
Being very believable
Response being
So based in his own ego
That like this is what happened to me
I need to discredit all video forces except my own
I need
Disturbia reality event situation better than
Ben himself.
Absalom
A-to-z
Is never
Time somebody gives
Very direct question
To answer
Affirmative
Or negative
The person responds to
Well you know there are a lot of different things
Do you know what the
Whatever answer you wanted to know what guess what I've got
Not no no
He's excited for Ben Swann
And he wants
Him to work at Infowars
Dependent not want to work
He's not
He's pretty friendly and seems to be
Congratulatory of Alex
Accomplishments
He says that the Piers Morgan thing was the best thing he's ever seen on TV
I would imagine he knows well enough I like Ike
Huge f******
At least he's
He's willing to leave
Things open until
Other local
Right
Adapter
Alex
Doesn't want
Medium
Future
Off-base
Alex
There's no problem
Haha no
Exhaust trivial issues it don't really matter to you now
I would say the rest that interview is not worthwhile
It's mostly Alex trying
To cast aspersions about the media
I got forced out or whatever
But
We've heard Alex a lot of really onyx
I would say
Today
Shirt
And
I would say to defrost a lot of lines
This next clip
He's crossed another line
And this is why I'm going to have to
Take very serious
Kesha
We're following her I want
Tuba
Don't you dare
Mess with Kesha
Right of music
Yeah it was really weird to me is like okay this isn't April April 12th
Kesha released Die Young
6 *
Yeah it was like fourth quarter 2012 that that came out
Zeppelin real real trouble there's nothing current about this is your taking potshots at
Also that song is not encouraging suicide most of the night like we're gonna die young.
And it's not what they say
The likes of Alex Jones
How dare you
How many times
I've let this one go
I still can't go after
No new pink Alone 2
Although I haven't heard anything of hers for quite a while but
To run out of
All over pink
That may end up happening at some point but
Kesha
Carly Rae Jepsen
Lana Del Rey to some extent
Lana Del Rey think I've heard that before
A lot darker
Yeah I heard from Alex
I've not heard it I'm sure it's great
So like I mentioned has been hired at this point
Describes this bit that he had her do like a lot
Complaining
When this is how he describes
What he's having his employees do
You just admitted that you stole from someone else
It's already been done
Great. Alex
Original very fresh
I hate it when
Nocturnal
Obsession on this episode with
Visa
Prank man-on-the-street videos
I think Alex might be recognizing that like
Okay
We're in a holding pattern
I've already got really extreme in my rhetoric
Now what we need to do is create a ReliOn waiting for something to happen
Completely manufacturer perception
We could just cut out all the people who talk to the van on the street that doesn't go along with
Preclude
The preconceived notion that we're pushing feels like
Talking about this Mark Dice video work
Yeah it's weird the real strong say
That I get
And just one
Revise to every
Especially those
How many times have
Go out on this
Dunked on
Some random ass
Shut the fuk up what happened when that kid flipped him off
Also you talked about this marked ice report I think there's some weird stuff going on
First of all birthdays reported
I don't give a s***
Nothing about it could ever be persuasive compelling funny into
None of it
Response to it and how he's using
I signed kind of
Because they
What's real
Video about like to hear that the
Duke China earlier this week probably high or drunk out on the boardwalk
About what this guy is saying
If you were to ask me about that on the street I like I don't know
Because I haven't heard that
Yeah but also I don't want to be like that didn't happen cuz maybe I looked at the news that day or something
It's manipulative
It's just f****** not said he's using it
The idea that everyone or zombies
Part of the game when you're doing man-on-the-street chick
Frieza
Unbelievably
That is
So
For real
Do you remember
Do you remember 9/11
Nobody was like
The Twin Towers
Moving on
Used in 2013
Yes
Because it didn't happen
Your response would be
Or something like that
Cut out of the video
Most people
As long as they were angry the person asking them to question
If there was a sort of
Friendly
I don't know that you're that
Or something
Or whatever
The only way
Tells you that that you don't already know it
In a genuine way
It is
You watch
Crowd of people running
You're like always
You find out it was an Improv Everywhere
I wouldn't I wouldn't put it past the organized crime people to run and yell at somebody
You say that you don't believe it
So now more about the Bar-Kays video about taking
People gone with the petition
Done
This is so weird
We are builders
We're going to just repeal the 2nd Amendment take the guns away from the crazy right wing
White extremists and just make sure that's the only
Alex be really focused on doing talking over this video to point out people's races
Like I use another example of it
I'm just a little bit later
Away their guns go birthday
What is going on
Why is it that most of the commentary that he gives over this video is like
The white guy signing it
That's really it's very strange that there is a sense of
Some somehow this has a real racial component to it
To Alex
That I feel is
Uncomfortable
And obviously
What I'm getting
FaceTime
Acknowledge of a
A white dude
Signing
Is this
Sign that the
Globalist
Veletri
Or just saying that he wants crazy right wing
White guys
Right
It's a betrayal salad
That's what that is
Because I did that I got but again I agree
Can't prove that feels like something
He does a bit
I meant ality that he has
So in the video Mark Dice
Fox around a little bit
I have visitors
Ustedes son slave thank you
Free Xbox to repeal the 2nd Amendment
It's pure genius charge birthday to offer at Xbox
That is there's no way
Anybody that has anything other than
Absolutely
Revolutionary Xbox
Stephen Hawking
Because if he had been listening
2 hour show
He could have gotten an email from
Got to confirm
Does prg
Here
Tewksbury fought
Mac
Arthur right right
Arthur
Name the words cause so much confusion
The worst
So Alex at this point
He's got to go
What he knows
He knows that
Steve pieczenik
You coming on his show all the f****** time
Stretch
Of April
I am so he's that intro in Steve here
I think the way he does this
Is like
So laughably abs
You gearing up to introduce Steve pieczenik he's complaining
Government people intelligence
Smoke
You're introducing a guy who fits that description perfectly what is wrong with you I was wondering
There's a
Which is
That's a great idea for a good guy
Former government but it's okay to have them on my
My show is just
Anybody whose former government who is willing to come up
And who's crazy and baby complains about minorities working in the TSA
Glowing introduction
In this club you'll hear some of that introduction
Steve a question
Human cannot
This isn't possible
Whatever he wants
Listen to this f****** question
This is absurd
Like if you're starting an interview with somebody
You don't do something like this
Between North Korea and others
Is not a good intro question
He throws out like 50 f****** ideas
If you have 5 references
His own website
I will be there not like
You don't need
You could just ask a straightforward question for a minute
I am just a person who supposed to answer that question
Possible for dab cuz they can't respond to all of them
Couldn't respond to all of that
Absolutely
Introducing either-or question
Those are all the options
Another possibility Focus this year
Irresponsible I counted eight
Is Alex out platters Eminem puts forth his version of what's going on
In North Korea which has been
His his
Business over the last week
What's a rolly
May or may not have been in South Korea ain't no f****** idea
But you know he does he does what he does best
And that is
Flatter the s*** out of our
This is unprecedented
No not at her Alex slept for so let me congratulate you I came here to San Francisco
Berkeley last night
And you are a hero and
Organization called the universe you are sitting at home
Audio quality isn't that different from when he was in South Korea very strange
.
Weird
Sitting
In his goddamn recliners
I'm in
I was at Berkeley and I got to say you're a hero of the left
F*** are you selling
What he's selling himself to Alex that he's doing a great job
Crazy is so good at this
Is flattery game
And the fact that Alex doesn't see through it
Naughty naughty
Brutal
If you were to go back in
Thought that would break
Got2b
Knowing what you know now listen
Yeah
Like this one
Is on me
Consistently for 5 to 10 years
That one's on me
Steve is running a quote-unquote psyop or whatever his actions but
Yep I was
Really other s***
Just seen that one
I could have asked you a follow-up question
Ever
Previous North Korea
Call Switcher
String pullers
Kim Jeong just really being a charge
Whatever
So it's not really worth all that much
He does say something
Respect
Dismay
Clip
And it's kind of indicative
Things that you be telling Alex
Years later
The CIA John Brennan who we know is totally incompetent and created a lot of them
General
Mike Flynn
Doesn't know anything
Michael Flynn is a part of the rent that he's putting together
Narrative needs to be put in place
Mike Flynn is a heroic
Know-it-all kind of General but now here
Next Windows no he's not
Interested in Mike slim that's interesting
Very different
Yeah
It really feels
Change
Not not the
The narrative
But the p
Pieces inside of it
Eunos like the narrative remains
However they were
Yeah
So we can Saturday
I don't have much
From this episode
It's really boring
It's like
There is a real lack of clips from a lot of issues because it's just kind of
Retreading the same stuff
I'm s*** over and over again
And I guess I did
Had an interview with shooter
Who he claims he's not having lunch
Because he loves Waylon
But
Inconsequential
Shooter I want on the
Infowars
The one from
Happy Gilmore
We can do that
Is completely irrelevant
Next is Alex signing off
The show
So here's a completely irrelevant
Piers Morgan
Record
Exclusive bodyguards there
Your Piers Morgan
Employees
Blackwater the former Blackwater guys
To go on planes with him everywhere
So I don't know he does
His wife does carrier
Revolver
Fine
You still need security I always bio
Come on
So that's that
Just a little bit silly
Here's how
He signs off the show like there really isn't
Much going on it's all just
These exact
Talking about that Family
Kidnapped kids and tried to flee to Cuba
The government's trying to take
A protester
City councilman
So repetitive
Just
It was my numbing to listen
Unto these couple days
That stuff about the mind-numbing
Very real
Terror in that too
These same things that have already looked into we've already discussed
Creating a panic
Naked still creating
A mentality in reinforcing it repeatedly that this is Armageddon
We're in the middle of this Civil War that I have decided we were in
Everything is an existential threat the globalist removing now because the Ten Years late
On their plan
Demonstrated
Yeah nothing is happening
It's like Road
It's like when you've been driving for a long time
And you're falling asleep
Like it cuz you forget
I am driving a
4 ton murder
Right
Honestly close to Falling us
Sleep
Conscious effect on people
If I'm here listening to this
And researching a narrative
And I am experiencing like
This is so repetitive
Being critical when you're listening
Like you internalize these things
I've internalize them as
Is it something you won't stop talking about but if you don't listen with a critical eye or even a sympathetic one if you had
Ears Dam
Like you could
Very easily
Without realizing it
Create inside yourself
The feeling
That these things are actually happening
What is the end of the world this is
The Democrats in the globalist
What's our about
To take the gun
And take you and your family off to it
Afema torture cap
Like it
Like even if you
You only listen
To Alex while you're in the
To the grocery store
But you have it on everyday
So you listen to 10 minutes everyday though
But if he keeps
Keep hearing the same
You're going to say
Oh my God
Talking about it yeah
If it weren't
So
There's a subconscious thing the people expect people to act
Straight up you know like so
You would think
Whether you actually think this or today
Subconscious
You'd be telling yourself like if he said that 2 weeks ago
And he was wrong correct himself just keeps going
It kind of you must know what he's talking about he has
Correct
No one sued him
Rice
It's just
Write the experience of it is really weird because
Yeah I know that the Boston bombing is tomorrow it has chronology
And I know that
So I don't
You never really find exactly what you expect
I guess you could
Kind of
Because there is no connection
Necessarily
Between his show
And it's not like you would expect the show to be
To real-world events
It's fascinating
That it is it is this way
It is molasses to walk through it
It'll get
Where it's going
But
Off the show
Tomorrow 11 a.m.
AOL
So if you believe that America has been taken over
Keeps calling
The people in the government in occupying
Force
I mean we could unpack for a second how that's the exact same rhetoric
Exact same mentality
The exact same
Description
As neo-nazis talkin about a Zionist occupied governor
He just texted the Zionist apartment
You can talk about that
Touchdown a bunch of the past
You talk about how
Like
This is all this is all just waiting
Looking for the spark
Yeah like all of it is so bad
And waiting for the spark that comes
Tomorrow
It's
It's exactly what he needs
This is like re-watch
Dragon Ball Z
Like wet when they're doing the tray
Dude I know tomorrow we're going to f****** fight Frieza
Why are we spending all day today just
Easter 2013
Episode
Have experience
That's right because the things that are going to happen
I bet
After the bombing
Continuation
Of the rhetoric
And
The world
Built up over the course
All the last
2 months
Isolated
Right I'm almost positive everything is going to be
Hey I was right about everything and complete escalation
All the dangerous trend
Particularly
Beginning
Probably going to see Steve pieczenik stick around
To take an even more prominent role
It's a mess
The map do the circumstance
You feel
Raymour and
People who already
We're sympathetic to
What are now like
Not only is he
Bi-Rite
Right now well because he frames everything as a false flag
How dare you ask that
How dare you
Because he sees it that way he's going to make the argument that
Forever the Volkswagen, I told you
The last week's was about to happen I could feel it and all this but we've got over and listen to it
Always him saying that the globe
He's going
To be right
If you are dumb uncritically listening to the show but he's wrong
Actual
A real serious problem
I really think
Well we live in 2019
And yes it is
I think it's going to be a bore of you and your problem
He's going to be able to play around with those ideas of credibility
Maybe
Much like Icarus
Give him my too much
Fly to close
Bassano's
Saying everybody is actors in
He's already there
He's not saying the hook with actors
Buddies dancing around
He's tipping he's dipping his Towing it prior to the bomb
He's calling other things like the Aurora shooting there were actors there
Is the victims and survivors
He's already
On the precipice
What's the razon devices
Future job
With or without the bottom
I think it's unrelated but it also might be a huge catalyst
Immediately
Aggressively
But we'll see
Kind of like a little nervous bouncy
Open down
And then
Boston bomber
Yeah it almost feels like this
Except our prediction was right
To the Boston bombing
Cover
Alex's response
To the tragedy
Boston
Next 2013 episode
Not like the 2015 investigate
Station at
So many different
Yeah
It's very weird Baryonyx
Expected but it's
Baby
Baby learning
Anymore
Kind of like covering both the president and
Somewhat
A targeted
Simultaneous
Diagnose a AAA
Also on Twitter
Yes and at go to bed Georgia
We're also if you would like to download our podcast then you should go to
To iTunes
While you're there
You could leave a review there are other ways to listen
Spotify Butler
Favorite
Going to want to do
Go to your nearest
Sports Bar
Turn on
Poker
I know it's been a long time you know remember Chris Moneymaker
Texas Hold'em on TV you're going to want to watch
Our
And 8 minutes
Then the bartender will
Turn around go to the bar grab you a
Shot of
Hams
And
Whiskey
And then out of the way
Whiskey shot
Hammond
Virginia Senate
No you can't
I can video I'm Leo
I am dzx Clark
And
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color