Respectful
College bike I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
MoneyGram
Who Alex
College.com
Fella
Rights
That was sort of like
I got
Wrestling announcer
I will check out let's get ready to rumble
Bumpers are going to come after you for that it's not like it when people tell people to rumble
What's up what's going on
Yeah ever ask you this
Show or outside visit make for an interesting question.
Comedy
Do you ever
I don't know if I told you that when I was in church
Maybe a little bit
Trying anything I could
Community there there's no real opportunity
Do stand-up all that much
Play started my own bar show
It went pretty well and then I also tried to get in on the internet
Little video game
No good at very bad at
Little video sketches
Do you have anyone that's memorable
Comedian New York comedian
Columbia Missouri
Sweet had one sketchware
The whole premise was it like
We are trying to
To come up with a nickname
Toranoana couch
Coming up with name
Games that were like
But denial later Earth
Something bickering
Like there was a whole thing
Meet him and Ryan Beck
Another comedian
Three of us would always get into fights
About how I thought the essence of Comedy is arguing
People just have a disagreement
Either they would disagree with Abby and
They didn't destroy that absolutely.
So those meetings about
Sketches with probably more fun
And funnier than the actual sketches
Is themselves whatever.
It wasn't
I can't remember lines that well I'm not really good at improvising
I can have a conversation
The pressure of like we're in a seeing and I've got to come up with something to ask to
Follow the gamer I can't
You don't really get into the moment
Nope nope
If I were in an improv jet like I've seen a lot of them
Am I reaction
Like what are you doing the brakes everything
Compared to Colin Mochrie like
It's stupid and I just stormed off Ryan Ryan trials I've got to go
Should not be as compelling television
That's right
That's the theme of this year's show
29th
Interesting stuff that goes on
Cepheid infuriate
On the 22nd largest
Stuff to say about that would infuriate you might have a take on the climate protest
I wonder if it's it's pretty good
It's not for somebody that's pretty good
Pretty great is how I feel about people who
I took a couple of them their Folk
So first of all Chris thank you so much
Next
Swift
Christopher
Thank you so much already
You know what that's already
Onyx Justin thank you so much
Jenni with an i
I'll be goddamn sure about that
Text Michael
Amapola
You are now a policy
Click the button
I don't know
Today
We start on the 23rd
And this is really interesting
The show with the music that I've never heard him use before
Charles Stanley are here
Chronicle what's unfolding
Three things first of all
Metro
Is opening his show with a song by Lana Del Rey
After we talked about him not liking her on our last episode
They are f******
No it could be misconstrued as I like sending subtle messages to us and I were the type of person who likes
Text to create false
I would probably accept that's the reality of what's going on and I would tell the audience
Hey Alex is f****** with us by playing Lana Del Rey
Oh no
It seems like Alex
Really likes Lana Del Rey's new album normanfuckingrockwell
I love it great
Great I had to look into a little bit because I know he hated her in the past
What are you doing
The new album by Lana Del Rey
Easy he thinks that she's celebrating Americana
I think you might be missing out on some of these subtler artistic elements Atlanta
Music critics out there
And I found
Clip from late August
What are the shows that I must not have listened to
Episode Alex
Goes into howdy
Just downloaded the Lana Del Rey album.
Beauty in the world that's great reminder
At a school
Shofar
American flag
Moving California
Real quick that's California
Who's gone and moved away out of America and I want to f*** you.
Metaphor for America
Pure
Martian Street metal
It doesn't matter the past
Real quick also
Wow he's talking about this they flash up on screen the album cover but cuz it's enormous
Divided
The singer from Aerosmith
Album ten years ago
Be there in San Diego
Stop.
Oh
Go
To go
Metallica
I just don't
Care about
Rockstar
Okay here's ago and stuck in Gray
It's ridiculous this is ridiculous
That's so strange rice pudding
I'm going to tell you honestly I cannot go out with you
Too busy
Fighting the New World Order
You know if you refrained the new world order as Alex's bulshit I might have turned down a number of invitation to my license
This is really funny
Article quotes
Lana Del Rey
Trump with witchcraft
This was in response to Lana tweeting about using witchcraft to unseat Trump so I guess I can have to give it up to him
Normanfuckingrockwell
Cited the sheet music to the version of Americana that he's into
Weird
She's been working on that album for a long time
She started on it in like 26
Recording the songs are on this album
In the same time span which
You decided to take out Trump with witchcraft and Alex got really serious about it
Further
Diablo's co-produced by Jack Antonoff who dated Lena Dunham for like 5 years
Someone who Alex thinks is a literal demon
Does he somehow think that the person who dated a literal demon for a half-decade
And a person trying to untie
Trump through witchcraft came together and put out a straightforward album glorifying
The right-wing fantasies about America
I couldn't find a specific article but I also do remember Alex Chabad house
Like Lana Del Rey Born To Die album
Celebrating
Doesn't matter
You got to Blick
Dan
It's probably time for me to jump
All on a first listen I think it's a great Lana Del Rey album which is to say that it's lousy with dark sarcasm
And most of the songs are about f****** dudes you probably shouldn't f***
About Lana Del Rey's work usually has dual meeting
Involved
A complicated
However in an interview with GQ she explained
. of time when she was that
Boarding
School at the age of 14 because she was a child alcoholic
She also revealed that you almost
Exclusively drank alone
Which kind of introduces the thought that a lot of the characters in the songs on that album
Might not actually be people but drive is within herself
A lot of young does work if you view it as an ironic
Take on the vet parody of Show Business
Pursuit of wealth
I'm over everything else
But there are also other things Atlantis
Clearly expressed
Which one of the things that makes our work particularly interesting
Sound that makes
Bitingly dark
Pop songs
They also have layers
Obviously she's not the only artist out there you can speak that about but it doesn't really matter
Enjoy your work
If you disagree think I should be listening to better things
I also listen to Carly Rae Jepsen what are we doing
What's the point
One consistent thing is characterized Lana Del Rey's careers
We tell ourselves
About our culture's our lives and our country patriotic imagery for ironic
Make a fact
Alex Jones because he likes his ability to analyze things
Season American flag and thinks it's up tickets patriotic
In effect
He is what she's mocking
Because because Lana Del Rey makes really good music
Even the target of her ridicule is lured into
To thinking that she's on their side
This is really impressive stuff and it really
Delicious piece of stupidity on Alex's bar
Like a big glass of water with Juicy ice cubes
I do I do really enjoy
Unexpected twist first of all that Matt drudge is into normanfuckingrockwell Alex
Put out his gal
Wow
Americana
Really interesting
These people can both
8 +
Glorified
What album is
Representative
Back in my day we listen
What do real spring-trap
I wonder what he thinks of
Her National lamp
I wonder what he thinks Jackie O
This idyllic life
The children
And all this assassination by ASAP Rocky
That's
At the beginning of this episode is like pretty depressed
An ostrich
Patel with his like I'm your Alex Jones house
That sort of fumbling intro
But he's a little bit down
And you can hear it as he introduces
Special Report he's about
How many are 80 Harvey
Put some images to
1980s
And then we are going to
She come back
There's just a Vibe of like
Just doing it
Yeah he's
He's not bringing it
It's really interesting
Cialix
Co-opted by Paul Harvey
These days when he has a special reports Play It's always one of his employees to put it together that's a johnbowne reporter Millie Weaver
Special
Three rare frame does it take someone else's material and put images over
It makes me wonder John bowne is getting too expensive
Prowling around
The reason is choices intro
Give me though I've never heard Alex talk about Paul Harvey before
And he absolutely should have a lot
Blueprint for
Extra
50s on work
I'm not nearly as interested in those sides of things
Because I think off the beaten path
For most conservative
Speaking terms of style
That being said
There is an element in which Alex is the truth
Descendant of Paul Harvey
More than anyone else could ever hope to
He got drunk a lot on
I don't know about that baby
Smith discuss Harvey's careers episode
Consider after Harvey
Lead singer of The Cure Robert
No
MPR
Familiar
Barbie style with unique and always compelling
Even when he got to the ads
Move into his pitch making it into a story just as riveting as the news around here
The product
The intensity was the same
And for it you would pay dance
That sounds familiar a little bit
Paul Harvey's ability to make add sound like they're part of his show
From that mprp
Bruce demott
Broadcast
Communication
Advertisers love Harvey
Well
Because he moved Prada
I mean that was the key thing
Answer another article about inform NPR said quote Harvey's voice transition
Seamlessly from a Story 2 commentary to a carefully placed advertisement
Became a kind of brand
Kingmaker
People trusted what he was telling until they trusted what he was selling
Paul Harvey blurred the line between newscaster and outright salesman in a way that Dumont describes
Lesbian quotes very unfair
Feebly Behavior
For any other newscaster to engage in
A breach of ethics
Paul Harvey's careers touched a lot of the right-wing media in ways that often go unnoticed
Somewhere stylistic touches a political move
Look for Alex Jones Harvey was the king of integrating ads into your show and make them feel the same as the news
Is probably very unseemly in the 50s and it sure is unseemly today
That's so fun
Yeah
F****** Morrill stamp
What the hell are you talkin about advertising
Advertisers like him so much because he was able to use the content of his show to push the ad
Alex Carreon
Today
And I'm sure radio guys
Looks like he is
Episode
And over and over and over again
It almost more structured than other episodes
Amazon
First h s h in 3rd hour
Discreet sex
There's still a little
Alex still goes off track
But there is definitely more of a feel of like
Theme
Phim
Sarasota
Feels like it's possible or maybe Alex just like
Recognizing that maybe I should try I don't know what it is but it's very different
You know maybe the reason I'm going out of business
Baby that's the only thing that I have nobody to Market to it's really sucking up
Maybe I should ask her myself
It's too late for that but
It's interesting to see
The first
Section
The episode Alex is trying to
To push
They want to abuse
Your kids in the
Narrative
In the first hour
Do you know there's some reasons that he's doing
Directional news
But most of it spirals out to really really disgusting talk
And I'm going to try and keep that to a minimum
Except where it snows
Necessary to
Explain what he's up to
I think is really telling
Because I talked about his Jocelyn elders
Ideas
About what she was
His ideas but she was saying manually
Masturbate
School children
Specifically
Now guys I know a lot of people misunderstood me but
Go to make my
Listen clear
I want the teachers to jerk off Vicky
It was not what you was about and I was not what you was advocating for.
He remembers that
Any accidentally kind of reveals in this club first of all that she never said that
When I
Just one year out of high school
Real quick you my dear Lana Del Rey the background
Yeah he loves her
Remember listening
And I remember going looking at the things you was talking about
Play the audio
Over and over again
What you doing
Speak
Is your rates.
Then she went to Congress
I spent
Hour-and-a-half
Obsessively
Trying to find one
Version
But it's a bunch of cut
You spent an hour-and-a-half trying to find this clip excessively didn't find it because it's not a real thing that you said
It's the right-wing spin that Rush Limbaugh had back then that you've internalized as the truth
And you can't confirm it
Because it's not real
Seem like something
Claim and then people remember things
I need to confirm that I'm right
Weird
Real real
Real real big memory
Mandela effect
Jocelyn Elders was the elephant
And I didn't know that's how she supposed to do that impression quite a bit it's right up there with Bernie and hamsters like his favorite aunt
North of Ralph Northam characters
For sure
The backlash Shane Gillis got this much backlash Alex Jones
We ship
I think I would give him a shot I figure you know people who work for us
Probably more graphic than
I would like necessarily
So it's necessary in order to get us
To the point
Of what he's doing
But when your daughter's vagina or your little son
If they can do that
Infowars.com and newswars.com slideshow
Support
Little different
First of all
Today's f
Episode
It's
Brings up an interesting
Same thing but I don't think I've ever fully explain
I'm at is on Infowars actual website
They have articles and then they also have posts for everyday
Video embedded on it today's episode
And so what he's describing their that headlines
It's the doors pedophilia world
Typically the episodes post
The video of the show but no substantiation of anything
So specifics about the headline are anywhere to be found it's just quick
I decided to check out the page anyways
Make this official that the Democrats are now endorsing
There's nothing for me
But there are,
Here's a sampling of some of the responses from his listeners
Quote Epstein was extracted in his cell phone the Dead Sea waiting for Hillary to take a rifle presidency
And retroactively change
Consent to sex
She'll be just in time to party Democrat donor Electro super delicate and KKK leader Ed Buck to
Clearly
I'm not coming to claim to be the victim of Catholic
The priest abuse and says he saw one of these people targeting
Another commenter replies quote
No time like now
Another commenter says quote The Souls of our children and no one absolutely no one is doing anything to take mathematic
Collection 2
Stop them
Has done nothing absolutely nothing to save America's culture way of life liberty
Without a single unified culture ethnicity there is nothing!
Separate
National
Pretty much I'm going to go with
Decriminalize
Wilshire that's good another person I'll tell you what this is truly the directions public education is heading
Public School teachers and administrators had better arm themselves
That's really awesome
To hear all I'm hearing is look for
Peaceful transition
Power in 2020
I hope the war comes quick
This country is already past the point of no return the only way to get it back is to take
It back sure
Sure could work
Accelerationist belief on display hear this comment section
Looking for Alex isn't responsible for the actions of his listeners and Brie with that to a point
The reason the argument is pretty uncompelling to me though is that Alex is intentionally misleading his audience
Mostly explosive issues
It's clearly doing it to make them
Beatles
Commenters
There's supposed to want to Outlaw political opposition
They're supposed to want to threaten their enemies
They're supposed to
Feel so hopeless about the world that the possibility of
These people very May well have had these feelings
But the reporting style that he needs
To use in order to
Keep making money justify those feeling
Nurture those feelings
To make them worse
It would be hard for
For me to believe
Out
Endless drum beat
From Alex
It's somebody would you
Out of nowhere beer
All of my sick
Six-year-olds teachers are pedophile
Start a civil war
And they better arm themselves
We're coming
Yeah I don't think
Spontaneous
We generate within within your grasp
I bet for a small subset
Hannah people I could buy
This feeling of being
Expressed in these comments
It's pretty it's pretty unnerving
I would say
So I looked into this and tried to
Figure out what he's talking about
It's
There's an article in the mirror about the underlying topic
Text Alex's discuss
Totally made-up thing
But it's more or less just sex education issues being turned into right with b******* about the future
Performing sex acts
Some kids
The mirror article includes an image
Depart of this manual
Sex education
It's not really even encouraging kids to masturbate
The right-wing news people are are
It's really more saying that that is a normal thing people do and you shouldn't feel dirty about
He didn't even like
Sexualizing really if you look at the
The contact
Lots of people like to tickle or stroke themselves as it might feel nice
They may play with their hair stroke their skin or they may even touch their private parts
This is very normal
That's not sexualizing
No you're you're just
Is wrong everybody who died
Hose Beast
Then they should be condemned to hell
Dictates
There are
What is an average day
Everybody does
Nobody
The right-wing is our galaxy
To touch themselves in
The better the shower
Without giving any context to where that comes up in this manual
Emmanuel's using those as examples of places it's appropriate
Specifically to make the point that it's super inappropriate to do that so when other people are around
Quote it's not polite to do it when other people are about
It's something we should only do when we're alone perhaps in the bathroom shower or in bed a bit like picking your nose
This is not sexualizing this is
Stigmatizing it's
You can
Hear myself
Ya hear that Carl
In the bedroom are in the shower.
It's not even clear it's not even clear that this manual is meant to be the curriculum itself
For the teachers
I don't even know what the point is but
As far as I can tell this is also just a UK thing
This is not America
It's only at 240 schools in
UK
For some contacts
British educational suppliers Association estimates there are currently
20925 primary schools in the United Kingdom
This is very small portion better even possibly utilizing this curriculum
Alex is intentionally trying to conflate this story with the other story that we
We talked about about sex
Classes in California
And also with erroneously remembered ideas about what Jocelyn Elder said 20 years ago
Narrative that will infuriate izadi
Hey based on the comments on his website it looks like it's working
Pretty f****** well
Yeah
He's telling
Play false
Comfortable knowing
He's 100
Well if you want to have a conversation about like this should be taught at home as opposed to in school
About it like if your problem is sincerely like this isn't appropriate at a school
Escalated to giving kids handjobs
Do that
You if you had a problem with
Something real
You wouldn't
Completely exaggerated out to
A completely absurd version
That only serves the purpose of radicalizing
And you're already in the direction you want
Capitalize
And that's exactly what Alex is doing
He doesn't really long
Disgusting
Segment about this
Immediately after
Tomorrow's news today
I've never
Obsessed
Supermodel
He's literally claimed to be a Calvin Klein
He's talked about how we used to get beat up cuz he was too attractive
I got present self or whatever
He has for his youth is
So he does this disgusting sex
About the child
This crucial report
It starts with a never been saying
I like I don't like where this is heading
Irritating
In the last
Month
Religious
Nowhere so good
Wawa
Drinking more water
Workout
Better
Justin credible
Miramar
Great
It it literally is just
Does all this rile people up anchors
And then throws it to a special report
Got a really
It's just a commercial being played on the actual show cuz he knows
Migrated commercial onto the show
They could not even him doing plug
Just throw a commercial and pretend it's a special report and crazy
That's probably something
Needlepoint outages
Content
Disclaimer there Siri on Speedway
So I was so
Flabbergasted
Did buy that like first of all
The way he does these things
About
Like childish
And that's what is so
Utterly repulsive
They always make
Soulmate
And then
All just to be like a lead-in for this ad specialreport thing I was like
Go f*** yourself man
I wanted to check in on two things in the present-day that might make us all feel a little better
Couple of things
To serve as a barometer of what kind of Engagement
He's actually getting in the present
I felt like I would take a look at some of those
See what we can find out about House Fan
The first thing we've seen recently was Alex launched his troll petition to get the White House
As the 51st state
Which also actually if you go look at it includes a suggestion
Annex Antarctica is the 52nd state until the UN
The f*** off
Okay
Proposal proposal maybe it'll get water.
Big-time celebrities
Amplify
Certainly
Expand
As of noon on September 24th this petition has been up for a 5
Never 712
Which is just shy of their goal of 100,000
This is a really bad time
Progress every every vote
This tells me that the Trolli meme crowd that Alex think fully supportive are either an imaginary audio
Dance or they've left him
Like no matter how much you bring up Carpe donktum on the show that's
Not your crowd
Because if they were they would have AstroTurf the s*** out of that
For the
The reality that Alex wishes
Is to portray
Yeah he's not going viral viral
Let's storm area 5th
That's not going to have
Clearly
Meant to not have Infowars on it
For the sake of like being able to repost it or whatever
Financials are
KB on it
To like not put any red flags on here
Too sad
Is that is
Carpe donktum
On the show talks about him being great
Well he is
Spirit world
YouTube social media center
Play still looks like s*** I was scrolling through it quite a ways.
Wife a butthead over 100 like
It was Ben Garrison cartoons
And it only had 104 likes
Oh boy
I seized the dunk
The cartoon Thomas Jefferson quote about the tree of Liberty
Be watered with the blood of patriots and tyrants I can already see all of the Ben Garrison
The cartoon is a tree
A bird with a hammer and a sickle a caterpillar label Democrats
Globalism
Brilliant
Thirsty which is to say it's time for bloodshed
Right I'm not sure I've seen a cartoon
But also it's probably not that dangerous
Event Garrison's audience need all those damn labels to get what he's trying to say I don't think they'll pick up on the subjects that he's saying
People's blood
Feed the tree
If it's
I am going to have some
Complaints to the manager
Label put it on you
Hell
Subscribestar so I thought I would check in on that
He currently only has 349 subscribers
Profoundly low number for someone who claims to have the audience size
F****** Sargon of akkad is almost 2700
Subscribers
Is a damning indictment of Alex's non popularity
YouTube rip offs
Yeah he claims that that you set up that site to be place where all the people from YouTube
Disrespected
Even though he says that
It's still just an Avenue to put out in Fort Worth Conte
Every single channel is one of his
Employees
Unsurprisingly
Owen Shroyer David nights Channel
Dead zone
Almost no traffic
The same is true of Alex's new show Firepower news
Couldn't have less interest
I don't I don't even know any
Don't care
It's not going to last
Something I found that kind of interesting is
Also has terrible traffic
Realized
Kicked off of course it has the real world
It's like when it stuff is still available where it's always been that's going to be a problem
His most popular asset doesn't really mean
Meet the qualifications for being on this site
Specifically
He hasn't been there
Video
Another issue is that there's no way for Alex to Alper monetization for any of these videos
Do you have literally no appeal to most advertisers and there's no way that the Stoke Limerick guy can subsidize add
All the crypto-fascist videos that site has the potential to host
It's really a serious problem
It's like
What he's doing is solving all the wrong problems right like the right-wing scammers on YouTube remotely
Mad cuz their scam got disrupt
They figured out a game this
Suggestion algorithm
Massive amounts on Google ad Revenue
Demonetization is just as bad as being kicked off for them
And now it's really has no answer for
Let's say one of these daunting for warriors employee Maga assholes comes over and wants
Start posting pills here
There's no reason to expect there's ever going to be a way to replicate what they had with YouTube and no reason to suspect
We're going to be money in it
As a place where Alex can just post his videos
It serves that function I guess
Deep lyrics
Survivor time
The amount of content he wants to push it out to
Vicksburg post
I could see this as a good decision to make
Better time
When you could afford to take a hit as an investment
And something you could build into something
Like you lose a million this year to make 10 billion in 5 years
This kind of makes sense
Desperate
A little too late
I don't think you have time
To build this into what you want it to be
You also would never want to allow for
Beach on there
But you never want that
Course he doesn't want guns in his goddamn
Like the idea that the complaint is that YouTube doesn't allow X
On their channel on their platform
Now you created your own platform
If Alex were drunk
And be very honest that's exactly what you would say
To allow X
You don't want to you don't have to
Alright
I've got to pitch for you this is my brilliant idea
But made
Sure no one wanted to
To use it and no one would
How does that sound as a business
Look I got nothing else
The drive Wolverine backed into a corner let's video
Sure
Little indications that I
I can get are the
Aldi's
Sort of deduce
Impact
Don't match up with
Alex
And the way you present
Is audience the millions and millions
It matches up with a
Fairly successful podcast
Are about you know what you expect for the
Not for a imonti stations all over the country and Putin listens to
Yeah although now I think that puts
Listen to running for shows Putin might listen
I think
And that is that Alex revealed why he went to LA
It was to be on T.I.'s new podcast
T.i. podcast
That is supposed to drop on Thursday
It is not
It is not the Thomas
Star of
American Pie
And I can't imagine not being a fight
I don't know I will I don't want to listen to it but I do hope
T.i.
Podcast
Alex back in Austin
I think it probably will be a fight I don't know a very strong running for my cover on Friday
Literal insanity
This guy has much more of a reach than I could possibly hope for
Let's do this even if he yells at me
But
Also on the first hour was that gross
Child abuse
Second hour
Alex gets into the The Climb
So this is going to be right in your wheelhouse
I can sense it
So he's been rambling quite a bit
This point about
Just meant to
Destroy
America the weather
It's really interesting here is the way he frames
What the goal of
These climate change initiatives is
Sedam that are Target
Europe
The US Canada New Zealand Australia make the cuts and no one else does
Not India
Products
Anyone but us
I don't
So now this is interesting
List of countries
Air Canada Australia
It's weird that it's basically the exact list
Countries that formed the acronym cause
Which was the name of the organization founded by Neo-Nazi white supremacist
Alex's just swapped out New Zealand for South Africa
You know when Lions made that organization
It was in the 90s early 90s
So South Africa b b
More of an interest to him back
Not know about
We talked about it.
Appliance EMT Patriots defense fund
Specifically designed like a white supremacist
After a little while it was a little bit too problematic
Does the first
Pro White Law Firm
Because Lions felt like
Countries where the white race
Was under attack
This grouping of countries constitute
Is closely related to older whites
Supremacist beliefs and propaganda about those being white
The places where a white majority would be threatened by the Eagles
That could be a coincidence
That Alex is using
But we've also heard
Is the same thing as white
Supremacist
And applying them to the climate change
Conversation
The reason that this feels like explicit white supremacist propaganda being masked
Does beating something up being about something
Is it only these
Cortical white countries to lower their carbon emissions
But that's never been true of any climate change initiative ever
Yeah I'm pretty sure that was
Put out
Immediately after the
Treaty was signed like the right wing
Immediately
Producers of a
Is in the world in Daytona
Everybody everybody
Well
Start from the
Enforcement
No one was forced to
I caught
The things that we can do as a country or things
Are carbon credits
If you had
Used in order to help with the climate
Situation
Of course those are only going to impact.
But I do
Be a leader in the world and other countries follow
You can't just be like a high we're going to enforce our system on a
He wants a
Large
Governing body
To force
Countries
To do
What it
Says
Did you know in spite of their
Some word
Sovereignty
That word is
Doesn't depict reality
I'm not sure if all of them because some of the developing countries in the world actually had Target
That work increases in their CO2 emissions
Because of needs that they would have in terms of
Developing industrialization
To help their countries
There's no real bulshit about how these agreement
Climate change initiatives only Target
Glaringly like this
Additional white supremacist
Worldview
It's enough to make me pretty
Suspicious about what point houses really trying to make
Feels
Not about climate change
It feels like
It's all around the world
Provino's Restaurant
We're just White
Around here
You know
White knit up finger guns listen to Lana Del Rey
Cool
Of course
What evil they are
Sure
He makes the claim that
Absolutely honest
The world
Enesco
System of the UN
Haitian culture logic
Jason
Organization
Global policy
This is just
25 years ago at
Briefly
In case anyone hasn't heard the episode where we went over this
In 1993 the international lesbian and gay Association
Applied for consultative
Status with the UN economic and social
In the process it was found that NAMBLA was a member group within the ilga
At which point the ilga full membership voted to
Spell NAMBLA from the organization
Reflecting a possible unawareness that they were affiliated with the group
To begin with
Jessie Holmes introduced a bill to make
Dissociative do you want head pro pedophilia View
Resulting in Section 102 of the Foreign Relations authorization Act
Of 1954 and 1995
It's a matter of withholding all funding to the UN if their group
Associated groups with pedophilia
UNESCO is one such group
Requirements
Describing is literally
And it'll legitimately
Zero idea what Alex means by saying that Annapolis on UNESCO steering board
Different initiatives that UNESCO undertakes usually have different boards to accomplish different goals
However
UNESCO does keep a very public
Tons of non-governmental organizations that they work
What do you know
Blazing on that list
Because a f******
Corsair.
I don't know if they'd ever take the time to sue
But this is probably legally
Slander
I don't I don't know how that would work or anyting but
That's definitely
Malicious
Lie
Yeah he has reason to know that that's not true
Absolutely so I don't know I think that's probably
Desi
And it's not like we
You know it is a wood bee
Sue him
Permutations
He says the part of every group that he wants to attack internationally
Episode
Whose daughter was one of the victims
Parkland shooting
I don't have any clips of this interview because I find the whole thing
Deeply upsetting
I would venture to guess that doesn't have a good idea who Alex
But he's done even surrounded Park
When shooting itself
And if you did I would assume you wouldn't want to
I find little interest in critiquing the interview with the parents of a victim of a school shooting on Alex
Shoe Show
Is generally Alex being a dick in
It's not really all that worth
Also I mean
Pollack dozen
Don't seem like he's all that
Carstarphen
I don't want to mock him
Even if he has
Some beliefs
That are
I can definitely tell you
I could have debunked the number of
I just take no pleasure in that
Not mentioned in this interview that Pollock was instrumental in helping get Florida Senate bills
26 pack
Teachers carry guns
It's probably fine
However it also raised the age to buy a gun from 18 to 21
Haband the sale of bump stocks
Provision
Forlorn Forest
To take your guns
It made it so cops competition
Courts to take your guns and ammo if they think you're a danger
It made it so if you've ever been committed to a mental hospital
Can't have gone
Creative
Bygone
This is exactly the sort of Bill vitalik screams about all the time
To him and he has a as his guest someone was
Instrumental in getting gun-grabbing path
And get Alex doesn't
Seem to know about that or else
He thinks it's better for his narrative
To just ignore it
If I had to guess Alex knows the Pollock
I called for better safety
And try to refocus
Debate about gun Centric
Being safety
And Alex knows he can work with
Alex brother knows that he's being sued by Sandy Hook parents right now in Alaska
It's best for the brand to pretend that he wasn't involved in the Bell
And then later you can be all about how Sandy Hook parents are this kind of monster
It's pretty decent albeit Transpo
Parrot as a move for him to make
Ultimately it bores me and it seems like Alex is just using
If someone has a prop but that's nothing new
Yeah that that has
Toss-up ID on the Whiteboard
Optics how do we change the narrative
Oh I know we have
Somebody involved in those and we can be like
I believe you this is 100% real and I made mistakes in the book
And he's trying to sell that books at work
Beyond but
I don't know I'm not Charmed by that
I don't want to pile on this
B o
Stressed out
No
In the past is talk about how the new world order
The Illuminati
Approached his father
David Jones
Dentist
Either you got a protista literal
Beetlejuice yes
The whole thing
And they offered him to join up with them
To be world
Royalty or whatever
DPS
No thank you
He's not
He saw through their b******* right away
Is genius one of the smartest people in
It's from the agent
Well the stories change the little bit
Play Civilization
Explain God
Lisa first time
What
But the point is what
Know what will follow
So they asked if
What does that mean about you Alex
This is stupid
Abby doesn't clarify that.
The first time
Because I don't believe anything he says I don't care about that but it is funny
Is he in there now
That the most important thing about this
Alex said the name of the person who tried to lure him into this cult globalist
Dr. Erwin spear
The 2013 is outside the statute of limitation
Context of human amen
Who the person is that he's talking about
A day ago retelling the story
To take one and one together that's the story about there's every expectation
In every reasonable person
Would know
That he's talking about the same event in his father's
He has just committed slander again
He has renewed the statute of limitations
Erwin Spears family could absolutely sue him for
I don't know if they become less and less Irwin Spears was involved in this
It really doesn't matter
I don't know if they would win
But he is absolutely in jeopardy
Because of that brought up the story that he has explained in the past
And from what I understand
That does renew
I'm glad that you re up the subscription to getting sued
For the rest of his
So just on this episode we have UNESCO Spears estate
Possible litigants against Alex
I know you probably have
So Alex gets around to talking about how
The ruling class
They're coming out now
Kill Everybody
And there's an element of this that makes Alex
Mad
Trump
Disconnected from us now
Get rid of all of you for the Earth
Are you afraid to go to the mailbox because it letter after letter from the IRS
Great transition
Miracle cures are coming
Will not
Look into Occam's razor
Why is
Now I'm going to throw this out there
He was lying
The crisis is like falling for a con
Deeper
It's one of those things where a lot of
What some of the old
Get away with it so much
Because
Who is too embarrassing
Sing to reveal
6 million dollars
I've staked my career
Built over decades
Yep
Based on the
Convert this guy was running
You might as well would be like pushing for Randy Cramer
Alright
Feels like s*** but
It's just really sad
He's an adult really sad
So there's bad you Betty is
Climate change
Conversation that Alex has
From a little bit here but he gets back to it
And the bottom line is that Alex is trying to push the idea that they're just trying to
Are you
All the stuff is all based on
Beer
Does ironic for Alex to be complaining about quite frankly
In his work
But he
Really stressing over and over again they admit
That they're just trying to
The scare you
There's so much
Unpacking here
I'm sure you're going to
First world
And this is the talking points and then a woman is one
Element
I teach a penguins are dying
They teach him that they can't swim
They're not drowning
Middle School girls commit suicide
Lead people saying that they're just trying to scare you
I was trying to figure out what he's talking about
Cuz he doesn't use any specific
The EPA McCarthy
She recently did an interview with scientific America
He's talking about
For Alex
Any interview McCarthy has asked about taking a more systemic approach to climate issues
The conversation
Has largely shifted from one where the question is is this happening
To a question of what should we do
She commenced Cory Booker's recent comments about how his cabinet would view all of their jobs through the lens of climb
It goes on to list a few ways this
Play out in the real world like the military converting to renewable ener
All these provide opportunities for the entire complexion to the
The discussion to change from I want to
Are you into doing something on climate to
Let's be smarter about federal dollars being spent
People are demanding action that's going to be benefits
For their help
She's explicitly saying that she wants to be I want to do mentality to not be how the debate is Freya
If this is what I was talking about Alex and all the right-wing just repeat this bullshiter
Completely 100% without a doubt intentionally
Consciously taking McCarthy statements out of
The only other possibility is that they didn't even read one sentence over words
Then decided to attack her anyway
This is some b******* right here that's only if this is what he's talking about
And I have
I have every reason to assume
Because this interview came out like a day before this episode it's like it's fresh new now this is Almeda
I mean the whole that whole like
They're just trying to scare you thing
That
Guarantee that this is
Is all made up because
It's coming from everything
Single gas
It's coming from anchors are any
They're specifically
Please stay out of it
They're just coming out here to make
Substantiated
And if the news
Innovation word
Coming out here
Afraid with literally anything
That is a good point
And actually I do know what happened
I honestly thought this is what he was talking about but the reality is far stupid
McCarthy's comment because she does say the I want to scare you
You took that out of context
It makes total sense
Nonspecific about it like it makes them
That this is what he's pointing to its so much more disappointing close to right
Before we get to all that in the realities there
Little bit about this polar bears
Alex constantly makes a grave error in his attacks on the narratives the constitutionalist have about polar bear population
Their arguments aren't necessarily the polar bears are all dying off
Now it's set in the future their species
Serious Danger
Polar bears of fluctuated
The 1970s
It's from a species of least concern earlier on
The 2500 upgraded too vulnerable
It's not in dispute how many polar bear population
In the last decades
They're so
A little while back
But
Clearly know that it's because of protection that were put in place by conservation groups
Hunting polar bears
Or introducing negative environmental pressures in their habitat
The stabilization of polar bear population is large
Do the 1970
P3 International agreement on the conservation
No polar bears
Which I think Alex
Who called world government
Presumption
Yeah I always love whenever they
They're like polar bears
International law
When we needed it
Now we don't
Another factor to consider is in that. We also put in place a lot of restrictions on commercial steel
So the food source
For these Bears dramatically increase
In the same time. That it was becoming illegal to pump
Faster with more bears not being more stable food supply giving them the best opportunity to replenish the
Population
Polar bear populations of recovered somewhat
Taken up by all manner of right-wing climate denial punta
They all use the conception that
To climate change must be a hoax
Because as the climate warming the polar bear population is drastically increase
2007 book by Bjorn lomborg called cool it the skeptical environmentalist
Guide to global warming
Oh I know Bjorn lomborg
We go way back I do the name rang a bell
Brilliant
Pull that back
Okay
1860s
Any Citation for that was an article of the LA Times by guy name
Clifford Crouch
The Journal of the Society of environmental journalists look back at it look back in 2008
Peace by Peter Dykstra
I have a solid source for that statistic
And told dijkstra that quote he understood the number to be widely
The only other citation given by lomberg was a report by the Soviet Ministry of Agriculture and 19th
That guessed there were between 5,000 and 8000 polar bears in the Arctic
To talk to Dexter were quick to point out that our ability to accurately gauge
The population of polar bears was really bad
Until at least
And numbers before that point of really unreliable ask
One big problem is they polar bears really remote areas and their very hearts
Since there were
And so is the entire Arctic
I don't understand why that would be difficult difficult
Without
Technologies developed later it was really a
Precise game
The people were doing
What's the number of marbles in this
Webster
Threw those marbles into the into the
Now guess how many marbles used to be in the
Challenge
So people who study the issue state of the populations have recovered in their higher than they were like 40 50 years ago
But not nearly the jump the climate deniers constant
Bentley pedal
And they're also quick to point out that the issue of their recovery has nothing to do with climate change
All about the international
Restrictions on
And the Food Supplies replenishing
Because of international law
It is it is them claiming
They fought
Chanel 2K
And now using a
Propaganda tool to fight tooth and
Janelle to make sure that
Absolutely
F******
It makes you want to rip your hair
The problem is a polar bear's do rely on
As Alex's accurately
Are projections currently look like by about 2040
And that likely approximately 30% of the remaining polar bears will die off because of
Which will lead to
A big
The discussion of polar bears is one that's around
Make it about comes that we are
Experian
Not a description of things that are happening now
Alex is really just pedaling thoroughly misleading
In order to attack
Now the last part of that clip
Suicide because
Does the climate change
And I have no idea what specific case Alex
Talking about
Young middle schooler killed herself be
Because of climate change
I'm not saying that didn't happen
I believe it's possible that it did
I can I looked I couldn't find the story
But he's talking about
I don't want to say this
Never happened right in the off chance that it hasn't
Couldn't figure it out and find the specific story Alex gives no information about it
Outside of a middle school person
Suicide climate
The right-wing talking
When is about house
But I can't find one
Specific person
Who did
Commit suicide
Because of climate
This year old lawyer David buckle
Email media Outlets are made unhealthy by fossil fuels
Early deaths as a result
My early death by fossil-fuel reflects what we're doing to ourselves
You left a note for First Responders saying quote I'm David buckle and I just killed myself I fire the protest suicide
I apologize to you for the map
David
Brandon
Tina's mother
Against the Sheriff's Department
Who told Tina's eventual murders
Accuse them of rape
Which almost certainly liked his murder
Arbuckle was a civil rights lawyer well ahead of the Curve
At a protest suicide was absolutely not the result of
Published
Climate change
Connection between climate change and suicide
But it might be inclined to draw the wrong
Conclusions
Marshall Burke was the lead researcher and you found that there is a link between
Temperatures in suicide rate
So the conclusion was it if consistent temperatures are higher than you
Increase suicide
It's easy to take a poorly-written headline about this study and Come Away with the wrong idea that this is a study Lincoln climb
A change in suicide
If you don't read the articles you might assume the climate change
Beers are licked
Play suicide by this
Just not the case
I found that crop damage caused by temperature
Increases is
Is associated with elevated suicide rates
India so there are definite things to be worried about
That said I don't know what case out
Is referring to
And I don't
I don't think whatever he's talking about is a large phenomenon
That's it going on
I think there's other conversation
The people are having
And other insta
But Alex's
Clearly
Well there's
We always say we
Correlation
Causation
We always say
I think that's
As far as I know what the
Point is space
I don't know if it says
Survey
But a large
Number of people on
Under the age of 20
Weather now
About climb
It for them of course.
From
Talk to your therapist
Crest about how there's a
Fear about what the few
If you were to do it like Alex
Probably isn't
Therapy
Play you know the fears that Alex has introduced into their lives
I don't know if he's just a big old hypocrite
Therapist wouldn't be like
Now that's a legitimate fear
I don't know I just think there's a lot of
And there's just a load of b******* in it
It's really
It's pretty crazy
So when you see these things
He's like really direct misrepresentation
Past off
It makes this next clip even more
But I think at this clip is really just like
Describe it other than like this show is a parody of
Do you know like what you do when people try and make fun of the Juggalos can't
Yeah makes fun of that
Damn braces
You can't do it
I always feel like I can't
Fun of this clip
I don't know what else
I think it's ridiculous
Please don't forget
We are bringing Black Friday
Percent off all preparedness water filters air filters
Troubleshoot
Look at that
A free shipping
We talked about like the Easter sale yeah I got nothing for two months early on Black Friday
That's just beyond
Yeah
Defeat what you
Commercialize while at the same time being like
Are Black Friday sales 2 months
Early
Intuit
Is commercialism
I got it
I don't have many Juggalo reference
Fluoride bagel
Alex has
On the show to talk about 5
She is an employee of Infowars who went out to the climate protest in Austin
Aaron's
Tristan footage
I bet they're going to go out
Very important talk about that
They're not important at all
But I do have one thought and that is that I think Savannah Hernandez
This is unfortunately
Very similar to everyone else
Possibly kind of
Because she's talking about how she was afraid of climate change
When she was younger people that she uses to describe what she was afraid of
2012 was not necessarily about climate change apocalypse
All the signs
Coming out and saying guys we got to prepare we're all going to drown in 2012
You talkin about the day after tomorrow that like Faster movie
That was what
2004's of the remember one that was talking about that
Yeah
The cultural fears about 2012 weren't driven by let's take
As much as they were people like aliens people
Alex Jones nothing Fair he wasn't
That is
Great
Albert very good
Distillation of
What it takes
To be good
Infowars employees
Be afraid of something and then find a movie and then call the movie fake
And now you don't have to
Yeah
Just had like oh yeah you know what if you're listening to her and not really paying attention or know all that much
You'd be like we're afraid back then
True
Obviously climate change
Bored
For that one so you don't want to bring that up
On the show
It's been wrong about predictions
Actually like
I don't know that one
Might have been right
Scientist predict super hurricane
On the list
So great didn't even know there was a category 5 on the third Category 5 of this year
The other one I don't care too much about that
Service of building up his idea that to everyone who talks about climate change
Lies
To you about it
Uses a specific example
Little unfair
National Geographic
They took a picture of this
Actually States
So
What
She's kind of misrepresenting things here a little bit
Two things
National Geographic took
The picture and stuff and
What happened here
Was it a photographer named Cristina mittermeier and found
Captured footage
Expedition was explicit as explained
Photographer Paul nicklen
Communicate the urgency of climate
Documenting its effect on wildlife
With this imagery thought we try to help people imagine what the future of climate change
Might look like
Neither She nor Nick ever explicitly tied the Bears condition to climate change
That was done by National Geographic when they picked up the footage and attach the words quote this is what climate change looks like to
The video
Mittermeier responded to the backlash
The video caused from climate denial list fired
Set the caption was probably going a little too far
And even National Geographic
Get that as much
Any flight retract
But that's far from saying that they are just making
Stop up
It was only a recognition that they could
Prove the climate change
To do with the specific bear starvation
Which was never claim being made by the photographer
But you know what that's kind of
The point
Inventor Myers explanation post about this
She says quote
I can't say that this bear was starving
Because of climate
But I do know the polar bears rely on the ice on Wichita
Fast warming Arctic means it's
Sea ice is disappearing
Increasingly longer periods of time each year
That means many more bears will get stranded on land where they can pursue the seals walruses and whales that there are their prey
And where they will slowly starve to death
The caption implied more than anyone knew about the specific bear but the specific bear wasn't evocative realistic portrait
What the future holds
A polar bears
If anything
Sloppy editorial work but absolutely not a guy at all climate change activist
A conservationist
Are just making s*** up to scare kids or whatever
Just a indica
Fat that whole thing
Have like
Look you're misunderstanding
Everything in your make
Faith argument towards us
Maybe you have the
Tennis
Ferris
Sliver of a point
Still we're just going
Can you come out and words
We don't want to do
We just don't want to fight
This b*******
Fine we can't
Polar bear is dying
Never going to stop saying the
That's what they should have said was
Go fuc yourself
Right that's what I ever
I also see the side of National Geographic erring on the side of like
Let's
Let's Pretend are
Our standards
It's not that I don't under
And where they're coming
It's absolutely not that and it's not even that I
Sara Lee disagree with the
But with this
Bulshit
That's why we lose the messaging
Over again
We are not going to climate
Because of
Bunch of s*** but we talked about this
All the time
If you and I
Have a slight disagreement
May fight you emotional
People like National Geographic need to uphold the standard
Hey we need equally
Not equally large cuz
Because largest
National Geographic
Making that go f*** yourself
You know people like you can say those things
Can be a messenger
Can play by
Editorial standards
Or actually yourself
And we just have
Editorial Sandra
Abu star go f*** yourself
That's your mission
So earlier I thought
Sarcastic
I was saying earlier that I thought that I was basing they've admitted that they're just trying to
Are you on the comments made by Obama's former head of
McCarthy
Saying that they could easily be taken out of
Seems like Alakazam most
Had all of the pieces in place
But you know what
I was giving him
Way too f****** much credit
But later in the show he reveals what he's talking about it like
I can't believe I thought he read an article
Because you know what
It's just a random person in Savannah Hernandez report
Irreversible
Sometimes
This is what he's basing it on just
Brand of people that interviewed at the climate change rally
I thought he was talking about the former head of the EPA and lying about her
Just random man on the street s*** dude the leaders are admitting all yeah
What the f***
Describe
Flimsy the s*** is
From
The right way
The climate March
What about Goes My Mind
And is literally
Every answer that
Is actually very real
Reasonable
Intelligent and they're like
Look at these dumb dumb
They don't even bother with
First news after that like
I
Irreversible after
10 or 12 years but
That is the data on it and
Sure it is scared
But you know what you need
Scare people
To force them into
And I mean that is
That's something that everybody knows
Great
When I was listening to this
Report
If you filed
Why is she getting straight answers
Climate change real
She doesn't have info
Well so she heard a lot of facts
Certificate
Citizens
Action 7 News
She's with Action 7 News
Manipulative
Alex knows that when is reporters go out to places they'll rightly get yelled at
Flipped Offenbach absolutely with always going to happen
With that
Don't get me wrong it still serves a purpose
He knows that when he sends Kaitlin Bennett out for him
At her and tell her to f*** off
People questions and they all just go cut girl at me
She's a lightning rod for that kind of response cuz most people know who she is
No interest to do much more than laughing at her
And the best way to monetize that reaction is selling victimhood narrative
You just do that about everything
Like what the climate protest
It's a little off Target to just paint the protesters as a rabble-rousing
In Crowd of rude people
That's all just really hunt on
Everyone else is rude
How to run the risk of the audience eventually catching on and realizing
Just saw the public response to you
Can't really do much in public anymore he's sort of cross that recognizability
Threshold so people don't really respond well to
Like children
The perfect solution is a new woman reporter who no one recognizes
Is pretending she doesn't work for Infowars
No one has any idea who Savannah Hernandez
An Action 7 News sound so bland is to be
Probably real
And that she's able to ask people questions and record their answers under false
Pretenses
Most of the people would not talk to her if they knew that you worked at Infowars
Both she and Alex are fully aware of it
What they're doing is like a hidden
Prank show but with no reveal
Can we do
Wells interesting
Okay there we go according to the ethics section of journalists. Org
For the news to have credibility
Ethical Lenoir News gas
They go on to say quote most news organizations agree that journalist
Generally should identify themselves a news organization in the course of routine newsgathering
It is not appropriate to mislead or deceive someone you're interviewing
Subterfuge
The general exception to this guidelines when someone is doing investigative reporting
And they're Undercover
But generally speaking the guidelines on that are really
Based on like is it appropriate is the news that you're Gathering
So crucial for the public to know about
That it justifies go over the cover
Is it is it
You can only get this by going undercover is there a safety
I don't think the meat packing
Industry was going
Going to tell up to
Sinclair everything on
The update on the up-and-up it's probably not
On the updating Upton if you
I want
But if it's wants to play it
I guess that's
It says something deeply pathetic about the state of things
They're so not credible
So disliked University mop
Republic protest
They have to conceal their identity
Amazing
That is bad
Daddy's back
Sunglasses and Charlie Chaplin
In order to go out and
In order to adjust normal interview go
You have to resort to
Sinclair levels of
Deception
I mean
Unseemly
That's not good
News Operation
If it was subjected to that kind of scrutiny
All this s*** they do be
So laughably disqualifying
Pretending you work somewhere else to go do man-on-the-street interviews
The f*** out of here
Rur
The response
Is this app
Because you're using
Deception
To ask
Right
So buy a by default all of this stuff
You have to do is like well
Throw it out
Even though these answers if the people give are innocuous
Financers to question
It's still like
You do
You're lying to retrieve that information
That's interesting because
It's almost
It's almost the inverse
I would I would say
Like if you were
If you are coming at me with an Infowars micro
I would never give you
So the only way
The only honest
Answer is going to come from Jessie
They're only going to get
In response to an alternate reality
Deceptive when Gathering the information
India
Interviews and then be further deceptive and how you present
Responses that
At the point where
For Infowars to actually get a
Can answer from someone they have to go full under cover journalist
Great
That doesn't bode well
Everyone's disposable once they are recognizable
That is really in
They have gone
Through that
The abyss no longer looks back at them
Like hanging out with you
I will bring them
Stealth Destroyer amazing
He's that goes viral that ruins her usability in any other video
People start to notice
Owen Shroyer can't really do is man on the street B because everyone reposted the videos
The kid
Telling him to f*** off without anyone
Ford
USA
Like anybody that he has
Has to stay obscure
There is a ceiling to the amount of attention they can get
Which is self-defeating
Getting popular blows their cover
It's like that
I'm doing one of those
What are those interviews with somebody who doesn't want to be identified so they're in all black and they
They've got their voice modulator
The interviewer is the one who said all black with a voice modulator
Walking to the to the door opener does not look good for the future
So Alex
But it's very uncompelling
Think we've hit the lot of them
Alex
At this point
He's brought on Jewel-Osco
Get the cows in there which is interesting because he's someone who doesn't like Trump
Someone who has wings
His influence on Alex
Amadeus
Alex
Like used to be
You far more of an ex
And him coming around
Does
The Alex is more willing
Criticized
Moving on anything
He is a rock
Give someone who is
Very dead
His ways
Has his own business
The world affairs brief or whatever
Comfortable
Alex is bringing him around I heard him on episode
A couple weeks back to
And he been gone for
A bit
Yeah I can't remember the last time
Talk about a present
Periodically
The longtime
In between
Edwards before he was pretty regular gas
Slight
Wavering on a
Is part about Trump
You want to talk about
Geopolitics
Whatever you want whatever is that you're thinking of
He's got a dump
False
Everything is about
Uniform
False flag
Got everything
Alex wants to impress
Temperature out video
At the beginning
Lana Del Rey
First let's go
What's your from this little piece that triggers leftist
Introduction for the video and already it's probably going to be again
Alex made a second Ms video where he's just doing that Asian
Because it's let's get
Triggered
Video
He's just a second video like this and it's just a commercial for his band videos
That's just
Wow I have no I don't know
True sympathy towards Alex
Two and a half years still don't
Hi I mean but that is
It's just
The closer
This I can get
Is just like watching
Look he's a monster but if I was walking by Eminem
And he was
A goddamn gutter
Likes it all over his f******
A chimney sweep from Mary
Okay
I'm like Alex
I really hope you die sooner rather than later but
Taxman
I'm sorry if you're a family member a weird Asian
Voice
You do it
Triggers the liver
Anybody talk about this other than us
And we were not triggered as much as we were mocking how sad desperate attempt
This is
Trigger people
In order to get them to repost it
Talk about how bad you are in order to get free
Like we're not triggered by this
It's a little too it's too transparent.
Just promoting your stupid video website
You couldn't be more clear what you're trying to do
Any soap
Proud of himself
The the
The cherry on top
Look at what I did
Gazzali's left
Sydney weather
Tylko home
Bad job
Thousands response
The video
He's an ID login
He's not going over to Alex's side
Skeleton is still polite
Do cows always so serious
He was not
Brilliant
Come up with
Info
We will be The Gatekeepers abilities
Sure seems like
Kick people off if you want the lost by not allowing long
What is Mike Brian stelter
I'm still on YouTube
Such ridiculous bulshit presentation
This is all about promoting Infowars
His own content
Contact I guess
I highly doubt
But like
It's about that it's about funneling
People to Infowars
And anybody who's not
There's no reason for him to give them
Unless there's someone here
Like Sargon of akkad
If you has a big fan base
If he wanted to channel on there
Allison probably allows
Him more traffic
But they're still
Stupid
Even for what
Aspires to be
I don't see the path that works
And it's not worth it
It expires today
No it is
It is
It has all the Hallmarks
A half-ass
It has every Hallmark of
People like
What we got to do
We just got to do something
Because everything that we've been doing isn't working so let's let's try this
You don't have any
Providers other than
People who work for
It's responding to something that people want
Like you hear all these
Really messed up
Places with internet
We need an alternative
To you too
Right
Thinks or Acts
It's like he's feeling that need
But what he's actually doing is
Gatekeeping
Creating his own space
No one
Who are in those
Say crypto-fascist
Neo-Nazi or Jason
White nationalist
Pipe world
They're not going to
To come on Alex
Right
The thing itself
Success
Have to have before you even launched
Had to have a bunch of people already Chris totally
What's the people who worked for Spotify
Few more cable
You have to have a catalog
When you launched
Otherwise it
It's going to disappear nobody
So either this
Completely
Clips
Care too much about that
But three things that I think are particularly absurd
ER
Countdown
In no particular order just in chronological in the interview order
Here's the first one
Well they don't have any basis of knowledge
Pro Services because they don't understand the concept
Socialism always have hidden victim regulations always have hidden victim
Capitalism
Notoriously
System is
Entirely right or without problems
If that is one of your Marquis criticisms of people who
Push for socialist
Cleaning policies
You are an idiot
You're pretending that
Hidden victims are your problems and you should also have robots
Critique of capitalism problem
It's not unique to this
His problem is he
In socialism
Hidden victims
Where is right now
That might be more accurate way to read his comment
Even if you don't want to apply that like assumed motivation
He's still making any
Credibly Slim
Lindsay argument
A nonagon
Stupor
You know your response everybody not an argument
God I hate
She's the worst
Making a prediction coming in at the number two
But the big
Problem comes in World War 3 when we're going to absorb a nuclear First Strike our military's going to be decapitated in Raleigh-Durham
You're going to come out
We didn't know this was happening but the only way we can defend ourselves now is to join in a militarized global government with tax
So we're going to absorb the first nuclear First Strike of the globalist
To be in Bunker's or readout
Emergent create a one-world government
False flag
Nothing has
You know what I find
That nothing is ever happen
Is that
Nobody is talking about how the only way the human race survives
Is if we
Absorb
Do you know what I mean like
Except a first-strike kind of created equal a reaction of
Nuclear
Super clear you're not saying the only way
I don't know if I can hunt
But I'm inclined
Agree with that
Because that's one place
Being nuked
Diversity
Everybody what's the Chain Reaction starts it's all
The only way would be if somebody is
Like guys
We're not going
To respond
The State of Affairs is everyone dismantling their nuclear weapons
But
That were not responding with
Equal measure is a preferable outcome
CIAA events Nuclear Strike would be devastated
Being one of the worst thing that could ever happen
Right
Of all of the
Do we need to have
To keep our ability to strike first on the table is like
You're insane
You're absolutely
You would ever use them.
And anybody who doesn't say
That is
Insane is insane
Yes I had a hard time tracking
F****** stupid
Then you simply have to say I'm sorry we're not dealing with this anymore
Public Schools you don't try to improve an inherently evil institution it just keeps people in there longer
How to Public Schools even through private her homeschooling education
Everybody skousen
There are some hidden victims
Maybe a couple baby a couple
I don't I feel like
Is
It's the same thing with a lot of these initiatives that Alex really wants
Gaston
In This World Views they put forth
4C
An ideal situation off in the future
Which is like everybody's homeschooled and we're all great
Realize is that the process
That outcome
Would be devastated it would destroy countless lies
Pluto from ever reaching the destination
There their method
To get to where they want to go
Makes it so that end goal is
See where you coming
Bvn
I just think it's delusional to think
You're ever going to get to a point where everyone
Able
To take your kids out of school and homeschool
Like from a financial
From a life Logistics
There just isn't
The ability
For everybody to do that
In the sky
What you're advocating for is
Never
Prove the public schools
I find this repulsive
I find this to be a terrible
Prescription for life
Are people who
You know wouldn't be able to
Use the remedy to begin with right
Would be able to homeschool
Work multiple jobs
It's just prohibited for them
By what you're suggesting of let's make the schools worse
Yeah well this is
The first clip is
Is very clear
Where is right now
I am not a victim
And I don't really
Care about the
People who are
When you talk about the elitist
This is out of touch
Completely
Ballpark
He just doesn't
Even comprehend
The live
The people who aren't
He also goes on to say
That doesn't mean
Think that you should have
Everybody everybody
Has a choice I guess I don't know
I mean specifically
With the scouts I don't want
Teaching anyone at the arch
Family of anti-communism I do trust
Curriculum
Yeah
Hi I just
I think it's
Absurd
Mentality you are just like
Applying whatever is true
Subjective
To you on everyone
Objectively
It's deeply unfair to
People's life
What you're advocating for is hurting
That's all
It's that same
Kind of concept
So many of these
Well you know what
Is that the government is running
My family's running
I guess
Why you think that
But you're an idiot
So go back to f****** public
Old school and don't listen to your dad
Yeah
Never been
Situation where people are like
Schools are so good
And everything is just whatever's on sale
These guys
The really cheering for
Negative outcome for everyone is unlike themselves and that's
Very consistent threat
It was interesting to me I mean like first of all the Lana Del Rey
Is just like
Cannot be more excited
About this
Weird progression that makes me
I do feel a little weird but where do we go next
So what are you got I don't think you ever get on board of Carly Rae
I'm out
Never going to be
Rainbow
Rainbow Dash
Yes I think you would have a lot of trouble with like woman
Yeah and
Learn to let go I don't think you'd like I really do
But they would like that
Really evolve dozen artists from her days of like
Warrior album
She's definitely come a long way but the progression is something absolutely not be on board
He's a
You going to go backward
Michelle Branch
What else
Neko Case
Maybe
I don't I don't know it's very absurd I love it though
Texting is this sort of like
3 act structure
Show kind of hat
Things that are
Kind of on message
For Alex
And that's very strange
You know you have the kids
Then schools
And the beginning and then the interview with
The Parkland father
That makes up the first hour
2nd hour is all the climate
Third hour is interview with Joel skousen
Much more of a rigid structure that other
Episode
Leaving to the present day that I've lived
And I don't I don't know that makes
Easier to
But it wasn't
As much of a chore listening to it
Alex is like scattershot and literally just bouncing off the walls
This very difficult
Keep up with him
Keep track of like what are you even saying
Maybe this is
Blessing
For me and Subway
Terms of actually
Dealing with you.
In keeping with Alex
Truth
It is one of those things
Either that
Giving a
And trying to make a better show
Studies completely
We're giving up
And me letting somebody else tell him what he's giving his producers more
There's no lighters
Anymore it's possible that like his sobriety is
Kicking in his clearing up a little bit from those days when he was
Scream about the ways to learn
Sometimes helps you with your mental organization
Stirrup for a while
It could be I never believed him
When he says anything's yeah but he has
You know
Not drinking and trying to exercise more
And there's a decent it just puts him in a place where he's better able to organize
What is presented
If you look back
He's all over the place but
You could make
2019 2018
So much just like
This guy
Is on WOW
Process of thinking
Is disorienting
There's still a bit of that
Maybe maybe it's a sign
And it is just as producers
I'll be more on the ball or
It could be is
Last-gasp
Attempt at like
Maybe this will write this year
Control mice
Who knows
Alex
Rainwater
Ice Cube NWA Ice Cube
Juicy ice
Alex
On Friday with either another present because Alex
We don't know his response at
Set timer recording
Where you said that
The future is not for globalist
It's for Patriot
And we have to assume Alex's freaking out about that
Skip this episode on time we don't have time to see this
We may have to do that on Friday
Or we might have to do the
PTI podcast
Website
We do have a website
It's knowledge fight
You bet we also are on Twitter
We are and if you want to download the
You can go to ice
Believer of you that be really great
You could recommended
But let me tell you
About the bay
Way to get
The shop
Country
Exactly you got to go down to Sonoma you go through there
Is Rosa padros
Does grapes if you've ever seen it in
In the fall time of year
I've been amazed
You're going to walk down the 38
Throw of the Sonoma
I thought for sure one of them
My brain just shut off all the wineries
Grab the third grade pull it out there
Driving there now
The problem of specific
Guys will be back but I'm Leo Clark I am the juiciest
Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color