Respectful
Knowledge fight
Knowledge
Need money
Cam
About Alex
Exhausting time going on
Real quick
Sure
Question
I might have time for both of us
Picture of
Or receiver of
A surprise
Nope next
I've been involved in one
Hey there is no memory
Where I am
I know that I've yelled surprise at somebody
Idaho
I am sure that I've been at a party where we all surprised but
To the extent that I remember any specific way it means I might have been like a third to your friend that was
Therefore a surprise birthday
I don't know that I think I'm pretty lucky in that I don't think anyone has ever thought like
I think I would actually probably definitely
I would enjoy is not the same as thank you for syrup
I will try not to be grumpy
Unfit
No idea
Assume I have
I was just checking
Clarifying
Notable
Surprise party
I do know a lot about Alex Jones
Today in the world
The hills are alive with the sound of b*******
Going on in the world
Put out our last episode
But we've done it before a lot of the news that's irrelevant people probably interest
Analysis
Gone the present
September 24th
Open 25th
Which would be worth that Tuesday and Wednesday
Have this week Ryan
There's alot going on
So we've got first of all for everyone who doesn't know the sort of the
The broad Strokes of what
Been going on we have the
Trump Ukraine situation
Posterity
We have the news breaking of the impeachment inquiry in the house
We have Trump going to the UN and saying that the futures for Global are not for Global Entry.
He said Patriots I can't even listen to him speak for
Speech
Beyond Justice contact
It's delivery was like a dude who got hit with a quaalude Dart like it was very lethargic
Every time somebody describes
Maybe I should listen
It was upsetting
Alex playing Alonzo
Of course you got all that stuff and then the big breaking news on Wednesday was the Alex Jones has launched his web
That he's been talking about forever
5 blocks
Space
As we go through
There'll be minimal bar
And make this podcast.
So first of all
You are now policy walk
Next
I'm a policy wonk
Ruto thank you so much
Cayenne pepper
Hyphen hyphen
Thank you so much right now apology
Amapola
I'm a policy wonk
No I'm so also a couple people who have signed up on an elevated level
Config thank you so very much
Apologies
And thank you so much
Sign
Oh no
Plau gauldin
You know it's not fair
It's not fair I don't want to be
This guy who can't pronounce your name
Will putting two I'll take the blame
About the appreciation thank you so much allow fine
You're now along with mosque
Wonderful
Heroin
So good
Freakishly large
First one absolute
Correctamente
Looks like it's math can fix
Patreon
So
Is an out-of-context drop
From Today Show
Stupid
Why can't you turn on the country
That's rough
That's bad news for Americans
When they lose the king of Americana the king of loving this country
You people are soft
As we get into this
The beginning of the show is the first 20 minutes of it is just a pretty uninspired attack on Greta thunberg
Who is 16 years old
Alex spent the first chunk of the show comparing her to Hitler and talking about the Hitler
I had to be sure Greta's age doesn't make her above criticism but it's her off-limits to this style of Target
Even if you thoroughly detest the message that you
Keep putting out
Like I missed out on some prime Duncan opportunities in the course of doing this podcast
As it relates to self
The racist fourteen-year-old or Alex's done wreck
But it's just not right
To treat you just like that even if you disagree vehemently about their position
Or at least that's my position that I think that
A pretty decent way to operate
I mean especially if you imagine yourself back when you were
Some of the things that you were you said you probably saying
F****** Hitler Youth for crazy
We've even talked very little about the Covington kids
Almond podcast accepting the contact
Barnes lawyer
Yeah like they might be assholes or whatever but it's not
Leave that for other people
And I don't think this because I don't think Greta
At her age
And being a part of this younger online generation
I'm sure thing is her skin is thick enough to not care too much about what a loser like Alex Jones
It's more the disordered Behavior as the exclusive action of someone who is it by
It's a sort of thing that Alex would be deeply ashamed
To do where he capable of that emotion
And think it's even sadder is that he's just
Repeating other people's ideas
When are Wednesday episode came out where we went over September 23rd
Responses from listeners wondering why we didn't cover Alex talking about Greta
If he was complaining about the all that climate change
GameStop through a good part of that Epic
And I probably should have made this more clear he didn't really talk about her at all on the 23rd
It wasn't until Tucker Carlson did a segment about her on the evening of the 23rd
That you even really entered Alex's head as a Target
Who's talking points
Escalating them
And repackaging them for Annex
Estadio
That's really all that's going on here at the beginning
It's crazy I was looking at the episode
Why we're almost a half-hour into this thing and there is nothing happening
Except that
I watched
Heroin
Man
That Alex does misrepresent belongs in a movie of the one that we're living in
Where we die very shortly
Generation is playing
Generation
They have reason to know what they're doing and still failing
Alex interpreted that as a big brother
Call Ray Charles
Call Dowd
Because people applauded at that and I was just looking at all of them
The all of the people applauding
Those are the ones she's watching
Actively f****** destroying the planet
Don Alex
Is that her Target
Who she was
Speaking most
Condemning lie about wasn't
People like Alex or even these climate deniers necessarily
But the people who will love
Conviction to do so
Entire conference
Pelosi
Sure
This was a big chunk of the episode cuz we're going to get into
Stop
It feels kind of in media res
A ways into the episode because it is
I just don't have any
We're listening to him
Y'all about how a sixteen-year-old kid is hit
Pathetic we are still going to talk a little bit about some of those,
Yahoo
That's.
Why
Alex has
Here's what I want
Popping in
Great
To talk about
The death of
The Donald
Pro Trump
Or domain
So he's going to have carpet
Right right right to give a good moratorium on the Donald
Really standard stuff
And we'll get into a little bit of it but even without listening I knew what this was going to be about
I'm going to talk about the
I copied octopus started his memeworld site and he's trying to lay claim to the legacy of the Donald subreddit
He's hoping that he can direct traffic from the people who are there
Is there were millions of visitors do the Donald
There are not millions of visitors
Exercise
Parsley because his website suck
Partially because what made the Donald work
Aw to do with the infrastructure of Reddit
How old is desiigner
Memeworld has a vastly inferior structure
Google casually browsing the site
Who are the targets of the memes that would come out of the Donald
Without the underwear audience of millions upon whom you can subject
Your b******* lose
And I suspect is going to learn that lesson
The hard way
Cuz he is really pitching in with
Disney World built
Vague
H.h.
It's like watching two dinosaurs try and drive
That's like
Do not belong
Wrong
You know globalist
Stuffed starts ranting about demons
There's no better way
Just ranted about bulshit
Program
Intron
The program
Forbes India
Free will destroy
And
My systems
System
Colossus
Built on mud
Keep
Empower
Look at you you're falling and ugly
Check on their form.
Nothing more than slaves let's look at Greta
The Grinch
What
A fossil fuels pictures
They're real or not for parrots a
Hey guess what
Vaccination records is my next
He's clever
Videos how to make a sentence
Girls baby
And it's just
It's Pat
She's attacking her
Your mind's been destroyed
Even great to do an adult
Do you know who insulted
16 year old
Cool guy
Sixteen-year-old oh yeah
Do you know who shouldn't
Adult year old
Brilliant genius types like Alex Jones yesterday
That she's trying to get rid of the fossil fuel
She's trying to rule by destroying fossil fuels
If she can successfully destroy fossil fuels
She could forget you have shown yourself
To be a fossil fuel
You have put yourself in League with
Literally I well yeah I do that so you may not know that but I got you
Weird things that
It's almost like it's a god
Earth starts losing its atmosphere
A trace cash
1%
Suddenly we find
Giant supplies of Hellboy
In the Earth
Poquito
Zoom in
Sure
Yeah
So I find this really weird because here we see Alex telling his audience with the real issue with climate change
Change is a parademon CO2 to the air because the Earth is CO2 deficient God placed
Fuel reserves into the ground so humid
Find them adjust the time
Attar's
For me because you know the ravings of a lunatic
But it's also weird because I thought it was
Rich Al Gore and George Soros destroying the last
Now it's a plot by demons to stop
Story straight
Metastasize
CO2 levels are at their lowest ever
Complete bulshit
Thousand Years
Which is a lot longer than Homo sapiens been around
Some 10,000 years ago
What's the present day
Highest atmospheric CO2 level
Where it levels unseat in recorded history
In order to know when the last time
It's
Uncharted waters
Sick. Was marked by Massive
CO2 explosion
That's why the plants
Priscilla large
Are some theories
Port
Can't argue with that
What do you not want sports to do well
Sports
Completely opposite of credible Source I can find
He's not living in reality
Just promoting real battle of Armageddon
And you really got to ask yourself why would someone do that
So I should tell you this
I got you about an hour into the show and it dawned on me that
Hadn't even read
Prince Donald Trump
Where you know you said that
Future doesn't belong
Which is basically him doing Alex's show
In front of you
These Trump gave his remarks at approximately 9:15 a.m. Austin time so it was legitimately No Way Out
Should be unaware of that speech by the time he goes on air at 11
You seem really strange to me that he's waste
Thing is. I'm rambling about Greta thunberg and
Talking about that guy we're going to have Carpe donktum on to talk about the Donald
Doing nothing related to
Everyone else is concerned about
It's very strange to me
Videos I want to cover
It should be like we are
Tyvm the secretary-general
Because if he
Play the
The clip of it everybody go
Where you haven't listened to
And Alex does play the clipse
So weird
Country this is
Business
I hate globalist
I love Patron
Here's the president saying exactly that
He's going into the den of vipers and he's like
Statesman coming up there you can make all sorts of this is the easiest
Kingspan printed today
It's so weird cuz there's no indication until
The show
But even really has heard it knows anything about it
It's very strange
Instead
He spends time
Complaining about climate change
And tell him almost certainly fake story about his birthday
I have that
Parents
Lisa daughters the song Summer
The great Stan
My daughter comes home and cries when she drives by Tuesday
Just want to die
And so I kind of hear what you're saying is right now
A true story
That's a true story true story if it was
Explain by going to last episode you talking about like middle schoolers
What do you have to back that up an apocryphal story about a mother at a pool party
Didn't happen
Middle School
That's a problem
That is a
No problem I think there is some holes in the story
Libero volleyball
Even if your kid was best friends with Alex Jones
You're not
Going there I mean you might just because it's unsafe
You might assume it's unsafe otherwise
I don't even know what this conversation
I don't even want to try and decode with a reality the Salvation might be what kind of polite conversation Alex's
Whatever
Ceramic Appliance more about Greta thunberg and this is great
Production Value Inn
On full display
So let's go ahead and roll video.
You're just a brief Exchange
Come walking in the UN
Are you up
Look at that
Amazing
That wasn't
Oh no
Oh no he can hear it but we can't know video
They are about doing the radio show
Cheese's
Yeah there's a reason I don't think we've ever played like
A video
And I know Alex like I bought all these
Butts
You should you should think about the format
What you doing
It alright
Play wonderful
Keaton short right now everybody's
You know there's conversation even on the 24th that's going around about
Peachment
Trump
Starting to throw this around people having the conversation
Should be like we got to do it
Butter in Adel
Strongly
Curtail
The subjective actually
Doesn't have
To deal with any of the
The Mercury issue
The desert their conversation
I would say
Moving so fast
Coming up
So wild
I was on Morning Joe
He said that
To turn that into they're calling for the assassination of trump
Hey it's a Republican
Trump list
Anderson Primary
Start talking about the UN
But he still doesn't really bring up the
Globalist Patriot
Instead he has the
Nope
What
Abortion the Second Amendment
He's just done a lot
You got a lot
Making does he actually believe the Trump is the fur
First u.s. president to use talk about religious persecution
He became president
Horrible set September 2016
From that speech
Progress is possible to preserve our identity
Dominate another group
If our religion leads us to persecute those of another face
If we Taylor people who are gay
If our Traditions lead us to
To prevent girls from going
It's cool if we discriminate on the basis
Is the race or tribe or ethnicity
The Fragile bonds of civilization will spray
Right okay you mistook that for a
Speech about
Religious
You're mistaking
Against religious
Said if I were allergic to persecute those of another
Right civilization Wilfred
For religious
Let me read a little more
Religious
We will see. We see this mindset into many parts of the Middle East
There's so much of the collapse
In order
In order because L. Not because of policies or programs
But by resorting to persecuting political or religious
If you do literally any
Like literally I
You'll find tons of
Into the pretty much every president the crying religious persecution one address
We went
Jordan
Alex isn't talking about the crying religious persecution especially not as a universal issue that needs to be done
Play some trap for validating
His bulshit narrative
About his version of right-wing Christianity
That's what's going on
Respect religious freedom it's about celebrating having a president's Barber
The freedom of Christians then in all other religions or non-religious poke
Expensive all other life
Not religious
Can still feel like he's
Correct when he says no president has ever talked about religious oppression
All those other presidents were talking about all religions
Which isn't religious freedom to someone like Alex
Alex has a focusing on this aspect not really even highlighting the fact
Repeat that
Do you want which again
I don't
Yeah it
It's like
It's like a
Alex
Not since
Woodrow Wilson had somebody given such a speech on Racial equality
Yeah I think still is like operating off of like all right
Expected to do this show based on the talking points
Tucker last night
Speech was a bit of a curveball in the morning
Let's see where it lands let me let me feel it out on air
Before I go too far with
Let me have my intern listen to it make sure he didn't say sike
I don't know what it is
Globalist
Bendy's.
Future not going to belong to
Ralph your the globalist
So it focuses is very largely on
Because again
What everyone needs to talk about
Attack
And we've come to a point where Alex is now following in the wake of people like Tucker as opposed to being the one who's more extreme
Now he has to wait
Follow their lead and make whatever they're saying more f***** up
And that's not even a really good game for him anymore.
Plenty of other website to do that
Industry
Scaramucci will record a video and send it to you for $100
So Alex complains a bunch bunch of little different
Interesting
One piece that's sad
Better on a petty
Okay
Popular in Europe
Emissions
And truck shows up
Literally
Lost the thread they're trying to be like
Alex
Just kind of making that up I don't remember her being rejected
Probably
Nothing in Her speech would lead a normal person to the conclusion
I like that question was
Actively against climate change action
Who contributes to leaving the youth with a disastrous
Why do you scream all day everyday
Do the hoax whenever I know for sure
Real world
It's because of Greta you please
I love you baby
Narrative
Anywhere
Turn back around on him
Like he constantly screams about Democrats being literal demons trying to destroy the world now knowing should associate with them
So what if your fifteen-year-old Infowars listener whose parents are Democrats
Would that constitute Alex trying to break up your family
This is a stupid game to play
Yeah it is this
Which is why he's
Alex is also doing everything in his power to associate Greta with George Soros
Which has been a big mission of a lot of the right-wing
We're grasping at straws
Trying to attack her
Used Services is a picture of her posing with Soros
Was actually a picture of her with algor that someone to put cirrhosis head on outboard body
Alex's version is a little bit more about how Greta has a Soros link
Handler
It was obviously a writing or speeches for in coaching
Greta who was along with the operation was handling
Okay I'm not sure what bulshit website he picked us up from But ultimately The Source goes back to a qanon Twitter account called
World Wide Awake
Q army Swiss division
Images of Greta with what appear to be the same woman
Neubauer
Who allegedly works for a company called One Foundation
Which has links to
Soros Soros
Sure why not
Even if all these pictures are the same person
Neubauer does work for that Foundation
This is still super weak
As a connection and doesn't do anything
To prove that this is
The credibility of this source
Qanon Twitter account
Pizza things originally posted by Jordan
What are the big figures in the Cuba
Those guys are pretty
Who's Jordans
He's a good big qanon guy on Twitter
Supple know that.
Alright
The division of the coupon
Is crowded with qanon tweets and retweets of people like Paul Joseph
I did notice a whole lot of posts to be suspicious about Greta's hands
Somewhere about the size of her hair
I'm not sure why
Conspiracy
Others were about how she went speed limiter
It's a very good morning and it reminds me a ton of the online
IPad after Sandy
About earlobes
Approved
That was a really huge thing going around a message
Woodworth people comparing earlobe
Wild wild time
They're putting into
Maybe if it's
A sign that they're wrong
Anyway from
Is the source for sites like big league politics to report the Greta thunberg has a
Soros
Is not this thread is not
It starts by saying a quick look at Greta and her bisonic cabal ancestry
Alright tag
#qanon
Mysteriously that first tweet that starts the thread
Isn't cited by Big League politics
A random f****** weirdo qanon
Twitter account through all of this
Right-wing websites that I found that use this
Call about serious why do they not sew
Flights
I don't know
Sources include like I don't know.
Turn on and also this is her Masonic cabal
Ancestry
Family being in the Illuminati because
List of names this guy found includes both like hop
Sunburn
Jacob
I guess if we have any listeners with those last name congrats you're now the Illuminati
A couple pictures of Greta where she has one of her eyes cover
Aspire Shadow and another one appears to be a coin
Any online
Conspiracy World everyone is convinced that anyone who takes a picture with one of their eyes covered is signaling to other Illuminati members are there
Part of the group
It's one of the older and stupider elements of
Conspiracy Message Board s*** and I'm honestly shocked
Steve it's still around
Everybody takes
Seriously B
You know if there's no accounting for qanon
I'm fine
With that
Conspiracy theory
For back in the Polaroid days
Where is like
Pictures have more Intel
When there are
Now there's ten million
I couldn't I could pull up my phone and
10 million photo
Because people that have pictures with one eye covered in the Illuminati
And then like
Fashion photographers started doing that with people
It's sad.
If you
You got
Again much like the earlobe
You got to check in
Go talk somebody
Picture
I'm doing in one moment
I concur
I will tell you I multiple pictures of myself intentionally cover
This exactly
Like legitimately some of the least credible bulshit I've ever
Did anybody. Wedding problems and their operation
Looking your way Big League politics
But that's attacking the messenger
So what about this luisa-marie neubauer
What about her
She is Soros Handler
I don't know does she work for big
Chew no
Gina twenty-three-year-old climates
Activist apparently has
Has been at protested events sometimes with Greta Thun
So f****** what
So is they're both involved in the same become friends
As we're working for the One Foundation I don't know solid sourcing on that outside of it
Keanu Reeves got like 5,000 retweets
Conservice
For all this right-wing reporting
People so much
I told Louisa's LinkedIn page has been updated
What's up
You can find Spencer for working at a group called y7 climate delegation freelancing for The Huffington Post
If you scroll down far enough you'll find the chief volunteers
With an organization called one.org
As a youth
But here's the cord is not a climate change organization
It's geared at eliminating extreme poverty particularly in sub-Saharan Africa
Nothing to do with being a climate rally let alone
Completely unrelated
Tyceno
The board of directors at one.org
Former Senator Kelly ayotte
Suspicious
George Soros
I know that and I can
Yeah
Tax documents available for public review and Louisa's not a paid employee
Confirm that
I've reviewed their financial documents and I see no evidence
Soros's heavy One Foundation
Want action
It's donated
I would say that
Sure I mean
I could see that controls organization is running Louisa as a Handler to get Greta to do his bit
Why is it
So many
Become an accepted fact
Within the
Conservative right-wing Circle
What assholes tweeting something
Well because there is look more real than what I
Described here
This is a lot of the faces of it
Yeah I was able to find
One website
Call durable Reloaded
Better bit of Evan
Wait so we're talking about 1. Org and Europe Reloaded
Is all a front for the Wachowski
Wachowski
I don't know possibly but sat on that website
Two page on
Gates Foundation
Website about 1
Posted said that Soros was one of the many people who provided funding to create an organization called
Data
Poverty education
Within a few years this group combined with a number of other groups to eventually
Create one
With the primary funding coming from the gates
There's no reason to assume from this or any other information that I can find
Cirrhosis any involvement other than being an initial funder of an organization
Part of another
There's no indication that he had anything to do with one
Outside of his involvement in data
Which literally could have just been him writing a check
One time
Though this is better proof than that qanon Twitter account
This is still
Completely failing
Approve thesaurus
To do with this organization
Nor disapprove that Louisa has been photographed with Greta because she's a Handler work
Through one Foundation
All that is completely unfounded b******* nothing more than
A couple of out-of-context photos
An overriding desire to invalidate the words
16 year old girl is not being her own
It's an intense
Showing of weakness
Save-A-Lot
It's very
Still sticking
Nene's really pivot
Like I said
For the last couple years it's that like
Like if it did been jacked
Pacific wouldn't have ever
Gotten a job anywhere after his
Mike cernovich wouldn't have a career
.
Wayback
Your Name Is Mud now use zelle
Register doesn't work that way
Just doesn't
Yourself a man now people give you a job
Cuz you're slippery
Dammit
Largely is that there is no evidence
To any of this
Being floated around
About Greta
Soros
You look into where it come from
Nine times out of ten it's going to be that qanon Twitter account
And the other times it's going to just be
This is going to be Miss representation
Being
Made up of a bunch of organization
Data which Soros gave initial fund
Going to and that's fun
Thin
But even despite all that
Do you
What's wrong
They know the greater the
Know what they disagree
Sweetly they love Greta the youth are really the Greta
No I mean like she's really cool
I'm 32 and she's really cool
Write about other
Established
Pikachu
Looks like The Walking Dead
These are they
Pathetic followers
The cannon fodder the useful idiot the moron just munch
Mark
People that bought the condo
Is there a mirror
Oh no
They get mad at you twice
My family
Winchester branch
Isabella
That's a good deal
Do it
I knew it was coming
Business
They wouldn't talk to me I still got ripped off by
I thought I called the Nigerian
Why were you in business with this guy
Also Alex
Very clearly got tricked by both
Solutely
So
Add the chicken or the egg situation I don't know you probably got taken by the Nigerian scam and is trying to make it up
Parking garage speaker
I got it
Yeah
Stop complaining about Greta for a bit and because
Good time to talk to the doc
He's going out to break here and he's talking about the Donald
Subway
He's going to have them come in after the break
I believe
And
This is
I would say that this
Is
Something
A f*****-up person
Of the Donald subreddit
Don't put lipstick on them
And sometimes
I'd like to remind you this
What is the difference
Subreddit
Is a dead horse
No life
Right
People have
Aha
Okay now
That is an
If it's not positive
Right
I don't know
Okay so then
If it's if that's what it is though
Then it's not hurting
Well there is that angle
It's very clearly I would legitimately feel an obligation to
When I come back from break
Explain what I meant
And is that
Sort of metaphor that you come up with when you're trying to describe
Right right right
Corpse to have sex with its bill
What was that
Female Tom Petty Mary Jane
Music video
I feel like there are other metaphors you can
You come up with
Describe a similar thing
Are keeping around your old cell phone even though it's dead
That I don't know
But it's not as f***** up
Anyway
Alex that comes back
For break
The dog
With the dog
This is
Crazy they are just talking about
Exactly as I expected and predicted
They're just trying to talk s*** about the Donald
Mostly Alex
Because my doctor still being a little bit diplomatic
But Alex is just trying to drive traffic
Exclusively / 2
To Carpe donktum
I need it it is way to do it
Is to completely lie
About Reddit
World
Died I agree up
That's his Intro by the way
Impossible to respond to
Really fun to yell at
People that don't
Reddit reddit
Little bit of truth behind this but it's also a big lie
This year the Chinese tech company tencent
Invested 150 million dollars in Reddit
Course that means that they've taken over read it and banned any Trump positive
Of course the problem in that is
The quarantine of the Donald didn't happen until 4 months later
Read it was super
Clear that it was because
People on the Donald
Posted content
Supposedly advocating
Don't forget about that
Forget about it that's nonsense and bullshittin
It was 150 million dollars in investment from a company that is
The Destroyer
No I'm not
150 million dollars definitely sounds like a lot of money
But considered most recent
Place the site is being worth
3 billion dollars
If this involvement even involved
A 150 million dollars would be approximately a 5% ownership
Company which is nowhere near enough to unilaterally direct their action
Motivated
The revolution
Explain that in the same round of funding
Wright also received an additional 150 million dollars in Investments for burns likes
Rapper Snoop Dogg
Bring up that the majority shareholder in Reddit is Advance
Publication
I may have been for a long time
Parent company of continents
Who bought Reddit
Do in 2011
Just became a subsidiary of it
Publication
The whole time
Did Alex's loved praise Reddit
The entire time
Dikshit their parent company with the same company that owns the New Yorker Vanity Fair
Who really Publications is a gigantic media conglomerate
They'll tons of local papers around the country
From Michigan to Alabama to New Jersey
They own pitchfork
Which recently gave Lana Del Rey's new album
9.4
Get the f*** out of
There's still the majority shareholder
That wasn't making an investment
Reddit
That's okay children thing
Do italics is approaching
Tracing absurdly oversimplified lines
The causation where they don't exist
Anything to dogs taking responsibility for
For creating environment
4 tons of users felt totally comfortable promoting violence
Probably all the
Yeah yeah every time
Corporation
What they own
And how in Turkey
Curology
No no I don't want any of this
Wait till you're saying that also owns this group
But that group owns a subset of other groups
That are their own independence
This group over here
I regret to inform you there is a lot of
So Alex
Go fly a kite
Is Chinese Bots Reddit
So stupid
And February for months later
Quarantine
Happen
You can't pray the
You can't trace a causal
You still could
Disagree
Makes it even more obvious
The only
Smartcompany
Make them wait for money
Cupid
My reasoning has been Trump
So
His message largely is it like they're trying to get rid of me
By getting rid of the Donald
Basic farming
Communication
So you give this browsing
We're going to keep on Mima chill
Morals
Is almost over
You hear that we're going to keep doing it and then plug me world man
Very sad
He is losing all those
Cut off by that break after that rousing Braveheart of memes
He comes back listening to
The real classy
Is the Alicia
There's a family show every speculate about what thunder and lightning in The Highwaymen
Silver Stallion
Waging War on corruption is Alex Jones
Alright okay we got the one
Yeah for me that the Illuminati
This is an Illuminati a or may not be a lifelong love
The second time they asked we don't know what happened
I can rest easy now knowing
Norse god Odin
It's probably come off as Quirky bulshit
Where I ain't know where Alex is trying to flex
To completely surface-level knowledge about some Arcane subjects in present
He's a religious studies
That is probably what's going on
Completely honest
However
I should point out that increasingly the religion of choice among white supremacists
He's often called
According to a 2017 report from Public Radio International
There were at least
6 cases where white supremacist who identified is Odin
Domestic terror attack
It is trial Anders Breivik announced that he was a longtime Odin
Really f***** up wide identity
Fun fact
His handgun after Thor's hammer a new car after Odin's horse
Anyway
My point here isn't that Alex's talk about Odin because he
He's an openness
I'm saying that I would completely
White identity Focus
The place where you might find references to Odin
Suspicious
Another context this comes off as like a little bit of trivia
In this context
It kind of sounds like it might be a knowing wink
But
It's probably just Alex being a blowhard honestly
I don't think the community but it
Doesn't look
The Highwayman
Totally
Kris
White
Are we talking blade 1 or Blade 3
Whitebeard
19th Street
Is that the old man who fell in love with
So I want only to be like
This is
It's suspicious only because of the show that Alex does
It's completely innocuous thing to point out like
Hey there is one ideology that I don't like but there's also one eyes elsewhere
The show that is very
In line with a lot of white supremacist white identity ideas
He has a guest Vox day who really loves Anders Breivik who is a longtime open it and put the religion
Ideology on the map
The many ways
Sinbad
Yeah but
I shout
Yeah I mean
Spell right
Might just call it Christian today
So Alex gets back to talking about how wet it's owned by the Chinese
Play this clip here because
She's already said but it's important
You need to nail down like what he's really trying
Did you know that a communist Chinese control tech company
In February of this year in Reading
Guesstimate
The site was frozen and put in quarantine
He's lying about the investment in order to try and get in remnants
Betty has
Crowd to move over to Carpe donktum
Stop because Alex is associated with Carpe donktum
That makes him have more
Adjacency to wear this
Stop would be happen
Is there any like
Directions
You comes on the show more than
Make sense
Yeah but I don't think he's an employer anything
Memeworld really hard
Hosting
Immorality
Does he have a
Not that I can tell
Just a case of like
This would really help promote
Yeah it would really be a good advertising Avenue for me
Control of someone who is associated with me
That works better than
Dying
Millions over there
That's not going to happen but
It's pretty transparent
Hey night in the words of Jimmy
And that's something you just can't buy exactly
Never going to work out very well encapsulated
Start talking about who's creating content for me world this is a wild list
Gmail.com
Show me other amazing people
Are there on the side
The great Mark Dice
The Great
He's agreed to put some kind of
Exclusive content up
I have myself I'm on there as well
Oval Office with me
He's on there
Swervo
Famous figure at Trump rallies he always wears
I when he goes there
If you are listing people and like
For deep you got the guy who wears a wall suit to Trump rally
Send text New York Times
F****** Avengers Garrison mark.
Greatest superheroes
Mark Dice
The somebody guy guy who is a f****** walls
Promoting sounds
This is great to learn the guys
When are you don't use real names
State fair fair I apologize
Not too long ago we heard Alex talking about how he wasn't going
Exist in a year
Infowars
65 days and I'm pretty glad that we approached
I think that we thought there was
Possibility
More likely it was bulshit
And the way he talks about his sales
Right here this next clip
Leave me to believe that it was probably
People wait for Sino
That is put me into a pickle
40%
So he's talking about the sales that they'll have next year which implies that they'll be around next year and that there will have products
Nexteer
Also I don't know how good it is to be like
We're be around but hey I'll sales are not going to be as good
You're going to pay more for the prices
Yeah I f***** up by selling stuff
Unsustainable
As a
Reproach
Now it's not
So it's Alex yells about how
He's lucky
The Chinese haven't killed
That is good
I think we're all Lucky
Chucky 7
TheCHIVE
Gmail
Diarrhea
But it's true
It's no coincidence that
Within a month or so of
Of their investment
That suddenly
Subject has been
Extra for years suddenly just
Gets quarantined
Zoe
Has every reason to know that this timeline isn't true he absolutely he is someone who's involved
And the Donald
We reason to know when
The investment happened and compare it to when the quarantine
I came around you know that it wasn't within a month
He's just parroting back Alex is talking point
Because it makes a better argument
And that's not true they are lying
That's the only reason
Riveting
I mean he's so good that he's decided to make memes
Alex
Now descends into like yelling about the Chinese
The bunch
Another
Dragon video
Has another day gone
Let him doing it defensive
Character
Is that a new that's the new like you've got a face for radio is it
You got a voice for me
Steve level for me
So I hear that Alex
Complaining
Vagina
So this is a big headline that he repeats all the time
I know that it's not
Truth I haven't really got into it
Brookside what the f*** let's talk about
Washington Post
And Alex wants the headlines
Crush Trump
Because Alex wants the perception to be that the mainstream media has bacon the foreign leader to destroy Trump
This service is Market strategy of maligning all not Infowars
Adjacent media
And you know it works
However the actual headline is quote
Geez choice
Destroy Trump
This was not a news article
It wasn't
Which naturally is where Alex takes most of his headline
3 protons are news article
Now just go to the
Find something sounds weird Al about it
Opinions
Is entirely about
Clickbait
Then the other side going
And then you writing another opinion
Has Rolling Meadows on its own a Brazen Act of manipulation
Legitimately doesn't understand the difference
Journalism and commentary
And I would say that
Probably
It could be
The editorial
Question needs to learn how to use soft power if he's going to maximize maximize his success
As a world leader
Note
A leader
Not v l
That's important
It runs through how dealing with India internal dissent in Hong Kong are all examples that make his leadership style not one
That makes China really qualified to be government the world looks on with budget
Probably FairPoint
The stuff about Trump is towards the end of the editorial to headline
To reflect the actual article itself
The argument here is that she is holding all the cards as it relates
The only move Trump realistically has
In terms of their relation is threatening a trade War
And she doesn't really care about that nearly as much as Trump
Show me article
60% of whom spent less than $10 a day are far more accustomed to economic pain than Trump
And they have no meaningful right to vote
So she can probably afford to absorb some economic pain necessary to push the trade War past election
It's all presented as the choice between soft and hard power
The harp our route would be to crush
Enforces hand with a trade war that would likely
L recession and diminish Trump's chances of being re-elected
The soft power route is to make some token
Concessions the Trump could parade around and act like he's a master negotiator forgetting
As the article says quote
Graciously spring
Trump from the trap
Keith stepka
This is ultimately weaken our ability to negotiate
Further but gives trumpet artificial
Can't save Trump and weaken America
The editorial is not a call for G2
Cross-draw but you'd only think that if you hadn't read the article
Or you have and you know your audience
Isn't going to
Either way I was just completely lying about this s***
In order to Moline that the Washington
Supposed to
His
Mainstream media rivals
You know I really loved
Huge fan of all the really really
Yeah it's trouble like the problem solves itself if people just read
Like if they read the articles
The problem of bad headlines
Kind of solves itself whenever
Materialize
It's a problem
The screaming about how like
The world is madness
And no one cares
The Chinese bar
I mean we got other s*** going on man
You know
Do your magic no one cares
But don't care because the thing didn't happen
Alex turns heat along the American people
Men
We have a country
A little
Fidgets
Growlers and ass kissers public about week
Devil worship
I thought you loved America what are you doing I mean
Well
This is Family Show
Bright
Did normal Americans are devil worshippers
God unmasked
Like a guy who likes America by
Seems like that for the entire time
Talking about him
America that is
No I really really hate that kind
Douching
Despises
But he really loves the one that's in his head
Betty would like to impose upon everybody else without their
It is very quite
So
He loves America
Asterisk
The one in his brain that nobody else is aware
Yeah I noticed that a lot of the show's been about climate change and yelling about Greta thunberg
Now
With a little
In the in the way
Right
Which was a good diversion pressing issue of climate
Sure do that
Alex is like greater doesn't know what the f*** she's talking about
But I know a guy who does
Oh no
Chabad Congress of course
Abuse of the children
Cuz I I
Still have some hair left and
Prefer not to watch me rip it out and
But I did like
Lord monckton knows more than Mark Moreno like that's going
Why not because he's over my parade
Any reference would piss you off
So the reason that Alex has
Is because
I guess Lord monckton has branded himself a Greta thunberg expert
Alex multiple times and he just seems like
Like a dick butt
Before their interview gets going breaking news
Fort Mountain
Sunbirds you're quite the expert
Powerglide
Parent support the child services in Sweden
This morning
So that's
Turn on
Person
Elsa pictures of her concern about
Abusive parents
District administrator
Syndrome
Jennifer Stockholm Europe
So Infowars at this breaking news article about Greta reported
Imma give you a couple clues who the source is on this and you cannot guess
Until I read all three click first clue
He's taking responsibility for 9/11
To the invented
You'd better the fake religion around the Matrix movies
3 he's recognized Jesus Christ by both the Jews and the Vatican
His real name is mirroring into eulogizing this
Getting ready to interview
67 year old fraud pretend to be a member of the House of Lords
Hey we're going to do Black Friday sale to get the other night
Complain about Greta thunberg any of breaking news from Leo functions
Warpath
We're past the Looking Glass
Dialysis now look
Cork crafts
Against Greta
Super afraid I'm terrified of it
In your old girl that's legitimately
24th
Stop saying that
You know the globalist
Deflected a little bit in other episodes about Ukraine
GameStop
I just b*******
But not the newer develop
I know I just was looking at this
Substantial show
He got the memo that he needs
To talk about Greta thunberg climate coverage from the 23rd
Buy bring her into the conversation
Carpe donktum best Chinese buying Reddit
It's a very weird show is like that is unsatisfying
For anyone
Did you expect
Alex's take on these big news item
Did not get it on 44th
Sagami
Doc three Horsemen of the fuk Paca
And of course
The guy who wears a wall suit
Who is really good
25th and Alex situation with
Ukraine
Opposite reaction
Liberty
Purple
Propofol
Conversation
We'll get into the specifics of this a little bit later but
Just so you know Alex is going hopes on this one
F*** off
Alex
Very person
In 2015 when he
You say
Yeah he's mobs up Alex
You know full well what a person talks like when they are extorting
How's that memo of the transcripts right Alex should have trusted his 450
Timeline
So what
And much greater depth is this episode
This next clip is what I texted you about
I texted you last night
And I told you I found
Perhaps the most f*****-up clip that I've ever heard of the show
Somali pirates is definitely in the Run
The one where you talked about being on Artie and then being intelligent people
That was weird
This one is definitely up there
Big is this
Is
Crazy
This is only
Davis you got job
Trump
That
Is mind-blowing
That didn't look there are red flags and then there are red flags
What is the post scholar on US History think Smith
Presidents who have been impeached
Arrowhead proceedings open up on them are Clinton Trump and Jefferson Davis
Like 41
List is actually Andrew Johnson and Bill Clinton for those who have been impeached
Even that listed leaving office open but was never impeached
Most importantly
Was not a president of United States
Yes but no one has ever been impeached
Well
Destroying a country of
You know what I mean like
And he got impeached very well might be the biggest Freudian slip I've ever f***** hard
First of all the Alex
Compartmentalize is Jefferson Davis in the same part of his brain
U.s.
Which is not not good that's not good.
Also it means he's really f****** stupid cuz he forgot about Nixon
I understand
They started
Nixon had the articles of impeachment brought to the house
A list of
The point
These are big
Things
Then he should remember
Pics of
Kristin Davis
Considering
Time
When
Andrew Johnson
Davisware
Contemporary
So
A kind of
America during the time of Jefferson Davis was an ill
Legitimate America in dust
Counted our f****** hiss
Jefferson Davis
Just present
Galaxy
Is that
You want the best
I want to play this I want to play this clip
Just to show you that he doesn't correct
Himself because you would think
If he said that
You would then be like
I f***** up yeah completely clogged up
He does not
Famous you got job
The next round
Approval rating
When he did this
So he doesn't
Seem to even recognize that he said the Jefferson Davis was
Who's the president of the United States
Really f****** troubling
It was really 48 f***** me up because originally I thought it
Going to be hilarious
But never in my wildest dreams would I have
Come up with Jeffers
And now address
Yeah
According to 538 Trump's numbers disappeared make a little stick upwards
Recent days but you still looking at net
Negative
Approval rating which is not ideal
Text out that is
Not just now
Something that I do
Don't care about
Thing that is actively harmful if
If you care about
His
F****** of approval rating
In the
A criminal trial
I don't care whether or not
The f******
Jury like
The defendant the problem is the crime
Yeah you're not judging you approve of the job
Right
Seems that way
But Alex doesn't
And here's why
The Deep state is making it right now
Free Society
This is a major question and you saw that incredible speech
President
Why the systems coming after him because
And parlayed our military
So it's retaliation
This is all just for Trump
We just make sense
The
Just started before
I guess he's being it
That wasn't
To release this map
Clearly
Certainly handle implies it
Because
I don't know
I don't know about the memo
Alright I want a little bit before we get to that Alex
So recently there was
News about
People warning
There might be a shooting
Premiere of The Joker movie
Aurora Theater would not show
But if I recall correctly
I will not be surprised
See that but that wouldn't
Surprise me too much
Alex believes the global is signaling that they're going to do a false flag
This that movie
About this a little bit something really interesting
It's worth pointing out
President
Getting Love Of The Nation
Emergency alert
Cell
I didn't know that they were a cross-pollinating
Battle
Nonexistent
Loosely affiliated
Group of people that are
Demonized by the right
And then the other one is a bunch of
You're going to get shot by
Sarah never ever shooting
That's because if there are
Clarence Alpha profit
The Army did release a warning to service people that they picked up chatter from the dark web about shooting
Screening of the Joker
Relating to insult
Who spoke to Gizmodo said that these sorts of alerts are pretty common
Email that got sent out
Specific threat that anyone could take action
They just advised avigilon
There's nothing in that armies email or the FBI statement on the dark web chatter that would leave
Fashion
This is specifically about incel groups but without
Make a compound epithet
In order to
This is mine
He does this regularly in order to demonize groups that he's opposed to most notably with his attempt to make the lgbtq
T2p thing
I work
You know trying to reflect his completely erroneous claim
The lgbtq community adopted pedophilia into their rank
This is the level of s*** that Alex is working with these
Just trying to create
Epithet
To demonize groups
Just linguistic
Yeah it's really pathetic it's a sign
Not
Really having much gas left
I'm just confused
I think that would be a good idea
Considering incel
The Intel community
Woodcare
Like anybody who
The s*** is going to give a s*** about what the right-wing says about
Are far more likely to support Alex there on his the Donald
You know there's some
Play there's so many in that Community is like
Maybe well
Compared to Earth
But I'm asking
You know they they don't
Ascribed right
Ideas about virility and the energy produced
Being so Central to what do you want
These people to be
Yeah now that you say that
I can see that
But
It's still just dumb
This is all stupid
I don't know probably about a half hour or so realizes that
He said the Jefferson Davis was
Was president
Red State
Any comes back today
Fourth impeachment
420 is Trump
So we're going to be looking at
All of that Johnsonville Clinton and others
I suggest
McDonald's purpose
He said it for some reason for some reason
That he would even say not on purpose
That works
I didn't mean to tell you what's going on in my brain and that's all Confederate ships
It wasn't completely muscle memory reaction that I have
Confederacy of the United States president
Alex
That is great
Style
I promise to get to Alex's take on the memo
It's not good
Nothing
The shareholders
Sanford
Partial ownership
Put it on the board
This whistleblower puts in the complaint
Intelligence says that's not a legitimate complaint nothing wrong with
Please don't throw me in the Briar Patch
Level four
People up what a shock that reference becomes up with to describe the situation
Splash Mountain or something like that the president United States
Really
It's not right
Text David
So Alex is conspiracy theory here is the trumpet playing games trying to get this whistleblower to testify
Open the door to talk about the family's involvement in Ukraine
Hey Joe Biden's involvement in the firing of grains former
Prosecutor Victor show
All that information is already very public
James rice and wrote a story about Joe's done hunt in 2015
New York Times
Anime 2019 you right-wing sites were already aggressively circulating the accusation
He'd gotten the prosecutor fired in order to bail out
Ukraine
The idea that company The Whistleblower to
In order to get this information into the open
Absurd
Just makes no sense
Replace back up his claim Lee all about
Is a Cooper Biden saying that he threatened to withhold a billion dollars in Aid if they
Fire shokin
And that is a real quick
However what's missing is
Contacts
Here are the parts of the story that are
Did work
To get Viktor shokin fired
Missing Ukraine
The rest of this narrative that is completely fabric
Joe Biden
Most of them not good but in this case
Experts agree that he was in the right to threaten to withhold
Unless shokin was fired
It was deeply corrupt
Installing avert prosecution on
What are the big prosecution's was that
Nicolas
Lorraine crane
Biggest independent Gas Company burisma
This was a bit of a mess
The shefsky was also yanukovych's
Environment and natural resources
Would you get imagine could introduce a prime opportunity
Felix
The energy
Conglomerate there
Well as the guy in charge of
And natural
What kind of ridiculous
Backwards ass country
They're f****** regulator
What
Hahaha
Not investigate or prosecute cases
Cuz like that
Which is what
In exchange for the delivery
So now the story The right-wing media conspired in order to protect his son Hunter who
Was involved in business in Ukraine
I should probably tell you that the sketchy business in Ukraine that Joe son was involved with none other than burisma
The very company that was insisting
Be fired for not investor
The Narrative completely falls apart when you realize the actual pieces
That were in play
The factors that were involved
Nobody people of theorize that buries them is hiring of Joe Hunter Biden
Might have been an attempt to Shield the company
Impossible empty corrupt
Crackdown
But there's no evidence
Played out in the real world
So to sum things up I'll quote from an article in the interest
Ricin
Webbie interview
The founder of Ukraine's auntie
Corruption action
What I'm pissed off about is that show can who is
Totally corrupt
To undermine the reform of prosecution
Performers
And who didn't want to investigate the shepsky
Now appears in
New York Times
Article
As the hero who wanted to investigate is olszewski a yzma and who suffered because Joe bike demanded
To dismiss him
Because of his willingness
Charisma which is absolute nonsense
Absolutely did not
Set the up Democrats or Biden
And find any faith left in the process
I would think he's in very serious trouble
And this week s*** is the only spend that
They have life
You got you got a lot of really bad looking variables but I've been
We've done this too many times
The course of the last two years for me to be like
Anytime
I'm done with people who are
This would take down any normal president
Like this would take down a present
Cannot take down the f******
Criminal terrorist Enterprise that the
Do Europeans turn into
The president has nothing to do with how
How corrupt in all
Well
But he's just a
He's just a manaphy
Gestation of
Yeah
The.
Has Fallen
Amazing
For the first time
I think
This one in
I think they're
You very
The GOP
Power structure
Who read that
It heard that Balboa
The whole thing is really
Oh no
We tricked ourselves
F*** now we believe this
No we were using that to
To trick the dump
Yeah
Yeah it's it's
It's a bridge
Too far I think
I don't know I don't have
I don't have a whole lot of faith
Slitherio
But I hope that it's enough to
Really Joplin
Out of
Believing
The b******* line I really hope it is
Because it's
Who year
Some of the factors that are
From the reporting that come out about
The Whistleblower report just got released
Matches up with
Reporting it come out
That's a prior to the phone call that Trump had
With Ukrainian president
Specifically
Put a hold on a
Prior to this phone call
Not after not during no preliminary
Which states
The phone call and messaging
You want
Is Saint and the b*******
So like
All of these things a reasonable person would look at that
Conclusion
There's enough here that really needs to be sorted out
This is untoward
And if allowed to stand
Is just
Suspicious
Oh no
There was a literal
Violation of
The emolument clause
It's not a transcript
The Trump slipped
Trump Hotel
No that was also reading bad read that memo is very much
It is
Is Stevi B's right the Ukrainian president lines hear the dialogue on that
Is Soco
Clearly
Literally going like
How do we get him to pay attention
We flatter the s*** out of
Right right right
Craigslist
Is a
Comedian
You can pull that show
Yeah it's
It's troubling
It's all just
Real trouble
My feeling
It's the sign that every other country
What we all should
We don't already
F****** pathetic weak-willed
Tiny little baby hookah
He stroked his ego
Will do whatever you want
And it becomes
Machine
Exactly it's it's
But look at all the available evidence
Kind of feeling
So we have a lot of feelings about this
Medications that are coming out aren't good and make it look like there's probably
Real bad thing
Confident that everything's cool
What Trump said last year also Foods left
I would anyway go over the phone
No way shooter
Easily torn and honest man
Isaac all stories of con
Is there a run on on at Regal
Conning honest man
The only don't want to talk to you at all
This is all not true because Trump said I don't commit crimes on the phone
It's a routine
So Alex needs to Center this around by
A projecting onto Trump crimes that bike committed so they could deflect from the
The fact that he committed those crimes
I tried to take out Trump
It sort of capitulate
Best Buy
Now it's important to point out that in the clip it out to talk
I'm about you never says because you're investigating my son editorial
Theory
Bulshit being applied to the actual
If you don't
Terrible story
Is that true
I hate
Investigation
Something happened
Such a lovely
Right
Is there such b*******
What's plays the actual clip of Biden
I don't care
I'm not into him at all I don't care
Find anything
Necessarily wrong with what it says
And
I remember going over convention
Convincing us that we should be providing for
It's Not Over
1213 time to keys and ducks
And I was going to supposed to announce that there's another
Prosecutor
The prosecutors not fired
Each other's ass
So
It matches up with Alex's narrative he didn't sell
I was working at a sketchy company Ukraine
I didn't do that he's not saying that he did it to stall the prosecution that's built that b*******
Sweet spin
Nonsense
Specifically
He's saying that
They were the ones
Who forced him
Like the deal was already done
He was he was never he didn't plan on doing any
That was already negotiated
They just changed the deal at the last
Then he went
No
That was that was it
What kind of Investigation that's done
Which I think is always
Appropriate if they're done
To reflect
Like
Hail Mary desperate attempt
Create cover
The only reason you do that is if
You know you need to cover
And that's probably what
What's going on
This is
Best moments
Poor
On the fox
News media
This is the this is the when push comes to shove
You're holding up a memo
Trump saying
I committed
Look
Putting it in people's face
And thanks
He didn't commit
For people who love to yell about 1984
It's interesting
Ecclesia
We live in a cliche and this is that last moment before it's like there's no coming back guys now you believe whatever the
Is he can put an apple in your
Come out and say it
If an orange and your
I agree
So Alex Barnes on
Barnes-joseph
Alex
Because what you haven't talked about how he's doing
But Alex
Like I said
Has a priorities
I mean
I would say that that's probably an accurate reflection of what you should be covering your own Petty both or
Duration of our country
You like that
Really close
It is not it is not a disc
No like that was neck-and-neck finish right there
Barnes all day about
Yeah
Yeah it's it's pretty crazy
I need to say this really quick just off the top
Video people listen to our show
Which they do not
I need to say this
Please do not cover these lawsuit
If someone was a pretty good handle on Alex's current situation in life it's hard not to see these as an attempt
Ag Supply
And further as an attempt to obfuscate his main Sandy Hook lost
It's my feeling people would be wise
To leave these cases alone
Let them run their course and not give out
Exactly what do you want
Which is tons
Coverage of these cases
Even if the coverage is mocking
He needs an inflow of people to his sight in order to be potential customers
No matter how he get that info he doesn't give a s***
And this stuff
Reek
Alex The Young Turks Brianna Wu and Andrew Kimmel on Wednesday
And I've read the complaint
Hi my first thought is
Was written by Robert Barnes
Generally when I read legal filings for the show the very dry really formal and by-the-book
This one is
He let the crowd vote on how it was going to say my toes
It does include Barnes big catchphrase couple times
Saul Good
What essential problem with this argument relies on a
From the filing
Parents
School shootings has employer
After the suit was brought hackers and cybercriminals ideologically aligned with a
Descendants
The computers of Joneses
Employer during the time. Does he unwittingly quote-unquote discovered
Lawyers involved in the case
By using terms in the emails that have been ordered produced by court order discovery
It's very clear the barn
Coordination between the people who's doing out
I mean you put the word discovered in quotes
As if to say there wasn't a real discovery
NFL lawyers and do what they do because the hackers were their ideological allies
All right here's how this here's how we go
Let's Roll
Okay alright
So
Here's what
Shadowy Bando hacker
They got together they
Elkhorn computers
At the behest of
And I'm not going to say who but there happened
Another group
People suing Alex and
I'm just saying there evolved
Anybody out there
It was all of there it was all that
We got to take down The Young Turks completely unfounded and unproven disconnect
The violin
Ocean. Infowars Corporate email accounts were attacked by online cybercriminals
With spyware and malware
Including Sandy Hook
Hidden embedded in the emails that hackers sent to various Infowars email address
The emails were never opened by anyone at Infowars
The court in the Sandy Hook
Emails included
Sandy Hook
It appears the hackers who tried to
Emails on Infowars servers were aware of this discovery process
It deliberately using terms in emails to create a false counter
This seems incredibly speculative isn't information to be included in your legal filing
The basis for framing Alex is a pitiable victim is being laid out
Ernest setup between
Does canceling the hackers weather formal or not
There is there's this idea that's being presented
2 gear and it's just
Pure speculation that's meant to opt
As always I'm no lawyer
But this seems deeply irresponsible as a way to
You frame your legal
Go complain
What is he asked
What what is with the lawsuit
They want to trial against
These three Defenders
The Young Turks
Brianna Wu
Fans
For what
For saying that Alex sent child born
Defamation
Gotcha gotcha
Hear what these folks over is headline statements that
On a purely technical
However barnes's big move on page three of the filing
Is to argue that Alex didn't
His employer Infowars turned over emails
The plaintiff lawyers
And Alex Jones is the owner of Infowars
So I feel like that argument might be a little thick
Play from
His name was in all caps
So it's actually the states
Alex Jones
From what I understand might have
Sovereign ideas about taxes.
Okay so we can look for
And his meteoric rise
Shortly after
10 years in jail for
Who knows
The only exhibit
Is a screenshot of a tweet from The Young Turks
Lincoln to a video titled Alex Jones
Ignore Andrew
But I think there might be another thing this document that is a gigantic red flag
Listed in the case
Are The Young Turks
Brianna Wu and Andrew Campbell
However
In the nature of the action section of the filing
Details about The Young Turks
But there's nothing about
A camel
There's a complaint about Larkspur
Who's not listed as a defendant
What
Forgot
I'm not sure it's very confusing
And probably not a good
Lazy motherfukers
I think there might be some implication that Andrew Kimmel wrote for Mother Jones
Stop about somebody else
In the nature of the action part 180 is the defend I don't
Seems
This is
Same like
The Republican
Accidentally sent to ya
The criminal mastermind that is just
Absolutely
Oh yeah
It's even more it's
Even more of an insult
Here's some random thoughts I have about this case that I
T-top for Alex
In claiming that this is defamation Barnes tries to argue that this is negatively affected Alex's
I think it's going to be insanely hard to prove
Reputation is s***
And 42 because Alex
I remember him saying he was doing better after the corn attack
Like the audience
There are things from Alta show that could be used very easily as like
His reputation
Solo among the rest of the world
It could only be raised
Biax
People among the people who follow
Interana second in terms of the specific statement quote Alex Jones
Like if you accept it enforces all by Alex at the lawyers work
For Sandy Hook parents
Think that's technically.
The Young Turks
It doesn't necessarily imply that Alex knew what was
It doesn't apply
Really hard time arguing
But this is a defamatory
Really steals defamatory to Alex
When we covered the story was my position that sing I'll accept this torn with a bit of a sensational
I thought
True
It's still probably didn't capture the reality of the story
I took the position that it wasn't a good headline story
And I was probably kind of
The clickbait behavior
But I don't think you can sue someone
And if you can
Alex Verdugo scrub literally all the contact off Infowars
Think it's something he does quite often
Is Poston stational unprovable Headlines by people that are meant to damage the reputation
Consider his big
What exam
I figured if you wins the suit
But you almost certainly will
I even make it
The courtroom
Baby talk
Literally anyone he's written
Really chilling
He went to his own abilities
Know the person dupid idea the person who would be most damaged by him winning this lawsuit
Somehow
Ulta
It's my feelings
Attempted of publicity
Hopefully
Infowars
Because the suits are
Corridor Hill withdrawal them
I don't think this is going any
Further it really feels like this
The temperature portray Alex's figure
Something related to Sandy Hook
In order to sway public opinion before his actual trial begin
On that
I recommend actual media Outlet leave this thing alone and let it play out its course
As much as it might
Feel really fun
Two dog pile and jump in and make fun of
I do think
But that's his goal
Let's all
Just let him go to the
We don't need a dragon
It would seem
So I get to talk about bar
He does think it is
Their secondary to the
Two barns about that fighting video that Alex has from the
Actually say it is
Really yeah
Cfrvideos
The prosecutor
GoPro
Noah
It's very easy to overcome
But notice the language
He described as a prosecutor who was quote involved potentially
In investigating Biden son
Even Barnes knows that there was no investigation
Dividing something to curtail
But the Optics are so important
Here you got to present the idea that there was it could have been babe
And sincerely when this is all said and done I hope Barnes ends up disbarred
His behavior on Infowars over the past couple months
It's been a complete
Disgrace to his profession
He is not operating ethically in any sense
It does kind of seem like you
Evil DLC
So yeah
I would like to know the timeline
Just f***
Flipped
Probably after defending
Yeah maybe I don't know go on the show immediately
After
Starting to work on
Friday quotes
Is pretty close as anyone you know
Just on the
I think he was part of that
To that Griff
It wasn't it wasn't
Too far off
From when he started defend
He's always seemed to
You know he wants the spotlight
To live out this
Reality TV
He got some attention and then all the sudden
Sunny got a dick
Get to the attention
And now he's
Loves 80s
Great broadcaster
Infowars
Making
Five grand for an appearance at a bar on a
Friday night what's going to happen which is why
The setup this evil at TLC
You got a
That's true.
Which makes
Next clip even more
My family
Course
So you can talk about anything
Let's look at all of your old cats Alex
Category
So sad
You never knows until
Travel
That is trouble if you still believe
You've noticed
Left pechenik
Your show
Which suggests that you also do
Music Carpe donktum on bragging about talking to a guy dresses up as a wall
A real heroic endeavor
Listen to this phone
Between Alex and barn
I really think it's
As time goes on it becomes so much
Weworewhat their relationship
We don't
As for Everybody's Free Speech
Jetcost
At the level we're at right now
Dot-com
A member
I have a strong suspicion
Pure advertising
I have a strong suspicion that Barn for free
Regal pro bono work
Alex is promoting the free America
Or whatever
QuikTrip
I think it's pretty clear for statement has been made in the pattern that we're seeing
You know baby Barnes had ideas to get this off the ground and knew that Alex has a big media Empire with tons of listeners
Is a great place
To try and
Cultivate
Support for it
Enough money
Defending Wesley Snipes
But I don't need money now or whatever I can take a hit work for Alex
Free Takis
High-profile Escape
Play it don't believe that for a second
But you work at a reduced rate in order to make yourself the only option Alex has
Use them to f****** evil splc off the ground
Halex great
Don't know who you are
Prince know and he's onboard
I'm evil splc helps Alex to
That all
It kind of works in both of their favors but it's pretty clear with the arrangement
Used to be yeah but one of them
Is it going to lose
They're both
By losing Barnes
Alex Just Lose It
That's debatable
Yeah I don't know
Either
Sure
So there's big news in Alex's
Also talked about for a second
Connecticut Supreme Court was hearing the arguments
About
His
He appealed the
The punishment that he got for going on are drunk and trying to intimidate
Supreme Court agreed to hear that
Small section ride
And here's Alex presents
You know the judge was a
Barn should not allow Alex to say things like that representation
Supreme court hasn't taken over his Sandy Hook
It's a small
It was described in Connecticut paper that I was reading as a sideshow
Of the actual case is a small matter about the sanction
That was imposed because of his
Million-dollar bounty
We started recording this I don't know how that worked out
Was being hurt
I've got no thanks
Relieved I don't know but whatever it is it has no real bearing on his actual case
No and
Either way
He does get this
The next day he'll say so
Worthy of
Undoubtedly
Imply that Alex can do stuff like that on air if you want and the punishments won't come
None and I guess
I don't know
Talking about how crazy
Into the quarter Democrats
If you really listen to
Listen carefully
It sounds like a perfect description
In about
Of the Democrats because they're so crazy
Set the deepest
Are you f****** with me all the time in various different permutation
I'm just describing
The other side doing exactly what they're doing
Even down to staying at the other side is saying they're doing with the other side to do it
Think it's just
Intended to confuse
People
Yeah but that perfectly describes how my view of Alex
Is from looking at his show
Backed into a corner scared of
The world's being what's actually going on
It is operation
Sad
The cover for the bike
Stop or there cover for the Trump staff
But you see the exact same behavior
Like it's all just a
Dumb Shell gas
You know
Could
Absolutely
Insult
Alex
Friend
If you just started it with
I know this globalist
Went on a laundry list of
You started Radio Show in completely lost
I agree
So
I come to the end of all this
Is
A sense of like there's a lot of really big ship going on
In the real world
Interesting angle
And you really don't
You're really died altimate leaves very disappointing list
These episodes
Makes me think
Quite frankly he's not drinking because his response to this
Kind of high-level s***
Even six months ago would have been
If you look at the show and it's just
Yelling about Biden Greta thunberg Hitler
Uninspired in Alderwood
Absolutely have been in a
Emergency
Report
I couldn't find one I don't know if he's allowed to do those
Because of this
Unresolved
I don't I don't know I don't know what it is I feel
Disappointed
In some ways
Interesting
I think it's interesting to learn about the
You know the angle
Being attacked on sunburn
Soros
Qanon Twitter account
That's interesting
It's interesting too
See the reality of the bike
Stuff in Ukraine
Alex can do better
Or we could do better
It's something
Realistic be more into
Disappoint
Expect better propaganda
You are not that any
I really I really
In his life
That clip of him
Just
Telling everybody
Right
He is going
Dude I look
Man in the Heights
Hightower in the Heights
Moment of life
There were two pads
I could have gone here and then there's this reality and I went
This way and I got
Sure that's what the
Castle is about
Fair enough
Just like you misuse and Philip K Dick's
Fight
Even if this is kind of uninspired and weak
Propaganda that could just easily be done by anybody else
It's still worth it
To go over there
For the revelation
Alex
The Jefferson Davis was the u.s. president
Tank that will live on as
Probably the most on Branch Road
Yeah I can't think
On Monday with a new episode
It's been a long time since we did a Wacky Wednesday up
Might do on a Monday
Palate cleanser
Wilton
That is a good point things are moving fast
I honestly think we have finished recording it
But we'll see.
Knowledge B
Dot-com
Correct we're also on
Twitter we are on Twitter
Knowledge
Underscore fight
Go to bed George
Correct
We're also on Facebook
Do you know that way
Yep download
The podcast
Could leave a review Butler
The best way to hear this
Is go down
To your local
I don't know which one is yours
Specifically is off Highway
Okay
A real salty cup of coffee
Terrible Diner terrible you that you had that
I'm not sure I have
And
When the woman brings out your
Your check cuz it's
She's going to bring out that Notepad
You going to have it in her little late
Underneath it
Poems like a magician
Thumb drive
I don't have our
Situation
Emilio Emilio
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color