I have great respect for knowledge fight
MoneyGram
Stripe.com
Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex
What up what up
What
Panicking over
Vape fever
Is going
Vulture
I'm old enough now
I'm old enough and has a career as someone who smokes
Long enough
There's kind of a little bit of a panic of some kind that we're marketing things to children
And then you restrict everybody's access
Stephan stop
I will call at 9
Twenty years or so
Cigarette
And Campbell came out with a line
Cigarettes that would come in at 10
And they were like there was a vanilla flavor it wasn't cool
Really awesome cool wallpapers
About that manded up having
Lingered for a long time
You can't sell menthol cigarettes 100 feet from a school in Chicago
Rules about like
These appeal to Children therefore gone
Now we're just going through with the Next Generation
Technology
I understand like I don't know
Vape cartridge
I'm not proud of that but I do
I bought the sour gummy worm flavor from UPS to vape shop
I have to try them I love the novelty I like I like the weirdness of it
I don't
Government overreach
But I do also understand that there are problems that are possibly
About Vapes
That's a weed
Just didn't have enough time to really understand
Some of the
Dangerous
About the
And if you do things are motivated along those lines
I was wondering
I'm not thrilled at the I also just miss those camels
Logo soccer picks
Everybody is pointed that out but never not hilarious
Walmart
I'll take two packs
Feelings about slavery
Tobacco products
And then Oliveto
Alright
And highly anticipated and anxiety-provoking
Episode of The Alex Jones Show
We'll be going over
Today where is the Boston Marathon
Athens
Real-time
I sincerely think
That this is one of the Grim look
Better man
Off to a good start well
Very fine
That's one of the things I think is really the most difficult and most rewarding of
This podcast
And that is the whenever there's something like this
Tragedy
Newsbreak
You really get to
See how Alex Benson
Wheels in real time
How the
The
The ball moves forward
I think is really revealing
I meant also I lost
Overstock
For someone that I breathe
Leo zagami does not show up
That would be wild
Alex doesn't know him very strange
Disgusted
And up and made this anxiety-provoking episode possible
So first of all thank you
Your nail polish
Next Kaitlyn
Galen
Let's just take it so much
Journal policy
I worked at movie theater with me
Deanna made him Furious
Was dusting
I hope that this person is
Is not living in this
Call Drogo
Text Claire thank you so much
Next Lenoir I believe
Lenoir
Bank of America
And emerald
Thank you see you both you are
Fun pimps
Is freakishly large
Admiral Cavendish
Absolutely
Sports
I'm not sure what it would be but whatever the case
Would you like to
We would appreciate it
Only have a tiny little speech
Restarting on April 15th
And on April 15th
249 Eastern Time
A bomb detonated near the finish line of the Boston Marathon
14 seconds later a second bomb Place 210 yd
Three people were killed
264 were wounded 14
I required a
The high number of injuries was the result of the homemade bomb impact
With nails and ball bearings
About to be shrapnel to hit as many people as Pop
The bomb cells were very rudimentary
Authorities to believe that this could easily be the work of amateur
Their basic construction of the bombs is just a pressure cooker pressure cooker filled with gunpowder
A little wiring
The Trap
Gunpowder came from fireworks that were purchased
Emptied into the pressure
Just chilling
To think about
A person with really terrible intention
Do so much damage
Easy to get material
If they're so motivated
And drawn that direction
When this all happened I was working a terrible temp
A job at an insurance
Company that I do business
For it was just
Very weird
Circumstance
They had very little work for me to do so a lot of my time was spent
Conspiracy
Towards pass the time
I remember April 15th 2013
Very clearly
And I remember how everyone
Conspiracy world was following Alex Jones
So many of the narratives that I heard listening back to these episodes
We're taking it concrete
Exact
On the sites that I would kill him
I went posters on those sites
But being pushed to provide a source
It was very regularly Infowars
I struggled with how to present this episode since everyone listening knows how this plays out at least
Or at least they know the basic
Our episode today is going to cover it
Exclusively April 15th
And I kind of feel like if I lay out everything that happens
Whitby
The aftermath
And how
Little too deep
Construction talk about when the later events come around cover
Future episodes
So I apologize for all that stuff
Unfolds
For now by the time Alex goes off are on the episode on April
No one knows any
Sing about who did the bombing
No one knows what their motivations could have been or if they were even working with a terror
Here's all the information that it come out by the sea
Within minutes it was clear this was not an act
Since there were two explosions a ways apart from each other
And video footage showed explosion
Inconsistent with a gas
Explosion
Something along those lines
It was clear very quickly
Initially a whole lot of media coverage was about how about people who saved each other's lives
In the absence of any concrete things to report
Most important story to tell
Reassuring
People were embodying that Mister Rogers
Spirit of looking for the helpers
Obama's press conference beard highlighting bright parts of humanity
Come out in the tragedy
The people selflessly helping each other the runners continuing to run to the hospital
How to donate blood
Inspiring a unifying image
Just like we got to tell people something
This is something that I was really doesn't talk about at all
Over the course of
Insincerely the human aspect of this both
That's inspirational
That's tragic
Cialis being all that interested in any of
Call distance
Act of Terror but wasn't necessarily calling it strongly a terrorist
I'm Andy kind of caused a little bit of weird
Conversations around
Which I will touch on a little bit
The FBI was quoted by the BBC is calling it a potential terrorist investigation
Boston Police Commissioner Edward Davis held a press conference
No specific
Intelligence that something like
This would happen
I ended
The country but Boston particular was in a very f*****-up place
Something that helps
Positive connotation
Marathon
Have been turned into
Terrifying
Marathons with the sort of thing that you associate with being the culmination of hard work
Dedication
With family in French
You want to make it there
Steps to get across
Finish Line
The bombers are taking this Association
Replace them with blood trails
Missing limbs
She's very hard to deal with
As a country
Hey even if you're watching it on
Even if you're away from it
Particularly for
For the people immediately
What happened but everybody
His is real
To an extent
And on top of that the culprits were still on the loose
And there wasn't a lot of clues about who dumb
Boston was on high alert with heightened enforcement levels on the
No one knew if this person or persons
We're going to strike
Again no one knew what to
No one knew anything
Except
And that it wasn't
This is an incredibly
Situation
That's one of elevated anxiety
Any information
Patient to help them make
Expensive
It's the kind of situation where someone like Alex Jones is at his most
Because new no one knew what the story was it what it happened
The story all his own
And no one can really prove that he was wrong
It was a very definition of that metaphor I always use about Alex needing to
He needs to act while the concrete is
Is wet
Until that concrete dries you can easily put his initials in there forever
But if you wait too long
You going to need a jack
Impression
I try to approach this show our podcast
Proposition
Elevate myself above stuff
Not let myself get too mad
But I can't tell your Pretend We're going to go over here today
Infuriating
One my family lived in Boston and Cambridge from just after I was born until I was six
Searzall
And while I don't remember much of that time
Nor can I really
Claim any credit
Vegas OCH
It's still a part of my life
I've always held a real fondness for Boston and I was a huge fan of Mighty Mighty Bosstones growing up
Little to do with my
I'm not trying to personalize this to
What makes me angry is if you pay attention to Alex
You can very clearly see that what he's doing
Is intense
We often discuss the
The stupid versus evil quad
Squarely on the
I hope by the time we reach the end you'll see what I'm saying
Decision in order to maximize his out
This episode will take a straight through to
And like I said by that point the world really doesn't know that
We're pull two days away from the FBI releasing photos
3 days away for
From an arrest
But those are all things will cover on a few
Future episode
At this point we know that the bombs were pressure cookers
You know it wasn't attack
And that's about it
At least
As Alex's show begins on the 15th
The attack has
He has no idea what's going to happen by the end of the time he's on air
And that's We Begin Today's Show
Very familiarly
In the sense that the show
Holding pattern
And we hear the familiar things that we've heard
Over the past couple weeks
But knowing what we know
And knowing how is Joe
Before it goes off air is going to have this
Giant purple throne
Very surreal
You're the completely normal
Thing
The beginning
And so that's where we'll end up jumping it
I feel like I should pull curtains
Spaghetti
I'm sorry that's a bit I had
I don't mean to be I just felt they needed
Be more of a Visa
The best 10
Then normal
Cuz I'm a little bit away from the
Listening
These episodes with far more of a strong
Feeling of like
He's doing this on purpose
I can see the crack
Then I in other times
The past
Smaller-scale things it's obvious
He's doing that on purpose
But in this case it was
Pretty over
Actual
World-shaking
Pried open
The artifice
Personality
It would be very difficult to concretely
As much in the moment
If you're listening
Much more difficult to see
The ways the manipulation
Being done but now
Later looking back
It's pretty f****** clear to me
I'll present
Eclipse that we have
I hope they can
Conclusion is a
Almost precisely this moment
I need a strong
We start on the 15th
Has a narrative
To begin the
6.91% to $1,300
6.9
Worst
So he's leaving the show
It's not real real
6.9%
Do you need to lose before it's a problem
Gold price
PriceRite
It should be pointed out he's indicated by the same guy who owns Vitus resources and gold sales company
So anytime he has a narrative
It surrounds gold
Like wow I don't know why I don't know about you man
The first thing that I hear is
Him being so don't worry about it
Because the ice
The Next Step
I actually actually think that
Conspiracy behind globalist
Idea what you do
They just want to be able to drive it down to
Embrace
In April 2013 gold prices
Plummeted
Percent drop from here
Percent drop
This absolutely feeds into Alex
Does paranoia
Adjusting about this drop
Open price is
It's one of those Universal features of Alex
His worldview
Hi there this is this happen to it
The globalist are so overpowered they have complete control over all commodity prices
Push them up or down
They're suppressing the price of gold
Alex Witt
Stop suppressing
But they're not just depressing
And the price is the price at all
Like the earlier one
Except for bigger
Right
Global it right there in bed with the Federal Reserve
Whatever
Berryville
I'm not sure they are
I don't know if fiscal prudence
The old adage
I just think it's absurd to think like
Little bit lower in
Globalist
At any time
Whenever they want it
But
They're mostly worried about
Inconveniencing a lot of people
Selective
But very encumbered by whatever restrictions I decide to put the on them at make it
Convenient for my Naruto
He's a big restriction
I think that will always come
They have to make you agree
They can do whatever they want
To say yesterday like vampires
Consult more grounded data sources like the international business
Clear what's going on
Post-mortems that were done after the fact
The first variable is it gold mining companies were having a particularly bad year
Around it which is an indicator to investors to be worried
These companies took out expenditures and law
Coming through
The picture looked a lot like a lot of these companies
Provide a lot of
Playa gold were in trouble
Stream
The second Factor was automated commodity
He's Trading
Algorithm
But they also set them up with very similar or the same buy and sell point
So when the market bearded One Direction you had a number of groups are following the
Same pattern
This wouldn't have
That too much
Price of gold
If you're just one or two entities automatically buying and selling
But as Commodities analysis
Jeffrey Christian told the international business
Quotes it was more than 1,000
Steve's trading in
The 10-minute.
Witch hazel
Beer impact
You see this in a lot of Commodities Market
Probably something
Sucking regulates
Super heavily
I'm well-versed enough and markets
To know if it's a good idea for us to say like
Navigation to that
But we should also
Let's get this.
Control Michael Lewis
Wrote a book about
Automation
And how
People
Like the larger
Set up their servers
Closest park
Because
Fukkit
Fiber optic
Trillium
Automated
Stop mean
Means that you win
11 trillion
More than
You're making
10 billion
You know whatever
Yeah
No it should absolutely be again
100% because you sat like
All the sudden there's just
Splash
Crisis bed last
20 minutes in people lose and a lot of it
Could be
Accidental are based on
Computer whatever
Random Twitter content
August 9th
It's alright it's
A computer s*** that ends up effect
Real world stops away
I'm saying maybe
There's a barista
Situation in 2013
Honestly I think about this escalating
He's been putting out
I mostly didn't
Consider it because he hasn't talked about it much
Until this episode
The price of gold dropping is a huge part of this financial collapse
So it would make sense
Whether or not
I feel like this is the background
At least these April episodes
Other ghosts
Just
The dropout
Gold price but maybe he thought it'll course correct
About it
Kind of gets distracted by something a little later this episode it doesn't it doesn't Factor too much into
The coverage of the bombing
But I wanted to bring this up here make a point out of it because I have a corporated
Forward
Because it does not stop
But a particularly bad
And it does make sense
From
All of his hustle narrator
And to make sense of that would be
Fear Factor
Ann Arbor
So the financial side of things
There's the
Are all of the same like they're going to take the kids to Global is to trying to get the veterans all this
He's yelling any reaches a despondent
And he starts talking about how he doesn't know what to
To do
How's my daughter supposed to protect yourself against
The globalist
And I honestly think
This is one of the more likely response
Possible things
Because
Very smart person
California
Water
Going to head out
Tasty Licks
Set
Man on the street prank videos
Huh
It's $0.08
That's what that's based on first
Servall
And second of all I just really think they like the escalation in his rhetoric that we've seen over the past couple weeks
The showare
It's really
Very seriously getting to the
The point of like we are fuc
We got it like
Going to destroy it immediately and all that stuff
When Alex has moments where
He's getting really emotional and saying I don't know what to do
You are
Derelict in your duties
Is you have riled your audio audience up into a frenzy and you were saying
Look I know I'm the captain but I don't have through this website
Which leaves the audience
I got some ideas
The ship is going down you're on top of it
It's even worse that cuz I was like
I am a boat expert I know everything about boats
Most brilliant mind against the globalist
Doesn't know what to do maybe some of my ideas would be good
Freeze them up to not really
Alex Azar
Along the lines
This is a nympho
When you have him admit like I don't know what to do
Tid of like I trust your own it
If you're going to act like
You give you like
I do like finding out more
Unique physiology
In that
My mom is very even though she's intelligent
Where you're like you're taking the whole
Fruit of the knowledge of Good and Evil tree a little too literally
I think knowing something
Apparently mean that you lose it
Interesting possibility I read it more along the lines of
Innocent as naivete
Assertive
Of the
And is that clip
You know
The world hasn't changed yet so Alex
Where he can make
About pop culture
Like
Children listening to on their iPads
Shut up
You leave her alone
Iowa remember there being some kind of Satan
David Young videos can I watch
How to kill themselves
I started watching some more Kesha videos I might talk about your love is my drug
What you talk about some of these real uplifting
Great job pop songs
Auto recent episode we heard Alex talking about how he stayed up
Late night when they play the job
Led Zeppelin
Yeah
Call you're doing
Grumpy old assholes
Music
Yeah
That's all
So in the next clip Alex's
Street reports
Interesting videos
Discussing
Plans of video of a man on the street
And I think he's going about it wrong
California
In distress
We're going to
He guarantees because he's going to edit it
McHugh's music all right here's the piece of propaganda put together without on the street
Yeah
Okay I guarantee
That I can craft a narrative that I will
Universal agreement
Dude that is not how this works that's not you can't
You can't allow yourself to
That's reporting
I think the fat Clippers trivia
Anyways
But I think it's important
Because what we're about to witness
With his coverage of the bombing
Very clearly marked be crated amazing perception
Here we go out as well
When you see the way the
Minecraft
A narrative out of this bombing
See before the bombing even happened he was talking about doing a very similar thing around another topic
It's an MO
So Alex another another little lie
Bee in his bonnet
Is
Easy
Complaining
About the house normalization
Immediately
Resolve the complaints about the
TV shows like
We hate Paul Revere that never came out bacon Patriots look bad on
Making
TSA look
Good in commercial
You probably already
That's the point of the Pillsbury Doughboy
Do you know what is catchphrases it's not words it's him giggling because somebody do
Most ridiculous things possibly
The Geico
Cuz you know they had that other people
Cialix
I love you I love how weeks
Kind of gazing
Cigarettes
It's almost paradise
The satire to it
You remember that
What's better than this is not the
The Pillsbury Doughboy
What the implications
The TSA
That is what they are underlying joke
Conversive
But Alex
Maybe the issue isn't
Next Clippers very interesting probably important for a hook for
And that is that
Tower before the Boston bombing happen
Alex expresses his position
On Sandy Hook Visa V actor
Thank God this is
So it's really interesting about this is Alex keep saying
Kind of different
I don't give a f*** if you think some real kids died if he thinks it's some people there were actor
Because he could believe that
Robbie Parker is an actor
Are are actors that are
Sue again or whatever
I'm still think so
Picking and choosing who he wants to
Using one person
Who's
Child
In that shooting up
Is
Everyone
The same game
And he's he's passed away
He has crossed the line into a cure territory
He's being on specific about it
These people like Robbie Parker acting like actors
The conclusion that you have to be
He thinks
At least some people are lying about their family
And that's f***** up
Are or I suppose Ferrari
If you want to make that argument as though it's a real thing
Then you have to go line by
Yeah
You can't have a responsibility everybody because you get to choose in the moment
Well
This is the one who's an actor and then you look at you look at
The next one you like
They're real kids
What you're doing is a half-assed everybody
Yeah and giving your audience
Permission to decide for themselves
To watch.
Exactly it's really
Narratives of really ramped up over there
This leads
Alex to like really get mad
About how like Glenn Beck is
He starts screaming about how his job isn't
Fun because all this stuff is real
You know like all this stuff is real
Hotel with his
And so like
Start screaming about that and he says
Something that you will later consider
A remarkable
Aurora
Obvious
Colorado
Screaming about therapy.
On the day that there is a bombing
He will be like I said earlier in the show
Regularly
You know that you can't talk about
.
Matter when you look it up
There's about
To be something
Feature of his broadcast Style
That's all I don't ascribe
Too much meaning
It does
Jesus dad
Nobody
Happy about this
Except Alex is going to be very happy
He is going to
Gleeful that people I'm not sure
Knox
Experience like a human
Richard Belzer
Yeah Richard Belzer
I do like
Well it's kind of like when you put your seatbelt on a plane
Here we go
Was Christopher Walken
It's just down right next to the shards
Recipes chicken recipe
Christopher Walken in no time for Alex
Completely
Richard Belzer is on to promote a book that he's written about the JFK assassination
And of course.
Earlier in the episode lost
Respect for somebody past relationship
Get real high
Ice-T
You kidding me
Baseball bats
Amazing
When I was younger
I don't know
I'm being good
But I had a real fondness for my like the idea
Is character John bunch
Travels between like homicide
He connects all these shows into a
I like that and I wasn't positive Association
Call John
But you like him
Amman
You listen to him talk to Alex and realized
Open to in a long time
I must say that your
Programming your documentaries
Your news
In my research
Appreciate it.
I want you to always
My friend cuz work
How do you say we're treading in Dangerous Waters now.
I heard that and I was like Richard Belzer
Stupid
I was like
He's abusing Alex's resources for his research and no
Ono Ono
Bad bad news
That isn't a belted never gotten the
Do you think he would be the
Conservative comedian prototype
All that conservative
I don't know
He's a conspiracy theorist
It just like all those other comedian conservative guys
Say one thing
And then people be
It's really hard to cook that
Especially given the way conservatism
Is changed
Those times
Like with the hypnosis comedy
Work I see some stuff that I didn't I didn't think somebody was terrible.
I honestly don't have any memory of it
One way or another
But
I think he's just as a low standard of
Evidence for things
Wahlburgers
Truth
Alex doesn't make things up
That's pretty crazy
Bowser's on here lauding Alec
You're one of the truth-teller is that use your stuff
Just kisses ass
He means at 4
Which is more troubling
Opposite
Exactly
Elevate
What's my favorite book
Is the
Listening to people explained
I love
Ice-T explaining things
To anyone else
Law and Order
I'm so
Richard Belzer
You know he has his whole career behind them
Conspiracy thinking
Aliens
What have you and
Start talking about the
The bank
Got weird
But
I have an alternate exit
Donation for everything
He's trying to
To cause panic
You're getting to the bank
You know
The current
Going to places
Oh my God
Are we just having too old
The batteries in your mouse
Cassius doing all this
I don't know
Your mouse needs a new battery
No it's the same
It's the back I started talk about the bank and I was still on Law & Order special Victims
Look if you want to if you want to put them down
Like my Advocate stopped working at now we're talkin about the banks
No you can't
Magic
I'm not sure if you said
He probably does know probably
Generally speaking really bad sign
Yeah but I don't know what
Takes about JF
Like maybe he's difference
Stop
Howard hunt
And I was like oh no
Richard Belzer stupid
What's a jury trial
That's very super
That is very
So first things first the spotlight is the publication
Liberty Lobby
Alex's Chief Bilderberg
It's a trash publication
As for this lawsuit
Richard Belzer's playing fast and loose
The details
Spotlighted just published a Howard hunted been in Dallas on the day of the JFK assassination
Gaza
DC at the time you decided to sue them for libel
The question of his involvement in the assassination
Was it matter that wasn't germane to the case
And in no way was decided by this case
At all
The first lawsuit over this one
And he was awarded $650,000 a day
Verdict is overturned
Incomplete instruction
On how to give their verdict
In 1983 the case was retried
But it's important to consider what winning this case
Perhaps more importantly what winning this case
Doesn't mean
Bible doesn't mean that the thing that you wrote is
True
We just say that this trial doesn't even establish in court that hunt was in fact in Dallas
Witness
Necessary for this
I'm not liable is it Spotlight had to have reason to believe this was true at the
Set timer publication
Which is what the jury decided was the case
A lot of this is probably based on the Liberty Lobby building up a good case that doesn't
But they weren't just making it up
That's not the hardest thing
To show in court
Which is why it's important
For these Bible laws
Pretty
Lenient
Towards the media
Because otherwise you can mail them for things
Good faith errors
Is that got made
Does that the bells are doesn't understand
Flag
He's putting forth
All other information to put haunted
In Dallas
The campaign
Or the alleged deathbed confession
Hunt made to
Two of his son
Although it's important to point out that
Widow and their other children
And if the Suns coach talked
Say what they wanted so they could prop it up
Yes so
Well what it wanted what is he going to be pissed
Evil probably but I don't know I don't I don't care
We can't have today turn into a rock shoes
People Finder
Is the
Everybody already thought you probably killed
So
I all this is to say that Richard Belzer thinks that Zach court case
Determined
The E Howard hunt was involved in the assassination which means to me that he doesn't understand
He's talking about and he wrote a book about that
That's bad
Bedding
In like
Civil court
They proved
Call Jeff
All of this starts to make sense
Bowser starts talking about
Fired him down the road in life that he's on
You and I both were inspired by this book
Across the dollar
So he's inspired by
David Simon
Argument
Target baby
OK Google
Problematic
Source for them to share
Get the f*** out of here
Iams Alex's to overdrive cuz Belzer's are they having a great time
Let's do a fourth our plant
He doesn't know about it for about 20
He doesn't get the news immediately
Somewhere in that range
He comes on air at this is it immediate reaction
Well it's terrible news related
Explosion at the Boston Marathon the punch up
208 Central
Boston Marathon 308mx Eastern Time
Explosion style man
Horrible
His first instinct
Not even knowing any information about
Bleak lotion or something like that
His first instinct is to Guess Who they'll blame
He thinks they're going to blame our arawn
The Patriots
Veteran
Two of those
Are based on
He's big narrative
They're going to
This
Explosion happens
His first instinct
I wonder if he'll blame it on us
That's not good
That
When I think of
As of tragedy
My first
Thought
Sympathy
The Patriots
To Mike Epps
It's my first. I don't think I don't think this is a trap
Help the victims are okay
My first thought is the real victims are white p
That's the truth
You know they're going to demonize people with guns because
Anyways
No anything
About what time
Haven't watched the news posted on Drudge Report
Anywhere else
And so they start talking about the dynamic
Better going on
A one thing that's really important
Very quickly
That veterans and right-wingers are going to be
You mentioned before about
Is the very
Official reaction
Show me
Yeah
I'm working with veterans
Special Victims Unit
Units
About who had
Because he was having flashbacks
And helped us
Story
Veterans looked at
Narratives that he's been building up for weeks in months
They're going to blame the veteran
Which is good because they don't know that
It pointing the finger at anybody
Are constructing this
That's important
Here's what I think
Right now listening to Bells I think
He is
Incredibly
The line that buddy glasses
From Friday
Just that
Wee-wee overburdened with an
Can a good actor travels
You know what I'm saying interesting doesn't have much going on in the education
It's a mess it's that there's not much going on in the in the storage
Listen to this long time
I'm about this episode and I thought it was
And for the longest time I just had this idea in my mind
He's riding
Active
Participant
He is he is helping Alex
Threadless
So Alex is still kind of hoping that it's an
In the immediate
Just learning
Think about this
Stage
After explosion
I hope not
But I am
Even if
They will use it because
Everyone's focused on now
People can be controlled when they're all on the same emotion at the same time
So now it doesn't even matter
Al-Qaeda it doesn't matter
Still an attack on the veterans
This is a narrative
You can see it very clearly
How much is it is like
Knowing what they plan to do in the neck
Next few days and how much of it is just like this
Wonder what
You doing if he was at home buying
Or creating a narrative
Reacting to Something in real time with a
Alex Jones already
Influencing you be someone who you kind of admire
Is going to be
Or I imagine
It's going to be like I'm going to follow the leader
And the leader is saying
This is a false flag
I can tell you're like yeah
No I mean within minutes
And how much is that
You don't have any
Wow I think someone forced because they go to
Jana and they start looking to it Alex
Reality
Underway right now
To protect an event
That is over
That's so they can
Alex
Attack already formation.
He doesn't have
Cuz he has kept up with the story as
Evolved over the half-hour that in
Busy right now
And 45 seconds later
He goes back to sleep
It's clear why they're reporting it as an attack
This is information that's already
Alex
Didn't have some
Reason to be looking at the situation
Within a minute he's like
Need to calm down
That's really the bottom line
When you look at a lot of this stuff when there's crisis reporting on Alex's show
He needs to
If you need to check out
They are not doing good job
He's
F****** Christ
Crisis report
In a way that
When you're so unfiltered as
As AJ
Reacts
Certainty
That level of crisis
Is almost
Possible for
He can't wait
For a second to the
Oh we're going to wait
He has to react
Is validation of the brand
Is today right
For twenty years and know their game plan
So you need to have like
The answers
And that's a problem
I'm soaked
What they do for most of the rest of the show
On the 15th here
Is
Correct
Guessing around who did it
The government will
Create a narrative
Will be a fabrication to shape our thought
Military
Facebook
What they were
The Arkham
Is going to be
You know
I'm really proud of them for moving
So quickly I'm really proud of them
Making it way past that
Stage of a yeah
Holy s*** f******
Sociopath
It really is
You can hear already that this is fake
Yeah
Minute
You're in overdrive on air
Absolutely nobody know episode
Azrael
Paper rose
Delete my might give us
What you're saying doesn't have to be on here but Alex recognizes the lack of information
So he what he does in the middle of the 4th hour he announces
We're going
6 hours today
Takes off
A little while
Jakari Jackson and David night host
A h
The next like 3 hours but taking calls and stuff like that
We will listen to a little bit of
But not from
From this
Because I can't find that audio
And I feel like
Whatever they might have come up with
If it's something that sticks
Alex we'll talk about that
So we will get all of that
That coverage as it were
Extremely
Very fast
Him doing it it's like okay
You know a couple of minutes into the fourth hour of your show this tragedy happen
But halfway through the hour drive we're going six hours today
It's very fast decision
It's based on the lack of
The ability to
Have the concrete
Make your Market
Which is why it is
Which is why
He has to be
Call Moline
I definitely feel like a vaction
Indicate a certain amount of that
Gleeful whenever he's out
Like I said the only real substance
What's going on between
Bowser and Alex
Is that they're just sort of gas
Who's going to be
Tourette's
I don't feel this very productive
Well menu
Their needs
I pray that they
What menu
I don't know is it
Demonizing of the Patriots that happened in the last
Forever I don't know
The new enemy is
The Patriots
We've never had to worry about
Well I mean
Hey earlier the f*** you
Perry the actor
Advance of the Superbowl
Don't know my conference okay it's okay
It's okay
Alright American League versus The National
Father
I don't love it
Today's the demonization of these truth-tellers Patriots all this stuff that's going on
Richard Belzer
Interesting
Considering what shows
He said that
People's brains
Children
So it's real funny
Complaining about the very future
Washington d.c.
Bureau chief Jerome corsi was
Very beautiful
Just know where you are know what the hell you're talkin to have done
Corsi's and associate
He's working for WorldNetDaily at the time but he's been on the show a bunch of the two
But he's considered an expert in s*** that's so funny
Did you can complain about the demonization of John Kerry
Show up
I'll be like hey you never make things
This guy I love
Incredible
Completely unrelated
Venice
Yeah
Building up this
Insinuation
And a lot of it has been steering towards probably going to be
Especially Alex
Steering towards it's going to be the new enemies
There's a whole lot
Then
It made sense
Alex realizes
One way that he can bat
They're all entering
Omigod omigod
Realized
Oh my gosh
I was right
Isaac Beckley
Bullied
On this episode of information
Patriots Meredith
It's Crystal Clear how excited he is Patriots Day in Massachusetts
Patriot's Day was not celebrated nationally on April 9th
It used to be
On April 9th third Monday of April
And the Boston Marathon has always been on that day
They're basically the same thing
Exhausted especially
More importantly though there are a lot of other things that could have been
If This Were Somehow Patriot related
You know there's a lot of reenactments there's these
Are the Red Sox playing at home
Is opening day
Every year or most
Visit a tenuous connection
But it's
Super important to Alex
Because he's engaging in a behavior known as motivated reasoning
Alex has a predetermined conclusion
To arrive at
Namely that the globalists are blaming this bombing on the page
He needs to get there because Vermont
He's been warning of a big attack coming back
He knows he's probably not going to get a better chance
To validate his narratives and rhetoric
And the process make a bunch of money
Get work at get to work at crafting this and make it
The behaviorist
Alex is exactly what you'd expect from
From someone who is not
Didn't reality
But interested solely in manufacturing upper
Perception
It's been consistent since the news of the bombing broke out
It's all been an attack on media coverage but it's not intact
It's based on
Instinct
You have Alex sitting on CNN for assuming it was an attack when they only did that because video they knew about the Alex
He doesn't have any information
About the attack itself North
Goddamn bunch
Rainbow
Think of the globalist going to blame
Alex doesn't want to guess who they're going to blame
He wants to establish
First of all B erroneously
And secondly that no matter who asked
Actually gets Blaine
Is all about
Getting it is dumb f*** gun buddy
I didn't know exactly what I would find looking at this episode
And on one level none of this is surprising but on another level
This is making me a lot more angry
Then I expected
Add straws to find a way to make
His tragedy about himself
And it shows worldview
People are f****** bleeding on the street
Other people putting themselves in danger
To help their fellow citizens
People are scared some people don't know where their loved ones are
This is a disgrace
And it's willful
It's an affront
Payment people
Boston we're going through exact time he's on are spreading
This is a perfect
Encapsulation of Alex Jones
Brainstorming
To spin a tragedy in
Profitable for him
While the victims of the tragedy blue
F*** him
Nonsense
They'll be more Ranch
I really really dis
Respected
It's such a next-level version of what he does
Like you do at the realities that are other people are existing in
And the way he's behaving are just
So
Out of style
It's awful
Do you would like
And lack of air
Is
Besides
The size of the United
If you are living
Belgium
And a bombing half
That's a
And so you don't treat it as though
This is an attack on belgians also
Right
In the same way
Belgium is a lot closer to France
Functionally
I do think that Alex
Believe she lives
Country obviously
In his mind the only
And it's a state or a country
Understand
Behaviorism
If you're just like if
CNN is reporting
If belgians were reporting this way about it
In France I would still think it was pretty rough
Interview at without
Like all these people are f******
I don't know if you can
So Alex need more information
Going along and there isn't much
Is unknown
But one way here
Sizing get around that is put out a call for people
Call Lynn
Anime what he's doing is just ask
He Intel
What are you going to get for your callers that is
The idea that you
Just crowdsource narrative
Transparent
Bulshit
Well I don't have time right now.
You guys give me a bunch of ideas
Adultery pick some to put into the narrative later it's
I know it's like a contest
I don't trust
To buy employees to read the news and synthesizes warm April
Alright
Give me some give me some wild ship wouldn't have debated
Responsibility
Crazy
That I want to really nail down
Down and talk about
Because I think that they
Kind of
He's trying to do
April 15th
In the again
Within
1:20 hour after news broke
We are
There is no
Olivia Ron part out of it
For now
Right here by the most dangerous possible for Alex
To frame a conditional
Call statement
If they blame libertarian Patriot group
Big trouble and they're moving ahead with it
Alex's injecting a classic if then state
As reality
So if you see blaming Patriot libertarian
Didn't necessarily follow and there will be bombing all over the plate and the March 10th
Camps is Eminem
This is a purely logical statement that you put in for
The problem with this when you frame an argument this way
You need to be pretty careful about how you present what the media is
With this if then argument
You're actually arguing that the globalist are about to Ron Paul and nobody
It just necessarily follows from the if then argue
You can't get around that based on
How words work
Formal logic
Cannot lie
The falsity
If you have a valid argument and the premises are conclusion
You cannot be false
The actual form of the argument that Alex
Who's making is this
Premise one
If the media blames the Patriots
Then they're moving ahead with it
Rabbit stew
The media is blaming
Conclusion therefore they are moving ahead
In this clip we're seeing the first premise
Introduce
Which is why this is stupid
Alex still needs premise to in order to have this construction of an argument work
And if we
Manipulating things in order to establish premise
That's immediately
Then what you really seeing as him lying and manipulating to jump
Notify the conclusion
That they're moving ahead with it and there's going to be
Is it pretty basic deception stuff
And Alex does variations
Kind of thing all the time
How do you spell like pointing this one I was particularly important
Very glaring
I will get through some more of this stuff you'll see why this is very
Important
He needs
Primus 22b
Be established
Doesn't work
He no longer has a good argument
If the media isn't blaming
He needs that to be there in order to
Justified
Facilitate
Baker's archery
Look
Extreme
Right
So I would like to
Hotlogic work
I would love to I would love to see Alex
X1 trying fumble through
Explained
Exactly
It is the argument
Look at it
Very like
Absolutely
Because
We'll see
I assure you
I'm so in the next clip Alex
And then he says which is code for
Man I hope
In trouble
With my famous 1776
Man I am amazed at how quickly these guys move on from grief
Anthony real personal concern about hypothetical yet
It sucks
Gross
He's working on Primus
But he's trying to make
It makes it so much clearer these actions are in
Service
Propping up the flimsy part of his argument
In order to make it all look real
Questions
In the area
And this pisses off Bowser
Exactly
?
Yeah I got to go to Drudge
Clips
As if to imply that he's asking about their right-wing groups
Special
Patriot's Day events going on in
YouTube
This is about the holiday
Are there are going on
Yeah
Is Patriots Day
Yeah there's a lot of traffic
I think that means it the right way
This is already the crafting of perceptions based on
Hinging on this word right
To make the argument work
Let me know
It's it's really easy for him to use this one because he wasn't
He's not burdened with that ability to under
Understand words
I think that this is one of the cases of
You don't know any
I think this is one of the cases of evil being map
I think that he knows exactly what he's
He wants to spread bore suspicion
Around the idea that the bombing was
Was planned by some
Nefarious globalist
Richard this is looking worse by the minute
Devon Google guys
Important to remember
Marathon running is a big
Sports marathon is one of the biggest annual marathons in the world
Someone off of insipid way bigger in terms of number of runners
But the Boston Marathon is huge
C97
Making it to the world's oldest annual Marathon
Like the marathon got brought back to the Olympics in 1890
The next year after that Boston Marathon started it's been going ever since
It's a huge deal in the international running community
Coming from all over to take part in this event
The second winner ever in 1898 with a Canadian
In 1907 a Canadian member of the First Nations named Thomas Longboat won the race
He has a very rich history
It was mostly Americans in Canadian
Until the late forties
And then you see the list come to life winners from
From South Korea Japan Guatemala
5-minute recent years a lot of Canyon
Only one American won the marathon between night
46 +
The only American to win that time
Kelly which happened to be the same thing
Spelling is elastomeric
And those dude
Work-related
The race has a crazy history full of weird trivia
They let women start running
Guess what Jordan
For six years at that point
Remember that
The Scottish guy who
Who single-handedly try to keep women out of
The marathon
There's a wheelchair Division and record holders everything
When you see that line of flags
Finish Line of the Boston Marathon
Or anything like that
It's a recognition that this thing that could just be people running along with
Is so much more than
It's a celebration that crosses cultures and
Community brings people together
According to the Boston marathon's official
Facebook page
Quote
Each year about 100 nations are represented by runners in the Boston Marathon and their Flags
Stretch of Boylston
It has nothing to do with the UN
Rather it's to honor and celebrate each of the runners
Takes part in the race
How to take a physical representation of cross cultural celebration in togetherness
He's using it to create suspicion around the bombing by just making s*** up to attach it to one of his big bad guy
You went
This is shameful s***
I really do get down to the bottom of it
Is it use any kind of mulch Multicultural Unity
As a um plot
And I think there's a name for that
You know it is almost like
He is taking
Let's call it the Boston
How much is a cross cultural event celebrating how regardless of where you're from
We all care and we are all humans
Then we are all empathetic
And he's turning that into something
Evil
Which browser is not in favor of
Yeah
Alex that has another revelation
That's how he realizes he can use to make this
Look like they're blame
It's always
What
That's nonsense
Also they took him like half an hour to realize it's text day
Weird
He's got a
Probably
Like I mentioned earlier in this episode
Talked about how they're going to bomb in Blaine bus earlier the episode so he looks like crawfish
And the whole crew
That's the thing he says everyday
Coincidentally a tragedy
East Rock
Shot heard round the world
So he's a psychic who predicted everything
And
How long how long
This is towards the end of the 4th hour
Because the thing
I
Here is a genuine
Enterprise
Self for being correct
Which suggests
He doesn't even think about it
Things are going to blow its autopilot
Like they're all going
And they have to tell him remember you predict
Yeah
Yeah elective memory on the part of his
Forget about it every time you said that
Disorder if you make
Should all the time everyday
The financial collapse is coming
1008 2009 crisis-hit
You look like a genius
The time
I just
You know if you want to play this game
Youcanplayit Alec
Text B
Five Star Pizza
Information during the break
From Rob do
And it's at his brother
Oh God no
Well there's a misunderstanding between the two of them
Alex really overinflate
What happened
Running the race today
Starmie
So pretty
Stupid misunderstanding
That's one more example of
Sure
Should have
Knothead Rob on a bike
When I've dropped
Disinformation
I think I could have spun this a little better
By willingly and very intentionally misunderstanding running
He's running
The right yeah
He's not running the ring
He's running
The Rex is that robbed his brother was there with the army
And he was
And at some point along the Route
Came to him
Signs of dehydration
And he was made to
Leave the race
Army army ranks
A high-level Military Intelligence guy
That's exactly what was going on
It is being put forth here first of all
Who's directors dad is in the FBI is brother-in-law
That's the sort of thing that really makes cancer
You can only say not I not I not there's a good guys in the Spy
Before people decide you work for the man
Well he probably
Personally I don't really believe these credentials or at least I think they're intentionally
Proximity to legitimate in
How much does it all the time
Why believe Steve
Mechanics take resume
Call Christopher monckton Lord
It's all just what works best for the brand
And the brand is
Deception
I'm inclined to believe considering the robin Alex offer no evidence to the contrary
They have signs of dehydration
Allow me to lay out my Kik
Lyrics
April 15th 2013 was a fairly cool a day in Boston
What temperature is around 48 good person
Finishing a marathon
Pretty high for the Boston Marathon
However
If you have over 20,000 and
1000 people
Who for one reason or another don't pass
Past the finish line
Are pretty good number those people
You kind of have to assume didn't finish because of medical reasons
It seems unlikely that they would train go through the steps
Qualified plan had registered for the marathon forgotten about
It's Not Butter
Work
It's something that takes
A lot
To get to the starting line the most people
Look that's why 95%
You're not having anybody who's like
How to lurk I'm just going to go run the marathon today I woke up a little bit late
It's not uncommon for people to be unable to finish the race
Actually died
Before
One thing that makes the dehydration or exhaust
Exhaustion
Story
Is it a pretty common for enlisted person
To sign up for this Marathon
Honor of their fallen Brothers in the service
They do the symbolically by participating in what's known as the
Shuffle Rock which involves military backpack
That weighs about 40 lb
That a variable could make it far more likely that someone would have a difficult time finishing the full Marathon
Brother-in-law was doing toughrock
But there's definitely
The marathon
It's literally impossible for me to figure out if any any concrete information exists on that
Could be robbed sister's husband
But whatever isn't even his last name
I've no way of tracking down any
Information
And they don't offer at
Because of course they do
All this is to say if there's possible explanations
For him being advised
The marathon that have nothing
To do with conspiratorial paranoia
Well I looked into a little bit and
I believe his name
Private
So that doesn't that's dead Rick
The best thing I can say is for this is that information
Doesn't prove
The worst I can say is the dues allowing Alex
To use his brother-in-law's medical situation
To be used as part of his attempt
Capitalize on the death of
3 people
Injuries of 250
Tupac's others
Which I find to be an immoral act
Yeah he should have gone from dude
I agree
Let's see if Richard Belzer has a different take
Operation
So
Counter Theory
He was dehydrated okay well you could believe
Because
He said it
Right
You know what year
That's not even
It obvious
God.
Yeah
I don't even care
Do even
Has a brother-in-law that someone was going to have something sore
I thought you were
On the road
The Alex is overdrive fourth hour
Coming
Do more
In order to
Laura-leigh
SOB jump back keep the fires
Stoked
And we see that Alex has decided to make this a regular thing
Future rapper
24-hour straight or longer
Nope
Still not true in 2019
Long time
Striking while the Iron's hot
Here's the thing out of it
There's not a lot of information coming out
For speculate
People are in the right headspace
Conjecture and b******* in order to satisfy
4 something
And I'm going to fill it
Yeah if there's a
Someday everybody wants some
Nature abhors I abhor Alex
So there's no information
The 15th
Come out about the bomb being a pressure cooker
Those little bits of information
Have
Come out reporting
I went back to the room was looking
Through like articles posted in that day
And a lot of it is just a very
Standard
Little bit of
Information
We're not yet
Noah Wyle
Put out by
Everybody the internet
There's a lot of feelings
In the course of this
It's not just
Everybody else
To let people off the hook at other places
I have some critic critique
And if
So
Talk about how you know I've been saying cuz it can be a false flag forever
Great
How many complaints about OB
Obama's speech
False flag
What
Sure
Narrative they're going to carry out
Whether it's
What's your very rare
Deter attacks are rare.
In the malls
Ratcheting up of the overall
Martial law
I want to press conference
Really ugly
Black and white speckled
Paramount during press conference
I looked at that
So bad
Oh yeah
The first thing that came to mind
What what does a fear monger
It was about the people who helped each other like
That speech was about the runners going to give blood
It was about people taking off their clothes to make tourniquets for other people like
Fix not fear-mongering right it's almost it's almost like
Took one of Obama's strength
Empathy and orator
And attacked it and tried to make him look weak
Almost
I always love it when he gets into the like
Real I hate the belt
That's just
Rock the Bells
I love you I love you and Alex metric
Specific numbers
And so he gives birth
But this was real
Screenshot of 100
What are out of 100
But this is real
Alex has had time to gather resources
Figure out a way to
Defense
Krampus 2
That they're blaming coming for you
And here's how he
Stepped out on that road will be going on throughout this
Where are they
So this is such a classic Alex
You have tons of evidence
Already bore you with proving his case
This person should be strong indication that he does not have a ton of Eva
Manufacturing
Perception
He's clearly distorted wolf blitzer's words in the closing segment of the April 15th
Episodes
That's one instant
Something he thinks
Is proof of blaming right-wingers with Bob and it's b*******
The bombings could be related
Axelrod's comments were regarding the fact that Obama didn't immediately call this an act
Actor terrorism
Explaining that quote
The word is taking on a different meaning since
He went on to say quote
You use those words and it means something very specific in people's mind
And I'm sure what he was what was going through the mind of the present it is well we don't really know who did this
It was
Someone who is pro you know you just don't know
And I think his attitude is let's not put any
Inference
Let's just
To get the people
Responsible
And that is why
Everybody
Hahaha
It's
It's really tough to parse exactly what Axelrod was saying
A possible reading of it is that Axelrod fix that Obama B
But another reading of it is that Axelrod
Dim stuff just
Another reading is the fact that it was texted was just
Example Axelrod came up with to express their a ton of motive
They could be behind the bombings and no one really knew what the situation
I'm inclined to are towards that last one
Also says quote
Inference
Literally
I'd like that's almost
Worst example of
Example
Well we don't know who did it
Cuz everybody lose their
Maybe like this is a terrible
He has to give like an explanation for why
We're not
Come out and say
I'll call you
Yeah yeah
To say it could be
It could be
Islamic
The first one
In a defense
Of what
The explanation of it is there a lot of votives
The first easiest one that people could under
Is
Wow is also text
Which by implication consider that a terrorist
Probably
Motivation
And anyway
On a scale of total b*******
2 they're blaming
A1 or A2
It's easy to see how it could be spun to say if they're pointing the finger at xprotect
But it's entirely unconvincing
And only work
If you take it
Completely out of
So
Alex is convinced this is a false flag
He's very thorough
Nevada
Through this entire episode which is
He believed that media
Like Media Matters
Mediaite
Him right person go to blame right-wingers
Is there a saint
Right
Tangled web
When first we set up to tell the truth
So here's Eclipse Artisan body
You are busy analyzing
We playing Doctor Who
That was very predictable
Media Matters
Because you're
Gotcha everything posted letters from the time of the bombing to the point
M340i
About
On the morning of the 16th Matt Gertz
Published an article titled reactions to the Boston Bomber
The 1st century was Alex
With a screenshot
That killed Boston Marathon
Aztec Falls
Hashtag
The rest of the list of people
I hate I hate living
Free solitaire
I love love love indoor plumbing
But I want to go back
Tuba for all
I just I'm not for there was a bad Road
The rest of that list is just people like Laura Ingraham and Pat Robertson
Is there's nothing about criticizing Alex
For saying that they were going to blame the Patriots
There's another
His enabler
But this to doesn't seem to be critiquing
A saying that the globalist going to blame the Patriots for the bombing
It just seems to be people rightfully and rightly responding with disgust
Quickly Alex
That article probably had him more worried though
Since it was discussing the people who validate alley
Consistently wrong
Great
Specifically
And all the other supposedly credible mainstream people who unwittingly Elevate Alex
If I rally
I would probably see that
As an attack but it
It still doesn't fit with what Alex is describing
I really can't find any evidence
Media Matters was condemned
For saying they were going to blame the Patriots
I think they're just kind of offended that he called it a false flag within minutes with no information
Kind of wrote an article like that but if you actually read it if more just an article that's like look at this ass
Kind of the point of that article
White House front group
Still employed
Wesley Glen
Perpetrators
Turn out to be Muslim just like it's possible
Extremist right or right wing
Or busam fearing Anders Breivik
Or lone individuals driven by a political mental illness
Do you even calls out a few Democrats on Twitter who made suggestions along with calling out islamophobe
The thing about being Muslim
His take on it was pretty even-handed
No way suggest
But it was a right winger
Hijack on The Young Turks conversation on a different reaction depending on who the bomber
Conversations priest
But it's
Not at all
Hypothetical
Looking over the mainstream reporting in the immediate aftermath
I didn't really see a lot of people blaming right wing
Extremists at all
There's some suggestion
Based on the timing and amateurish nature of the bomb
But all those suggestions were accompanied by disclaimers that we have no idea behind
Too early to say
Alex's rhetoric does not seem to match up with them
Which to me is an indication that
Like I keep bringing up
He's trying to build
Promise to
Of his
In service of the globalist about to bring this whole thing down Panic everybody
Primus too so even if the media doesn't do what he's
Predicted they will
He's going to go out of his way to make it look
On a very basic level
This is purely designed to cause panic and fear
I put his audience Apocalypto
Estate
It's disgusting
Respond to a legitimate tragedy
Because it's
Fantasy him use this like
These
These Outlets
Are responding to what I did
Like humans
Might saying this guy's a f****** a******
And then they blame
Patriots
Adding that wrinkle into it sort of invalidate other people
Correct credit
View
Even worse
All this is just a psychodrama
Forcing on his audio
And
Kind of weird me out of
Which
The whole point of
Victor make people afraid
So why are you
Saying that you're condemning them
And
Estranged
Almost
Relationship
Supposed to
It's weird how that works really Alex
To himself
He thinks that all he's doing is like ask
Question trying to get to the bottom
But you can see that's not the case
You can see in this next clip that what he's doing is using all the narratives that he had built up over the past couple months
And applying them
To the current situation
We warned you before
Lexington Concord Boston
Stewart Rhodes is Charmed in leader of The Oath Keepers
Who does Alex go to immediately
Kumite bomb something
Consider him an expert
What you see there is a fine-tuning of the old narratives that Alex have been building now that the payoff his come
He chisels them down instead of Chicago in order to
If they are
Staying
Veterans
You take whatever it is is functional out of the myth
And the narratives that you've bailed and apply them
The present situation
I pretend all the other s*** never happen
I really
Having a
Who after the boss
Was it one of you guys
Out of the few of them
How Wild is
Is that yeah
Crazy to have
Have a bunch of known
First group
Like
Second degree
Just threw Larry Pratt of America alone
Contact
Yeah it was pretty weird
You don't need the Kevin Bacon game now
No it's
It's a very short
Yeah
So I have this clip it just kind of off-base a little bit and I like it's kind of not really related to
The primary stuff that's going on
Is it something that Alex does not believe
Just
2 years later
And
So Alex believes
Aggressively
A very strange
Is he talking about like evidence
I think he didn't know
Part of a drill is correct about some
In 2013
We find out in 2015 he changed
Everything
Part of the argument
Everything is
There's always a drill that covers up the actual false black
Everything is vory talked about that turns the Sandy Hook
It's Universal ride is rhetoric
If there was a drill
At the Boston
Oh no
Now what came out
What's her freaking out
Discover.com
Manheim
Alright whatever you have doesn't
Little bit later on
Before I discuss it I'll let
Latest
Let's go further
Finish Line
It's just a training exercise
How much is the alternative
Prisonplanet.com
Remember this being parody
Very heavily
Right after
Turned it into a
The perception that there were an ounce
Like just before the explosion
In the aftermath of this
Is a drill
And that's sort of the way Alex's
Presenting
I like I said whenever he wants to portray something as a false flag the only arrow in his quiver he chooses
Feels like unassailable
Is the argue there was a drill going on at the same time as the event
Meant to provide cover for the actual attack
If you look throughout his career it's almost Universal
Part of almost every
Conspiracies
Never promoted
It seems a little weird
Because there was a
Describes
In this case he's taking a local Boston news article about a runner saying that they were bomb-sniffing dogs at the race
This is meaningless evidence
Pictures of people on roofs in hoodie
None of that proves a damn thing
It's just titillating
I consulted some running forum
To see what kind of chatter there was there in the aftermath of the bombing
I found a lot of accounts of people who claim to have been there
Just post on message boards but they do seem pretty
With
What the situation is they were told not to Pepe's dogs
And the dogs that there were there
For training /
The dogs are being trained
Weird but that's only because
There was a bombing
If it hadn't happened you just look at that and I guess that makes sense
Get the dogs acclimated to a setting where there's a lot of Buffalo
Tons of people around and tons
Mustafa could distract them
That seems like a tough environment to artificially create honestly I don't think there's any reason to assume
That the dogs were there for bomb-sniffing training purpose
More freaky
Krowd
Position purpose
I don't understand all the ins and outs of training
Dogs but I can imagine how this might
Pretty universally this was the position of people on running forum
It was an announcement not to pet the dog
Be calm around the dog
Don't startle the dogs
It wasn't
Cromwell there's a bomb going off
Even after surviving the bomb
These people are reporting
Weird
And I-10
I mean
There it is it there were announcement
Especially
Okay
Before we break down even a little bit more about this
I want to talk about why this is stupid on it
I was just trying to argue
The bombing was a drill that went like
And he's arguing
Piece of evidence from the speakers
How to stay calm it was just a drill
The person making the announcement was involved in the drill
Knew or believed it to be a drought
Is there actually running a drill
They would be doing so
2 gauge police preparedness
Headed towards accurately gauge
It's important that people act
If it was 100%
If someone were to convince everyone to stay calm
As it would completely alter the crowd's reaction to what was happening
I guess
I could be a good girl if you're trying to
Police response to a group of people who don't believe in attack is actually happening
But I feel like that's an area isn't very useful to prepare for the real world
But now it is becoming more and more you
Are not going to bail
Freight
Got on a PA system and told people not to panic is actually incredibly strong evidence
Thought that this was a real bombing
If it did happen
Which I don't think
It could have been misguided advice
Expected well-meaning person
Trying to help in crisis
Orderly
Triple everybody there's a lot of us right
The reality of someone saying that I would interpret that as
Evidence of reality
And I don't think that's actually what happened
I think it's a misrepresentation of
This article
He would still be hard to explain if this someone did make that announcement
I don't think I need to explain.
If you read the actual Post in the local 15 news out of Boston University of mobile coach Ali
Stevenson
And he says that there were announcements at this is a training exercise
However there's literally no indication
From the text or anything
These announcements
After the bombs went off or
Just before or anything
If you read his words and compare them to other accounts of people who were there
He's just describing the announcer
Not to pet the dog
Animorphs
Suspicious way than other people might have chosen to
There was something like 20,000 people running in that Marathon
And all the claims about announcement there was a drill
Conspiratorial interpretation
Comments of this one guy alley Steve
It's very hard to take this too serious
When there's tons of videos people captured on their phone
This announcement doesn't show up in any of them
When they're literally 10,000
This up other than wanted like don't startle the dog
I'm not even saying that I'm sure that Stephenson's making anything up
You know there's a really good chance that people were told to be calm around the dog
I hate comments could make sense
In the context of Runners being told not to bother these dogs
Acclimated to height
Stress lots of people environment
He might have been factually right but spoken in such a way the conspiracy idiots
Decided to read
Exactly what they want
To hear from his words
As I look at the information available it's really hard not to reach that conclusion
This guy spoken precisely about being informed there's a dog training X
Exercise going on and to remain calm around the dog
And Alexandra silk of taking that is proof
Set the whole thing
That's my assessment I feel like
What this boils down to
Now in future episode
There's a
Big wrinkle
About drills
But that will have to wait
There
Alex
Alex will find a piece of information
I don't know this to be the case from listening to his episodes
I remember that he finds a piece of information
That proves to him.
And it's far far more complicated
I will get to that
Sorry
Do you like Fox
Programming
Okay
Seasons 9 through
Arrow season 2
Fantastic
In advance
The Boston bombing with
Plan because they showed
I want a I want a
Get a drill
You wait until
That was
That's a weird
That's a laugh that somebody who actually caused the bombing
Talk about the bombing the day after it happened last like that
There's literally no context Family Guy
Affable behavior and I described that as Monster
I want to talk about an episode of Family Guy that have been released on March 7th
India episode
Peter is a skydiving accident meets a guy named food in the hospital
Southpoint
Peter Griffin is not a tea party guy
Episode that aired on May 13th 2012
Peter
Where the whole joke is it Peter joint
Episode was
Corporate interest
Computer learns that and reinstall the government
He's not a party guy
Character
Sure
How do I invest in the episode Alex become friends
Which leads Peter to convert to Islam
Broke into a plan to blow the Quahog bridge but
But as the episode
Clam doesn't get his table ready
Which it seems weird
But the phone is rigged and causes the bridge to blow up
I'm not a Family Guy
Message
So I'm going to leave that alone how shity
Rear weird muddiness
Some of the messages
What is the claim that Alex's
He's saying that this episode predicted the Boston Bomber
Use the cell phone to blow up bombs
The finish line of the race
And that is absolutely not
True
The cell phone is linked to bombs at
The Quahog Bridge
What Alex is doing is combine the end of the episode with a cuddle
From the beginning of the end
When Peter is skydiving
He says I haven't felt a rush like this since I won that Marathon
And it cuts to him driving through a crowd of people in the Boston Marathon
Put someone edited together the clip of the episode
And the cell phone gag
From the end of the episode
To make it look like Pew cell phone trigger bombs to attack the Boston Marathon
It may have been created in-house
Might have been
Might not
But even if it wasn't Infowars
The first Outlet to widely circulated
Anythink
Completeness of misinterpretation
And misrepresentation
The only reason someone would push something like this
Is it they're desperate
Counter reality
To the one the rest of the world is
Experiencing
He's an abusive active media and now it should be
Found
Yeah it is
Very clear
The the misrepresentation
It's clear the intention of it
Yeah probably
Travel f*** with people
And gave it to
Yeah when it
Alex
Occam's razor
Technological
Better to err on the side of Ali
Alex
Also another important
Even if
Complete misrepresentation about this Family Guy episode with
He still at this point has literally no idea how the bombs were detonated
The initial theories were that it was they were on a timer
Used for
It's really important to look
Stop like this
Because absolutely was a false flag
And the defense has given up his theories are really weak
If you look at them you find
Misrepresentation
The conclusion that it was a false flag which Alex's
Decided already
When you have to resort to that kind of approach to make your
At sign
Yeah
You know
I have anything on the 15th
Never he got the new
And everybody's
Tell him that
Said that there was
An explosion
Oh my God
I halfway think
Coverage that
Infowars
I think it's possible but I also think that he didn't expect they wouldn't catch the people
I don't get any expectation
Stretch it out over a day
Like this
Lost without a map
But I think
A clear sauce bike maybe even a rap
Within 24 hours
Have a secondary
He's the best yeah
An image
They are telling you
And then
You can twist it to
Yeah instead he just has to be like
Create
This is a drill
Misrepresentation
This article
Yesterday it was a false flag before completely
Manipulative I edited clip
Crazy
Continue with the
The cement can't be wet
Isn't somebody else can
Yeah.
Such a
Between
When an event happened
Actual information
Yeah because the longer it goes
The more
You need to work
To drive a concrete
I think that's kind of what
Was like trying to solidify this
Argument
Trying
Dryad
Right
Ticketworks
Piece of advice
Based on the fictional reality
You should never
Be involved
At all
Drill drills
Drive to Evergreen
The mall
Michelle
I didn't tell talking about the movie that I use of the reference to talk about
Which is poorly
Slapstick Manor
Shop
Alex
Something
Not good
For his present day
Lawsuit
In Sandy Hook
National news
Boston Marathon bombing
There was a drill
And the police know there wasn't a drill
So Alex has ownership of Danville
Present
He is trying to distance himself
There's a lot of videos of embarrassing people
He was an employee
You know we kind stuff unfortunately later in the episode
Are just phenomenal
So you make the clear that he hired that don't
Valley Stevenson
The short for Alice
Talking about
This the situation
Allicattt
Baton of spin
And then
Learn a little bit about
What
Drudgereport.com
Starline this morning
He has no reason to assume that people on roofs are bombs daughter
Ostracism conjecture
So that means that
Sprouts
No kidding
Salute in Tampa.
That is so brave
Yeah
So f****** Brazen in frustrating that I that like
Weird
We're doing journalism
Who is
Are not true
And that
So you got a day off
Big holiday
Guess what you have access to buildings rooftop
And you're near the front of the
Boston Marathon
The start of the boss
Would you and I say go up there have a couple beer
Beers and watch it
Are you asking
Also even the idea there were authorities up there
It doesn't it doesn't ring
Necessarily
And a lot of the stuff that like Stevens
Like if you just listen to it through the prism of there was a dog trainer
Exercise where would the places that
At the beginning
Tons of people are
Mile 12
Real Journal
The first question
Was there going
He was about to have a heart attack
Of course
There were no police dogs
Everything's fine
So I really interesting how excited particularly considering
In the present day
Dude
And I wanted to like
I went back and I watch
Deposition video in prep for this episode cuz I remember that comes up in
The questioning
About that
It's at that day
I think I noticed something really
The opposing counsel shows Alex a picture of a down day and Alex's first responses to get a huge smile across
To space in last
He very quickly realizes that this is a strange
Respond
Composure really fast
10 seconds where Alex is looking at this picture
There's a
A feeling of wistfulness for the days gone by
Buckets
Cast descendants
Pro wrestler to go yell at people
Disrupt event
I might be reading more into that that I need to or is appropriate his big laugh and smile quickly received
Realizes
Newtown
I could pretty evocative image
It's particularly in the context of him congratulating but beyond this episode for harassing
Boston
This image is really
It has a meaning to me
Whether or not I can prove
My reading of it is accurate
Well badani was in Boston
Doing all the report
Infowars microphone that use for his reports
Which I can't zoom in on enough
Confirm movie got that the rental War
He's there an official capacity
Not just as some guy who's videos Alex cover
Big narrative on this episode
Is that the media and the establishment couldn't handle
Describe it like he was asked
He was literally just
Yelled right
Brought up false Flags
They couldn't handle it
No I think it's
Articles about Massachusetts governor Deval Patrick
But none of them say the conference ended abruptly after his quest
I told video of it and he asked his rambling is this a false
And Patrick just replies quote no next question
The next question that's asked
Isn't the question to Patrick answer
It's about whether or not they're specifically their self
After the question is asked
Patrick steps aside and let the police represent
How to feel the question
If you edit the footage just right though
It kind of looks like Patrick is leaving the press conference after pedati asks
Question
And that's absolute ball
Also it's kind of surreal because as badanti is prattling on the camera pans across the stage and Elizabeth Warren
I m course he was
The real now that she's running for president
I strongly suspect that this whole thing is about trying to create the perception that
The powers-that-be are afraid of the words false flag.
Ordered
It's saying them in the president presents is the equivalent telling a judge do bouquet
It's purely an attempt to convince his audience
All these people
Hi and that thing is the truth
But Alex is
Disseminating
Alex wouldn't do stuff like this if you were making a real argue
Is it
This is manipulation to trick his audience
Accepting a fraudulent version of reality
It's intense
Cuz that press conference
Jeopardy question
You just stepped aside to allow the police commissioner
Varieties
The governor ran away
Couldn't handle
The fuckening
If it'll be closer to real but he does
Is it makes a fault
False version of it
Africa dandi broadcast
Alex
Episode I'm going to play something for a little bit
Really drive home is
Being repaired
Cuz it's intentional
Like constantly reinforced
Sing the same talking points
Your head
And Family Guy apparently is a big piece of heaven
The family
First
About multiple things about this
In order to make
He has to be Peter Griffin has to be a tea party guy
Islamic record
About the character
He has this
F****** crazily edited video in order to prove his
The bombing was
In the
Before it
Layers of manipulation
It is
Always watching
How many time
Can be wrong
You know
Usually people need a lot more words
To be wrong about
Four or five
Send Alex is everything wrong
Yeah you got it you got to give it up
Roads of The Oath Keepers on
Alex
Alex talks about humble lions
Enforcement and military organization
Constitution
To how incredibly evil
Go to no evidence
Also spoiler alert storage never shows up on the
Need I remind Fairfield Cleveland housekeeper who was arrested in April 2010
Charles Dyer
7 year old to be in possession of a f******
Plenty of evidence of The Oath Keepers RI
These actions of these couple people
Ethan demonstrative of everybody era group
But there
Or actually doing something horrible s***
And Alex
Turn the Blind Eye to that
Blown
To demonize the Oak
Because
I'm sure Alex would say that if
Earlier in the episode he said you know the media is also it's the right-wingers
Tea party libertarian
You seen all the clips
And he starts laying out a couple of specific
How well
He is doing reinforcing
Premise 2
That the media
He's blaming the right winger
Hays first one
I regret to inform you
So the eye is referring to hear in interviews
Riptide security analyst Peter Bergen
Allow me to read to you
You from Medi article that Alex has rapper
Quote
CNN National Security analyst Peter Bergen told host Jake Tapper on Monday that the explosions in Boston
Work of al-Qaeda terrorist
As much as they could
Extremist
Right-wing extremist
Either of those sorts of terrorism
War possibilities
And the situation is still unfolding
Legitimately
Bergen said that hydrogen peroxide hydrogen peroxide
Behind the attack
However if there was another explosive you that may signal signal right-wing terrorist
The number of failed bombing attempt by Al-Qaeda Burger
Caution other extremist
Right-wing groups trying to attack for instance Martin Luther King
Parade in Oregon in 2010
He said that he thinks that hydrogen peroxide bomb was more likely
Who's here
Are likely more likely Bhai
This article CNN analyst
Based on what he believes
He believes that for it actors are more likely
I don't know
You just had that I
Aren't they both right wing
Exit
The government has set up would be considered a liberal safe-haven
Different I know they mean different things but for the same thing
Bayou Vista
Article that Alex is talking about there which is presenting is the media
The Tea Party
Conclusion that foreign-based Terror groups are more likely behind the attack than right wing
His Source literally and Coke
Wheatley contradicted Meredith but it doesn't matter
Bergen in
Stability that Alex's militia weirdo bodies
And any insinuation that right-wing terrorism exist
Is really just a plot to demonize a good guy picture
He's blaming the boss
Boston bombing
Doing terrorism
Mentioning that right
Yeah
Well you think maybe for this one but he's setting you up
To say that the
That
Yeah it makes me kind of think that there's a possibility that Alex himself believes that right-wing terrorist
Might be behind
Yeah
Part of his motivation B be pre-emptive damaged
Control if the pot like if they do arrest so I don't know part of it
Center group or militia extremist group
Self-involved
Just went on his own
Like
This
It has a real utility
In terms of preemptive control
He was not involved
I think they're blue
You get the sense when you start to look at the
These things you see like
Don't don't say what you say or say
Why are you doing that
And I can't really tell you the why
I have some thoughts
Preemptive damage control is a possibility
Financial motivation is certainly a possibility
Just making
Himself
Right
Yeah
There's a number of possibilities
Without knowing
His own
Brain
I couldn't tell you but
It really does feel like there's there's at least
There's a nonzero
Probably thing
It could be a right
Thinks it might have been a good idea
Commit a terrorist Act
Well we're going to hear a later a clip of Alex and what kind of terrorist attack a right-winger should commit
Pretty f*****-up
So this article in the independence just explain your eyes on Twitter
That the bombing was either Islamic or right-wing terrorism
It doesn't say that it's either it's really just what you might call it
One of the two groups
On the right-wing side they point out that it was the anniversary of the Waco standoff as well as Patriots Day and text
On the Islamic side
They also point out that it's be 65th anniversary independent Israel
Also hold
The groups all over the
Honestly a fair reading of this article would lead you to think that they were making the point that Islamic terror is more likely
The part about the possibility of information
It's just a list
The fact
Like this date means there
Where is the part of the possibility
Includes an interview with
Professor of security
Studies from King's College
And references
Someone in the Boston Globe
There's a before wait behind the section
Then the right-wing possibility
Alex I sound like a broken record but this article is not blaming
Extremists at all
But again to Alex anyone pointing out that right-wing
Extremist groups
Exist
That
That's basically all I can say
Going on here
So I got another article
So is
Article
This is close to fair is Alex's
Headlines quotes FBI following up on a variety of leads to Boston
Embalming
They reference a counterterrorism expert Richard Barrett
Who says that quote the incident had hints of a right-wing
It was too early to say who was the blame for the marathon
The article isn't about who did the attack really
If I had the FBI's getting
Epson working through that
Inasmuch as the article does
Contain an expert
Suspected could be right wing
Extremist sign
Conspiracy Patriots
On a bunch of s*** he's a lying about in an article in the Irish Examiner
He's more than welcome
Come to but I will say this is
Thin f****** broth
The problem
I have with it
The most
Is that
Every expert
Everybody every reporter
That went for a
Quote
Every one of them
Is looking for you too
Every single one of them wants you
Doesn't matter if you have proof
Doesn't matter they want that for the article cuz you need it cuz it's
Article still don't know what's going on
You want an article that says this
And then whenever they tell you well it could be this or could be that then you say whatever
Sensitive information
For too long
Even professionals will resort to pack
Caution
Of course
I think it's
I better write the same Story 3 days in a row
Diminishing returns
So Alex has some more bad news.
Breitbart
Call
All of that is
The same thing
Outfront media article
Where the guy the guy said
Peroxide
Foreign terror is more likely
Cz's that three times
In this list
Articles
They all are about the same interview with Jake Tapper on CNN
Is that we create the illusion of there being tons
Of people saying the Patriots are to blame
Or the same source
The right way
Powerful
They're so good
Creative
Monolithic Unstoppable force of reinforcement
Just because they can always create that
Said something one time
Townhall
F******
Fox News
Breitbart
Name it they'll all write a story about it and then do all reference how
Must be a bunch of different things
Brilliant
You got to give it up
And all of this is to reinforce premise
In the Arctic
That's all this is
And I know that I probably sound like I'm making too big of a point
Of the construction
But it's how Alex in the immediate minutes
And maybe like half hour afternoon
Almost as if
Next
After he's already done this
Manipulative
Disingenuous work to establish premise
I promise to
You trying to like
Reframe the argument
Now that he had the second promise with him
This is the whole
It's over
Total communist takeover
So now you see how this works
He's now he feels like he's established that premise
Now it's about
If they blame the Patriots
Which he feels like he's established
Is is is there
If they do that
We don't we allow it to happen
Then it's all over
So now you shifted thing
You created the presentation that your first argument was right
Now we fight
That's how this works
Yeah
Well the other thing though is he added another caveat
The Republicans have to also apologize
Tubi
Illuminating
He doesn't
And if that in and of course
The solution that we're going
Going for a don't apologize to White terrorism ever
He doesn't actually want a civil war
So every time
He believes
He's proven an argument
You going to have to add another little caviar
So people don't actually follow through with the whole Civil War indicate exactly what
Narrative or this argument from
But its original form to now including
The right-wing and the GOP not apologizing for the party
I want
My weirdo extremist friends to be worth
I want them to be accepted if they are not accepted and they allow this
Demonization that I'm imagining is happening right now
Zayn
It's all over
I mean
So similar to the way political
Don't give an inch
Not one
Single
Yeah but I mean
The point being that
No.
Geopier
Not one
Can come out and say that a white person is
You capable of
Noah
Not one
The garden 2013 probably
But not forever
His new
Mr. Blaming the right-wingers
Does
It does track
Can you see that in the way the theater this is sort of shifting
Right
Alex
Warriors response
The Boston Bomber
You wanted critical info
The first bit of that
Go ahead
Hey Alex, you know I was just sitting here in a buddy of mine
He is a federal job and he told me
He comes over here
Can we talk about the bombing and what not and then he tells me
Okay there's reasons I can't give you but I feel bad if I didn't give you a warning
Buy as much ammo as you can
Is not he will not give me any critical information as to why
He just told me
Why is much animal you can double it I don't care if you have
2 if you have 21 shotguns or whatever you double that by the end of the month
That's exactly what he said
Boston he said no they declared a state of emergency
Different
You know I heard different things and he said all I'm going to tell you at all I'm authorized to tell you
It's the same thing I've been telling you
Buy more ammo Alex has been saying on his show for a really long
Say that has a friend who heard from somebody else
Is repeating third hand
Information and no matter what
He said
There's no use
For this being
On the show there's no use as credible information
Stash weapons
Like when is the message is coming from
This lack of credibility
All you're doing is scary
All you're doing is
Creating a perception that inevitably really soon
With the government
The Pentagon is the
The root against
Buckingham
Just be like the price
Gold going down about 7
Percent
How you figure Emma's going to go up
I feel like I should be presented slightly differently
The most generous
OneSource
Another source
Who I think
Mike is crazy
Martial arts
Sure
Video
I should be really clear this caller identified himself as a Marine
High-level information
Eat you presenting this as like actual In-N-Out
It's not
2 seconds before the plan
The lady with the black shirt black shorts
She's the last one to cross the finish line before the bomb goes off
First letters are 1979
Important
Every historical.
Started in January
December
Prime minister in 79
Elrond
The hostages in 1979
Also
You do have a 1979
Alright
Excuse me
Second shift the f***
Well no it's not even tell it to do
Free
Why not. 97-93
Globalist to finally going to
The flight number of the globalist
As important as 1970s
Hostage crisis
Great look sharp
Turn on the man in 1979 okay
How about the Happy Meal
Specifically arriving in Boston
Joseph
This show sucks
This is a stupid fat p****
The commercial inside I want to let you and you thought that meant
He goes back years how this goes
When you get the facts
Is this something you speculate on
Marine Corps
Domestic
International
That was
I'll send you email
But I can't talk more
Good question
Goodway
Price of oil
I'm also
Embassy
Credible
Edible
Incredible
Is incredible
This is actually like a really good Gamble
If you're someone who's
That is that there will be another event within a couple days because you've got to assume
It's now the next day
It was part of a terrorist organization
There'll be another bomb
That could be what you're referring to
And
That could
Pretty f****** scary for a little bit
Nonsense he's talking about it's a really good within a couple days
There'll be another event
Makes total sense
Doesn't prove any kind of
Intel
Credible
Immediately Alex gets on the phone with Joel skousen
Who also sounds credible
Sure
Skousen comes in and he is like I love that last caller and I don't think he knows what he's talking about
Information slowdown I've literally wrote that.
Sounds like that's not the kind of expected years
Immediately turns
Insulted him Alex
Cheese crisps
Immediately
Joel skousen
It has all the Hallmarks of a government operation
First and foremost one is they always pick high-profile then
Good. Good and out
Has all the Hallmarks of a things
Inventing which means I get to tell you what all the Hallmarks of that
Alyx belt
Recipes interviews playlist
False flag doesn't have dementia
Yeah
You could almost make a pretty cogent argument people
Constantly calling
False Flags only allows the government
What's up everything is right
If I was
Like this would be a great time for Iran
Because
Everything
What Iran.
I can get away with it because
Is your giant
So Alex is talking about this being a false flag it is
I need a false flag
To be human sacrifices
You have yours
She was false flag
Alex discipline
Disgusting
Go fuc yourself
Like he's not just making up some abstract possibility
He's imagining
Kid who specifically
Did die
In this bombing
To sit on a duffel bag
In order to kill them
A publicity
That's f******
Insanely disrespectful
Hi to parents
To the child too
Everyone
This is disgusting
This is not how
Like this isn't asking questions
This isn't journalism
This isn't exposing truth
This is all just a monsterous person
Hurting people
It goes no there's no value
Disgusting
Concrete
I guess widest infuriates me more than
I expect
Good to hear s*** like that and that's not the only time
He uses this flight of fancy
He gets into it a couple more time
I get the garage
Cast
Real winner
Doug
From the report
Refer to him as heck.
Poorly rated YouTube show
Or he pretends to know things that often interviews Coach Dave daubenmire
Doing good
Even after she
Shut yourself to Twitter's
Pac-Man on
He's given for him
Are we getting
Somebody who should also be ashamed of themselves
Enabling Alex's.
Work
I'll be on for the full show
Alex
The day after the Boston bombing
Horrible
Coast to Coast AM on for the entire show
George Noory
Everyone who works at Coast to Coast AM
Apologize
Go f*** yourself and apologize
You're complicit in there
No I don't think I would either
No
I saw a ghost then maybe they'll read listen I love you guys I love everything that you do
Apologize
For this ghost
Write this is one of the reasons and one of the things about like that show is
So fun and fanciful the fall of it
Paranormal talk
A dangerous
Place it also occupies
And it's by
Mainstreaming platforming by helping disseminate
The messages of someone like Alex Jones the day after
Rhetoric is
Counterfeit all of it as lotion
Who are prime
Any Main
His most
Compelling evidence
I want
Like he does Cox
Evoke
Like 277 bombing in Oklahoma City
Aurora shooting
What is evidence
Quotes
Good things
The past or it would require
Way too much time to get into
But I discount a lot of that
Cuz I think that
The forest for the trees
But I know that if Alex were listen to this
You be like bulshit
Here's my response back
Go fuc yourself
Sure
Even if you worked
The present Doug Hagmann
His most compelling argument
Expected to be
His most compelling
And this is what you got
Director
Kakashi argues with his dad
Marathon
Coming up to the Finish Line right before all this happen
What's his most devastating evidence is
Hearsay about Rob Deuce brother-in-law that he's
Clearly
Start of writing his own little embellishments on it
Every confirmed in any way that the brother said that he wasn't experiencing any symptoms
These nuts
He's taken down
Such horseshit nothing you have nothing
On the show
Steve doesn't help
No cuz you just get your whatever the f*** you want
You're devastated and I assume that have robbed you had been able to get ahold of his brother and there were more details
Call Allison.
Alex would have even more details
Just now like
Did I you know he wasn't always a horse
To be so many
So many times where I robbed
Brother-in-law
Evil look
I get it
Keep my name
I don't want
Any part of this
Like that
That would suck
So bad
Sisters
Husband is
Also brings up that used to be in a band with the guy who flew his plane
To the IRS building in Austin
True
So Doug heckmann said something that I think
From this episode
I think it's this mentality
Doug Hagmann
Expressing
I think it's
Bulshit
You know it with all of the accusation
I'm saying well you can't really say this is my fault
Flag attack or you can't really
Concluded
While that might be a true statement
Today
What
You know our Are We Wrong
Or little gun-shy about
About what we're seeing here with respect to to this incident
I wish I had like a air horn to yourself
Can loser cop-out I've ever heard in my life
What am I
Is shark
We built up a world Youth Day
That's all.
Disqualified
Yeah you know why
It did because this is presented as a new show
High-level sources
These two are sitting on this show different
Like
It's just one man's opinion
We do not present it that way
When they spread their s*** they have an expectation that Their audience
Responsibility
Was the government of the government
Like when you're someone like me
And you listen to hours and hours of
There's a lot of really maddening things to get Express
And this is right up there in the upper echelon
Doug Hagmann
Runs a website called Northeast intelligence Network
It's not the whisper Network
It's an intelligence Network
Reflecting the b******* notion that he's working off intelligence
I'll probably overly pissed off about this
But it's just such a
Clear moment
Yes
These people are right to criticize us for saying that it's a false flag
We do not know that
That were ejected and see how many people
The other direction
They're they're criticizing
The right to be
Because we
Look you may be right that were wrong
But you shouldn't say that we were
Thinking bad about
According to the
That don't make any sense I can't because it hurts our feelings
So I think he's got his comeuppance already
I told you earlier that Alex would say what sort of Terror
Attack
Tea Party
And listen to this f****** clip
And consider
This is the day after the boss
Listen to the way Alex is
There's no real
What the f***
Building
Oh boy
I think I think a very ungenerous but not totally unreasonable reading
Is
I wish they are we going
Crafts Direct
Your listeners to go put a bomb at the US
Love you at your ad
True right-winger for whether or not
You're a true right
Jesus
I think that bad
We don't often see eye-to-eye
I'm with you on that
High-level sources
And tells the people
Again based on my source I think it most
Important
Today for today's broadcast is
Expectmore
And look at these as diverse
And that's that's pretty frightening
As far as I'm
What should you be looking out for if that's diverting you from what
Why are you talking to you I get to pretend
High-level source
Game for everyone to play cuz there's
Like seriously crazy
Student clinic
Stop doing this to people
Hurting people
No s*** you're killing people
Alex
But if they're terrorists
They have to be mad
It's almost as if the facts don't matter
It's almost like the facts don't matter
Maybe the terrorists came from Mexico and they covered up
Exactly like the facts don't matter based on
Everything we've heard in the last
About 3 hours of the shout
I told you earlier that skousen said that Alex's caller sounds like someone make
Wingstop in Alice
Idea that there's misinformation
Being spread online
Because that's the only place
That a lot of
Stuff is getting serious
So I think
If I had to guess
I would say that this is an attempt for Alex
The claim
Authority in that space
By critiquing some of the theories that he hasn't
He will be able to elevate his own theories above the muck
I think that there's some
But either way
You choose to post on Reddit
But he's decided as a troll Pub
Is amazed
Addressing the information I never seen
I've never seen
And now he gets to reading the article
And listen to what
Happens to him as he reads this up
He's fat he starts agreeing
He starts with the troll post
Is already indicating of like this is a sort of
It's insane
You can't
It parody
It's him looking into a f****** beer and being like look at this
Jesus
So Alex
At the end this is the last clip of Alec
If you leave a half hour early. Three and a half hours
McAdoo take over for the next hours
Show
But this last clip is Alex
Indicating that he doesn't like that
People are saying that the right-wing or Islamic terrorism
Those are brought up as possible
But but other people also like
There have been a lot of indicate like
Immediately after the bombing of Saudi national was reported to have been arrested
Like he was cleared he wasn't at all
Being covered
Alex
Clearly chosen to only hear
From sources that are saying it's the right-wing or right-wing extremists or Islamic terrorists
He is ignoring
Call other
You kind of pissed off
Intertops
And and they're already
Well I mean
He's talking about the literal
Which email
A possible that there's an
Eco-terrorists
She was always property
There's some copycat attacks groups that they'd kill her people but the right way
You know they're pretty consistent
And going ahead blaming the weathermen for those
Leaving that aside
Even if the Boston bombing was anywhere near the mo of the weathermen
At the time of the group for a full 30s
3 years old
How old is Bill Ayers
Early
This would be like if there was a bombing today
And you wonder why the media isn't blaming the police
And I don't
I mean the band The Police
We broke up in 1984
And
There's nothing like a good hi-hats
Sure
Crazy
That's sad
We are all like old dogs like
Tim Allen and last ride or whatever
Ridiculous
Because I want to demonstrate to you that every wanted info
Everyone
If you are there and you're witnessing
This clear misrepresentation
What's going on
Aldi's
And you're allowing this to happen you don't walk out
I don't give a fuk
No they were just following orders
That difference is always historically been and I do not let Lee Ann McAdoo
Off the hook
That much
But she just started eclipse
Looking for enough maybe she comes in like
Half an hour later
Butcher
Are very clearly
Conspirators
They are on board with this
They're spreading the same s*** as Alex
They are just as guilty
Here's a clip of Jakari Jackson talking about
Episode of Family Guy
Cowboys
Is a participant in the Boston Marathon
In the marathon
Boston Marathon winner
How did you do it
Tampons Boston
Dial Grand
Well that heavily edited completely change all of the context
Jakari Jackson
He presents himself as a newsman
It didn't even consult the episode 20 minutes
To watch the episode itself
To see if you're spreading misinformation
Is Takeoff
And repeat it as gospel
You have every reason to either know that your s***
Hate your job
You're lying intentionally to push
A narrative
And go
Fuc yourself
Well I would like to add a third
What's the weather
Interested
So your night time again there
Here's where he gets his go fuc yourself
The day
They talked about Urban Cowboy he gets aligned and I
Episode with
Islamic terrorist
Okay so that
Did you want because
Their talking points
It's very clear because one of them is a guy
So you see that
To see the Repertory see these people who are
They are doing
They're doing
The day after a national trauma
You see these guys
And they're f****** in line
And spreading
Dangerous propaganda
And for that there is no coming back
Cross the Rubicon
As it were
Quickly as we did Even though this is
Long
Watch now?
Three and a half hours
Yeah it's up but it's dense there's a lot of material and you see what Alex is doing when you take a second
Deconstructed
Can you take a second
MC like
Okay this works.
He misrepresenting that at Allstate Center
To the same pattern
And then once established
Bjarki
Tubi
If the GOP
I turned it back on my extremist friend
Civil War
The political radicalization in
Stream
The bottom
Yeah of his agenda
Enough motivation
Beyond Richard Belzer go f*** himself
Jhacari
Sure night
Everyone Infowars
I mean to allow this s***
Don't
Wake up
Can you imagine being a new high
The day like that
Like how long has she been
Like a couple days prior
It seems like she's new
If that's your f******
It's like
I don't know what I'm going to do
There's no way that this is worth
0 weather
Remember episodes
Afterlife
Traumatic events
What day would do is take calls from people to talk about their feelings about
You know what people have experienced
Yeah that's because there's a
There's a natural health
People heal heavy breathing process
Kind of I think
Well I have some other issues with
Certainly Adam carolla's late-career
And maybe in hindsight some of that
Earlier party
I think that's such a good model
For how to be
Africa
Stewards of the public Airwaves
You know that you have a responsibility
When you have
An audience and your daily live radio show you can't take the day off
Come in and do something
You have to care and nurture
People
Because if you don't
You're disrupting a prop
At Alex's deeply disrupting the process here
And the only motivations can be nefariously political
Or nefariously personal
And I don't
Respect either of those
I honestly think like a bunch of episodes
Re-upping
I'm falling to a low of like these
These episodes of come up with
Trying to get people to move to West Virginia convention 05
Greenland
Lose track of like the villain aspect of it
Episode episode
This that there's a number of them along the way but they really
Reinforce to me like
There's intent
There is absolute
Queer
It's not an accident
He's not stupid what he's doing
Some of the stuff being done
But he's not just
Mr. Magoo fumbling around propaganda
This is direct
NYC
Do what I mean
There's a direct
He is he's a cop
Actor
And if
Sucks
It's not like a
Head of HR
Story is this
He's the guy who
And
I hate this already
And I really dread
The next like
Please show because this doesn't resolve
Well
A lot of stuff does
Does
Towards
Yep now I'm having to have a man
For the suspects
Is the sort of thing that it's Alex's perceptions of martial law
But at the same time
What else are you going to do
Like you did
The police are put into
An impossible situation but the Optics of it work really well for Alex
I just don't I don't look forward to it but we will get through it as
Pruitt
But for now
Jordan website
We do
It's knowledge fight
Ross on Twitter
Is at knowledge underscore fighting
At go to bed
You're correct
We are on Facebook
Download the show head over to I-10
Sweet love it if you left
To review as well
Yes wonderful
Anti weed be found elsewhere
Next time
I'm near
I'm late
Dzx Clark
I am the juiciest ice
Alex