Alexandra Thurston color
Sit around and drink red wine
Discuss
Proposal threadworm
Think I was looking for pitfalls
Unless Alex Jones is
Is 100% honest about everything
Even when he trips
Yes
We talked about The Life and Times about
Hey let me let me ask you
How much do you know about
So much
Isaac
Absolutely
When we go crazy when we finally do this show it's going to be
Who would want that Billerica
Speaking of the people who like to give a shout out to your friend Mike what's up Michael
Yeah that's right
Into the ranks of policy walk
Also what's this week what's up
This world has gone mad it's a mad mad mad
Mad mad world
Cuz what's up
Do my best friend in the world Nikki gift you are now policy walk my friend
I'm a policy wonk
It was the Irish do nice to meet you mr.
What a big week for us
Spectacular
Dumbass Alex
Adjust nightmare storm
I would say that Friday has been one of the worst days
If you probably ever
Thursday into Friday
There aren't
Bring up on Thursday night
The jury and his custody case
Came back
And weather
They were against two
They were not big fans
No it's
Sole custody of his children before
And the jury came back with
The decision to
Give the wife
Joint cuts
What she also has
Where the kid
Yep and they are not they're going to be living with her
And Alex only has visitation
And she gets to decide all that
So
There's more to be worked out apparently in the courts
Like the judge has
Do ghetto get the
Time and stuff like that.
But it reads
It's an owl
If it's enalapril Alex
It's not good first of many quart Elvis
Text going to be experienced Chobani lawsuit
So we're going to get into our episode 10 explained what we're going to be talking about today but
Before we go for our
Out of context of Alex Jones
It's fun
We agree
We're honest
The Rock has become sentient has worth
Boy
I keep I keep saying we're about to get into this
We have been about to get into a lot of
I'm a little hungover I got to be
So I have no idea
And this is a new thing that we're going to
The startup
You're on board
I'm not on board for that
It would be fitting
Ultra Simon Alex Jones's life for us
So just break up crazily
So
If you don't agree on at any level you become a policy
That stroke you get to you know Alex nights you over over over our Airwaves
And you were officially in the weeds
Details
Now if you donate $10 or more a month
I am going to make this offer
A bunch of old episodes of Alex Jones
Okay
And you could choose
Any date
And as long as I can find the episode
We will do an episode about someday in the past
Of your choice
The day that Trump announced his candidacy
You can just send an email
Just to tease this even more
I would like to take us back
The February 1st
Of 2016
I found it amazing clip
Valic
This is the day after the Iowa
Primary
Okay drop the first one where Trump won
17%
Everybody was like
This is a blip on the radar it's was not the
That's what the rest of the world
What was Alex
They had tanks
People with gills
Humanoids
Aeon Farms or embryos
I keep them alive
The doping
Open their eyes
Skills in there
Place where humans
Yep so that's what he was up to everyone else was talking about the Trump
Trump is not a scary the joking Alex Jones is like a pimple
Is basically living in the shadow over in
Is living in an HP Lovecraft novel
1 fish
Two fish
Redfish
Picture taking over human eye
Cookbook
Rich people
With horror
Human horror
The kind of fear that only humans
Skin experience
These fish people
Anyway
And I was really down
I started research
Can I have a pet
Okay now the answer to that is
If I have $8,000 to send
Maybe
There's not a fox
Embargo going on with Russia
You can also order from Indiana
You get a pain in your leg
Can I ask you what the point of Israelites came arrows what I'm saying is
Now I know I don't want a pet
No I want to fish
Person
Scared all the time
My play with it I feed a little fish food
I grind up freeze-dried steak
That's what I do
Lest anyone think they were making fun of something could be happening
Offended on behalf of fish
People one
I bet you know some
I did some research into this
The information you can find about fish people
Fish hybrids
All unsourced
Heather's onelink I was able to find to an article in Daily Mail
Which of the
Daily Mail
Hackers
And today I
Goddamn Murdoch's
The article that they linked to is about this guy
Who is a genetic
Scientist
He
The article was about how this guy believes that humans
Were the result of
Monkeys and pigs f******
Make sense
Actually you know what
I want to give you some more rope to hang yourself
I'm not
That's the end of your research
No no. Yeah it is
Alex Jones
An article that was about
Chimpanzees
And pigs having sex
Creating human
Evidence
Official people
Great
Okay
Were there were there
Also
Considering that whenever he was
Who's on the
The courthouse steps
Trial
Interview
After being ass like
How do you feel about
Moment On You
Just read it
One of those
Was very unhappy
About chimeras
Intellectual publication
Yeah
Here's the deal
That is the kind of stuff we can find that fish people
Stop is what we can find on any random
Just cuz sometimes
It's it's interesting that you brought up
That press
Yes
Because that's what we're going to be talking about Alex Jones
On Friday
Put out a video of one of the
Fakest looking press conferences I've ever seen in my life
There were maybe
212 reporters I would say maybe 15 from being generous it's very sparse
He gives you give the press conference that is
Ostensibly
Supposed to be about
The Cay
Just children
And all that
Erase
Chimeras a little bit everything except
Come up a little bit
I know that it is
People
They might be
Teresa
Chrissy has a tank
So
Does custody suit
Now we are
A Wyatt
Alex started talking about it
Personal life is not for us even as we discussed this
Talk about it
Raz-Kids
Satire
When you confusion tell by your voice
His personal life is no longer
Congratulations Alex you're doing this to yourself
Here is the beginning
Beginning
Alex Jones
You did it to you
Voucher
Post watch online
Put online
I need to file for divorce
Four separate times you file to take him away
System
No way is that true
Closing argument
Now
That's why
You guys
Actor
Dial Alex
A big Corporation
Is it who's it doesn't he's already way off track
Please
These things like you know
There's no there's nothing back
He's just a serving
She's not
I actually think Alex is website
He said he was going to post the documents
Posted
I even searched
What infowars.com
It specifically says powered by Google
On his divorce
To see if there's like some article
Anyting about like
Imitation
But I would like to read you a list
Of article titled come up when you search divorce
Infowars.com
The war on men
10 ways masculinity is under attack
By Paul Joseph Watson
Another article
Lee Ann McAdoo and Alex Jones respond to dating allegation
This one's from 2012 this headline
Review Michelle and Barack Obama's divorce papers
Diddy
He didn't
Another one
Nope
Another headline
Will men finally start like men again
A lot more racism is happening
Batman
This is one of the headline 420
Quote I'm considering going after the clintons marriage
Headlights
Why men are abandoning marriage
By Paul Joseph
Spoiler alert the article is
Women aren't women anymore that make sense
Men are men women are women
And then the final one of the final article that I have pulled from
The search was
Photo
Michelle more muscular than the president
What should you count trumpets tilt
Is that
Is that why they
Do muscular
Yeah so Michelle Michelle finally beat the
Fish it out of her
It must be
So he's not really he's not dealing with the he's not providing any in
Information he's just broadly a certain thing
And then not following through the trial other than
How the news media
Lies Rodgers trial
It's Sarah.
He actually kind of has the kernel of a good point there
In that they did
A lot of the reporting on the trial was
About how he ate a big bowl of chili and couldn't remember his kids teachers name like that
Clown on that
Of course people are going to make fun of that
But it didn't
A lot of reporting was not substantiated
It was more about hey look Alex Jones is a crazy person and he's being forced to testify
I'm has a point but he goes the wrong direction with that fair
Write any plays a
Massive addictive game
The kids really
Only what the left
Because we know he's
Classical
Is a libertarian
True libertarian Victor
Absolutely
Call Joseph
Who's really really afraid that masculinity is in crisis
Bingo
Baby that article should read reasons why
Scared all the time
And I didn't really cut out anything this is just
Again segmented
I think it's a fake breasts
Smells bad
It has the wrestling promos
It kind of does cuz the people who ask questions
Until the end
BNB goes off the rails a little bit but the people were asking questions
Like if I were in the Press
And I was there
I would be
I'll be going to
Pound on him
There's so many questions you could ask that would be
So hard for him to answer
I made us all very tame question
And then on top of that
Just abusing them
No one is like f*** you doing
Places really trade for that like if you go to if you and look if you're in the White House Press brief
Sean Spicer
She says a word every one of the rooms
You're f****** lying you
Editors are allowed to do that to Barack Obama
But it's not because of race
Selling a business
You know
Good
I totally agree
Defense
Of the
Throwing absolutely
Not writing
But not the voice of the oppressed
Costume shoes
Choose anyway
The next one
Alex Jones makes a statement
Are you reading
You can tell that
Because
Kind of an edible
He thought a piece of paper this is a statement
About how everyone's wrong about what
Course in this
So
Here's my basic statement that I wrote
On this whole situation
I want to respond
Somebody else wrote it for you
SWAT
Every two years ago
Withdrawal limit
Supervisor
That's Austra
Began three years ago fishery agree we should remain as joint
Conservator effectively a change of 10 miles
As only the judge will decide what amount of time with her children
That the judge will carefully consider the various schedule that have been put in place
Last two years of each of us does appropriate
German
Schedule
Regard to their own wishes
So this is the last instance of him being professional throughout the entire
Episode
The chest
You really really hit a lot of those points I don't like the way
Conservator
Minute of reading
Obfuscating like crazy is really muddying the waters because he like we have joint custody
Technically that is true
But she is
The conservator or the person who is in charge
Primary parent now
Isn't not allowed
And they can stay with him
She says he's
I'm not sure she's actually allowed to do that
Apparently
Apparently he does have to have supervision
Stuff like that which is
A complete inverse of the way it was before
Supervision before
The idea that
Doesn't seem to understand the jury either
Sequestered
Like you don't understand that they're not watching Colbert
I'm seeing these like for Trails what's going on entirely on what's in the courtroom
Rite Aid if they go in
With one situation being true
Is the main parent
Sam has the right to
Choose all these things about
Kids
Bob louder there where they live
I am at the end of the other way
That means there was something
Compelling
In that courtroom
Probably just listening to Alex Jones
Holyshit
George Soros is responsible for getting good
Quoted as saying that he smokes marijuana once a year to lay Siege how strong it's getting
More effective for you
Kids from doing drugs
The Dare program
Fear of course fear of global
Absolutely one of those
Bulshit and the other one
Isabel
Globalist
Open up Friday
That's the
That one was
Wasn't in on Friday
Probably probably
I think he recorded this video and then probably
It was really tough to figure out what was going on inside the head of
Paul Joseph Watson who's hosting
Armand Owen Shroyer
Cuz he's doing his live 325
Michelle
Both of them were sort of like
Trump
Globalist
What
Dewey do
We hate
Global
It really really texting this whole premise that they
Try to sell that is like we have no invest
Rendon Trump himself
We just like what he does
Yeah now that he is said I'm a nationalist and a globalist
This is their out this is
The way that they escaped from
From this nightmare
I don't think they want to be though cuz
There's no there's no champion
And it undercuts all of the narratives they've sold up to this point like
Remember they were saying
But those narratives
No don't they didn't they were very compelling like Alex
It was claiming
That Donald Trump was a 30-year
Secret Patriot
Sleeper Cell Patriots
Typical back in time you were f****** wrong this
Holt
He was co-opted by the powers-that-be volcano
If you think
Fish people are fine
Yeah
Why not even just start throwing out the old timers
It's true all four days might as well
At the very least as attention deficit
Yeah you listen to talk
Using like neuro-linguistic programming
And I want to do it
More in-depth
Report on about John Rappaport
Tricks you can use
That are basically
Suggestion
Subliminal
Suggesting
And if you're not paying
It sounds like a normal
She might be worms
First female president the absolute worst
Kush
Which is stronger because of George.
Wordplay
Almost
All
Could be sort of summed up by saying everyone is lying about Alex Jones
So they were going to get into that here
Cuz I was just blown away
Horsepower on me
Social workers
Alcohol drug testing
You're a wonderful dad
Put a few people Tacoma
50% of my ex-wife
I had my kids
Am I taking them
Alienator
With the literal definition of alienation
Was engaged
Yourself
All I want
Is the truth to come out on Oliver
Because
File for divorce
I didn't figure this
My children away from my ex-wife and gave them exclusively to me
I love
What the f***
WhatsApp
It's mind-boggling to suggest that
And Court
Things don't have proof
That's why Court exist
It's not a perfect system
But you can't assert things in court that you can't backup
But if you get caught doing that during contempt of court
Evidence
Thrown out you might do a night
The Pokey
Perkins
Bright
If you're rich that I wanted
To cover this even though we've been staying away from
Situation was because
Highly Illustrated
Fuct
In court
The propaganda skills that he has argued in our last episode that
You know even if he gets destroyed by Chobani it might be a good thing
You can see here he's making an argument that his audience
Will like
Yes it will appeal to them cuz they're not engaging with what
You're not the reality of what's going on
He's really good at
That he is a propagandist
Spinner
And then when he's out
Street talkin to people
He can't win in court
But you can win on the street
Do you win on a in a verbal street fight
As it were
Formal education
Not really a strong
Street smarts
As long as they're involved he's right up on
But he's also not very streets don't nobody can handle the aquarium's quite like like
He's swamped swamped with the best of them I don't know
Got to realize that he's
He's not very good at you
Using lawyers but
Next clip
Plays the victim
Really hard
Okay from a truck
Is one of the first modern trials read a corporate establishment mercenary media
Birch in the
There comes a truck but also
Who are the first trials that has corporate media adversity
Okay
Annie bratayley anytime of celebrities on trials
Third assertion for him to make and it's just him trying to
Give credibility to his victim status
Yeah
You come to truck
Accelerated the demise of the corporate media you guys Wonder
Why you have willingly assist why you don't have support just because you
Why do people
Before you do that
It's going absolutely
What is ex-wife
You are actually not using emotion
And all the experts
Hold on hold on can we
What
Is he saying
Are those words related to each other
No
You think that everybody in the media said that it was going bad for his ex-wife
And that's the only thing that they got right
I don't think so
I don't remember anybody saying things are going bad for
Oh s*** things are going real bad for Alex
For AJ
Yeah
Yeah I think the only
The only stuff that I saw that would sort of validate that is just like they're both
Open trouble
Let like it doesn't unlock don't look good for either of them
The only losers in this
Situation
And
The truck the truck made
Are any of the s*** Alex Jones
Driving home
Elizabeth's children
All of it
She is 30% off
For no reason
There are plenty
I also
He drops that there there's no reason and then earlier he had said that his wife
Wanted to divorce for no reason I mean I understand that that's what it looks like to you but you don't
Really
Care about other people in a meaningful way so you don't understand what they're going
Human emotions
Add stuff
It's tough but he makes the argument
Repeatedly throughout this that he is in fact the one who is the victim of alienation
Which is which was a central part of his ex-wife
That he was turning their kids
Against her
Yeah
Global
Sure from what I've been able to find
From
Coverage
Cheap is right
But it seems like that is
And it definitely fits his pattern of behavior
Now we don't know whole lot about her maybe she was turning them against him too I don't know
But
What's fun I was trying to find like the court documents cuz Alex
And this next clip is again going to say
Court documents
He's going to make them public you know what you know where they're talking a lot about this
Divorce Stormfront
Oh yeah
I don't know what's
It's a Nazi
Bored
What does Alex Jones ex-wife is Jewish
And there's a lot of people
There's a lot of people connect community
Who believed that she was like his Handler
And because of her
Speak out against Israel
Even though he knew that Israel was the real problem with
And the reason that they thought that
Is because globalism is toad
Wow
So
Learn about this
Sorry that it is
It's almost I'm a leaving you
It is a Billy Joel album
Yeah we're basically this
Hitler knot it called
At work
Great Alex is finally going to be able to tell the truth
But even trying to tell for years now that he's out of the situation
The bunch of the really smart other commenters jump anime like
Hey guys
Don't want to ruin your fun but his new wife is Jewish to
Alright
It's really fun when like hateful bigots are stupid
Ghetto
Tapas bar
Is the
Quickest sign to
Knowing that some
Booksmart
But it's not a thing
Mike cernovich is
Monster
He is a
Chimera of a
Amman
And
Whatever it is that
Another man
He's just a
To do to file
So I'm going to skip the nightclub where you just again repeat the
That you can get these documents
He discusses
How what's going on is
Reality is becoming
Reversed
Those are inversion of reality
And then goes on to
I am
That is very reminiscent
Obi-Wan Kenobi
Unreality
Spectacle
You got spinach
And then so it's probably okay for you to do it
You covered with something
I'm rubber
You're ugly
Would 80 + million viewers in West
In one week
Thank you all
Has only intensified
Across the world C
Bosses attempt to put me in jail if they were
The internet
I'm standing up for this country and I'll tell him the truth
Mysterious men and women
Nationalism
Awakening again
Corporate
Swept Away
Flooding into the gutters
Would you like to
To see your children Alex
Okay alright is Mom on that topic but he really wants to make the point that if you strike me down
More powerful
Yeah and I'm lying about his audience
Stressed out
There's no way
Literally no way
No
If you had 80 million people who listen to the show
You would be
Flooded with people that Prescott
The courthouse would have been beatlemania
In front of that Courthouse it would have been A Hard Day's Night
Just being chased down the street by young girls
Which I think is what he thinks goes on all the time anyway
You don't have 80 million people
You got it
Consider that
Probably half of your audience is fake
And then another like
Quarter
It's probably people like me who listen to hate you
So
You know
And there's one more guy
So
Combative
To these people who were were videotaping
He tries to
This reporter asked
If you hate
The Press so much
Why are you here
A very obvious question
The first question
Kicks office
Ring of keys
Does not answer
Is a little bit and then gif
Really f****** abusive
A lot more coming in the near future as we move forward in defense of this Republic defense of freedom and defenseman
Infowars.com take all the viewers illustrious out there
Some of them might be real
Normal
Let's Pretend Walker
And lie about me and my family.
Show
Something real people after watching
To what you said and what you question and what you did
I really get back to the abusive just want to point out that that's not trolling
No vest setting a trap kind of
The most generous
Call it is
Sure
What is
Okay okay so
So in his mind
Point of this
Is 2
Hold the media accountable
Because
Twist his words
Since his words are now on
Quote him
Then we can always go back to the tape
Can be like
See this is what I said
I said this
Say that
He's now said that he's only going to do interviews that are live
Or that are he's going to himself fully record all of them
Okay people
Can cut and paste is his words
And lying to take him out of context
We don't need to lie.
What does an episode like 40 of the show all contacts
You don't want people taking you in contacts
You kind of don't want people act
Truly listening
Right right
People aren't going to go away
He's getting he's humbled
He's not
It's going to be a
But
Little bit of
Funding
That's a dick
Dick
That was a very legitimate question
Any real questions
The very legitimate Quest
Listen to know if they are
Perhaps
Are are any of you not projector
Directions of my brain right
It's very close to salt
Very close
From the unicorn man in the back
Video chimera
There are always
Unicorn Mann
Alex did The Rock
By opening up
The Florida question
Cuz now people start asking
Quest
Response
He's very expressive and
Make sure that they
I feel welcome
5 questions for if you consider that one of them is ask
Twice cuz he doesn't answer it
If you can't hear it I'll just tell you what the question
Reporter asks
Tell your kids
Public I never called the media to come here
Call
All part of this
Pointer finger know there's the bad man there's a bad man
Corporate media lies and they go to school make her about this
They know the truth and I say why does the media say that why does the media say this and explain their not the media
Are the people that
Call Todd Jackson
We're in this country and they realized it is Parasite as little followers as at Stanford
Posing as trendy that their time is short
So
What do you tell your kids
He tells them
Set the corporate media lies they're all like know what about like
Do we get to see you more often
Girl Little Vampire
Are you still going to pick up
Score
The meaning of lying to you you know the truth
53% off
The phone
The drink your bone broth
And go the f***
Too bad but the question is what do you tell them about the
Current situation
To their mom's house and s*** like that
And he's like
Obviously this question is back
Where are you tell them
Totally right
Course
And there's everyone's out to get me
Of course
Good that's the truth Alex
Have you ever told you
That you are not
Hey listen up I want to tell you guys about
How many
So
So are we going to live with Mom now you know this yogurt maker
Guys Pizza
So like
Are you going to bring your mom or I always tell my kids to feel their hands
You're going to take a bath or it's time to fill your head
Are you even talking to us anymore
I realize I could consciously there got off on a Hyundai hulakai arant
If you came into my life
Beer in my mind
And that is because the next question
Is about
Chobani lawsuit
Jesus pay more lawsuits coming at you after the Chobani
Lawyers
Nope
Corporate strategy
New York Federal Reserve
Board member of
No he's not part of those things
Your lawyers
I think you are going out to things that aren't real I think he is involved with Alexa
School lunch stuff
New York Federal Reserve
That
I don't
I don't think he's talked to lawyers
I think he's making that up
I think that he's just being blustery
I don't really
Because I can't imagine a lawyer
Talking to about it
Is Ambien like
Look into whether this is
Is true or not act like it is
No lawyer would you
Disbarred
Let's let's not say no
Sure sure
Let's say if you're a friend of Alex Jones
Likes
You might be giving him bad advice because you also don't believe it real
Mike cernovich is a lawyer's that's possible that the two of them have had conversations
I talked to my lawyer
Solid case
Yeah which
How can you be a lawyer
Although although that is a really good question
So how can you be
You're right
The answer.
Like what do you do when you see the lawyers in court defending the
The travel ban and all that
It's so bleak
To tell that you shouldn't be doing
So those lawyers are doing it just for the money
Best go
If you're Alex Jones
Lawyer
You are not going to
You tell him
Hey this is bad for you
Because
That's a good point going to tell him is whatever it is he needs
So he will continue writing those checks
At this point is almost a dream
Client
So much work
So much Billings
Hours of it
I can't imagine like
You don't even know
He's just going to talk
Woods
Just be it okay if we go to court
About this
You don't say
S***
Ankle
You shut your mouth
Going to get that lawyer
Court is going
Lulu's crazy yarn
That is not true at all he's going to reference Breitbart articles
Yeah
Isn't it going to be a delight
Yeah if that is why
Take a week off
Pastor watch
Oh my God that would be a good fast
That would be amazing
Broadcast live
I don't think they would allow us to do
In the courtroom
Reporters like it a basketball game play-by-play
Horse fall on that one
Did not answer the question
Answer back to this
He has more to say
Cuz I was Ludacris
He's got going in a monopolistic
Boston Herald
Lawsuit
About the report at the computer cabinet
Yogurt
No trick the owner
To purchase for refugees to be brought in
With George Soros and George Soros
Owner of it himself
Other people's report
What happens if when we get attacked
The liquor ship and support just goes up exponentially
Support
Yeah we get home
Everybody loves
Bummed out
Discovery on shabonee
What
Yep
Yep we're looking forward into learning about
Chobani
That we're also going to
Defeat turkey
Do you think that he's upset about the Kurds
Because of like the pasteurization process of time
Well do you know it
What's up
Globalist globalism
Hamdi ulukaya as giving a lot of money
To the
Curds and Curtis
Call Isabel
Because all that they're murder
Kind of smart
It like do a countersuit
Because as I said
If you going in for the defamation lawsuit
He can't introduce all this crazy show
Is outside
The scope of the
In order to
Marriott down with you
Turkey
Soros
All this s***
Right not in the
Being brought against
So that's like I said
It's called
Yes
Could you could lose that case to put
But if he gets
Absolutely
Questioning this cell
You don't even have to work because you know the case is over like
You right up
Like you write up
Bad book report
Basically Joe
Ambiano what if you are that lawyer
If you are that checks out
Cares
Now the Alex
To be honest
Time now
It's got to be excited
Mr Smith Goes to Washington boner all up in arms
For it for like
20 years baby
Look at it
He's so slippery
That making predictions about him is very difficult
But it feels like we've entered the third Act
Okay
What we
When we started this podcast
In January
Four months ago unfortunately
He's a hateful dude we're just going to document tube and make fun of him
Yeah we got it right on the decline
This is going to turn into
This f****** guy is
He's ruining his own career
Assume
Does it end well
I think I think it ends okay
Just Wynn
Everybody
Beauty and the Beast
Stride that's what we're dealing with we're dealing with one of the other Hamlet turns into Gaston
Blob
Jojo
Anyway
Like
It's just like I understand
Question was about to Bonnie
And what have you
You could have just
Working on that but you know what we're here to talk about today
Little children
But that's the opposite
What time is it in Boston gal
Any any
Possible subject is not lost
This trial
You have to claim that he didn't
Anyway
I wouldn't be shocked if
Somehow he tries
Make it so that in the
They also have to give him custody
They're trying
Take my
That's not globalist
Single Jew
Who happens to be his ex-wife
Stormfront really full of a lot of really intelligent critique
I hate that place anyway next question is back
Question that comes in and there
The status of
The custody is
It's like what is
The situation
Between
You going to get to have the kids on weekends or what
The Beatles and you'll see how well
Regarding
So what was he
Exact
Decision of
The judge
Alex
Decision of the judge
A different question
What's the
Exact
Right right
He's not a
Text wife it's hot
Soul and supervised visits
Okay
And so because that happened
I was always just trying to get
Horst 2005
Arizona
Big Lots
I would argue that's a real lab
The social
Are you on here if you're really cool.
Set an alarm called you a narcissist
At all
Perceived
The past
Situation
Since their divorce
It wasn't 2005
And I think
Dimetrodon
Yeah but listen
His is understanding
Suspect
He would have had to have those other kids with her after they were divorced
You know like
As we've already
He is not willing to give the benefit of the doubt
Let's say
Maxine Waters or Nancy Pelosi when they have a slip of the tongue
It's only fair
Living on
These female
I think he would be able to
Is that we would definitely dance around
This planet is flat
Staples
Grounds
First one
She was in Rome for a while and then
The third one and then we live on one of them
As I prefer to call it.
You might have noticed
Reporter whose little rebuttal and w
Give another shot
Where we at
With where
The judge
By the way
That's Cody
Otherwise
Bart
I'm seeing his kids ever again
The judge was correct in this for what he is referring to is that
She refused to let anything
Any political
Contact because you didn't want to bias the tree against
There was a video
Right right
I mean we are still in Texas
Let's truth but it's
Liberal Austin
Occupy
A video that the
Tried to
Emperor in
Video of him and his son throwing darts
Hillary Clinton's face on a dartboard
And she was trying to demonstrate
This is like
But you didn't
Who played because
If someone was a Hillary supporter
They would unfavorably bias them
And if you were anti-hillary it would
Wrecked I think that's right but that's what he saying
Also like a lot of his other videos where he's drunk
Talkingshit like that
They didn't she didn't let them play
Really
Extent of them
That
We might think of
That's what he's trying to say
Answering the question
Going to not answer
For another man
On what does jury do
She is still exactly
Show all the
Telephone
I just wanted to give Mom some more time
4/4
Social worker
She called Dad Robertson have any children
Because
What's natto job is worth
Not sure about my ex-wife
Situations
You
Little girl
Play the football future
Can probably recite
What he's about to say
Verbatim
I'm not going to cut me out saying this here
He says that every single time that this Colbert thing
Brought up
I'm not
It says I'm at
Sort of
A retrospective introspective whatever he says
They're going to cut out anything
It's just a bit
Adam Carolla ranting about
Left turns
You're just doing your doing bad material
Alex
Quartermaster
Also that doesn't answer anything
He answered at the beginning
But he's lying
Rap God
So she's the main
Conservator
They're doing everything to deny the ruling
Right
Maybe this is maybe this is
Beyond
We haven't
He's acting like this is a loss
No
I really
Where and he's doing everything possible to avoid talking about oh I get it I get what you mean he's acting like it's a loss because
Cuz he's acting like it's not a lot meme
But you probably going to come out and say it's great the trumps global
Is this
No probably not
I think it's a big win
I don't want
Seem like
Understand
Somebody with MRSA
I don't think you
It doesn't seem like it's from his words
Could be partially like you might be in tonight
If it's possible they really does care but he
Really actually believes that the
The verdict wasn't against
What could possibly justify all this
Based on what we know of him and
The exploration we've done over the last month
I think it's far more likely
That his
Is being really flat about the kids
And him skipping off into Aunt globalist topic
Video
It indicates to me that you're right I don't think he cares
And I was going to save money on that he's going to have a narrative they took my children away
Any has way less responsibility
Maybe
Only now that he can't see him
His kids whenever he wants
Will he actually
Music
Tears in Heaven
Now that he can't see his kids
Now it seems like
Even harder
I think he would fight even harder in the court of public opinion but I don't think he would fight Nightcore
Because again as we discussed earlier
Can't win in court generally only women propaganda
So you will act like he's really trying hard to get it I'm fighting cuz I love my family
That's when in reality is not doing s*** today
God damn it if you don't tell him
No I think
All the way
Can you take a cup
Set precedent a propagandist
Find one more question this block of qna
And this person
How often he will get his kid
Question is very relevant
What's the matter at hand
How often have
Bow Down
Reside with
Is that discharge
Pictures of horse.
Christina the truth
What does it have to do with your kids
As long as
What
Little hanging fruit with 45 million listeners
He's talking about consigning Assange to he said if you got more stuff give it to me
Also you didn't say that he said that you Russia
Donald Trump
Mlife
Russia to provide those emails
Not Julian Assange
Which means
Stupid
It doesn't know
The difference
Or
Because he's friends with Rodger Stone
He does know
The WikiLeaks
Is
Affront
So if one of those two things either you're stupid
Or you have access to information
That we all
Very clearly suspect
You just said he's all but 100%
Slip-on
But I think you did I think that's possible
That wasn't
Sing Julian Assange instead of Russia
He's talking about Trump
Yeah well he got well I mean all of this
Nonsensical and magical
What is
Is that a slip or what is or is not
Something that he believed
Who knows what nonsense lies in the throats of a man
I don't know
Thank you
Swift
Real poetic as well
Declares himself a libertarian
Good
This goes out
That's not good
You're going to see what he brings up a sort of evidence of his
Libertarian
Right and that would be
His
Nope nope that's not going to do with this
Libertarian
Human animal chimera
Funeral for body parts
That's wonderful news report
Yep
12.15.9
Funny because people are followers and it makes them feel powerful
Cuz they one way or another
Dangerous
He's creating
Allergies are way up
20 years ago they had a rhesus monkey
Glow-in-the-dark
Monkey is medical experiments gets funny
Itsfunneh
It's something good the last
It's fun it is very fun
Dude you got to prove these things
Like
It just doesn't work
To just say
I mean
Spider goats is a real thing
Spider silk
Introduced as well and they have they have
Combined
Jellyfish
DNA
Glowing or glowing tobacco
Plants that can glow and silver
Pretty interesting
In a lot of ways
When you're trying to bridge that into
Fish people who have terrified human faces
And stuff like that
You got to do your work
You gotta prove it
You can't just have an unnamed
Source
I told you about this it's not that doesn't fly
People make fun of
Cuz this s*** is not real
And your clown
Why are you talkin about
What why are we talkin about chimeras right now cuz he's a libertarian
Libertarian
I didn't cut it like makes that make sense
It's just I'm a Libertarian oh that reminds me I meant
Realized
Take my fish people
I'm starting to realize that I think he probably talks about chimeras way more than I realized
February 1st
He's talked about it three times
So
Concerned
Well there is one actually Internet America
No but there's one interesting thing I kind of
Think I mean
I don't I don't believe that what he's saying is happening
But if it were happening
One thing that is like
What he brings up is the idea of
Different diseases being in
Introduced through that like
We could get like
Animal diseases
That we could then become susceptible to
Or we could just
Create diseases
I'm not even sure if that's
Possible
But be that as it may
The idea that
Supper some medical
Lost because of it
Alright
I'm listening to that
You got to prove that it's going on first
Yeah but
You know that seems like an endlessly complicated
Smallpox
That's a fair point
We need to get Chimera so we can get disease
Accidentally
Like
Mansion play God diseases that he's talking about
Diseases
You're right there's way more things
Worry about
Chimeras
Which
Debbie
Kind of cool I'm all in on science
What's what's the f
Vixen clothing
F*** it let's calm s*** I don't know we'll find out later I don't know you can't really know us something really wrong until YouTube
I know we shouldn't test
Cosmetics on animal
Sure
Cuz that's a bummer
Very much so
I've never seen the human-animal hybrid before
How do I know it's bad
Documentaries
Why not
You know what here's the thing you were going off on that I started to realize what it is that makes Alex Jones very off
Waffle in court
And it's because there's a burden of proof
He can't
Proofing
Service fish people with terrifying
If you were to try and make that claim in court he can't prove it
So
He's f*****
On the street it doesn't need approval
He just needs to
To assert thing
I hate him
Anyway
In this next
Flip
I cut that part out cuz it's just them Milling around and it goes on for like 2
It's just just some dude
Some like bailiff
Not even
We just need to have room so people can get through that salt
And so they they Shuffle about and then Alex
Alex gets his lawyer to come over and see if you were
Which is about advise
Randall will. My great lawyers named family love up here in Texas is never seen try like this is 30 something year
State of the Union
The family Union
I want to give a little bit of a warning
Randall Wilhite
Uncle Mike's
This is very low
Absolutely
So it so what I thought I heard him give
A boilerplate lawyer
Call Keepin On
Very general broad results
The Galaxy Center
Already
Yeah and that it was
And that was that
Flipped out of the back of his head
F****** much already
Then goes on to say a little bit more
And I think
I think this is one of the first indications that this dude might not be a very great lawyer
The only state in the United States
Did you catch that
Visit the Texas is the only state
As far as I know
You should know
Seems pretty
Specialty is family law
But who cares
You should know
State of the Union
Because he is
I mean
For you
Don't put my business on the street Alex I just lost your f****** case
Shipt
Still charging you by the word
It is by the word
You and I
Control again
And one of the people asked how his kids doing
The great question
Theoretically well we're living in this world
This is not going to go great actually even answer
Or if he's going to end up talking about
The destruction of the United States
Or you didn't do that that
There was so much going on in the trial where
There's a lot of stuff where there wasn't
Play the net
That's what happens when your
Yes we all remember when John Quincy Adams that is
Kids taken away around the founding of the United States
That's what happened
Detective
Yeah you know that's why they call them
The founding
Alienated fathers
Exactly the sounding fathers who have
Poop like a
So like
That that's what happens when you try and be cool
Right
Not at all
Llorona
To blame for this
North Korea Venezuela
Control orders
Competition
Are there prayers to come over here and
What is what you say he throws away the toys and he does this
Chaos
Call Joseph
Mainstream media so discredited
That the more that is degree
But in little
You don't desiderio the followers like you're in Austin Texas pretty clear that the
Iago government loving corporate worship system
Herbal system still has still has tentacles go growing and doing well and so
We're just here for your listeners
Great
Tonight the kids on the weekend
I look forward to hearing how you distort this
For like the thing is so f***** up is it
Possibly do
I don't know play it
In context
Scotto's
Distort that's why I love that
Key piece that came out that was just the unedited transcript of the interview with Trump
Cuz it's like it's so much worse than article
What else is there to say
Frustrating since 9/11
With
Clearly degenerative mental illness
So I also this thing is super awesome
Does Alex
As we go along we just friends
These behaviors that he does
Adolescent behavior is the
When he's like
Surprised
It's the exact same thing he did when he was like
What's a Chobani
All right Muslims have never heard anybody ever have never shot anybody
It's all you're doing is
You know that the argument against you is bad
And you can't
Engage with it so you just
Trying
Overblown
Pretend
Like that's what the first
Actually is
And your
In trouble
Very much true
Trouble
So
That guy walking by
Wednesday
Some s***
And
We're going to
Have the introduction of a new character
Rainbow
No
This is not an intentional character
Okay
Here is here's my pitch
Alex
Has rainbow snatch
Or whatever face Millie Weaver
His daughter and
That's not I think you would be into that
Stickman situation
So
No that's not the character
I'll f***
It to the press conference
Yep
You suck
Become Alex Jones
Keeping control of the situation
So crazy
I want to pull up this cuz he they
The only coverage on infowars.com of this whole thing
Was
An article about this homeless
But it's like an in-depth article or anything like that
I got to pull it up here
I want a quote it
Appropriate
All right so the headline is
Trolls media attacking Alex Jones
That is their takeoff
As if the homeless man is like
Look you can see that
That's the guy
You shirtless
The PSV probably
A rough life
I would assume
It's a very
I got to step up for my man Alex
People listen to Listen to Infowars
That's just a true fact the only connection on have that I think
You probably believe there
That's my only that's the only connection
If he gets them
So that doesn't really
I'm not sure but I wanted to introduce him
Is a force
In the end
The story
Just about like a really
Etsy just abusing
Tell him.
All perception
Jurisdiction
Play play semantical
Call Mike
Whizzer on again
That's exactly what you're doing
But also
Atrocious because he's made this
Exact statement
30 million
It's
40 *
I know you said we weren't going to talk about it anymore but I left it in here Forest
Specific reason
But he doesn't want to go.
MD reporters start actually
Questions
Falls apart
Him introducing this idea of a
Play characters blah blah blah
That thing is actually important
Night for the laugh everybody Federal White
The fiction you guys come up with how you quit this is the second
Sugar Steel the image of rooster and goes upside down so
Will continue being serious issues
There you you hear a female voice there right
Leads to this
Next question
But it is important to point out that
People
I have being awful and you know you don't realize that the only reason you hate us is because we're Trailblazer at
Anxiety
Sleep
Dum Dum Dums
I have an interview
We're making history.
Speaks to the
It's not fully clear what the lady is asking
When is
This is a serious situation like
Why are you using satire
When things are so serious
Basically
No one wrote that headline about who
Whenever you started putting
Goldman Sachs
People in
He was Betty tried to make the argument that like
He needs Goblin guides
Right you know he's like if he's going to get through the goblin territory
Use
Local
As it were
What is metaphor
I have no one wrote an article that
Thought they were literal Goblin
That stroller
Doing is not parole
Stoic
Gyros
This is the man who will see where this goes
Lose
There's another person
In the crowd
But isn't this is fully off the rails
If you're watching the video of the homeless guy is
Alex has her like
But this is kind of stupid
Yeah they can
Course
Because you
Is not appropriate at least it's a dumb question
Better formed a better form version the question is
You're really bad at satire
So why are you doing
If that's not a question
What is foundational
You're really bad it's at
If you're still fat such a serious situation you're going to
Would be better for version of the question
But
Again it is important
Because what it leads to
Homeless guy
Dylan play
Dress up like
Yeah this is not my favorite thing
It's worth it just like it took like
Half an hour of the press conference to get to this but now we're here at thank God
Every time you heard
That
The other day
That's the homeless man
I'm sorry the train or not
Butts
Detritus and the press conference
Again there
And here is why the question was important
Because there's a follow-up this person
Asking specific things
This satire
Nope
Peter answer is good
So the first one
At all
Just left
The first one is regarding
Alex Jones is Obama's children might not be
That sort of thing
Imaginarium
Qdoba
Who is the lady that was Joan Rivers
Rivers jokes
Medical
Experience she was going through
Then I should look Joan Rivers said she's a tranny
The meaning of Inception
Obama was
It was clearly a joke
What happened
Don't use that language Alex that's
Stupid and bigoted
He's lying
A hundred percent
It's very easy to find clips
Of him reporting
On Michelle Obama being a
Secretly a man
We've got over
Astro
Michael Obama
Sometimes
And I mean if you wants to say it's joking fine but that means that the way he
Joke
Serious sounding news reports
And if that's his argument
That's worse
Let him just being like we got that one
It's way worse
Yak
Is that opens up
Literally everything he's ever said
If you watch the coverage of
The
God now all I want
Next
During every Infowars
Infowars
The derby
That would be amazing
If you guys want to hear a full breakdown of that eclipse and everything is on our February 24th
Episode
We played
About Michelle Obama
You're busted
Pretty wack
Somebody's at the door
I got it
Oh no
I like to add a little more depth
Also at the end of that last clip there was another voice
That was like
Was Sandy Hook satire
Somatic
Another question
Is going to lie about what
That's a joke
On the air
I know you were talking about
November
No I don't know I clarify.
Something totally accurate
Create that story clarify
You lying Alex you lying about
You were not playing Devil's Advocate
You literally said there were no children killed
Synthetic event
Swiss cheese right there
I never even lying further about what you did in the
Every situation with
I mean
You lie and say that you didn't
Claimed that there was
Abuse going on at Thomas
Pinkfong witch
Sarah videos
Deleted from the internet but people still have
Betternet
Turn those really hard
Lying about what your apology
She was your cowardice trying to dajjal
F*** you
Very very sad
Wandering Inn
The Masters bummer if you didn't
He was a decent person
Horrifying
Like this is just really
This is just him
Struggling so hard to get out of
All of these
Traps that
He's locked himself
Yeah
He's just
The word for today
Some of it other than other than wind Chobani really murders
Chobani can get like what
10 million dollars from or something like that
Call Guy want them
I don't know what side of the situation
He's not done anything that specifically like
A felony
Call spell matters
Everybody's
Well even though you use you saw it on the storm front
People are already trying to make up
Reasons that now he can
Get away with all kind
Signs of others
Pooping off of his
Because of the incredibly fun intersection of like anti-semitism
Misogyny
Yes culture
I mean power due to
Find hubs on the internet
All roads lead to Rome
Miss Kay's on Fortune
Zen Massage
Cool I love it
What you're saying is exactly right
The people on that Stormfront website
Another like biggest
Message board
Does having the exact same conversation
Edit
It is if they're making excuses for him like
Their problem is
He's not calling out Israel
Yeah
Light
Right but instead of making that his fault
They make it his ex-wife
Asphalt
Because she's Jewish
It's insane
You have to go through
You're contortionist
Intellectually
But that
That's
It's like this is such a real bummer mainly because
If there is there was going to
Possibility that you
All of the
All of the right-wing
Like all of the Fox News
If there was any chance
Mr. reach them
Then you would see like that
Beginnings of it here
People would finally go like
I'm going to stop list
Or I'm going to
Nobody
Nobody who loves Bill O'Reilly
Is changing their mind
It's like this is something that you
You have to be able to do if you
Of this world
Falling apart look at it from their perspective
O'Reilly and he's obviously
Obviously
And his argument
The truth is going to come out and it'll shock you
Yeah
But he
He's being lied about an event
Now we can Flash Forward a few years and no truth that is like
Because that argument is enough
In the same way that Alex is here being like
Lock the Chargers got a rule on stuff in the specifics might be like a month or whatever
Brett
Flash-forward a month people will be talking about the chobani's or whatever the next thing is
His narrative
It'll never have to deal with like no one will even remember that he lied to them about that
F****** very frustrating
Very frustrating
But I guess we did choose to do this
Set Sonos
Yeah yeah
We we fall into our trap of Our Own
A grade
We proved ourselves
I just
Small subset
Wait
He is
Volumental
It really does
Because if you've been a fan of Alex Jones for
15 years
All the sudden you finally have
Have to come to that
Spot where you go
I have been lied to by this
This map
What else
Was he not telling me
The truth about
Spoiler alert
Everything
Like the moment you get there
The moment that happened
It tips
One way or the other
Well
We're going down like a
Interesting long-ass here but the reason the most
Can't do that
Especially
Do you found Alex Jones when you are
Young
Where you were
An angry impression
Cannibal obviously white person
White male
YouTube
There's a lot of things that he says help you
Make sense of the world and why you're not as
Successful if you want
And there is a utility to the wise
4 people
Understanding the world in
In the confusion
We talked about this all the time
Off mic
Barbie ideas like people having to make sense of randomness
Yeah you come up with whatever
Explanation
You come up with
The random chance of life
No it's
Obviously
Does it work
EXO
Once you have that
Mind virus
In your brain
Getting rid of it
Create
Vacuum creates a gap where now the world doesn't make
And that's really scary for me
So I think a lot of time even though the crutch
Is actually hurting
So there was this guy back in Columbia Missouri
Come into the liquor store my brother worked at all the time
Is it the younger guy
If you like 40 or so
And he always in a wheelchair
The story came to learn over the course of time
Was that cute kind of
As I recall he was a scam artist kind of trying to get disability stuff
James O'Keefe
He was going around in a wheelchair
For really long time
Because he stayed
His muscles actor
It got to the point where he needed to be in the wheelchair
Exactly and so he wasn't himself into a wheelchair by scamming a wheelchair
So Alex Jones listeners intellectual wheelchair
You don't need to be in a wheelchair
So they think it's easier to go through life with that wheelchair rolling around then it is to walk
Right
Realize you do this too long you won't be able to get out of it
You won't you just
You'll never give up that wheelchair metaphorically
You'll stay in it
Great f****** metaphor thank you
You just crossed it out within the context
That should give a press conference
Anyway
I mean you know you stand up for long enough and you
Microphones for a long time and kind of used to putting connections together also if you're not a f****** idiot
About you but
Alex
Fish-people Jones
Alex Jones
Two more Clips laugh
Unless
The camera kept rolling
Excellent
I need to William F Buckley
I need to do some research into this is I understand
It's Alex Jones
The Stepbrother
Or something like that
Brother-in-law
He's a guy who's like a behind-the-scenes bigwig at Infowars
Okay the cameraman
The two of them go into the courthouse
And I can
Confirmed now
That the room with all the books
Is inside the courthouse
Allowed him to
I don't know
Cuz they're doing it on an iPhone on OneDrive book not but
I mean
I saw the answer is they did not ask
Cuz if they had asked I would almost guarantee they're like
No
We can't report cuz we don't know but
8 Ball
There's two clips
One of them
Is Alex
The jury's decision
And kind of
Body being really murky
You about it but this first one is about
Contacts if you will possibly
Who's first one is about therapist
But
Describe this is a fever
Mike
So bizarre like when I was listening to it I thought I'm not well
I thought something was going on like
You pulling in some
He's
Awesome metaphor
Exact opposite
Crazy like I really thought
I drank way too much
I got to quit drinking
I feel that way when I listen to Alex all the time
I'll do it
Lawyers
Missouri lotto Allison Wilcox
Famous lady that lived the longest pregnant on a boat
Averhealth
So that's the first instance of like I don't know what he's talking about
The longest on a boat
Pregnant
Fiat
I don't know
Live longest on a boat
Google cuz I don't care I want that to live in my
Confusion
But like right now
I don't even want to know that she has
I just want him to be like
My psychiatrist was the lady who live longest
Great song
Translate
Literally no bearing on skills and professional
Probably negative
Also like
Okay so she lived the longest pregnant on the boat
The capsized
That is a plot for a movie
Blue Crush
It's true I've seen into the Blues
Guardians of the Galaxy
About the pregnant lady on a boat
Also
Still need to go see
The fate of the Furious
Still haven't seen it
Pissed off about
If I didn't want to go to bed
9 tonight 100%
Anyway
That is sort of the first
Extensive like
I think I'm losing
It goes on
You too late
And that's when the issues start
Amazon stock price
Let's go
2017 watch few months ago
And what the jury just rule.
Conservator rental see my kids
She filed gravity in Spanish
Sr4u
We'll make the joint and we'll send the primary residences with mother
Please implying there that the jury's ruling was based
And pity
Which is
Unconscionable
You should not
Leaving earlier he said that she went to a tree
Facility in Arizona
Mexico
Which is very cruel
Here he's saying that he underwent like the
The drug
Pregnant boat lady I guess
And then the problem started because she needed to go to it
And because he doesn't get into it
The audience
Obviously goes to
Or she was pregnant on the boat
She didn't break the record
Right
Honey
I told you we are we are an exceptional family
Mainstream media is lying about the other lady
Totally boss
Okay
Because we didn't put all this on we were just like mister nice leading the whole thing
High Road
14 psychologist
Press conference
Alison Roman
I think I'm hallucinating
It could be fishing
Said that had to set up about National alien
That's from Independence
I don't I don't know what
I don't know because he's not making a coherent point he thinks it somehow is
Proving that
She's wrong but
I can't understand how
Because
So convoluted
Disease
How to evaluate
Was reporting multiple times that Alex
Was going to
But did you see any of that
People covering it that there were like it looks like
He's going to
Because it is
A big deal
Conservator
Make these kids move
To a house that they
Leaving for the last key
Right
It's not massive on the scale of like you can't see this person
Never again
But it is not a decision that made light
No it's ruining the lives
Children
And people
Let's really pull the curtain back on the side
You're uprooting the live
White children
Ozon under the under the
Sort of the rug as it were with
People who are minorities in poor disenfranchised population
This is a celebrity's kids
Who's Richard
So they would not
I think most of the reporting it was like he's probably going to win
We're in acknowledgement of like
I got to prove a case that they're going to change
And fact
There's absolutely
But also Alex
Alex also debunks his whole entire press conference through screaming at the media bias
Do all these media reports are saying I was going to win
The great when they agree with me they're bad when they disagree with me that's the that's the board that's a Baseline
Truth vs fake
Truth vs
Chirp
Degreed with me
You're telling me
Replacement
Your fake news
It's that simple
Bill O'Reilly's to have pinheads and Patriots
No I don't
Where every week
And
Patriot
Also do you remember Sean Hannity
However
People would call in
Your great American
I miss that so much you are trustworthy
Is dependent upon how
Trustworthy you think I recognized the Great American in me and Ergo YouTube
I don't like Alex people being on hold for a long time ago
I wish I lived in that small
How easy is that
I don't know man just start doing it
We could start being like that all these people donating to a patreon
Starbucks
Clearly satire oh did you put your mask on
A boy
Yeah put away this next clip is a Alex
Reading the series
The verdict
As it were
Don't remember why
We'll see
Children's
He does not
Any of those words
Some is
Start this from the beginning
It read
Exactly what he says it doesn't
And I remember now why this
Because
He's going to claim that this
Isn't the jury
Decision
But this is just what she wanted
Circumstances of children
Facts about a quarter and it goes on
Conservator
Get that
Possession Order possession
Visitation until
Witnesses
Yeah
When you want to discuss
The case and you claim you have documents
Portent to the case
Mnu
Do your press conference where you real on the media
And then
You go into the private room in the courthouse
And you have a couple of documents and you don't really engaged
And then
Your website doesn't even have those documents you don't
But you do publish the story of
You're not really
It might indicate the blah blah blah is kind of all you've got nothing he doesn't have anything
No
Reason
He doesn't have a case
He's not a good guy
Doesn't seem like it
I wouldn't want to be
Buckley seems to enjoy it
I wouldn't want
Be raised in a cult environment
As someone who was raised in a cult Environ
Closing statement
Is ex-wife
Closing statement Alex Jones is
Personally a cult leader to you someone
Behaves like that
It's obvious
It's so obvious to the point word
Best to trickle down to
His personal life
If you agree with him
You're good
If I'm a good guy
There's no way I'm going to
People that he has on his show on his phone
But when you're raising kids
That's the other thing
Imagine imagine you take
Even the slightest modicum of that
Good trust is you believe me
Globalist
Does you disbelieve
Anytime that child disagrees with
That is then
Exact
Every liar every
Vitamix
Pressure
To never say anything
Sing the Dozen
Agree with him
Just make it to
Whatever it is
He says is what you believe
Has to be so into
Horse
He's a cult leader in the
And you're going to be denying your own sort of
Existence your own reality in order to Boulder
You're just a you're just a planet to his
Is solar
I want to make it even further clear that like I'm a hundred percent and I agree with
His ex-wife
You're not a cult leader why do you have
Cult leaders on your show regularly why do you have Stefan molyneux on
You know what
As defense
But he's not a call
Al
Don't hang out with it
Nobody
You're right
Hey you should check out this cold over here
If you're ambivalent
Add stuff for people to not eggs
Is it like not have people in their life who dis
Agree with his
Weird libertarian ideas
So you should cut people out of your life they don't agree with you
The process called
Booing
Ridiculous B look into that s*** it's so insane
Cut off all ties with
There's actual website about people who have had to rebuild their lives
Because they were destroyed by
Saxofon molyneux
Philosophies
It's really crazy
He's a frequent
Gavin McInnes
Created the proud boys
Which is
Essentially
Lately homo-erotic fraternity of dudes
Into the idea of white males
Being in charge of every
Light
Mike cernovich is a lispy lawyer
I don't know
I'm not certain he has a cold but you know these are the sort of people who he have on his show
Tendencies
Tends to
Track light
You don't
Generally have people who are like
Fuk fuk
I just
Makes me really mad
Somebody should fight against
Baby I know it
Flight to remember
But I'll show it's fun
Yes it is
Checkout.com
Drive to us on
ITunes
Leave a nice little
If you become a policy
Ewok if you likes
We are not called leaders in
Who respect the decision of Sedona
If you are our children
You're smart
Wanted to donate $10 a month or more you cannot assign a date in history for
Appreciate it
Forgot
We should
We should let people
Will know that
When they become
Come a lot like us
MPR rarefied air
Me too
Alexandra Thurston color