I have great respect for knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Monica
Stripe.com
No we need to do
Do perfect 30
Question
Air Jordan
What are we doing alright
But
Have you ever been
2A
You know the kind where you walk through and there is a
Like the
No. No no
Shows up in your mother's would never take me to one of those things
After I was of the age where I might go by myself
Don't think I would have chose
Christian extremist haunted houses
I've been to monster truck rally
I've been
Missouri
You just like to go to places where is easier to draw
Right up there in the middle of Mexico Missouri
Actually it was one of the craziest
Group of friends
Friends
People
Country music list
But I did work at a subway for a little while ago
And I used to go to a karaoke bar
Pretty regularly
Peppers
There was a guy who would go there named La mate
I was also quite country songs
Strokin great version of it
So I have these friends
Acquaintances
Good friend
Give me some contacts
Call me baby boy
Which I never knew how to take the monster truck rally with somebody's
Hey now we're just out there drinking and I run into who's out there for the monster truck rally
You know that
Later
There's like a weird Revenge of the Nerds situation where you got your friends
Romeo and Juliet
But there was no tension or anything like that
How many people do you know it was amazing
It's all really good Anna monster truck rally was
It was alright
After a while
Cars running into each other until they all stop
Will be really interesting
It's not on TV
Classic I've gotten way too high and watch those
There
Even then
Count
Like my my intellect
Buy almond
How many hours is
Alright I'm not a bad guy but if you're there for the whole time
There's some question I can kind of understand especially like
Understand the entertainment value of the cars are really functional
Other
I guess he got a stick
Stick with it
I don't know but I respect everybody in their entertainment Dorothy
The car is near
Demolition derby
Today is we're going to be going into the present day
Sorry
Pictures Sunday and Monday this week we're going to see real upsetting
We might have had a president of our country
Tweet about Civil War baby a little too on brand for Alex
I will see how he responds to that before
Just people have signed up and are supporting the show
First of all
Sorry
Joan
I'm a policy wonk Juan John's
Next
Journal policy wonk
Elizabeth
Text Greg
Craigslist
Skylar
Very much so first of all packaging Inc
And also Patrick
You so much
I'm a policy wonk
Heroin
Is freakishly large
Patrick
In some ways
First bolts pathogen
Pink ink
I should tell the good people out there cuz there's people.
It's been a little bit delayed
The show tattoo will be gotten
Donation for little while
But that is all completed
Quite frankly
Surprise
You son of a b Elite the fact from repairing will be good for him
Auburn and Patrick I sent the message
You would like to challenge at
I to go through this episode
Without me
Okay you are not allowed to say I don't understand
Sarcastic
Do that
Try out that
It works out
I make no promises
So are the 29th and 30th
From Today Show
No
Right
So it's already on the 29th
Episode
I thought was
Going to be a bat
On the 29th
Begins
With a little bit of motivation
I didn't know how it was going to manifest
I wanted first heard it I thought busy
Populist
Collision Course
Be in the streets
How do I go to bed
Alexa
It's a rare day that Alex has a plan
Yeah that made me worried first of all
Only okay when it's coming from the Doobie Brothers
And then third of all
Straight sides
And then they aggressive
We got to get a grill
What I heard
Is Alex going to f****** jump
Is he making
Is he making that rhetorical
Is this the day that week
Claire War
I wasn't sure it's
See where the
Repercussions
He's also teasing
Tower on the program
What have you
Avant
Is in the early stages
Really Ali
The I've got solution
Bad news
Jesus out to keep eyes
Program
About how much you love
But there's things that he wishes Trump would do better on
We've got to get
Tipping the Lyft app
Be like his chief complaint is like Trump hasn't got me back on Twitter yet
It seems to be that's what's up
His cross
Deplatforming
Stuff they use Experian
Has led to A disruption of the inflow of people
It's critically hurt his ability to make money on his Apple
About Alex
New people
Stefan molyneux really like
Lay that out if you like this is why I don't have new people coming in
People are leaving
I do
Not have done that
Entire episode about that video
Pointless
Voicemail
Makes me want
Support and allow these people to
To game their algorithms in order to get more attention on their b*******
This is this is pretty
I mean you see a pretty good case
That this does work
It works well
Milo particularly like they have
You know they've been very public about how much
Kidworks interns
Disrupting their ability to
Exedra
Crowder
Or whatever
Crowder of the show louder with Crowder
Louder with Crowder
DC radically started his career aspiring to do, but he's also the power
Right-wing media
Shortcuts to popularity
From 2000 to 2012 he has a number of small roles within various projects
He did a voice on the cartoon Arthur
He played pretty kid in the 2,000
Flix movie The Covenant
Okay
Duchovny movie The Secret
Where I
Takes over his daughter's body
In between a father and daughter
Wow I've never heard of that one
Crowder's
Weirdo
For landing any roles at all
Justin kicking down on MTV play classroom
But an actor was Dead on Arrival
Is over the course of twelve years you aren't really able to get any juice any momentum going
Cut out to act
Steven probably realized that was the case because in 2000
Water being a low-level funk
He was an MC if the 2011 presumably because use one of the only people they could fight
Idol performing
To give you a reminder
Part of the problem
Here's a list of some of the speakers at CPAC
Michele Bachmann
Amazing okay Foster
Billionaire donors
Alright
Paul Ryan of a couple days
Workshop sonship
Pamela Geller
Stephen Baldwin
It's way in 2011
Silly
Videos on Fox News
Particularly distasteful report that he filed
In December 2012 Michigan right-to-work rally
Where he was mixing it up with a bunch of Union protest
A lot of the window dressing for his reports and all this stuff is really unimportant
The Chase
Steven ended up getting punched by one of the Union
At least started parade video around right-wing media making appearances on
Fox News
This clearly demonstrated protesters are violent
Completely negative light
An ineffective demonize the cause that they were out there protesting
Pick 4
Credit-challenged
Becoming a new Shining
Star
Even showing which showed him being sucker-punched manipulative lie edited
Diversion
The guy has been attacked because the camera is focused on the right spot
This wasn't an unprovoked attack
I guess Crowder hits
Along with all the right-wing
Erection in the Cure
No they did a whole 24-hour news cycle on house
Well maybe someone did Imagine maybe someone was
After this Steak Rolls like classroom Bowie anymore
He started it louder with Crowder in 2015
Quite successfully
By making you contact incredibly stupid but also stopped
Trojan Horse conservative
The concept of super attractive
Which is really the place that he lives in in the park
The only reason he's a worthwhile commodity to the right and why is part of Glenn Beck's Network The Blaze now
He makes
Videos
With their unformed
Brainscratch
What is an adult it's embarrassing
Nickelodeon a wholesaler for conservatives ideas
Flight over the years is guest
Noted over and Benjamin
It is YouTube videos sometimes Benjamin will take a break from blaming Jews for everything that happens in the world to accuse Crowder of being
Being gay possibly with his assistant.
That's kind of the level of humor were talking about here
Throwback podcast website
Surprised to find out that the
Can post in that sex
Can on his website entitled quote
Moderate Islam is a myth here's why
Pretty early on he starts to have the soda guest
Natural connection
Propaganda
People like James O'Keefe
Paul Joseph Watson
Sargon of akkad who appeared on the show originally as an expert gamergate
Sometimes
Knocked out a lotto
Not a lot of good
Dave Rubin Lauren Southern
Tommy Robinson
Dinesh D'Souza
Stefan molyneux
Blaire White
Benjamin
This is a show that's Taylor towards the youth
Who's a crime
You're enabling a psychopath to pray on your audio
It's not like Stephon was on just once
All those people that I named we're regular gas
Who appeared
Multiple times
Along the way the heavens over over the top
He also had access to people who are supposed to be legitimate politicians
Pokemon is guess
People like Governor Mike Huckabee
Rand Paul
There's a reason that this brand-new politician would still go on a program
Is littered with extreme
Outright cult leader
Holocaust
Steven Crowder is useful to them
Husband
If you lied about that union guy punch
Along the way crowd has made a name for himself by posting up on college campuses
Only two genders
Insisting students
You that guy
F*** you never really tried to pull off a stunt like this with adults
Referring to just befuddled
Along with batteries famous for
Do you even talk
Who has been trying to get them to
Except
Talking about with it supposed to
He's learned
There's a post screenshots
Seemed to imply that his channel is being shadowbanned
Some dumb s***
He posted that if you search for him or someone else
In League with
Show you any of their videos
Videos from other chat Channel
And this is a conspiracy
Filtered
Video option
Selected
Their baby's father complaints
The crowd was Raising but I don't really
Care all that much
Is careers and reliable source for just about anything
And this there blocking my content
It's such a Content constant
Fraudulent refrain
For these right-wing Cottman
So I don't really want to take too much time up
Sort out
Get to the bottom of any of this
I really just got this clip so I can talk about Crowder's guest list
Taqueria
He gets employees under the radar a little bit but
Episodes of
Dangerous
F*****-up ideas
But I've watched a little bit of it and I'm like
First of all he's trying to be funny
It's a what is that
Witches
Right but it also has a penny worth
I don't want to necessarily take up a bunch of our time
Humor Redwood
Extreme ideas behind
Do you like walking through molasses
Trying to be like
Painfully stupid like it almost
Is
Like it would feel like doing
Critical review of
For children
And I just don't I don't know how to
Weirdo
And he doesn't eat should get a pass
Actively
Promoting stuff
Stefan molyneux
I will literally fight her
I am fine with it in this one case
I want
So what episode
Continues through
Is that easy
You might have noticed about out of context drop by Piedmont Satan
Alex
Deeply
Into accusing his enemies
Consciously in League with the Devil
He gets into that talks about how we're both offered
Huge careers if they pray to the devil
It's hot
It's not just him
Years ago
Crossroads
See you at the crossroads
Still out here doing this song so you know you're still on tour
I do but I don't take it for granted
Wow it goes back to the Destiny saying how many
Target
Long time gone
Holding up my hand
Jabari
Thicket where
I am now
Should I ask who you made the bargain with
Commander
The chief commander
Okay Alex compound
Alex plays about God
He doesn't have to be the devil
Of course he's talking about
When it comes to Alex and his interpretation another Dylan quote comes to me
Sometimes it's not enough to know what's
Don't mean
Literal deal with a literal devil to get where he got invite
There's a common metaphor to describe having to make sacrifices
Give up things in life and pursuit of your overriding
The deal with the devil Dylan got to become one of the most important songwriters
Possibly in American history
She could never live a normal life
For an artist wife is never really normal
On the path to success
Their focus has to be so squarely on their crap that they don't
Parts of life that everyone else does
Beacon live in poverty so they can dedicate
Tons of times what they're called to do
They keep completely different hours than people with normal jobs
Essentially around everyone but apart
And then if they're lucky enough to sit
Become a famous musician
Their life will never be normal after that
From then on never really be sure of anyone in their life values them for themselves or for who they are
In the world
Social interactions becomes
Distorted and whatever alienation they felt before is an impoverished nocturnal performer is only elevated
The gold
Shooting for
I don't know
Doesn't stop performing or making music because
He's keeping up with his end of the bargain
Expressing that he made a deal with his own town
He committed to be the music this musician to the exclusion of other human comfort that he swore he would never
Stop creating and he's not going to stop now
Just because he's old rich and famous
This is embarrassing satanic Panic level s*** that Alex is doing
He's basically pretty much every famous person every celebrity
Appear to be doing good social work now that ship matter
By definition
He's just everything that is
Involved his version of right-wing extremism
Even think that
Is intrinsically evil and a threat to his body
It's sad on one level
Anywhere to go in the future other than viola
Everyone who doesn't agree with you don't b******* is being literal Satan worshipers want to take
Kids and kill them
I put you in a slave camp
Is there a is there some point
With that sort of group
Seems like it has to lead towards escalation
You know I think Alex
Probably have to be aware of that
What people are willing
Satan worshiping the child killers
Like we were you going to negotiate with them
Ghetto after
Opening
I don't know
Making a deal with the Devil is
It is
Born almost
Entirely out of
I was just talking about like Robert
Conversation absolutely Dylan's comment
Or I guess a literal devil is for making music
Because I was a condition of a deal they made to get The Times They Are A-Changin on the radio
But
You know you got to make a literal deal with a literal devil
Newton Federal
Didn't sign up with the Devil the bill was paid
He was I women
I don't know
This is all bunch of bulshit
Gives a s***
It's because this is a clear editorial.
It's all it's so much State there's a lot of things
Yes
Like I know Alex talked about Satan and all this stuff a bit
8/8 over the top
And very consistent throughout the 29th
And 30th
This is just rambling b******* about God
That's what this is all about
But if you really love God
Little fake priest
Powerful
You know
Understand
Brakes
Okay
M8 exhaust
Like weird weird over the top
Religious
Naked making this political struggle in the middle of
Somehow have breakfast
Spiritual apocalyptic Armageddon
If you only do if your gear in people opted for an expectation of violence
Just I really can't look at it any other way
I can only
What is it
Technology
People don't
Devilry
That person is doing
I don't know why I'm going to go with
And that's just the way that they are you f******
Can shut down any any
Kind of openness
Is that
It's also something that does not have
Like possible Avenue
When
Georgia killing dogs
Being recruited by Satanist
We don't know that he hasn't
Situation
Who's the bad guy
To think that a good guy
We are actually good
Because Alex himself
Is the Satanist
Occam's razor
Extremely engaged
And
Because
Make sure that it's
Record
The
Everything
And releases it as a special report
He can't even be bothered
You cut something like during or after the show
TVs look to record it
I need to focus real hard so we can make use of it
Let me get to the positive note
To the big news here
Massachusetts
You are
No
If you as an audience
That's right Alex stretch
Actually got 3 hours to fill stretch
Tell me what it is
Go for it
I need to be laser-focused
Cuz I know that all these rabbits
Like the devil
So at this point it's all vague and all just so we got to be
Aggressive
There's no sense of what he's talking about it could be like
It could be protesting
Or it could be go firebomb globalist Church
Between Maybe
It's obviously not the ladder
But you don't know like I don't know what his
It may be very uncomfortable
Could be
Not telling us what it is other than we got to take to the streets
Nea he's like
I don't get butterflies
Tried to pick up a hot chick
But why
About 5 minutes ago
Watching television
Powerful
Drum roll
Ice cream ice cream
Stopped traffic because I returned with by sensationalism
Who is in the second segment of the next
Telling you all about how important today
Made me really unnerved that he's talking about how he has butterflies and
About reporting this
For suggesting this
It made me worried that like it is going to be something
Like Beyond
Acceptable
I don't think I don't want to be like this
Reveal of what his suggestion is
As if to imply that is like
You got to understand why if you're listening to this
You're like a little bit like
This could be anything he's going to add the engine
His listeners do
And then what he says something like this it makes it even more like
Are you going
What is that then
That's what he said right
Stop
Listen here and my response
Condescendingly isao
Jesus Christ
The model of those man
So his solution is yellow conspiracy. Okay
Sensei
And her and have a list
And there's a list that Alex is going to put out of all his points so you can just overwhelmed people with a flood
Is verbal diarrhea today
Great you guys you guys want this is amazing
It legitimately just go Yelp
Wow
Inner
Participate
This is such stupid
Zoe I also go to
He has further suggest
Reaction
Contest
To go yell at Bill Clinton and Hillary Clinton
The problem here
He doesn't realize that
Thousands of dollars
To get people to go troll those rallies
So I don't know
If it's going to work out
Whatever
Besides
And then also be like that
Realized
Great America
So I think Alex just learned about
ProTech
Not realize that was an option
Go outside
It's weird
Alex is still Alice
So he has to make like
Caveat
That are like
I think they're important
But for now he has to make like a real disclaimer
I think it's a
Facebook
Couple hundred bucks on
Find airplane to get your infowars.com
Daenerys
Legal and lawful
The trend
Don't commit crimes
Because I know my audience
That's an assumption that I do you guys want
Very hyper-specific about
What you suggested his audience might want to do back in 20
You're not watching mad out at the end
She's like by the way all of the stuff I told you please respond to that note legal in Bothell
Going to think
I should go commit a crime
You're basically career talking about doing
Alex like I said earlier
It existed because there was
He was paying people to get on the news in
Bill Clinton's a rapist
And even he recognizes that like
Kodi problems
Repeat
You need to work faster
We got Trump elected
A good way to finish
Thousand dollars for the
You got last time
People were motivated by that
Also I don't like that you had $300,000 for that the first
He was way more flush
Just done like a regular old
Campaign
What 20 G
Not as effective is Buzz Marketing cuz those people who are at those rallies most people don't know that Infowars is
Paying them to do that appears to be organic
Grassroots people who are yelling at Bill Clinton
In reality it's people who are AstroTurf being
Pay by Alex
So it's it's a really
It's manipulative it's very
Insidious the way that that's able to penetrate local news and news source
Who aren't aware of what's actually going on
I think it Alex values that much
More than like say
This is paid for by
Towards
The message
Shows just Special Report
90 minutes.
The streets to fight back
I literally have no doubt that he left his show and got his ass out there it's a meaningful direct action
Either that or he met with suppliers about the billions lawsuit
He's mixed up in currently
Either way it's a real sad State of Affairs over Infowars
You have a guy who's yelling all day about how does the pivotal point in America in human history
I am right now
It's good versus evil on the future existence of mankind is on the line
To finish his own show
It's little things like that that really provide a true Glimpse at the house and see all of his ranting
If you really believed a word of what he saying he would finish his show
He doesn't need to finish the show though because he said all he needs to say
He did some extremist ranting he did some ad reads
Plus he's finally discovered protest
Exist so that's a big
Anybody who is he
Sincerely in the position
Wood wild horses couldn't drag
Their post
Just like anybody who actually likes me
You betcha
So we get to the 30th
Monday
And Alex doesn't want to read the news
It's kind of weird that space
There's a lot of stuff going on
And warning
This clip includes
Probably the longest pause Alex's ever made your iPod or phone is not glitching
Very long
Just becomes part of the
Brown noise
The paws
President-trump
Couple days ago on Saturday that
Alex is very excited about that
Those pauses are outrageous
So he is now found Trump is talking civil war
Also other people are talking civil war like Rush Limbaugh was talking about at the cold Civil War
I give Alex
The utmost credit and by that I mean discredit people are sounding like
It's a Hallmark of
His
Rhetoric
2015 that like
We are in a state of Civil War
It's all under the service
Is very much penetrating
People who are supposedly
F****** president
Realized
They can't realize that there's nowhere to escalate from
Right
What you can't go higher
Civil War problem
Death-squad
That's the problem we're going to have to wrestle with
September 30th
Because
Expression are when the going gets weird
The Going's getting weird Rush Limbaugh's turning pro
In terms of getting on board with this
Escalation is rhetoric that Alex Jones
Employed
At the same time
Alex now has to figure out what
He does with that
When the rest of the world is doing your extreme is b*******
What do you do
Episode
I'm going to try
That would be great
I think you I think that actually would be wonderful
I don't go overboard and I don't want to get too out of control and say
Calling for any
Was actually calling for a civil war
President a little bit about what Alex is actually saying
Alex
In order to build up to make
Sort of Art
This Force
All eras of the show they're demonized
Flix movie
Call Jay
Stories right here
No
Funded
Have you heard of this
First first things first
Michael C Hall is legitimately the only person in that I've ever heard
Also this movie
Wait Michael C Hall Dexter
Okay alright
B a b movie
According to the director I couldn't find funding
Set the movie studios in too weird for a big-budget outfit
Also the movie
Quite being adored in the way that Alex seems to be pretending it is
The a.v. club headline for the review the movie
Rodger Ebert's website
Most reviews I've read said the plot is a little convoluted time travel
Okay
It's not about squirrels trying to kill Patriots
I know that's probably what it feels like the movie is about
Not
It's one time traveler
As opposed to multiple
Suggest
And she's not traveling back in time to kill Patriot
Killing people who are specifically part of vinegar
Extremist white nationalist militia
You're using words
Exactly
She's killing that because they're instrumental in carrying out a job
Also that bomb doesn't happen in 2020 to 2024
But who cares about is just trying to make it look like this is about
Whatever
On the surface it would appear that has no idea
But if you know how I operate
What's up
Alex is so averse to white people ever being portrayed as being incapable of terror attack
The winner fictionalized white nationalist group does a bombing in a movie
He has to whitewash
Just good upstanding Patriots
The reality behind this is Alex deep down and probably not so deep
Was that the Rocky Mountain rendezvous
Along with Aryan Nation
Planet tons of extremist
Militia figure
He knows that most of his anti-communist Heroes came out of the failed presidential campaign is segregationist George Wallace
Which also spawned William Luther Pierce
The Turner Diaries
And the National Alliance
He knows his heroes in the John Birch Society where stash
He knows that his primary source on Bilderberg work for a publication that denied the Holocaust
Which is Ron B Neo-Nazi Willis carto
Alex knows exactly
And you know damn well
He's going to stop making money
If he gets on here it says he's mad that flick movie
That's what he wants
To say because he doesn't think they're bad
But he can't
So he calls the Patriots fighting globalism
I resist calling is a Rosetta Stone
It does that all the time
But I do think that if you understand what's going on question the broader application of is used
I'll go ahead and leave
As soon as they just Russian question
For the class
And how he hides it
Behind
Facade
I'm positive that you have a lot of movie reviews
Ethan Hawke
Before Sunrise
She's like a woman
And then became a Time Loop
Kills himself
Weird
Or it's not I don't remember
Kutcher movie where you at
Movie that is about someone traveling back in time in order to avert a terrorist
To provoke a civil war movie about someone coming back
To kill conservatives and Patriots
In order to stop them
From fighting global
It's very very clear what he's doing
Yeah I know so
I'm imagining
If they bomb a movie
Weather
Actually doing
Fighting
Because they are on
I mean if the only reason they would
If the globalist had already busy
What you would say but it doesn't matter
Yeah I don't think it matters in terms of rhetorical
So anyway
Make that up
The shadow of the Moon
PetSmart
I was just making this up I could tell you that without looking into it
In reality the movie was produced
The partnership between
42 automatic
Nightshade
The privately-held company meeting the Chinese government does not own it
Yeah it's based in London
Press release in deadline
All the partners in the company or list
They are Ben Pugh
Catholic
Hey Josh Varney
Obviously fake the well-known industry
Absolutely
And that's just probably
You think his death affect his death to turn the public against big tobacco
Automatic is run by three guys who used to work at creative artists agency
Can see who decided to do their own
There's literally no indication that they're even part-owned by the Chinese government
Seems like just a
Production outfit
Nightshade Studios of closes Alex is going to get
We still way off
Mission statement introduced independent movies including
Asia
But there's literally no indication they're even partially owned by the Chinese government
None of this matters
Alec has zero idea who even produces movie he doesn't know about 42 automatic or nightshade
It doesn't matter because the reality is not important
He's built up a narrative
The Chinese government owns Noble Patriots of America
And that narrative has to move forward
It's so crucial to protect a narrative that Alex is willing to take a movie about stopping white nationalist terrorist group
And make it into a book
About the
Make it look like the Chinese government
That are about killing
Do I had to leave
Exhaust
It would be
I know this goes bad
Respect for his lip
He doesn't hate hesitate for a second and saying this movie was produced by the Chinese government
Knowing it doesn't matter
Whoever is listening still at this point is going to believe him
It's a real bummer to stop back and think about the poor people that are cotton
So let's not
Text movie talks about some other movies
Police movies only shows
Weather
The Purge is a long series of movies that are just about
Laws being
I don't know if I want to
Engage with that but let's talk about that
Inequality
Let's talk about the hunt though
Does most ridiculous thing for Alex
Never got released
Because of right-wing backlash
Trump decrying the movie which I should point out he had not seen
That's really f***** up on his entirely accurate
Some reports I've seen claim that
Attempts to get conflated with the right-wing backlight really easily
For sure what caused it
It's not come out but either way the right-wingers
Definitely try
To get it not really
Annette pathetic
Because the movie is really just a retelling of the story The Most Dangerous Game
I remember
I'm fine with this movie
Whatever
It's
Just a rich evil people hunt humans
Supersport
The John Leguizamo movie
Movies
Most notably surviving
Richard Belzer associate
Associate
Americans called deplorables by their captors in the movie The Hunt
Are kidnapped
Heroes of the movie people who you see the movie through you experience their story
The audience apathy
It's literally their Story of Survival
Follow
The film was produced by blumhouse
Studio company that made Jordan peele's movie get out
Hughes said
Confront white liberals with their own country
He told variety quotes
You find a DMC
Hideous qualities that white liberals have
The gut-punch of the movie is ultimately meant to say that racism is a human problem
Call themselves
It's a pretty fair assumption
To think that might be
In the film like the hunt
Where the audience is faced with
Dehumanizing attitudes many liberals May hold towards rural
Conservative
Younger days
From literally everything I can tell that's what this movie was about
But because
Right-wing media
Completely out of control stupid insensitive
They were to receive engage with satire that's meant to bring people together and encourages liberals to explore their unexamined bias
Think it's crazy to me complete disconnect with
Reactionary and stupid
No other way to put it on the billionaires
Come to the conservative
Billionaires
Completely
Destroyed any
10th Ave
Reality they have
The billionaires
And one
Percent of America
That's pretty
Pretty amazing
Defeated reality
In some corners
But I don't think it's all 47
Wizard
And I think
Vape transcended
Yeah
Okay
Alex also one of his go away after a day
What is his name
Preemptive damage control
Cuz he needs to
Did anything happen
Is a setup
Lower the comes out and says something
Obviously
That's a plan
Trump sexual assault
Inoculate them
Come to the idea that they're going to be
I'm f***** up things
What's going to happen
Million
I want to shoot more stars
Closet
Diversion
Congress
He's essentially saying that he
And a lot of his weirdo militia friends
Things Fall Apart
There's no doubt by his right-wing Buddies
I mean
Great
I mean whatever it turns completely f***** up on a radio show
Because it kind of encourages his audience
Globalist
School teacher who
Teaches you are 9 year old and they're pushing
They're pushing UNESCO education in order to children
Probably fluoride
Lexington phlorizin the food
It's it's Triple A
Can't be saved
Even even if you're creating the pretense of like
Preparing people to act
In such a way
It goes against whatever
Disclaimer
Saying
That the president sang
If this happens there will be
Or intimidation
Purely neutral as
Stating a fact Peters do
Faribault Civil War
Yeah I think Alex is a mob.
Coming back
A sharp Focus
This is where I think
We get
Be a pretty clear picture of why even if Alex Jones hides behind all this like
I don't want violence all this stuff all of his words
Like it does not matter because
The larger worldview that he is
Perpetuating
Necessitate
And you'll see that in this clip
Tech
Call Civil War
Top it off
Memes are wishes for that
Stop all this
But
Hold on
He said butt
Understand the clock is running out on them
To be defeated
Squid
That's unacceptable
I really think that everybody needs
To carefully
Considerate
Exactly what he's
Whatever the f***
Is a civil war scale is a ludicrous trivialization
Serious topics
But I'm going to leave that aside for a sec
What's important is that
Escalated very severely
One more notch
That's the shooting War starting
Bubbling over
Heroes of water shooting War he says
He wants the Salt Plate what a relief
Alex wants to resolving peacefully
And then he says but
That but is his whole career
That but is the map that uses to cover up his extreme
Gleanings
He pretends to advocate for non-violent Solutions
But
After that but he clearly explains that there's no chance
Of non-violent solution
Because the globalist to take the Patriots
Heather not go down without a fight
Around these parts were giving Alex Jones benefit of the doubt
When everyone was complaining about his battle rifles, I was clear that I thought he was stupid you wasn't at
Dating Violence
Necessarily
Who's more f***** up to kill people in self-defense
Super common for him
High Point these things out but I generally don't they
These crossed some sort of larger line
I think that last clip is crossing a line
He's telling izadi
Civil War and there's literally no hope of any kind of peaceful solution
If you're listening to s*** like this and you believed him
Why you going to wait for the globalist squid to take your children to the bottom of the ocean
If you believe Alex business
The declaration of war is inevitable
No matter how many times he pretends he doesn't want violent when you portray the supposed enemy of being a rampaging squid
Unless you kill it
You're advocating violence against that squid
Alex is probably totally find legally at least according to rulings like Brandenburg versus Ohio
Punish people for abstract calls for illegal act
But I'm less concerned with the legal side of it
I'm bored still moral and ethical
What Alex is doing is turning the temperature up on his rhetoric
Troubling
When Trump is referring to a possible Civil War
People like Rush Limbaugh or following that
Supposedly mainstream right-wing media has nowhere to go
He has no reason to exist
Past the horizon
I want the horizon
Discussing a cold Civil War that means Alex needs to talk about
Hot one
This rhetoric is particularly unnerving on the heels of Sunday's episode where u r a l
That wasn't the solution to all Global's meddling on Sunday with gogal conspiracy theories at them
And here on Monday he's talking about civil war with Millions dead being inevitable
This kind of disjointed message
Escalation
Although it doesn't make it more likely that someone listening will be convinced that the war is coming to why the f*** should I wait
That does not happen
But if it does
Be very
Very aware
Did Alex did everything in his power to make that outcome more likely
That is all he's doing
And like I said I don't know I don't think it's illegal and I don't think
Think he has any punishment that's coming
For it but don't
He knows
But he's playing with fire
He's playing with
A gullible audience
That's willing to believe clear misrepresentation said he make about literally
Just about everything
He's
The inevitability
Is so
Like you talked about that all the
Feature
Of his rhetoric
The idea that whatever
All that stuff's all good and well
We now have the president tweeting about Civil War
The climate in the world
Is
So insanely
Touchy
For Alex to ramble his b******* and say like
We got to take out the globalists there's no way they're going down without a fight
In
Times when like William B.
Be
When he's out of Step
With larger Force
When he's
Just being
Crazy and extreme
It doesn't strike me as merely a danger
Climate
Political climate where
These things are being bandied about by
People who
You enter a tear
You enter a territory where you have
A real serious
Isaac Issac ate it feels very different to me
I think
8in this in endometrium
Explain my thoughts
None of his listeners
Fargo
Just started
Probably not
There.
Probably out
Very outside of big big population areas
50 +
Disengage
Makeup
Mastiff
Even ask
Terrorism
Face around the idea that there
There's going to be a
The thing about
He is going
Kill people
He's going to get
Especially because now there's so much Civil War
Right
Or could
I would say
More fair to say
Not that Alex is going to get
Increase the likelihood of that
Because I don't I don't want to draw a direct
Causal relationship
This escalation is
People sucking killed
They all are
I don't know what more I don't know what more to say
To frame it that way more precise to say
That the way their characterizing thing
And the way this
Is being discussed
Especially Alex Jones
Like what it does
Is raise the Tanner
It increases the temperature and makes those shorts
More like
And if you express it as
They're killing people
I just
I disagree with the framing
Only from a purely
Sandpoint
I don't know I just think you can't bathe
Exit it
Corrosive
It doesn't lead to anything other than
Whether it's
Increasing the likelihood of something terrible now or later
That's all it does
Like what you going to do in
Six months be like wow we've reached an agreement with the globalist
There's no way back
Kick it home from
This is the place where you're gone
And it's not like that's going
To attract
Nuvue
It's not like
It's not like you're Jumping Frog drop
You're probably already with me
Radicalized
There's no point of this that leads to
Takes you anywhere other than
Whether it's the destruction of your everybody
Davis
Mihail Evel stores
One of my favorite classic blunders
Come on
The Limited
Because there's
Hello
I love Construction
Frederick Douglass
Slavery
Institution
Fought the last
Civil War to uphold
So cool
God
That those very
People who enslaved
Attributed to
What's the temperature in L closer and closer to another civil war
CNN
Did women start the end of the Civil War
So
Again to reiterate Alex is expressing that there is no hope
Of this being resolved
They want to fight
How to be successful
I think you're smart to play that
Music
Lake Blackshear water
A very clear articulation that I won't stop until
You're advocating
I don't I don't understand like pure
Reasoning standpoint
If for them
Their only motivation and all of our Patriot heads on the wall
The obvious conclusion that you're driving people towards
Is
They must be crushed
They wanna be crushed
And you must do it before they
Exactly
So
Because
The answer to that
Yes
You can make
I mean obviously
Play Alex
You can't win
How is it look like
You can make a deal with the worst human beings on the f******
Planet
Live
Not sure sure
It's right you know. That's also kind of problem
Because what happened
Over the course of history
Is the evil grows
Another Wars
After Wars people get back to goodness and God
In order to normalize the idea of we're going to have to go through this then on the other side it's going to be Gray
Tragedy
Horror that would come from people fighting
Bra
Change the world
So
He's a student of History
He says what the f*** was he talking about
These in the middle of facilitate a second after the last one
The devastating Reconstruction Era
Normal everything was fine
Equal rights
With the gift of hindsight that's not a. I would call coming back to God and trying to make the world a better place
Americans really suffered a lot at the former Confederates were treated with policy of
Look at that differently than I do
What's considered
After World War 1 was the creation of the League of Nations and ever World War
Those organizations at least attempt
Make the world better
Human annihilation
Alex however sees them as globalist plots
2 take away is gone
This doesn't quite work for what he say
Looking over the history of Wars I don't think that his argument makes sense
But it kind of feels right
But like everything that comes out of a turbo
Nations in the UN words
Come closer to God
Yeah I'm not sure exactly entire world
Biggest Wars in history have not lied to coming back to God
To destroy the world
Yeah I don't f****** know what he's talking about
I think he's talking s*** people
Towards a f****** Civil War
That's bad
Really about
How a
To be real tough
If it like one side would
Probably
And then everybody else
I don't know
That radicalizing people to the point where they would
Commit
Is is
Possible
Getting appearance is what's going to happen
But
The construction of
What you would call a civil war
Is
More likely than the South and the North
Terrorist
Insurgency of like a million people
I get the rest of America
In order for it to fly
The paint all of his enemies
Which he's been working on
Previous day
It's a very major piece
This move
He needs to make sure
That you understand
Everyone
Who you hate
They're all willing participants with
And so you take a shot of Jack Dorsey
Who sold their soul
This tweet from 2006
From Twitter
Good pasta
No way beautiful
He's not talking
No
You dumb f***
Shoulder soul
So you already understand what's going on here
The Satanic Verses
The 1988 novel by Salman Rushdie
Title of that book is an allusion to a group of divinely-inspired
I said to Muhammad by Pagan goddess
But the word
Particularly interesting
Circle
And that's because it was already subject to intense scrutiny
Since Jack's the good pasta
And of course that's code for killing children
Bulshit on this going back to November 26th
But I think it's funny is that Alex is trying to reintroduce this
And use it to call Jackie child killings
But also protect
Because of course in the present-day Alex is trying to pretend
This is the kind of skills Alex's bring to the table
Pretending that a very famous novel that got a fatwa declared on Salman Rushdie
Even if you haven't read it videos not rushed
You can't be
These feelings of real concern about the escalation
Violence
Incompetence as a propaganda
Is anyone listening to the show Google The Satanic Verses immediately see that I was either lying
Or he has no idea what he's talking about yet he's making it a big part of the information needs
Disseminating
Alex is doing
But I also see how easy it would be to get out of his trap
You know if you were trapped
Because of skill
So completely deteriorated
And I really sincerely hope that people are able to see their way back to reality
Because
This is this is
Taking the form of
Like a really destructive
These are ramping up of the
It's not good
I don't
Man if that if you
Start a civil war
And your guy is
Is the guy who is
Telling you that
You actually
Morlock
Semblance of
Of intellect whatsoever
It's Jess
Intellect
Destructive
Into like there but there's also like people who have had emotional
Now you places
I think people could Escape those bonds a little bit
Appear so stupid gullibility
Some people have or vulnerability
To this sort of attack
But Alex's
Is carrying out on me
Which plane is more the intellect is overwritten
Yeah and I'll brief you on that
Are you
We're just normal
Humans we are mere mortals flash bags
Obviously we did make a deal with the Devil
We don't have the gift
It's someone like an hour
Learned that he's psychic
Yes and you talked a little bit more about
Empathic
Person
Motionless energy
That makes this worse
As
Everyone has
Particular Touch Too Much
The Shining
Energy level on the planet right now
Explosive
This is a hundred percent real
They're going to try to assassinate the president
Years ago he and Rodger
Stone said the Trump
Diet Coke
Sedative addictive or something
You and so they could be right.
Is the same stuff he's been saying for 3 years now
Knew about this
I guess
Maybe is more my point with how irresponsible this stuff is
When the world is in
State of Affairs
Not a hot Civil War
Lehigh
The same sort of things that Alex does all the time take on
Completely different look
They become so irresponsible
In other times like a gopher
But Wednesday
I don't know it just
You can't
Take this out of the context of the
It makes what would normally just be like ignorable in like a Goku
Keep I keep rambling Alex
Intuit
You could get someone to do something bad is this kind of talk
Yeah that is the guitar strings are very very very tight
Yeah I guess that's a good way to put it I mean like it's destroying the super tight normal strumming could break it where as normal strumming is
You can put up with that in normal time
Unless it's at a house party
Whatever
But
Realize about
The ADL
He says that they really love
FIFA
There's a page on the adl.org entitled
It's kind of a description
Used to describe a collection of individual groups
What's also not all positive
Their presence of the protesters and
Dissuade race
But the use of violent measures by against their adversaries create a vicious self-defeating
Jackson blame
This is why most established
The argument the article goes on quote all forms of violence are problematic
Additionally
Just another Raven
Extremist and can't be used for recruiting
This is what you might call a middle-of-the-road
Anyone who opposes for automatically
Or what have you
What else
The urge to make moral equivalence
Even if you think their violence is not great
Quote
That's said it's important to reject
Attempts to climb equivalent
Right-wing extremists have been one of the largest and most consistent source of
Domestic Terror incidents in the United States
They've murdered hundreds of people in this country over the last 10 years alone
Related murder
This is not a document that celebrating antifa as much as it is recognized
The jewels are responding to a real problem
But the ATL doesn't like some of the meat
Good witch they're doing
Alex's make grape is at ATL added some new entries to their database of hate
Reflecting that certain things had been adopted by far-right extremists
To the way to signal to each other
The bowl cut
An okay sign list as was the use of
Images
The bowl cut
Yeah cuz it was dylann roof
They're getting bowl cut
Apparently
If I had to guess the reason that they added this images to their list
To circulate images about them are far-right extremists
Video argues that these images generally the antifa logo of two flags
It's just an updating of the white supremacist iconography that was used against sharps
The group of anti-racist
Nothing about that says but if you don't like answering so you're a Nazi or anything like that
All they're saying is that right
Extremists and whites
Message
I don't think that's a debatable point
They're definitely doing that
Using one of them
Start
For example they list a hundred percent
As being a symbol of extremist
Because it is, shorthand for 100%
And was used as common slang white supremacy
That in no way means that the ATL thinks anyone who says like
Keep it 100
Is signaling that races shouldn't mix
This is an intentional misrepresentation by Alex
In order to
Demonize the ATL
Indicative
10 years old
As a way of
Confirming themselves
Four-wheeler videos list of symbols includes a whole lot of things are just
The number 12 is included because why
You make the letters Aryan Brotherhood
But used by those
It's not to say that the number 12 is
Baker's dozen
13th and Broadway
To know like
Is there another
It's a very minor thing
Because they opposed
People who are like
Pretty much
I don't know who this is
Like stupid
I think we should get back together once again you know they come dressed in uniforms they have weapons
I think we need
In terms of our law enforcement approach
So
We need to classify
Because they showed two demonstrations in the uniform carry weapons that are almost in Malaysia
Who shows up
Actually
You broke the rules I probably also already
You can say that
Are you saying to me
Fit somebody Ford
Two edges on it's impossible
And that's why this type of thinking is so f****** stupid
They are still coming up with a metric to justify class
Also inspire all of your dumb Friends
I assume the metric number of videos I've seen where people are yelling
Either because that what you want to start
You got all
Yeah it's kind of a mess
A little bit
Cobra control of the entire government
Empower otherwise my Alex
Alex is 100%
He's absolutely trying
Advocate for
Make excuses
Incase
Trump
Consolidates Power Authority real passion
Pilates
Christian music
Then they can be compromised
Because they still
So he's got to take over the
The judicial
Wing
I don't like this
And we've described
This is such a lie
Alex
Has
Novak
Nothing
This man is a
Pathetic
Week
Backbone list
F****** jelly
All of his posturing
So pathetic
Really
Call Perfect Right There
After the fact lobbyist
Think about grow
Does higher and has employed a lot of
Primary complaints as we
Learn from listening to the time when Obama was elected
One of its first place with
That was his critique
Of Obama
She has to try and
Administration
Yeah I remember being very unhappy
And then 22
16 half an hour
Restrain
According to opensecrets Trump Administration Employees 177 people do old positions
How many people do the 100 that's just their both lobbyist
Senior advisor to the Department of the treasury
Patrick
And David Bernard Secretary of you
Interior
To have a active financial interest
Austin the policies that benefit
I'm not sure past presidents
Don't might be less than other Administration
I don't think I really even matters
Lobbyist
Involved at all but the largest
Alex
Rogue
That's just that's bulshit
Transcript
Just say that he's corrupt
Didn't you like it
F****** the president of
Is a corrupt
Making him a s*** ton of money off his f****** corrupt God
Now
Making it
So he's predicted
Movie premieres
Steve are going to shoot up a bunch of people and they're going to blame
Just washed up comedian
Mitch Match
Shootings and bombings
Taylor Swift
Adele
That there are groups planning organized mass shootings dresses Jokers
Real quick that's not what
Set it all complete misrepresentation
False flag
Was Trump in Alex Jones support
And they're going to March into those movie theaters and they're going to Gunn people now on
Blame you
All I hear there is Alex
Terrified someone is going to shoot people at a
F****** terrified of that to Deeks he's creating narrative
Right now as they're faking their social media profiles to make it look like their fans about
As long as they are at been on social media
Years old
Right right right
Beautiful
It was all a plant
Right
Something
Preemptive damage control
Who are more likely to commit are also more likely
Being aligned with him
Good luck
Cope
That no one
There isn't any
Is probably overblown there probably won't be
Problems
Premier
Alex
TVs are elaborate
You've got here even know how to set up this cliff
Exactly what they're doing
Devil worshippers
Texas
Ohio
Incel
Don't kill people
Ashaway weather today
Good news about ever
Singer doing falling on their face
Sunburn
Animal take your phone calls
This is the big Push by the globalist
If you follow that the Siri is
TVs are High TV shows are high
Caserta thing in order to precipitate
Shootings that are actually false Flags in order to take away Alex's guns which will track Civil War so that
The Chinese can take over
The globalist
Because we're on how many
This is like a game of mousetrap Alex's mom
This is absurd
Rube Goldberg ass brain
Get out of here
Close to funny as we're going to get
Go to the coffee room
During the break
And he has a real has a
Break room
Coffee
Psychoanalyze myself
Oh my God
What
I really sat back and so do you.
We need people
Plan
Go to the street
Willie do it
Just scanned
To find out when Democrats are common
Or San Antonio or Dallas
Yeah I know s***
Doing that already
Lakewood
Hilarious
Realizes I am not
No idea
Cheap publicity by going on
Why the f*** if I'm not done that all this is
Realizing
Back when I was a young man
Reaper publicity and attention
Ezi
But now I do Alex
You are not doing a good enough job
You have to Google
You have to get Battle
You have to do the very basic
Minimum of knowing
When your enemies are going to be in your state
People
Drilling you up with like
Stop this problem
And then when you get down to the solution
We good Google
I don't have any solutions
Butterfly fish
Great
So Alex
This episode on the audience thinks we should do
Is usually a bad sign
What should we do today
Because
History Staffing
Take some over
Messages
Great idea
Civil War
Here's the problem.
Any of them
The problem with
Call about things like flying planes and stuff
How do we stop this before it becomes a physical Civil War
When earlier this episode he already clearly articulated
So why are you
Call
On what we can do
To stop
What I've already determined isn't necessary outcome because you got it
Given America
You got to try
It's like the opening of its like the opening of The Wire
Why do you let him play
This is America
You got it right
Night I don't I don't I think that
I think this is nonsense
Everett
Is leading you to the ultimate
Conclusion
There's going to be Millions dead in a shooting War here in America
So what do we do to stop it I don't know let's go
Get me more press
It's right there and I'm sure Alex wants that message to be
Distributed
But all of that is
Like its rearranging deck chairs on the Titanic
Like he
Has said the ship is going down
It's almost like
To do before the Civil War
The best-case scenario recruit more people on our side
What kind of Aldi's
He's doing
Legal over the entire democratic
Hey if Bernie is giving a speech in your makeover
I guess what he's just saying is like detract attention
Whatever
Public debt
More life
Repeating it
What do you think we should do
How to legally lawful
Play Sublime
Excuse
Outcome of the rhetoric
They're planning to do that
You can't blame me for that cuz I can
Reason to believe that my audiences
Incline towards non-legal.
That's all that's going on here
Keenly aware
Wait what no this is Vee I'm going to murder you politically
No I mean like the legally lawfully
Bet you half
To say legally
It's a way you wouldn't be like
Why did you need to say you weren't going to rewrite
Exactly
Has a bunch of f****** weird
Predicated on the idea that the globalist
Kill Everybody
And the reason that the
Alex has a theory about that
It's not a good one
Rose Garden
Bars at Trader
This is far too complicated to get all the way into and it's a lotus
But basically Alex's belief is that there are a ton of indictments on all these
You back
Alex's stuff
It is yeah
If I already hate
You're like I don't think he's going to be like takeover
Losing
Without
They're guys
Give directions right
Kind of
A lot of the followers are kind of
Already
I don't
Work
That is funny how is how so many people who would
Describe themselves
Individual
Starset
Lost for what
To do the MoMA
Fictional being no longer
Forgive them
I don't have
Post on a message board to tell me what to Google anymore
Oh no
Alex
I think the most important pieces but Alex is
Just like Auntie level
They're all these indictments
Give more public
You actually think that
Everybody around Trump is doing everything
Possible to keep him away from TV
Siri like the end of f****** Ironman
I think I think a lot of Trumps enemies would like
Kim to do more
He wants to find out some solutions
The products but I honestly think the best thing that anyone can do right now
Can you sort of hysterical situation
Is get a trump t-shirt get a high
Go out there and represent no matter where you're going
Alex's Eden
You can hear he has a mouthful of something flies are going
Solution is
Where Trump merch
To both plug Alex
Texas products but also wants to let everybody know.
To buy Trump
I mean I'll write absolutely not a corrupt God that we are
A tall is our best way to support him
To purchase things
Lionel Richie
That is not corrupt whatsoever Our God that
A leaving that aside for a second
Like
That's your suggestion
Close
You are not doing it man
The Civil War
Hats
Okay
Screaming conspiracy theories
Awesome the right
Not just getting good at comedy
They're good at
Organize
The Hat thing is kind of like I guess you could be overly generous to that
Suggested to be like Congress
Support for Trump because of all the hats
Because Alex
He believes that would solve an essential problem
And that is the Congress is to
Congress
You are amazing
Democrats
Baseball game
Really
Security officer
Who shot
The shooter
One second
The guy opened
Second
That wouldn't have happened could have killed a lot of those members
Stop
So small baseball practice
There was approximately 10 minutes shootout with him before he was taken down
Completely making that up
I'm in the process of that shootout he also shot a police officer Congressional
Who buy Alex's definition problem
Congressional baseball Bragg
Oh well
None of the people that Alex names
We're at their practice
Jim Jordan
Jeff Locke was also there but
What is true that the perpetrator of that crime
It's kind of Illuminating though to see the different
Responses
Of particular note was how Bernie Sanders responded to news that the
He said that there were bad people on boats
That's what he said
I've just been informed that the Republican baseball practice
I'm sickened by the stuff that despicable
Let me be as clear as I can be
Unacceptable
Real change can only come through nonviolent action
And everything else runs
Powder to our most deeply held American value
There's no didn't work on his campaign there's no attempt to make him look bad
I find it hard to believe that Alex would respond similarly if I don't know
Las Vegas
Nope
Alex. That was a false flag
Yeah also Alex at the shooting of Gabrielle Giffords
So I don't think he has any f****** ground to stand on
After that trains
Situation
How does a real
What happened there was that on January 31st 2018
Bunch of Republican Congress members in West Virginia
When it collided with a
Trash truck
No one on the train was seriously injured but
Was killed
Seems to forget about a lot of them all the other people who were shot at the baseball field
This guy who died in the truck
The national Transportation safety board conducted a full investigation of that into
I decided to what it happened was that
Trucks
Tried to go around the lowered safety gates
To cross the railroad thinking there wasn't rain coming
Are they believed based on a minute-by-minute breakdown of the event
The driver wasn't
This is a tragic accident
Which
Is imperative really quickly
There was ultimately no truth to that
At all
Alex's narrative is particularly stupid because there's tons of pictures of the aftermath of the accident
Republic
You can see that after the Collision
They're so easy to produce evidence
Tracks it blown up
And there's no evidence of that
At all
There's plenty of evidence that defends the version of the story that I have just told you
The only thing backing up Alex's version is
Alex said it
There's nothing True to this at all
Well you may have screenshots
From video game
Snidely Whiplash
Skip back to his big plan to go yell at them
Democrats
Close like you can
Every live show
Getting there
What
Has to keep saying legal and lawful in order to
But when you're saying it like this I'm going to go out and you can get closer to them
F***** up
Whitaker
Why is proximity important
With their with their corruption why is it why is proximity important it's not important at all
Whip Whitaker
Dodgeball
Jordan
Bulshit
Bananas
The twin
Turbines of
They're going to
Duo
Massive Attack
Blame it on us
You need to protest legal Aloft
Tubac
Do this legally
It's such a
Consistently
I am doing
Everything in my
Ipower
To have
Documented evidence
Tried
This s***
Absolutely
It's
You're watching WWE
But you can tell from the way they're shooting it but it's clear that this match
The Optics are meant to be played in a
Sizzle reel
Iconic with the actual match
Isabel
That's what I hear hear what you keep saying over and over and over again
To defend Infowars someone
Gets up close at one of these rallies that does something
Write it.
It's it does feel that way
It's particularly important that I keep driving home this point at Alex's Express
A civil war is inevitable
This is not business as usual this is not status quo
A hundred percent chance
What
100% false flag
Senior
Doing what
God
Like
Like this is too much
To the point
Like does he know something
Like how f****** I know I know know know
Hear him say that
Secaucus impossible to get away from irrational
It's so suspicious
It doesn't indicate anything
How
Consistent this is how weird
Like 88
No I think
I don't think he knows something but I think
What if he does
Your irrational thoughts
Probably a hundred percent Nitro
What actually I think
Illustrates
Demonstrate
Is that Alex
Is smart enough to understand
The prince
In the actual world are lining up and down tangling with his rhetoric
But it's very likely that someone is going to do something f***** up
And so this is
Preemptive damage control
Hopefully no one does
Infowars as a business
That's what he's doing here
Wow at the same time
Can you bring all in the same
Make
Please sort of thing
These tragedies more like
It's completely irresponsible
It's absolutely
Disgusting
But I don't know if it's illegal it should be probably
More than happy for
Push-backs
And don't think that I think this
Truth it
But
There is a part of me that hears
Go on.
Like when he's
You think
Feels like you
No because if they
I do
He's going to get a lot of
A picture and
Don't want to believe
He's that much of
I don't think that you would do that
But it really does
If somebody did
F******
Do something
Then Infowars
Going to be all over the news
And he already has the legal and lawful defense
Prepared right
I don't think there's any way
Trying to do
Episode when we are talking about the day we heard him be like
So I don't know
I want to believe
I don't want to believe that you would
And I don't want to believe that you would ever do it
I don't believe it
There we go
One of the issues that comes up I think
Is
He's framing things
So I can
Consistently
The Jocelyn back and forth
Between
They're going to fall asleep
Nosey people from Power
Don't know how you can
It's spiritually right
To start committing violence
Against these people because they're so terrible
Because they brainwashed if you do that it's going to be bad strategy
Are completely irresponsible unacceptable
So
That's f***** up on its face
She goes to calls again
And you get the caller who brings up the remnant
For the people who will be less
After there's like a big calling
On the Earth
Not the
No DiCaprio
Avatar
The second season of bundyville
Explainer on the Revenant ideas
Yeah so this caller brings that up
If you understand that you can hear the code
And the discussion
What's going on on
And she has a solution for
What's
People should do
Stupid
Also know that
Christ said God said that
A remnant
It would be sold out to him
Okay because he only needs a remnant
That will stand up
To this evil this evil has been
Has been going on since the beginning
Starting with Kane will continue until Jesus comes back again
My suggestion
Okay now we can really make it this different than fighting this war
If every
Mingle
Princeton
That is a regular listening listener to your show
Would commit to give just
$5 a month
Faithfully every month
Until this thing is over and again it's not going to be over until Jesus comes again
Let's say there's 2 million
Faithful listeners out there
If you multiply $5 * 2
Million
That would be
10 million dollars a month
Alex would be getting in
That he could kill.
Absolutely
You know what somebody that works there
Like to jump around on it but I honestly feel the same way
Cuz later in the episode another call from another religious weirdo who has another suggestion
How to deal with the coming crisis
You're a modern-day Apostle Paul you're fighting the same side he thought you understand is he
Our Real Enemy
You all was every show
You mention Our God and Savior Jesus Christ
Is our only solution
You
You're obligated Outlet
To ask for contributions
That would be graciously given if you would set up an organized way
So that we your Lester's
Millions of Christians around the world
So there seems to be a real Trend in these collars that are calling in
Religiously Basinger
Tons of money
Yeah that's strange to me he's getting
There are many calls cuz he never does
Religious extremist
Who were calling in and
Millions of Christians should give you money and the other one is a more concrete
All of your listeners should give you $5 a month to give 10 billion dollars a month
Like it really seems
I'm not saying that they're playing
Prove it I can't prove it but it's
Weird
Cannot prove
It's weird
Come on
It's train televangelist has their own
End
Well actually
Call Hugo's on
To say some others
It's interesting
Victoria and that's why you need us behind you we need
Need to be giving to your
On a monthly basis but commitment
To your ministry
Is that your
These are nice we got the bigger Army we got the bigger stick his name is Jesus Christ then I might throw
Donald Trump in there along with him
So turn down the level of somehow
Which is sacrilegious I really I really don't think
Clearly
In their religion would say something like that
And then
The monthly thing coming back up in that second caller
It seems like Alex might be trying to Launch
Like a patreon clone or something like that
Subscribestar
Already about it yeah
Pictures in the world wanted to go and give $5 a month to Alex's subscribestar
They could do it
Now and they're not doing it
Because milk millions of Christians aren't listening to
Because he is outrageously
Sacrilegious
It would offend anyone who takes their face
Televangelist
Do what they do
Mcmillions
Sarah little smoother
I would argue Jim Bakker
Included
Now that is somehow transcended his
He did Raisa
I don't know I don't know
I hate to extend into things that I
Can't really
Even looking to even if I wanted to but I do have a strong suspicion that
Both of those collars are not real college
I think it when Alex is getting on air
Eddie's talking about Solutions and how do we avert the Civil War
Two people would be overt religious weirdos and they would both come up with the idea of a monthly donations for Alex
Which already exist
It seems
Estranged
Find it has to consider
Real
Who is the guy who made Gap
Is great
Hey wipe the two of them have a little bit of a bull session about how to launch its own Google
They're all 9
The right
Who cares
A little conversation and I don't really care that I think it's worth
If you call someone
YouTube
Sprite
Classic play by fire and fascist
Situations vulnerable communities are provided protection
A private
Citizen if you dare breach their guidelines about political correctness
This is aggressively in terms of motions ever made
Projectile lgbtq Folk
Air Canada Bill C 16 of 2007
They're constantly decried by right-wing scam artist as being about a ploy to lock you up if you dare use the wrong gender pronoun
Non-binary people would immediately become overpowered
In reality the cantabile is about housing and employment
Discrimination
Expression into the category of things you're not allowed to discriminate on
In terms of public
This is the same thing your guidelines they were about workplace discrimination and protecting lgbtq individuals
For being the target of unsafe
Now here we have Alex promoter of the owner of
The place where bigots and Nazis going
$50,000 fine
If you call someone an illegal alien
What do you think the story is really about Jordan
If you
Kick them out of their place because they did
Didn't pay rent
If you
Illegal immigrant
I'm out of their place
If your
Inflammatory like that anymore
You can't literally hand her over.
It's about workplace housing in public accommodations
The new guidelines laid out by the New York Commission on human rights do it how if you're in a position like you're an employer
You can't treat someone differently because you assume they might be in Hamburg
Princeton
Get there a legal resident because they have an accent
Unless you ask
Everyone
Who doesn't have an ass
Quest
The same goes for discrimination based on English proficiency
So you're anything any kind of stereotyping you might have
That's probably fine if you're a private citizen
I mean it's already against the law if you're an employer to do that
You would ask them
They be like I don't like
The document also clarifies that quote
The use of the terms illegal alien and illegal humiliate or offend a person or persons
The workplace amounts to unlawful discrimination
Of course it does
In terms of the housing Porsche
That all
These guidelines and anyway you can't evict
Undocumented immigrant even if they don't pay rent
Bulshit literally everything I've
I've ever known about any
Right Alex is trying to create a perception that people like undocumented immigrants are above the normal rules
Even Noble Lightfoot friends are subjected to
Because it helps to feed his victimhood complex without wouldn't have ever made a dime on this show
The guidelines clearly layout Waze
Document
Status or nation of origin
Can be evicted
If your landlord you just can't
For instance by threatening to call Ice
This extends
Ignoring tenant
Complaints or attempt
Not complaining about property issues
By implying or threatening to call Ice
Here's how I know that Alex
Torba are gigantic
If they weren't
They would be discussing these guidelines
As they actually exist
Instead of trying to create strong men to attack
Because to oppose these guidelines is to Advocate that employers and employees
Abusive working environments just because they think they're undocumented
They would have to advocate for live like a legitimate systemic racism and xenophobia
Wear it if you want a white person you just had
Just suck it up and live with whatever ship people in positions of authority
And here's the fix
B21 advert
It's the situation they want to have in the world but they're smart enough to know that if they came out and made those arguments sincerely
Run the risk of being
This whole facade of free speech disappears
The donations from non-racing
Completely dry up
I can stay if we want to take a the lawsuit
That Alex
His treatment of them is
Yeah he just want to be able to threaten whatever bulshit he wants
Create unsafe working environments for minority with
Guidelines without making it look like they're really just want naan
White people to have no protect
Society
They create the strong
You'll be assigned a quarter billion dollars and just like that they can turn their
These human rights protection without having to say why they really take issue with
His 13 Elementary tricks Alex does all the time
It's awesome
The statute
This pattern is to cancel
He knows what he's doing
Attempts to attack societal protection against
And
We can go f*** himself
This is all just
Coated White
Missy videos
Black
It is my squad
We get back to the violence non-violence
Alex is putting forth on
Help my brain
Not going into combat mode
Restarting combat Bowser losing
25 years
25 of the years
Clippers 35 seconds
That's not a good sign
That means there's a problem
Like I completed mission
That your show has a problem
You don't say twice in 35 seconds
Even by Alex's own behavior that
Implies an awareness that the shows
So Andrew
They
Are actually
People that project
I was in Savage
It's fair that maybe some people are definitely far to stereotyping
Southern people in also
Far to stereotyping the other direction of people at North
Although I cannot believe for a f****** second
The story that Alex
Stalin
Until I went off to college
Oh my word
I can't do a show without somebody coming up to
To me afterwards
Looking both directions
Being like
How do you feel about jokes like and then insert minority
Is trying to malign anybody who
So congratulations you know let's say aggressively
You might be Pro fascism
Is your sport of demonizing people who are anti racist
It implies that maybe you have a kinship with rape
It doesn't prove
But it implies it
This is this is not a good
And his next life doesn't help any of the feelings that I'm having about these
And we are the great
So
That's pretty good
Coach Taylor
Clear Eyes
Fohawk
Clear-eyed races start
Christian straight
Speaking truth and where
Cool
Good conception
What works
Actually mad about
To deal with
Worshipped
Single day
And it's like
And I have to
And all this time coming up with ways to argue against
Human rights protections for people make it look like it's actually about a press
I think I think if you had like Wheels.
TWA of racism
Labor
If you have real complaints you wouldn't have to go out of your way to misread
Folks in New York
You just wouldn't do stuff like that you would spend your time on Valley criticism
You wouldn't misrepresented Netflix movie
You wouldn't
One of your shows talk about Bob Dylan
If you misrepresented Jack Dorsey tweet from
You wouldn't do any of this stuff if you had real complaint
This is all misrepresentation in service
Justifying
The victimhood status that you have which only serves
To justify why
Inevitable civil war is coming in your right for it
It's all that's going on
These last two clips that I have
I think that these are bad
Back to this
Violence non-violence
Back and forth
Is trying to convince people
Whether he's making the argument clearly or not
Let's
I'm just allowed up right now I know you are as well this is
Politically
If you hide out there going to get you
You can't hide
You Can't Hide there is no opting out
Earlier
Michelle
And listen to some of this language here in this life
The holdup
Again it's just
Con man
It just
The medes
About how there's a literal devil
Asian against be great Noble white Christian Patriots of this country
If left to their own devices
Everything I'm saying entire worldview everything I'm screaming about
Leeds YouTube must be destroyed
Politically
Literary
Where it's like
Your
By turning legal in La Follette
Into a refrain
Your turn again
Into a winking aside
You don't want lie
Prejudice I think of that I think it's an interpretation
That's certainly not
I think I think that I think there's all sorts of interpretations you could make of this
Not a very good
B
I mean if the bottom line is I don't think it's illegal but like
I feel so
I don't think that this is a good episode of our show Eva
Because I so much like
On Alex's part
Construct outside
Raditz
Because what he's saying
Is
Leading towards
Negative outcome
Yeah so I hope nothing happens
I sincerely hope nothing happens
Is National Treasure
Should
Alex
His entire career at this point in 2019
Exist
To normalize
To make that more likely
It doesn't amount to a hill of beans
Because the overriding
Overriding
The rhetoric everything else
Is
Contradict
He can say that to keep himself in legal safe territory
But it doesn't matter
That is not what his show is about
Legal and lawful
Conspiracy theories
At politician
That's not what this is
Now the only reason
This is legalism
Brandenburg versus Ohio
Abstract calls for crimes are not illegal
This is just
Stay away from
The pointless argument
I agree with you there
But if it's
Specific
Let's start with
I think it's no it's a ninja
Discussion
And maybe the courts
But at the same time it's a secondary organ
Who is this
Absolutely unethical
And the only outcome of this
Making it more likely the terrible thing
So
I don't know
Very much
Anyway I wanted to do
I didn't I want to do what you want to talk about space weirdos and had some
A little bit lighter and a break
From this s***
Cuz I think we definitely do need it
But it's such a bad timing of a
Coincidence
The World episodes
Really high tension points in 2019
Just crazy b******* going on
I promise we will get back to more frequent
Braixen diversion
But we just can't
Realized
Returning back to territory where in you are a witch
And that
In the present day
We talked about some
Something and then
Comes up
Currently
Both in 2013
Ended 2019
The World's End
The world might not be
Alex is rhetoric feels like it's coming
I don't know what to say about that
I'm not
Galaxy
Have the
On Friday
Please go to iTune
Castroville app
Sure thing
I'm Leo mdvip
Time traveling
Alex