Damned important
I have great respect for knowledge by now.
MoneyGram
Knowledge vype.com
Everybody welcome
Little bit
That's right we do Jordan
What is the first time you ever felt achievement
The first time you want to race
Literally crazy I know this specifically it pop directly to my mind and I'll tell you what it is Dan
Equestrian
I understand that the rhetorical technique I remember in
Week
I want a personal pan
Too many for one
All out I don't think I read a book again for like 6
I read all of the books and that was the first time that I truly felt like I did
I bet f
The rest of the class kicked your ass
You're correct
Just absolute disgust like I read so much
That sort of embarrassed the rest
The tears the Macarena cancel
That was not a sense of achievement for me as much as it was
There was another
Woman
Head always
Read more books than everybody else
She was like famous in the class
For being famous
The whole school
And I kicked your ass
Wow
Bizzy Bone easy on you
Okay so yeah they're probably like I don't know
Ramona Quimby Age 8
Jensen
Today something that isn't okay
That's not bad
Taking over this episode
Had to give people a little bit of context
Listen to present episode for Friday about Alex's
Intensity in the present
So I felt like it would be kind of repetitive and not really
Serve anyone's interests all that well
Simultaneously I thought it would be kind of abusive to go and do another Boston bombing episode
Keep going
Like a light
Mnml you know somebody's Wacky Wednesday folks are bringing it there's nothing really good over project Campbell Atlanta
Reverend Manning I don't really think that guy
Dave's boring shitt
A lot of these other candidates just really aren't all that interesting someone like a Steven Crowder you know we can't do an episode about him
No joke I considered number these over
White supremacist typo
You'll have to talk about cuz they are overt with a little bit of
You guys are being raised
Okay criticism a little bit perfect
Let Jordan take over and seen what happened it's the one day of the year Dan remembers
I think I will relearn that once again will find out I don't know anything about what you're going to do
No except I have a hunch that'll be probably surrounding one of your big picadillos
Main issues
Redwall
Weird weird
Yeah
Conor friedersdorf
Partially because Twitter fight with you
Just responded to you it was lovely to call him
That was one of the most surreal things ever
He's not wilting for this
Punches right back if it's a nationally syndicated
Backed out at 8 p.m.
The combination of both of those things
Insignificant weirdos day
Mark Moreno
Is a giant pizza
Certainly what you went over on the last time you took over the show
Not just
Ever needs
To speak to Mike Moreno Everett
I will get to that proof
It just one moment
So first of all Thomas
I heard about a nap, that I was just really pissed him off
I won't do that to this very kind Donuts
Next
Episode
Text Journal about was you want
Text Gianluca
Look up
Wonderful technocrat
Money off at heroin
Freakishly large
I would like
Button set for the show
It's all you buddy
Sure counter program
That makes sense just called lord monckton
Out of context
We can go to Walmart by so we can stop this nonsense about the green New Deal
Alright
That's my favorite
Express renewable energies and we would need a green New Deal
Okay as a sarcastic aside
Is just like sure they say that we need renewable energy
We can stop the green New Deal
I was just
Absolutely surreal
He shows up
And Friends
Morning
It is filled with type of Dum Dums are going to allow him
To say
Absolutely ridiculous
Sure
But do you think about him
Is if you are booking him
In 29
You know exactly what he's going to
Completely invalid
He has nothing new
He has nothing that hasn't been debunked
A million times
Reference
So you put it on yourself
For one reason and one reason only
And that's it spread climate denial
And if you put them on yourself that that is what you are
Trying to do
God dammit
He hasn't
It's ridiculous
This time
He has
One ring
He is done some
Man on the street
These people are so convinced that those means
B Wild
You finding so many different places
You know what I mean
I guess Fox News and Infowars are too far from each other spiritual
Bone weird
They're supposed to be nude
Here's the weird
Or at least
Is brilliant as far as
Strategy
Unlike
So many other man-on-the-street interviews where the idea is
People who are together to make it look like all these time
Stupid
They did something
Really really
I think
Which is they got all these kids to say 100% true and accurate things
Every one of these people
Nailed it
Every single thing they say
Is correct
And it's just like we talked about where they're going
For your strength
You on the strike they're not trying
Play Taylor Swift
They're trying to make their ideas
Coming from
So here's our first interview this is the first thing that they play
About like
8 years old and the other one looks like she might
Photobomb
I guess with the argument that I can gather is sort of like just believe
This you agree with children
It's like Hitman children are sometimes right about things like chicken fingers are great
Universally children are wrong about everything their reasons for believing that what they believe that
I agree with might be
Different
Chocolate
Around 1
Open Gmail
It gets yelled at me by friends a lot cuz I don't like a lot of foods
That's what they say that's basically what it mean
I don't like
Like the tofu
The fuk away from Factory
I cannot chew that
Right
Kids
They want you to look at how silly this girl is
Jumping and screaming
All the same exact words that those kids
Random talking head on Sienna
Say what sound
Perfectly read
There's no way that you could take those words in that order
They don't react to that with
And here's how Trump is helping they just
So the idea is
If you're watching Fox
And you see that
They're saying
The deck stain
Sentences
And you're laughing at them cuz they're children
And then on CNN
Somebody says that later that night and you're like that's what that stupid children
Yeah it's a good strategy
Killing our shooting the messenger kind of thing
How to deal with what's being said she's already
Said f*** the kid
Values like you protect the children kind of celebrate
The child
God bless
You know that that kind of network and yet there they are using
Just the appearance of children is to make an idea stupid
Oh yeah that's the Great
Good stuff
Let me ask you
Do you know why children
Love
Credit Karma
Probably version of
Seeing themselves reflected in her a little bit
Some sort of identification
Compactor
The idea that
Making positive change in the world
Through her believe that maybe they too could make positive change in the world that by guess
Price Rite
That is interested so many young people
Rusty stellosphere
That's why the youth are still into Alex
Haha
I thought they were going to say
What is that
What's your name
I was also thinking of what was the other one
There's another like
Young woman who
He's taking of like the Ricola
Longhorn Cafe
Absolutely
Yeah I don't I don't know if I agree with them so far
I'm trying to take a really objective
Costanzo's I've known to do
Seem like
What was funded
Literally
He is saying
Throughout this entire interview
We need to be afraid of Greta
And he is
Basically telling that to everybody who is watching the show while at the same time starting with
Greta is the one who's trying to make you afraid
Our message is one of hope hope
Found in fossils
Sixteen-year-olds scaremonger
Is out there trying to make you afraid
So be afraid of her attempts to make you afraid
The warmth
Soft comforting blanket of coal
Basically we are we are going to keep going with this interview it is all like
Here's what's wrong with Greta here's how Greta is hurting you and with Beth
What's the best part is there's always like
And also
Children
She is also doing yeah we heard from Alex
Caswell
Greta thunberg started in Sweden every Friday outside the Swedish Parliament
And it spread to skip school in order
They have a future and otherwise
She's actually said
Angie's address to EU the United States Congress testified
Why should kids go to school if they have a future that will be no more
Unless government passes laws like the green New Deal more UN treaty
It's her fault entirely she's telling all your kids to go to school
Probably before Greta was born
There's other
And she's just weaponizing that towards the positive
She's weaponizing the fear that people have
Being formally educated
You can make an argument for that
But I don't know how much that
Stray kids
I dropped it really hurt me that much but still wants College it's no big deal
The thing about that
It is
Unbelievable how
Quick quality
It it's really really amazingly
Here's what here's when Greta started
A year ago
That was it there's the strikes right by skipping school on August 20th
2018 school and goes outside the Swedish
Telling them they need to do more on
Yes Wellness
On the 26th
She did it again
And this time
A bunch of other students
And parents all came along with
In September she began to do it every single Friday so this is September 2018 is about a year
All the sudden
Are doing this
In November
More than 17,000 students
Walk out on
On Friday in February of this year
The protest
Take place in 30 countries
In March
Sundberg is nominated for a Nobel Prize
Peace Prize
So
In August
To March
She got a Nobel Peace Prize
Nomination
You're describing Bisquick progression of it
There's no way this was the track
AstroTurf
It's now at the same time in March more than 2 million students
Over 135 countries
Start walking out
In May
She's named one of the most
Influential people in the world
She started this when she was
And in eight months
She is one of the most influential people in the world
I don't I don't know if you have this in your research
Has Mark Moreno ever been named
Has he ever been
Nominated
He's got a Pulitzer
I think I read that nearby I was
In
In August 14th
She gets out of climate neutral
To be she's invited to the UN climate Summit
Against
And then on September 20th on September 20th
That was the climate strike that took place in / 185
Countries the number is in Cal
Are people who party
And then on September 23rd
He finally speaks
Hope everybody has watched
And seen the entire video but
It's just impossible like
Speech the entirety
And then I watch
People talk
Sing about it on
All the Talking Heads
And they're just talking about it very
Call muddy like
Greta thunberg's
The US
That is not how she
I shouldn't be up here
I should be back
School
Appetite
Young people
How dare you
She had the balls to save it to the f****** you
What's up with the un's going to kill her like I mean
It does take a lot of strength that I'm not taking that away from her at all amazing actor
Of Bravery
Whittier 16 I don't think that most people would be able to just give a speech. Let alone something
Thing that confrontational
Powerful people
It's not like they're going to kill it's not like she became an incredibly famous
Caldera Bunton
Little Dipper
It's not like Yonker
But just for comparison go ahead
Play the this is this blooper
We also think press
Trump for Cummings
Hopefully our discussions here will be
Useful for you when you
Formulate
Climatology
It's not like they're going to kill us
Isn't that the position of strategies
8:20
God
That's what let's hear her
Okay
My childhood
Yeah she's a
I can't get over this
I cannot get over the fact that she is 16
I could barely do that now let alone when I was sick
Sure
And the amount of pressure and everything that she has been under and how she has responded to it
She has is so unique
I really could not
Greta is
Trulia
Beyond anything
In a long while
She's very forceful and she's right and she's telling the world off
She's making sure everybody
You know
What she's representing is a large group of
Authentic
Who are worried about the Earth
Worried about the
There
You would think that climate change
Is a threat
Future right
Not true
Mark Marino
Knows what the real
Kids are getting anti-anxiety medication
She is the great effect she's stealing fear
In millions of kids around the world
Okay
Mental illness anxiety disorder did not exist before
August
Congratulations bar
You made a spectacular argument
I know I was looking into this cuz he said that you specifically
Ceu
I couldn't find anything specific
To the EU was because she's Swedish
I would assume
Riding
No I mean like she's yours she's comes from European countries that's why you saying you you
It's it's like it's just that simple
But couldn't find anything about the march of 2017 the American Psychological
Really thick 69-page report
About this very idea
Climate-induced
Anxiety
And it has a bunch of tips for mental health professionals on how to deal with
Solastalgia
The distress that is
Produced by environmental change
Impacting on people
Here are some of my favorites
Okay sunscreen baz luhrmann
I know
Tip number one
Build belief in one's own Raziel
That's pretty good General
Easier
You'll find a running
A running tally of that
General good tips for
Okay
Foster optimism
Not a bad idea
Tip number three
Cultivate coping and self-regulation
Tip number for
Kisses that help to provide a sense
And tip number 5 promote connectedness to Family Place Caltrain commute
These are out there
You don't use the f****** b******* about that
These accusations causing anxiety and fear and other stuff
This would be
Totally right on
If Greta was getting up and being like you know what
And we should do about it
Coming up with a message of nihilism
Form of death called now
Is
So along with the anxiety there is
That might come up in some people
There's also an optimism there's also a clear actionable
Things that can be done
I don't know I just don't I don't buy I don't buy the idea of it
Climate activist
Are causing that kind of a reaction cuz there is
Action
Is there is
A way that would cause I just don't get it
Tires
And what she's doing all of this stuff and now they're anxious
They're they're all losing
To be true
But
Augmentin
OG's concept
Just raising temperature
Concept
To study
1001 by Anders
And another in 2005 by
Sinister and Cooper
Sinister
Send mr. right it seems like
I thought it was a guy from
Sevenfold
I don't need another Ethan Hawke movie
Causal relationship
Between increase
And in increaser
Summers in Chicago we all know
Well it's
Really f****** annoying to be hot I think we all know that just on it
.
It's
Suck it
Really bothersome
I'm a sweaty dude to even worse
It sucks every little bit every little temperature causes more and more aggression
I got to think about how expensive it is to
The Trap what is freon
Bright
Which also is killing the planet
It's a vicious cycle
And also it's not just like
Aggression towards other people
Higher temperatures have been increased levels of suicide
It appears that this is from
Smiley
At all
Distress of feeling too hot can overwhelm coping ability for people who are already psychologically
Climate emergency exacerbate pre-existing system
Symptoms and lead to more serious health
Sprite
So
Probably not Greta
Increasing iron
Difficulty there
Yeah
The worst one
Destroyed me
Conselho Whitlock
Which I don't know if
They examined the impact
Climate change on a small Inuit
Community
These people have
Very personally indirectly
Climate change
Action
It's not like
Not like that you know living in Illinois Lottery it is right
They see their land disappear they see their hunting-grounds disappeared
Just like most
In all of those places
Except they can
Tell people and
They specifically said that because of this
Change
Started feeling insecurity anger stress but most of all a loss
Community
Like I didn't feel connected to each other as much
And the elders were specifically concerned
And about the preservation of the Inuit language
And culture
This quote is
We are people of the CIA
If there's no more CIA
How can we be people of the sea
As we see climate change
Progressed
The biggest issue is I think his is one that we're not really
And that is
Massive amount of
Displacement
Combined with the loss of community
Urban areas that are going to be like
Weather going to be
Uninhabitable
That
Yeah if you could be
Could be pretty severe
Yeah absolutely
And he's not really
Climate change
What about the people in the farmers in India that had like all their crops
Increase suicide rates month
Most people attribute that to that
Studied it
Political scientist
As well
But that probably the first war
Directly tied to
Interesting
That caused all of the previously
Disparate farming communities in all of the small community
Lose all of their food
And so they had to move to
The city and the City
Wasn't ready for an infant
That many
Nobody had
You have
18 tonight
Twenty-three-year-old
Less than
60% on employment
And
Kaboom
Yeah that makes sense done
I was unaware of those variables connection
Nobody
Grievances in Syria
Yeah there's a few bad guys
We get back to
The children
Won't someone think of the
Someone needs
Then that person is Mark Marino and he is something that he would say
To a child
Watch their other
Say certain things
Earth Day projects
Or her
I would tell them the government can't legislate the climate
Fair
True
To some extent possible that temperatures are going down
What would you say to your child
I imagine
His child being like seven or eight
He's just like well.
Legislate
Curvy nice reassuring
I also love the idea that Dulce just jumped in there and called like
With the curriculum pure pressure
66 seventh-grader whatever they made us learn about like one month was monarch
Reply month
Better learn all about goddamn monarch butterflies next month was pastas
I got to learn about different pasta shapes
Like
I don't want this is stupid it wasn't pure pressure
Durham School
Authority
I learned about pasta quite a bit
I don't remember, okay
Thirteen-year-old me good told you all about it
Speedy spaghetti
Is it called frozen pizza is out it is now
I don't know I don't know what mark would actually say
His own
He has called Greta and
Prophets
Sure
He's not been very complimentary
Think that you can
Will you can't legislate the climate now you cannot
Which is fair
Right otherwise I pass a bill that these damn plants
Need to start getting some peppers out of them
Wish I could do that
You still have any types of Bell right here peppers
Splat watch
What's up I made a mistake I didn't realize that you had to plant each
Sapling or treat like seedling in its own pot plants like two or three to a pot
Realizing I'm going to have to lecture
Cold in Chicago
So I can't be by the window
I could get a heat lamp
Look there's a lot of struggles I didn't plan ahead I don't know any of this stuff if I could legislate
I would do it
Yeah
Planting will be better next
But I'm sorry I didn't mean to derail there
You have
Nailed it on the head
Here's the problem
With Greta
Right
And with really all the kids
They just
They just don't want to
I just don't want to work
That's it
Say if you really want to
Do something challenging
Skip school
Social media
Credit issue
She doesn't do anything Chow
Haha
I guess there's different definitions of challenging
You know
How's there's consequences that can come from skipping school
Or from
Encouraging
Everyone to school
There's consequences that come from that take
Is a challenge in another cell
So what yes the active school if you want to go smoke weed play video games
Sure I mean there's a risk to it
There's a little bit of a challenge
You're not coming out and saying I'm skipping school to do that you're trying to hide
The openness about it is what's the meaning behind it adds a little more of a challenge
Absolutely
Giving up social media for a little while
I don't know people are really into social media
Social media while she was taking a climate neutral boat across the
Atlantic Ocean
Happen because her hands
Word sunburn
When she got off the boat
Really
Right
What other
I don't know I have no idea
I didn't look too deeply into it cuz it seemed
Crazy
I mean I don't know I guess parsec away to attack
Black people who make
Moves
And that is to say there's something else they should have done because there'll always be go on a hunger strike
Still using your phone
Will always be ejected
Your bodies are going to eat it's own fat you're fine social media not giving that up his stuff
I really feel like we are not that far away
This argument against anybody who's doing something you always
It's just a matter of
How
Craven do you want to be how opiate-like how transparently full of s*** do you wish to be publicly
I will set the standard by which the
Integrity or anything of your protest
Is Judge by and I
It's just
Amazing
2/2 yeah that that naked Craven
Attitude
This
This girl is about
Speak
To the UN
This is Vista giving this interview like
Bananas
Absolutely banana
Insults in every possible way
We finally get to the sweet man on this
Oh hell yeah
Edited together three interviews
And I think you'll see
Through-line
We need to restructure the economy
That's not articulate that all that well to do I don't know
It's not really that nonsensical oviposition like whatever
Resented my parents growing up because
You know
Things would ever be acceptable
They refuse to buy me Lunchables cuz there's too much trash in them and stuff like that
Big little sweet bear with little pizza
But as I've grown older I kind of realize that
It's so much watts trash then
Costco box of something I meant Tupperware
That last person talk about sports
Kind of similar in the sense of like
If we had
We could cut down on a lot of trash that were
Especially plastic trash
I don't know
Little
It was like
The concept is correct
I'm making a little joke out of that last little boy
What's a sports a f****** funny word man
The concept actually is 100%
A very very good idea
But even intuitively I know you're about to explain why it does make some sense as long as you're not pry
Prime to Market
If we were like cuz the idea that
Their Express
If we took
What if we have forks and we have spoons
That's twice as much as if we had one utensil
Theoretically like the idea that their Express
You can even make a little sore
Hold on for going to be rich
Hundred percent already exist
There are about
Jose in
Science magazine
Published on February 13th
Study found that there are
Between 4 and 12 million metric
Tons of plastic
Poured into the ocean
There are
Garbage barges
Spinning around the fucken ocean
But maybe even more important
Is that plastic
Itself producing it
Leaves a massive Lehigh Carbon
Everything okay
And cutting it down in half would be
Ridiculous
Cutting down plastic of one Spectre
Lately correct but they are in a very stupid
Solve everything
But it would do something
So
Even the most simple
Possible solution
Mock them first
Impossible
To do anything
Especially if
Large
Most importantly
Any reduction
Huge
Especially at this point
Anyting
Not only that
There are also
Here's the other thing
About what
There's a third one
There are a lot of there's a lot of poo
Pollution in the production of
It has to be there usually
The plants are built
Near water almost all the
The study done by the Clean Water Association
Shows that
In the Bay Area
Two-thirds of litter on the streets
What is made up of single units
Figleaves U10
Let the litter
On top of it
Every part of single-use
Silverware
Forks and spoons
Hey did
Massively destructive
Bright 2
Yeah
There's nothing
Counterpoint
When I make turkey bacon
But if I use a metal Fork to flip the bacon
They often will end up scratching my pan
Doesn't do that
Ergo
I love
Disposable silverware
You're right
That isn't proven
Hit me up Mark
Beatbox
He could really use your help
Cuz he's a little bit
Wouldn't imagine that
It's if it's just
It's almost like medieval witchcraft
We can save our planet
I don't know if that was the right way
Can you play one more
I like to say that this is no more than medieval witchcraft
United Nations
Can save our Park can save the Statue of Liberty
Can save a species of
This is just
The height of Raikou
I think it's the next one
Sacrifice
Real rhetorical flourish be like
Death
Do you think I'm saying when I say everybody knows
Exactly what you going to say
What he shows up
Funny
Interview quote-unquote he's going to call climate change stuff barbaric wizard
Cool that's his plan
100000000000000
That's just what I had to find a way to get that one is getting
I can hear him say that over and over and over
Queen.
He just doesn't understand
I guess this is fairly similar to some of the Alex
Be kind of s*** you know like calling things witchcraft
Giving kids vaccines
Oh yeah
More similarities than I'm comfortable with
Interview on
Fake interview on Fox and Friends
But it just turns into Sanders and Elizabeth Warren
Fly all the time
They say we shouldn't meet all the time
It's one of those it's one of that same Peyton I have
Very similar things
It goes all the way back
What you felt good arguments
Over and over and over again no one has rubbed the Witchcraft argument so
Going to keep doing it until someone
I don't think anybody could ever do that now
Later on
After being a complete idiot
Before Greta
Sure on Foxon
He goes on Barney show
Comedian okay
This is after gratis
I don't know who this guy is
Okay
Think that the solution
I know this guy just by his voice
Quote-unquote solutions to climate change
That have been offered are they still popular in Europe
Because Europe is really suffering from these so-called Celeste
Deficit increased
If this guy wants to know what the Europe
I'm seeing a real
Disinterested Lord monckton even on Fox news Wichita troubles me a little bit
Yeah probably be apart of it
Denmark Moreno's bitlord of climate
So people in
People people always remind me of the last episode
You know
Like one of those cases that he would bring up specifically looking
There's so much more going on here this has to do with financial stop
Climate change measures
Poverty
Oh yeah that is borne out by the office of Nash
Statistics
Is the most British name I can think of for a government age
Ons
These are our national
That's what we do
It America we call it the office
But
Actually what I found out was that winter deaths have increased
I was really I was
All geared up for fruit to be like this
Completely made up this
It's all bulshit
I don't even need to worry about
But
The number of excess winter
That's what they measure
What do you mean by excess
Access number of deaths
In winter
The other three months
Okay
Between
What is
April and
July and July
September
Does an average of 100
Then there's 115 in Winter that has excess.
Alright
So
Steps are expensive
Highest
Number of x
Seth winter.
Play recorded
Mainly due
Increase influenza
And of course
All the way around
Nothing to do with climate
Addison even further disingenuous argue
Because well yes you can
Can say it's the Hyatt
Is recorded number
The 70s
It is also
One-half the number
Since the fifth
So it's
Absolute b******* the trend overall has
Dip down right over and over and over again
Complications of illness
When measures are past that make it so
Like the electric company can't turn off your electricity during the winter pay your bill they can't turn it off
April measures like that that are protective cut awful
Needs to be across the board
Protected about that
Resources for people who are
Experiencing homelessness
Fast response
Remember when there was a blizzard
The last time here in Chicago
There was a lot of focus put on report them so we can make sure
They don't
Stay outside
Message from your local neighborhood
No it's that wasn't nice
Number down to as low as it can possibly go
Even with
Severely inclement weather winter temperature
Better solution
To look at that whatever Mark is talking about
Absolutely
It is amazing how
I have never
Seeing him
Give any
Straightforward
I've never I've never seen it not once
Even if it's one that's not even damaged or
Like almost unrelated
What about that
When it's dry out
Yeah so it is
It is kind of amazing
Because even this is just a cherry pick
Like he had to say from the 70
He couldn't even
Couldn't possibly be like
Well it's twice as many years from 2014
Hastily
Create this chair
That is
Misleading
It's just stupid
We have to whenever you hear people using
Majestic Theater
Wise to look into contact
Larger trends that they might be ignoring
Just so consistent across
All
Distorted media positive
I don't know why I don't spend the time focusing on those
I'm sure
Use on both sides
The persuasive argument
Easy game to play you sound like so like
Irrefutable whenever you pull out things like that
It's bad
Absolutely this is why I still want to know
What the OPP's
Weather in Major League
Sure it's unknown
He said they gave us like 38 home runs
Give me what is on-base
Yeah that's what I was really looking for no type of organ
Say Missy Football League you're going to play ever tells you what humble rating is
Bridges punch / fumble
It's a very crucial statistic to understand
Tells the whole story
/
Bumble Mark get on
Moreno Moreno
I didn't know he had control over that to make himself useful just like Greta shouldn't be going out of school
I like it
But you know what
The biggest problem
The biggest misconception
Course
I'm trying
Erupting like I do
Welcome to the
Club I guess you just deal with that Silent Night
You called me out on
Fair enough
I was going to let that one
Do you know what people are not
How great we are and how we don't need to do anything else
We're doing better in United States then these European sinus we're going to be at the UN Summit in New York shaming President Trump wear
Nobody ever points that out
Nobody
It's been pointed out a lot
Pointed out
Specifically
Scott Pruitt
Noted
Definitely not corrupt monster Scott Pruitt
In 2070
We are leaving the nation
Excuse
The world with respect to our CO2 footprint
Introduction
Another b*******
Cherry Picked
Because
What
He did
They are doing
Is they are
Judging
Differently
They are
About
The way that's
China-india both admit
More carbon
Right
Because they are
Then
Where is that a conspiracy
They're actually smart the Mercator Projection is actually right
People living in
And they were the ones
Right
Yes they are absolutely huge Carpenter
But
When you go by per capita
You find out that the US produces
16 1/2 metric ton
Per capita
Compared to China seven and a half
India
One point
Savage
So
Inaccurate fact that America has reduced admission
More
But in terms of what we're doing it is
Absolutely
Nothing
Like we went from in terms of reducing emissions
16.5 metric
When's was in 2040
Down by a little average
One-and-a-half
The 2%
Around that
Even as a whole I understand the point
That's all good
But like
Just other people aren't doing good doesn't mean
Instructional
No doesn't the didn't help anything
He's disingenuously trying to attack every possible counter argument
Argument here actually strengthen the counterargument
Feel like other people are doing worse
It kind of falls apart upon it any kind of inspection when you're not talking to her
Varney over here
And the Duke he is wrong
As a
In 2018
Almost directly due to
Trump's bulshit the EPA
Complete abdication of any moral responsibility
And so forth
Emissions rather than dropping Rose by the largest
Amount since 96
It was hell yeah
Are the second-largest
They Rose by 3.4 per
Effectively wiping out most of the
We are not leaving the
World
It is not happen
Ironic
In some ways
Timing timing base irony
He would have been fine
Here's here's a weird what I like this
This is very bad
Someone proposed of the UN climate treaty or the solution
Regulation Europeans are opposed to that challenge the science or look at the reason
Attract that
I couldn't look it up there a citation
Yeah
In America were like wait what
Europeans are more into Central planning and regulation
Therefore they don't question science
Right
I don't see the relation
No it doesn't
No I think you might have
Problem with that construction
Seems like the
Follow
If you trying to say that
You can use that argument for like everything
No take science out of the conclusion
Europeans are more into Central planning
Regulation therefore
They make more balloons
Sprite
You got it that's it that's an omni purpose
It's it's constructed the same way
That 90
Def Comedy Jam
Europeans be like this
Sure
Leading climate denial guy Lord monckton
Ford Mountain f****** parachuted into a year
Just to cause a big big publicity stunt
D.b. Cooper Rudolf Hess
But he doesn't have any military service
He's not a trick
How is it
That we
Lead the world
Fictitious I heard marks
Okay I'm I don't know I'm excited to learn
To technology and Innovation and then the troops truly to fracking
That's how we
Chiefly through fracking
Counterintuitive
And then never mentioned
Of course
Tracking
Again
Recitation of
In the world of Medicine
Because I have drawn the most blood from people
I like it
Robert
Cornell University
He does not believe
Improve
Commercialization of shale gas and oil
20%
Has dramatically increased
Listen
He continues on
Shale gas production in North America
Contributed
Half of all the increase
Methane emissions
From fossil fuels globally
Approximately one-third of the total in
Increased emissions
All source
Over the past
Yeah that's pretty universally
Promoting I've looked into
Like
Save it
Cracking great
Nope
Knowing
Absolutely know what for I guess there are certain people who are on like payroll
You know
I am covered Coronavirus
That is
Absolutely and utterly
Right to pretend
Even if you mistakenly
We are leading the world in protecting the climate and I know that cuz of all the trash we burn
We have Tire fires are height
How we protect the ozone layer
Like what
So there we go
Lowe's
No fracking does not
Not even not help it is
Utterly
Utterly destroy
Admission
Talk about pollution
The f****** destruction of the Earth
Like you name it fracking is one of the single worst
I've ever even saw
The same is true of like a cool fan
Anybody who presents that as being like a good alternative
All information is worth
The processing
Usable is
Heavily polluting
If there was even there was some sort of
Netflix
Net
Offset
Like even then if it was
Just like this tiniest little bit destroys the Earth but it's 1% better when you factor in all that s***
I know it is absolutely
And there's nothing that
Anybody has ever
If it were
People would be for it probably
Like if these Alternatives like anybody who's Into Climate Change activism or would have
If one of these Solutions
Actually did like let's say cut down 15%
Emissions
It profited boil companies
He would still be for it
They would not be paying Mark Marino's
They wouldn't eat
But again
One of our biggest
Obviously they are mercilessly mocking and being mean to
16 year old woman
Really is about
Is how much they care about protect
God Bless the Child
Different these kids are testifying before Congress saying they have no future unless we can essentially
Killed the market economy in the United States and impose essential plan on it that's what they're testifying
Talk to me the children
Yes into the amounts by
Adults
Yes
To have six
7%
The best
Back on
Today's that figures
They will not be any solution
Appliance
Placenta
Because these numbers are too uncomfortable
You are still not mature enough
To tell it like it is
I could see how an adult would like to hear
Haha
That's
Put those
Juxtapoz Ciara
Obviously
Right
But that really got to Varney
Got2b
Sure he doesn't like the idea that
These children are
Basically pointing out that you're a bunch of f****** chilled
He probably a good time to point out that there are not just read out there
Other activists
Maybe aren't getting as much attention as her that also deserve a good bit of like a
A shout-out
A tip of the cap every one of these every one of them across the
The world wasn't organized
Personally by Greta no
Every single one of those
Vitriol and praise is being directed at whereas
There are there are many more people
Who are coming out in that
You know being being very active in the
And I'll just climate-changing across-the-board
Terms
Social causes
They're a lot more people who are
That generation
That probably deserve a higher profile
Shout out to
I didn't prepare for this episode and I can't remember anybody off the top of my head
Cuz everybody's talking about Greta
Well let me know
Let me read you from the very mental health manual that I
From earlier
And I think that will be
The way that they
In some cases
Information that increases perceptions of the reality of climate
Denial
And that's a reduction in
Concern
Support for act
This is.
McDonald's
Communicating
This complexity itself may be a
One study showed that
Steve more complex information
Felt more helpless
And more inclined to leave the problem
To the government
And those who felt ignorant about the topic
Or more likely to want to avoid hearing about born
Okay
Exactly why they are
Talkin the way that they are
Making sure
Fat people are
Exactly
Because
Good morning
And also
Because the more helpless and more inclined
How real you feel about climate more likely you are to be in favor of Regulation and
Government
Yes and their stated
Life
They keep their audience ignorant about the topic
So they don't want to hear anymore
Negative adverb
Right they want to hear America is leading the world CO2
American is yours my warm car
Exactly
And they know it
And
Mark Moreno noses
Everybody who books him
No that's what he is going to do for
He is
Slimy
I hate him so much this episode get them to
Mix it up with this guy
I I just
But
Still further
This
It like
How many times
Has he been brazen
In his
Complete at Polaroid
Office episode very obvious
Very miserable
Non-stop flights
Pitter patter of
I cut the clip short so they're not as long as
The ones that you normally
Mainly because he speaks
Structural different conversation
Where is Alex's the long-form
Rambling
It's it's definitely like I just a function of
The Source material
These are obviously going to be shorter
Blurbs
I mean I could I could have put the Whole 30 seconds
Clipper
He's just such a unlike Alex where it's like he's got those
Rolling crescendos and then he break and then rolling
Moreno is just
Rapidfire monotone
Just like I'm before you even have a thought
I'm onto the next
Thank you sounds
Super credible through the
Quick
Make it sound like I know all these things and monotone certiflat delivery that you think that I'm
Emotionally delivering this information to you
So different presentation Style
But it is
But this one is this one's broke
It's for the kids
I was at the when she spoke for 11 minutes to symbolize 11 years
Until the planets dead unless
Legislate storms in weather
6 hours earlier in the day said she needs to do something f****** challenge
Slater
The message coming from someone who accompanied his parents to a Diane
Proof that the Iraq War when I was a younger guy
You know argument that that's going to traumatize and scare these opposite
Like I was younger V Zombie the Iraq War I was like 19 or 20 at the
I didn't have any kind of
Feeling of it is like
So Terror inducing in my own life that I can't suction it was like this is an expression of how severe this
Reality is that we are
Against
So I don't know
I don't I don't I don't find it to be compelling
That was an old man assuming the children don't have cognitive abilities
You got it yeah
Children
Cuz it's different it's Greta was five
Caressed
I will I will save it
We do not
And neither does anybody else
And if anybody has
Mark Marino anywhere near the
It is
Completely invalid
Invalidated
This one
Distance from
Something that Greta said
Which I find
Incredibly helpful
And I will see how it goes
You said you hear us
That you understand the urgency
No matter how sad
I do not want to believe that
Because if you really understood the situation
I'm still kept on saying
Evil
In fact I refuse to believe
Sure
She refuses to believe
But they are evil but I will tell you something
Mark Marino is
F****** evil
She wasn't talking to Mark Moreno
I disagree with her on
About or to him in this regard as well
I am also disagree with
Are you suggesting I'm not 100% sure where I land on that but I respect your opinion
I'm on the fence a little bit
In terms of that Call of Duty all the world leaders evil
AOL
Consider for a lot of world leaders that I don't I don't know where their head
I will tell you that their heads are not
Most recent IP
Because
Very long
People didn't actually
All of the
All of the articles
Stuff I read about it
Play problems
The guardian or anything
They were all
Kind of in this Middle Ground
And this is something
To be very very
You know that I have said to you many times in the past where
I suspect
That's
Scientist
Have always been climate scientist
Is the specialty of always been downplaying the
Actual
Severity of the
Forever
Incessantly
Yeah I thought that was something that
From a study by
Quotes
Over the past two decades
Two decades
Skeptics of the reality and significance of
Anthropogenic climate
Frequently accused
Alarmism
Of over interpreting or overreact
New evidence
However
The available evidence
And suggest that scientists have in fact
Conservative
Protection
Knox
Cautious
There is even a term that
Call it airing on the side of
Drama
Right but I still your conjecture
Thunder playing
Manipulating but I honestly don't approve
The stuff that you always help me
Low balling
The conservative estimates are different than
But be under playing the severity
I don't I don't think
I still don't think that matches with
Your suspicions
Well let's go vote of estimates versus
Extreme estimates
Iru I mean I understand
Okay
What I'm what I'm more talking about is the way that they present
The data
Because
Here is the
Here's some of the data in the eyepiece
This report
And this is all Based on data that goes up
220 50
It does not include 26
Obviously you can't put your
In the report
Our best-case scenario from the Paris
You keep warming 21-point
5 degrees
And the report says
No matter what
If we even if we reach
1.5 degrees C
Is as a
Hazard
Steve warm water
Coral
It's just gone
There's nothing we can do unless we go well below
1.5
That is not something that was in any of the reports
Any of the articles I read none of them said
No matter what we're losing Coral
Amazing
Beautiful
Exactly right
All of this stuff
Now what it doesn't include
Like I said the pass
Three or four years
One of the issue
They have a couple different projects
Is going on
They have the ones where we
And stay below 1.5
Very very
They are the ones who don't do anything
They just measure what it would be like
We stayed at the same
What they don't have
What it would be like
Continue sucking up
More
They couldn't imagine a scenario
Not only did we not just
Stay the same
Bright like Alex advocate
This this idea that idea of like 11 years we have 11 years from now
To adjust our actions and all that
Not act
We don't have 11 years
What because it's from the date of the end of 2015
So whatever we be talkin about we should have been talking about in 2015 where has this been 3 years 4 years
Since then
But
That number is not as as of
It is a g
Write two years
Active damage
Doesn't take us from 11 years left 29 years
I can't tell you I even then the projections aren't like
This is exactly accurate
Right it's like the 538 election Bridge
Where it's like 75
Percent chance that
Republicans
The same thing is true with climate refer
They can say
What they're telling us
There's a 60% chance that we have 11 years
To do all of
Yeah they don't say
There's a 40% chance we're already past but there is a significant
That were already past
And there's nothing that can be done
To keep us below one
To keep us at one point
So
Really
A frustrating
Text
This is a f******
Seriously
Dangerous and scary report
And it is amazing to me that it went
Spying like
One day there was a new cycle of this
This report that
It is
Amazing
What are the
What are the things that I love in the report
About
Governor
And how they're going to act on
This
There is no single climate governance
Panacea for the ocean
Empirical evidence on which governments
Arrangement
Which contacts
Still Limited
Good governor
Scare quotes
Norm's indicate the importance of
Deliberate
Reflective hoodie
Responsiveness
Social learning
The co-production of knowledge
And respect
Ethnic and culture
And the reason I like that
In there is
Does that mean
They have some Eco fascist that they were talking to
What
Instead
We had one guy do every
And they're like
There's some people who would read that ipcc report and go like
Democracy is a failed us
Baxter
So they specifically went out of their way to be like
We don't want anybody I know you might think it's a good idea and you're like
These sorts of things could be very
Dangerously used under the
The wrong
Absolutely
Here's another
Great pizza
Today
Just today
September or October 3rd
You got a report was really
From the guardian
Trump's attack
Science are at 8
Crisis points
Deny climate science
EPA from presenting research on
He's barred the Nash
Hill Park Service
Proposal
And he's actively published a misleading environmental review
To allow mining in
They have anybody
Who speaks out
Or points out how much
B******* science
But the thing that
Weird to me or not weird but
The Department of Agriculture actually moved
Acrostic
Country
When they published
Analysis of how
Fox farmers
Under Trump's proposal
The interior
Reassigned a climate
Counting roll
After you just pointed out
That climate change will be back
And just for the win
They suppress the report showing
Toxic substances several States lottery
Absolutely suck you up at far
Far lower levels
They actively abstract
Yeah little bit as a f*** you up
Basically and this has been done by all of the everybody
G w
Rhw
Absolutely
Devastation
Guys like Mark Moran
Sucking
Make everything
Thanks so much
They facilitate all the
You never ever need to listen to
If his name comes up
Just f****** go away it's really your thesis.
Ever again
If we're going to do a reverse knowledge fight we talk about the same guy over and over
If I'm going to do it I'm going to talk about a guy we never speak
Okay and I think Mark can explain
Don't understand how people can fall
Bass
Rhetoric nonsense
Yeah you hear that that's exact phenomenon from all these people so often is like expressing exact
This b*******
Salsa from 2014
Well that's a bummer
I don't know I mean
Brandon sucks
I don't know this subject matter nearly as well as you do it you know you're very busy
Singularly focused on in the same way that I am like
I don't know anti-communist propaganda so it's a little overwhelming
And I hope to have a lot of
Not geared to respond to things
It's a challenge but it's
Good job
You as well
No I went into this big Mark Marino Stockton now I am
Come out similar thing
You really
F****** hero
Absolutely
I know this was a little bit of a depressing ending
A little bit it's a little bit of a bummer and I don't want to leave people with like a sensitive glue
You know
You might have
No it's not it's not a little bit because
People like Mark Marino attack
Greta you know that
The reason isn't
It doesn't work because there are so many solutions
I worried that the way you frame
Does lead to anxiety because of the
That the climate scientist from the ipcc report
They're under playing the reality of this underplaying the severity of it
It does lead to possibility that the conclusion is there is nothing that can be done
Sort of a fatalistic we're f*** no matter what we do kind of stay
And I know that that's not your message and I know that that's not what you believe we should do anything cuz we're already f*****
To come away from
If you're not super clear get that impression I never want to give that message
Because even if that's true I don't like
That perception were true
It's irresponsible thing to
Here is here is why
Did that and it's mainly because
Severe mental health
Separate
That was there
Which stated
The more people know about it
The more they understand what it is
The more likely they are to accept government
To make me action
Protest just need to protest
I'm out of office and get new people into a responsive and understands the situation
I think there's four
People about reality and
You know pollution and its effects
Bratwurst
Yeah cause aspect that we should do
That people being wore read up on
Lead people to what that Mental Health Report is talking about
That is
Realizing the government needs to do more
Everything is way under selling it
I don't think that people to recognizing that the government needs to do more
Regulation is necessary
That could probably lead to people having a crippling
Inability to act
You're doing that
Part of that
While I do agree that it is important to stress to
Folks that this is not
Business as usual there is a crisis going on
I think
Viewing it in a
No matter what happens we're f*** I think it's detrimental and it doesn't leave
To the effect
But that Mental Health Report
I just want to I want to fight back against any kind of
Gloom
I thought I might even be feeling a tiny bit towards the end
I suppose I suppose the main thing that I
I suppose the main thing that I want
Is for people to realize
Is that this is not
This is not a future
This is
Serious
Right now right
That's why I get so angry when I read an article
Whatever
As I know this is
Now
This is we got
Do that
We got a
Well we need to get people to
Direct action and
If we don't do this by 12 years from now
Going to be really trouble
If we don't do this you know and then
Where the
That's pretty soon that's in your lifetime
I mean
Chicken Little linguine
This guy is
I get you anything there's a balancing act to it which is one of the most difficult things about it because
There is the immediate
Especially when you consider the experience of like the people in India
Or the people in places that are experiencing drought
For the people of the sea ice
It is an immediate thing for a lot of people and we are slightly privilege
Position that we can look at it abstract
Cutting through that to make it an immediate
Issue
Is important
At the same time
Finding a way to do without
The fatalistic Doom
The part that threatening about people like Greta these other younger
Climate activists as I think they're effectively able to do that
They're effectively able to walk that balance of
This is severely important right now
And this is what we need to do right now
Without
Falling into traps of hopelessness and Gloom
Little England is not necessary to make something immediate
I mean
I suppose you also
The people who are
You know that always that gets
What do clapping
Not understand
No like there's 100 reasons
Wasn't like the whole audience claps
People who were
With her in her group
You know that you don't know who was classified into it a lot of different
Scenario it's delusional people don't understand
Cheering section who was along for
The speech
There's a lot of
I don't know
There's a lot of assumptions that could be made
IHOP
It's just so
And you're absolutely right that she can thread the needle
Again
There's a reason
Absolutely
Play that's what makes her so threatening
Because if it was me
Effective messenger for this
Probably
Well I mean on a grander stage I would have gotten to tell them
That they're big dumb dumb
And that would have been very satisfied that is true when you get to town
United Nations ready to cut the US stick off or something
So I mean I guess I think
You know
Just have to you have to treat it like
Like you're saying
Immediate right now kind of situation
We also have to look at actionable items you have to look at
Productive
Solutions
As opposed to coming to
Ideas that there's nothing to do
I agree with you it's such a balance
I can see that that is important
That balance
But I do not know what the
To
Mark Moreno
Never use single-use
Utensils
Ever
A long way
Because single-use utensils are one of the hugest
Largest contributor
Factors to all of the plastic
Pollution
And all you have to do right now is never use that f****** through trying to put those good Americans at the sports Factory
Out of a job
Bring the sparks in
Justice
Spike that piece of s***
Fatalistic
Spite
Against
Perfectly
Bring your own Utah
I mean it
So
I think we have a website
I suppose that makes me
What am I
Dgx-500 I'll tell you who I am
That's who I am
Holding
Alex