Air Jordan 5 sweat it
I have great respect for knowledge babe I'm sick of them posing as if through the good guy
Monica
College vype.com
Hey everybody
Chuck about
Alex
Surname Jones
Words are
What's going on
Good
Quick question
Last thing you volunteered
I volunteered to do the show on Friday
I do not respect this very rude of you to a reception but not actually
Accurate anyway I was thrilled
Enjoyed it
I don't know the last time I fall in
Yeah I need to do more of that I'm very busy
Spirit like
Food pantry
Younger but you know
Yeah it's tough
Or
To unionize the movies
Theatre that I worked at and it's when I was like 17 and they're like you will be fired immediately
I don't understand the ramifications
So okay
I will not do that
Trucking
Those are not Crossing picket lines
No I wouldn't cross
No I would
Strike with
People if I were in it
Situation to
The end of jobs at
You know
With had strike capability situation we found ourselves in
And I would join a
Zacian effort
If I were
Situation not a 70
Cedros working
A minimum wage
You ready Hero 2
I don't know what it would have done because there was I don't think they're actually was
Concessionist
Yeah but the union is I understood it back then
And was mostly for the people who run like
Large
Projector like the ones that are at
I'd like IMAX
L
There are some projectors that are still like
Fairlead
Those are the ones that like glorious
That kind of
We were working with brother there was still actual film
Specialized work
You still pretty dip
Ghost-type
It wasn't nearly the level of
I don't know I was I was
Vinegar and thought I was
It probably would have been
I guess I don't know enough about volunteering probably should do more about that I'm going to write that down
I do have a little bit of time I probably should if I'm going to put it anywhere I probably should
Explore those are
I only know what you that's for sure
I'm so Jordan today we're back in 2013 we're looking at
The Boston bombing
Continue with our exploration of Alex's coverage after say
Hook
On our last episode we went over the day off
Today we are just going over April 7th
That means
There is a lot
In fact it's pressing
My wife
I don't think very far off
Today's episode
Completely insane
Take us
Places I never
Expected Define
Course
Things that have nothing to do with a lot of things that I thought I was looking for
I got to give a shout out to
Are supporting the show
So first of all Drew thank you so much you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Ewok
Is that big body bes
What does that mean
Hilarious
Everybody back
Alright text Tyler
Is that Tyler the Creator Chris conspiracy
It's Chris.
Thank you so much
Journal policy walk
Is that A Little Priest
Is that a one word
It's
Yeah
I don't know maybe it's a means of someone throwing a nose
I have no idea
Didn't want to be old
Yeah
A couple people signed up on little bit of an elevated level
So first of all
That's one
And monkey Nexus Overdrive
You are now a technocrat
Heroin
Is freakishly large
Unbutton and Oggy
And the monkey Nexus Overdrive
Surprised we haven't got
Supercross
Considering everybody knows what
Newsradio
That is true
51 day
Sweet Day
Coming up on 25 years old
Paquin Joe Rogan wizard
Back what it was on the a.m.
Back when Andy Dick was employable.
Blackboard
Phil Hartman was alive
April 17th
Crazy crazy day
Stuff going on
Dramatic
Breakdown of the world
To set the stage for I do I want to point something out episode
Alex Jones
Has a catch
He is saying that everything is unprecedented
Over and over and over again
Seems like almost an intention
And here's a Supercut of him saying
This is impressive
Unprecedented
Precedent
I'm not certain I got all of them
At least
I'm pretty I'm pretty sure I missed
Some of them
Quite frankly
He's a real f*****-up headspace unprecedented
What's going on
We think that everything is
I mean what he's doing is lying a strong precedent for that so
I don't support real into this
I want to just like
Llamas in studio last week
Tricked by that
Like all the people who were posting like screenshots of Alex with llamas even if you're making fun of him
If you listen to the video of that
He's talking about how this is going to amplify his rating
In the middle of having llamas in studio he's talking about like
I want one
It's just you're all amplifying exactly like
Yeah individuals who might have enjoyed the tweet
People putting out or anything like that
I don't know how much it is
To mock him
For it if you're hyper
Profile account
You wanted
You gave him free publicity
See how likes
Though some of these
Making it go viral putting it out there
Even the memes of him with a llama like
You could f*** around and accidentally give him like
Tens of thousands of dollars
A free traffic
Website could translate
Into
Sales like it
Whatever he was doing is pathetic and sad
The desperate attempt
To get attention but it worked
We're not going to be covering
Event to say
Congratulations Alex
Poke
He's not a level regular
His desk in like in between him and the camera is a llama just
Chewy
Betty White
Donovan
All right otherwise episode factor in manipulate headline
Comment the Guy episode in order
Defend this feeling that the meeting would blame Patriots
Quotes
For the Boston Bomber
We saw him start to craft this narrative in the literal minute
After he became aware of
The tragedy
Haven't discussed on that last episode by the time you get off air on the 6th
There was not a lot of information available about what it happen
Other than
The obvious
The FBI and police were following up on
Investigating
But if confirmed there was very little to go on
It has been announced that the bombs were pressure cookers
It has been announced that the reports of a Saudi national who is detained
We're possibly misleading
Was not involved in
Beyond that there wasn't much
As we begin on the 17th
There's still not a whole lot of credible information
It's being reported
By the end of the day was reported the FBI had an image of a
Potential suspect who was he carrying a backpack and dropping it off in the area of
Second Bob
That that happens by the end
But they did not release
That image
April 17th is a very important day in the Fallout of the bomb
We had reached an out two full days after the attack and
Still there was a lack of credible information about who did it why they did it
And any real indication
But the authorities were any closer to making the rest
Then they were 24 hours prior
In this environment of outrageous
Very critical things
The first was that
The Silence of information with
Overwhelmed by the growing volume
Baseless speculation
Bulshit
Coming out of alternative
Well it stopped short of credible Outlets
Repeating internet rumors
People were reaching a point where they needed answer
When the mainstream isn't providing them they started to look out
People got a lot of traffic
Out of
Baseless conjecture
Surrounding
It's a fun little
It doesn't matter who you are
Hardwired
I need to make
Something is amiss
And no matter how many times you tell yourself like investigators
Detectives were working on this no more
Can't put that information
Out because it might ruin the possibility of them being able to carry through the investigation
You can't
Tell your brain doesn't allow you to accept
They went people are
Willing to give you the wrong answer
You'll gravitate towards that
Now that's one element that's happening it.
These
The noise
Of their alternative
Folk on places
Reddit 4chan
Putting out these Radiohead
Shirk's
Putting out this bogus nonsense it starts to amplify
Considerably
On the 7th
I'm saying is that well the alternate alternative media
Please downtown blog
They Were Striking while the iron was hot
Drawing in math
Massive amounts of attention for people who just beat
Something anything
Anything at all
Same time
The main
Medium
Critical error
And their drive to be the first to report
We'll go over some of that as we go along but both group
The alternative media and the mainstream media were driven by the same
To be the first Outlet to report important information about a major story
And the results were
Disastrous
By the time Alex gets off are on the 17
We're no closer.
Really NE
Gabriel
The FBI is announced by that point they have a photo of the suspect
They still haven't released it
However while the real world public is no closer to knowing what happened
At the marathon by this point
The same cannot be said for Alex
In this episode will see
Is certainty that the bombing was a false flag
What you determined
In second
And over the course of his broadcast
He'll transform it into so much more
He'll find the people he decides to the culprits
He'll point out privates
She's decided of the Patsy
The globalist
Going to pin the bombing on
He'll discover the motive for the bombing
He's likely party to the commission of a federal offense on a
Everyday in the stretch
The 2013 that we're on right now is not
I thought that the bombing would be the worst of it and I was
Shocked at how much are the mods
Pastor Alex Wells
15th and C
But I'm comfortable saying that he outdoes
Himself
Considerable margin
He's legitimately the worst
I can think of very few things you could be doing at this point that would be worse
Then what he's conscious
Wesley and willingly doing
Writing the Boston bombing
It's unprecedented levels of monstrosity.
Resident
At the beginning of the episode Alex
Because they think they're talking
Idiot
Alex Jones
Know everything
Audience of emotional
Watching football in
Percent
I'm here and I'm working around the clock
Coasttocoastam
I slept for two hours I didn't our place this morning
So now we can add coasttocoastam
Alex Jones
Disseminating
10th time
I would feel that everybody
To get ratings
By throwing Alex
On your Shelby
You're you're being very
I thought that
Reproach dad
Hey let's get Lewis
How to make slime
Yeah yeah
Detroit becoming the fourth our house.
Was one of the 4th hour
Set up his own studio and all that
He also
4th H Alex
So that kind of makes
Everything
But
It should be pointed up at that point worth
Popular radio show
Hayward
The comics by deji
Further spread
Odysseus respond
Possible horrible ship
EXO
They should probably
Like really feel the same
George Noory
Even if we're not going over the episodes with that they're on
Alex is on those shows
Just know that you're helping this get out
Alex believes that all the media all they're doing is
Demonizing
We saw
Basalt
His number one talk
Compliant
And of course
Everything about the rollout
Flip
Michael Moore Christmas special on
The Boston Marathon bomber
White person officials
Boston bombing terrorist
So I guess Michael Moore speaks for the entirety of the the
Which is consistent in Alex's career
Take a comment by Michael Moore and that's what everybody everybody
You know what take a comment by Bill Maher and then you've got the
Flavor of the nation dinner
Officials
The same thing we went over on the last step
So you don't need to go into that
But this article is new
Boston Marathon bomber is a white American
That is a real headline
However
Alex is not gay
To that article
At all
That piece was written by David Sirota and his overarching point
Is it the identity of the perpetrator of the bombing of the American government respond
And the best-case scenario for World Peace
Is that it turns out
Away Tamara
Right
From the article
The terrorist attack
Search white male privilege
White non Islamic terrorist
Are typically portrayed as representative
Not a whole groups and ideology
But Islam will threats to be dealt with as isolated law
Meanwhile non-white or developing World terrorism
Reflexively portrayed as representative
Spiritzys ideologies and religion
It must be dealt with a systemic
Text Brett
The kind of potentially requiring everything from law enforcement action
Into military operations
Civil liberties Legend
Relation to foreign policy
Sirota goes on to argue that regardless of your political party affiliation
If you care about everything
From Star Wars
Reducing the defense budget
Protecting civil liberties
Immigration reform
You should hope the bomber was a white domestic Terror
Why
Because only in that case we'll privilege worked
Prevent the Boston
Send a text from
Eventually undermining progress
On those other
That's a pretty
Find
Liberals everkin
Considered
Taking over
DHHS
And ice
From the inside
We're always against
Why don't we take over DHHS and then
Terrorist
I don't know
I mean I think they attempt
Pickover
Internally attempts have been made
Put that Focus
On
The actual threat
What happened
Report came out like a right-wing
If your
Fury outrage
Listen
See now that's
Interesting
We start shooting cops
I don't know I don't know what the effect
Not listening
Going to that backlash
I know what
People like Alex
Chinese militia weirdos I know what their rhetoric
Indicate
It would be
But I don't know how much they worth
Yeah that would be
Tire possibility that it's all talk
Longwood
But also
The flip side
I don't think
People are making their
Policy decision
Solely on
Fear of the threat
Biosphere right wing-back
Why we got to
Obamacare
Listening to the right-wing
They turned out well
Sure
That article was published
Pointe on Rio
O'Reilly about it
Fox contributor they were all talking about it and I'll talking head shows
And it's nothing
Up in arms about
In response to Roda Roda follow-up title quote I still hope the Boston are the bomber is a white American
Where you pointed out that
Even when complaining about his Salon article O'Reilly
Same premise that the articles
Muslim terrorists and the reaction would be severe
American Terrorist
Then it will just
Quote be another stain on American
That's from O'Reilly.
This is really basic stuff
Zerodha wasn't saying it was awakened
He was just pointing out that the double standard that exists about how the public
And the government
Response to tragedies
And how if the bomber is quotes
The double-standard May prevent an overreaction
Boston
You can make a pretty decent argument that this article could come off
A little
Considering the timing
Babies
Still in the State of Shock and
I'd be willing to hear those criticize
I don't know how
They are but I think they're valid
Complained
However I don't think that I can find too much in the subs
So his point that I can say
Take issue with
Ultimately big picture and most importantly
This article in no way strengthens Alex's argument that the media is blaming right-wing
Go to music
Is absolutely out of line with what the article a
The article literally States we won't
What's blame right wing
History
History has shown that that's not the response
Initially I thought the official
I initially thought that was actually just the same
I think we talked about
Last episode because it's very
5-second actually look into
Is a headline
Written by Paul Joseph
So it's not
Really
Yeah yeah yeah
In the article Boston
Certainly
Just lorious was talking about a video they had of the suspect and said quote
The person who did this was someone's friend
The neighbor and co-worker
Which Paul says is ruling out the possibility that the attack
We carried out by foreigners who had
Great work dude my responsibilities as a they ruled out that the attack was carried out by a foreign group
It might rule out the idea that the terrorists just showed up and did the attack
Talk two days later solutely does not exclude people like
Could be
Here for awhile headed out
You know here for awhile
Any of this could be a possibility that is not excluded by the
Reasoning is incredibly shity but that's Paul for the course
Don't ever look at me in the eyes
Hello
The rest of the evidence Paul has his quotes from noted media Darlings
What my favorite member of Congress
I actually don't like him much but he has the best name
And Dutch ruppersberger
Vacations
Domestic terrorism
Neither of them say it was a right-wing
Extremist
Suggest was a patriot group
Just that it would be a domestic
Group
Profile low
The weapons used
It could have been eco-terrorists
Indications
And that
Is being taken to me in Bible
Also this article includes
Cheats for Michael Moore
The king of
The media
Jay Mohr
Which is to say
Who cares
Perfectly fine
For his
18 years ago
The best Paul has other than that
The tweet from an unofficial Twitter account run by someone who works
U.s. Forest Service they're afraid it's a right-wing nut
This
Does not Merit an article
Intermediate we're really trying to pay
The picture that this was done by right-wingers in order to demonize the Patriots
Paul would have way stronger evidence than boars Twitter
This is a perfect example of Alex editorial
Decision but the narrative is that the media
Patriots and then go out and find
We can't defend the narrative
No other explanation makes sense
Why would it be this pain
Why would the evidence you have
Scattershot
Saxby chambliss
Investigate something but you already know the answer
Ignore everything
Except
Singers be like I'm going to set out to
Approve this with my man on the
I'm already
That's all they're doing that's all this article is
It's really insane
So
Alex has
You know
Really dumb
Right
I think we've established
Realize that
He was a jerk
No
He's not
Well you haven't heard this next
Also studied a lot of criminology and I do mean murder mystery books
Fascinating
Criminals Act
And they are pathological
Over and over and over and over again
I honestly think you might be talking about,
Like I have a little bit of a Batman seal from the
Alex
Do you know I love that he's sitting here saying like I read pH
Bi-level Tech
Textbooks has the most 101 you get from any like
Homicide
TV show any kind of like True Crime stuff
If they say their next president
Say there an expert in everything
F*** off you're a psychopath
Why do we even have the psychopath test just ask Brooks
How many things
Send it I'll just bring the box to the Box
Because
He believes that everything that's happening surrounding Boston bombing
Follows the exact
Same
Pattern
That has happened with all the other false Flags
So
He is now
Buc-ee's
These things that are happening
The world he's connecting them all to
Together
In the same way that after 9/11 there was those anthrax
Letters
Ragazza
Right after the Boston bombing there were ricin letters that got sent to Obama
Alex has decided that he
He predicted this
This time I should look at another bio attack if this is an inside job
Obama a senator have reportedly been met mail dries in now so either you
Hugo
It's perfect
Evidence
Alex cell
Alexandrite
I want to be totally clear
I don't recall Alex saying there will be a bio attack if it's
Is a false flag
In the episodes I've listened to I don't remember him saying that
He would say I have no evidence
Did predict
But I would believe he was free associating on the Nightly News.
It's a possibility but I do not have evidence
Either way
Matter cuz I was just full of s***
On April 16th 2013 letters laced
Ricin were sent to President Obama Mississippi Senator Rodger wicker
And a judge
Mississippi
Address in Tennessee
And because there was just a giant bombing in Boston
A lot of people made a hasty
Poisonous
But guess what they were not
And this is one of the crazy
Stories that I will ever tell you
You know you got a lot of axes to grind
You know the story behind
S*** out of me to do all this already
Not the only thing
Because we have a
Missouri represent
Mississippi representative
Personal
Because I've never heard of that
Sippy
Police arrested Paul Curtis
And investigators immediately were sent down a completely insane rabbit hole
There's power
Recommend a lot of information
Comes from other sources other news articles about that
A lot of it also from this
I recommend
It cannot do justice
Do all the layers of completed
Now you got arrested
Two first name
You got the guy who's right
Two Street
We know who we can trust here Dan this makes perfect
Except
The police arrest code is for the crime
That he does not know anything about the crime
So they asked him if he has any enemies who might want to try and set him up
And he immediately respond that there is one guy
James Everett dutschke
Who fits that description
Courtesy of gender by profession and an Elvis impersonator by Passion
Him and his brother did a Duo act younger Elvis and the other was Vegas outfits
Perform together
The media really latched onto that when Curtis was arrested arrested
Overshadowed a lot of the story
The clown on the weekend they be like
REI
He landed a contract to clean the floors northern Mississippi Medical
I threw some weird coincidence
He ended up in the board one day and saw a body parts that really freaked him out
He wasn't authorized to be in the morgue
He was reprimanded for being there
Punishment for him seeing body parts he wasn't supposed to
Curtis Melda conspiracy
Stumbled into a black market organ harvesting operation
That's the first thing I would say
Absolute
So he started pursuing this conspiracy theory
And naturally this led to his life
He began to drink heavily his marriage fell apart
And all of this only only led to him pursuing his
Conspiracy interest further
He started disseminate messages about his theories online
Like my space at the time
Tagline
Quote I am KC and I approve this message
James Everett dutschke was a local insurance sales
Man who was also in a local band called Robo drum
Which describes itself as quote Progressive guitar funktronic everyone in this story is played by Robin
Good Williams everything is insect
More importantly here an alternative newspaper in
When Curtis heard about this newspaper he was sure that this was going to be able to
To get his message out about the or organ harvesting
Cost of Dusky at a party
Cuz dutschke work
With Curtis
Ex-wife in an insurance company
Glad company party he came along and confronted
Responded to his email and asked him
Big scoop
However
Dutschke was not interested
The middle of trying to run for public
WIC office
I need felt a story like this
What her is effort
Get elected
Would you end up
The story could have solved
A lot of problem
Curtis decided in a fraud
Relationship it started off
Very sour
Dusky lost his bid for office
And completely insane online Feud
I were they both
Accused each other of stock
And other both probably right
Spy versus spy cartoon
This entire circle
I'd like to think it's really awesome as if you read this GQ article they talked to like Curtis
Text wifey
You guys have so much in common
You guys should be friends
Because the one person that everyone hates the mostest
Identical
People who want to be
Performers better also crazy
It's not
Since the 90 days
Bryndis
Exposure
He would stand
Is he would stand naked his window and use a laser pointer to attract the attention of passing toolkit
Big Sean
Big time
I would agree
In the process of him trying to appeal this conviction
Music touching three underage girls
The martial arts
Studio that he ran
Naturally
After this
Curtis started gloating about his rival being arrested online which
Really pissed off.
Long story short
Dutschke decided to frame Curtis by sending letters with ricin
Addendum to the Mississippi Senator Obama
Typically hits sentence
Kurdistan
Six months in jail prior
Alright alright
So so far
We've all been doing well
Plan
Comes a little bit out of left
I'm just I'm not saying I wouldn't have expected
Escalated
Baby Alive
Well some people who suspect
To prison for
These underage girls
He could get
I have your sentence in a different
Facility
If
He got caught trying to do this clunky
The frame-up job and it was actually effort to not be put in prison primarily as a pedophile
Text to Matt reminders
Witness lyrics you're giving the guy who is in an online
With an Elvis impersonator who thinks that
There's an underground
Black Market Oregon
You're giving that guy from prison
Like
Keyser Soze
Find much
Credence to that but then
Like all of it is explained by
These guys be an idiot
But the real one of the reasons of people
Suspect that he was trying to
Caught is the heat included Curtis's tagline
Quote I am KC and I approve
This message on the letters that he sent it was an incredibly funky frame-up job
If you
Exclude Curtis
Haven't done that he's the only person
Possible person
So it is
Clunky but also if you're just
Kind of dumb
He seems like he might be
It is the sort of thing at work
See look I signed it with his
Of course they're going to
2014 used 25 years in prison
Very clear
Nothing to do with the Boston butt if you don't look at information
The Paradox sensationalist b******* because
Feel like something is
You'll end up sitting
It's not related
It does
Lately insane story behind world is very big
Don't have full information
Can you go off half-cocked
You miss the forest for the trees
If he had correctly predicted that an Elvis impersonator and
Insurance
Would get into a fight that would lead to sending ricin
The president
He says forever
And it's really tough to imagine they're like You could argue that this way
It was a false flag
Depended on these days
Elaborate
Set up got this in the bag in the bank for 20 years
He was stumbling organism
Something
But you know what's even crazier
In May 2013
Someone else
That was also a plot to set someone up
In that case
Shannon Richardson
Who was an actress in The Walking Dead
Was going through a divorce
So she decided to frame her husband
By sending rice
That just makes
Too much sense
It does
With the Elvis impersonator
But this also
People just
Thundaga president
Trouble
It does have a certain
Whimsical Flair to it
You know like a like a romance novel kind of
Situation
Love that story
I'm glad no one got hurt
Dutch
She cooked up was so impotent
Even if Obama had open the letter u
Like the judge did open the letter
But the story of this guy stumbling into a borg Vicky's found a conspiracy
Story creator
It's unfortunate that it has to get into the public exposure and JoJo molestation
I wish that wasn't part of this plan
Otherwise the human Insanity that's behind this
This is so
It's an amazing story
Stop
Cause and effect
It's our belief
State if you have a
A story that begins with
The janitor went into the morgue
And you
Consent of the president
Time as the Boston bombing like that is so we're outside of time
Time it. It's a that's what it is
Everything has been done and will be done
And is being done.
The world is big
There's a lot of people in it a lot of them have agendas
Situations
They're going
Through that
They are not immediately apparent
Answer when you see a story like there's rice in letters sent
President
To assume
That you know everything about it with that nothing about
And Alex knows nothing about
But you've decided it's very important to include
In his narrative
Do you have
Rodger wicker
Has happened to Corey
Recorded
The guardian reported that the Senate voted against a background check
54 to 40
Whatever plot there was Congressman to follow guidelines
On this very same day
April 7th
The Atlantic ran a story about this gun control measure
Being shot
Senator Rodger wicker gloated in real time
Wicker Then followed up with a press release going into detail about his decision
And yelping
Familiar
I have not and will not
Support or undermine the Constitution Second
What amendment protects
What was his NRA voting record
Doors for like
You're more left-leaning bar
Civil
Right
I suspected Alex's misunderstanding vote from April 11th
In order to build up his case that he was on the fence
Cuz it's voted yet about this legislation
But he wasn't holding on
On the bill
He was a cloture vote his gave up was
Debate and I'll put the measure up to a formal vote
Since a lot of Republicans were trying to hold a filibuster in
This could be seen as
Some form of support for
For the belt
Republicans voted exact
None of them got letters
Because they wanted message
Mississippi the target of this crazy.
Mississippi and the
The president is like
Small-scale attacks I don't know if Alex is just intentionally leaving out the judge
Or if he has
Become aware of that I'm not sure exactly what the
The situation is important
Discover it
Other voters who voted not have
The filibuster
Put this up to a vote
The 16 other Republican
15 other Republic
They didn't get lighter
Gun legislation because of it
Alex's just creating a
Completely alter
Reality for his audience
Delivered where everything is connected
It's all an elaborate plan to deprive him of his gun
It's manipulative
I didn't saying how profitable
Yeah yeah
I think
I think it's great that
Good job
Telophase
The 16th one of his major pieces of information
It was the Family Guy clip that manipulative
Nope episode make it appear from
Different parts of the same episode
Peter Griffin
At the Boston Marathon
Very inaccurate
Manipulative editing of the episode.
By the 17th
People were saying
You guys are pulling a hoax
Yeah because
And Alex is still pushing the Family Guy
And also if you listen to this clip its
It's really interesting how he's creating a
Strawman out of the
Complained
About his cover
Of the episode
Marathon
Narrative
Remotely
No one sent me episode isn't real
Some people did have a misunderstanding from what I
Two different ships
Is
Different episode
The way Family Guy works
Is there so many non sequitur jokes
Completely unrelated to anything else
And that's what is being represented
The beginning of the episode
A flashback
Combined with
The culmination of the main
Simplot
And that is just
It you might as well be using two different episodes
Episode and whatever
When is intention
Understanding
That are being used against him
Exist
No
People are saying
That you are misleading people into thinking
Did the episode included Peter bombing the marathon
And there's only one reason
Do do
Why in
This time.
Before we have any
That people would
Even engage
With this whole family
It's a cuz everybody's on kind of a high alert
Situation
Everybody is
Trying to fill the
The blanks in
And so naturally
There's going to be
Hoaxes and
Incredible
I hope this
At all
But now
Just can't help it
Shut the fuk
The Family Guy
A lot of traffic and
Predicted 9/11
Spider-Man trailer for Spider-Man at the Twin Towers
The people's mind when you're trying to make
The idea that this existed in media before
Or whatever
Fold the dollar bill right now
Hit some sort of lizard brain
It's kind of a hijacking
Your base brain
I understand popular I get why Alex
Brilliant
If you are dealing with things in a real way he would deal with the actual criticism
These are different parts of the episode
We put out made here
Peter uses a phone to detonate bombs at the marathon
That's not in the episode
But isn't it strange
Set the Boston Marathon
And a bombing exist
The same epi
Episode of Family Guy
It would be diminishing returns
It is a little weird
He needs to lie in order to make it
By itself that behavior
Isn't dictative of dishonest
So
The Homer
Quote
Evergreen
Just cuz I don't care doesn't mean I don't
I think about that quote
Doesn't care about the truth
So
This that splah
Alex starts
To how like
To Boston
He started yelling false flag
Alex
Still running on me
Idea that the
The governor
Patrick
Ended the press conference after he got confronted in
Dislike
The guy who got caught with his hand in the cookie jar
Alex starts telling a little story from his
Pass okay
To this story
And recognize
First of all
This probably isn't
But second
If it is it indicates
A complete disrespected
Disregard for the truth
Has lingered in Alex's career
I just imagined Alex and
Yep liqueando real
Cable system over there
TV shows anymore
And it was on the only cases were people on the the fraud what is going on everywhere
Just because I was willing to go in
He's bluffing
A man into prison okay
Even if true
You suck
So it is true the John Villarreal a former Austin
Community TV manager
7 years in prison
For embezzling
That is definitely
Alex
I'm not sure I can find any evidence that Alex
To do with the arrest investigation or even
This very easily could be a case of Alex taking credit for being the truth-teller about something
Long after the events already
Transpired
I seen a bit of that
Yep however
Get to the bottom of this
I stumbled into an archive of media clipping
Things from the Austin chronic
Many of them
His time at the office
TV station
Portrait of Alex's early days
This has nothing to do with John Villarreal by accident
Some stuff that I think is
So there's an article about a bunch of suspicious
Does related to the firing
Other Act
View host who had issues
With Alex
Okay
Without
Cuz it's such a mysterious complaints that ended up getting lodged against them for what's called
Commercialism
Which isn't allowed on the station
Buzz Marketing
Alex denied filing the complaint
But some people were not so sure
That article includes a little story about Alex
There's another hosted AC
TTV name Christian
Suicide hanging
This person had a bit of a beef with Alex
He barely attended a rally that Alex was holding to counter his rhetoric
Your Christian went to
Counter Alice's rhetoric
And when he arrives home he got a call from a detective
Accused
Stalking
Just for showing up to a rally that I was older
What else was fired from kjfk he was
Considering filing a wrong
Termination lawsuit again
Station
He went so far as to have hockey
Depose
Because you suspected that monkey had been involved in
You can't keep saying honky
This didn't turn into anything but would later Almost Do It
After he
Email
Was fired because he was an immature little punk
Who cries until he gets his way
Yeah that's
Picture of Alex trying to use
Lawfare
Against people in this
Early career people who
He refuted with
Fire.
McAllen
How much is football not entirely sure but these people
Like
They're pretty insistent that this
This level of
Multiple people getting fired for tax
Complaints about commercialism
Suspicious
I know the answer
I can't really show my work
But they're still
These clippings Jordan
There's a letter to the editor from
From July 2000
We're at from someone who rebuilt Chapel at Mount Carmel
For the Branch Davidian
Alex was involved in getting the building restored in charge of the memorial event
Do you remember the Alex one of the biggest things
It is early career building of the Branch Davidian
You made a giant himself
Going out advocating
For this
He's always
So about Waco
Championing
Before these people
So what are the ministers twelve-year-old daughter
Celebratory dance
For that Memorial event
To the editor
Even Angels were moved by Angie performance
During the white chiffon dress with gold trim that floated in the air
He was a gift from Heaven that afternoon
Alex gave her last
Place on the agenda around 4 p.m. after most ever wanted last
Including the media
Earlier that Memorial Day I heard Alex tell Angie's father that there was no time
I watched tears come to Charles's eyes
How is he going to tell his beloved daughter there was no time to
To give the gift
He hurried out of the chapel
There was time for Alex
Describe hatred and vent
But there was no time for Angie's dance
No time for beauty
To the people that he was
Supposedly
Yeah that's the amount of consideration
He gave
Turn this event into being about him
Read of this
This child dude come up with an interpretive dance
No not so much like Alex
Yeah I mean I get that but also I tried to dunk
Give a s*** about that
ICare with a twelve-year-old
There's a difference
Opinion
I understand that but you know how much it would mean
People
You know folks who are rebuilding in line with what Alex was
Trying to bring
The center
Of this as opposed to Alex screaming about the government
And all this s***
Stump speech
Each for himself a publicity stunt
For his own industry and his own business
Not understand
The Branch Davidian
In reality
None of that is important
What is important is Alec prioritizing himself
Over the people that you supposedly
They're too high
And so it turns out that's been the case
For very long time
Aldi's archives Alex had anything to do with John Via Real skate
Bye 2006
When this all went down Alex's wellpath
Information that's available
It seems like someone
Buddha talks about it right now
Like all the people who were
Working at the station
Who come out and talk about how big
The s*** Alex was all that
Someone would have mentioned that he was involved in cracking the case open by barging into a meeting and blasing everybody
Accusations of malfeasance
I rate this story total b*******
You can't prove it
But it doesn't make
Yeah
So
If you get back to Alex talking about the boss
Ebonics
And
In this club he talks about how
He knew all
All along
Everything
Like he's predicted all this you predicted the ricin letters
None of this seems to actually be the case
But you calling all of his prediction
Correct
Motorcycles
Around the corner
Before
It could be
Come flying over Alex's trying to buzz Market that goose game
Backup app
Yeah the Untitled Goose game
You're calling a man
Tired
Did you just
Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo
Yeah
When do the Boston bombing is the balrog
As far as I know like I said I have no indication that Alex this is a false flag they would release of Iowa
He repeatedly predicted that the global still going to Nuke Chicago
That was pretty
Inconsistent
But I don't recall hearing this prediction
At all
Father you say
I suspect that he didn't make his predict
Mostly because of this
That we just heard
Alex absolutely did not say on his show that they would wait a few days while they figure out which Patsy
Now did he turn Lisa
Absolutely did not say anything even close to
Sometime after the bombing
I can I can be very confident
I believe it with Alex's
Just posted
The opposite of prey
This is one of that happens
And I suppose prognosticator
Massage variables
About their prior claims
This is closely related was known as the hindsight bias
Expensive an ass
Predict which outcomes they believe are likely to happen about upcoming event
What about notable examples of this was
Researchers asking people about Nixon
Trips to China in the USSR
After the events happen they're asked to remember what their initial prediction
Work
And people consistently show heavy skewing towards Pinky
Weather prediction
We're more in line with what actually happened
After the fact
IC
A very high level of hindsight bias analysis cover
He's already decided with no evidence of this is a false flag
He's already decided again was no evidence
That they're either going to have a right-wing pasty or a Islamic Pat
Who's still only being blamed in order to take right wing
People's guns
This completely manufactured reality is being propped up by isn't
Consistency
Predicted all of these variable
He thinks he predicted a bioweapon attack
Densidad
Does ricin letters are
Completely unrelated to the bomb
He thinks he predicted that they wouldn't find a suspect immediately but I don't see any evidence of that either
What I do see evidence of its completely
Failed predictions Alex's
What is Emma's at the Goldwater going to blame the Patriots
Use this to take his gun
Since we're in 2019
Bleach
Another prediction was the new king of Chicago
Or one of the others
Notably not Boston was not one of us
He was way off about everything but he's passing
Self off as a prophet
Based on
So does the fudge
There's an interesting elevator
Hindsight bias
A 2011 article in the Journal of experimental psychology learning memory and cognition
Quote
Hindsight bias
Provide the illusion of understanding
And can result in a failure to learn
This is a pretty common Point made by research
New study memory
The less conscious you are about your
Experiences in life the more likely you are to fall prey to cognitive bias
And the end result of that is
You never learn
God I think I always think
The people who read
Historians
Are the most
Frustrated
Planet
Yeah
Right if Alex were a honest actor
Situation
Straight up and not trying
And manipulate people
Is self-destructive and selfish
Because he's disallowing the possibility that he can
Reflect
Then think about like
I said they're going to Nuke
Stan and I was wrong Chicago
I was wrong about that
What can I learn from those mistakes that I made along the way
Because he's a just a rank manipulator
None of this matters but for other people
This is an important thing
To consider about
If I was the president like I would
Create a new cabinet position of
Historian who tells me what I'm doing dumb
That's all he's at that's all of his Lookout band
Let's have her right there and she's like
Hey
We've done this
Before and I'm like cool let's not do it there are a lot of horns
Defense Rumsfeld says it's a great idea
History horn
We're looking for 6
The Oath Keepers
What's going to be on
Cuz they were going down to
Can't agree never to hold their annual
Oath renewal ceremony but they do around the
The time of the Revolution cosplaying idiot
I hate them still
SMS
Because he was driving
Episode and there's big news
About The Oath Keepers
And there planned event
Housekeepers that constitutional lawyer Ron Paul Stafford
Before you think of that footage
Astrology.com
Oath Keepers
National
But but there's a
There's a bit of a problem
So it is true that the permit was suspended for the oak
Is Rally that was going to happen
Ultimately doesn't matter
They held a rally on Friday the 19th
The Oath Keepers were not
Pacifically targeted to have their permits
Suspended as Alex
Suggesting
The Selectmen of likes
Contented voted to place a moratorium on public gathering
Well because there was a bummer on the loose
I don't know
Public gathering
The feeling was not to have any large public Gatherings until this thing is sorted out
You can pretty easily
The decision-making process they will go into this
Seem like a very linear
Yeah
I think the Town Council did what they thought was
Right
What was that
But ultimately you just played into those Keeper's hands it allowed them to an
Amplify
Do tons of event permits were suspended
Lexington
That place was probably swimming with really depressed reenactors who didn't get to do their their War re-enacting
But I want some store roads don't care about the larger picture when there's a possibility
I'm single. Because the globalist
A conservative
That's not the case at all
And honestly when I was reflecting on this
I thought about it I thought like it played out exactly how it should
They'll I think this like men of likes
Listen to did the right thing
It turns like
The public
Is bomber on the loose
Multiple bombers possibly
And they have attacked a large public gathering
It's probably in our best interest to make sure that
We don't provide
Now I hate you
I think they suck
And I'm not thrilled with them
Ever
Okay but at the same time I think
It is
Healthy
For groups
To say we are
To dictate how we live our lives
The idea that
You know they would be, Target
For them isn't
Enough
Necessarily for the human Spirit to be like we're not going to
Still having it without the permit
I almost think is exactly how this should have played out as well and thankfully nothing happened there wasn't any violence
Deteriorated
Eddie ugliness
And honestly if there was a bomber that was going to attack a large would never attack
Is there alright
They're the ones who are going to probably carry out a better terrorist attack
Later
I stopped short of soup
According The Oath Keepers and what they did
But abstractly if you just look at them as a fill-in-the-blank group
I think it's played out habits
With the exception of
They were single.
Responsibility
Stupid and propaganda
I don't know I
I think
I think it's
Maybe not the best thing
Your government's 22
Like the clientele permits for the sake of like
There is a danger
Because if it is dictator
What we do based on
Threat
Stop servicing
Pateros
At the same time I do think
Publix
Is the primary objective
Enough people voted on it and that's what they decided was the best way to do that
I don't know if it's
My place
Something wrong about it but
In my estimation
Chances are from everything that I know about
The best way to respond
Intuit error
Is 2 treated as a
Fake terrorist attack
Unaffected
And there goes the terrorist attack
Very effect
We destroyed America because of
Right
At the same time
100-percent
There is no way you will
Convince enough people to
Just say
We are going to
Except and absorb
No response other than
Have the police
Those responses in Fallout 2 are
The goal
I don't know I'm not in
Government
Decisions and I don't know what variables
I don't know
I don't know it's it's very complicated
Outside with Yoki
No they're also terrorists I'm not cool with terrorists also being allowed to have rallies
Difficult about this like I even our conversation about it
Variable
People in Lexington
No
They would end up getting caught a couple days later
What no
Space of
That's a threat
Or what could be out there is
Doobie
The imagination is the limit
Things were wrong and I think every
Thought that
Got to them
To where they are
Makes perfect sense
Samsonite under
Is
Afifa
Yeah I mean wise Maybe
Like every thought they had along the way too wrong
Correct
I agree it's like a it's like a math problem
Alex talks about how he's certain about everything
Hardly move
Exaggerating
This is a false flag because
Bare minimum a provocateur
So this is a false flag for sure he knows what's going to happen he's telling you what's going to happen
He's saying that there's a entire possibility
And so that's his way of saying
All of these things
And I am right
Now
If the reality that comes about in the next day or two or whatever
Doesn't match my prediction that's just because the globalist
It's a perfect way so you can always be right no matter what it is you wouldn't act like this if you were Siri
In his head
Constant cat-and-mouse
Chaska
You know where
Different movies like
I knew you were going to make that move as well that was a different possibility and I
And it's been sort of like in the background of a lot of history episode 4
Circularly McCombs
Very
Relevant
The idea that Alex thinks
He's having a discussion
Yes the globalist real time
Loses
F****** my
Okay a little bit later than
Episode
Globus tours dad are still there incest
As we know or something
More importantly look the same
It's pretty much one of them
Pictures of Alex's Atkins
Conspiracy and
I got to say
I know exactly why he's
Beer
You talkin to call Joe spot
He's got him on the phone
It's really freaked him out
You're a hoe
When a cell phone
Add
Everywhere
This is how stupid you are
Let's go ahead and go
Zoe
It's obvious that Alex knows that these are from
From part different parts of the Apes
And then they cut
Misrepresenting
Entirely
What people's criticism
Lake Hughes
Is showing awareness
Yeah of what he's doing
He knows absolutely Paul is very clear that he understands this to
I don't get involved
Found it on YouTube
They amplify
I never would have gotten the traffic that without Paul and Alex
They did it though
Themselves
Let me grab a coat of I've no f****** idea whose YouTube account
But I think it's license portal
And then the fact that they are the one
Who made it
Circulated
Like I said that last
Alex is showing he knows
Why this was f***** up
And Paul dos2
Long seen as a side
Finish Line of the Boston Marathon
Coveted
Dismembered limbs Etc
It's the main character in Family Guy
That's amazing 2
Explosive devices
An attitude
Isaura
Proof of an inside job of some Grand conspiracy
In which
Themes
What did
Was weird was bizarre with strange was interested
The four-minute commentary video how
Yesterday
Within hours
Within about 3 hours
The video was deleted by YouTube
Immediately
The Family Guy
The listeners probably are wondering about now why is that Family Guy episode coming up so much
On the show
Why is Alex talking about it so much
It clearly doesn't prove anything
Improve
It literally does nothing to further his argument that the bombing was a false flag
So what's the deal
Seth MacFarlane respond
This was created by whoever created by Paul Joseph Watson
Infowars the point where Seth MacFarlane the creator of the Family Guy messages about it
To the point where he had tours
Responded this was an alteration of his work
Any feels terrible the people are doing this
With his intellectual property hurting the people who are the victims of this
Nuggets B really f***** up
That's why Alex
Is continuing down this road because his Target didn't ignore him
Over and over through his career this instant
SuperSU Preston attention by fostering people weigh more
We sorted 2013 when Alex essentially big Piers Morgan to have him back on the show while he was pretending to confront him
Gun Shop
We saw it in 2019 when Alex threatened to murder Joe Rogan politically
Nicole
Sneaky Snake
Let's not even broach the years-long will-they-won't-they feud with Glenn Beckley this is his strategy
Hijack
Alex has a power that
Hijacking celebrity
He ended up going on The View after Charlie Sheen
Freaked out because she
Started his public meltdown show
Alex from The View
I did not know that
I thought we covered that the path
I feel like we did
But I feel like that is one of those things that
It will slip out of my brain forever like Nova. No matter how many time
Times you told me that
Text me information
Places like
Not as notable as a lot of his other like weird appearances because
And it's kind of like
And I'm fine with that
It's just like in my head
It simply cannot be true
I understand
Cuz if you listen to these clips it's clear that they know that they're lying about
And they only appear connected because the video
Reposted manipulative lie
We added them together edit those parts together
He knows that is barely Rises
Hey yeah he sits here with his boss
But apparently also take
Italic
It's crazy
This dude's the worst it's moments like this to make it total
He knows he paid to build perception
Because if he was reporting honest
They would have been clearer about that did never would have played the video
Play
Because the video that they play
Promoted
Took apart of
The part of the beginning of the episode
I cut it in with
The part of the
To make it look
Like those are they played the part where Peter runs over people at the marathon in a cartoon
And then after that the part of the end of the episode where Peter blows up the bridge accidentally
Using a cell phone
They don't do that
They have the edited video where it looks
Like
Based on the edits
EyeMasters says how did you win the Boston bombing and then they cut of meat
To the cellphone and then the bombs go off and they show the people at the marathon
If they would never do something like that
If they were trying to
It's a manufacturer perception and they know what they're doing
It is kind of weird
Manipulative lie edited together
Set the number of random jokes
And distasteful jokes
I don't know.
Seasons of Family Guy
I'm positive that you could do this with a lot of
You could find some way to manipulative me edit
Create something out of it
It's only
Because there was
Shirt the Boston Marathon
But the character lives
In the Dorothy
Yeah like
A huge event
It's never going to it's never going to be.
The Simpsons predict
Trump becoming president
And that was just
Because they thought it was
Utterly
Funny and impassa
People to imagine
Run defense
Family Guy stuff
McFarland says
I don't know maybe we never said yeah yeah yeah
Wouldn't that be awesome
That's kind of the game that's being
Played
I'm so you got that he's on but he has another
You got the big break
In the past
From the
They show
Four or five individuals
Wearing
It look like the heavy and weighed down
So Paul Joseph
Has found
Pictures
That are going around
I was wondering when this was going to come up
The time in following the
The story I'm shocked it was on the 7th
I thought it was actually pretty
Actually been a little bit more immediate online but it wasn't
As I mentioned on the last episode I was working at
Message
The kill time
People were out with outrageously unsupported views and ideas were way more interest
Steven anything real
The time
Mountains of things to read
If you could look into that world
Message boards
A consists
Italy renewing source of anonymous Post in
Thought
I would be lying if I said that I was 100
Skeptical of every
Read back.
Wholesale
I definitely was way more naive than I am
Today I can still kind of remember the feeling that came from taking in those baseless theories presented
Is truth it was
Even if I didn't really believe the stuff I was reading there was
What if
Poston blog
It was injected
Into my mind
And I couldn't help but be
Somewhat effect
Goodbye it
That's the feeling that people like Alex and others
Like this who profit
From these worlds
It's that uncertainty laced with
That makes it vulnerable enough to lower the rational instinct
And accept whatever is offered by as a way of
Navigating these
And the aftermath of the bombing there was no information
From officials
I did not vacuum idiots online decided
Become Detective
I remember this.
So vividly
Because whenever a new picture for the marathon was posted by anyone it would end up resulting in
Tons of new pop
Possibilities
Suspect
In the images
None of them really stuck
With exception
Two men
Who the internet decided to look at
And decided that they were military contractors
And that's probably involve
Obvious
At that point all that was really known was
Pressure cookers and they were carried inside backpack
These two dudes were wearing backpacks
And there was
Sexy put together
Bada-bing bada-boom
They're suspects
Wanted to
There's legitimately nothing bored of this
Conspiracies
Two guys the internet salt looks
Suspicious backpack
Backpacks became the target of a
Giant online mystery
It's being here a
Fire
Invalidated by Alex and Paul Joseph
0 reasons
To do this there's no Journal
Rustic value today
I'm talking around
Under ungrounded
Based on block poster Message Board thread apologize
Just happen to stumble
Lacrosse
Dave Paul has found online posts
These guys with
Weird looking backpacks
Hello here we go
It's like I accept people have after work
Listen to all these two
There's giant groups
Shirt
And it's like I would prefer more people to
Steaks
But if you have
Rabble-rousers like
At 4
Yeah
Nefarious purpose
Just a bunch of weird
Like the articles that I was reading about the
And how this helps
Play doubt
One of the things that I was reading that was the idea of this like crowdsourcing
Investigative work
And what are the big things
That was pointed out as a
The failure
Process
As it relates
Was that it was a one-way
Like there was only
People online investigating saying
And that's
Were interacting with the people invest
Navigating
Turn the f****** terrible
Options because
They were looking at
Okay so all we knew is backpack
Let's craft
A narrative out of these people that we can find with backpacks
That's not enough
App to make this
The healthy part of that vest
Ecosystem
It's not like there's any
There is no
Strict oversight doesn't matter
Because eventually when the FBI does released
The picture of the suspect
It is a
We need help finding these people
That's the way the crowdsourcing
Is a 2 waist
And that was a that did not happen
Is the aftermath
And so there's all these people going over these images
The finding bulshit
And now Alex
Just found out about this
Real investor
You just a mop
You're just a mop and reply
Yeah you're blind
Eastwood movies mob
Please write so we got these guys with backpacks
And this is
Goodenough is proof
That's why there wasn't a military contractors they're running it
And Alex starts
The freak out about how he's right
I don't know why do you transition
Smoothly happened
KKK reference with the oath
Keepers like why did you immediately go to KK
Speeches for everybody only four more defensible because
A little more
Wow that's a problem
So I mean they just build this up as like
Proof that there is backpack
They had the bombs
And none of this is based on anything other than
Just gassing and things I found
An anonymous blog
People with large black
Epic sound
Just feet from the weather
So he's applying without any evidence backpack is
Don't know
Why you think you can prove that
Why are you reporting that and then
There's only one black backpack
Here's what's going on
If you look at those pictures
There are a lot of
Fans
They are mostly ignore
The internet had chosen
To focus on
Specifically
These two guys who they've sighted or military contractors
Boots
They look like
Appetite
Right
There is
A middle eastern
Not appearing
Person
And a guy who looks
I have Alex will later call him
Call Tim
Recalls on a Yokel
They are not the only people with black back
In these pictures
If you look at the pictures you can find a bunch of people with backpacks
End up becoming the target of
There's only there's only one
Backpack
There's all different kinds but there's only one black
Backpack and the reason that I appreciate your spin on this year
Focused on
Is because
These internet places
Engaged in building the same area that Alex
They were they were working
To try and
Prove
The talking points
Alex
Put it out
Know whether or not they were doing that specifically in-service of Alex
Or just that these corners of the internet where
Cesspools
Yeah whatever the reality of it is
A little bit unclear.
But
Because
They focus
This suspicion on the specific people
That would help Alex build his narrative
Specifically that he's trying to do with
Family Guy episode that is
Peter Griffin
Is a tea party guy who works with
You see this ham
You see Paul
Take this suspicion about the
People with backpacks
And it all gets funneled
Towards
There were two guys were military contractor looking
There's a middle eastern guy and white guy
Guys working
White guy in order to make us all look like we're working with terrorists
You see it happen
So smooth
The thing about crowdsourcing V
Kind of proper
Again. Conspiracy
T-Series
Is that you already have
Built-in audience
Because they want to be validated by you have not only given you the means by which to
But at the
The same time they're your main Auto
Weird
Like f******
Symbiotic
Right
Well I mean it's the actually the opposite of what's going on with the the place
Crowdsourced information
Alex interacting with his weirdos that are going out and finding the evidence
Making cars
Yeah absolutely has ecosystem
Eating
In that
We're not doing that
And this is what happened
Those Dynamics
One of the photos shows two guys
Call Keith Thompson cocky
On cell phones
It looks like
Stereotypical
At least one of these guys
Running right after the bomb
Wouldn't you
One of the backpacks is identical to one
Carried by one of these individuals info
Please Photoshop
Because the script
No it's
It's unprecedented
Alex has decided based on these pictures of some people with backpacks
Ozark
Oh my God
And Alex
Loses his goddamn mind
About this
This episode
Deteriorate
Southwest
Because Alex
Did they have got everything
Oh
Oh that's bad
That's very bad
So he apologized
Indicates that he doesn't really know all that much
Dinos
Thought everything
Why didn't you look into it
Why didn't you find out what the temperature was
It was in the forties
Banana
Lazy are you as an investigative reporter what the temperature was
Since my workout
April
In Boston
When it's 70 out
Early spring it might be a bit nicer but you know
Especially with the restart Early Access
You might want to
With a mullet
Pac-Man Heroes
It looks like
Huge way down heavy backpacks
I'm in a white outside of working with
Terrorists Muslim
That's a terrible prediction at all so I would say that
Only Fred by
You
It's not like a really
Provident mean you've already think
Like that
I've decided
The name of that
Bly.
We tried
Y'all Qaeda
That's what it is
Sure
We know
From how things played out
And every
You can find it
Just completely wrong about everything
They're like
They think
Two steps ahead of the media and the
The detectives and everything
But there are completely different
They're not even
In reality
They're just blaming their privates
Steps ahead of private citizens of a pterodactyl
On people who judge
Happen to have backpacks
What what is that all these like
Glued
Who are figuring everything out
Basically
Reliving
Law & Order
Don't get to that second part where they like
We have to build a case in order
Police with text
Your honor
Not there's no
And then what you do is you
Test that idea by creating like
A brainstorm
What are other possible explanations
Excluding those possibilities
Narrow it down
They would show your argument
False are wrong themselves
That strengthens
IC
No
Evidence
They even
The most
Elementary argument against the
Has been shot down
That's just a guy with
Once you would otherwise
You will never be a
Iraq
Alex really thinks
Scooped everyone
You really think
That like
Can't be real
So far ahead of this s***
It's crazy
Because these are just
Photos
DePaul sound on
Different Twitter accounts
Are Goodreads
Corsage
Backpacks that are talking about
Really really bad
Ladies and gentlemen
Wish.com
They're typing in the background
Information
They're not showing this information
Because they're working
Also important
Alex
Hackers
I wonder what those are
Very satisfying
So I ate more to these photos
Frozen What I remembered from the time
Definitely a lot more substantial
What I remember is just people look like
Pictures of like before the bombing at Red Lions and people circled in like
Hello here's this pretty
Sad
About those same
Course random shots people Circle the red lines everywhere
Did anyone with a backpack that closely resemble the ones used in the attack
Excluded people who didn't
Fat butt ever narrative
Started speculating wildly
That they were involved
I can't overstate how dangerous this
And I'm honestly surprised
Nothing ended up having
Those people
This was such a
And Alex's
Facilitating it amplifying issue
Presumably Millions
The people
Like it's so bad
Internet
And for people to take it upon themselves to speculate their privates
Marathon backpack
Can look weird
But that's awful
They looked
Bright
It's that bad but it's an entirely different thing for Alex to basis reporting on those internet rumors and Witch Hunt
Alex causes breaking news but there's no news
Break here
That's all this is
It's so dangerous
Like you and I know that I was just
Liar and fraud
High-level source
He knows what he's talkin
We act like this
Passing of Internet posts
Does breaking news
It gives them undue credibility in those people's eyes
And that can lead them down bad roads
One thing I find particularly interesting about Paul Joseph Watson
Post on Infowars
However
Is that it's a ton of crowdsource pictures of
The bombing the proof nothing
Another is one other image
That is not a crowd source
Picture of the
Images of screenshot that
Someone posted on
4chan
Ocular posted interesting on another line
If you read the body of the text
This is the exact same
Post that Alex read on are on April
16th
You remember it was the one he started out by saying was a
But the part about outlawing reloading powder and found himself
Post
Is now. Atropos
It's party evidence being presented
False flag
And if you weren't paying close attention
You never would have realized there was a sleight-of-hand
They completely repurposed
This post
It's frustrating
Decided
I don't know how we write law but you can
That's the rule
I didn't know that
Even be a thing and that's how it legal
It is if I didn't know what was coming up on this episode I would say this is a new low
We got another
25 minutes from now
Beaten to death
There are reports coming out that the FBI has information that they believe is related to
Add event pictures
Prison photos
These are not those
He's convinced
One step ahead of the video
So most of this
Stretch
Now becomes Alex just
Blindly analyzing
Sing this footage
Send pictures
Conclusion
He has no reason
It's just like
Okay
Oh my God
I'm watching video
Breaking news
Keep scrolling
Call man
Workshop
Wow that was
That is astonishing how
Just like
I bet it's quick because
Conclusions already God's this works
Alex has all the pieces of opted
Just right in front of everything in order to create the illusion that this is a false flag
Is so easily presented
For a visit
Yeah that's what's up
He's freaking out because he's realizing
It literally fell into my lap
So
I don't know how to set up these clips cuz a lot of them are the same
Suspicions on
People
Just for no reason
Suspects
Right on this evening
Oh my God
Military-type
The other two look like
If you see the guy in Lakewood
The r word
Just for just for the cherry on
On top of the ice
Alex's conjecture that these guys look military
Remember our last episode when we discussed how they were a lot of enlisted persons
They tough Rock
Where are we going to wear their uniform carrying a heavy bag in memory of their fellow soldiers
You've been killed overseas
Whatever go to the
Marathon
Possibility
They don't always do it in 50
Like they're not always in
Is the uniform that they wear
There's a lot of different uniforms one might
Possibility that these men had already completed the marathon
And we're waiting for someone
That is a possibility
I don't know that to be
Be true but tons of other explanations for their.
Consider before jumping
These are the sort of things
You need to consider
Before you jump to your conclusion
You can't rule these things out
Therefore you can't draw the conclusion that you
You're drunk
I can't tell you who these dudes are and honest
I'm glad that information
Like that didn't get disseminated widely
As far as I can tell
You can tell about the investigation to bombing
This was not irrelevant thread
Anyone who actually knew what was going on all the detective
Interviews of FBI agents who were involved in the immediate
Investigation
Their focus was way Sharp
Then the lack of public information LED people to believe
By this point track down where the pressure cookers were bought and had a pretty idea pretty good idea
They didn't Alex or Fortune heretic by throwing around baseless accusation
The people
Just because I have
Good for you only thing that
Doesn't have any source
He doesn't know any
14 is obsessed with a guy with a backpack
His reporting
But you really recognized like this is what
It's really f******
Scary anonymous
I just post something
Could
Guide him
Like he has no standards at all
Terrified
Investigate
Sometimes sometimes
Alex realizes something
These pictures
Yeah there's this one guy in a blue coat lose White
Chris Kyle sniper hat
Punisher later
His narrative is like only
The Punisher
This is
Old time
Fiat
Skull
Duty Orono
You're out Alex spend so much time
This episode about the logo
He's convinced back at the guy in the picture from the Boston Marathon
He's wearing this hat at The Punisher logo
Or he's being set up to look like he's on a seal
Expound at length about how only an idiot
The Punisher logo because the Punisher logo itself was just
Stolen from the Marines
Hey Chris Kyle was a member of a Seal Team
And he was known to wear this logo on his clothes
Not because he liked the Punisher
Because it was a Marine
Seal Team
Symbol Pryor
How to completely wrong
Hate
And having somebody do a bunch of Coke
And then tell me all their ideas
Is every every freezer
And then
They got a little
Accidentally
It does it does feel that way
F*** off
Who was just a big fan of
So he named
Punisher logo on buildings in Iraq as the Time magazine article
Try to mark their territory
There's bad
Because Kyle was super famous American
Punisher logo
That's being sold at people wearing
But even beyond that the Punisher logo started
The pop up everywhere surrounding War
American soldiers were stenciling it on their helmets putting stickers of it on their vehicles
But you know what
It wasn't only them
The fighters on the other side
Isis started appropriating the logo to
How many times do I have
Burger King guy
There's something unnerving about the appropriation of this particular symbol
He is pretty f***** up tactic
Achieve his goals
And the only thing that differentiates him from the villains he's up again
Is who he's torturing and murdering
He's a character without a finely-tuned Morales
Not an anti-hero but an ant
A villain
The idea of our soldiers associated with him is
Absolutely chilling
And suggest
Just get out of Foreign Wars
We may need to abolish the armed service
It's gone too far
Going to put the Punisher logo on it
It's f****** shirt already
Murdering people without any of
I've read tons of military blogs about this subject
Slogo because
It's part of the long-standing
Every single one of them talked about how
Specifically took the logo from the Marvel comic because he was a military celebrity
Because he was a military celebrity
Call Don
Autobiography
Are Kong's guy suggested it before the deployment
We all thought what the
What school he righted wrongs
You killed bad guys
Humane wrongdoers beer them
That's what we were all about
It made it all wrong
With some modifications
We spray painted on are Hummers and body armor helmets
Guns
We spray painted on every building and wall we could
We wanted people to know we're here and we want to f*** with
It was our first of psyops
You see us
Where the people kicking your ass
Firoz
Because we will kill you
Motherfuker you're bad
We're batter
Assume that
What's that
Translates to is
The Iraqi people viewing
This is all pretty upsetting
Stop particular
Character creator
Builders
Yeah
He's not a good guy
Conway told Tom
Realty logos and none of them seem to match Alex
Anthony makes later this episode about
Classics.
Eagles logo is an eagle carrying a trident
Perched on it
None of the specific
Field team 7
Insignia that are even close to a Punisher
Mostly seals doing s*** like holding knives and writing summer
Something logos are downright
The Galleria in this image that Alex is reporting on The Punisher head because he likes
He might be wearing it because he's a fan Chris Kyle he might be wearing it randomly
It could indicate that he's in the military
But it certainly doesn't prove
Absolutely just making s*** up that the Punisher logo is a seals logo
He's doing that to strengthen his argument that the guy in the picture
At the marathon was there on an official capacity
Is evidence is super thick
And this is what you have to
Alex knows that this evidence
That's why you need to work to over blow it
Symbol that actually
He knows what he's doing
And even his immediate recognition of it
He knows
Did Chris Kyle ripped off The Punisher logo
He later says the exact opposite
The Punisher logo itself
He completely contradicts himself later once he's had time to
To flesh out the reading
He's doing this
Intentionally
Sick
It is that
Same kind of thing
Happened with
The Wolf of Wall Street
AP portrait the characters
Absolutely
Evil awful awful
And then so many people are like
Man that guy's really cool
People model that
Behavior
The Wolf of Wall
Michaels
Morally gray characters are really difficult for people who are all that
Smartfren
Wrestle with everybody or anything like that
People have
Often times
Without engaging with more complex
Literature
You end up with a back
Charles Bronson is
Not the good guy
You know.
You understand his motivation
People get shot
He killed so many people who are not in that Ganges up account
Shooting guns out of
Third floor window
Well I guess the police did enlist him to kill that guy
What else
He's not
Thinks of these pictures that he's found
Now that he's got like
Involved
Like these
Is crack the code
It stalled who did it
No
Ridgewood
What looks like
You think they ever looked at those pictures already has all my gods are like so much
But not being accused
Suddenly break
Plainview
18 Plainview
There Will Be Blood
It's pretty
Sad like
Just like I know
You have to understand
I say this all the
And it comes back
Do the stuff that Alex have llamas in the studio in 29
Alex
He's interested in taking these things
Things that happened in the world
Using them to further his agenda but primarily
You want
To make money
Yeah you can tell
How clear
All your data right now
Internet
The ratings are in
The best ever been
Man
Fuckingo as irresponsible as we can
Drudgereport
We can't confirm
Because it's because
In the absence of official information
Infowars
Here's to people who don't know what the game be illegitimate
Professional is looking website
They have a guy whose title as editor in law at Large
They have a TV show a radio show
Eat it
Easy to trick people into thinking that this is legitimate and yes he's doing that
You strike while the iron is hot while there's an absence
A credible information
He's injecting himself into
To that space
Just so clear
What people like about how
Make me really anxious
Because I see
Iic like
This is working
Alex's seeing defense strategies working
Naked
Can almost
Feel
The deterioration
Eastandard
But like the path that leads to the presentation I really feel like you're seeing a lot of them
Beginnings
JustBats
Like
God he's
So grateful
To the bombers
He's just like
Thank you
Thank you so much
I mean how could he not be grateful
He's got these
Pictures from
Fortunate
Prove something
We put breaking the story
It's going to
To be the best
Even better than our best
Oh my God
Yeah I don't understand
But I mean come on
If we're going to if we're going to make
Conspiracy theory about the
Boston bombers
You want to go cui Bono
I'll tell you
Alex Jones
Adjust
Craft here
I see your tension in order to elevate
How you do it without parently it works movie Just
People like Seth MacFarlane in
Responding to our profit
So let's keep doing it
Let's blame
Now
It comes out
The FBI does have pictures
Of the Peace
Alex
Takes that
Exactly
Model
Under your bed
And you have that playing at home I got I get caught
So you've got now reporting that FBI has the other pictures believed to be the
Joseph Watson
Has forced them to admit that they have the pictures
Forecast
Completely different picture
And it keeps going
No
Unprecedented
So the announcement that the FBI had a picture of the suspect absolutely has nothing to do with Alex
To shameful coverage of these 4chan rumors
The news had already broken by the time Alex got on his little
From the Lord & Taylor Outlet on Boylston
Affect dropping a bag at the location
What separates this evidence from the evidence Alex
Paddling is really the element of the person of the footage
Dropping off a backpack at the location of the bombing
That's a lot more compelling
This guy looks like he's in the military is weird
This is another case of Alex just instantly knowing how to lie about an evolving situation
What's the world appear to support is fake
In his alternate reality broken this thing wide open
Completely inconclusive pictures is British friend found on 4chan
Wednesday
The FBI is a picture of the suspect it only makes
They're just doing that because Alex
Too close to the truth
It's really fascinating to watch him and ask
Is everything is distraction
Bluster and misrepresentation
But it's also so natural to Ally
You don't even think for a
Second
Suggesting the CNN is watching him
And the report isn't
It just flows out of
There's no concern for ethics
Answer for how this might affect his list
It's all good
Pandemonium in
Sensationalism
Anything to ask
Good it'll lead to more traffic
And more money
F*** the concert
What I'm saying
Is there
This is a really really bad person
But it's crazy
Because part of it is conscious
And part of it is
Yeah like part of it
Just instinct
Actually a bad person
Just operate
From a place of
Bones
Psychopath
Yeah I know I ate now I want to write a
A series of
Call Jones
Ben Watson
They always
Catch the wrong guy and
And they always say
Airbnb good Prejudice and Zombies
It's the same shipper
Is Road for a while assuming that they're talking about the same thing
Right now
So he gets off the phone with Paul to go make the story more sensational
Alex thinks he scooped
Goddamn idiot
Alex
Descends into a places
Because of how crazy
Can you see the guys win the backpack with the pressure cookers
Explosion the scraps
It is incredible
Different
The patchy
This is unbelievable
So Alex has no he's cracked the case he's figured this all out
Nitsa overwhelming
He does say that
And just
Is wrong but yes
Like if
You don't need to apologize
Retract all of this s***
What you don't need to do is that
Really was this guy
A cover-up
This I mean I'm sure yeah I would imagine that he does still think he's right
Such
Gymnastic
Except to go through
In order to
To rationalize
It's crazy
II
You know
Every time he gives up
That list of life
I halfway
Expect him to
Keeps going
I better the pink elephants and their the cells in the sky
AR in my brain
Website
F****** Urus
Cam
Right now ladies and gentlemen
Images of suspicious
This year's on
So the actual headline has a?
?
Over and over
It's an exclamation
Huh? Is really carrying a lot of legal I think it is
Paul Joseph Watson later headline
So what is kept thinking about while I was
Listening to
This is like
You know who probably loves this
The bombers
And you were on the lamp
If you to do everything in their power to point the finger at somebody else
Phuc yea it's his great this serves my interest perfectly
It cast
All kinds of Suspicion or other people
I'm not even in the equation
I got a thing you got to feel good
This is this probably provide Comfort to the actual terrorists
Bomber and then
You're all geared up for getting caught you're all you got your f****** Manifesto you got everything going on
Worried
Interested in just
Ramrodding 12 other dude into
Prison and they are not going to look at any
Anything towards you you're like
What's that
The authorities in the mainstream media aren't really saying much of anything.
The out right focused completely other direction
You don't know what the FBI's actually
Would probably give you a feeling of
I mean it doesn't matter I don't know how impactful it is
On the actual FBI people probably not at all
Actually they all listened to a show along with
I think you forgot that
The ultimate end result of this though is
Distracting
Absolutely
Great congratulations
But Alex
Even though he's wrong all the time
Cannot emotion
Handle being so right
Chris Kyle
Guanaco
More
Ladies and gentlemen
Looks like
Seymour
Please forever
For good
Forever.
I was just was wrong people say out loud
I wish it was alone
You're not
Play so weird
Raise
Ora Ora
He might feel like he was
Actually right
For the first time
And it turns out that
The only way
It turns out that
It's so ridiculous I'm so right all the time
Oh my God
And also I mean like
I don't want to like
Put
To find a point
Very little
Care for anybody affected
There's not really any indication of
Empathy
Nope nothing
Is broadcaster
Is almost devoid of
Concern for victim survivors
The community of Boston
The entire
Reflection of a psycho
Earlier I think we discussed a little bit
He's doing now
The opposite of prediction
The post diction
Are you taking applying them to
To the Past
In the middle of this one
I'm trying to do that again
Play when did he die
Blueprint over and over again
He told you yet before
I just
He said after work
Don't get involved
Part of a drill
Bombs
First off
Need to say that
To your audience
Wow the bigger issue
Given this warning
Prior to the bombing gives him some sort of a predictive ability
Is just being like a if the future
Don't do this
It's a ridiculous
Predictions
And then there's
Sure
So we learn here little bit more an update on brother who was the army guy
Dehydration
Animals taken out of the race
There's that there's
Which are actually not
What are your friends
Marathon team
Dehydrated
Finish
His wife
Wife
2 Days Later
Why would they
Why wouldn't they
If I were them I wouldn't talk to you ever again
Like you was going on
Millions of listeners
Being pulled out of a race for dehydration or exhaustion is somehow related to a plot
Took murder civilians
Why would you ever talk to that person ever again
Yeah that's a good long break
Yeah I just specially I'm not going to talk to you when I know you're going to repeat what I say
How dare you turn my silence
On speaker
So Furious that you would use my personal life
Has a way of propping up your propaganda
But you know what
And I can feel this
Rob
Let It Go
Alex now realizes
Weeping in Great Raid
But it's only going to continue
If we make sure
That everything is
Is as over-the-top as possible
Got off the phone with Paul like
10-15 minutes
Prior but he needs to call Paul back
And if those guys aren't special forces
I don't know
Believable
Boston bombing
Denver on the, there?
What are your points
And he's not asking PJ dubs for his
This is an editorial meeting
Yeah he's asked me what's your take on this in order for Paul to see what he's going to put in the article and for Alex
Let's make this more extreme
And Alex
Blown this whole thing wide open
It's just so sad to hear that
Well
The back of that smoke cigarettes near the site of the explosion is the one carried by the
Stereotypical
Disheveled
So now we've created this like
It sits firmly in place
That there is a dialog going on between
Is intelligence operative
Adjust their coverage in order to
It's it's
Isn't saying the level of
Non reality that's being presented
In a very delicate situation when
People are
Freaking out
People are anxious there their they're
Almost
Deserved it
Make that
Worse
Yeah and also
Help get suspicion off of the actual bombers
It's kind of it's kind of Amazing Alex
Manage to
His job title in
Into just delusion
Music ranchera
Like here's my job
Delusions of grandeur
Certainly during the middle of
You've always thought that the world
Circulates around here
It's just interesting to a
Certain measure of Granger
Buyer only
Having delusions
And you can only really
Creative around horrible tragedy
Absolutely
Geneva
Justify
Proves your delusions
On a very deep emotional
You eat
Yeah that's
He's facilitating it
Making it worse
Also this
Report
Sbisd
Again Alex
Without any
Information
Is
Dead set
On his audience believe in
Tomorrow to make the announcement
This is ridiculous
He is just living in a
Fake
Put work
Like you know what that that's the thing about it is like at least in this case
The Optics are
Versace that like
I get why someone listen
Would be true
Especially in the absence of real inform
I don't really like a lot of the time when people fall for Alex's
And how you believe this
But because of the circle
It's around this particular instance
It makes way more sense
Why people would fall for it
And for him
Play the same games
Movies playing in that circumstance
Like
It's just
Unacceptable
I really really resign
CNN
Intelligent
Particular
Is
That
Empty
Vacuum
Moron of a TV announcer its
Secretly a
And not just the unite
Israeli intelligence
I don't really have anything to base this accusation on other than
Butcher was born in Germany where his parents were living at
You were call
Maita Toyota
In the United States
He was educated
He went on to work for the Tel Aviv desk for reuter
You work for an international news wire in Israel
And is Jewish there's no proof
This is a blatant Act of anti-Semitism and divided loyalties
Around
This is pretty
This is just
So Alex
The military contractors
Spies and what-have-you
And you found the pants
The day is going to be
Multiple paths
Because you've got the Middle Eastern option
And you got the good old boy option whichever way they want to go
Alex believe
But he's figured this out and once they reveal the information that the FBI
They're going to frame
Oh my God
We're about to see him hard
Reality
Not compared to what's coming up
So Alex is really trying to make clear to his audience
That there is that two-way communication but
Keyboard something cnnsi
Respond and it's important because it really elevates the idea that what he saying memes
And he's right
And the globalist
I noticed within five minutes of us announce
Department store in another one
And they have identified
Boston.com
Alternate possibility completely different
So I mean not even
So they're different
Second reality he thinks that he's in this situation is full of Espionage and Israeli intelligence
Pictures on Fortune
And listen to this
But this is crazy the way he
A present 4chan
Your website
Twitter Facebook news channel
Cam
Hours ago
Adjusted
It's definitely all there
It's a big hacker website
As opposed to being a place where
People anonymously post
Bulshit
Yeah
Anonymous
I think that's what I'm talking about
To some extent I guess
Channels
Much less about it
There are a lot of different boards
On there
Right now those different it's all like one
Thing is dumb
And also because of the anonymity and because of
Serta people who gravitate towards step
People who want to talk or can't do it about
Like a lot of it has to be taken is like this is not by itself credible information
A site and all this because
It also lends the idea that
Like this is all credible information
Found information
And it's not
It's just random bulshit that's
But Audible
Dum Dums on the internet
I'm just saying I cannot
Understand why he would
Make that jump is like he's going to the f****** anime forums
Know you know
He doesn't f****** know
He's decided that hillbilly guy who called the r-word earlier is that at
Designated Patsy
Sure Alex decides to
Did you send it to
Fairly expensive
Reenactment of how that guy got roped into the drill
You're in the Army now
When is you for National Security
You're going to fight for America now
What
You're going to get $5,000 billion
America
Thorazine
That's the end of it
For shopping
It's disgusting and none of that is real
Who's f****** fantasy
He's disseminating his sick
As proof
To his audio
That's gross
So he's mad now
Sure he broke the story about the unfortunate
FedEx
It's happening
Similar
Haha
Why why are we having a fake fight with somebody who's not pay
Paying attention
That we think is always paying attention
It's so stupid
Is actually wear
CNN
Makes their critical mist
Any photos
5 minutes
From Fox
Stretch
Founding fathers
Patriots are going to blow you off
Marathon
They might change their plans
Getting yourself out of yourself
The right there at the end
The full of s***
They may get out of jail free card
That's in preparing his audience for literally all evidence to be completely opposite of what he's yelling at them
Open the door naive enough to believe that the difference in reality and Alex's narrative
Is due to the globalist in immediate danger the story cuz Alex
Right
It's a sad pathetic
Dambal that no one would make
Gambit
Excuse me that no one would make unless they know
Once the dust settles I'm going to be wrong about that
It's that it's like the metaphor that I always make about the wet concrete
And being able to write your initials in it
Intellidrive
Is the actress someone who recognizes that they can't do s*** ones get concrete
If you have to prepare for eventually that concrete
What are they
Or whatever
Like I said
This is one of the biggest f*** ups that the media was absolutely guilty of
Cinnabon
My coverage
CNN reported that one suspect had been arrested
Based on information allegedly from three sources
From there a lot of other outlets picked up on the story and reported that news
Or at least reported the CNN was reporting
As we know this was not true
Nancy and I was forced to make a retraction which really hurt the media's image and a time when they needed it the most
She was anxious
Boston particularly so
It's the media's jobs
To convey the information to people needs a f****** is a really bad luck
CNN turned out to be wrong
And I think they should have been more cautious
But ultimately
And retracted the story and apology
It's fairly easy to see how this mistake could be made by people who meant well but didn't double and triple check info that was coming from
Sources they presumably
Even if you can see how the sort of thing
Could happen it doesn't take away
How much of an unnecessary
Egregious error
Here we're witnessing Alex
Use his phrasing
Piss all over reality
As it relates to the bombing
He's never going to apologize for being wrong about literally every aspect that I've heard of this
He doesn't have
He's a liar by trade
So you give a s*** when he's completely completely f**** up a story
We have to retract a major story like this in the midst of a very high-profile ongoing situation
What happens if the Alex is being given a perfect opportunity to attack the media
I pretend like they're always wrong
And by extension he's always right
Of course Alex is always right when's the last time you heard a story
Story that's
Listen to episodes
I'm starting to be able to see the spin happening like in Matrix bullet
You just know how it's going to play out
They're going to retract the story about the arrest and he's too hot on their heels
Yet it's just
It's crazy it's absolutely crazy and it's
Stabbed
Was
Precious with the reporter
Yeah
I understand why
It doesn't
Make it
Horrible acts of recording but the circumstances
Has turned out to be that the effective
Was
Awful
It's f***** up
Because
In the sentence the same thing as
Somebody saying it's
There's going
To be a there's going to be a school shooting
Coming up
It's like saying that the media is going to
Sooner or later there
Right and you've already set this
For the one mistake they make
Is every
Other than
What is going to f******
Deal with that
Flagellating themselves over
A fuk up is only going to
Play into that right
Flagellating is not necessarily
Post-mortems dissection wrong absolute how to improve
Media criticism
It'll read a bunch of articles about
This likes her looking back on what went wrong and what went right
During discovery
That really healthy
Ecosystems
Engaged
Never
And it's just no
Big game
In terms of his stuff
Like it's hard to also wrestle that joint 19 where you
So many different shops
Yeah they are so similar to Alex
Where is back then he was
Still on this
Seth rich
Naat 2013
The Oath Keepers
He's on the phone there's another
Who's on there
Episode
Spoiled for the two-week moratorium
They're presenting as
It's just
Attack on the Earth
This narrative almost complete
Completely blows up
On air
Because Alex
If other events had their permits pulled
Houses
Delaware
Dozens and dozens of different
Terraria
America
Story
From what I gather now on the counter protesters that were demonstrating against us
Counter protest
Some reason
Counter protest my pro-gun rally that's not going to be happening anymore
What about the other events on April 19th
What's the re-enactment took place
The past Monday they do it early
So that's awesome
YouTube
This is just incredible
So
Being
Specific things that already happened
Other events absolutely did have ever talked about any other event
Scheduled for the 18th 19th 20th 21st
Where was everybody
That almost fell apart so hard
Even see it
That would kind of hurt our argument
Yeah the only reason he asked it
It was so you would say
No and it's just us
You didn't let there were notes but don't
Sprite
And that other guy who's not the roads like on the game
Who is that guy
Is the guy from Massachusetts
But I don't know exact
I don't care
Civil War talk from the right wing
They've always been talking
The last 6 years
People in this
These communities
These media ecosystems have been
And believing that we are in a cold Civil War
It's going to
They've been preparing for this
Shift in rhetoric whenever
You know that's it's not it's not a new phenomenon
Tell them the truth which is that they're a bunch of
F****** cowards who are afraid of any kind of
And they're not going to do anything because
That's what they can't be
Can have a rally on Lexington Green without a permit
That's okay
So
Alex
He said this
I realized we were in
Thousands of thoughts racing through my mind as I am
Shut up
Open the phone shop for
Alex wants hearsay from listener the right
Is going to come in and give his two step
He is becoming
Very
Broadcast
I don't know how
To put it is a fucken load
What what you end up bringing to the table
Is
I don't I don't know how to
He's lucky
Quite Frank
Okay
And we'll get to that
Steve shows up
So Alex has declared victory over the media has retracted the right
Reporting
And he starts
Yikes
I feel
Sure he's wrong about everything but
To crank I do love that sort of jaunty
Nonsense
Yeah part of this could easily be explained by him repeatedly says he's not 2 hours of
So part of a lot of this
The really terrible work right by like I haven't
Go to you right that don't exist
Andrew w.k. we're cranking it up all day
Justice
So Alex
Sing a lot about this
No
Gallows humor
Your ancestors
Alex
Godspeed
That's what you do my daughter what you do
Yourself
Alex is like brain and his
Conception of God
Even is rational
For being
54 laughing on-air somehow wind up with him back at the end being like
And that's why I'm happy about this
Even if you're bored
Human way to do Ruby
This is an absolute awful awful situation
These people lost their lives but lost loved ones
The city is traumatized
It doesn't make up for that
But at least
Through this we were able to find evidence of government machination
Usher Yeah
Honoring the Warriors lost
While at the same time trying to make your anti-government argument
Possible
And he doesn't do that
Because he doesn't care
It's not Gallows humor give a f*** about this
No one is going on
After a sukkah
Mass shooting and then being like
When do we get to Texarkana
Are we all excited about this
That would kind of be the office
So Alex
Earlier this is a really important
Things to do whenever you're trying to process
If you have an idea about something
You need to do
Is consider alternate possibility
And I do from there that is really easy
First step
What else could explain this phenomenon that I'm seeing
It's just like
You learn this
Junior High
High School
It's pretty simple stuff
Imply that he
He has done that
Clairol my God
The other guy
Now you're off
Taunting the New World Order
Wow wow
Try harder
He's not here
He's not capable of actually trying because
Trying
Is hard
Is really hard if he were to portray any of the things that he's covering in an honest fashion
Like I don't even think most of his audience would find a compelling
Because
Oh
Find me a obviously an explanation
That isn't doesn't match your paranoid anti-government
Like
He knows that he doesn't have a
Place in the world in the computer fries
The only the only
That's this is the result
Needs to try with that either Lowe's from him like a memory
He gets a caller who is
Huge break
This is regarding buttface radio transmission at the time of the bombing
You can find it by searching
Blondie
Marathon
Brio
Bl0g
GOG
Don't say that
Marathon
Police
Radio
The police radio with the timestamp
Goes from calm business-as-usual to an officer breaking in tennis
Definitely devices here
I need officers
Definitely definitely devices here
Explosion
Infowars.com
Don't need to do it
Because Blog Dog Boston police scanner is good enough Alex
Finds this
Unfortunately it does explode right in front of their eyes
Boston Marathon bombing police radio
Explosion he goes right to death
Obviously
Gallows humor
Something
Dogs looking over the guys front page from around this time is reporting is mostly just reposting
So this means that kind of a feedback loop that situation
Open the recording app
Stumbled onto the bombs in his truck to alert people that their device
Is important
Isn't she saying this is like the first
Reporting officer
This is before the explosion
It's just a noble cop was not part of the drill realizes something is
However if you listen to Alex he's clearly contradicted this narrative already
The first bomb went off
2:49 p.m.
And the second was 14 sec
Alex just gave was 251
Is it 2 minutes after the explosion
This is not the first reporting of the bombing on police radio
It's a case of
Found another
Makes total sense to hear on a police scanner in the aftermath of something like that
You don't know what's going on
You can't be too careful about the possibility that there might be
Bmore bombs
If you find something
Pictures of course you're going to call it in and get some
That's all that's going on here is
Blog dog this collar and Alex
Did the proof of their downfall swag Theory
This narrative is further complicated though because I realized
Clip
What is after the bomb
It's being a thing where this place is
On the police radio proves that the police have foreknowledge of what to look for
I would argue that the two bombs that just died
With or without any preparation
If you're the protector of Public Safety
I think you invited
Immediately
With or without anyone telling you
Keep your eyes out for anything that looks like a bomb
There's no prepping
Natural reaction that you would expect to see
You know what else you expect
Professionals
So the other people on the police radio aren't going to be yelling like
They're trained to handle crazy that
How to
How is this woman
You know you have some dress
It's like what how do you hold so many
Things in your head at a time when
Actually
There's a
Remote
Course
For driving on block.
Okay well that's good
Riesling
So I basically just formed this narrative
He is leading the world
In terms of Boston bombing
Coverage
I'm just blown away because you're on the break
Is it world
Spetsnaz
So this is the space that he's living in
This is a crazy you're listening to a guy
Like
Really
I mean we can hear it right this is a paranoid delusion
Presenting
Paranoid delusion in order to make yourself more
Groundbreaking stuff
Cit
He's being sincere
Cedar here
Mainly because
Is for somebody who has broken
20 years old
Pittsboro Way by thinking he might actually be right one time
I think I did alternative explanation for that could be found in a clip with Paul or he's talking about how the traffic is
Is through the roof I got to figure out exactly how to maximize
Elements are falling into
Really work towards
The narratives that I need to build to maximize traffic
Whatever
Assertive
Sincerity that you're hearing
Could be sincerity on
But it's
Almost certainly one
One of the two
It's definitely not the listening in right now
Media coverage
As if that would as if he could run the
If it wasn't
Is Alex Jones
Perhaps
What actually happened during the bombing
He's making all of this up
I don't know how they're going to get around now
Backpacks
It's
There's nothing to basis on other than I just came up with
In order for everybody to hang their black back
This is
Did I
He's just making
Absolutely
He's losing his mind.
Yeah
Yeah this is nuts
Responsible
Like the motive
A motor very clearly
But the other motive is
How you present
What is happening
And this is where we get to that
Alex
Stop that
Is
Barriers box
This is out of control what is it
This is
What this is the culmination of Alex's prophecies about them blowing stuff up
The Patriots
If you believe that Ben Warren is on
How are you
Is the beginning of all of it
The globalist
If your Prime for the narratives that Alex is put into the world
This is a call
This is a call to
I know he's not in one clip but it's almost impossible to escape that as the conclusion
If this is the big one this is this is this is the beginning of the globalist
What are you prescribing
Queer
Well I mean the good news is
But
Kind of shows
His audience
There are
War percentage
He's got millions upon Millions
Good listeners
Suck it
Ridiculous Infowars base terror attack
I mean you've seen enough
Yeah right
Now that Fox News is calling
Civil War how much
Civil War
We're going to have
Probably
Yeah I don't think we need to get like
2 descending into
To those
Steri-fab
So this caller that Alex is talking
To hear
This guy's really dumb
These callers today are
Real talk
And this one actually
Is relevant to our larger
Investigation
The Sandy Hook one
Alex how are you
Montego Rochelle
About the whole Sandy Hook thing now
This whole
What's going on
Sandy Hook thing deeper
And I found that deer quiz gas company bought
And 2009 blowout the city of Sandy Hook
Steak and I can soda Newtown
I found out my deep searching was
Nobody has lived in Sandy Hook
Past 3 years if you go in the US Census interact
Map
Truck places on interact
And then
Zoom into Newtown
Iucu Newtown on the westside of I-84
Light up
On the right side of
I-84 Nissan
Asia population wipe it all
They put out
Marathon
Will t-shirt
So first of all it's not a city
A-Town it's a village with in Newtown
When does guys looking at the US Census interactive population
To the granular level of villages
New China's population
Blade witch
Contains the residence of
The village of sand
There's nothing suspicious
About this unless
You're very dumb
We're trying to make an argument that's not base
Reality
We just call her is one of the
What are you talkin about with the Iroquois
Is that they built a 1.6
Six-mile stretch of underground pipeline through Sandy Hook
In order to provide additional gas to the northeast of
This was proposed in 2007
Find a Newtown Bee article discussing this suggest
How to plant
If you do look up that article you'll find that this plan was to build not a new pipeline
What's the building additional pipeline to supplement the one they'd already built back in 1989
Which finish Construction in night
So the big issue that they ran into wasn't there were a number of houses that have been built in the area since night
That would make it almost impossible to just wanted to build another stretch of pipe
And in order to do so
They would quote
Need to purchase land
From about 6
The Uruguay gas company didn't buy out the villages
Had to pay off a couple landowners in order to get permissions to build this pipeline stuff
There's no truth or evidence
But this isn't
Example of Alex
He has no idea what this caller is talking
His credit he doesn't pretend that he does
Which is weird
However
Not to his credit
How much is responsive possible
Ability to critically assess this information from
A caller is something
Is a really bad sign for his coverage moving forward
I really don't know I think that
Indicates an openness
To these
Large-scale conspiracies about Sandy Hook
One of those
Prefab towns that they used to test nuclear weapons on in the desert
Tomato nose
You know how you want to dress
So now Jordan
Really
Haley dumb
You want to believe in slime
Ford really gullible a really delicious
Like at the root of it if someone with
Yeah cuz it's misrepresenting
Fact
Like this person didn't look into the Iroquois Gas Company
And then find that they bought the city out
What
Blog post
About this misrepresented
The land-use
That were bought
Are you still working
Yeah he probably found a blog post by like James Tracey
Yeah
That's more than
Paul Joseph Watson
Did regarding
The weather
Sure
Savannah Jordan
Everything goes
Terribly wrong
Steve pieczenik shows up
Oh boy
Brianna is freaking out about what else is going on
Even I come
The same conclusion ironically
Oh boy
Steve is validating all of this but
Conclusion
Different angle
Explain his anger
But listen to this clip very carefully
Because both
Are making
Maybe too much of a point
Pretending that they haven't talked off air
Pretty consistent in Steve's appearances
One of the reasons why I called you yet
I didn't see any of the point you know I didn't have the advantage you that on the video but this is what I wrote
And it's not it's not
Different from what you said
What happened to Bush and Obama and the US military for the tortures of 9/11
Reported on the same day as the Boston Massacre
At the level just below but nobody read it it was in the New York Times
Using Bush jr.
Can Obama war crimes equivalent
Japanese internment during WWII
Mayan psychologically
You and I came to the same conclusion
I don't see your blog post from him
For predicting this only after yeah
Reports about torture that came out
In April 20
Need to figure it out
Regardless of what you was talking about
His main point is that he believes the Boston bombing was a false flag because there was a
Committee that just decided the people carrying out the war on terror war crimes
Has the bombing was made to make sure no one noticed the reporting on this report
What are the reports
To put out by a nonprofit called the center for victims
Torture
And nothing I'm going to say is my
Impugn their you have no
Steve
You know it's not related to them at all
From what I can tell their group mission
Is the fight against the use of torture and further to establish centers were survivors of torture
Rehabilitate
And hopefully get back to a normal happy life
I don't know what time about them as an organization but from everything I can try this
Seem like I'm doing really important work
4 people very much in need of
Is there report that advocates for stopping torture and for Congress to fund rehabilitation program victims
It is not the reports
It's more widespread than just
So I consulted
Like I said
It's a report that was released by the Constitution
In Project
I don't like that
It's titled the report of the Constitution project task force on
This again is a report that was released by a nonprofit advocacy
But Steve is literally calling it an indictment
That kind of language is so
Sloppy for someone
I guess you could say that it's indicting their behavior in the court of public
This is not a government or legal product
Go on to say
This is an indictment that will lead to them being arrested
Criminal indictment
The whole f****** Criminal
This report is 600 pages
And I don't believe that for one second Alex or Steve even got the page 9
They just reported tortured
Besides connected to the bombing as a motive for the false flag and it's Off to the Races
And I didn't choose page 9 Ram
If they got the page 9 they would have found this
Quote
This report was supported in part by grants from the Atlantic philanthropies open Society Foundation open
Proteus fund
Rockefeller Brothers fund
This report was funded by grants from Soros and the rockets
If there's a string pullers of people like Obama and Bush
A report into
Have to pull off a false flag to cover up once it's going to be released
That seems like a level of self-defeating bulshit
The kind of invalidates this entire argument
Well that
We talked about any organizational types probably murdering people as we speak
Eyebrows for sure project is largely funded by grants from store
Of course
This makes complete
Why
The f****** Grant
F****** report
Good
To get away with being lazy
That's so much work they would have had to
Change their narrative
This much work for me to get 25.
Kim 99
None of this is to say
Anything
Against
Investigating the torture that
Steve
Supposed to report 100% disagree and I do believe
Attention away from the conversation
Festiva
Supposedly trying to bring
Light
Cover up your torture you got away with it and a half
The people were like
Go
Also in December 2014.
Committee released a report which actually more possibility of putting people in legal Jeopardy
Weird
Weirdo kind of like all this is bulshit made up
So anyway
And Alex go on the motive
For the bomb
Earlier Alex found the culprit
He isn't conversation telepathically with CNN or whatever
I know they have the motive
Am I heard Fox News
To torture and cover it up
Obama and Bush jr. in prison
Legitimate
In the world of counterterrorism they would be so-called neutralized or didn't put in prison
No they wouldn't
This is
Please put out this report
This is not a legal indictment anyway
Good people in government
Because these weren't people in government
It might have been people who had past careers
In government they might have been former
People in Congress or
It's a lot of lawyers
And stuff and it's funded by Soros
God I feel like I'm
Given a Viewpoint into like
The coke fuel
Night that they wrote back to
You know
I don't know why
Jesus Christ what all you need and it's like I told you
Lizard man
You got you got to keep moving
You got to build this in fast route you're a fallen that f****** water
You take at 2nd
Two critically read this
Report
Everything falls apart
Now
The good guys in government
Is very reminiscent
The counter-coup narrative
B d pechenik pulled on Alex
In 2015 to help ease his way into supporting Trump
What do you know there's a counter-coup going on in 2013
Correct this is exactly right Alex and that's what we've been saying all along
You haven't Saginaw long
Pre-show interview question if I ever heard
He has been saying it all along and he continues to say forever and you just
These theaters
It's always this
It doesn't change
There's a counter-coup going on
In 2013
In 2050 you just pretend it's not the exact same bulshit you say all along
It's broke
Indictment
It's going to put people in prison but it's covered up by Bob and Bob
Coalition, the basic story of the indictment
Junior and two presidents have
Brookline
I would have incarcerated
Because nobody even listen to it
So do you got this
Verbally
Normal firmly in place from a very reputable source
President
Commit war crimes
For Christ's sake
Yeah
So
Yeah we've already had Alex say this is the big one
The globalist defensive his Bugatti
We've had Stewart Road leader of a paramilitary organization
I save it
It's going to turn hot
Westie
Internally
Exactly as I said before
And I think the New York Times has been exceedingly
And signifying how much of a
Establishments
Exactly
The false flag sneaking showing at the guys like me
Fix the newspapers talking to it
Alex communication with Sienna
Read the articles in the newspaper editors are placing them there to send hidden messages
Like as I'm assuming that
That they are communicating to him
By hidden
The paper
Yeah
Lll
Article about this sub this constitution project paper
His message
So just everybody zodiac
He's everybody's the Zodiac Killer
And Steve's B
Cool
These are deluge
Real information
To a vulnerable and gullible audio
Wow this is Joey response
And it gets so much
More irresponsible as Steve starts talking about what we need to do
Describe
That's not good
Sign usually
People need to be
Pacific organization is good
Generally speaking whenever people want to get together
We talked about unionizing I like I like I like an organization
Strike but Wednesday VP says organizing
Already
Replaced all of this is a war on America
You know
Stewart f****** roads it was on earlier say that
And it's not good because Alex has been convinced to Steve's narrative
And that's the motive for the bombing to cover this stuff up
And now
He dehumanizes
Pretty much anyone who doesn't agree with
That's so f***** up
I'm coming to you with a extremist anti-government message
The globalists are making their offensive Warfare guy on here telling me it's time to organize
Militia leaders inevitable
And you know what if people don't agree with you they're dead already
F****** hell man
How to use messages get heard by people like
I mean the only thing I can
I just
Steven
Jerking off
Witf
Like that's just what they want Alex probably
But
Specific
Recommend
And I think yeah
I think these bulshit
And the third one is what he's actually at
Describe the larger spectrum of where we are historically
Call Shirley
Where we are right now is exactly where we were when our forefathers were in 1770
Being oppressed by King George
Literally now
I'm non-legitimate
President
CM government and executive we have not had illegitimate government
Presidency under Bush jr. So frequently 12 years now
Affect what we have is a non-legitimate
Hierarchy cord had a mini older us so we have the right
To indict our presidents to organize
Not only for this president for the impeachment of bush
Junior and all of his
Now
Nuremberg Trial this is a war trial now
Junior
And the bilateral commission saying that they were criminals
Request a new election as soon as possible
Can we go into what is called the Revolutionary Moe's
Can we go to the guns
I have no qualms about that
Forces used to suppress basketballs flags are used to give us honesty
In the face of tyranny treason is Patriots
Let me say it again
Tyranny which we have right now in the bush
Which is an act against the government
Keepsake
So
What you have here is Steve Morelos declaring open season for AC companies
He's saying that we need to call for impeachment
These Dum Dums been calling for a peach and Obama for over four years at this point
His second suggested calling for an Erbert trial isn't absurd for him to suggest Alex's audio
What's the one thing more than anything else
The concept of international law
I just see it now Alex calling on the UN to remove the elected president of the United States
That's ridiculous
Non-starter
Absolutely ridiculous thing is that they're three
And the underlying unspoken messages that the first two aren't really
The first ones went right over and over and hasn't work
The second involves a complete breach of the fundamental ideas that the Patriots and weirdo militia guys at about sovereignty
Something not going anywhere
This is about finding a way to rationalize calling for an armed
What's Steve doing on this episode of made the movie the most dangerous most irresponsible thing I've heard
Daytona
What's the show
He's walking around his fake resume an imaginary credentials
Incredibility
Come on to the show and lie down says audience of profits report
I'll torture being actually illegal in the bush
Obama
Is it this is the time they've been waiting for
This legal indictments been made and it didn't do anything
They just did a bombing to keep it out of the news
The really the legal and appropriate channels are not how this thing is going to be solved
He's stopping short of saying the people should be committed violent revolution
But that's 100% the message
Did he put in for
These guys are trying to get people
Oh yeah there is no way around that
Listen to listen to this s*** man
Are we in fact in charge
You are now in charge your commanders and chief or not
They are illegal
Are legal presence
And therefore Justified
Can internal in the major levels
Questioning Authority the commander-in-chief
Entry level because they've been indicted for war crimes
Authoritative
Indicted
War crime
Therefore I ask our Military Officers
Stand up and say that this is enough
This is what it comes down to
To work with us
This cannot be run anymore by a little legal
Criminal president
Who was indicted biozone Congress
And the former president is well Clinton
Okay what we got here is him calling for a military coup
He's calling for Insurrection essentially with it the military rack
He's that this is
Is like
I love your idea hold on one second of History over there
Military dictatorship is a bad idea
Wolf Road
Unabashedly
Can you do that
I don't think you
You don't think that you can literally call for the military to take over the government it is actually kind of sticky
Legal question
And I honestly think they probably wouldn't be able to
The s*** though
I think Brandenburg versus Ohio the Supreme Court decision
Leaves a lot of gray area in terms of advocating for illegal things
Bmac from a legal perspective
In order for the government to be able to punish someone
For even advocating illegal act
I think he's on the wrong side of it but I'm not illegal
I want
I think Steve is
Is confessing to what he's trying to do
I wish you would because
Rhetoric like this
Is far beyond
What I believe
The first amendment is
Because
Steve is saying like Okay we need to have this impeachment Nuremberg trials or whatever or armed Revolution
And the mean
To getting
The president out of office
Choose a new president
Now what
A Democrat
You think they're going to be happy either election results
Legitimate
Except
Three presidents in
I wonder how he feel
Feels about Reagan
Reagan was probably his last widget
He works for a didn't work for
Steve essentially is arguing that
These people who are advocating for this coup against the government
Need to be able to choose the next
Come true
There's trouble
And then we nearly asked for the election
And Lilo
That is exactly what we have to do
Do that
Then we use whatever we need whether it's
Which will determine the outcome of the United States
America
Today at the moment
We will regret the day
That we did not stand up
Scrapping is super immediate
And like you literally says this is
If we don't do this today I guarantee you you will not have an American
Tomorrow
That is
So
Stocked up
Do you know what that
That sounds
Just be like
The manifesto of a right-wing f******
Terrorist
Have we had any of those manifestos recently that sound
Exactly like that
I think there's some
So
Listening earlier like
I don't know if he
He could really be
Successfully
Because of
You know these why
Births that are given
To free speech
But if you listen to this next clip
Steven Smith
I'm committing treason
Transmission
Connexus where we are literally in the position of a war against our own federal government
I know what'll happen to me I will be warned repeatedly again
Time in MA
I have everything I am boldly saying I am in an act of treason against tyranny
And I will do that as an act of patriotism
That is my defense
If I go to prison
I'm committing treason
The government is patriotism
Put on trial
You just said
Your intentions are clear you're trying
Insurrection
Death knock
I'm like one of those
Guys who
Goes in
On his own
Turns himself into
The cops
Killing like 5p
People
Anime invest
You didn't
Do that
Right
Yeah I feel like I was part of the game
In the middle of Florida
Korea whenever I want to
It is
It is strange
And probably their best defense
Almost cuz one of the other things
Brandenburg vs Ohio another one of the standards
Is
Likelihood that it will result
Likelihood that your words will lead to Illegal Acts
I guess could be made by Steve
Legal defense
But it doesn't
Match is in
Right isn't
Are predicated on IV presented on Alex's show as
Wonder most credible government insiders psych Warfare expert
It is ever lived
I used to be a part of the CFR but I left because they are bunch of snakes
The presentation of this on the show is
Let's get going guys
Let's do it
And he's like
If you listen to this next clip he's legitimately calling for lone actor
Dude dude
Man in the world is the lone man
We are in slowness we are each individual's that's what makes America great country
Using the internet using other means than supporting our candidate
We can bring down this President we can bring down the government the government is the collusion of the Russia
Cronyism
Nnnn.
Fearful Anthony that cannot stabilize very well
You will have to go through.
Start in the last election
The parties didn't really exist
Are you got over here yet
Jeff
Think this is
Insanity
Now I'm just
Securing of lonely
To tell myself because
No one
You're all I have
I need to re chaos through you
It's talking about how the last election
Wasn't real election
Complaining about
Starts talking about Hillary
And this is a little bit of foreshadowing 420
Fiends election
And then you had Obama who's already pretty much in place as a result of social media
Just an extension of a transgender Hillary Clinton
It's all Hillary Clinton Clinton
Any extension to Obama
Well I'm saying she's more is more an issue here with Hillary than you would imagine she's not exactly
What's the
Dangerous and she's also not legitimacy
She was also indicted for interrogation
Terrorism
In this report
It's not an indictment
Also I love the idea that he's like casting these like
Stupid Hillary's
And then
Inflammatory
So ridiculous
More
4 attacks
That's what the government
Cyber attacks
Cyber War by anyone
Anonymous
Take down this government
Well the point is the truth has to mobilize people in fashion
People now have to ask a bird the truth
Now been told and reaffirmed by their own Constitution
Constitution
Breakaway tours
You got it
Slaves
I got
I want to put too fine a point on
Steve pieczenik is Super Lucky
What he's doing is explicitly a federal offense
And because Alex allows him to do it on his show
Possibly be in trouble too
According to us code chapter 115
Team section 2385
Whoever knowingly or wilfully Advocates of bats advisors
The Doodie necessity desirability or propriety of overthrowing order
Destroying a government of the United States or the government of any state territory District
Or possession arrow
Or the government of any political subdivision there in by force or violence
We're by the assassination of any officer
Or whoever with intent to cause or overthrow
Or destruction of any government
Prince Publishers edit
Issues circulates paused
Or publicly displays any written or Printed Matter advocating advising or teaching necessity desirable
Or propriety of overthrowing or destroying any government of the United
Or violence or attempts to do so
Shelby find under this title or imprisoned
Not more than 20 years
This is the section of the u.s. code on treason in
Sedition
It's because he's committing treason
But he has decided that it's patriotism
Because of
Tucson project report
But he's misrepresenting as a criminal in
There's a big f****** deal
Steve pieczenik is actively and clearly committing treason
And Alex doesn't cut him off
Or even really given much pushback at all
And that's where that second
Closet section 2385 comes in
Possibly make it
Compelling argument that Alex's printing publishing circulating Distributing
Not granted that statute that specifically say printed
But I have to assume
These dudes are probably legally in the clear
Thanks to Brandenburg versus Ohio
Which roles of the government can't punish speech
Abstractly Advocates criminal Acts
But this is walking right up to that line
Stevens getting pretty smooth
He's calling for Lone Wolf actors become a cyborg abstract anymore
Tossing out ideas
I understand with you from
It's it it's that
But I don't know his legally
Write the definition of abstract
Might be a lot broader
Then
What you and I
Common sense
Perspective
No use telling soldiers that there
Command has no Authority
The Brandenburg standard of what government can still punish is if the advocate
Be construed to be advocating eminently
I'm not a lawyer
Very much seems like Steve is trying to
Where I think Steve runs afoul of the law is that he literally said
Isaac
You're not going to
Call for treason
I'm going to call for armed government I don't give a fuk
Come at me bro
Well I don't know whether or not
To be successfully prosecuted
As always
The legal aspects of this is secondary
Steve and Alex both now
Impressionable state right now
Because of the bomb
Alex has been priming the pump for a while now
And in this episode he's clearly told his audience repeatedly there's a false flag attack against
The Patriots
And this is the big one
The beginning of the gobbos defensive round up the good white people of this country and put up in
Hebrews at Stevens Annex
And when he comes in the payoff to all of this is it
Licit treason
And advocated war against the government
Which is totally just patriotism because the government is illegitimate as proven by
A non-profit
Like this is unacceptable on so many levels
Steve's talk
It's almost
Like you forget
But the Boston bombing
You know like
The context wherein
This conversation is misrepresenting in lying to his audience
To create the appearance of like
This is it
We got to jump we got a job
And
The payoff is a psych Warfare expert coming in and telling Alex
Would like
I'm committing treason
The soldiers need to turn on their chain of command
Cyberattacks against
The government must happen
It's time for us to organize into groups
Like I didn't
Think it could get worse
Once
To live in the world
They are not
Not knowingly
Trying to cause
Trying to call
Terror attacks
Every nice
But they are trying
2 caused
Set that is not
You came up with
Like this is a thing that they did
Affair
Play X
Play
How to kill people
And they want that to occur
So
There
You guys are attempted murderers
By like what
What would we talkin
Traffic report
It really is like ideas literacy
They're doing everything they can
To make this work wow
Just as bad
And I heard the stuff up with Paul and the pictures of the people
I thought like well this is as bad as it gets
And then Steve shows up and he's like I'm committing trees
Aaron like
I don't know how much worse this can get
This doesn't resolve
The Girl Next Door
Mama didn't get shot
So
Finishes up his interview with Steve
He signs off
After about four and a half hours of
Haha
Goodnight take over for some more time to the do in the six-hour broadcast
Who cares about what they're doing probably
Who gives a
I believe that he feels he's cracked the case
He's found the culprit
Patsy
The media is responding to his coverage
And now we have a motive
Text to Steve
And I he's rattled his base up into incredible friends
Betrayed
In front of everyone where they
The pressure cookers
I mean this is just
2 hours equals
T-Mobile stay on present
This is G
Because
The next
Those photos
Unbeknownst to Alex on a lot of the world
Had gone back to their normal lives
Buy one of them younger brother
I got back to college
The factor was video that came out
Of him
Some parties
Like nothing had happened
And the older brother got back to his life in his apartment with
And
When the photos get released
It Causes Chaos
Because they realize that they didn't get away with it
The way they might
Based on all of the coverage have no information
Based on
I want one of them as we will later learn is a fan of Infowars
Completely
And that is not the case
Everything blows up on the 18th
Happens in the evening of the 18th
Are going to be such
Insanity
And if we're at the point where one of Alex's most
Trusted sources
Is coming on Aaron advocating
Treason
Before any of that stuff happen
Before the Manhunt
Before the city is put into lockdown
I can't imagine how dark
Chris is going to get
Before we get through it
So yeah
S***
Not good
Arrested
Millions of dollars
I wish I wish
I wish that anybody pay attention to Alex the way he imagined
Like the law thing
Justice would have been such red flags
Yeah like this is real bad
Yeah
Pretend
That's not good
Nope
But the good news
Is we have a website
No
The Kerry Cassidy over project has gone bad
And we have an extra day this week
So
If you're feeling everybody
You're feeling really overwhelmed by this
Look forward to a nice break on Wednesday we're going to get back to space weird
First off let's just remember
We are in 2019 the Civil War did not
Yes a lot of this is
Sound and Fury signifying
But
It is also the sort of thing that's in
Talib people
Like I mean
It's not a direct consequence of this
Coverage per se
But like
You know a couple years prior to this
One of Alex's listeners killed three cops when his mom called the police
A year after this
Two people who are big Infowars fans
I killed some cops in Las Vegas
Like it's not
It's easy to look at this stuff where Steve is calling for an Insurrection in the military and all this and bag
The large-scale
Version that you would be afraid of happening
But that's not to say that people who are
To take in his rhetoric
Hasn't
So
There aren't the terrifying world-changing consequences
But that doesn't mean there aren't I
Seems like
Their ultimate goal
Because
Cuz you and I both
The GOP does
It all have
Like my dad doesn't want doesn't
Secretly want
How to start an arms
Right
4A
Do this
The government reacts and then people like my dad
Well you know I don't approve of those guys bumps
But the government
Spirals out of
Control from there
And also build up a narrative that those people who bombed
Stop in the first place
Was a false flag by the overreaction in order
Yep very transparent
Cam also Twitter
Rose wallpaper
You go tonight
Whatever
Castrol app
To using a
And I could leave a review
We love it
Neil
I believe
Dzx Clark
I'm the juiciest.
Alexandra Thurston color