Damn important I'm sweating
I have great respect for knowledge B B I'm sick of them posing is just through the good guy
MoneyGram
College vype.com
Outside
I like that
Because just before we started recording you informed me that you've never been booed
I feel like after that indeed you got that stew people listening
I know you have announced
But have you ever tried to repair a wrestling
What's a great professional
You are going to run a ad campaign
I did some in ring announcer guy turns out I'm not very good at that
I'm pretty bad
Bystander
That's not what you do
I'm not good at that
No I don't think so
Powerbomb my friends at the bean bags
Columbia Missouri
Borderline megachurch room full of bean bags
Some of the early
Early in the Church of development that's what they'd have the youth meeting
They're tons and tons of giant bean bags
You do like ddt's and power bombs
Backyard wrestling
Proto
Office is like a text start up off as like a Google where it's like we're all sitting around
Similarities
Feeling similarities
Watched
Hell in a Cell WWE pay-per-view and
Did not did not go Gray
Really want to f****** Hershey's chocolate
Is all f****** legal
Is this what I did in a disqualification
Which is supposed to be exactly, to the rules
Let's just said no no no no no
Read while I grew up watching like Triple H
Scarier
This is ridiculous
So
Dissuade me from ever
Actually doing
Bad taste in my mouth
I don't even watch that much wrestling anymore I just like randomly checked in on Sunday
Disaster
Great
Everybody is pretty well-versed in the wrestling
Match but also the meta games played above it on the underwriting lover
It seems like they have far more freedom to do whatever whatever they want
Ending in 2212 occasion of his cell match
Kayfabe
Is gone
Yeah it doesn't reducer like what was the decision
You you thought about that in advance
I guess
From the other night and I know a lot of it I was just
But it doesn't matter Jordans
Long overdue
To finally.
Who goes around and interviews face weirdo
Been to space
Have a lot of the interactions with space aliens
One guy who works at a bus station as telescope
The roster is not good
I was going through it
Albeit
Remain lunatic person her biggest source
Is the guy named Mark Richards who is in prison for masterminding converter
Absolutely
Aashiqui
We'll get into that a little bit as always
Tell scary stories about the secret space program
The greatest heroes that Humanity has ever known
Flying Dutchman
Remember his first name
He's got an invisible
Minerva
Detailed episodes
But this is the eleventh interview and it's very exciting for long time for Jerry do anything worth going
Here we are
How about before we get to
Amapola
Phone Zone
Next Cara
Kahoot
Hippos
Israel
Elevated
Nicholas
You're all wonderful technocrat
I'm a policy wonk
Business
Money off at heroin
So good
Freakishly large
Thank you so much William Rochelle
Shoutouts
People are waiting a long time
Couldn't button that says that's where
Which
How do you know if they still exist
Anyway Jordan
Let's do it first
Sears in out-of-context
Text Rob from today
Now who you going to call when you go to work
Ghostbusters
Know who you going to call if you answer is not the Ghostbusters
Google call it's in the song
Without the real knowledge of what she was doing
I can't imagine
I really feel like I know
She be like I don't know what ghost
What the answer is a Ghostbusters
Secret space program
Episode introduction
Hi I'm Cherry Castle
I carry
My latest
Interview with
Captain Mark
And I
Interviewed him in the beginning of September however I've had multiple
With both
Computers
And
Various
Renditions
Little Talks
And now I'm trying to
That's all
So here we go and help
So apparently she has recorded this couple times over
Visit Mark Richard maybe like a month ago or so and now she's finally being able to get this information out
And that's great
Every single time the Carrie comes back
From visiting Mark Richard
Recording audio
The
Prison people don't have a pen
But
She does get a small pencil
So what happened
Only allowed app
This is called
Total Recall
So what happens is
I go into the prison
And we have around
3 hours
Sometimes longer
I think this time
3 hours
I am able to
She asked him as many question
Since as I
Although I'm not allowed
So
If I didn't remember
To ask
You requested
I do apologize
Some information baby see that that flow being
I think they probably confiscated
To talk to a cult leader of the murderer
You responded exactly as I
Saturday
Huge jumps got there
This clearly Tech problems going on there's also like you'll see develop
He's just editing this very weirdly
Broadcast
The cheese that she's putting out about that
But what's important is that Mark Richard is not a murderer
The court system
Confessions of his conspirators
Spell all natural
And for everybody who hasn't heard all the mark Richards episodes here is Carrie's playing
In the beginning
Want to save this
Text place in Solano Prison in Northern California
And
For over 35 years Captain Mark Richards
Has been
And still is
A prisoner of war
Are in the war
Between on-and-off Planet races
Have dominated Earth
For centuries
He is an honorable officer of the Navy
Because of his
Rebellion
Against the Draco
And
Just called the loose
Safari in Alliance
Is considered a threat to their Opera
He was framed for murder he's accused of
I'm having Mastermind
While he was on a mission
Send off planet
In service to humanity
He wasn't captain
Starship Enterprise
Vessel
From an very early age
In fact
Probably early twenties
That
Until he was
Was arrested
I believe it was 19
As a master
Again he is frame for a murder
He is accused
Having masterminded while he was
Is on a mission off-planet
Humanity
You hear that that's just exactly repeating what you just said
Redoing
This what is going on
I have a big theory about that
She called the prison guards like zinus
I think that I don't think that's the case
Different pictures that we have over from what we started talking about
Yeah I think so
She might believe
Some things like that I don't think that's the case
I think they
I think is just clunky editing
She is going to
Create
I do not
Keeps this speaker
Because there's
An instance of this later
Where she uses the wrong name for someone and then there's immediately jump cut
It's pretty clear to me that what's going on is that she's f****** up her script she's poorly editing the pieces
Together and then after the fact is inserting
An explanation for it
I feel like I can tell you that now cuz it's kind of implied
Visiting other interviews of hers bees like
High-level terrible presentation
The flip-flops
She says for this murder to do is all planted in service
Small paws
It's like this is just
Move this out
Text Kate to lack of care about the product you're putting
You know like if it's this bad
Jump cuts to the point where just anybody listening
This is only an hour long video of the long drive
Turn our 2121 measurement
The substance of what's going on
Into
I don't know this is the big deal
But it takes up a bunch of overtime
And that is the cheetahs run into a super soldier
He has a
Half brain
Harebrained idea
So the first
Real topic
Take that we discussed
Is the Randy Cramer City
Situation with revisiting the alien
Black scenario
And I told
Mark briefly about that idea
And
Randy Cramer is
Super soldier
U.s. Marine
At the Young
With
Me and others
And hopefully that footage will be available
In the near
Fingers crossed
We got Randy Cramer who is this
Mike Richards
It was a super Soldier come out
Scenario
I will just explain it to you right now because it's really hard to put together from what Carrie say
The bottom line here is that she believes
That Kramer is coming out today
This conference
Whatever speaking at cussing
Behalf of his military handlers
The idea of
Precipitating an alien false flag in order to force disclosure
Okay
Disclosure of alien existence
We need the world to understand that there's a battle going on
Down the street over Lake Michigan right now there is a
Every storm battle
Actually Spider-Man
Probably
Giant spider
Because that's the real world situation
Yellow the alien stuff however
The evil powers-that-be the globalists the New World Order the Illuminati
To disclose all of this stuff if it is disclosed
Humanity and population will learn that they've been hoarding all of the secret technology for themselves
Free energy all the miracle cure
I guess probably Alchemy
Uno
So all this stuff is alien technology that they've stolen for themselves will be revealed
About on the street
Trying to keep this technology from us in order to peacefully
Do this
Dayton Air
To have an alien false flag
They need to have a
Speak
Version of aliens appearing in order to explain this technology being rolled out
Randy Cramer is coming out and saying that he's military handlers or whatever allowing him
Him to start talkin about the
It's convoluted right why even just playing clips of Kerry talked about this
Okay
That's Randy Kramer's
Input into the process
The plans of their perceived enemies
There
It's stupid
I would feel betrayed if I found out that
Like f****** Nancy Pelosi has all kinds of
Secret eggnog
Right there schemes to counters
Are far more ridiculous on top of
The other two
Miracle cures that Randy Cramer talks
Right like Eternal youth that kind of thing
Why would David Rockefeller end up being like
A super unhealthy ninety-year-old dude if he had access to this
Life extension
Age regression technology
Always
Occam's razor
This leads into talking about this situation a little bit more
Audi
Kerry might not call it the globalist
They call it like
Secret
Illuminati folks
They have all of this
The technology
This leads into like
The Dynamics of the disclosures
He was talking about the military
Frustration
With our current standstill
On planet Earth
With regard to
Disclosure
And the fact that they have
A very high state of
Technology
In the secret
Unable
2 releasing
Into the public domain
In part because
Disclosure
Everything
More difficult
So what we have is a roast
Zacian
Which involves
U.s. military
Secrets
Program
The Illuminati
And various other factions
Including
Very safe
He races
Short and
Therefore they are
Operating
Basically
What can even be considered
Be thousands
Of what we are
None
So this is a big deal and
Randy Cramer
Military are now
Coming up
With a solution
It has to do with
Revisiting this ID
False flag
Bluebeam of course
In the past
Only people
Or a fake
Alien invasion
So this is the solution here project
It comes up
Call the f****** time project maybe if you know things
Maybe if you're a researcher
It's one of the biggest most popular UFO conspiracy paranormal community
First thing that I should point out to you I think is very important about that project it's not a real thing
The name refers to a project Bona claimed exist
But no evidence to support the claim has ever been present
According to Montes
In order to New World Order
The bad guys first created New Age religion to replace the religion people currently subscribe to
It also seems like he's mostly interested in talking about the breaking down of Christianity resources
Christy other world religions
Christian
Destroy Christian whistleblower
Sure sure
The primary focus destruction of
Christianity
In order to achieve this goal they need to destroy these current religion switch
Specific sites around the world
Which ultimately Unearthed evidence that contradicts the known world religion
This'll be a dumb plant that's most religious belief is not based on empirical evidence and it isn't really susceptible
Career Point
Either way
What's this new world religion is in place the NWO venues hologram
Avatars of each religion
To the people in the areas where that religion is probably has the Buddha
Buddhist
I guess I throw a tree in for wiccans or something I don't know Daya
These avatars with emergent Grice
Whichever one with that worship but it's all just a trick it's all Holograms
Now that the public accept this new God the NWO would begin using electronic waves
I to begin projecting thoughts into
The people's heads
Making them think that God is talking to them
This would facilitate their ultimate goal which is making everyone think that a real crisis
In the form of an impending Alien Invasion or the Rapture whatever formation I detect
The people will be so scared that they would beg for the implementation of the New World Order and just like that the one world government isn't
Easy as riding a riding a bike
Everything goes according to plan
00, States along the way
Machine of a silly plan there a lot of really dumb parts and probably too many to count
Go to be set to motion
Incorrectly a lot of July
Analogous tikli stupidest plan is
Alex Jones definitely believe that Project Blue beam
Okay but he's smart enough not to talk about it because he knows if he does
He's going to look like a f***
Stupid space weirdo
First thing
I would definitely believe the globalist attracted
Destroy Christianity in order to have their own religion
You said this a bunch of time
Whether it's in the formula saying is the new religion or
Sometimes it is political correctness for the globalist
To trying to get rid of these religions
Because they're a threat
Like
The ability to the New World Order
Follows very closely with this project
Templar that religions are
Pesky
Suppose plan follows almost exactly the Hungarian dialectic
Problem reaction solution
The globalist Opera
They can only take power by creating chaos which they then provide a solution
That sort of thing really fits with Alex's
Conception
Everything in this Theory matches up with things that Alex believe
The UN is behind the plan
It involves destroying National sovereignty
It involves making
All money electronic
It involves the destruction of the family unit
It involves camps for people who won't accept a new world order
Involves the human sacrifice specifically of Christian children
It involves the literal devil being behind the New World Order Hidden Falls movies and television shows preparing
World for the rollout of plant predictive programming there's heavy overlap
There's one other aspect
Maybe there's one other aspect of this that makes me suspect Alex believe this
Most of the people who believe in this area are basing their belief on a 1994 lecture given by surge Mana
One small point about this lecture
It's only available as a transfer
Published on educate yourself. Org
Hey bad news about this
In the middle of the lecture the editor of the site interrupt
At this point interrupting the transcript I'm compelled to include three statements from the protocols of the Elders of Zion
Effort to reinforce this bonnet
Geico claims
Run by the Jews
How could we imagine that they weren't behind
In the lecture modest argues that the plan was originally to start this plan up in 1980s
Ultimately bringing in the New World Order the next year which explains floor Wells book 1984
Right
Yes it's like there was a 1994 and you know what that means
The globalist are 10 years
Behind on their plans
The Alex is so consistent
Like how we randomly just says that they're 10 years behind with no citation or explanation for what he's talking about
Hey my specific sources that I've been able to find that Alex is referenced in other contexts
I can't find any real concrete instances of people saying the globalist plans or 10 years behind
This lecture about Project Blue beam is very explicit about exactly that
Not necessarily
But it's a possibility
This very bizarre element
Is Project Blue beam was 10 years behind very explicitly
I don't know
Manny this is right around 1 Alex started his radio career
We're going to get coincidences
And maybe maybe could just be ozmosis like he's aware of these space weirdo
It's entirely possible it's just a coincidence and a lot of people have ideas about the bad guys being 10 years.
Listing of Project Blue beam of the time of the government
Consider using an alien.
I know she's learned that super soldier Randy Cramer
Very real military cohorts
Using the same tricks to force the government to disclosure
So the be forced to release all the secret technology they can keep themselves using the nwos plan against
Newt New World Order
The first two problems that come up here are what
Kramer's going to be
Faking It
He doesn't have the resources
Planning skills creativity
Definition
People have actually been able to trace down where Serge monast got his ideas from
Okay world order was supposedly going to be carrying out where all elements of an unproduced
Describe the Gene Roddenberry had written in 1975
In a first attempt at making Star Trek into a movie
The script unreleased 1975 when he had written it Niger
But in 1994 just prior to bonnist coming out with his lecture in Revelation
Joe langel had written a book called Gene Roddenberry the myth in The Man Behind Star Trek
Which included a bunch of information about the Shelf project
Never made into a movie back in 1975
Many elements of the original script were used in the 1991 Star Trek the Next Generation episode The Devil's Due
Which also predates modest conspiracy theory
All of this comes from
Picard
This is a Hostess raspberry chip
Of course
Really highly rated episode like more
Dancehall Soca
Just about like
Captain Picard
Get into like
Legal arbitration against Amalia
Yeah
Blue BBQ zazen
Example is first of all just like
I mean I love it
I love it
Purdue speedrun
That was very much like
Star Trek
Starship
Enterprise like crap
Never
Never surprising to me how little effort or imagination
Communities in paranormal communities have called this out about
Need to go to Skeptics site to find the information about Project Blue beam to people rip off from Star Trek
Site
They even discredit this s*** people who are on
Closer to the up-and-up people who are a little bit more critical of information or like
There's no way
Didn't take this from that
May just not possible information was out there
There's a really good chance
That he had seen
The Next Generation episode
Maybe read the angles book and just incorporate it into a theory
So
I don't know
Stupid
Astral projection
Gene roddenberry's house
Exactly
Exact
Even if you bring up and point out all this
Gene Roddenberry
That would be in a Star Trek episode
Need to prepare the world.
Silver dollar trap
We're trying to pull a false flag Independence
What's going on
More or less
So that's great and that'll come back up
Reappears
Of course is Randy Cramer coming out with salt
Information
Before we get back to that
We have some more information
From Mark
Okay
Is another Tran
That I'm seeing more and more of these interviews
And that is
Try to take
Okay and I think you do a great disservice
To reality
The idea here is that
Hidden War
Are also
So he can buy
Fires in California
2 years
We had fires in northern and southern
Simultaneously
In the month
Last year
We're coming up on the firestick
Season again this year
So you got these fires that are largely the result of climate change
And and
Yeah yeah
Dealing with that in a real way
Solutions
You pretend that they're just cover-ups for alien invasion
That's
A real trend
They were going to see
Not just in relation to climate stuff
But in terms of any kind of geopolitical issue everything is just
Does kind of enforces of complacency on people
Because if
If in reality all of the world issues are really just covering up alien invasion
What can you do
Other than
Tell us about the alien
There's nothing else you could really do there are avenues for productive change
Based on that everything is going great
There isn't International conflict All in This Together
Problem
Sure is there any way for us to broadcast
Our show to perhaps
Drake
I don't think they'd listen
That's how we could make our show you and me we could make
The difference in this f******
We could have our own little Yalta Conference
My house burned down like 10 years ago
Apologize
Okay
Thunderstorm
Absolutely
So are we get back
To the false flag
Alien false flag scenario here conference with Randy
Where she got to ask
Question
She is not thrilled with some of
Randy is
Responses
I challenge
Randy Cramer
And that
Created some
To do because Randy
Was not happy
The challenge
And
Actually we parted.
Friends Joey
It was all in
Really
Positive
Light
What kind of
Alien
Shoes
How's my first question
She keeps asking
Indoraptor indoraptor
It's it's all about doing to protect her
Friendly alien races military people that the Raptors shall not be used at this post Library
Performance
Look I know you're on your Griff Time on My Grave
Is great
But in reality
It seems like that might be the case
Although a Q&A session during the conference is still kind of performance time
No that's what I'm saying that's the feeder that there is
There is any actual
Behind-the-scenes self-reporting
Exact
Still all could be
To an extent performance
Positively
Oh I'm sure
There's only so much arguing you can do about imaginary thing eventually you're either going to fight or be like
Drink
Calm down
Whatever
I took this took place at the yelma conference
Carrie keep saying
The first 45 times she brought it up but Alma Powell
Yelm
Okay
A bunch of times
Thoroughly
You know
I figured
Initially that's like okay it's probably a bunch of space weirdos they rented out a hotel conference room what the f*** ever
But it wasn't never heard before
Started 2017
As an offshoot of the Yelp
Tell Danielle population
I watch the promotional videos of the Uso fast and it's mostly people setting up booths to sell alien t-shirt
And some absurd musical performance
Why people interrupt
Commercial Enterprise mixed with a state
Fair kind of entitlement
Barbie puzzle bobble heads and if you just imagine a state fair but it
Yeah that I got and it's an assessment born out by a number of Articles from local
Yeah
There's like people who do art like alien themed art for sale on site.
Good time
The UFO Fester's free since they want families to come in and enjoy the food vendors and weird
Highest number
Possible
Potential customers for the alien merch vendors
Symposium
The conference
Is not free
An article in the Daily Chronicle from 2017 put the price of tickets at $250 for a 3
3-day pass to the symposium
Okay
What are the spiders
That year in 2017 was a woman named JZ Knight
Who claims chicken channel 35 thousand-year-old Warrior Spirit named Ramsey
A large number of followers because of this
She's also dropped the blueprint for
Education center has described nights
The group as fulfilling main requirements
Destructive cult
We should start
The splc 2014 on videos of some of her lectures to her followers that include her saying things like
The following
Quote
God's chosen people
I think hard enough cash tip
I think they've earned enough cash to have paid their way out of the goddamn gas Chambers by now
Yeah
She still invited to speak at this Cosmic Symposium three years after this came out
Also earlier this year night tried to reach out to the community by saying that he was a Divine intelligence
This isn't surprising basic level
If a cult leader knows anything it's how to identify vulnerable populations for potential followers
People are the biggest game in town on that level right now
Who is a cult leader video later absolutely
Essence of H Guiding Light
They're ripe
Different directions
Sweep that s*** up and up
Very important to pay attention to
Isn't it amazing that you can
Steve these other parasitic cult leaders like literally tried
Find like the Giant
Section that's so wild that these people are so dumb
Mq2 this
Call it or call it in a bad place life possibly vulnerable
Look my parents were in a cult I know how you
You get into Vault herbal is a better way to put a conversation.
And a lot of people are in a circumstance in their life make them
Are the
Victims of the
Malicious Act
Not presume to judge
Is it best I can
I agree with you
First cult
But if you start at 1 and then jump over baby
No Maybe
That would be nice
But also it doesn't always work in the way where someone going to call and then it become completely disillusioned
They go from
Sometimes I think like this was right but something was wrong let me resign this
Another one
Part of one almost makes you more prone
Vulnerable
I wish it was the case that all of this was rational choice
100%
The people who are
Being targeted by her get a little bit more
Empathy
I mean like I said videos of her yelling
Came out in 2014 she was invited to the 2017
Y'all
Conference Cosmic Symposium somebody weight
What are the standards by which
This conference
If they allow someone like who's running a destructive
Very strong anti-Semitic
That's not just someone who channels a f****** alien
Ill-will
And they're still like
Sorry 2018 the festival's cut down to a two-day event the Earth UFO Festival
$150 for full access to the symposium
Don't really announces the lineup for this thing
Of this conference on her website
And this year
She was there along with Randy Cramer
But also Mark Richards wife Joanne was they have course
Mark Richards Associates
Simon Park
And there is a
Suspicious
All right. Duke on there I don't know what I don't know what that was about
I look a little deeper my founded in 2018
Last year Carrie was there too
She was there I got two years in a row that you're
3 hour time slot on Saturday which is well along
That must have got enough you know who else
Jordan sather
Denoted qanon promoter who's involved with that whole let's drink bleach thing earlier this year
Festival only book in the top people
Weird
Both speakers
There's a heavy heavy overlap in The rosters
Puregear
Yeah UFO Fest
Facebook page to find the lineup for the first year in 2017
What can't what
Simon parkes and Randy Cramer there that you're too
He's been there every year okay
I don't think so at least not in the official announcement
But get that
Also in 2017 you know who else was there
Enlisted as a child to go on teleporting missions to Mars with a young kid would grow up to be President Barack Obama
Can breathe underwater
Which fuse run for president in 2020
I need the I need this clarified
Where is Scotland
Hyphen dolphin not have
Dolphin hyphen Warrior
No not have a man who as I recalled
Call from listening to an interview
Bermuda Triangle there's a base down there and because he is half dolphin and can breathe underwater
He is able to swim down there
Years ago from now
Hey why he was there the first year
Okay I'm getting out of this conference looks like s***
It's an offshoot of a state fair ass UFO Festival
Regardless of whether or not they're completely mentally unstable regardless of whether or not their cult leaders
There's a lot of lame UFOs symposium
But honestly this once
Balalaika
Kramer putting out his UFO false flag
Scenario
Western
No I don't
You don't even think it's all up to the field man
Oh I got an awesome cool I would like to go to it I would pay for the supposed
Fries
I'm sorry I would assume
Sneaker
So are we back to this and talk some more about this
This false flag strategy
Close
You'll see what I was talking about earlier why I think she's editing
Cricket in the middle of this
She calls Randy Rahn
Clearly here that's exactly where the edit happened
I did talk about
This
Dichotomy
And why
They would have
Disclosure
Obviously
They don't want
Lynch Mob
To come forward
When
Things like
Free energy
Bedrock
The result
Disclosure
And
That this kind of
Create
A great deal of
After
Lakewood
After which
Trot out
Free energy
Commercial
Travel
The fact that they
Interstellar
There's so many ways to edit better than this
Why do you say that
Leaving in Ron
You can just be like
Sorry super simple
Seemed to imply that maybe she said something
Screaming obscenities
I don't know it's just very clear based on things like that
You kind of 300 whatever there's these jumps it's probably because there was some problem with the original recording
She's not good enough editing or production
You just like
You do another take and that you make it obvious that there's a second tag
Jump cut in the middle of the episode
Getting to be an issue and she has no real explanation for it
There is
We're drop frames
Happening with me
Don't know why
In this recording so I apologize for
For that
And you will see it periodically
Convenient that he's dropped frames
You know just
That's just like when you build an audience like that
We're looking into
What is clearly just
I'm sitting at edited
Or
Next.
Living in a reality that is cutting
And maybe like 10 minutes later
Reality itself is glitching
The only thing that I can buy
Probably
And I do want to say that
My
In a very strange
Disconnected
Because of the drop
Frame issue
But it's not really a drop frame
Microphone
Connected
Happening is
Internet
Interfering
Computer
Trying to
This interview
So please
Some kind of
It may be the
The military
Is shooting
Could
Sure
4 on the other
Absolutely
When she said it just
Could be I really thought she was going to say it just could be some sort of a processing issue
I knew for a new there was 02
Aliens
Hey look I don't really know this computer super well yet it's brand new
I don't know maybe the settings aren't set totally right there's all kinds of like
Little
Venusian through our recording
Different recording Serta paradigms
Set up over the course of doing the show
And especially when we switched from me playing the clips from my phone to doing it straight from the computer
There were a ton of little slip-up could have very easily been like Alex doing a DDOS attack on us
Technology you're not used to whatever system you're using or
By whatever don't like
I don't understand for bravado like that
I will tell you this 100
Percent here was my thought as she was going through that
Something's interfering with my new computer as I get to new computer
No
Champ
Inhale you will even acknowledge that that
Could be the possibility
Note
More Furious
At the great fishing isn't the fact that she doesn't know how to use that way
It is a window into how this thought process
Everything is an indication of what you wanted
Every single damn thing
Fits into the
Pre-constructed narrative the yardi have
I'm having a difficult time getting this episode together because I keep
Miss speaking or
This program glitches and I'm not totally sure how to use it yet
Pulse weapon attack
Yep
Throw up
Wonder if that eliminates
Like you know how
You have that moment
Suddenly
For some reason you've just lost the remote control
And you can't find it
Curious
There's no reason
That you can't find this remote control it's such a petty silly thing
Everyday
Pictures of bad I am as a person
She doesn't have that she's just like
Alright
I'll get a new remote
I suspect they're still the same anger directed aliens
I don't think this is like sort of frees you up to be easy about the frustration
His wife
It's just shut off self
Honcho
Punching a wall and I will
If I ever agree I will punch
I don't think I appreciate what you're suggesting
Were the case then maybe I would recommend being a therapeutic
Don't think that's the case okay
So you can meditate on
You can believe that
Choose your
Option
So
We get back to Randy
And now
So so far alien
False-flag disclosure
Okay
This is probably about
2/3 mark
1/3
But the stuff is a little bit more
Bingo
Like you know
There's an actual conference brought a project blue beam
There's more things
Butt cheek
She now kind of
Makes the conspiracy out of this there might
Randy Cramer might be working across
Purposes
A little bit
Sheetz
Suspicion
Now it is also important to realize
In this scenario
Idea forward
Through
To this very alternative group in Yelm
Which is a very small
And
Disseminate
Too cute
Humans certain
Amount of
Trickle down into the alternative community
And so that those p
During the battles with
Aliens that are actually real
Would be putting out the ideas
So that
There would be some cooler heads
Putting the doubt
This is again an Illuminati
But
On the other hand
When in reality
I don't even care
This is the first time
Where I've been angry at her
For coming up with the things that I would have said to mock her without stupid this planet I just
You want to say
Throw your hands up
Double Bluff
And then we'll move on Illuminati is getting
Brandy
Say this stuff
In order to hip
Some real cool people
Right order to be there when a real alien invasion happens to say a
Man
I just I can't hang
You've ever
Remarkable about it is that there is an element of this that is like really it's
But it's good critical thinking
Do you know what your terms of it being what are the possibilities
You know you can secure in the fact they're talking about a fake alien
Considering I got the motivation
For saying app
Like the fact that she's taking it that far into like alright maybe it's right
Fake sincere that half-ass Pewaukee
At least exercise down
Should walk with him
Yeah it doesn't lead you the right place though crazy
It's misdirected critical thinking
Almost
Even more even it's heartening in a way that is more disheartening that I could ever be
Is that
Through our time with Carrie
She has become
More critically thinking
The problem is
She is applied it to
Even more insane ideas
She used the most
Credulous person that could be happy just believe everything
Grown as a person only to become more paranoid
When you're asking these questions like what's more likely
Is it real life more likely that Randy Cramer is being
Or that he's been put up to it by the Illuminati in order to do this right right
What you doing is also excluded another possibility of s***
That's the part of the
Incredulous credulous Spectrum
Exercising critical thinking is flawed
Because
Compared to
This is a real suggestion of a false flag or it's a psyop or whatever
I'm not sure which one of those is more likely
Either is more likely than the other
And critically be like well here's this is all this is bulshit repair
So you're you're failing on a critical thinking level if you don't this all doesn't make sense it's all stupid
You have nothing to prove any of this
What
We used
Occam's razor
Subway
And that would be
He is right
You're absolutely right if you have that if you have those has two choices
Ed you have to
To choose one
Is more or less likely
None of this
Then
That it makes sense
Operate in a critical
Way of the options that are available your just exclude another option
Brandy I want to talk about him a little bit
I got mansion in the first episode
I'll Project Camelot super soldier
Young man
Whereupon he
This
Contradicted either being absolutely on Earth during those years
Don't be so naive
He was fighting
It all makes sense
I'm saying this for the listeners Who episode
The timeline
Absolutely
What was the push to release the holographic regenerating Medved
You swore that the secret space program has
There's a secret technology that doesn't want you
To know about it
Very suspicious
The idea that the man doesn't want people to know about this stuff seems contradicted by the fact that Randy's been going on radio show
Technology
InstaCare
He also had a GoFundMe running to develop
Help Humanity
Thousand dollars to save Humanity from all disease
And of course age
Regret
Really basically has found the Fountain of Youth
More people would realize
Eternal life
GoFundMe has been up since February 27th
How's it going $7,300 raise crowdfunding
Efforts are usually look up for people like this I think one of the reasons
Putting people's hope and Desperation
As you can clearly see you read some of the comments
People leave on the page
One donor said quote
My father needs a Medved soon he will go to heaven in a few months but the RV is very soon we
Or there's another donor
Please hurry
My hubby has Ms and is bedridden
If there's any kind of list to get on for treatment at cetera please let me know
People need solution
And when things are desperate they'll also be more inclined to turn to more irrational salute
A person may be holding against stealing
But they'll resort to it
Similarly if your dad or husband is a
A condition that conventional medicine doesn't have them
Solutions for it's hard to just give up on them
It's not uncommon for medical grifters to step in
I tried to offer false hope
For a price
These methods do not exist
High-functioning
I wish some billionaire would come along be like you need 70 grand here you go now it's me the f****** bed.
Every project
B******* you have
Is fully funded now
Yeah put up or shut up
Okay I'm filing charges against you for fraud
Defrauded all of these people giving you any money
If this is
Like it should be
Insanely Criminal
Like this is so gross
100% is a powerful
With all that money
We don't want your
Do that
People refusing
To debate people they know will destroy them activate
Not you
Crowder
But the other thing is that like
The other option is so like built into their world you already that is like
And then it's from the reptile
Explanations for why you can't do it
This is just
Custom
I don't care if you collecting this money this 7grand or whatever
From this disco font
I don't give a fuk
He is making money off this doing these these speech circuit
Even if he's not making any money
He still hurting people
It gets just
F****** disgusting
And a one of those guys who and we listen to it seems like
Episode
It's the
These people are hurting
People
Understand I am fine in American history
Is a certain kind of
Romantic concept of the grifter
Yeah I know
Dumb rich people are no smarter than anybody else
And they're going to get
Can for 100 grand
F*** you you learned your lesson
But these guys
Is our bottom
Reading lights
I am going to
To take this this dude last
Cuz I want to
10 bucks
And that's it
F*** off
And one of the most effective way to do that is to
Like an invading people's space who are struggling
Especially if it's metal
The worst part
Was even with a
The goddamn
F****** placebo effect
At least at least that much
This medbed bulshit with just
F****** sending him fifty bucks for his
There's no sudden
Placebo effect for a medvedeff never
You might be a little more optimistic or hopeful but that's not going to do anything
Calculate gross
It's legit
Disembark stuff
Done with the business
Next clip
We get into how
There's a bunch of aliens
But
Humanity
And the kind of want better property
They don't like being in the desert
We're putting aliens on reservation
Yeah that's heavily implied but they want
Better
Aliens
W
To be on the beach
Marcus Point Theater
With regard to Olive
She says
The military is stealing
Real multiple
Invasion
Getting harder and harder
To hide from public
They're interested in
Pushing
Time
She also stressed
Various race
Environment
And what access to our
And more watery area
They want to live on the beach
Totally
I can
100% relate with I would rather be on
Coast
Or maybe situation we're in Commerce and I-10
Under our capitalist system on airport is a very lucrative business
Maybe they just wanted better
View map
Desert
Blues Brother
Great
Sand looking out at the water
Bright
That's great they want kind of a part of another that happens first of all there's the
Disclosure
Then there is the rationalizing away any kind of like
Geopolitical issues
I meant also visit
New strain that I'm seeing
Of Mark
Talking about like aliens being
Expansion
Like they are not satisfied being in the desert they want to be on the coast
Bissell pop-up a number of other time
I'm not a hundred percent sure
Exactly what this is code for code for something
As we go along
Yeah we talked about predictive programing a little bit already the idea that like movies and TV rights TV shows
Repair people
When Carrie gets into that
Suggested
Ready Player One
Ender's Game
Halo series
There is
Alien
Sektor
What About Last Starfighter lady
And this scene
To be preparing them
Alien invasion
So
I suggested that
Grey alien
Achoo
There's too many races
Anime
You know there are good
A grey alien
Other
Version
Grey aliens
Different sizes
Alien setup
Facebook Sandra
The one
Alien of choice
Which are millet
Come out
So I did
Run at 5
Possible
Very possible
They're going to bring in the bugs
Sears
Mars Attacks
Stop
Nicholson
Get it
What
Once you hear her be actually racist in the real world
Then the moment she goes
Obviously divided along racial
And you're like
Alright well
A really really bad
It does have that
That's a limitation of us listening to so much of this and actually hearing
Her we can't be
Pretending
Not aware of those positions
That like
Is all of this racial
Specification of aliens
Just sort of a way to
Ask some other feeling you have
It's pretty difficult as all of their races which are
Completely different from each other even though they're all under the
The same race
Factions in real life
Alright lady we get it you don't like black
Just leave us alone
That's difficult for us to parse out it's really a challenge
Racial element
Your statement
What is the difficult for us
Feel like have to listen to this and like really trying to figure out like
You really talk about aliens what you doing
But
We would be so f******
Selfish
If we didn't recognize that this is difficult for
Carrie 2
She has to go
To a prison
Take notes with a little pencil
It's
So hard
Everything I'm
I'm talking about
Is available on my way
On a
Talk here
And
Basically
Did those notes
Taking right after I
I leave
Recite as well as
Time when I
Note to myself
Pencil
So I'm getting a lot of
Good stuff
Out there
Through this
Process but it is very low
You might imagine
And
It is
Aggravated
Weird
Appearances
We're having now
Testing my
There's no reason
Frames
These little
Just bear with me
It's very important
Maybe because I don't know if your CPU stands going to bring up hey you said it wrong
I don't know if I don't know what kind of search function you're going to use today
I mean
Is there a twelve-year-old across the
The street from her that could do this for a real quick like a flower
Hey that's possible
Get an unpaid item
So hard
So another Trend that's happening throughout
Going to get a Raptor
There's another Trend that's going through this episode and that is kind of optimistic that Mark might get out
Go to prison
Reasons for it are a little thin
Okay
There are men who have been
I'm trained to fight the
Men who have
Have been
Throughout their career doing
Young World
Where this is
They're being sent
Saturn
Mars
The Moon
Outside our solar
The bottom line is
People like Marco
Mark Richard
Would be
Extremely valuable
In the battle
Especially
So this
Where
There are some rays
I believe
These ideas
Real
Just a matter of how to be
The humans alkire
Yeah I got a break
People like him who been trained to fight
If aliens do come
I'm right with you were storming the Bastille together we're going to need Mark in the coming battle
Honestly if there is an alien invasion Marcus the least of my words
I've not sure I care if he gets out of prison helpful
What's a low priority
I also think I can honestly I think he is
Also in terms of
My positions about like prison reform
And stuff like that like
I do think Mark is probably still a danger to I don't know if it's not the
You could still accommodate with
Like good supervision outside of prison
But he's been in for 20-something years
Play I don't I don't know if it's really doing him any good
Movie based on how crazy he is and how he clearly is still trying to indoctrinate people
Maybe I'll become more medical facility is more appropriate for him
I don't have any empathy or like pity for him
But also based on my voice.
Assertive
Rapid prison state that we have
Would be inconsistent for me to be like yeah keep this old man in
With you if if the idea behind prison is Rehabilitation and not record
Then I agree there's no reason for people to be if there's no reason for people to be
In prison
At all we should have different whatever time I think it's appropriate
Condition
Same time
There are people like Marc rich
Do I do feel like
Being allowed to speak
Two other human beings they are at.
To the rest
Like there's no way
They talked
Cuz if he starts talking to people
She's going to get weird
Cordoned off for some
Nothing like I don't want
Bright do harm imagining like a conman Kanye
Look at them all a good site will put gdubs on there I don't think that
Illusion I don't know I think there's a way to
Construct some sort of a post-release program that would be able to like
Some sort of a
The caseworker who
Could keep an eye on like
Are you f****** manipulating rest
Yeah I think it's possible
Steel beam
You know
You're imagining his superhuman powers
Bring somebody for them has a certain superpowers that I'm unfamiliar
Call Bean
Charismatic
Sociopath
And there are plenty of people around
I don't know I'm not enough specifically advocating for anything in particular
Just saying
I do I don't know what the right solution here is I think maybe
I also like I guess to the
Baldwin's
If they were so if they were dead set on him staying in prison that I think I would have a dick
Difficult
Yeah I don't know I don't know I have a lot of
Ambivalent
If I if there was an answer for
I'm sure people smarter than us
Would probably have
And so far I don't know if there's
That's what they say to you
We will say all right.
Gucci swimsuit review but like the aliens
Look Paradise
I hate to admit it but I'll be a great show
Cuz you can have a ton of conman trying to con each other
There's no marks on the island
Children's March the World Series of Poker
Thousand dollars to start with
At the end of a week win
We're going back to Our Roots early early days on this podcast we had some great
TV ideas
This one might be out there
And I love this sort of thing on TV shows
That we're not the only one
Mark has been
Teaching a screenwriting class to inmates for the past two years and they have a neck
Excellent series idea he's been trying to send me some
So we're going to try
A few different
Tactics
To get them out to me
Obviously with my background in Hollywood
I am very interested
I'm going back in the Hollywood
And getting
Movies and television series made
Of course from the stories that I've Been Told
This feels more sincere than a lot of the alien s***
I get it
Carrie
Cuz if you were real
Said I'm teaching
Screenwriting class you could like
Okay that's a big red flag
I'm going to say maybe your
A screenwriting class
Yeah but you know how it goes like all of these things are so easy with it
The framework wants
Fictional sci-fi
It's actually a biopic
Play
Indications that disqualify
TV show going
You got it whatever
So much like the California fires were just alien
Other natural disasters
Thighs if that's a more
Hurricane Dorian
It stayed for several
Dave's over the island in the Bahamas and hurricanes just don't do that
It was targeted
An engineered and Mark has not revealed
The real purpose behind
What they did with hurricane
Dorian
But it was created and had a lot
Do with I believe
Removing people
Because of the intense amount of
Tivity
Going on at the undersea bases in that
Vicinity
And
So they wanted
To get people off that Island
And I believe that
To return so that's a very important
Point and again we've got
Populations moving
There a lot of people won't be able to return because they
This is so disrespectful to like
People who are going through disasters
People out of an undersea base
Look at this is just rewriting tragedy in order to fit into your mold
It is gross
I think that
That's actually maybe
Standable parts
Text because it's you're scared you're scared of the fact that this happened
It's too big
Yes
Comprehend
Just just living in Chicago I was thinking about this on the walk over here after
Just like
The amount of damage
That has been
Done
And is still going on
All of these
F****** failures of people who are in the governor
And I was walking here and I was
My life has not
Changed
All
Other than to be constantly.
Bright
Material
Play my my
Really hasn't
Like physically affected
You know I'm not
Now all day everyday because
Cuz of climate change
I'm not
My f****** land is in
You're not going nowhere up there now
You do want to
Create another X
Nation Ford
Because the reality of it is
If my life
Sucking the life out of everybody
To allow those explanations to mask what's really happening
On a personal level
Because sometimes it's
Too hard
The difference
Between
Taking a personal Escapist route
What they're doing
Is very big
Because this is advocating that as an explanation to an audience
The function of that
Is 2 take away the audience's impetus
To do any
It's
2 take away like
Okay
This hurricane was really really tragic should be on the people who are going through it
They're trying to direct resources as best as you can
To the people who
Can survive
And honoring the factory
Yes
Everyone's talking about the hurricane but in reality
Tragedy
Force your narrative
And that sucks
That sucks that's far beyond
Escapist sell therapeutic denial
If I if I had a
Friend
Who was
Expressing something like this
I might not be as a
You know
I might not think they're really smart
I wouldn't be as offended as someone who's disseminating it to an audience
I think I see what you
I thought you meant
If I was friends with Carrie I might have to use a grate
If Ellen was asked was friends with George W
Just emphasize totally
That ideas like
I totally get
Why you
Feel the need
Create the separate
Because it is a
Nightmare
Sure
Play nightmare
And if you're not
Personally affect
Impetus
Create an alternate reality that
Sense of it without having to
Talk to people who are a
I totally get that but all that doesn't protect your unaffectionate problem the expense of the people who are actually work
Directly affected
It's understandable on on a human
Ultimately
Destructive and damaging to the people affected by the cover-up
Look out your mouth carry
Sure
As We Know
The un's in the mick
Always talked about this a little bit
They're the cover-up alien stuff
Who cares
I have to say that in the past Mark has talked about
The UN and the
Meetings and
Peru
And also in
In Exeter
Example of
Where we have alien meeting with human
In a very steep
Location
This does happen
Candy Rush
Talked about this
So these meetings
Arnot
That unusual
Obviously
The UN is involved
Peru
Paul Joseph Watson oh my God
What
I don't know I don't care if the only thing I heard from that Cliff was Danbury
Meetings
I've never heard that name before
Most people have it
Because he got discredited real fast
Versus a guy who was involved
Conspiracy World drama
He claims to be a scientist working for
Pick 12
In the secret government that's a big group in a program
He's working on Project
Involving aliens in ship
He told some amazing stories
About life lived in top-secret work and you made a big splash around 2,000
The Paranormal
Conspiracy world is really bad
Generally
Most of the participants are hopelessly gullible or they're trying to run Conn's themselves so whenever someone comes forward with information that states
Send to their worldview
There was never tape
Take a step back
Question the new information
They typically just
Excitedly Corporation new information into their narrative
Accusing anyone who speaks being on the ferry of conspiracy against truth
This is not the case of Dan burisch when he came forward
Some of the space people found his story a little bit weird and decided to look into it a little bit particularly Coast
Coast frequent guest Linda Moulton Howe
I'm not saying any of this stuff
But she puts out generally
Aboveboard
But she did look into official records
Involving Danbury
Apply for Chapter 7 bankruptcy
Right around the time he started to come forward with his alien allegation
From there she Tracked Down record surrounding his education has debts that the bankruptcy Were Meant to clear
Employment history
This is completely worthless and honestly the story isn't as interesting as it may seem like it could be
But the bottom line is that all this available information
Alien research projects
He's just making it all up
Ultimately doesn't matter though it's already on even on this episode the logic of people
Program s*** it's airtight
You produce evidence that this guy was working
Completely different job when he claimed to be working with alien you can just cover job
That's of course it says he works there
There's no record of him getting a Ph.D that he claims to have
And you can just
Space program is keeping his diploma Under Wraps
If you know you're off Mission at a time when you may have committed murder
10 acceptable explanation for this
It's the same thing
Dan burisch is someone who
The only the farthest out there
Conspiracy folks
Still consider
Anyway worth ref
Project Blue beam is something that has been discredited by more critical thinking
Right around the corner
Those elements of this space weirdo community
They probably would have much
Higher standards
They're still not working off concrete proof they still have a more critical stance on it
There are different
Certain sections of the UFO ology
Folks
And the boar
Do you have Project Blue beam
Listed as
Credible things
On this episode
And that's two strikes
In terms of
Things that even
A lot of the UFO Community thinking
That's not good
Fun
His meeting with aliens
Exeter
That's not good I would say
I will give you a third strike though
Thinking that a murderer was our planet
I think that one strike number three
I think the employee for short
And all the rest of her career
Mark tells Carrie something
That is absolutely not true
Try to find evidence
That what this
And she cannot
So then she asked for the audience's help
Mark talked about a television
In which it has a red-headed version of me
Who investigate stories
He said it's worth watching
They're disclosing.
Can I haven't found that
But if you find it or know what show it is please let me
And I will
Search for it obvious
What's up there's a show on the CW carry Butt-head
I know I care
I don't know what it is
TW say something so specific
Possibilities for the programming
Who's alive who's dead
The first possibility is the Legacy
Okay goodnight show
Kind of red-haired werewolves and vampires
It also seems unlikely
But it's on the red hair
Maybe
The other possibility is that Marcus commercial for the upcoming W version of Nancy Drew
Which definitely features are redheads
If they feed you enough for everything it's all the Mysteries
I don't think of it all
Through the goddamn cellular carrier
It's just
The CW has sex
A specific in-house style that you're like
Course Mark Richards love
The CW
I honestly think that has to do with them not getting more cable
You get enough cable
The CW
If you don't
If you're in prison you may not get a lot of choice it might be a democratic thing
Love you and you have to watch
Stereotypical
It is not a democratic thing in prison
But
You may be correct
Anyway I don't I don't I don't pretend to understand how marks entertainment
Choices are drawn to him by side
The flash when the flash put
True does he solve alien Mysteries
Okay
Figure it out neither can we
So we get back to this trend of like geopolitical issues just showing alien
Babies really
It's always past the point of acceptability
But this one's pretty bad
Mark does talk about
The reptoids
Africa
And he did talk about how
The race from aldebaran
Would be expand
A lot like
What happened
Durian
Bushwacker
In America
During
Settlers and the settlement started
And get larger and larger
Sounds like
Africa
There are
Let's see settlements that are
Spread out
Further also on the way to the main base and
They start out with
Acquiring
One or two
Item
Skechers chocolate
Certain minerals
But apparently there
Expanding
And this has become
Problem
This is what I mean
And to look for those indica
Tell you you're getting
Clubs in some truth
Which would be
That there is
Skirmishes
Way
And methods
So when you see in the developing world
Modern-day consequences of colonial system
Sorry about those things it's just aliens looking for chocolate
This kind of thing going
Sudden shortage of chalk
Naturalist
Probably cuz she thinks it would sound
To say here's how you know
Not enough
This is just
Whitewashing
It is
Trying to take
Real world situations that you should be
Concerned about
Create
Is agitate for alien disclosure
Hey Simon parkes and Randy Kramer and Jerry
Stupid it's misdirection probably
Well-meaning
Here's the thing that nobody wants
European colonialism
Talk to the world and we're still dealing with the
500 years later
And it's probably going to kill us all
So
How about me
Alien
Sprouts
New episode it turns into like
A situation where mark is really mad at the hater
Is Yorkies super pissed off at the people who were talking s*** about him
And I really hoped it was awesome
Does he have online access
I think you must to some extent
Limited
Heavily
I don't know I don't know how much that is
Like of his own accord how much like his wife is telling him that he's telling him
It's possible that he's getting everything
Secondhand
I really hope he was talking about us
But I don't think he is
It's really sad
I wish
Now regarding the attacks
Mark Richards
In the alternative media
The attacks are aimed at marks effort
Commuted sentence
And
Could affect the ruling
The weather
Parole
Let's see he
She is Ben
Quite
Concerned
About the attacks
On him
And his wife Joanne
Say as well
And the rest of his
His family
That is
Something
His lawyers to deal with
Regarding
Is that tax ID
Communicate
But I think that they
Provide a
Platform
That serves the dark and the
People who want to
To remain in the dark
And
Cannot harm
There is death
Currently
Mafia
Gay Mafia
Pedophile
She's right there
With the group
Also have some
Background
Sharia
What area
And I am also
British Intel
That's what I realize this isn't about us are you saying that the gay Mafia is being
Run by British
This is about Kevin but obviously
She's already made these sorts of allegation
Pedophile Mafia
I wish it was I know it was about us
Somewhat viral viral
Contacted her
Has viewer that's true
Which is strange because his his
F****** channeling episodes where he says
He doesn't need to do voices
Absolutely riveting
I just
I'm just worried
Or being overlooked
We've got a lot of
Very public beach that nobody wants
It's like they're about it
I mean hate luck weave
Very couple of beers. I like we usually don't drink during
Is Mark Richards
We're hypercritical of his bones also not call
Calling for his parole not go through or whatever
Penalty
Good luck trying to link me with
That was mean
And like obviously
It's not us
It becomes even more clear that it's not us and
Mark has contacts in
Intelligence
That they are involved
This
Still
Possible
In my view
Gree
Mark and his team of lawyers
Found a substantial
Dirt on this hacker
And this will be released in a video in the future
Hardee's
I will not be involved
Packers
If their attacks
Continue that
This information
In about them will come out
Obviously
Pitstop
Bring it yeah so when I heard that Mark was mad at people in alternative media
I really hope that he was talking
I have to assume that we would come up in a Google search for Mark Richard
But it's hard to know how far down the results
Most of the top results are about a surfer
Who's also
Yeah I feel good
I had a few different thoughts about a possible Feud developing with Mark Richards
The first was that it sounded like a lot of fun
I could just imagine us getting casted acolytes of like the spider leadership or some s*** and honestly I
We belong somewhere the mythology
Pictures from my past we could dig up and repurpose
And honestly I do feel snubbed it we're not in the mythology
But is this point
Personally I think I should be a few
But Beggars can't be choosers
I feel like I feel like I want to be
Mercantile dog
My other thought though and I think this is a bigger thought that I had is that it's probably good that he's not choosing us as enemies
This guy's a murderer gets out of prison and the last
Creative angry guy stuck in prison of Stephen about me
I don't like your use of the word
I will give you creative
I will not give you really
Until you do better than I had a Starship Enterprise like vessel
You don't get a really creative
I think he's able to incorporate all of these
These disparate pieces of Syfy
Into something
Agree with your assessment that it's not good but it's created
A
Creator creator
Very
Exactly OK Market
Any gave Terry a four-page letter
And it was addressed to who Mark is calling quotes
Himself is Jesus
Which is a murderer to do
The first thing I can tell from this letter is it was definitely written
The voice is completely different and honestly it's pretty well written
From a rhetorical question
There's good good balance between short and long sentences good use of metaphor
There's some inaccuracies like him saying
Judas sold Jesus out for 30 pieces of gold
Instead of silver but I'm not
In the letter mark
Calls out his enemies by name
Attention
Because I'm all caught up on the drama I know that this has to be about Kevin Moore the guy who's creating a documentary about Mark
Carrie
Doesn't explain the personal
Why would Mark call Kevin
Not like this British documentarian is a former friend of his
That's explained by the fact that for his documentary Kevin his interview people like Marx
Text wife
His former best friend
And the guy who are convinced to commit the actual murder Crossing Hoover
I'm guessing that this letter is specifically about Hoover talking to Kevin
Scientist most damning piece of information that could be in a documentary
It's tough to get around the guy who did the murder say
Mark was there he told me to stab the guy with
Screwdriver welding watch
You can understand the impulse to try and intimidate that guy or preemptively
Discredit him is working for evil aliens or some s***
The letter itself Beyond it's surprisingly decent writing is a Showcase of Mark's manipulative ability
He portrays himself as a heroic bringer of Truth in the victim of out-of-control Internet negativity
Holding close to his main thesis
Quote
If all I'm doing is trying to bring out the truth why would anyone attack me unless they're working for
Getting the truth the Press
Sure
That's a totally reasonable argument
There's one line that I thought was particularly funny
It also gets to me how such negative lunatics get more and more carried away with our personal attack
Rather than staying on track with either science or any sort of rational argument about the facts
You want to stay on track with the facts inside
Do that proved to be the Rapture aliens want to kill making chocolate
The person making The Sensational claim is the one with the burden of proof
It's not like I could say in addition to the murder he was involved
Mark Richards also set off a nuke in Manitoba
Rightly would I reply to this is absurd night no evidence of my claim
That Manitoba has ever been do
If you really f***** up and stupid for me to pretend that I was being attacked by him responding
You have no evidence for the claims are made
Yeah
That's one level of this
It is another great line
It comes in this letter after a passage about how Judas hung himself after he realized that what he did was wrong
Now that might read that is him calling for his enemies to kill themselves but I'm going to leave that alone for the
Mark says of these people quote
I've nothing but titty for such people
As the weight of such a weakness and guilt has to be crushed
No wonder all of them are such failures that everything creative they've ever tried to do a life
God dammit that's rude
Coming from Mako Shark ramp
Here's the first thing that
Based on your assessment of the writing
In this letter
I assumed it was written
What mid
Early to
Early 2000s
Was written
Last week
So and when was the
The shity book written
Long ago
That's a testament if we have any aspiring
Even if
You're terrible right now
Lock yourself up in prison for murdering a guy and then really focus on your writing
20 years later you will get
A good for paste
Take your argument make it a little better
I would say that if you want to get better at something
The prison education system can make you better at something
Why not Avail yourself of the available resources
Lifelong learning is available
As it is
Is a
NeverEnding Story
Murderous rage
That the people who
Perpetrate these awful crime
Will preemptively call other people the purple
Portrayed
Of course
Universal to everyone everywhere
Exactly what number of times people Liars in that letter is
Rosier pastures
Find out
So there's these fires in California they're covering up an alien invasion through portals
Logan find out
Batman this guy knows how to deliver the goods
They are
Populated areas
Making speaker
The distance
Fornia
I did ask him again
And what
Kind of
Invading
Through that port
In Paradise
And he said they were
Spider
Octopus
They are Hunters
Planet
That is about to
Versailles
And their Moon
Jordan you're laughing
But what else would a spider breed with been an octopus
Makes sense
Makes sense for the spider would breed with an octopus
Eight legs
Makes perfect sandwich house scary giant spider that can spit ink would be
Crazy
Biggest squid
Has no bones
Octopus alien
Here's my favorite doesn't matter any animal is now an alien eyes
Mark understands
Holy
The conundrum of the Marvel movie
Which is you gotta always racist
Every movie has to raise mistake
Octopus
Screenwriting class
You breathed the four-legged alien you end up with six legs
Duck
So stock
Between
Finger Lakes
That is the dumbest s*** I've ever heard
And also
That is f******
Brilliant
Such sense
Great
So the California are alien related
Regarding the fires in
Amazon
That is erupting
Version
He said
Those are
Creating the
Sapphires
They have to be very very careful
Not
To have
Dumb rich
Entrepreneur
Or liberal go down
Catch sight of the reptilian
Shep's creating
The fires
So this is a problem
There's a lot of collateral damage
In the area
The Amazon
Why is it a problem for liberals
Weirdos always have
How to be fascist
You know I don't know if they all are but a lot of these voices like voices
Are just covering up
Symptoms of fashion
We can't have a liberal getting in there and causing issues
Spore bolsonaro
Amazon conservation effort
Yeah
I mean
See this over and over again
Africa
And now fires in the Amazon that are very clearly cause
By bolsonaro
Shipping of policy
Like is just like rewriting real f*****-up
Geopolitical issues
Into an alien framework
It's tough to not be real
Offended by that
Where is unlike these stupid pattern is consistent
Like the pattern of
Go to sleep
Is almost 2
You know some sort of
Limited Hangout
It's not a grand conspiracy
Conspiracy is that
This person doesn't want to deal with reality
And there
Weaving at elaborate yarn using a murder in prison in order to reinforce it
I guess the only thing that I could
Holiday
Prosody laundry
Yeah
Or or potential atrocity laundry
Car wash
As a cash-only business
You're hiring up murderer
As a lies
Combined
Effort
Their interest of the audience
She's misleading down these
Could
Have some effect
Like whatever it would be maybe
The people helping organizing
And work towards like
Like really solving some of the issues that are behind the things therefore
The derby
Distracted down this road
But
So let's listen to something silly
This is something that our military was doing
In places like Nevada where they're said
Nuclear tests going on there's actually weren't really
Kenny we're fighting
Then
And the Raptors think that we
Crazy to be doing this
Humans did not realize
That
That there are aliens that like having Woodmark call Zay
A frat party
Where they are deciding it would be fun to go off
And invade Earth and Kill Some Humans
I'm so this is the kind of thing we're dealing with
I know it's serious
Just the Celtic people
Gyros
But Coker.
Whatever you say next we are going to do to f***** up to drive the spaceship
Hit the Taco Bell on the way to Earth
Aliens are joyriding around us
If there were aliens
Some of them would Joyride
No it's not a personification of aliens
Brains that we are just making all these aliens like a bunch of different forms
Yeah it is it is what what's the
I can't remember the theory on
One Last Hurrah I know
What you wanted
Are frat party alien voices are very Chicago
Just get dropped
Chicago
Party Town on Cermak
I hear stuff like that in my kind of love it like that
What I wished I wish there wasn't the elements
This is to related
Actual
Important actual real-world events
Yeah yeah yeah
I probably look past
If there were other things
Just be an isolated
Absent all of the other rewriting of
Important
Within the context
The totality of his
Yeah
So we have like
Now
These aliens are frat party
Who are like
Nai
Also are very humid
It turns out
I don't know what this story
Carrie is about to
Spell actually
Like I assume somewhere
I guess that that's probably with a space space
I didn't look into this at all because I realized like
There's no way
There's
Who cares
The story is
Themselves
There was a story about 1 drone
It would not
A bay a direct order
Decided
It was
The problem
And
Even when assured by the humans
It was not a problem
It would not believe that
It
Was ordered to read
Illustration
From outer space
Refused
And
Ended up
Getting
And the Drone
Selfie
Destroying itself
Refuse to
Obey the order
This isn't the military
This is
Kind of things
Dealing
Level
Involving
AI
This is a soft pitch for the next Pixar movie
These self undershirt drone
The Drone that doubted place in the world
This is the first time a Isley
You know what we really understand the Nuremberg
I won't do it I will not get your spaceship bulshit
As soon as she said it was refilling a spaceship that's when I realized I can't
I could probably find an article about a drunk rat
What value would that be for us to discuss
But it's so great cuz I also feel like there's a Wally aspects of this maybe I kind of feel like
I really wish I honestly I was like
I hope that I have the f***
Coronavirus drug
So that's the only way
To win
Is not to play
Again
That's fun
This personified Wiley X drone
Won't refuel spaceships
Is fun
Frat party aliens
Hilarious
It's always mixed up with
S*** like that is not fun
Is very clearly trying to rewrite real world
Scenarios
In
Kind of races
I ran by him the idea that
The program has
She's talking about the alien human hybrid program
Otherwise known as Central and South America
That it
Is one of the reasons
For the
Increase
Control
Because
The Trump Administration
Concerned about
X-Men
Factor
Having to
To do with special
Powers that
Children
Who are now growing up
May have
And
She agreed
He also said the TSA scanners have nothing to
Metal
But they are all about detecting weather urai
Augmented human
Human or alien
And so on
Increase border cruelty and Albright
Really it's just because Trump is worried about Wolverine coming across border
United States
Kind of a whiny little assholes
What can I do
Gene board
Jim really f*** that up
America because the alien
Program is so strong in Central and South America
Holyshit
That's the real world
Don't worry about it
You see parents being separated from their their their children
Logan being separated from coming out of Cruelty
Memes
Consider the alternative
Nightcrawler is going to be
Jordan career stats
Magneto's
Nuts
This is B that's the primary function of a lot of gay stuff
Really
That concerned with that really think they are but still
How
Her listeners
Interact with the real world they won't care about people like ACLU or immigrant-rights groups
Talkin about
The issues that are going on because it's just f******
Trying to keep Psych
Bob Sapp
This is not good
Feel like
Exploiting is
The inherent distance
Allegory
I've liked the fact that because
I am I am
About
Mexican immigrants
If I say
And you are a person
Empathy
You're going to say
Ibanez
Using an allegory for
Coming across the border
Are evil
And then
Exact
I don't want to be mad
Human beings are all in this together
Programs in Central and South America
Anybody
Trying to have no f****** idea
They could have super Pacs
You don't want to let her I would rather
100 migrants are detained at the border than one X-Men get through
Over
Hi
In order to reinforce this as a recommendation of a source you should look into
Regarding the X-Men special powers
Alien human hybrid program
I want to recommend
Find a movie with
The X-Men
Movie called
Logan
What are we go
Call Earl
Scholarly scholarly reference
Jean-Luc Picard
Scholarly reference
Made by Carrie to a source that any
Legitimate researcher would be like well she's got us
Yep that's if you watch that movie
Look she's right
If she had chosen like I don't know X-Men
The last
That's what no one likes right
Which is like
Superhero
So you got to know she's awesome
After taste
I would love this if it wasn't so over
Clearly damaging to Oliver
It would be
Sophon
Navigate to Trump
Turns out that Marcus kind of
Oh Knock You Out
Mark is also much like Jay-Z night that we talked about earlier
Might be a little qanon
Yeah
Regarding Trump
He says Trump is always trying to
Tweet out
Messages
With hidden meaning
He's not owned by any group
He's highly unpredictable
Mark admires Howie's maintains himself under the attack
And doesn't let
I'm around
Yeah he said he's likely
Reincarnation
Patent
Naturally
Yes please.
Hallmarks of the online Cube class now
Anytime there's like Miss spellings and stuff people try to figure out like what is this really say
I'm not pronouncing it on Prince
I will only do it in that voice
I am like my Richards later
So that's good
I don't understand
Positive thing
El Segundo the timeline
Works out
Let me look this up I don't know babe
World War
When Patton was famously already
General
Call 45
Get born
I actually
1946 holyshit marks onto something
He's done his research on the podcast
Hey
You know what
What issue a retraction
If we hadn't just Googled it on
There's a war going on
The Orion
Area
Right now you didn't know about that
Yeah most people right there is a big war going on
India Ryan
Yeah
You sure I don't know how else to say than area
Before you question
Easily be Google
Artist
Stars
Constellation Orion
Physically close to me
I got a sexually close to each other because they are closed
Relative three brothers and others
As well as
Yeah
Scale
Something closer to it like two stars
Equidistant from each other that are closer to the Earth will appear closer to each other than Stars
That are further from us that are the same distance from each other
That is
I don't know how a rhino say
Because they're bright
Retraction
Okay there's a war going on there
Are trying to distract us from that war
Carrie reveals a specific piece of information here
But I just think is fun
Unstoppable
He said there's a major war going on
For the past year
In the Orion sector
The Drake are heavily involved in this war
And
Why
Attempting
There was an attempt
Distract humans
Raptors
From
This War 5
Creating issue
On Earth
They're already
Around 50,000 human serving in there
Front
Why and fighting the war
We got to distract from This Is War is going on in the
To give you some scale of like what are only six
4000 troops deployed in the entire
I-Ready of Europe
I understand
But this would literally be like 90% of our troops in Europe being in space fighting Reptoid
Hard to imagine that no one would notice
You know nobody has audited the Pentagon budget
60 years old
Without 50,000
Dish Anywhere
It's also crazy high number of combat
Sphere like the
Preliminary
By April 2000
For there were only 20,000 300 troops in Afghanistan
Orion battle is
Double that deployment
The Troop level in Afghanistan didn't reach 50,000 till the middle of
What she's talking about would legitimately be
Possible to pull off without noticing
Each of these 50,000 people supposedly fighting in a Ryan
Bill have loved ones in French
It's kind of hard to imagine that none of them would slip up and accidentally reveal that they were off.
This would absolutely be impossible to
Compartmentalize
If you're that large
Like it's just crazy
Presumably they would have had to been trained up on how to use the obviously different weapons and tactics
Using space combat well it's nonsensical there's no way that 50,000 people
Let's
Arrow Ford nodes in their own life right now you got 100,000 to keep quiet
And that's for people that's phone number foremost
Of those individuals
Geometric the
Totally
This is this is impossible to imagine the first five years of
Silent
It's ridiculous
I think the frustration that I have
Most
Is in moments like that
We talked about the minutiae of just
What is 50,000 people were deployed
Anyway it is frustratingly
Detail Ori
If we take one step back
We have to always admit that these people are yada yada eating fast
No there's no they all assume the last one
You make a great point
A satellite Travel Wichita
Goddamn
Kind of brought up there like
What kind of training
Is
Relevant
2 space battle
Infantry ground troops in a space battle
It's not the same
Define more f****** Mars has different gravity there you can't breathe
Here's the trick out your using
Purely amphibious
Trained
All right so the Navy Seals
They go from water
Easy step from space
That's tight
At science
Space
I don't think the same things that filter air out of water worksheet
Devices
I don't think it would but I'm not sure
I don't I don't I think there's some holes
Okay that's fair
Earth Fare
So
You know right now we got some issues with the brexit
Well turns out Marcus
He said there is a group holding it back it is imperative that the British
Are able to
Come over to the
The American side
We can't fully
Trust them
This time
Which is strange
Because they are are
Allied
Still have brexit has to do with them coming to America
Weird
This to me is like a real strong indication that whatever is behind a lot of the
The worldview that Terry and Mark have
Has to do with
Anti un anti-eu height
Sorry Valenti
Sit up with
Alex and his wife
Is here or her like a Reptoid
Call just sort of targeting these International Organization
Cooperation
Yeah
It's not really that different
He is to have different
Costume
It is frustrating
It is really frustrating
Because that is
Fitting Within
What would it What was
Would you call it nationalist
Populist
Reality of brexit
What the what
Johnson is really doing is
Strip mining
England
Selling it to America
America billionaires
Exact
Bada bing bada boom
Yep and that's what sucks about this
I fucken like
The Escape
These Wacky Wednesday Project Camelot episode
The reality is the first
The more it's so clear that it's
Whitewashing and apologizing for
Radically again
You know
You cannot answer the
This question right
I might be able to
Do you feel like this is
Social media
Cambridge analytica era of
Migration of space weirdos to that same level
Different
2011 if we were doing the show in 2011
Would we have an unencumbered
Space weirdo experience
For good
You know I'm saying I don't know for good but yeah I think I think it probably is
I'm not ready to say like
Totally
The distortion
Sort of radicalization on all front
Since 2015 or so
It probably does
Affect
Even even
I think that if you look back on
Earlier
Interviews that she did
Are the races
A lot of that stuff but I don't
Know how overtly like
Right in line with the
Angling neo-fascist
World
View narratives with Aldi
How much is this is coming from Mark and how much is it is her interpretation
What Mark said impossible for us
She's just remembering a conversation with a guy who's in prison
Feel like I don't I don't know how much of this is
Her influence
He's saying
But yeah I think for sure I don't know
Well I supposed to
Question for me is
Parallel
Very similar to when we talked about the
2013 yeah looking at routers
And you're like
Discuss
Question is
How much of their
Currants
F****** esneault
Fascist state
Was
Simmering below the surface
It's something
Was it always there or is it
Is the question I can't answer
Yeah who knows
It's context clues from Peebles record right
Adjectives for that
The level to which were seeing on this episode
In a lot of carries
Maurice
Work
I think it is different
I think it has been affected by
Those world
Yeah the change
I think that's the
That's the issue I have with
It's a weight
The word
Do you know what I mean
Someone talked about
Increase in white Nash
Terror
Plies though that
All of this
Just that
What year was a bowl
So does that mean every time you use the word emboldened
Are we really saying that
This is always been there
In the fascist right
I think
Two populations
Influencers
Dodos
It's such a distinction
The influencer is perhaps our embolden
To some extent
People
AR
Maybe being
Taken down Road
Very good
Even being a fact
So as
People
If you just take it on a microcosm
Carrie
She's doing her alien space weirdo staff it's a lot of derivatives
Protocols
You have that like service
Space
And Carrie gets in
Influence
The events that are happening at the world end
Changes a little bit along the way
Right
The audience
Comes along with it not realizing
That the source of information itself is
Yeah
Do the feedback loop between Trump and Fox News
He really does believe in the Ukraine
Conspiracy
Pushed
By the propaganda
Supposed to be
And instead wound up
Influence
And so on and so forth
People who watch
Spock
Rving change
By the Yeah Yeah Yeahs absolutely not realizing that the source of information
Has been
Very seriously altered
Over the past few years
Right but the messaging has changed whether it was good or bad to begin with
Come over the course
Few years
That the audience
Did it
The same source of always got information from
Lose track of
If you don't
Just check in from time
But
It's just life
Special powers I asked mark
If he has special powers and I are
A bit about
My own
And he said yes
Dodger
Further about
What his special
AR
I got I have a gas
The murder other people
Now that's
Telekinesis I would respect
If you had said
I don't
That's how good I am
Guy like you just like everybody else
And that's how much I work
That's how hard I do things you know I'm just a human trying to make humans better
Nokia
Pyro
In his defense
That's a good idea
Always have your enemy
Guessing what it is you
Never reveal your
We talked about all the time
Specific
Star Trek next Generation
In arbitration
Captain Picard forces the the alien
Jordy
And they the ship
Is found the source of the power
I-Ready i-Ready
Mostly remember because it begins
With f****** beta
Hanging out in the Holodeck
Doing a f****** dick
Dickens
Play
I remember your ability to recall certain things
So incredibly
I have a weird trap type brain
Nothing affects me until you accidentally hit a box
Mariota
Boop boop
But it is
It's very similar to that like
Arbitration
Scenario
Get called out
Know your powers are gone cuz we've disabled
Mark is never going to say like
I can move things with my mind do it
A pencil
The government actually
The powers of
Easy
Oh my God another photon
So
Jordan
Raptors are good
Sure
They're good
Headstrong
The Raptors are very difficult
To control
When you're like a human who's trying to like
Lead a group of Raptors Jurassic World
Not Pine
So you saw the rapper
Chris Hemsworth Germany Chris's conspiracy of Chris's
This is not a problem
Regarding the Rock
Mark said
Especially
Difficult
Command
They don't obey you
They have
Decided
Before you give an order
What order
Going to give them
Goodwin
First of all
Do dogs run
Also it's Chris Pratt
And so you can
Discussion with
About
You on the order
Because they've already figured out all the
So he says
Therefore
To command them
However
Mark is known
Quiet
Loyalty
And love for
They love him so much
Even though they know all the angles ahead of time
He's just unique
He's just unique usciences special
I just don't know what to do with it
I am on honestly
Somehow
I'm far more on board with
Raptors loving
Chocolate
It's tamahau him just being a great come
Commander of
He's a rapper rapper
Ridiculous
It's bananas absolutely bananas
Because he's so good
And because
Situation in the world is so severe
There's so many of these alien
Battles iqc
See the fires
It in Brazil
He is Amazon
You see
Trouble in Africa
They're all just covering up for alien battles
You need people like
Like Mark
You need him
And that's mean
He's probably going to get out of prison soon cuz they need it
Regarding Mark's new job
And you can see more about this in interview
Basically
I had raised the idea that maybe
He is being trained
In his job
Because he's handling
Like large numbers
Maybe
Technical building lenses for
Medicare
As I understand it
And Mark is in
Charging all of that
It looks like
He's learning
New computer programs
And so on
Anna
The military may actually be testing him
To see if he is able
To be read
Recruited into the secret
PACE program
You can handle the current state of play
That are military
Stealing
And Mark
Agree that this is
Possible
An exact mark
More than
Ableton
He's great
Okay
We have ventured
Purely into demo
Yeah
He's still Vester Stallone he's being brought back for one last job because there's one
That's the first thing comes your mind facts
Prepared
Bright technology
Etc
It's frustrating
Creative
Yeah
World to live in where
Becky's going to get out of prison cuz they need him to fight these
Impossible to deal with
Anybody else
Well you're not going to able to handle this much easier
Because we have
Just a couple more Clips life
Cuz there's not much like
Tipsters largely
Like what we talked about.
The
Mixing in
Fun goofy dumb space bowl-shaped real world
White washer
But you heard earlier that Carrie got a new car
We're going to learn a little bit
More
She got that new
Computer
And
This is a little bit
But also
It's grandiosa
So any
Financial
Help you can give
Would be
Very welcome
To help fund the snooker
Computer that I now have
And have had to
Credit card
I will deduct it
Eventually in April
I had to
And
Payments on it
Which races
Computer
So any don't
Preciate it
At this time
With an audience of 232
Thousand subscribers and
Actually 63 million
Worldwide
Viewers it seems.
Small donation
From
Quite well
Perhaps
Something that
Consider
So that
You very much
To do so
And
I will continue to
I don't have any like
Interesting kicking her at all but I like the idea computer on a credit card
The reason I play that clip is because there are it's like this is Philemon
Business like this donation
And great I mean like you're doing work on some level that you should
3 million people list
It's really helpful
That's crazy
Go to Project
Downloads there are
II
The world listens to me
Okay
There are very few things
But I am very good
But somehow financial literacy
And
God dammit
Every f****** company run 0% interest promotions on all of these things
Find one of those that has a 12% interest option
Keep your credit score high and then later on you can cancel
Adoption
As long as you make payments on that you can keep going and paying this
With 0%
Indefinitely and the fact that she doesn't know that she doesn't know
That's a good point
And also I should say that this episode is so
F****** heavily monetized
It's an hour long and it's
Broken up by
Hunza
Commercials
Really yeah
I had to edit out commercial
No yeah absolutely like
Like is a recording it from the YouTube
It's just 880's interrupted by commercials like
An hour probably like 6 commercial
Coming
No
If so they would not have had those ads in there
So whatever.
I don't know how much
Like honestly I don't because YouTube is never been an interest of mine
I know
How many pennies do you make for a Silverado
But
Her ads videos are heavily monitored
So
She is making some money on that front
Like
I don't know
The fee structure
What I do know
Hi there she is
Or
You know how to Leverage
CareCredit
Could be a combination of both
Although like 50,000
Yeah that dude has imprisoned episode where they recorded
Call from him in prison
Tampa Bay has Iran bears
What is the sadnam
From Mega Med Episode 12
Sloth
But I honestly also think that she's
About
Some of this
Will also be
Be considering going to
Turkey
Being invited
In Romania
So these things
Are possible
I do not get paid much
Out there
I also
Half and half
So this is
Welcome to the Red Dog Life
Consider as well
Here's the reason that I think that's troubling
She's been talking about the Yelm conference this
A bunch of this episode
And every single article that I was able to find about the conference and they were talking about the
The price
Of admission to the cosmic Symposium Mission all of the money goes
Go to the speakers
So if $250 is the ticket price for that
It looks like 20 people
Paper that covers
Travel
All the speaker
Easily covers
People having to fly in for their
Whatever price
Cost to do these things
Is minim
Now
The flip side of that is if you're not getting
Go speak let's say in Romania
Then you're not a draw
What you're doing is not important
Are you a numerated
I understand the desire to
I was slightly different
You can't have it be like
We have 63 million viewers around the world
And say
I have to pay to go do the
Trips
You can have one or the other
You can be like what
I'm never going to Bluff them say that we have the biggest audience of the world
Did you compare it to other large bachata
I'm never going to pretend we are the biggest thing in the world and then go speak for
For free
I'll go speak for free because we did not have a very large audience
Honestly
The thing that I am
Amazed by with
This podcast
I have
Certain up at 2 a.m.
Become a draw
For 225 people
In certain region
And I will tell you something right now
That is
Not
There are plenty of headliner board they're plenty of Headliners that I have worked with over the years
Stoked about it
Jirachi
You as opposed to
They're tricked by advertising or something
It's not like somebody
If you would like
My point is that like with this
I just need to play
Like I
I don't
Resent
Carrie saying I have to put this
Computer on my credit card
And if you like what we do please don't
I don't resent that at all I also in a vacuum don't resent her overblown
Like I understand darcizzle
16 bigger than they are
I bet
Them being combined and also being in service oven
Inflating
Information from a murderer
That is alternating lefun and then the other side of it is whitewashing atrocities
Yeah I can't get around that
And it bums me out to be like hey
Listen
This is Lady
You are doing this thing and look it's sad
When you're talkin about needin put this computer on credit card
Andy donations
No one pays me to give speeches
It makes me sad
Insult you or like
Critique
Put
This in this
What disease is a long
Stretched out version of an ad
With Alex whenever he's trying to kill you
We got specials
That special ever Easter sales going
It's the same kind of thing but stretched out
You have the entire presentation over
50 minutes or whatever and then
Then this at the end
Like it still
Still trying to like
We've done this at now
I just don't rush
No
On a certain level
If she is correct about having
T3 million views is not possible
Videos
So is there 6
63 million
Views
Not
Yeah like
Back when you're talking about the monoculture a trillionaire
Call whatever
You know
Content
So
If you if she was if she was at Nickelodeon
3 million
At least five or six dollars
Million people watched
Anyone of her videos
Almost three times
Elon Musk going on Joe Rogan show
It's not it's like if you have
63 billion people who watch your videos over 12 years
Those aren't
63 billion unique
People
It's the same Five Guys
It's
Number over the top
It's not the same as
You put out one product
Do you have any eyes on it
Well I think it's
Partially a function of
Of the
The
I mean I guess
Supposed
Niche
Entertainment
Really knows how much
Time is worth anymore
You know like
You see it so often with free Lord knows well I mean Sports Illustrated
And how they is
Troy their staff and now they're trying to create those
Like almost multi-level marketing
Writers were it's like
Your best bet is 80 hours a week
And you make
10 bucks
I probably paid $3 an hour for the work I do here
You know it's it's but it's
Tutu pink
Nobody really knows what the valuation is
No
For that no
While at the same time I can't
Endorse
Yeah yes yeah I could be fine with all of the
The end of the episode
If the other stuff was
The other stuff being there makes it really tough for me to swallow feel really bad or or
RPD
100%
It's tough it's tough week we have this supposed to be
To get backspace
You still see shades of the modern world you still
Fifty Shades of
Fascist
Did Jason propaganda put out in different ways
I mean that's just the reality of it there is there is no real
Anymore
I wonder if you're listening to this
Not too late
Plenty of places are offering
Zi less than
2%
You can get a new credit card
Transfer your balance from your
High interest rate APR credit card
Over to a 0% interest you pay maybe a 2%
Get in contact with me and I will help you start your s*** out and if you're listening please make me a cat
Oh yeah
I would like to be a dog merch
Before we get out of here
Morning Joe
Funky ass transition from us talking about Carrie trying to raise my own
Steve-O
First one
Text Bronwyn
Another Bronwyn
Bubble Braun
I always do.
That's one of those names know where you're like
At this point in time in 2019 year like
I don't know I might be a much more
I'd like a far more common name and then we realized
I don't know how to pronounce
VI
Lle
Okay thank you so much you're now policy
I'm apologizing
Thank you very much
Your nail polish
I'm a policy wonk one of my favorite comedians
Oh absolutely
Waste
A few years back so what I worked at the Laugh Factory
I was doing stand-up I became a regular at the last
Cuz you're very talented
Jamie
The owner of the Laugh Factory
Jamie Masada
And he became like a good friend of mine
Gave me his phone number to cell phone number call me on the cell phone all the time
What's up buddy
He wanted me to start a show there and his idea for it was
What about
Female comic
Like we put a beard on
Is a business as always
Yeah it was
That I would hang out with him then
Can you call me on my cell phone from his come hang out
I'll go hang out with them
Stories about like the early days of the Laugh Factory in La Pryor and Carl
They were rambling f****** stories
Cat being
Disabled
Leawood
Be at the theater all the time
At the club
People be sleeping there.
F***** up
He's great
Posada is necessarily like a bad person
But he is so distracted by all these dumb ideas
Interpreted as a bad
Nea
Whatever
I was
I was hanging out with Jamie
Frank and talking about
A show I eventually ended up doing it called the
Peoples Temple of Comedy
Comedy
Did not do that okay
It did not work
The show is a disaster
But it was concept
Subways
They made us do it
Sunday
Styx
It was a disaster I had another idea for a great like live comedy show
Another person would be
Right
Essentially a podcast on stage
Eventhubs
Come up
Recreate
They said no.
I was hanging out with Jamie one night and Dom Irrera was in town
You showed up so f******
He was just gone
Like it was early too
On
Comedy most amazing
Experience
What's a very bad about got the most comedy
Yeah you know
That is the traditional
Comedy
Very nice
Thank you very much.
I'm a policy
Meg
I'm a policy wonk
Margot thank you so much
Journal policy walk
Apologies
National Lampoon
I'm sure that must have been
Orchids
The next
Is not Buzz Marketing for a promise
This is not Buzz Marketing
Thank you so much goose
I'm a policy wonk
Oh and I
I know there's another one coming out
John Henry
Continue to be a metaphor for
Working Man against
Onslaught of automation
Call back when I was a younger man Columbia Missouri
Oh that's how I was pretty popular around town
I don't know if they
Did they beat the engine or no
I just remember them being name around town
Turn off a result
Florence and the Machine
I would prefer
Next and finally go on
Thank you very much
No doubt different person than the other go on Chapo
Interesting how does
Hey
No go fuc yourself
It's interesting that you think that we would even be at
Send a message
Verizon email
I'm a little
Disappointed in myself
Formerly I was of
Well you should feel some change.
Anybody want to come out
Paprika let's go
Good references for
Appreciate it
Probably with a present I think we should check in cuz we will
Alex Jones
F*** out today
Play in the present business
As usual I have not listened to
Today or yesterday
Trump allowing turkey
Do that s***. I'm going to go the opposite direction
Have to assume everything I know about his
Geopolitical
Has to be right we will find out on Friday
I am going to go the opposite direction
And I think he's going to just
Find it
Percent
He's going to be like we need to get out of Foreign Wars and so on and so forth
Way too good to know because based on his entire career
Website Twitter account
Jordans
Check in on Jordan Street
Or else on Facebook
Please go to iTunes
It would help if you left a review
Vinca Court
Paradise reviews lately also
You didn't do that
Review
Look up a couple
Is very heartwarming
Appreciate everyone
This is really good
If you just got rid of Jordan 90% of the reviews that are like just glowing like this is great I love the show
It's awesome
2% Argo f*** these guys
Percent is
Truck Georgia
There are
0 in the other direction
What is done
None
Themselves
Well you're 8% self-loathing
You're right it is expectoration
For another episode soon but until then I'm Neo
I'm Leo
I am the spider octopus
Holding
Alex