I have great respect for knowledge by now I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guy
Stripe.com
Alex Jones
When was the last time you under
Unplug the plug that you feel comfortable
It's been too long
Certainly not too far back but it's
Wake me up at Buddy's generally go on float trips
That's always a good
Although even work what's your smartphone you can still kind of bring them along
Kind of
Check out at the
I've long felt the call of nature
At least the last couple years
I've been definitely feeling like I want to do more camping with
Difficult
Emulating
A little crazy
And I have a cat
Call Mouser
That's it
Chicago apartments version
I want to go camping but I have some difficulty
Schedule of this show is very difficult
I like being outside
Things I miss the most about being in Central Missouri
Do you just go a little ways down you got to find a little bit of forest somewhere
You're going to be at
Take a walk
You'll be outside
Slightly folks to your memory other than that actually it was real but
It was much more accessible Campground
Chicago realistically there probably are bunch of places that are not very far
From the city probably should go in Camp
No camping I told you it would go camping and you evolve
Almost fit on you have been very against that idea
I'd like to I'd like to do do that
Unplugged
Unhealthy to stay plugged in
Turn on the present day when we're going to be going over October 8th and 9th
Some interesting takes
On them
Tremendously
I'm in one
Alright whatever
Take the people who are
Doing Hong Kong protest
And is against the companies who are trying to silence those protests
Exactly that's why I said okay to it okay
I agree with that
Be run by the literal.
BNB
Not the devil
I guess it was another horrific take to but we'll get to that as we get to it
So first of all
Amapola
Girls
My love my life and my lady
Is between your like looking glass
Text
Text Evan
So first of all
And Neil thank you so much you're both wonderful technocrat
Business heroin
Freakishly large
Baby lovey
We start off on the 8th
It has to do with
Syria
Alex's big
Scale
He's not even dealing with it on those terms
He's dealing with a situation where it's
Totally cool to do whatever you want
It's in Northern Syria.
Just go for it
A very element
Entry level
One of the pieces
Which is not a great take
Position
The takes an interesting Journey throughout the course of this episode
He should put them in Hong Kong
The other one is
The other take that he has is that
Options
The other one is worse
Was Obama and the
For 50 years
Real
What's a neocon to the globalist
Wizard
With you
If you try to do that
That
Sir Alex's whole thing is you know I'm going to let these
Syria
Come through the Border unless I can set up this
Space
Taking what
Call the dictator says
Yeah right
With
You can always trust them to follow through on their word
Precise
Accurate
Options
Nuance
Absolutely dealing with the 3.6
Million more refugees
In Europe
Course we have to let them
People there
Historically turkeys never
Committed
Vasquez
Alakazam talkabouttd
Pat Robertson
If he does this if he allows
Yeah
Particular
Of Pat Robertson
Sims words
Robertson
Chinese proverb
A
So
One thing is true about the East Coast
Probably.
But on a larger scale I would say that there is a lot of
Divine
It surrounds Trump
Girl I don't think that
Pat Robertson is quoting the Chinese referring to that I think it has to do with their ideas
Is about divine
Rule
Robertson says he has the Mandate of Heaven
And that's a really important
Squabble
Do you want
Overtures to the idea that
God put them in our
Evanescence
He said internet
Should have been impeached
Get out of here
So I think that's really interesting and
It's 8
It's when I heard I was like Alex
You know how much you talk about God and and Trump and all that
Like you know
Pointed the finger at a Pat Robertson
Similar ideas in the opposite direction
Something different
You're an ass
Yeah so Alex's is p
Robertson
Chinese proverb
In order to
Turkey to
Come in and
Start
People
Fair enough
I'm in Alex has an inch
Interesting position on sort of a
Circumstance where in he would be against
Record
Being attacked
Unfortunately that has not been outlawed
Northern
What
Turkey
The United States has used the Kurds
Special Forces
People are so brainwashed
What Muslim
So what
It does seem that Alex has a bit of a like
Christian
That's it.
Real scary
You know he's got
Speaking small number quite Parks Mall
Necessary for
It's just a
We're there and we're watching
And to remove them as a signal that you
That bombs away we are not watching
The letter of
Go ahead and commit genocide
Annoyed with this phone call
That's usually not
You are
Really
Winging it
Or you're just lying
I'm not entirely sure which it is
Because he gets
Completely 18 episode
You know there
Trump
You're taking him out of Afghanistan
He's going to bring the boys home all this stuff
Just realized this is a completely stupid argument so but it's weird
I know all this stuff like the course of his episode like within 2 hours
He's like just
Change
All but one thing we know for sure is that all these whistleblowers
Coming out about Trump
His phone calls
Well it might not even be just a Democrat
It is
But you know they're allowing
We're talking about allowing
People to testify
Because I suppose
Which is what he would
Maybe but it you know their conversations
Surrounding
That actually just going to try and bring like
Clapper
In
End of story
The latest ladies and gentlemen
Whistleblower
Benicio del Toro
So because they've been burned Trump haters
Discredited now they have to put a little pixel
Whistleblowers
Grade school
I like it like that
House floor
And they just turned the light
Lights down on him
He's got a little vocoder out of
It's from
Peter Frampton
It's not a
I don't know
Cecilia
Maggots the spirit enemy starts ranting about how his show is basically
Just the spirit of America
Are we all just
Just going to let it go that
The Democrats
Ratably afraid
That if they
Share the identity of the
Stihl blower
Other house representative
They will leak it and kill them
Are we just going to all be like this
I guess I guess I guess that is
Americana Republic
The future
Information Warfare
This weekend if you know I'd really plug on
Doggy style plugin
This is crazy
We are the South America
Now I got to look
Listen right
I'm not doing a good job
I am bad at
And I want to let
You know that
And that's why you
Big voice of Americana plug
All the time but I'm having a problem right now
So Alex gets back to the issue with.
Again
I think
Crystallization of his viewpoint
And it is a I don't care also Trump is doing the right thing
Here's a president
We're going to move in and take over Northern
There's a present
Man United
You know when that
The voice of Americana huh we've always been on the right side of History
If I recall correctly whenever we say as a country
It's not America huh right
Everybody when they read the history books are like
That was of the right
It certainly seems like that's the
Find it to be compelling
I do not find it too
Be at all
Responsible or good
I'll because it's playing I guess who cares
You see that is just
Epic
Anyways black
The people who are going to be affected by the
The people are going to be murdered
Yes
Not affected
Bright they would be affected
Behind all this, started all these
And what have you and
I'm sure there was there's more military action under Obama.
I'm comfortable
Open unfortunately as he's discussing that.
He ends up
Piano
Really showing some cards
About like
What he believes is going on in the world
Obama wants more towards bush
Eliza country
Martial law
The whole Middle East is fighting over control
It's what the Muslim to hold never stop fighting
So it's just what the Muslims do
It's right
Now I would
Counterpoint
Maybe
Colonialism
Exacerbated
Which okay
That's what the Muslims do
Essentially we already heard him say like
Syria was in the stable place
Under Assad and his father is
Under control
He's essentially advocating for a world where like you can't have
Under an oppressive dictator
Theocracy
You know that
Wanted
We wanted to
Country it seems like a lot of this is a lot of what he's
He's implying
Underneath
Police state
Mister anti tyranny
And he seems to be pretty clearly expressing The View that some people just got to live in tyranny
Fight with each other Kill Everybody
It's what they do
Just that he's also
Also kind of Express
At least
Overalls
Strategy
With the Middle East
Will let them fight it out
Yeah and then we'll deal with whatever is left
The other there is a little bit of that I mean he did literally say it's not our problem
Set
China
Issues
On the side of against
So these companies that are trying to say
Spencer Hong Kong
And that sort of thing
Human is what we call
Humanity
Years of looking Gaucho
And Alex has the Chinese government been exposed
Censoring people that they aren't
I don't necessarily think
Sync battle
Stomach
In normal political
Talk
Pretend that's not
Even for the people of China
Don't have a access
Tattoo vpns in the like that again
That allow them to see
Internet
I think if you are
Not one of those people
Looking around for the
Because of
You're not at the repressed
Wheeler's understand
It's not hard to figure out
Yeah it's not like you're brainwashed to where you can't see this
404 not found
He was taking off social media and all of these
Kicked off YouTube
It's all because
He had the program
To take down the Chinese government
How to fight the Chinese evil government
And now look out
They're all
Everybody who criticized
Is China
Completely silenced Ananda
And there's an essential problem because he's also won't stop talking about the new episode of SouthPark
It was all about China
It was all about like
Absolutely
That is a counterexample
He doesn't understand that he's like everybody no one's allowed to talk about
Not as great as Southpark just came out
Please suck it
You do realize I don't I don't know how what the ratings are doing now but
On Comedy Central
Biggest shows
Maybe you're the last decade
Yeah
Enter Alex tries to play eclipse
From the South Park episode
It does not go well
He is totally fine with
Drum roll please
Music
Next hour after our guest lasers devoted Club
It's not a big deal happy with it
Cell phone
Guy who said
Furious
Alex but overcompensating
Yeah we know the Pulsar attack
Yeah I guess coming up after the break and that is of course
The anti-communist himself Joel skousen
Joe Cason comes in and you know I think he is
Providence in the show
Is hedging
A little bit by Alex's Park
Still very aggressive
Pro Trump
I'm frequently on Alex's show
Says that Trump is stupid
Coming up more regularly now makes
Methinks italics
Who's trying to like
At least leave that door open a little bit
Okay you think
If
It goes down in the public
Opinion
Then he'll be able
I had this guy on there
Critical voice
Keep him credible and fresh and the audiences mind in case you do decide I got a jump ship on this
You still have an expert you can go to as opposed to all the other
Yeah
Alex talk
Earlier episode
Alex's thing was
It doesn't matter what's going on in Syria and it's great
Thousand has a completely different take on the
But there are several much more larger bases with combat troops
South of that area insurance
And so Trump has been given some false intelligence that you're going to be leaving Siri if you take out these two outposts just not true
I think he's been snookered by a larger agenda
What major war start with turkey and the Kurds that will then justify
Pushing chop into letting Armed Forces come back in the series
A massacre occur between turkey and the Kurds
Turkeys were the largest conventional military
Alex
He's definitely eater
A hundred percent
Gadsden is very accurately pointed out this is not good
To be a meaningful withdrawal this is
If anything cause
Awful result
Make it more likely that more people will go in
Pushing forth as like
He said he's going to bring the guys home
It's not our problem
I mean it's sad how easily Alex
Completely Falls in line with
Cousins position like he's completely convinced them
Within a matter of minutes
To go completely against what he was saying earlier in the office
Sharia
Question
What does President Trump
Let me talk to sleep
It's crazy
That Blake
His position I thought he was going to
Ease into it maybe be like
I think you have a
Set up
These are these are serious issues
Like he doesn't have any idea
Break for him to completely change the narrative
You know when your commercial
I think Alex might be
New career for a commercial greatest changes his narrative
What's a president
Sitting in there and he's on the phone
He's like
Go ahead
Battleships
And then what are the Secret Service agents you know what I think we should
Protect the joke about this
Do you know because it is very serious threat like
Elderly against
Military
But there is
I can't obey
It's the
It's really tough
The only thing that
Amusing about this
Is the fact that Alex flips
Like it it seems like something that she should care about more
It seems like something that you should
Have a robust position on that isn't influenceable just by Joel skousen today
You're wrong
But really
Has anything until
Detox
Now move forward
I'll contradict myself
Episode
Who cares it is weird how in
The span of
2 days
We've had
Search
Obviously
Evil ship
It happened that
Even the Republic
Jesus Christ we have to save it
Overwhelming
But
We come in on the 9th and we find out whatever
Republicans are in
In a bad position
That's not really true if you look at real poles
Marvelous
17 to 25 points
How many of the Democrats America is
I don't like being gassy
Athlete that bad
Politics as a reference
Just pulling data
Literally every
He was down
1.2 Trump
Every single other relevant Democrat that they had at least five
Points
In Outlook consistently
Another study the came out of
Beginning of this month I believe
October 3rd
Trump
Is down 11-2 a generic Democrat
Just fill in the blank Democrat
Jesus Christ I don't know what real pools you talk about
I don't know
Phone internet polls
He couldn't couldn't actually say that 97
Percent of the population
That's just too far
17 to 45 points we do know that he has a real tender
Towards those unscientific internet
The real
6 people that is the same
Yeah and you're not even
Sure
So Alex a real
He's feeling good on this episode
As we saw that last episode
He was not even internally right
Oracle of Omaha
He always has against
It really is true
No one is as accurate as info
Almost you know more than I do
We are at the crossroads
Communist China
Capitulated everything else
Even talk to me good little politically correct minions
You did an hour on the South Park episode yesterday
I don't I don't know I think it's definitely possible to overuse
We're at the crossroads
Living proof
You can overuse things like
They're making their move
Do you do that
Main push
It's overused
Shirt that could be overused
Yeah there's not much he doesn't
Everything
No but that's how he feels
Really get into the intro music
Commercial break
He really gets into the
I do know this is one of those things I like
Sometimes it be like I hate this guy but that passion is effects
This might be one of those cases
Although you might not be susceptible to it I'm not sure
Original Florida for you
Compromise
Information Wars
Freebirds knows I can't change Lord knows I can't
I guess that one wasn't as good as some of the other
Time to Stone s*** like that
Modern-day Patton
That revivalist
1000 people in there and I'm watching
Oh I got to go I got to get out of here this is a very scary place
Are you know like he's also talking about like we're going to give it to Hilary I should point out that
Is now really ramping up his Hillary is going to run talk
Talking about how Trump's really obsessed with her keep Street in the batter and like maybe we should have a rematch
Things like that
So excited about that
Everybody in that right-wing world is so excited about
She said something to indicate
But she's going to run
So now what
Together
She's going to run again
Play the clip of her on that talk show couple times
Great man
In our lives
What we need to do
You need to choose what team
Nothing for plastic
We need to choose whether we're with
The globalist
Or
Right
Is a false dichotomy the Bears
No
Or do you want to go with me
Ideals
And the Renaissance in Christendom
Dodge Hellcat
Or do you want to be in a
Gremlin
It was don't either sound like choices
I mean like
So you've got on the one hand the globalist authoritarian State and China machine
Of course
You've got the ideals of the Renaissance ultimately lead to
Coming sluggish and awful
Or whatever
Avengers
He does
He's not at all
Is so
Write these ideas of the
Right there so strong a breeds
So much.
Success for everybody
But the first generation
Well
And the third generation is all evil because
Whatever
Like being trapped in a cycle of
I feel like there's another option
These are the only games
Downtown
Go on
Infinite wheel
Reincarnation
In misery
Can go on these
Straight line
Nope there's no other out
You change scenery a little bit
Preferable
It's like well it's like
Because they
They're going to be in the generation
Not the one that gets f***** over by
Does feel that way a little bit
So Alex is realizing that he's kind of
Supporter
Speech
What have you
But he realizes more
Need to actively
Support free
I'm not sure exactly
Mkg about that
Entirely sure what
But if I had to choose
I would say that's probably what it is
He is in the situation that
Is that where he's not on Facebook
He's a threat to China
Google
And all the people
Months ago
Hideout
Celebrity that virus on CNN
If popular gets a sword
We weren't
Supposed to believe that
Weird feelings about this what does that mean like what do you want
Like to go to war with China
Do you want to cut off all economic relations with China
These things are
Like productive
Suggestions
I don't know what he's advocating for
Other than getting him back on Facebook
Well
We're doing great
So I suppose the next logical
Conclusion
Is regular
Registering
I guess you probably could rationalize that
And it's military
A lot of people are suggesting he is turning on
A little bit
He's running
As a term or less
Promoting on his side are critical of trump there's a
There's a change in opening over on the Old Judge report a little bit and
Article you can find about that and I know that
CNN's not a really great source
Now it's his world
The guy from Gateway pundit
The f*** is going on with Matt drudge like people in the world are starting to notice that shift editorial
Towards a critical one of drop
Yeah
If Alex loses Matt Drudge
Baby
I don't know how I like
What are the reasons I think that is good
Can't throw Matt drudge overboard
He just can't
Still aggravated
Alex's yeah I don't I don't know what else I don't go check out the Drudge Report
Love story
Little bit
But Isaac bore importantly because of Alex's narratives that he's built up over the years
Matt drudge is the only Patriots still last out there
If you can't let that slide
Like I think that would be a bridge too far from The Cross by the globalist to something like
Really don't think you could do that
Judges to Central to Alex's
World
For him to
To turn him into a villain
For to like
Allow him to be working on the other team
Alex would have to migrate with Drudge
You know that's that's
Position for
Because
We're really finding out right now how
That's exactly how much
People are are
Like
Lindsey Graham is
So far in
One of his big like
Is pervious like let's not allow them
And now he has to be like
I guess I can't I can
Can say I don't agree with it but I can't say f*** this
Functionally like not a
An interview
Republic
Not voted on
He's not
He has no accountability for criticized
Unique position where he like
Create so much of the tone
The conservative media sphere with
There's so many lazy conservatives
He has this
Kinship with the audience
If he starts going
Towards a critical stance on Trump
That allows
People in Congress
Easier time to not have to
Eutawville because the people down
Stream the citizen
Did the consumers of the
These news articles
Will start to
Change along with drugs
It'll become more acceptable
Which is also very sad
Thing to watch
Can you
Ramp down
The propaganda
Because they can
Critical
Can't do likes
Anti-trump
So can he
Mission down or has
Pandora's Box
Aspen open
And we're just
You know
I don't know
I don't know it is
It's an interesting question
The proper
Machine Head
Has been going
Hi
Since
Late
Early 20s
Whenever everybody before that
Yeah probably
But
Now it's like
Can they can they still
Control it
It's something that I'm really in
Did you find out especially as like
Your community is like a people
That are so outside
Ivanova Drudge
Redbubble
Bush jr.
Easier
Being
CertiFit disseminator of talking so much
Diversity of crazy
I don't know how much like
100% change
Or it would be even more alien
Because those people are going to come along for that ride
World
Cuz I was like
I mean
Splinter in
In order to combat
The fact that they filled it
Single worst
Human being in history
They had to turn the propaganda
All the way up to
Revolution
You know
They've never been a
Without horrifying
And now
Because that
Splinter is a
They won't
They probably won't be able to put it back
It's just going to be
What's Brent realities now instead of hope you're wrong
Wolfie
Alex
So to speak
When everyone else Facebook
Apparently
He said Trump some letters
And they got delivered
Guest by hand
I don't know
So after this Alex got some
I'm desperate
Describes
You threaten his life
I have one
Suspect
Jobs
So I believe that
Does the government
Is an epithet that is only attack I've ever heard in Alex's show
So I wonder if he threatened
100%
Descriptor has overthrown government is unique
I guess that it's very distinct
Rivers
Who else would he
You say it about
Jeffy
Delivering
Royal Flush because God did this
Move all of it
Impressed on me
The message was
Literally
God
Alex you got to talk about
Leadership
Americana
That leadership
So
God or his subconscious
Is telling Alex declare himself the leader
I'll l
I'm going to go out and I'm going to save it
He thinks
He has the Mandate of Heaven the reason I play that clip earlier episode
Because his behavior doesn't track somebody
Crazy for Pembroke
He has
That God is telling him
To declare his leadership role
I don't know if
I don't know how many times
Uttered by people
Well
I'm going to go to the Secretary of History over here when somebody says
To God and he is told them that leader how is that going
I would assume a couple times like this
Let's say there's a difficult project
To be done like a community garden
Getting built
I got called me to help build a lot of times alright individual
Jewels
Express
Right on healthy way
Someone like Alex
Never find this to be an incredibly troubling
God called me to declare my I've woken up in the middle of the night
I know it's not even break down the whole f****** idea of like him being like
My subconscious
Alex
Those different things
If he is expressing that he doesn't know the difference between his subconscious and God's voice
Not a problem it's a big problem
Speaks like a goddamn preacher all the time of the show talking about God's will
Helping
Ascribe religious importance
Desires
That's not good
Yeah that sucks
Colt really did learn the right lessons
From Waco I think that's what we're learning right there
Declare yourself the representative
Tell people that they have to do whatever it is you say because you are there later
The only lesson to learn from weight
I went on a show where it like you saying s*** like this
And you're also existed
Like
Head
As a guy who's like
Yeah you know what turkeys going to go in and take out these cards I don't care that's not our problem
Muslims just fight all the time
Have you read that deeply upsetting for someone
Act like
Let's take a trip down a little bit lighter
Alex looks at a map
Of the United States
All this Matthew has all the like red areas and blueberries blue on there
Talking about how everybody in those blue areas
And then Alex realizes that he watched
Tombstone the night before
Like John Wayne
Clint Eastwood
Bruce Willis that are patriots
It's really almost everybody
Bison
Set timer
Basketball player was
Sarcastic
Broccoli
The Patriot
Charlton Heston
Unwatchable
Kurt Russell's attractive whatever
Don't have to feel weird about that
But I can explain
Yeah it's not that everybody likes turns out to be a patriot
They like him
He is our all the sudden the huge fan of
Jen and I'm going to go out and I just wanted to
Askew
Haha
What do all of those
Number of
Are old
Number of liver old
Yeah
Qualification
Having a money
Do we know if John Wayne liked Infowars
John Wayne was reportedly
Spider-Man
I just think it's awesome
Like these sorts of like presentation
The
See that these people are Patriots and I'm saying to them and then I learned that they're secretly fans of mine it's like
I did it it's a reinforced everyone else sucks
You just don't like people who don't like you
Great
Mustache
What's tombstone
Kurt Russell in Tombstone
Gloria
Sure
I don't know
Inquiring minds want to know
So
PJ dubs article next episode
What's your favorite Russell I have a favorite Kurt Russell escape from l.a.
I don't know
Look Paul Joseph Watson articles
About how to
To deal with China
I'm old enough to remember when
Alex
MP JW specifically
Constantly decried people using boycotts
The particularly they attacked people like ilhan Omar and those folks for the
Idea of an Israeli
They have been very.
What is politically expedient for them whatever we figure it out
Everyone
They really can't
This deal with
There's no way that they can
Engage with the reality of this
Ocean which is where orbit leader is not their leader is not
It is money
China has money
To have
That's it
So they do whatever it takes
Perhaps
Issue
Is not with
Leaders
And more with
System
The most
Explanatory easier
Explanation
And then they would have to say well
Maybe there is
Baby there's one negative effect
Capitalism and then their whole game is
Like manifestly inconsistent
Besan Alex
Paul's Behavior over the course of
The time that I've been watching
Fight like I'm not necessarily totally opposed to the idea of like some sort of Target in Chinese
Like that's the strategy
Fine
Good on you but
They're not willing
They can't resist
The urge to make cheap political points
When other people use the same strategy as
And that to me is a real problem
To everyone should be
Write the fact that it's not a problem to them
Troubling
Alex gets
Talking about how like
Orbitz
But he can only ever really come up with one example
World
Because everybody knows
Oracle of Delphi
And there's just a bunch of poison gas
Until people started listening and thinking
God
Oracle
This year's research and focus and studying the CFR
Putting the world which is
Within
15 minutes prior to this 20 minutes prior he was talking about God talking to him
Position
Subconscious Ludacris
Absolutely selfie
What the hell is going on
You know what they would just go there
Woodstock under a house
It's the
I don't know
I guess it just does work but it seems so awful to exist
Is telling you to do things and other people who believe God is telling them to do things
It's very strange
Explain why religion
Your is your goddess stupid virgins in heaven
It's the same phenomenon as the boycott
It's the same
Everyone else
Not realizing you're trying to do the same thing
8th Street
Absolutely infuriating that they always get away from it and they always get away with it and they win
Furiated is probably pretty close to write on
Steve Miller sounds
Oh that's
That's true
That's not good
Entire organization
I would imagine spray-on hair
Probably look bald
Maybe that was a pilot products
Brian Head Force
Mateo Coronavirus
Look like a group
New product
Get out there
So it's science Corner time
Alex got the bad news
About the flu shot
You know you're after here for the last
The flu gets worse every year
50%
Free flu shots
Alzheimer's and Dementia
So frustrating
So easy
If you consult the cdc's.
Six on a flu season
Even if you just look at the years between 2010 and 2018
Roberts really fluid you know some seasons are worse some artists bad
There's a lot of variables
That's what I told hymers thing
Supported by any actual science
According to a paper in the Canadian Medical Academy journal from 2001 at which was just writing up of a study that looked at
Exactly this possible correlation it senior citizen
They found
After adjustment for a****** and education
Past exposure to vaccines against diphtheria and tetanus
Polio
Poliomyelitis and influenza was associated with
That no exposure to these vaccines
Getting a flu shot annually
Actually says your risk for dementia
But these studies are all clear to point out that the results
Definitively say there's a causal relation
What are you saying is 100% supported by
Absolutely not true
I don't I don't
I don't understand
The framework
Any study that
Be centered around
3 years
Flu vaccine
Like why would you choose three
Say longer.
Yeah he had
Probably
I'm sure it's everybody
Certainly
Who are anti-shock
Fox Sports
So what are you talkin about here is a conversation
Arizona Cardinals
Not gotten
He was offered wanted
CVS
Which isn't the same thing as Fox making him get one at all if you really get down to it
I took one flu shot my life in immediately got the flu I did that was the last one
So seems like he's not trying to talk to him to get a shot either
Seems like those parts of the story things I was just making up in order to make this sound good
Just a dumb conversation
Shannon Sharpe and Skip Bayless
Hey look I don't
I refuse to engage with
Somebody who is quoting
To tighten
Uptake
Inskip
F****** Bayless
Send Shannon
Sure great
I don't give a f*** what they have
To say about
Literally
Anything and that includes photo
Vetta Sports
Those two idiots are still
I think I think it's interesting because we have is the
The kernel of something real
Fox Sports
Another never going to take only one of them reference getting the flu after getting the shot
Which
Better explanation for them
Get walkers
You just explained
The whole career
Next
Alex is talking about how he's right about everything
Michelle
Good God
Subconscious
Mandate of Heaven
So Alex
Reference in particular alien
To mr.
Project Camelot Animal Human hybrid
Totally right about all that
I'm not so interested in that
I know that he's not engaging with real science
He's creating sci-fi weirdo
Quit demonstrate
Alex
Is still
Really mad about something that happened to him in Delo
Distant
Okay
Major topically
That was an MIT research
23 years ago
Because they never saw it on the news
How much is the
Grocery stores
Pizza places
It's in the simulation to put your hands on me again
What is
I didn't realize that was before I think the point is that he's mad
Maybe unduly
And it was a perfect
Conan
Conan's Pizza
Seems like it's on Branford place
Just wright
Got2b
Toyota Concord
I just find
Things like this no this is along the same lines
Just a real under the surface
Severe anger
Creeps out every now and again
Look at
Explicable
Especially for something this trivial
Sure
Let It Go
Alex
Does exploit detox about you know
Surrounding
Is something better is apparently Chinese a nature so I don't know why
So he's the second coming compared to Hillary
The same thing it's still just a religious save your messages
Yeah we don't we don't have to
He's doing that because she is now throwing her head back
All the time
But I mean he doesn't need that
Obviously
Please don't talk about her all the goddamn time
But yeah
It's just it's just enter
Like this
This this level of
Taking such a fan
Pat Robertson's comments
For the reason that you have
Laid out
The Mandate of Heaven is
Chinese Communist influence
Creeping into America
And then you go ahead and just use very similar
Terminology
Imagery surrounding
Very much like
His real issue is with the Mandate of Heaven be
Traditional
Thought process
No
Not that it's not Robertson had said
If you had
He is no longer supported by God
Alex would find a different way to hate his approach
Get to be like
Now if Robertson
Trump
This wouldn't be a conversation
Alex
But just because Pat Robertson
Traceable back to
A Chinese tradition
That's the best way to go about this
Easy
So on our recent episode about the present-day Alex was doing
Black Friday comes early sale
Yes
My position on that was
The good
Thing turns out it was a great thing
Compared to his
Call Shelly
But a lot of things are coming back in
Wild horses
We're selling it
At forty-two 70% off
Going forward
Next year we can go further
I am I am I am transferring everything to liquid fuel
I have many connotations
That are good
For Everything Must Go sale
The only
The only business
Everything Must Go is
I didn't take those can
The places you see that sign
Over and over and over again for two years at least that had the everything
Moscato
Always
Never anybody in there signs at let's say I don't know a Halloween pop-up
Store in November 3rd
I don't think that most places that are doing well
Heaven Everything Must Go sale
Everything Must Go not a good sign
Everything Must Go is not a term
Vex
I feel like Alex be aware enough of that
This looks bad Marie kondo
Could be
I don't know I don't know based on
But also according to all these products are selling out
I don't know I don't know
As always
Speculative analysis
Full of s*** all the time so
I'm not going to put too much stake into anything like that
But I do feel like he has to know that his audience
Like
At no matter what is true no matter what you can talk them into
I think everybody who's alive
Understands that an Everything Must Go sale
Is very close to a going-out-of-business
People's minds
It kind of gives
A feeling of
Surrender
Yeah
I don't know if I were out of soda
I would go with the
One last car wash to save the rec center sale
Redford
Everybody wants
To rule the world
That song
It gets really whiskey
School for him
You get very sentimental
This is a f****** weird
Will tripped-out Alex's brain
Drink war on corruption Alex Jones
Listen to an album
Okay
Does a family show Jordan
Tears for Fears trying to bang mom
What am I telling this girl
Weird you're very weird
Cherry strain
Alex gets into small business
This clip doesn't really matter too much except for the end of it cuz it demonstrates
Ineffectiveness
Information that he gets in real-time pulls up information
Document and stuff like that
He ends up but he's not able to process what he's seeing at all
Perhaps over confidently gloatingly
That are
Table runner
Unbelievable
What's up
More
True
The total amount invested by everyone in that round of funding
What's 300
There was 150 million from other sources with investor in the session
That's a completely different thing
150 150 that they invested making it 450
Million dollars
150 million
2 million if we're going to run your three billion dollar company
Its 5% ownership if it was
Strict
By mistake
Is a control of the board
This is hot bulshit
But what I want to make perfectly clear is the way that Alex doesn't care about
It's just the optic
The Optics need to be that tencent is running
With $0.10 in the headline
That's got to be three hundred billion
Given fact check any of us even say later like oh I'm sorry I got that wrong it is
Round of investment there was other
Firms that also joined in
07:00
Well I know that
Who is that Snoop Dogg is a big investor but I'll take that much
For that
50 Cent
Tears for Fears
I've no idea
It's a present episode Jordan
So you know that means
Got to talk to Robert Barnes
Barnes
How is Barney
He's always on
He is never far away from Infowars microphone
So Barnes
Comes in they want to talk about this whistleblower situation with Donald Trump
Sure they want to
Incite a riot
Super boring
I just want to play this clip
Because I think
This isn't something good to hear from a lawyer
When you have someone doing something
Isn't
Adversarial
So I believe Robert barnes's is that you have to commit a crime in order to
From my reading of the definition
I'm not a lawyer
But I believe legal things
In order to obstruct an investigation
So
I don't
Know if I
Okay
Just because you murdered a guy
Doesn't mean that it was
As long as you murdered him League
Right
And it makes perfect
I guess so
Alright I'm coming around
I think he's a
Great lawyer
I signed the red flag
And frankly and record
Legal Minds
So Barnes about all this stuff middle of it Alex
William Binney
The former technical head of the NSA
And pretty
Wikipedia
LeBron James War
Very
Superman
Oriental people that can call things way ahead
Giddy about that's what makes me excited
Chicken you know what dimension
Sh.
Your child breakdown insurance
Those of us that love Johnson
Smooth there was
Really right about everything
One strike
Maps
Who could forget about the time that you came on Alex's show around the time of the Devin Nunes memo any claim
He had a copy of the memo which reported on are and they read from
It was a public document
I do not care about this dude
I do like Alex's to
Categories of person
For which you become speech
Speechless mathematicians
And Prophets
Well he's saying that cuz Barnes is still there and Barnes is a notoriously political gambler
F****** idiot so I don't really particularly care too much about what will you bring to the table
Guess what it is
Just everything is a G Street against Trump
I feel like with the Seth Rich stuff
I don't
Really
I don't view you as someone worth my time
Even looking into what you're talking about with the the Nunes memo thing
That was being passed off on Alex's show there's many ways from Vikings
Gets sent off to the Dustbin of propaganda
Witches don't care
Perhaps
I don't know if Benny's got it though
Careers
He doesn't have that
Spark you're not in this last clip
Because
Where we're going
Resigning off
They do talk for a couple minutes after this and then Mike Adams takes over.
As Alex's raped
Globalist
Somehow they just wanted
Destroy everything
Something goes terribly wrong
Control
This isn't
Hello
No
Hello Kitty watch the circus
Beautiful hello please
Over the music
That's the president
Has Mike turned off
I accidentally hit a button on Alex
Leaving Bill pretty high and dry that's why I don't think he has the juice don't show
Sorry to do is say hello
Very weird we'll be right back
Just over that big
Hello
Is anybody there
No
It is not
And like that is
Is pretty bizarre
Ultimately
I don't find
A ton of inspiration the present-day Ulysses
Episode
There is like a lot the real world
Touchdown by Alex
Irresponsibly
Absolutely
The situation in Syria
That's very
Serious and very real like that requires
Immediate action
Without
This isn't withdrawing troops
This isn't the things that I'm presenting it as
I just I just
It's so much of this is is
Very uninspired
Yeah I know so very predictable
Lick so much
Any piece of news could come out regarding the Ukraine
Any just going to say this is all about Biden
You know it you can you can have that
Happens in the world ads China's fall China sucks
I'm right about China
I'm the king of China
Yeah
They're interesting trends that I'm interested in following like we talked about the idea of what happens if Drudge
Leave the team
But that's interesting
But interns
It's just
You go in and expect to find
An interesting
Take Dora position
Is Alex going to
His principal should lead him
To abandon Trump over the turkey
And Siri really should especially considering how severely he took
Drunk on Aaron's cream truck show
That this would be sort of a like well there's no explanation for this
Acceptable
But it's not it's
It's nothing to him
It is it is
Bournout
I think what we
It's just
Just to bulshit
Yeah everybody is a overpowered and
We have the presidency the Senate the courts
Supreme Court like to know if it's still we're the victims and the little guys
Yeah you can try that and it
Probably works for a bit for a while but it's illusion falls off eventually
Especially when
Call mickley
Inept
Who has no
Connection to your
Reformer adversarial position
You're the things that you would criticize
The other side about you're absolutely
Given up or
Forgotten
Or whatever
Come to
Purity
That's good I don't need
Think about it
Going to make up shift
Fandom anyways I don't even
To have any credit
And he doesn't
Work
He just lies about
Where is
Power
It's much easier to Bullhorn
Absolution
Yeah
It's it's
Pointless
He doesn't have anything
Yeah
And then there's another Dynamic that is like sort of this
Ratchet
Should I get back up
Sort of more recent episode
So we've got over you see you like a real
Intensity towards
Civil War
And stuff like that
I take that still living in the background of these episodes
Not much of a fever pictures
Focus
Like I would like
Like having people go on that ride that roller coaster
Intense
I did this is a real threat
And then I'm right about everything
Yeah I mean
Intentional
I would also
Based on its based on
Erratic mood swing
Totally so I would say that there's a combination
Both of them
Happily dovetail into one-way dozen
Intentionally
Really consider the effect that might have had on people
Where is move on
I don't care that I was just yelling about the Civil War
Boycotting China and
Trying to make excuses for Trump's
Ridiculous foreign policy
I can't imagine
Just the the clips that
You know you share with me
It f**** up my sense of value
Like there's so many things where I'm like
Civil War
All of this and I don't know what's valuable and what's what we need to
How we can even
Perform triage on
I don't know all of them
Equally
And in his
It's always difficult divorce
Yourself from
That reality of life
It's a
It's got to be weird
Believe him
It's like I can't
I don't support
Anybody
Nobody is doing good
Figs in any position of power
It's so infuriating
Muslim population
That's f***** up
I don't f****** care I'd like I do every everybody
It's very it's very difficult
Respond to this with any kind of semblance of
I agree
Play more so
You got to do
It's a struggle
And I will someday but until then
REI website
Hello
Hello are you there for
We are
Not go to bed
Listen to the park
Please go to iTunes
Download
Listen to podcast
Austin do the same we would like
No I'm Leo
I am V Everything Must Go sale
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color