I have great respect for knowledge but I'm sick of them posing as if through the good guy
MoneyGram
College vype.com
Everybody dance
Dan
Is there a
Jingle you remember
Set a reminder Android
Oh really that's kind of O'Reilly Auto Parts
Oh oh oh O'Reilly Auto Parts
O'Reilly Auto Parts
It's just a divorce gone bad and she
She made her own business
Variety
Auto
She was like
F****** hate that
She just made O'Reilly Auto
I feel really fairly certain that I could be wrong
But I remember that we wish it was more of a local thing but I honestly also I realized that I had sort of Plaistow
Auto Parts in my brain as like a local Columbia business
AutoZone
Yeah
That's the that's the one that's
Sticks out most to be but I'm sure there are others
Well I just turned and looked over and you got goldfish right
So I do remember that
Watch PBS grown-ups have a lot of commercials
Myerly days
Mitsuba
Even think they would allow that
Jingles but Alex Jones
About the farmer and not about the law
Over April 8th
Teeth 2013 alright continuing are
Barger coverage
Alex's responds to Sandy Hook and its coverage afterwards
In the subchapter the
The Boston bombing
Fallout
I'm starting to realize is that maybe
What we were looking for was the wrong thing
Yeah where we embarked on was trying to figure out when Alex changes
Your story is the Boston bombing broke his mind
Hold on to
Pretty solid evidence that this is a
Major turning point
Career
He believes like we talked about on our last episode
He has
Completely outflank
Continues to lose
And we're going to go through a good bit of that
Things get wild
Before we get to that we got to give a shout out
Dozen folks who've signed up
Carspotting show
So first of all
Thank you so much you're now policy walk
I'm a policy wonk
You did said Britt
You were trying to do on Flight of the Conchords breath
This ad
Call Aunt Peggy
You are now a policy wonk
Yarnell apology why
I'm a policy wonk
Next
Text Joel
I'm a policy wonk
Maybe better than
Arabic
Lastly I'm probably going to miss
Is it pronounced
It's a cake AME
K
I'm going to say
Acme
I feel like we're getting
Impossible
Thank you so much
And
The button to support the show
Go to our patreon
Portraiture
Okay
Let me read my
Introduction
No they have on your your alert
For the final time I will introduce.
On the 18th
People do not know very much
This is the episode right before what I'm going to call the fever break
And it's the last episode where Alex has legitimate free rein to create whatever story he want
Out of the random bits of Internet rumors
But he can find
To recap a little bit
On our last installment Alex's found some out of context images on
4chan
And use them to create his own story of what happened at the Boston Marathon
He found people in the pictures that he felt fit his narrative and cast them like characters in a play
He saw some guys and we decided we're still uniform so they were they were buried
He saw a white guy but he felt looked
Stupid holding a backpack
Who the globalist
They're going to pin the crime on the
Barrett
He saw some guy was Brown.
The media is obsessed with the idea of white right when is working with Al-Qaeda
Which makes
All of this was just made up out of whole cloth
None of this was in any way based on anything other than Alex
Astoria
He came up with wild looking
Random photo
From there Alex decided he'd scoop
Forced to announce that the FBI had photos of the suspects because he reported on those pictures then again he found on
Unfortunate
After that point Alex descended into
A completely delusional state where you believe that the globalists were watching his every move and trying to counter in through the media
He was in a state of Open Season
And advocated lone actors attack the Federal
It was a f*****-up under any
Particularly
Yeah that one was wild
I assume that
Is much better and they retract all of that b******* today
Let me see all of them don't know if they do okay
They denounced
But they had photos of the
Homeland Security secretary Janet Napolitano testified before the house Homeland
Security committee regarding these images and videos
However
The actual images had not yet been released to the public when Alex
And then another media Outlet made a gigantic
The New York Post put a picture of two men to Moroccan gentleman who had nothing to do with the body
On their front cover with the title
New York Post they were operating off old tips
Law
Hood for a moment consider them Persons of Interest
But it already excluded them as having
Anything to do with
The bombing
This is a huge problem
New York Post
Discover on the
The New York Post
Nulo
Others described it as a
Appalling
They were all right
In the ensuing Fallout it was easy to conflate the two events
Send your head to imagine the picture on the cover of the New York Post
Was the same one as the ones that we're going to be released by the FBI and it been mentioned by Napolitano
Exactly this mistake
Which will discuss in greater
Detail azathoth
The larger point for now is that when Alex
He has a lot of chaos into
Infusion to play with regarding
These photos
In the absence of any real actual information
He could hope for
At this point
Sure
The FBI press conference
Is scheduled to happen while Alex is
Because he's extended his show 6 hours
He knows that once the press conference happen
He needs to be firmly in place with his narrative
He knows that that's the moment that the metaphorical cement
Is going to dry
Once there's information backed up by an actual investigation available
His rambling bullshits going to be pretty unconvincing
To anyone he hasn't already
Solidify the narrative
Establish a narrative about what the FBI release
Will be
In hopes of preemptively discrediting
M3
Throw conspiracies
Spaghetti against the wall
And see what sticks
And four of course
Salt the water before you put
That otherwise helps it stick
Also in this episode will premiere of an Infowars
Yeah
Someone I've never heard on the show before but I I
Actually talk
Weird
We're in here
It's on air
It's going to be
So here's the first Clipper Alex
What's the disorder
That
Talking about
The pictures
The FBI
People like Jack Napolitano
Talk about these pictures
They're just
Cover up
Because
Infowars
So on this
And
Completely
There's
When we show the photos
It's just a distillation of what
He's watching off on the
Claire like
Legitimate
This isn't
Yeah absolutely
You got to chase him with a butterfly net or anything like that
It's a balance.
Details
Is sincere
Buying his own bulshit
And if some of it is intentional
Ralliart
Exact ratio but yeah he buys
He thinks he's
Really scooped
The real media cuz he's so excited because he's literally never done that
I finally lived up to my promise
What years
What we talked about a little bit
Episode
Announcement
Giraffes
That was inaccurate
Never came from the Boston Police Department the FBI
It was something that was
From
Erroneous sources
Within
The
Text Tiana right
The ideas
You can you are right that was missed
Reported
Claim all of this
Because you running the Patsy operation
It's true it stretches credulity to imagine
That they're able to do that
I understand that the media is the present
So much deeper
Anyway
Amigos MSNBC
That's a surprise
I see that's the twist ending
Black Mirror episodes
BC all along
Watch that show
Cork from the night before
And that is about Obama
Bulshit
That will kind of continue
On the prior episode
76ers
North African
Direct Connect in Saudi Arabia
Talk going around
Stanmore is coming out today
Schedule
Call Porsche sedan
For the sake of Oz Trails off in the middle of a sentence
Intentionally
Keep trying to make it look like he doesn't he does not finish his thought
It just stopped
This is something that's easy to misrepresent
But I don't think it has anything
To do with the bombing at all
At this point
With leaders from around the middle east region
What's the situation with A-Rod
As well as the civil war in Syria
He did meet with the Saudi foreign minister Saud al-faisal
Find a story in The Times of Israel from April 7
20th 2013 Obama meeting with the Crown Prince
UAE
Mansions that Obama planned to meet with the leaders from
Qatar and Jordan
In the coming week
Arawn
The Civil War
The other meetings with foreign leaders were largely ignored by folks like Alex
The right-wing media because they didn't have a connection
There was already a quote on quote
Anomaly
With the bombing Saudi Arabia
Is the animator
Liza
Sure
Are bunch of a couple times so far in our Boston bombing coverage how there was a Saudi national questioned it after
The attack
And how the media been asking questions about whether or not this individual
Connection with what happened
And he been totally cleared
No problem
You know he wasn't
Involved he was injured in the bombing
Crown Prince
MBS
Would go on to cause a lot more
Talk about the national anthem
Look
Has largely ignored this story up to this
Reporting on this.
Hospital
When they founded
After he's been injured
Now Alex is picking up
That was a student who is questioned by the police
He was never thought to be guilty
Never came up
Outside of Gossip Mills
Reporting which ended up finding its way into the mouth of one
Questioning
Indiana Homeland Security committee
Because if you elect a Republican
Can your diamonds
This dude was actually injured in the bombing person whose question
Attention
Patient directed his way with probably grasping
It's Rasta cover story
But they had no real information
On May 24th 2013 Washington Post
Reported that the Saudi students
His first public
Covering an interview that he did with the Islamic month
He told them quote he is
Continue to receive death threats
Send hate mail to the degree that he has not moved back to his house or resume his normal life
In his words
Discussing being at the hospital while being questioned
Quote
They were really scared of me
I'm injured
I don't have anything and they asked me what do you have in your hand
All the police officers in the FBI and all the nurses
Doctors were staring at
I was looking at them like is it because of the color of my skin or is it because of the name of my country
Yes
To both
Media and cupboards so suspiciously
It is a part of the Saudi cover up
His life got derailed
I don't know if I'm going to continue my studies
I came in to study my bachelor's
I have a full scholarship
My country
I don't know if I'm going to be safe from other people
Because I lost my privacy
So that's why I'm really scared
So it's not an easy thing to
Forget
Simultaneous
As in mass
The chusetts by ice on an administrative immigration violation
Because they were in the country to go to school and had not registered for class
This is a completely different person
The situation was 100% unrelated to the bombing
But the right-wing media hurts. He's student
Twice and just assumed that they couldn't be more than one Saudi
In the school in the Boston area
Pitstop person
To survive
I would like to I would like him to survive with better critical thinking
Like
Like really like we kind of
There are so many big schools around Boston
There's Boston University Boston College Harvard Emerson MIT Northeastern University
Tons more
Pretty sure I just heard
College
There a lot of Saudi Arabian students in the US to pursue a degree scholarships
The program provides students with free tuition covers their living expenses and even pays for a trip
Saudi Arabia to VIs
According to the association of international
In 2012 the United States record numbers of Saudi Arabian students enrolled in academic
Institutions around
Backcountry
The number cited for the 2012 2013 school year The Chronicle of Higher Education is 107,000
Saudi Arabians
Enrolled in US College
Can't believe 107,000
Did the Boston bombing
How did they all keep it a secret for college factual
To help prospective students determine which school is best for them
Three schools in the Boston area in the top 10
A perspective
From Saudi Arabia
Northeastern University's number to Boston University's number 3
And Harvard is number seven
What are the qualifications
Recite YouTube
Turn the rankings was quote the presence of students
From Saudi Arabia
On campus
There were large numbers of Saudi Arabians
In the region at
These colleges
And this one being injured in the Boston bombing and one failing to register for classes makes total sense
I probably went too far in looking into this
Particular detail
I think it's important
To clearly show how unfounded in
Stupid assumption
Being made here about this that this is the same person
A student who is question
Who was taken in by ice for administrative violation
I can't
Anytime
Historically where the mob
So this is a
I just want to point out the Giza
These right-wing narratives are being built on
And their absurd if you take any kind of close analysis
Like you really look at what's being
Put
The guy questioning her in the whole night
Committee
Deporting this person even if they're not us
Information about the bomb
And she's
They're obviously not talking about the porting the guy who was questioned
There's so many inaccuracies in that question I'm not even going to answer that
Ava Roberts
Excuse me
I would like to say
To be great
Senator from the
Montana
You're fuking idiot
Shut up
So Alex gets around bragging
Because
Through his efforts
Brew
I don't know
Sending Dan badonde out to harass people at the
These press conferences
Datura
False flag
Become a very high Google
But this isn't
Memorial service
There's a certain irony to Alex saying that these people who are public servants
Trying to inform the public
Bye
My certa trademarked Google trending
And we had
Yes
Straight
If you like that
Episode of navel
He's accusing the governor of Boston
Crass
Infowars app
They will let your resume
If it fits disqualify
So the night before
There was an explosion
Interesting
Alex's
Covering it
Because
You think
It would be the biggest
Doesn't
Don't seem to cover it that much
Dismissiveness
Approached
But if you're paying attention
It's very much a like he thinks that this is a false flag
But he's pretending like it's so obvious
Itsblitzzz
Fertilizer Factory
Explain
Coming out
Incidentally there's a big
Spell
Exploding
Important
The magnitude
Undoubtedly is the culmination of 18 years of my work
This is my career
Got to focus got to focus on this one
I'm finally right for the first time I know for sure that the fertilizer Factory was a fertilizer at all
It was clearly fertilizer good for dryer
Obviously
It's just I know I'm going to be like
I think I'm telling
Burger for later that's what I think
The 17th of fire broke out at this fertilizer plant proximately 20 minutes later the whole thing
Blew up an explosion so large that it registered
2.1 on the Richter
15 people were killed at least 200 were injured.
Consider the amount of likes
Property damage
Surrounding home
Ultatel
What exactly is actually still a matter of intense
The ATF released the results of their investigation.
In May 26th
Fire hit
Some critics have claimed that this
Conclusion isn't appropriate since they feel that the ATF only decided that because they couldn't give any other explanation
For how the fire it started
I'm not entirely sure which side I think has the better
FairPoint
You would assume that if the ATF would make the determination that the fire was arson they'd only do that in the case of them have
Excluded other
Possibilities
It seems unlikely that they would do a years-long investigation
Declare something
Intentional without considering those other possibilities
That's that to this day no specific explanation is known
And no one has been arrested
The fire so it's really anyone
What exactly have
I mean
You got to be
Pretty stoked if you get away
It's blowing up
Fertilizer
Sure I don't know he's guilty
Probably
I guess I don't know
It's your goal to do it you probably be like
Suspect human involvement was an article in Reuters
Police records involved
Plant that they looked over from the past 12 years
Apparently the plant was a very frequent Target for these
Do chemicals
Pneumonia
Right from Reuters quotes
According to a 22002 crime report
A plant manager
Police that
Intruders were stealing for 25 gallons of anhydrous ammonia every
Free days
Inconsistent
Good map
And the problem here Jordan is that they ramp-ups
Security in response to these regular break
Reuters found at least 11 reports of burglaries
Ammonia leak
At the plant in the prior 12
Okay well I'm going to go with inside
The or just people who come in to try and steal with a valves
Wingstop
Becoming a robot Dusty old
Chemicals
But none of that's conclusive a pattern of negligence
The part of the plant
Secure the facility
Which would leave it open to
Either an RC
Semester summer triangle
Still shittin just makes a huge
Mistake that ends up causing misfire
Yeah it sounds more like
Doing with chemicals
Stu cook
I'm leaning more towards the guy came in and
He was like
Oh f*** I f*** that up
Recklessness is entirely possible
I'm not sure what happened here other than it was a horrible tragedy for the people of West
City of
Who is absolutely unrelated to the Boston bombing
Facetious
Catching on fire
I think he does think that it's related
Otherwise why would he bring up his alleged drill
The check place
I can find literally zero evidence
There was a hospital drill there
An article in nurse.com
Discusses how the medical staff at Hillcrest Baptist
Just Medical Center and Providence Health Center
Dealt with the chaotic and traumatic situation
With a near heroic level of poise
The two hospitals hundreds of extra page
Patients with a range of injuries
More less
They worked effectively as a team
And Heather Branch the assistant manager the Hillcrest Hospital Emergency
The department said quote
It was a life-changing experience
Experience will forever know that no matter what disaster rolls through the doors we will always be there
What are the reasons they were able to operate so effectively as a team and able to treat victims
I'm so effectively instead of your prior
They've been part of a drill that recreated an emergency
Situation like
Which involves hospitals from
These surroundings five counties
It involved inter-hospital cooperation
Piece of the response
The fertilizer plant explosion
Eileen Bohannon the emergency department director at Providence Health Center
Merced quotes
What we learned from previous drills were put into place for this
And I cannot tell you how smoothly it
The only reality to the idea that there were Hospital drills involved in the actual location
Is it a year prior nurses and doctors learned immensely valuable lessons about teamwork
Crisis management
They were able to put into action
Literally save lives
Do you do drills at
You're setting up a false
You don't do drills and
When you fail miserably
The globalist
So much
God
That's amazing
That's really cool
First thing to see the
Like the actual fruits of the drill
To see you like these people were able to
To do this triage
So effective articles talking about how like
Some of the people that were coming in
People that they knew
I so people were crying like nurses were breaking down in the middle of it
And people tagged in
You know like you be able to the other room for like 5 minutes and Noah
Because we understand that this is
The human part of the response
Right
To be done
We also have to accommodate people who are having
Difficult time with the job
You wouldn't be able to do that to affect
Actively had it not been
Infor
The consideration of
Oh yeah I imagine
Somebody you know
Your f******
You're nowhere near is
Important
I know you're my friend and
I'll be very difficult
I got to save lives
Now later actually more information comes up about
The hospitals that were affected actually in the area of this fertilizer fertilizer
That's
Alex and his people are actually talking about a drill that affected
There was an emergency preparedness drill plan for April 8th
Is the North Hills Medical
But it was cancelled because of the explosion on the night of the seven
Now this might be interesting if North Hills Medical Center was in Waco or in West
But it's not
880 North
In Northridge
Flint Hills Tech
This game is so f******
UCF flimsy this s*** is
Hey realize that there's nothing
Because nothing you could do to correct this
If you think a drill at a hospital 80 miles away on the wrong day is somehow
Cause for suspicion whether or not this
Lotion is real
You're almost certainly past the point of getting back
Reality
And that's why I was done
I'm speaking
You know that this s*** is f****** weak as hell
Northridge
South blow up Factory
Get back up there and feel like
Easy stuff
I'm not saying
A planned one before I'm just saying
Alex talk about the picture
35.
4chan
Do you like really strength
I think maybe when he got off very kind of realize like
You know what
Those are just pictures that we found
Fortune we might
And make it look
Some really of
Special ship
Is the start at the beginning of what happened
Anonymous
Has contacted us as well
National
So it's now some intelligence operatives who are operating as
Anonymous
Data dump
As opposed to Paul Joseph Watson
With us
Digital dropbox
It's pretty crazy
So as time has gone on now Alex
That he
And that the media is in fact
Scared
Of what he's doing on air
Like people who are aware of what he was doing
Could have
But I don't think they're scared
Going for
Ha
So Alex's is
Bedtime
He does something
Media was
MSNBC
The reporter
Photos
Edy's
Completely blown
Things are almost going to be like
Okay
And then
59er probably the only people who can't respond
Everyone else kindergarten
So terrible
Global
In hindsight this whole thing is
Through as a trip
Parent display of narcissism
The easiest way to put it is ahead of this story when he's nowhere near anything
The only thing I think is important to point out here is that Alex has once again basajja
Massaging fact
From the day prior
In order to make it look like he called every
First the announcement that the FBI had photos
To the erroneous announcement that interested
He makes a little sense for them to announce those two things simultaneously
Blurring of the timeline Alex's using to make it
It seemed like a mainstream media was
Leaving Brainerd disarray
And Chaos than they actually were
Because that's the energy needs
Resent
He needs you to think that they had legitimately no idea what to do because Alex is blowing the case wide open
And the response was
Completely nonsensical coverage
The second thing is that he never predicted the tienen was going to announce they had photos
He may have said that all fair I guess I can't prove it
Never said that on air
Alex was completely surprised when cnma there now
And freaking out himself
I predict they will need to come up with new photos of people
Because our two Blum case wide open
And this I guess could be called in at interpretation
Of the FBI releasing photos of
We different people than out
Another possibility which I think
More like
Is that the FBI's zeroed in on the actual culprits
And ultimately they were not talking about the say
Same photos
This is where Alex's groundwork becomes so amazingly and
On the last episode we heard him say at least twice
Figured out this entire case
There's a chance that the globalist
To change the plans
Could happen
That's single caveat is so crucial to his ability to sustain being wrong all the time
While pretending he's always right
If he's able to construct a reality where he's always right
And evidence to contradict
Predictions of narrative is just a global is changing their plans
Because he's too bright
There's altimate Lee nothing you could do to
Disproven
He's crafted an inescapable box
For his audience to live in
That's a really shity thing for him to do ever
But particularly in response to a large National tragedy like this
It's monster
His his like a
Retconning remind
Give me so much of a
In the loop
Have you ever seen that movie
Armando iannucci
Pic of it I thought you were talking about that movie that starts
Kelly was
American Idol
They were having
Meeting
It's like a thinly veiled
This guy is
Rewrite
The notes
He said something
So chilling with
It doesn't matter what was
What matters
What should happen
He's rewriting the Holt
Like that is such
Alex
It doesn't matter what I did say
Right and that's all that
Right now it's
When you try to pass yourself off as like a
It's fine if you're just like I'm a guy who
So in that last week we heard him say that Wolf Blitzer came on photos
A bit
But after that
Alex
Clear that the photo and app
Before
The botched
Erroneous
Alex's just making all of that up
He's assuming what was going on in place
Jesus knows everything about what was going on with the
People behind the scenes at the end
Repeatedly
He's completely he has nothing to base
She is because we all know that Wolf Blitzer can only say Wolf Blitzer he's like
Pokemon
Just some people understand.
Israeli intelligence
Wolf Blitzer
Does dwelling in a state of lucrative delusion
If they stretch
A spy movie on air right now
Taylor Robinson
I play that also too
Unprecedented
Like a spy movie playing at on-air by Alex's right
Misleading and really abusive
Bluetooth audio
Being played out on air
Talking about the anonymous
Data dump
Seems to think
There
Good guys
In like a CIA
Are the FBI's Shoreway Community good guy
It will show you the originator
Was Oliver
Avocado
Good job Drudge
Thanks drudge intelligent
Broadcast
I think it's so funny to me
Him announcing that they did a Google
Image search was
That is the most research they have ever
Admitted actually have honestly don't even believe that it's true
I think Alex just knows the Google image search
Right
Alex
Is now kind of because their questioning of Janet Napolitano involved questions about this.
Arabian
National that was supposedly
Going to be deported who's been conflated with
The guy who
Has now become much more popular
In conspiracy world
And so now Alex is starting to build a case
Probably going to get paid
And on Saturday
Completely
Emergency
Sing for them
To do
Little people on the internet
Out of context images that they've created
Does not really have an impact on an investigation
That's real
Yeah
I think it has
Level up
Asher
It's as relevant
So if Alex
Search
Yesterday
On the 17th
They were all set
To blame
White gun owners
Unbelievable
Beavis and Butthead
So Alex is just
Going to blame that guy
And now they're having to shift who they're going to pin it on
Do you think that's going to be
Probably because he
You saw the
Cover of the New York Post
Assume that the same as the dispi photos
It's very simple.
Is very bad
Yeah but what are the elements that he's using
Is mixed up in his narrative
Is that on the 70
They had a bump
Called into the courthouse
Ended up making them cancel the Press
They were going to hold back
Determined that he knows why
Unbelievable
I think it's impossible
The first thing he has literally no reason to think that this white guy in the photos
The blame
He is literally zero reason to think that the police ever even talk to that guy
Anyway important to the story is internet rumor and Alex's fantasies
This is the definition of terrible work on Alex's party
I don't know who this white guy these pictures
I don't particularly want
Everything I can find leads me to believe that he
He's just a private sitter
Listen who is at the marathon who became a central focus on the internet
Largely motivated by Alex Jones's death Britney Spears
Little white person was going to be blamed for the bombing
And tell anyone can prove that he is anything other than a marathon attendee you happen to have a backpack
I believe he deserves his privacy
And I wouldn't even to prove Alex Jones
Throng
But there's a more important aspect
And that is the weather at wherever this guy
In the days after the bombing
He was very likely not aware or maybe he was aware the pictures of him were being spread all over the in
Internet implying he was involved in
Plan to murder in Maine his fellow City
All evidence seems to indicate that he was a victim of this
This attack
They are not necessarily sure that he got injured or whatever you might have been I don't know
But anyone who's there I consider a victim of
And instead of plastic processes
Experience and move on with his life
He's helping playing for the very thing he just unfortunately had to leave
And I don't know what his experience
That was like
But from the account of that Saudi Arabians
We discussed earlier you have to assume that it wasn't
Positive
Going from experiencing the terror of a terrorist attack to immediately have an unfounded suspicion
Thrown your way
Give me different things a difficult thing for anyone
To go through
As I mentioned in the intro
On April 18th New York Post cover story with an image of two other people that were gathering internet
Suspicion with a text
Quote bagman
These two pictured at the Boston Marathon
The problem was this
And the one they ran wasn't the one
That the FBI was such a release
Or anything that the DHS
First to report they committed an egregious Act
This picture that they had published
Had been circulated by law
But it wasn't in the context.
Two were
Also other emails that were later produced clearly said that these men were quote not Aventura
And that they're being singled out was based on quote
Bogus Intel
In October 2014
New York Post would settle a defamation lawsuit for the for this cover for an undisclosed amount
But something
So important to not lose sight of his how damaging these actions are
To the people who were the
The Washington Post reported on one of the men featured on the New York Post cover
Who is only 70
18 years old
His father said quote his now only
Sleep 1 or 2 hours a night
And sometimes refuses to go to school
This kind of stuck-up
This deeply traumatic
To the people who end up having internet mob
Track them down
Or they can't go to school without everyone thinking they were part of a plot to kill
Civilian
As we criticize Alex
Discovered just important
New York Post
Because if we didn't it would be slightly dishonest
Stupid f****** Oblivion
Not to disclose to Mi I don't know how much
The important
Things it's the other side
Like as we criticize the media like them for their horrible errors
New York Post apologized
Alex Jones isn't held to the same standard
He relishes acting in this destructive way
For me that's a very relevant difference
As for the courthouse that was only evacuated briefly because of a bomb threat
It turned out to not be real
Evacuation
Back to work the only thing that's based on his own thoughts
There's literally nothing else supporting this
He can't prove even a basic piece
Service.
It's just embarrassing
It's made even worse by the fact that the same time they evacuated at Courthouse
The police also evacuated one of the plazas in from the entrance to bring them and Women's Hospital in Boston
Bring up
Alex has his explanation
The space of literally nothing except are paranoid delusions
Whereas the realities
Seems a lot like
City that just offered a bombing
And they're taking any bomb threats pretty seriously whether or not their death
Incredible
And that interferes with government business
It interferes with the
A police business
First Tech
You know you wake up
Like the internet thing
That's just like
It makes you almost
Everybody to have a
Kill switch for all of their social media
Profiles
Scrubs
Clean at a f******
Bug out bag
Yeah that's fine
Nova Scotia and stay there for a year
Dad's terrify
You can't
You can't doubt needs a liger
Just got to let it blow over and hope no one
Eudoxus
You got to lay low for
A while
That's awful
Text Cliff Alex pretends that he had predicted that it would be the Saudis
I already
I don't believe is true based
By listening
Episode
I'll let him have his
After-the-fact predict
Remember
Alex is very needy
On this episode of you had notice
He wants a pat on the head for doing this great reporting
Does a good job for the first
You really want
People that have to like
Sit down and be like
Find this one time
Great
Will give you this one
Yeah she just wasn't God you have been right all along I like
You validated years of b*******
Breaks the case
Initially I had no idea
About this idea
DHHS release
Same photos that you was rambling about
So what did you and I can't find any indication that
The DHS and released any photos of the
Backed up to this point
The farthest a gone was that Janet Napolitano testified that they did have
From further digging I know that Alex is just talkin about the New York Post
I consulted the Infowars website
Found it on April 8th
Paul Joseph Watson posted an article titled breaking
Police confirm Infowars photos of Boston stuff
Which is all just about the New York Post cover their making this faulty assumption that that is the confirm police photo
It's very unlike Infowars to make correct
Because the New York Post
Tickets for this
This article includes
Editor's note
The above photo was originally given to the New York Post by the FBI as Persons of Interest
Add a light
They were no longer Persons of Interest
That of course means that the
Police did not confirm Infowars photos
In his article is total b*******
However it does clarify for me
The DHHS had the same pictures as
What important Point here though is that the picture on the cover of the New York Post is absolutely not the same ones that Alex has been obsessing
Broken and the guy
Where's the post cover had these two Maraca gentlemen want of home
Doesn't even have a backpack
The FBI would go on to release the images
The suspects taken from surveillance
What's cameras on April 8th
In the afternoon
It hasn't happened by the time Alex
Iran are talking about photos being released
This is all probably another negative results of the New York Post cover
Alex has decided it's an official DHHS release
And now he's worked it into his narratives further reinforcing
The idea that he's right about
It's real simple
But but
It's one of those things like the path is really windy but it's not hard to walk if you just
Beautiful look at
It's not much of a maze
You don't have to
Is not there but you
You should take the article.
Confirm editor's note
Right
It's super rare on Infowars
Straight up
They just left
No editor's notes nothing
Supercuts
Yeah let's make sure we're not even
Close
So at this point Alex
Repeats a little bit of Internet rumor
About this
Conspiracy spaghetti against the wall thing
Asher
666 Boylston Street
Calling card
The marathon ended 666
Jared kushner's property on 5th Avenue
Don't look into that Alex
If you look up this bit of non trivia about the marathon ending its 666 Boylston
You'll find a bunch of very reputable source is picking up the story after the 18th
Probably response to a simplify
We're talking about UFO blogger.com
We're talkin about USA Hitman.com
We're talkin about Galactic connection.com Heavy Hitters
Hard-hitting New Trier and the New York Post
Wouldn't put it past
However if you reported earlier
April 8th
There's only one Outlet
Enough it clearly has to be where Alex is taking this
It's a little bulshit website called beforeitsnews.com
Beforeitsnews was started in 2000
Possibly with good intentions
At the place where any citizen journalists out there could post news items they thought needed more coverage
Naturally this quickly became a favorite place
Completely insane people to masquerade their nonsense
Anybody who takes
This place as a credible place to find information
The complete
Or delusional
Just for fun I decided to look back and see what beforeitsnews is running as some of their front page stories
Does taking the six
S*** from them I'm telling you somebody was a lizard
Unfortunately there's no snapshot in the way-back machine from The A-Team
But there is one
And here's some of their headlights
Travelers are among us!
Nibiru hard evidence
I don't think that evidence is that
Napoleon skull!
I like the! That one might even required
This one's a little tougher
The most profound mystery in the world
I don't know that's going to be bad
Is the most ambiguous about
Whether or not you can see it.
It's bad
The riddle
Very very
Boston bombing is a false flag and a lot of links to Alex's coverage
This is part of a tea cozy
Beforeitsnews
Finishing Line of the marathon was it 6
6 Boylston
And that is the fact that by definition the finish line
Tire Street
If one side where it's 66
Present
List all traces back to a purported Google Earth image
But I'm 90% sure is Photoshop
You're the reason I think that okay
The image shows a marker at 7666 Boylston
In the center lane of traffic it's indicating that the center of traffic
An address
The street itself does not have an address
The buildings do
Meet at the street would be showing up as having a physical
School Street address
The second issue I have
Is if you look at Google Maps
Can you consult the street view
You can easily find the finish line of the marathon
Regardless of whether or not it's Marathon
Isn't that line is always painted on the street
If you look at the side of the street that
Evenly number
You'll find the Marathon finish line is pretty closely matched up with the Boston Public Library
Whose addresses
The building immediately next to it appears to possibly be a different building
But it's actually just an extension to Boston Library known as the McKim bill
It's easily identifiable B
Inscription on the on the side of the building
The Commonwealth requires the education of the people is the Safeguard of order and Liberty
Ironic
And Subway is based on
So dumb
The McKim building is a home a lot alike research collections
God damn gorgeous piece of
Particularly inside
Look so cool
Buildings physical addresses
As the main entrance is on the in
Intersecting Street Dartmouth
There is no 666 Boylston
These conspiracy theorists
Real address and it being something
Okay then he's in the middle of the
Because what
Directly underneath
Boylston Street
Dude hell
Physical address
Everyone knows that he'll is actually underneath the WWE ring my life
Fever
Other Supernatural characters will pop up and drag someone down under the ring
So this is nothing more than bulshit promoted by a completely crackpot website
But stupid number
And you'd only be doing s*** like this if you wanted to create unnecessary suspicion about
People using
Ninja Turtles addresses
224 + 8 what is that
Pizza delivery
Alex's
Is expression
F****** pissed off
Coffee is that no one giving him
Credit for breaking these pictures
Of the DHHS
Announcing their pictures which are obviously
And now I
Congressional hearing
Are Fox News
Because
And they show you some photos
Sad
But it makes sense
How he could trick people into thinking this
In the moment
Like its
Day
When the FBI has actually released the pictures
This looks really
God stupid
This looks like a child
Thinking he's right about something that everyone saying
People would write hit pieces about irresponsible
Wrong
You because you were wrong about the
Right you were
Putting undue focus on private citizen
Deeply
Yeah we'll give you credit for f****** the s*** up but you are not right about
Bright
So you get that pat on the head
Is it now
Alex
Has been reporting on for a day
They're also now apparently
Congressional
Looks like
You think I'm running
Courthouse
Photos of
Today
Congressional hearings
The genitive politano speaking
With the homeland security committee
In the house
But these pictures weren't
She just
Disgusting
Fixers
That they had
So
This is just Alex
Yelling about nothing
Is b*******
But
On our last episode
Outside Steve pieczenik on
To commit treason
Yeah
But also to give the motive for the false flag
The next day that Alex is just parroting that
The exact same motor
Also
By Bush
Again this wasn't a bipartisan
Congressional report on governmental organization
Call Dee Congressional Constitution project
Is funded the specific report was funded by grants for the Rockefellers
And the open Society Soros Foundation
Does all the lot of bulshit but Alex's using it easy using it as like
They needed to get that out of the headlines that's why they did this false flag
You see all the
Who's coming into place
You get the answers for the why the house
If you need to do it cuz he's running out of time
Yeah it doesn't matter
Ingredients
And you know
It's so easy to
If you just look at it
But it also
Like I can I can
Project back
To that time
When there's not a lot of info
Formation available
It's such an easy
Anything to manipulate
Dangerous
Space
To have large groups of people in
High anxiety
Even if
You would normally otherwise be able to
Directly
Through that's for the
Apparent bulshit
In a
Emotional overwritten
It's just going to be
Can really
Do that your
You know you got the
On over your eyes
Comes back to the same thing where it's I caught recruitment is a lot easier with people who are invulnerable
Like you just have a breakup
Something like that
You kicked out of your house
Much easier for nefarious apps
To come in and
I think it was like I could
See how it'd be so easy
The Bewilderbeast
List of Alex's
Conspiracy bulshit
Like all of this is not based on looking at pictures
This is the perfect
Time
For something like this to happen the ingredients
So right
Right for him
And it's
I think that's a lot of the part of why I looking at this may
Makes me really Act
Is because I you can see the variables there
You can speak
Alex behaving in such
Which way is heat
He's aware of that
Like this
But he knows
This is when
The Tide is coming in
And I have to
Yeah I mean
Bournout
Throughout his entire career after every tragedy is his moment
Strike
Another level
Absolutely
It feels
Pretty sure yeah in a way that other
The other ones that we looked at
The government in the media and the globalist
During crisis
Right now
Because Alex is bust
Their whole game
Would you say it if you lose the Mandate of Heaven
Touching what would you say that the leaders lose the ice plant
Funny that Alex now.
Chinese
Robertson
Very consistent
Green thumbs
Perhaps
Exploit
Adt's has that he's got a message
Cuz he knows they're listening
It's kind of fun
But also I should tell you
You never give
Later
I have a message
He doesn't get to my message but you could argue that this entire thing is
University
Here's what I want to say to you
This Sunday
My first thought was
I'm a monster who should
Destroyed and my next thought was
Here's what I need to say to the club
I could talk s*** on Middlebrook
Alex believe
Let's start spinning into a little bit of religious stuff
Throughout this episode
And one of the things he discusses is the fact that he has
And he is literally on
Killable
That's pretty wild
I mean
Based upon
Mission of the Bible that is true regardless of whether or not he
Kind of heavenly
Protection
Yeah I know I mean like every boys
Everybody's date and time is
Predetermined by God
Like what do you say
I feel like there's more behind it
Bulletproof
Because he's here on a mission
From God
Totally fine with the idea that people have liked vague Notions about
Guardian angels and stuff like
Calls
Everyone believe protection I don't
Carol it's your prerogative
However
I think it's a way that Alex's framing this is super f***** up
He's making it a thing where God has to be
Decide in order for him to even be
Killable
Anything
Possibly due to have woodwork
Some gardening Angels our protector
That's all good and well
But if you really believe that obsessed with guns
Why would he constantly talk about how many guns you keeps in the studio
Shouldn't be comfortable in the fact that even if someone broke into
Infowars HQ with a gun they wouldn't be able to do anything cuz he has God's protection
Graton Casino
Who are allegedly ex Blackwater employees
Why would Alex need Mercenaries 2 protective of any attack against it wouldn't work
The only way to make this make sense
Is it Alex knows that
He doesn't have
Have God's protection
God heaven
Made me an indestructible Warrior
Deep down
He knows that he's manipulating people in his a force for bad in the world
Dial this Jordan
Under The Heading of more possible evidence that Alex did join up with those Satanist Antoinette dial
I think that might be the case
God helps those who shoot
People that's how
Esposo
Really like you only way to make that make sense
Is it like he wouldn't have Seth with the arming himself to the teeth
Yeah if he felt that he had Divine protection he would be all about
Send
Walking through life
Untouchable
Like
Yeah
The professed leader of his
Things of God was like
And it's house
I would assume that he does
The talking about.
Who as we heard on the last episode
The one before that
Has gone to Boston
He is an official Infowars employee
He's there with an Infowars bike
He's yelling infowars.com but everybody
Disruptive
These press conferences
That the mayor of Boston
And the authorities
To give
Call the public
Whatever information out
Is is known
Determined baby
Investigations
So Alex
This clip
Up till this point
Work
At press conference
But it takes him forever to
Stop talking about the footage
And this is just a camera
IPad
Doesn't recognize
The drill
Harry doesn't he literally just says no neck
Next question
He doesn't get mad
Describing
If you go and watch them you'll see if anything and exceeding level of patience
Display towards Tampa.
They don't kick him out even though he's clearly being disruptive and making accusations
Supposed to ask a question
Governor Patrick does
Steve enraged answer your question
Slight annoying
This is really important to Alex
His narrative.
No matter what response Tampa.
Officials being caught with their hand in the cookie jar
It's really a very basic propaganda
You go and send some annoying a******* to go yell at a press conference in a pretty high likelihood
If it gets thrown out you can argue that they can't handle the truth
If I the officials yell at him
I think I'll just kind of betting on something like that happening and I'll put down D managed to provoke is the governor
One word answer to his question
Because there's nothing here Alex has to go really overboard characterizing the video
That's honestly really but
Another important Point here
Is it the video that Alex does end up showing
Is edited to make it look like a press conference ends in response
Stupid Andy's question
Officials responded to other
People's questions
This too is a crucial piece of Alex's narrative
He needs to make it appear that there's
So afraid of this Quest
False Flags in
Drill run away from plan press conference
Reinforce
Reinforce this narrative
He's putting out he's so dangerous
Real
All this is smoking mirrors
And edit
Because I know damn well
Play the raw footage of the press conference will just look like a loser who the adults
That doesn't work well for the
You forced the narrative
They're scared
That would be good test
There
Alex's
Could you play the full
Unedited video
Coach people
So well but
Beforehand
That when they watch it
Did they do see
What's the nearest place that sells
The video
Like
It's almost like
I'm surprised that they even
Bother to edit
Well it makes it now makes
Easier as a point event
Cuz right now you can't
Show the established nearly
We're not going for just
The diehards
New eyes
To get people to
To do Google bombs where they like everybody search for false Flags
Analytics
Higher on Alex's
Articles
Are TAG false flag in the middle
You know that's going to drive more traffic
To him
You trying to do this
Yeah yeah yeah
The full
Press conference would work with people who have already internalized the narrative
But you need the edited version in order
To get them to
To the point where they would internalize
It helps
It's one of the only things
It's like intersecting with the real world
Of this investigation
Is we have damprid Auntie yelling at people to Prescott
It's such a crucial piece
Of the propaganda
Alex is putting on
Do you need to edit
I do agree
Eventually you could just show the whole
Yeah it wouldn't it wouldn't matter
Another really interesting difference
Between then and now we're
The president can admit to committing crimes
The people be like
Crimes people
To believe whatever it is
In the present
He's not really bothering with
To attract
The new listeners as much as possible but he's not bothering with trying to
He's like here's what you get
We don't often
And uplifting
Sing to his clipso you play the
The trumpet but they're often
Do you have the parts that are ghosts
Interesting to other folk art
Incredibly stupid
Isn't included
Presentation
To fit his narrative
For sure
Right
I think you're pointed also stand that he's probably left
Interested
In the wide net
That boats
I can probably appeal to
Show the photos
That he broke a date
Before
Electric current
Beam through this a
Just mad at the media
Covering it up
The control
The controlled media
Won't show the pictures that I broke
The government isn't showing
And the
So it's important that I imagine papers are thrown
About what's going on
This is what's going
It's so stupid
It is it is
Like a
Now it's
I'm so used to it
Still
Ratably annoying
Wendy's
Supposed powerful
Why
And whimpers
Is all the
Why is
Minion picture that's the flipside of Alex's North
Soft underbelly
Whining all the
The time
But the bombing
A lot of it is very intense
Like
Figuring out where he's getting these ideas
And this is one of them
Alex
Infowars article
And he realizes in the middle of it
Started reading this comment
This is great
Wards.com
Real quick just point out
It's really important
He said he loves me
He doesn't take it to actual
Sorella
Something is he set this up by saying I love this
Original Boston
Caliber
It was super pissed off about
When the company that moderated comments dropped him
Infowars
Like all the article
Yeah but there's just no comment
I can even pull it up in the way-back machine but comments don't populate any
I really wanted to track down this, cuz I wanted to know if am use the n-word
I'd say that's my only question
Alex realize that he started reading it explicitly
I love this, he realizes I'm in trouble
There's nothing funnier than Alex saying olympic-caliber
And it goes on it goes on
It's so stupid
On the screen
Are they may have
It's like
It goes on
He tried that trick when he was reading that article about his fan who kidnapped his children
We wouldn't have to read the part about the guy tying up the kids grandmother
Internet comment
By saying he loved it
The only question I have is how racist
It was
If it's through Alex for a loop that makes me think it had to be really race
Edward level
Oh yeah either way I was realizing
Cynthia
Tried to mask the comments racism
But he made the mistake
Of keeping on reading
And here's what
Sociopath
Obama
So stupid
I love this comment I had read it
Love this, and we're home. Edward ever f******
Coward
Started
He hasn't and finds out a rapist
It's titled the riddle of the Jews
30 white horses on a Red Hill I think
Is it the fact that he's taking time to do s*** like that
Should indicate
That this next
Cliff
Information
From the bombers
So the important thing here is it so important for him to paint
This Anonymous person
4chan being his source
Because
It sucks
In in the narrative
And he needs to patch up that hole
It needs to come from some very legitimate credible source
Which is these Anonymous good people within the intelligence Community who are sick of the bulshit
Otherwise
Closer analysis
Message Board what you doing
Understand how it is
Supposed to
How it is we're supposed to reconcile
Two things in the same
And which is first
We Google searched it and it's been on a bunch of Twitter
House already
+ 2
It was given to us directly by
These intelligences
Google Twitter accounts
After the fact
It's people had gathered all of those photos from to Alex
In reality Paul Joseph Watson with cruising fortune and now they've created
Nextdoor
For a better source for the information
It's
Annoyed not professional work
But reality
Fire. Alex knows how to
But he does know what's real which is good
Next clip under the headline of Alex
Just constantly complaining that
No one is
Back again throwing a parade
For his awesome report
It's so controlling
Drudgereport.com
The photos
He's just so bent out of shape but no one is
Congratulating a bad work
The first time you really believe
He did good work I think you're right that's why you responded yet
That he's like for real guys look
You know I know we both know what's been going on I mean wants a parade but
So focused on no one giving
Credit it does have a different feel to it then
Is wild
Hyperventilating on air
In order to sort of real serious times
And in the process ends up making
Ludacris
Of course
I'm having some butterflies
This is this is open-and-shut Smoking Gun
Marathon
Open-and-shut case man
We caught video
I don't think there's any other conclusion
Provided
This case
Is not opening
Explore with you hear some of the things you need to do even if you're going to listen to
To the way I was
He's right okay not
First you got to figure out who these people are in these photos
Ounces to anyone in this Anonymous intelligent
Does contacting him know who any of these people are
A hurdle that needs
Steube hurtled
That's a problem globulus remove people's names
Whenever they become
Next movies people are if they're willing to submit to an interview you can ask them questions
If Alex
The cops
Alex seems to imagine you could just take these out of context pictures to a judge
Or some s*** part of the globalist deal with the Devil is that if you get caught you have
To tell the truth it's a reverse the police have to
To tell you that
Next Imagine somehow you can tell these people to talk what if no one was ordering them to do
What evidence
If you guys like Alex thinks or marine Special Ops just said we were at the marathon
And you think we look weird
What evidence is going to provide to contradict
It'll be a disaster of a case to try and prove anyway
It's b******* where outages decided all these connections he's making his head exist in the real world
Really is scary
It's very scary if you imagined amines
You know like yeah
You approve any
Numerous lawsuits in the leg
It's almost like he really doesn't
And any of the laws
Or how court work
Like he just doesn't have any concert
Really shady
It's all we get back now to this theme throughout the episode of Alex wanting a parade for his great
Breaking the story
Is going well Alex Jones
In front of everyone
It's not all over the place
It's not
It's in the ship media online
New York Post cover
However it's important to point out that the post from the same source that Alex is pulling
From
Guilty to similar journalistic operating off bogus emails from actual lawn for
Reporting bad information
Alex is getting random picture
Fortune and writing a story about it
Because Alex gets all of his news from websites that are completely full of s***
Sensational.
He naturally thinks that the entirety of media is talking about the same thing
He was covering already
Just because he
Conflated these
He saw the post covering also heard that politano
He doesn't realize that the FBI is now
Not yet released these images
So most likely assume
Post cover is in
In fact the release of the suspect picture
Brown people
So he thinks that this picture is
Saudi Arabia
Saint Patty's
Now that he's blown up the hillbilly gang
He's further completed
The Saudi student who was injured in the bombing and unrelated Saudi student
Classes
Person in order to
To suggest that the Saudi Arabian Patxi's
Be taken out of the country
And that's what this meeting Obama had with the Saudi foreign minister was about
It's really interesting because all the faulty steps who makes it is reporting or pretty clear if you just listen to him
And have some distance from the actual event
Super easy in 2019 see the glaring holes here
And how you so eagerly fills them in with the narrative
His own design
Concretely point out these lies
You could say I don't know if that makes sense
You couldn't say like I don't know he was
There wasn't going around anxiety
Confidently makes these dumb-ass assertion
It's the duct
Really one of the worst parts
Outlook
Seeing have done what he's saying is
But seeing how easy it would be to be
But there's something to it
I know I'm saying that's kind of consistently repeat
Because I think it's
Important
I think as we go through this
Like it's important to not lose track of it
The climate and how people
How he's willingly and aggressively
Manipulate
Yeah I think he gave up
The media isn't
Sing Alex Jones
Of all people
Is correct on
That of all people
Note Cookie generally presents
Himself is being one hundred percent correct
All the time
Forced
To admit I'm Corral
Yeah supposed to
Cuz we both know that
Welbeck
Expressing
The media hates
People about that
Possible reading
So Alex
Fantasy here about how this
These pictures
Tortured
It's it's great
Jessica Jones
About the dude being tortured
It's
Got a gross
He doesn't know
Electroshock
Orchard
Dial
Just like
Pictures on
So bad
You needed the appearance of them
About this a lot of good evidence
Patriot folk are all over the media
And he doesn't play any clips of that
I went to Infowars I can't find any articles of them demonstrated
You've built that up as narrative that they are doing right is now established
Turn on his own
Previous
He needed that
It's gross is just a match
Images with this guy
It is decided that he's mentally
Decapped he's decided enlisted by a hero
It has nothing to do with any reality
Anything Auto
I'm always
Cuz he because he describes
Everybody
Traits
To therapy
Like always
If you think somebody is bad Hillary looks like
It's like all of that
Always
Curious of what it is
He would describe him
Himself as
Looking like
The mirror
Like I wasn't in the same way that I want
Specifics on
Cowboy Calvin Klein bottle
To be something like that right
That is how we describe
How could you possibly
See that's like that's something that
It's like what is it his eyes
I'd rather not
I should correct my
Alex doesn't
Just
Fantasize
Is about them
He also has
Founding
Glitter
In the CFR
So does Gary Hart letter
Floppy bulshit
But Alex is talking about
I'm freaking out mostly because I'm not willing to watch truth Rising just to find some
Contacts for what he's talkin about very Hearts react
I'm certain that Alex's embellishing and misrepresenting Gary Hart's reaction
None of that really matters
On 911 truth.org there's an article about this letter that Gary Hart wrote
The first thing that's important to point out is that it does letter wasn't written for the CFR
Or anything like that Gary Hart was a member of the
How far you wrote for the
Posted September 2000
The letter is titled quote unsolicited advice for the government of Iran
And what did the support into point out is at this point in 2007
Things were not good between the u.s. and Iran
In January of that year the US has right had raided the Irani and liaison office in a rock
Which was serving as the
Defacto console
And they took five Consular officers hostage
Which they wouldn't release these dudes until July 2000
It was super tense
And hearts letter exists within that
Was Iran
Huffpo
Unsolicited advice to a wrong was that the US does not go to war unless it's provoked
But sometimes it's
Like certain more hawkish elements like to provoke
Provocation
But it's important to point out what he's talking about is not false-flag necessarily
He's talking about a advising Iran to avoid giving someone like Dick Cheney
Juicy's Giant
Define to justify going into another War
From the letter
You'd probably be well-advised to keep your Force
Including clandestine forces
As far away from the Iraqi border is he
You might even consider bringing in some neighbors
To verify that you're not shipping arms
Nextdoor
Tone down the rhetoric on
You've established your credentials with those in your your world who thrive on that
If it makes you feel more powerful to her like his agents at the American Eagle have at it
Sticks and Stones Etc
16 months or so you should not only
You should not only not take provocative action
You should not seem to be doing
For the vast majority of Americans who seek no wider War
In the Middle East or elsewhere don't
Don't give a certain vice-president we know the justification he seek
Going to attack York
This letter in no way of saying
That's an absurd misrepresentation of the message
That heart was Express
But that shouldn't be too
I remember
Text daywind
Ayatollah
I had a
Unsolicited
Letter
Gary Hart
They just said
Who are you
Actually thought he was Corey Hart I wear my sunglasses at night
Stop wearing sunglasses at night
This is bulshit just keep that in mind
Animals
But surprise is nothing more than performative mask
There is no passion behind
Completely artificial
And most importantly nothing you saying is true
I guess that he's got to play any of these clips or any other media Outlets
And nothing I could find on his websites
The brew that at all
He's just playing his role
Anything else working
August traffic is way off so he's leaving hard into beat you over it
But unfortunately
Borrowed time
Because in reality
You knows that he hasn't
Predicted anything
Particularly interesting there's how he said that he predicted that the globalist would ban powder from the gun shops there at the end of the
He didn't predict
If you recall that came from a 4chan post that he read on air
Whitney Houston to present as a troll
Bougie started agreeing with as
Read it
If anything you should be saying they're blaming the powder from the gun shop
You heard me convinced by a troll post that that was going to happen
But that doesn't quite sound doesn't roll off the tongue not really
So now in 2019 I can look back in town
Outlaw powder
Fireworks in can still get fireworks in both places
And places you can't didn't ban the because of the Boston bombing
Did it because some kid lost an arm a decade ago in the city council voted in
Buford Drive to outside City Limits fireworks
Nothing Alex is saying
This is all just performance
Presented as truth because he knows
Traffic is up and he knows what makes him interest
It's this sort of b*******
Overconfidence I'm right about everything I predicted all this s***
He knows that's the honey
But he can get people drawing
I was like when he adds
It's those tiny little
Dad said like
Like
Going to the bar and watching UFC
I think somebody in particular
Brody won't have him on his bro
A little bit of Dante's Inferno whatever he creates all of these
Pacific Hills in April 8th set with people whose arrival
All the globalist
QFC like
Just feel that way maybe it also falls in line with
His like anger
Sublimating masculinity
Alex
Democratic fundraising letters
You found it we're going around
We need another Oak
This isn't true
Still have to play any of those clips
So I can
They were ever going to be another Oklahoma City bombing
There's literally no way I believe that such a thing
I would imagine that with being misrepresented here is
Some organization splc
Sent out a fundraising email to discuss the growing threat of right-wing terrorism not as a positive thing but as a
Business to keep an eye on
It makes sense for them to raise money by pointing out that
80s
Tea Party Movement has grown the more dangerous militia communities have grown along with it
Reaching levels unseen since the mid-nineties witch
Take me to the Oklahoma City bombing
Analysis track record is littered with him misrepresenting thing
Things like that
Probably assume
That's what he's talking about
Yeah
I can type
If they sent that an actual if they literally sent that address thing as a real thing
We will
Still be hearing it from all of the evidence
It's like everyday
The closest I can find us a couple of comments that people made that were saying that Obama
Be back in 20
Smartpen said interference on Hardball
Remember president
Remember President Clinton reconnected with Oklahoma
And the president right now seems removed
It wasn't until
The Clinton really clicked with the American public
Obama needs a similar thing
This isn't single mama needs a new Oklahoma City Bombing to save his presidency
It's connected with the American public in that speech after the bombing
Are Obama needs
Similarly Rican
It's not about the terrorist attack
It's about the speech
The other instance was Robert Shapiro's an article in the financial times
The bottom line here is that Americans don't believe in President Obama's leadership
He has to find Subway between now and November of demonstrating
I'm short of a 911 event or in Oklahoma City bombing
I can't think of how he could do that
You can read that as a guy saying that Obama better fake terrorist attacks soon or you could read it as a political commentator
Stream examples
Express how bad is situation Obama was in
At the time
MARC Penn, came a couple of days
After the 2010 mid
When the GOP
Control of the house
I gave six seats in the Senate effective
Most of the hope that Obama had
Of having a Cooperative Congo
Political commentator Mike
60 prospects right then
Shapiro's comment literally says quote between now and November
And that's referencing that he said this
Shapiro's articulating that there's a rising
Conservatism happening at the
Obama's approval rating
Falling
So he's probably going
The only way to read either these comments as expressive been for some
Fake terrorist
Is it you're already convinced that that's what the people are
I can't even
Like if I think about it
Hard enough
Obama we had a Democratic president
Supermajority that the House and Senate
Now is
Weld by 30
Seven Feathers
It's like
We could have ever imagined
Don't even think about it
It's about a democratic fundraising
Email or letter
I should tell you that I did find a fundraising letter sent out by then Executive Vice President of the NRA Wayne LaPierre
6 days before the Oklahoma City bombing in 90
Federal agent murder law-abiding citizen
According to an article in the Chris
Science monitor about the letter
Mr. LaPierre urges gun owners to
To take action before there's no Freedom left in America
Obviously the fire Timothy McVeigh blow up the Federal Building
We can be sure of that because of the time I guess
It doesn't work out
It's tough to get around the fact however
Exaggerated
Advocacy for gun right
Kind of looks
Fire Department Federal Building a week later
Oh and I also found an article from the LA Times
From April 28th
Just after the Oklahoma City bombing
Elizabeth damn headline
Oklahoma City after the bomb
Lobbyist stymie efforts to trace
Explosive technology
Such as
Such as the use of gypsum material Define blast origin has been around
It's usage
My first thought
That headline is unwieldy
Someone needed to take another pass that.
You see though
Through these indestructible microscopic
Call tag
They can be put in all
Explosive sold in this country
Any bombs used in the text like
In the 1980s the office of Technology assessment did a study and found that implementing these
The Titans quotes
Could increase arrest
Related to bombings by as much as seventy five percent
But you know what that's unilaterally
Ultimately
Can't imagine why
They're people who are like the group
That represent
Explosive manufacturers were against it as well
Their reason with explosives for like
Demolition
Position
Adding
Could make the
Morphe
Explosives
Other people other people instead
So there's a lot of x-rays aboveboard on
Anyway when people talk about how the NRA is basically a terrorist organization
It is some of the reasons
The red the red Rick is indistinguishable from to mess
The terrorists and their actions
Exceedingly difficult for law enforcement
To solve crimes committed by domestic terrorists
That's why people think those sorts
You know it's like
If Isis
Hey
Don't
Investigator
Because that's who they are
Right
Eventually does get around to saying that people are blaming
Rihanna
Might be the bear is a news
Report about how the NRA blocked
The efforts to put tag
Explosion
I'm guessing
Probably on MSNBC
Or CNN
There was a small piece
About this
History of vodka
Bombing
Probably super
But I don't know if that's
I don't know if he's tagging could have been put in
In fireworks as well I don't know
If anything it was just a discussion of
Their advocate
Making things harder to track
That's a noble cause.
Alex Ferris
People more afraid
Everywhere
Shower
But don't worry
Right now this is more attacks
Because
I've blown their operation
Everyone admits that I'm right
It's crazy this is insanely responsive
Freaking out
Is that
Harry Reid
And giving a speech
Said that we don't need to be
Got off track
Get distracted by these black helicopter types
Who saved those false flag
Naturally
Cell course
The blackout
Freak the f*** out
In
Alex's introduction to talk about this he accuses Harry Reid
Throwing a fit
If you listen to this
She's giving a very calm
Alex throws a fit
This country and everything
We can keep them off.
Please
We should keep in mind
Organized crime
Fountain Valentine's Day Massacre
So Congress dramatically Limited
Long time ago
Machine guns
Basically disappeared from history
Movies
Yes we can and should make the same common-sense approach
Dianne Feinstein
Because we must strike a better balance
The right to defend ourselves
And the right of every child in America
I'll go to the band because he is more important than satisfying conspiracy theories
Helicopters
Operation
Only sort of solution is
Good give me free advertising that's the only solution
How they were at skating for It Go
I mean
This is just further in that
Pattern that Alex has
That like
This is giving
Very common sense
Measured reaction
Out can't allow that to stand
It's too sensible
He's already portrayed him having a fit
So he has to keep interrupting that yelling over the cliff otherwise you'll realize he
He's not at all having
He's completely misrepresenting what this is
This is this is how Alex DLC content
Alter
Hey
Alex
Don't talk over
That's my job
Shots fired
In the hands of schizophrenic so who are on drugs
Continue that line here saying that they're going to have to do another false flag
Is blown up their original one
Now it's all screwed up by the grace of God
He wanted to frame us
Better
Sure
Motorcycle Waterford
A rare 2013 that was a high-quality
Breath Alex's Day videos no evidence or proof
Explosion in West Texas
This was
But because he's decided that's how they operate the imaginary enemy I created who
Always does that
Demented
Using that very same level of shotty logic
I could just say that one of Alex's Tire
I could just say that the fire was set on the night at the 7th
Set hours earlier on outer shell
Declaring himself
No authority to rule
Obviously I don't think it one of Alex's listeners blew up that fertilizer
But I want to take this moment to demonstrate the level of inference
Right
Actually yours makes
Is far more likely but it's not true
How much meth I imagine
Alex
Perhaps I don't know this
Could be
So this is kind of gross because at this point in the episode Alex starts sort of trying to reach
Playing with a story about the
Child who died in the Boston Marathon
Festool a starts trying to
Emotional about the bombing
Right
He's trying to
Pretend
He wants to use
The kids memory for something else
Rather not talk about that at all Frank
But it's important
Because in this clip
He discusses
His feelings about
Sandy Hook in whether or not their actors
And I think you might be surprised to hear where is that at
Calls coming up
Boston Marathon
Or does it mean that you
History study criminology
I meant what are you saying is that people who are saying
Reason on your show yesterday
But Alex is not presented
Since April 1st
Turn on this show
And he's someone who absolutely believe something
Crazy people
Socrate Alex Salas
You know talking about this
Make a pretty gross for Alex to do
As he talks about it a little more
He begins by bragging about his
Transitory emotional
Okay
Tea Party
Can you believe those dirty gun owners
MSNBC was going to come on in
Commercial
He's mocking an imaginary reporter being a emotionally moved by the death of a child
This is all just in Spanish
F****** person
Who's projecting that sickness on to Scottsboro
And I disrespected
If we talk about it
The first thing that you should ask
Anybody is like are you proficient at everything
Includes the one thing they are
Literally
Incapable of doing which is
Experiencing
Which is the least empathetic person
Starts
Arguing that these images came out the New York Post are the same as the ones
Has ended the media and the government
The investigators
Those photos
This whole time
Time sure
Eching to release them so they could blame the
Auburn metallic starts
These imagine
When the photos of a Navy SEAL
And the redneck
First
Adjust just get ready
Too long
That you were looking at things
Hurt you bad
They have
Close their eyes for one second and that's
She practically
So Alex has more pictures
Of the
And the marathon
He discusses
I've been sort of
No no pulling back a little bit of information Coy kind of dunno
Who cares
Major piece of Alex's narrative
And the whole thing is
Command
Purportedly
First started talking about these pictures of the Marines
There's nothing suspicious
Who cares about that
This is stupid
These people looks
But I was going to ask and now we got to that point where it Escalade
And it requires a bit of an explanation
Cuz there are the people who are in these pictures
More pictures of come out of them
And they are
So
He could have been radiation
It's purely based on a couple pictures
Created entire store around
Tyler Lee Adams on fantasy
More pictures and more information
Really
And now I'm going to lay waste
To all this.
The first thing
Is that Alex has repeatedly
Suspicions on these pants with backpacks
Because they looks
What are the primary things
Ever caught on camera suspicious
Is that they appear to be distracted and talking on phone
That picture was presented as being before the bombing
Happened
Their behavior the way they were looking around was used as evidence they knew something was going to
To happen
However later it was revealed that this picture was
Cropped version of a larger image
If you look at the actual picture
This is very much after the bomb
If you're distracted and not looking at the marathon because
Right right right that's a good reason
Thought
Hansen shoes
Asian detector
That still seems
Stopwatch
People who
Conspiracy theories that already found the answer to
These men were members of the National Guard
This was reported on CNN on April 15th at 3:45 p.m.
I'm just about an after an hour after the bombs explode
Troops from Massachusetts
It's National Guard were assisting police as well
This naturally raises the question though why is the National Guard on site at the Boston Marathon
You know this would be a good question for Alec
But you so far away from the actual story that he doesn't even
Realize the answers he's demand
Time to go already
On April 18th Sergeant First Class Johnson publishing an article in the Air National Guard website about
Assistant
That's common
Between National Guard units
In particular
Civil support team
Which is what these men were members.
Quote the Massachusetts
He was on duty during the running of the Boston Marathon
Augmented by similar civil support team
From the New York and Rhode Island National Guard
Alex legitimately could have looked at
Because
Number of these dudes have big letters EST on their back
Short for civil support
Carnival giveaway
I guess it'd be easy for Alex
You just say that it's
The same thing you know I have faith
Conspiracy theory of these dudes being
They're completely different organization and he's decided there
Probably not
On April 6th
The public information director for the New York State military and Naval Affairs division
Security newswire quote
Anytime you have a high key event where there's a lot of people
There's usually unit from the Civil support team in the area to provide assistance to first responder
It turns out this is a very common
According to an article in the Washington Military department's website
There's civil support team quote support of the presidential inauguration deep Governor's inaugural ball
Seattle Fire and Police at every Seattle Seahawks
Home game
They also help the Minnesota
Tea do to their increased need for assistance
During the 2018
Team Super Bowl
All of these events
Other large-scale Gathering
Police press
And they're regularly augmented by members of the Civil support team
And the only reason this time sticks out in anyone's mind is because it was a time when there was actually a terrorist
Activation
These teams are
Specifically in specially trained to respond rapidly
2 chemical and radiological Danger
Which is why you see one of them with a radiation
Detector in one of the pictures
From right after the bombing
Important
The security puzzle because
In case the worst thing possible happened
They're trained and ready to deal with it
It wasn't the case
What's a marathon
You be thanking your lucky stars that those dudes
Do they could have saved a lot of
This really matter
Alex could still easily say that
The fact that they were there means
The cfp being there Matt
I guess that's a decent argument if you want to call every Seahawks home game a drill to
None of this reality
Conspiracy
But it's still important to point out that
When does episode is being
Recorded
It's been 2 days
Send Erik durm
Publicly talked about who these
These guys are
Is Alex's researching this
Anyway
He's really into
The truth like he pretends to be
He should know this information by
And you know what's even more interesting
Noted callers notice either
This is very public information
Anything simple Warriors are really digging into the truth like they say they're interested in
I would expect for them to at least be coming up with cancer
Pharisees about the correct group of people
But they don't
They just beer back Alex's narrative that these are seals or mercenary group
And you know what I know that this is publicly-available stuff because I only used
Information
That was available by the 8th
Yeah yeah
Looking to who he
Adidas EST
Like it
It's crazy like I just
Express
How stupid
Alex being like
Demand answers
Right
But you never see any Islamic leaders
Condemning radical Islam after a terrorist was very much the same phenomena
The same ship
See what you want
You're not looking for answers
You're looking for your knee
Honestly before you even told me
It's really interesting really glad I learned
If you would said that he thought he had a photo where they were using a radiator
My first thought is like
This is just like those old
Tiny photographs where it looks like a guys holding up a
Cell phone but that's
Actually what I'm hearing
Look like
Whatever you say it is
Is that they were just like off duty military people there who were they are for the Bob
Director at the time Craig
Fugate said in an interview was that
Came out around that time for
From a different
Exactly
His point was it like when you have
Tragedies
First Responders in our mind our paramedics
Police but awesome
In reality First Responders are people who are there
You know like Yeah The First Responders
You know if the reality wasn't these word
The cftc
Team members
Medford
CIT members
Yeah
If they work
We're just off duty military people you could still see you like
Their first responding they have some sort of training
The police might enlist one of them too
To carry a radiation thing around
Off-duty is not
Just going to be like
And head home
Pretty much
Explain why a lot of Alex's
Today's photographs
This also explains why
No one
Interested in these photos
Because anybody
Drive me crazy
Soul Train
Enough
A maddening is Philip a catastrophe like
Known
It's no
It's not like this is
Closely-guarded Secret
Army birthday
I think it's frustrating just because of the immediacy
Of it in a
And that we've been
On this long roller
Coaster ride Avenue
I think it's like any but it's like any historian being like
Seriously
The Civil War was about states rights
The goddamn
It's right there if the added frustration to Lexington be like
Stopped like information is available someone could have
Me too much because I know how good Alex is at this job
Also know that the Cs
He does do training
Like they train local police
Apartments for
For some
Of the
Preliminary stuff
Because that's also part of their mandate
I could easily see Alex being like people there for exercise
Conspiracy
I don't know
I just I wish
I wish
I honestly.
I would like to
That would be nice
So Alex is mad
Because
Tampa dondi to Boston
Do y'all at the
Press conference
Derails
And rightfully
People are not
People are like this is bulshit
This is disruptive behavior this guy is full of s***
Answer he's mad particularly at Glenn Beck
Pretty cool
Scum
Bus come
Broadcast
It says there was security people there
He's such a bad man
Hate to agree with line back but no kidding when you're right you're right to the Somali pirates
When they know what they're too
Toronto predicting that all the people in the pictures that he promoted and put out are probably
Be killed
Is real nut
These pills were actually CST
Who is
Answer this nose
About already
Hey this is just
This is just
How do I Alex's they're convinced that these are not
Civil support team
He doesn't know anything
Feels but she'll probably
Higher-level that even Green Berets
Because there are levels higher than Green Beret and Alex
Has a great you can prove it
Unintended
Most accurate
Looking out like that
This is so bad folks
This is so bad
Yes that is bad that's bad very bad
Yeah maybe there are but your evidence of it the best
Stop
I would love to
I would challenge Alex to redo his career
With the stipulation the movie
You can never use a movie of evidence for your b******* ideas
Sure you know Alexa
So Allison is a pump-up speech that is great
We all love a little bit of
Passion
What you can do is
Makes a one-to-one connection between
And subscribing to
To his version of Christianity
Join me in the feelings are running
Grow up
And declare your Independence declare your Independence
Atomic level
Will will work its will upon the world being free isn't it
I know universe will open up and the Living Water of Jesus Christ will float
Sound of the time-space Continuum and you will truly be free
Wow
You see though there's this like explicit connection between his political ideas
Voorhees f*****-up version of Christy
It's very it's very
Clear in moments like that
Without a semi-regular basis
Like that
That explicit connect
Has drawn
It's troubling
Post info
All he's got to do is
Just added a bunch of those type of
And he's got the next
Best selling self
Right
Like that sounds so much like a
Can Eckhart Tolle but with
Talking rock music behind it instead of soothing maybe they interesting
Isaac is next best idea would be like
No
Never the answer
It would be to just be like okay I realize that the political sphere is never going to
To save the world from the globalist
Ironmaster
I don't think that's likely but
It's like Kid Rock going
Add cash grab sort of thing
One of our recent episodes
Present I can't quite remember
But I was talking about
How God was talking to him
But he also said could be God could be myself subconscious
Yeah you're right
Wichita
Very true
Because of mixing up.
It is an issue
This next clip
Presented even bigger
Give me energy
You're not but also Alex can't tell the difference
Between the devil and his subconscious
So now is he has a
Or feeling or premonition notion
That's really bad
This is bananas but
He reminds me so much of Crunk
Emperor's New Groove when he's got the little angel in the demon
Like he's just unaffected by either they're both saying nonsense and he's like
Yeah my nonsense to whatever and they just move on
That's so he's literally talking about having a little angel
Tell you music
She's just a symptom of
Probably just the difference between what's going on
God is telling him that he's doing such a shity job but he thinks
The devil the difference between Patrick Warburton in a cartoon
Is it Alex
As a radio show any other religious
F****** Zealot and right-wing
That's an issue
Find it hard of gold
On this side
Episode
Get the pictures
Aren't really the suspect
And that the New York Post
Recover was a f******
Alex's real fluid
So it's alright
I found a news article from the New York Magazine
Claiming the fazenda pictures of the two suspects coming out today
This news article it's not claiming that the suspects are
The two suspects
Enviro in always pictures
It's going to be two other suspects and these two suspects in the picture is gone viral
The guy in the blue jacket is actually a teenager
Running on his
Schools track
And the Guyanese white hat
And Black Backpack is actually attract coats
Forward
They're going to
Suspicious cribs
Suspiciously do that
Have any focus on at all
Is the people who actually you know there is footage of them dropping the backpacks
Despot
Yeah it pretty hard
Hard to get around evidence
Perpetrators
Weird weird that outside of all the pictures and show.
Mysterious leaks at the correct
Man that's
That's
Impervious
Pervious armor
Any evidence that you're wrong is a cover-up that
It's just added into the
The churn because they wanted
Tiff Buchan
Painted on this way
White redneck
Alex
All of this up this is
Next
Now
Be part of a special program to help America
America
I mean it's just so sick
This is one of this episode particularly in this stretch of time was like
Really laborious
Because Alex is
Kind of being affected by the lack of information
Yeah like he's able to spend
Do you like
Yoda pretending that the New York Post cover is the official thought we were right all along
Parade
The little stick
Like
It deteriorates into constant just like him making stuff up about what must have happened
Flights of Fancy that he has about
These guys being chosen
A season like
It's just like
He he's suffering from the same problem that they're mainstream media is because
As creative as he is his creativity is kind of hit a wall
Oh yeah and that does make this
A bit more of a
What's log to get through
The same time I was right
Noises that like
He's getting a lot of
Call sis
Thanos
Like this is
The iron is hot right now
So you can't do anything
Grandbabies
Next Hitler propaganda
They're not going to use the chair
You know that Alex embellishes
Just about everything but
I complete
Like I said he is getting some new stations
Because of the increased
Yeah yeah
Kind of becoming a really hot item
$8 people on the internet
Interested
Information
This app
Since this vacuum real official information
Is making people lose their mind
And Alex is capitalizing on that
It's really
Overdrive
2 calls
Some more calls
We're going to enter.
Where we get to see just how
F****** stupid
Alex Isley
Hate to say that I don't like to judge
Individuals as much as I Judge Alex
But some of these people are profoundly.
And I know that part of it is raining that Alex
You know like he doesn't
Watch out of them
E-rewards
Stupid
Speculation
And so that behavior is reinforced
That
Is first one just call her
Suggest that we need vigilante Posse used to go around and arrest cops
Alex is dead.
People with power and the other constituents
You see people break in the car
250 people breaking the law
Trip
Galaxy's respond to that is probably
About as good as you can do on Infowars
Reform is very needed
Going in assaulting a cop
Under citizen's arrest
Is absolutely the wrong tactical decision
I don't think you're going to be able to grab even the most corrupt cop
Even the most corrupt
Take them to the police station and have all the other cops be like
Thank you we didn't have the courage to do it ourselves I think
Even if you have a roving band of good guy
It's going to cause trouble
What if we ever had a rope
Roving bands are usually
Like there's a lot of historical precedent
Call Iran
Never one I wanted to tell you to your listeners that I watched I've listened to you for over 3 years
I have read probably 50 books as a result of listening to you
I can tell your listeners out there that Infowars
Is an extremely credible organization in the fact that you do things on such an evidence-based
Approaching the news and stuff I totally agree with I'm an attorney
So I take that very seriously and I appreciate what you do I don't know if their cousin
Some questions about the
Beatbox
I've watched 50 movies
Probably
Your approach to the news you just proved everything
This is sad but that's the perception that outputs out by the audience
They accept
Yeah
You're the hero for Americana
Next caller
But maybe he's just saying bulshit
Able to record
BB in South Boston ABC owned and operated affiliate ABC
In one of their reporters a compass.
Said that
The head of FEMA
Craig Fugate
Call Mary
That's good for
FEMA director Craig on April 15th
Administrator of FEMA Richardson
Lessons Learned From the Boston Marathon
Switch was released
In their introduction to the report
Sereno says quote I was in Boston on that tragic day in April celebrated in my hometown
And I'm here now.
FEMA deputy director administrator
But also as a Bostonian and former paramedic
Patriots
He's from
Austin so he went home to celebrate
That makes sense
There's nothing in this report about Fugate also being in Boston
When the attack happened
I can find literally no indication that the actual director Craig Fugate wasn't Boston
The time
There is proof that the bombing was a FEMA false
Scholars just f****** up with a detailed
He's really just talking about Serena being there
Suspicious
Boston
Everybody knows that team officials
Do not have any private lives
As whatsoever they were grown from a lab until they don't have any
Any hometowns other than
I don't know where ever
Sad amphibious Izar
Right now there's no way
For a FEMA official bee
Anywhere in quarters where I assume they live in
You also like we have to assume that
You know I found this conspiracy
A Blog about Richard Serena being
Fugate was also there you'd have
Have to assume that that would be a part of the
Conspiracy theory
It's on this blog
Because you got somebody
You can't was there
So here in this next clip I think we have
What
Alex Gibbs
Close to a mission
Statement
Doing
Right now
It's f***** up
It's about controlling the narrative
End
All good and well in your mind when he's talking about
Patriotism
Control the narrative to drive traffic to a website
Pre-sales
But the narrative he's pushing
Is b*******
There's nothing behind any of
All the things about the pictures that he's found
There's an accurate explanation
Just about everything
There's nothing suspicious except for what he's imagine
He's not pushing
A journal
Narrative
He's not pushing an investigation narrative
He's pushing his fantasy
He's pushing his
Perception
His
Storyline
He's come up with validate
The idea that the federal government is
Is evil enough
Crosswhite gun-owning Patriots
This always doing for him
Is evil
It's propaganda it's misleading
Is it man there's just
Flaw within our brain that is
Not going to be
Like it it's like these guys
Spin fix
Convince
A large enough people that
To be Danger
Herzl
Dangerous
I think monsters I think a lot of it comes down to very unique.
There are not many people who could put
Perform on the level that he
Their terms of like
He makes himself such a clown in order to be that like
Thing that seduces people in with the entertainment value
And then they keep watching
Vague references to things never explained
Never actually
No documents are approved
Is enough to be
In the aftermath of the bombing
He's able to use real-world events
And incorporate them really quickly
Into proving the narratives that he's laying out
Like if you were list
Link to all this you were
Maybe thinks Alex is inert
Listening
Like a lot of your suspicions
My Google doesn't know what he's talking
Is he interaction with the real world in a way
Vicky's presenting
Reinforcing his world
But actually doesn't
That's part of his
Other people can't do that
Like I just don't have those skills
Contemporaries
Maybe not but I mean there's always one of these
Like these guys are as like every
Seems like every generation
Has their own one of these
Can a permutation sir
So it's it's just like
Continues on this
Vicious cycle of
Bulshit
Disseminated by two people
We've by enough
To turn
Bulshit into something that is real in
And
It's
I don't know what to tell you
It turns out
That
You know how your IQ your intelligence quotient
Don't people have this
That you can actually will your IQ to rise
Call
Praise God
You just got up
Slug
So you guys raise your IQ do you want to just
Focus
It works you can also accept Jesus Christ into your heart
Ray's BBQ
Is your IQ absolutely
You know what I can
Kiwis or how to
Measure it
No
But I imagine he
Probably doesn't think much of his audience
A lot of Ember probably pretty
To be smarter
So appeal to that idea
So my IQ
Is that whatever I find Alex lying about something
I've given myself a little point
About to rise by 1
TJ
When is the show incredibly obvious
Anybody
Alex
According to the after-action report of the Boston Marathon
Did partnership by all manner of Massachusetts law enforcement in public
Thanks for not being
79 report in the section titled cook areas needing Improvement
They discussed security limitation
The area surrounding the Finish Line in Boston in the starting line in Hopkinton
Risk than other public viewing areas
A screen for the presence of contaminants at
Devices several times during the day
Interpret rule by law enforcement personnel
However these areas are open to
To the public
Are heavily populated and no screening of persons or baggage is
Conducted
The report itself wrestles with how security protocols could be put in place that wouldn't complete
Destroy the marathon
Because the Boston Marathon is a large public family event
There needs to be an appropriate balance
Security protocols
Ultimately
Some suggestions like prohibiting bags in certain places
Or increased police presence
But it stresses a second
Quote
These protocols should not be so intrusive at 2
To change the feeling of the
Alex is just making up the idea that all bags are screen
In order to read
Horses
Conspiracy
There's someone had a bomb in a backpack there
The cops would have
After no
And have to let them in with
This is absolutely not true
He is lying to as he has put it
Control the narrative
That's all this is
How long is
26.2 MI
Yeah it's okay
Alarm
Even then
If your
Talking about Target
Did near the Finish
You can walk
Such fun
It's just like
TSA worth
Even their report at least
A balance between
Giant dumb over-reaction
Theater in order to
Yorkshire Oliver
Watch them
Alex's recognized
Can go with the information that he has available to him
Like all Vicky
Respond so far the staring at random photos
4chan
He's gotten about as much mileage is
So what do you need to be audience to do
Is go find local footage
And come up with things
For him to talk about
Probably
Define
Defeat the enemy by finding
Maybe bad reporting
In the immediate aftermath
Fake people
Reporting things capriciously
Approve my up one
Literally all he's doing cartoons together
Make me look right all the time
Please
F***** up
No that's just not okay
That's like Barnes allowing people to vote
Do you like
There's just something very wrong
Center for legal
It might not be not sure
It's at least in Africa
And that is he turns over the show did David Knight host for a while
And Alex said he knows that the press conference
Coming up
Is that a little
Play some jazz
More phone calls
And in a press conference with Obama in an hour and a half
The new maps already discredited
Come out with
It's so fun
He doesn't even
He doesn't even need to talk about whether or not
His pets for the right ones
Doesn't matter
Here are their New Path
Normally you know what I would do is David Knight Jakari Jackson
But the press conference is coming up while the show is still going to be
Be going
And I know because I live in 2019 conference
Crucially important piece
Of this
And I needed reaction would be
And so I decided to keep listening
While David Knighton Jakari Jackson house
And someone that's very interesting is that Alex
Doesn't really leave the studio honestly think that he might be
Like it might be a 2030
Team drunk out
Because he cannot stop barging into the studio
Is interrupting that while they're trying to do their show
Becky rise
And I was just yelling in the
Studio
Ottoman
No you're not
He's not getting out of there either I love how we leave these
Piles of vitamin
Mad
She's so they because they're not great
At this point
David Knight Jakari Jackson are not
Super gummy David nightstand evergood in before
Do you ever got too much exposure on the actual Alex
But they're not good there
And one thing I will say to their credit
Along with the callers
Technicolor
The collar will say something for like 2 minutes
Analysis
Alright make a point
Will say something and then next caller like it's actually how a call-in show is supposed to go
Unfortunately
They're still Infowars caller
So they're still
Very stupid
Also I wanted to let everybody know that you know
You better understand
Alex Jones doesn't just pull all the stuff from his rear end I mean he gives you the tools
To give you all the evidence you need
A lot of these are all these other media sources they don't do that they don't give you the store
Police are arguing that
No Alex has a shell he's a
He's a misinformation
You just need to look into it and I just want to say I appreciate
And I love you guys
So stupid
Even in 2013 every f****** word is hyperlink to a source
If you go to if you read any article on Guardian
Hyperlink to the source that proves the reason the word Charlotte
Bulshit
Absolutely not true
But this next caller
Is stupid in a way that I actually find
Repulsive
I was calling about the guy you have a picture of its carrying that the radiation detector
Yeah he went on Wolf Blitzer and his name is dr. David King
But fear The Situation Room for yesterday about 6:35 Eastern Time
He was on there with him
And I eat claims that he left the race before the explosion
Situation
So
As always
Alex's callers or Ashoka
Case of stupidity
Alex has trained his audience to trust their guts
Just make connections between any
So when they call in
That's all they operate on
It's tremendously dangerous
Alex doesn't really have a heist
Standard for what information
He'll just repeat
But you've seen these things
Snowball
In this case
This caller is completely wrong
Dr. David King was a person who was on Wolf Blitzer
But he's not the person in Alex's photo
Nor does anybody else
Who has any interaction with Infowars
The story is callers trying to pitch
Is a disgrace
To dr. King
He should be ashamed of
For saying something like this
A nationally syndicated show with literally no Eva
King's wife was an avid Runner
And she previously ran in the Boston Marathon
What gear do you want along to watch
Finish Line
He saw the looks of accomplishment in people's faces
So why did he just loved it
They look like they belong on a weedeater
Every last one
So he decided to do it himself
Feeling
Marathon
And finished about an hour before the bomb
Light off
He lingered while to watch other Runners complete their racing
MCD excitement in
Exuberance in their face
How many left
On his way home news broke about the bonds and he immediately headed for Massachusetts General Hospital
He did that because he's a trauma search
This man has just finished running a marathon and he selflessly went immediately to try and help victims of the attack
I don't know everything about dr. David King but his actions in the aftermath of the Boston bombing of the sorts of things you could easily described is
Acts of every man hero is
When he could have easily just rationalize going home to shower or saying
I literally just ran a marathon other doctors someone else will help
This caller is randomly decided that he's the person in one of Alex's
Does pictures because of a slight physical similarity
King story of heading right
Because the photos
You there at the scene of the bombs
F*** this caller
Just a repeat the claim without looking
Without even knowing what they're doing
They're trying to turn euro into a villain
The person of their Noble
All the name of making their conspiracy sound more plausible
This is
Basketball Behavior
And I cannot stress that enough
All of these people should be deeply ashamed
Themselves his collar should still feel bad about this to this day
And yet they never will
For them
Doesn't feature the feature film is always turning
The people who exercise
Empathy
Initiative
Villain
Because what they are is people who
And don't
You don't like the way they treated
Story of shahrazad
Dad
And all of his Acts
Heroism
And then and then you see what they're doing to him
That's part of the goal
Yeah people are Heroes that you want to follow those well it's it's
Gyros
Narrative writing
Control the narrative antihero is heroes are bad for
To the narrative
So I just really f******
It does it drives me up a wall
Like David King date exactly what you would
Applaud
Someone doing
Award for
And here he's being painted as
A conspirator in a plot
To bomb
Civilian
Another stupid caller calls
My cousin just called me less than an hour ago there has been a bomb threat at Cal State Los Angeles
Cal State Los Angeles can we get on that guy quiz
They are evacuating the school
Call me to tell me that they are closing
I want to take that totally fair this caller isn't as stupid as all the others
Because that is a real thing
Allstate on April 18th
It was almost certainly the result of a
Prank call phoning in a fake bomb threat
Would you like something
What's Administration
Ignore
You know what Jordan
Some people probably don't want to stay
Think about is the Thera
F*** ton of people who call in bomb threats to
Schools
The Educators school safety Network do study on the phenomenon
It's really scary to think about
Obviously almost always a fake threat
But it's still such a horrible sort of prank for a person to pull
And to imagine that so many people choose to do it makes
Me feel real bad
About Humanity
He found it in the 2015 20
16 School
Their work 12:00
67 bomb threats made to US schools
There were 206
Since January 2016 alone
Which comes out to about
School day
That's a reality that school administrators around the country just have to live with it
Deal with
We end up hearing about almost none of these
Refilling a slot in Lake local news program
Is Cason Cal State is only something that because it happened after the Boston
The people are eating up any kind of bomb related to
Wondering if there's a connection
Had the suspect made it all the way across the country
My heart goes out to the students at Cal State that had to go through this
Obviously is not
Something you want to have
After experience
But the story being introduced into Alex's show can only do harm
There's no reason for this
He brought up
This is never happened in all four years I've been here
Great dude still relevant
I also feel a little bit bad about calling him stupid college kid
The real world
Is robust
Developing
And I understand that the outsized important
4 years to a college
Compared to somebody who is
If you are in college
And you have been there for 4 years
You should at least have learned by now that for years is not that big of a mess
It also is still stupid
So
There's no dumb f*** color
Yes sir I just have one question about Boston
If we had all these police when they're hungry
Oh no
I don't know cuz we've heard the reports.
Was in the Army I believe he's a job in the Army and he was
His brother-in-law before the bombs went off so
I know that he's asking a question to David Knight
But I think I might be better equipped to field it
Generally speaking if practice a journalist
Not the name all the people who were injured in the situation like this to protect their privacy
A number of folks made the choice to be identified
I would assume that they would
The choice to discuss their injuries
That's likely to Santa could possibly feel like an attempt to make the
The story about themselves
Maybe
Police officers would be more likely to not want that kind
I don't know
It's very difficult to trace down the identities of all the
I think that's a good thing
Leave these people to f*** alone they've been through enough
All that being said I can still tell displaying mouth collar that he's a f****** idiot
A USA Today story from April 15th
The day of the bombing
Literally says
Bloody Spectators were treated to a medical tent for runners
At least one police officer was her
So there we go we got it in your cop buddy
Now what does the bombing somehow make your paranoid delusions of the globalist pulled other agent
Would get her go away
Of course it doesn't
These aren't sincere
Question
Their conspiracy bulshit pretending to be
Curiosity
This whole doesn't want to know if any cops got injured
He wants to inject the idea that none work to reinforce the idea that there was
The false flag
That's why Jakari immediately start to talk about radu's brother
Because that's the Infowars
Meanwhile at least one cup
It was reported three days prior to them being on Eric here
And approve s*** about Rodgers brother
You might actually pentahydrate before all we know
This all amounts to nothing
Even if
Shikari or David
New
Fitness USA Today article exist
It says one cop was injured
It's in their best interest
Did not know that
Don't ask questions you don't want to actually know the answer
Is advantageous
Evan in Fort Worth
Could you have read this article displaying math idiot calls in and he's like
Yeah actually was reported there was a cop
Where do you go visit it's a propaganda
Journalist
Is disqualified
I suppose maybe you like
Short fiction writer
Better Suited
New-yorker byline
IFix
Alex barges into the studio again cuz he wants to laugh about how the
Conference
Is coming up
We will provide you with accurate information as it becomes available
Information
The press conference
Galaxy very excited
Live coverage
I do think
He's probably drunk
Colors now
You're so stupid a scholar
Just quick question I don't know if you guys have
YouTube
Charlie Chaplin
I'm sorry I can't hear you can you
LPS
Charlie Charlie Chaplin
I don't know if you guys
Watch this video on YouTube
Message to humanity
Are you
Or is Justin Avenue
Original
Message to humanity and it
What's the video about
Talking about
Dictator
3 minute 30 second clip
That's
Insane it's literally
Pulling a quote a little clip from Charlie Chaplin
Charlie Chaplin
The dictator dictator
But just callers informed about
You've already deduced is just a little clip from Charlie Chaplin's Great Dictator
The f****** movie came out
It also was nominated for four Oscars
That video gets passed around a lot and there's no reason for let's
People forget
Clip comes from a full-length
Movie
And that the speech being given its at the character is a Jewish man pretending
To be a character who's clearly
It's not Hitler
It is not subtle.
Actually the character of Hitler
Is that right
Anyway
Is one of the most enduring pieces
Comedic satire of fascism in authoritarian rulers
Released in the f****** middle of World War II
And it's pretty amazing that needed the car your day would really seem to read
About it's also pretty available this caller doesn't know who
Unclear about whether or not he was watching something
These colors are so f******
Stupid I know I know
I don't want to be
Kid
For not knowing that
I get that but that's like it's it's like dragon on people
McCartney guys going to be famous now because of Kanye or something like that
Your mom
You're mocking a Lac
Of Interest
This person is
Charlie Chaplin
Which he saw on the internet
Yes finding out who Charlie Chaplin
Is one click away.
Hey y'all heard of Charlie Chaplin
Call Infowars about it
That is worth Market that impulse is worth I know I want to be I want to be kind
I'm running Santa
Yeah
Also when I sit back and I can kind of understand how like the guardian David
Were people to work for a fascist cleaning propaganda Outlet Explorer
Fascism satire
Another
Stupid caller
Spider-Man
Calling in to make sure people were informed of the act of 1871
States into a corporation
Two constitutions
The organic Constitution
Has the heart
The act of 1871
Yes sir
Evans Scholars is stupid
Steven
I really don't have time to get into the ins-and-outs of this
Capitalize letters
That's soda bottle shaped
I honestly don't even care about this like if you look into it at all you just end up on dumb f*** blogs and Messi
Message boards of people talk about how sneaky the Rothschilds are
Deactivate 1871 just created the District of Columbia
They didn't create a new car
The tuition for the US in fact the District of Columbia was created the way it was specifically because of Article 1 Section 8
Constitution
And by that I mean the real
Katusha
Which is what this fiery is off
Sucks
It makes so much sense
Sovereign citizen
Are both the dumbest
And most vile
Like those two half
Venn diagram
So we get to the press conference
Pretty short
Images
It was not meant to be a half hour after I already
And so here is the immediate response
From David and scary Jack
Right after the press conference
The FBI agency
These are the only images that you need to focus on these two guys out of everybody in the crowd
I didn't point it out we have other images on infowars.com Duran images on other sites that may not be on infowars.com
Included in the
In the in the bombing
What do you say
He's not talk about me you talk about that
Listen to that Prescott
I could already tell how he's going to land
From like a spin perspective
Richard Delores of the Boston FBI
Pretty sure I'm still mispronounce
But maybe less so than what I thought it was Jeff laureus
Anyway you takes the podium in
Explain conductor the very intense investigation that are confident
Pictures of the correct stuff
Photographic evidence of one suspect place in his backpack
Precise location
Some of the site of the second
Explosions and other footage of the two suspects
Text walking together
And you know obviously they wouldn't have released pictures because
That would have
If they didn't know
Pretty certainly
In his prepared remarks he asked for the Public's help in identifying 22 people in these picture
But also says that other
Our pictures people are circulating are not relevant
And focusing on them doesn't help them get to the bottom
I strongly suspect
Did the internet
As much as it was a polite f*** you to the New York Post
For the cover image with two incorrect
But I knew as soon as it came out of his mouth with the real if it's been was going to be that the man doesn't want you looking
Kathy's forbidden images
I tell you the true story
And I almost
Gas
When Tampa dondi
Infowars having other pictures
In the background
At that Prescott
He was there yelling BFDI press conference
I should have realized
You know I really should have
He could be in that boat forgot that you was in Boston of course
I'm completely immersed in this stuff even for me
Interacting with
Interfering with the really important
Real world MoMA
You know it's it's one thing for Alex to manipulate and lie to everyone about highly emotional and sensitive
But I was thinking about this moment
And What official Infowars employee
Disruptive Federal
It was an impotent
It's not like there's really anything
It gets to be a public nuisance
And he's hoping to derail the FBI's investigation into the
He could pretend like he's doing it because he knows the real truth about the case
Tension is the same
His efforts are explicitly directed at creating publicity stunt
To get attention off the real stuff
And that's fun
Act up
I don't know that the crime but it feels like
Borders on obstruction
I don't know how much
Yeah
They would have to know that they weren't
Ethereal
Which
They do so
I think it is
I don't I don't I don't know
It just say when you look into that prison
This action
A lot worse
Studio
And
Yelp
And their cover-up
I imagine he
He tears his shirt open and
Might as well
All right now
Weave
Courthouse
They are in disarray right now
That is the good news
Thank you Alex
Yeah yeah
All right there you go Alex Jones 7 p.m. central Infowars Nightly News
Alex reneges on that that booking a little bit later tonight
Little bit later he barges back in
Questioning
Okay Adam
Play right there at
Definitely hurt him
Yep
Wow
This is up
What's going on
Wow I need all of you do my work for me
She's crazy big thing is
At the Prescott
Okay dance do you start asking your questions
Safely out of Austin
Yeah he's like
Reporting like he's in Africa
And not just at a very calm
Prescott only intensity
Obviously
I don't think anyone
Cares
About his bulge
Not like we have these other pictures at infowars.com that's what he was yelling during his question
I don't think they care
Like I don't think people are looking at these pictures of you like speculating
They care about the tip line
About the actual investigation that they're carrying out and they know that
Like
If people are trying to give them tips about the CST guys
Amwaste
F****** time
And you're not
A distraction but if you know who these two suspects are we need your help with that
We aren't we haven't identified them
I think that very easily taking that
I misrepresented as
The media and the FBI in the
The DHHS
I don't care
Leave them alone about that
Yeah it is
It is one of those
Situations where
Those press conferences in all the f******
It's like we talked about the name
Fourchette
That the UN
And all that stuff
They need a consultant to be like
Here's the language
But if you use this
They're going to Twisted
Do you like huh here's what you want to say
Alright
The other photograph
Alright I understand why you would want to put it that way because I hear words
And they make sense
Right but what you need to say is
We would like tips
Right Use the negative reinforcement
Have fun
With your piddly vulture
Dismissive and we would love that but hey
What are you go read articles from days ago explaining who those dudes are so suspicious
Always arguing to have a certain level of professionalism in
I understand that
I'm talking about maybe would be fun to see in a movie as opposed to what would function in the real world
Obviously.
I'm so proud Auntie here now it's gets into talking about how he just
Proof
Alex
Suggest
Dangerous
Play Novak
Alright
He's trying to get people to go to Boston to disrupt in her ass p
This is exactly the
Sort of about
For Sandy Hooks
And you see it's very clearly in his repertoire of action
Needs to converge on Boston in
Defeat the terrorists
Goddamn tattoo that backfiring
Can people taking him
Literally and Denver down to getting wrecked
Never works for him
Alex is celebrating like a returning hero glad I hired you
Alex
Obviously
He's probably already dead
They don't want the white redneck
Executed
Cam
Oh my God
They didn't answer so scared of him
I think their disgust
I think it's more like
Yelling stupid s*** you being super disruptive
I don't know how you react to that in a professional manner
Like they're acting like he's gay
Ulcer feel like
Thickened with someone is acting
Everybody was engaged with the real world understands that there's a tragedy and there's people on the loose
That these people are working really hard
To try and fight
Now you're someone
Just making a show out of
It's disgusting
Interested
The community
Quite frankly
Dammit that's
That's such a
Good just
Installation of Art
Back to Tampa.
They finished talking to him and then they realize that you still on the line
Back to him
And here is where we get a cameo
Expect
Cameo
From someone
Richard Belzer
Hear me I can hear him
That was Kelly that was Elvis's what divorce
You can kind of hear it in her voice
She does not happy at all
I do not know what's going on and that was f***** up
So
Probably time to calm down is b*******
Yes so they accidentally clicked over to the wrong line so she was talking to Alex on the work phone
Yeah they clicked over that's the only way that could have happened
I don't know what does not sound happy
Be there
That's the only time I've ever heard her on the show
Alex's wife
You're on the wrong line
It doesn't even sound that like
Annoyed
Yeah well that's possible tone of
There is a ton of a bit like this means Alex put me on f****** hold
Doesn't feel good
Nope
Continue encouraging people to go to Boston
At this point
Very celebratory about
Particular thing
Go to Boston right now if you're listening
People questions
We broke the record
Ignore
Hey down those are civil last 14 members that are very easily explain the FBI knows who they are
They're not ignoring the real suspects you're
Just full of s***
Alex is recognizing
How f****** lucrative this is
And what he's doing is maybe not illegal why don't we do this more
Crazy
Then he's expressing about a car traffic
The servers are smoke
Oh my God it's all happening
Yeah I think you should also I've also should have added in
She's talking to a clearly drunk
Alex as most likely very very likely
Describe this next clip itself parody
Because it begins
With David and Jacari
Trying to express Houston
The interests of Infowars
Alex immediately invalidates
We are about
World
Wow
Down
David Knight says we are more interested in truth been position immediately out of artisan bread
That's too
It's cheesy
Does Christ that's too bad
Go to Kohl's
Some listeners take
On what the Press
You know what they're feeling about it
And his first guy
And also wanted to say that you know
Play the song news conference was about one thing it wasn't
This was a direct shot at Alex Jones Infowars
Mention Infowars daily shot him down
Any other photos why because yesterday
Everything else had out about the photos of the field xcetera
I really believe that's the main reason they put this out
Yeah this whole press conference really wasn't about getting the suspects photos
This is parasitic levels of Narcissus
Like it's crazy
These people are narcissistic
Imagining that this entire city all the FBI
That is such a way to inflate your own
Turn Your Wagon to somebody
Like that stuff
Narcissism by proxy
Stupid ass
BFDI
What are you doing
I try to kill me that my eyes
We can solve this is that control the narrative somebody lock that man inside his house and
He probably doesn't get out that much
Alex
Barges into
Studio
Because
He is going to try and Bully Lee Ann McAdoo into coming on air
Because Leanne
Has Crack the Case
And figure it out why
These two
The photos of the suspect
Can't be the real suspect
She's
The Kaylee and Scott
Alright
Gray black backpack
I mean
Did she get a round of applause
Briefly do
Now-you-see-it-now-you-don't
This is
Welcome aboard
Here is only one picture that was made public of an exploded
Darker most likely Black Backpack
When the FBI released images of the suspects who we would soon come to Noah's tamerlan and dzhokhar Tsarnaev
Appeared
Possibly Gray
At no point it's been established
Outdoor hit list of the brothers were carrying identical bags
This Photograph back easily have been 21 tamerlan
Miscarrying
There's literally no contract
But because in Forza so insisted on coming up coming out with
Anything can be used to plant doubt
What is worth report
Beyond that one
Still photograph of a post-explosion backpack is an odd enough to conduct a forensic
Investigation
Alex's crew have no idea what effect the explosion could have had on the color of the backpack
Definitely think
Could've turned a grey backpack
Black
Justice
This isn't the behavior journalist
This is more what you do
Expect to hear from
Idiot smoking weed
Tregen if you're okay
Slightly impaired but utterly without Subs
Poor firstshowing Leanne
Really sucks that your first appearance on the show was starting half-cooked bulshit to help Alex profit off of lying about a national trash
Unlike these other people in the show
I know what LeeAnn was doing before she joined infowar
I'm certain that this is just a
Gig for her
I know that used to be a new-age hippie
Connect with source
Is the Mayan calendar ended in 2012
Which is shockingly close to when she won Alex's find a reporter contacts
I know that she'd entered another TV host in contest
The CW Austin star in 2011
And she been on a TV show prior to that called The Last Resort
I'm willing to believe that you may not have known what you was getting into when she started it
4 worst but if you're a Bohemian free
Free spirit out there practicing
Sentara one day
And not immediately when you see Alex behaving
Hornier since the bombing
I guess all I can say is I fucken hope that job paid super well
Because you're doing this
And you are you don't believe this
This is an act
I feel bad
I feel bad.
Maybe not for her later
Tear
On April 23rd
I mean I have for you by like
And I know that Alex is forcing her on Aaron she'd rather not
B
Still go f*** yourself
Yeah I remember my family had a blue minivan
And then we left
We came back there was
Just pile of
And so we assume that the minivan
Install
The definitely was
Inspire make sense
Because our minivan with blue
It was a blue minivan it was it a gray one made of Ash
Right
It makes sense
And I would feel just as bad about
Or mad
And directed this way
Like any of these people if I knew like let's say if I knew that right before Rob do
Joined Infowars
He was out there writing about Crystal
A left-wing active
Something like that
These people
Pryor live
Insisted like you are acting
You're doing this
You're doing
And spreading this property
I'm not sure which is worse
You know like actually believing it or doing it for a check
I think doing it for a check is less
Acceptable to me
Yeah yeah
Krystal's in Terre Haute
Not doing it for a check
That's no good
I don't know
I'm just
Absolutely
Studio
He was trying to spend
Conspiracy
Certainly
And so they get back to him and he's still trying
To spend this conspiracy
Address.
Thought you'd like to know that
I'm sorry could you
This is bulshit
Text unreal or whatever
What is a Coach Dave show
So Alex is full of this
This narcissism
About all of these
Cscope to Media
He thinks that even the release of the FBI pictures of
Vivica Fox
Our evidence
He's
He's being profited handsomely for it
Way more attention
And that's probably bad
On the night of April 18th tamerlan and dzhokhar Tsarnaev realize that they had been
As soon as the FBI release pictures of them
Yeah that's
They weren't getting any suspicion thrown their way online
From all of these blogs we're researching in
Finding suspect
The authorities have been tight-lipped about the leaves they were pursuing
If you were that cute might get the sense
You gotten away with it
That's pretty much what they thought
They gone back to their normal lives
Thought maybe we pulled this off
And then
That press conference happened
It all got disrupted
And they pant
The FBI press conference was at about 5
And at 10:31 p.m. the brothers approached the vehicle of an MIT police officer
Sean Collier
Do they vent
Most likely because they only had one gun
And there were two of them
2016 SUV in
The driver of that car managed to escape
Called 911 at 12:19 a.m.
He goes on to tell the police that the two men carjacked in Marathon
And that his car was equipped
GPS
So the police turned up the GPS
I began to track
1241 the police located the SUV in water
Along with the Sudan
I was being driven by the two brothers
And it's called a
The reporting officer is told not to approach until more units arrived so he follows
After a brief Drive the driver of the SUV gets out
And approaches the police car fire in a guy
At approximately the same time the police supervisors
And someone else
Comes out of the sedan
There's a brief firefight
And it's 12:49 p.m. the man with a gun who turns out to be Timberline
Is tackled by a cop run over by his younger brother
Who's attempting
Timberlands put in an ambulance and taken to the hospital
Where he was pronounced dead at 1:06 a.m.
Despite attempts at
Resuscitation
The Joker got away
He'll be about a half-mile away
Inflight on foot
Tonight was absolute chaos
I was all set and done one suspect was dead along with Sean Collier the MIT officer
Additionally
Officer Dennis.
DJ Simmons
Suffered injuries in the Watertown firefight
They were going to take his life for your later in April
April 2014
He's officially recognized as
The fifth victim of the bombing
Boston remembers him as a hero he's all too often forgotten in the story
In particular was pretty upset Wahlberg movie Patriot
Even though there is a memorial Loop of the other victims of that attack
In the movie
It's hard not to see that being erased
Might also be partially because it's a Mark Wahlberg
The entire situation changed overnight
Now the surviving perpetrator knows with the police know who he is
Better looking
But he doesn't know if his brother is dead or if he's being interrogated
Now the police know that these suspects are absolutely willing to
The murder police
And one of them is on the loose and armed
At least it possibly would even more IDs
The city
Previously on edge with an absence of information
Now it's come to the crest
Confined itself with a whole lot of information
And it's f****** scary information
No one knows where show car
How does Alex respond to all
That's will learn on our next
Where we'll also get to learn a little bit more
It's going to be a gigantic
Alex
I can't even imagine what he's going to end up doing with
Really not looking for
If he's gone this crazy
With the situation we've had so far
Blenders
Firefight
I killed cop
One of the suspects
Is Dad
Overnight I just can't even imagine how you respond
Possible the 19th
Now this is going to
Yep so look forward to that
God
You know what it's just like
You just think
That's going to be the most
Yeah.
Is just new levels of
Terrible Behavior
On his Park
It's
It's a it's a
Spiral down the toilet bowl
Sanity that says
Even without
Even without records
Cuz obviously it's easy to look back
But even if
Even
It is unconscionable
What is.
Yeah it is
How many
People flock
Simple
From the dumbest
In order to assuage their
Dumb fear
Are there
Is Whatley
Tubidy
Just like that
F****** micro
Probably because it's a more interesting story
Al profit
Alex and his operation
It's really tragic to think about and
Please
You can extrapolate the end of
Like you see exactly how we're going
Pretend
Soon but
That is exactly how we're all going to die at all really helps make sense of his later to decorate
His desperation to be
Piscinas en
On the right side the winning team
Star appearances of destroying
It kind of perspective a lot of like
Yeah I noticed that but like
This is him
Almost making that turn of like
Finally
I'm actually right
Like this is that is like that consistent that insistence that they are not giving me
Credit for being right
That belief
Holyshit
Finally the pieces are in place for me to present myself as right
Well I mean
In that day I really do think he believes
I think it's
Possible I think it's an argument you can make
I'm Lessard
As someone who
Doesn't trust him at all
Spiders nest
Scary things
It's mysterious
You don't like Cormac McCarthy wrote
Alex Jones brain
It is something that is
It's hard to decipher
You know you don't really eat you think you understand what's going on but it may be something entirely different
I'm ready sent to say that he actually believes
If he wasn't getting a ton of traffic off this I think you could make that argument much
Celebrating all this traffic and recognizing like
That really makes it difficult for me to believe
You definitely beliefs
Cuz that's the ulterior motive
If we know he all
Absolute correct X
Alex
He's possessed by the
I know
Or it could just be a sub,
For the devil
Maybe anyway
Trump Twitter
Start fights
And also
Please go to
Cast Yule app
You use a review
Friends
I reside at 666 Boylston
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work