Air Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge B
Monica
Knowledge vype.com
Jordan Jordan
Have you ever
They were not necessarily but
Stick out 1
The old buddy make Burrows
Who was picked over Michael Jordan
The NBA draft I have got it in my head
Is it correct
So short
To my family
Itsfunneh
Eunos
Major topic
Hispanic architecture
Lot of history is Uno's a lot
As he was getting almost
Call Aziz
Questions right then there was a question about the book The Picture of Dorian Gray
Okay
Picture of Dorian Gray
Vindicated on that
Yeah that was a big
Picture
A lot about Oscar Wilde books
I know the name of one of them
Exactly
Present day
Cover a number of episodes but there's no real reason to
Which is last Friday's
Episode
I think he's hungover from the Trump rally
He's probably
Sipping a few wow
Didn't
Sleep or something I don't know use in a f*****-up space
A retelling of
Popular Baton Rouge
Brings me great joy
So first of all
You're now a policy wonk
Jon Snow age
True
Jungle full of John
Taylor thank you so much
Taylor
Nickolas
Next
What's your name
I'm a policy wonk
Hayden finally
Boingo Boingo
New York knickerbockers
We appreciate it very much
Got in touch with me
Canyons I wanted me to say thank you on Monday because your birthday was over the weekend
Completely fuk that up super distracted by
The bobbing
Me and Jordan were going to harmonize we're going to be happy birthday
Lalalala lalalala
Terrible idea o.
Jordan 12
Alright
Happy birthday to you
We have to take
Technological issues
On the show in the past
Computer glitches and what-have-you
And somebody noticed that
They were so beyond
Incredibles
Technological problems
Recognize
Show our appreciation
Synonyms
When there's only one nothing that we can do that is bestowed
Title
Technocrats Raptor princesses
Actually created their own title
A very special drop
For them so Christy
Thank you so much
You are now officially
The black dragon
Stupid
The black dragon Queen
Do not
Please do not
But thank you very much we appreciate your help.
It means a lot
To October
Riches
Episode that I'm super excited
It's weird
Kind of
Getting more mad with Trump
Joel skousen on
Or more regularly
Idiot
Eviction Trump is giving lip service
Communist
Weird extreme right-wingers
John Birch types
Intubate
Is too stupid to understand the geopolitical situation
That's skousen
Right
Get music if he was actually smart and do what to do
April 1st
I think that's
We see that Alex is Hedge
He's trying to have
A little bit of what he's doing
Accommodate possibility of
We here
And Alex's
Freestyle rhetoric
Relic
Control
Everything
So you got him here saying
Uno's
Yeah it does feel that way
Heir of light
He requested that if he's going to give us pizza. Trump
Possible
I think
Is interesting because I feel like a lot more Republicans are having their disillusionment with Trump
Moment the same way we did with Obama words
You were this thing and you're doing this
Vista
Universal
Is that you know the
Stuff like that qanon
Reality doesn't match up with
Three stories that I've been telling
Work this
Scam that I'm doing
I thought I thought
At least
Create an approximation
Reality
The stories that I'm telling right
Hammer it in
No I'm not getting the results that I
That I like
He's our hero
I just
Start with j
Really again
Some thoughts about
The first whistleblowers as whistleblowers a hug
You can smell
Oh that's why
You can smell the
For more explanation for what.
I just made the globalist
That's what he's trying
Not good
The transcripts
Aviato defense
Sing All We Are
Don't know what I do
But if you want of my failures as a Critic
Love how Alex
Says
I really find it disgusting
Is that is the career
He's done one good thing in his is broadcast
To do that
Mispronounce
It's up mispronouncing it's over for now
Jordan early on
Classic
Folktale
No
America
I think so
I think so it might have The Brothers Grimm history behind I don't know
Let this play Alex
This is where I started to think he might be hungover for long pauses
To figure out what to do everything
McGruff
Distance
Right
I think he starts by trying to
Tell the normal
Story of The Three Little Pigs
Atlantic gets into like maybe a sequel
Really figured out this whole racism problem
No it's just
The system looks
Facade
Talk about the country
Tualatin
The door
Gaslighter
Jenna Wolfe
Probably sounds
How to make babies
Mommy and a daddy
Abstract
Amazing
Willy's
Do wolves the wolves globalist
Cheerleader
Famous Libras
Also I mean I guess
You know did the way that you could extend this to the real world
Wells Fargo
Lesson of The Three Little Pigs
Talking about how the
Who has allowed
And feed it if they're babies
For allowing him to treat them like this
That's at the core of the pigs
For not being strong enough to stand up to her
Rihanna higher
Thinking he's a wolf
He says you know what
I really hate your guts.
I'm going to slowly Tear You Inside Out
Little Pigs
Eggs
Forza be over for the walls real quick
This would be going
Tuscaloosa
People think have any Elam Alex gets mad
When there's not enough men to stand up I guess it's true
Nero Wolfe
I just want all of you out there
Intersex
I love the idea that a child
That banana
Call The Wolf
It reminds me so much of a Patton Oswalt bit about being a
You're afraid he'll do Alice
In front of his daughter and Opie
Let me tell you the real story about
Now the green pieces
For you but
Bright
It's toasty
Traditional
This is stupid
Navel gazing
Also Alex is completely unhinged
For the story of The Three Little Pigs and a little bit from the movie American
In the movie Chris Kyle character gives a speech about how
The Sheep wolves and Sheepdogs
The normal people have no capacity for violence or
The people who can be hate others are the wolves
Are people who can be violent but love everyone are Sheepdogs
It's a reduction of people's alignments and how violence Works in society
That became very very popular
Particularly a gun advocate
Basically they use it as a way to frame their need for gun
It's so they can be sheep dogs that protect all the rest of the
Like the wolves
Bright little pixel feet at their baby
Because it's sort of tracks with
Theme of that whole retelling of The Three Little Pigs
But
That's a book
Called written in 2004 by Colonel David Grossman
And it's a complete pile pile of violence Justified
It's
That sounds right
Honestly what I was looking for this I was worried for Alex
As this episode is getting going
You sound completely f***** up
He's indicating the Trump isn't going to say about that
Of this folktale
Somewhat Trisha anybody who cares about him at all like
If he's acting like this
You got a you got to go
I don't know if it's
You're you're a lunatic
I really have a hard time believing that that is actually broadcast
That is so
How could you listen to that be like
Well this guy's okay
Yeah right
I understand everything good like
You make excuses like
Yeah lucky
Struggles out there but we got another boat it's a great job
You got to stop kidding yourself this is
The ships going to come in
Further downward
Anybody cared about him in his life they would step
You know this keeps going further down
Like all of a sudden it's six bucks
Never Letting you back on never happened
I just I don't know really check
Indicating
Like pretty regular breaks with reality
Or actually since and how many are just like him talkingshit
It's really hard to say he's a man who's living
You having it
Difficult time
Differentiating between reality
Illusions
I asked pretty well transmitted in this neck
Text clip he's talking about how people who
Politically disagree with them
Excited
Evil
As they become an empty vessel the demons just can jump into liking the maitre
I can't disprove that
Okay
So I think I would like a little bit more from him on why
I'm looking for
Here's what he has to say
BL
What is that
Is the devil
Spoiler
From the Devil
What
First time I saw it
Edward goes into jumpsuit
Jump jump
Presbyterian
What is the
What the f***
Like
He's talked about this sort of thing repeatedly it's not
Grocery stores around here
If he actually has experience go to a hospital
Eddie he's lying about it
Then what he's doing is normalizing
The experience might have if they're having a break with reality
He said no no it's real
What's a Euro listener who's list
I'm going to shower and maybe you're experiencing something like that you're having loose
Auditory or visual or whatever
Alex is like that's demons
Mission from another
Are you going to take me probably go get my meds checked out or I should go get help
You're going to be around me
I better do something
Normalize
Destructive
Sort of dangerous side effects
Set timer
Even if
Who Alex
Turns into proof of his
Conspiracies
Feel like these symptoms are proof of this
Even if they don't
Commit like violence
Keeping them
From getting the help
It's still hurting
But even that they don't act out against
Now determined to be demon
Sure it's still
Alex's
Severely hurting
And I don't know which of those I think is worth
Which option or just talking s***
Normalizes
Normalizes the right word
I think
Giselle
I think.
Yeah
Actually
Very serious
And if he's not
Give me three and a half
Because why are you pretending
10:40
F*** you need help
Episode
Yeah yeah
Rambling nonsense
Ridiculous ESO moments of flourish
Eating ass
That does get a license
In studying the Transmissions of the devil that I watch The Matrix and I was like I didn't know that was
Was real can I watch The Matrix elliptical
Matrix
Here's what happened
Check out a little while
So this clip sound
Economic
Ultra spiritual
Ashley Manor
Much much
100 ft tall
You're going to see
Suicide
People Transit
What about the millions of nuclear reactors melted down exploding huge War starting
Linsanity
You think you've seen something so far
We're living in the millisecond
In our
I served under General insanity
You know
Most reminds me of
Charles Manson
This is
Straight out of Charles Manson it does have a similar field
Providing underage girls I think that's the only difference
Right now I can
It's called leadership
Also uninspired and and
Lackadaisically delivered in LA
I guess I haven't listened to a ton of Charles Manson
Speeches
Realtor
That's one of the reasons why the present-day also isn't
Super
Compelling to me
Is like
I did see somebody who'd like
Someone should be helping
Everyone around him is negligee
For whatever reason
Fear of Vikings reaction
Terrifying
I am help like I imagined
Someone saying you need to go talk to somebody
But also a terrible
Are you telling me that I'm not man enough to vote
Go to work
People who care able to convince
Themselves just doing this for Ratings or whatever
I think I agree with you to like even if it's just pretend
That is an indication of
He's clearly wrestling wood
I don't know I just
He aspires to
A problem that isn't all that interesting to me that
Most of his narrative
Stuff that we could cover and discuss more interesting even have already
Racist
Everyone's the devil like
It leaves me searching for things like those folk tale Three Little Pigs
Like he's just phoning it in boring as s***
Three Little Pigs thing is so wild
I'm still struggling
To comprehend
When you brought it up again
Yeah but did that really happen
What what is also
How are you still going
You are rewriting it also like how he
Explain the stories
Yeah
Cuz they're at they're like really just basic
Their function
I wonder
I bet you have to drink if
The Venom the fangs of the cobra
For a little bit and then we realize that he forgot to turn off the ringer on
For every action there is an equal and opposite reaction
Cool just Rambles debate about that wow like
Complete nonsensical unhinged ridiculous
He's also
Forgetting to turn off his ringer before he starts
Now back to this
Like criticism of
At least
There's a story line through Alex's
Experience with drop
At least I
It turns out that Alex had some criticism
But it mostly comes
He's worried
He will summon
Literally
Summoned the demon
Without knowing how to control
The rest of us
Here we go
This is
Further Evidence
Haha
In his
Conception literally summon the demon
Craft
The case of Charles Dexter Ward about what you can't breathe
Whatever
I don't
Properly told the story of the
The three little picture I'll tell you that right now
Your criticism starts it comes from
Your criticism isn't coming from
A place you're just a lunatic
No I think I did read Nancy Pelosi Adams
To the articles of
Edina Realty
Copy high crime or misdemeanor
Keep track of
Let me be
Like tears
It took the my intellectual Curiosities
Much less
I get really excited.
Because there's
There's still much too
How does this work
Is very simplistic
Put out
Lines on what specific
Anime of seven
Athena I was thinking azrielle pillowtop
Classics Beelzebub of course
Little Darkness references
Alex
Even though you can't put down
Dumb bulshit
Which again
Kicked off Facebook
And then all they do is just broadcast
This also is after Alex
Complains about
Getting a app
Video of what he thinks about Alex Jones
Being kicked on Facebook
Who's Alex Jones
Alex very mad about that
Right side Broadcasting
Trump speech
Welbeck
Even though
So I assume that that's all they do
Have their own speeches on Facebook
There's a little bit right side Broadcasting
To conveniently leaving out of his characterization of them that would go a long way toward explaining why they might not be allowed on Facebook
In 2017 right side Broadcasting
Mostly known for two things
Salad
The first possibly recorded himself peeing in his own mouth
First. Video
Specific
Swallow
Disappointed that's not what I paid to write
The second thing is known for the series of videos they made their were purported to show that black men were violent
What is egregious examples this was a video where he claimed he was setting up a camera on a car that had Trump stickers on it
In a black neighborhood and Justine what happened to it
Group of young black man, they destroyed
That's just how black people
As you can see from this video the black community is very violent
Supporters
That video hit a million views with an H
Largely driven by traffic that he got from it being reposted Entourage
Unfortunately for Joey
Someone in the neighborhood where he was shooting this video caught some footage of Their Own
Namely footage of the black man waiting around kind of camera tripod delivered
The entire video
Design to justify Trump supporters victimization narrative
Braces
Nobody was taught Joey tried to make excuses
And he said quote I thought I could get away with it
This isn't even close to the Omni fake race-baiting video he's put out a complete piece of s***
And if right side Broadcasting
Consider hiring him in 2017
Which is after you get that car hope
Also side note Joey salads is currently running as a republican New York
11th District
Congressional
Key and everybody's house
It's not just area tuxedo
And it's not an isolated
They also hired Nick Fuentes
Imagine any Bo Nazi leaning
Position a person could hold all about
Of course he denies all those labels
Self is a guy who loves America
It's all about white people
Pizza terrible
The network was short because in August
But the Constitution doesn't apply to Muslims and immigrants
Globalist
Time to kill the globalist I don't want to go to business
I don't want to be more honest I want people to be arrested and deported or
That is a
Hot Tech I'm going to give him that
The network also ran shows hosted by Mike cernovich
Sure I forgot
Also I literally just went to their Facebook page and 270 3000
Those little verification verified
Bulshit work is
He's lying about them getting kicked off Facebook it's very publicly that it's right there
Have you ever heard the phrase hat on a
Yes it's that it's that that's for white 6
So Alex the talking about
Sure are we still doing
Yeah Play-Doh sets
Some stuff about how
Lgbtq
Peekyou
Have five
C3 status
The other part of it
Anyway Alex is mad about the sdlc
Beto's mouth
Mouthpiece
Global Shoes
How many lies by something Trump
That's not it
Control
Forgot trip form
It's the hairy guy Specter Gadget Uncle Fester
I thought it was
Christopher Lloyd
Couple movies
Got that
Essential misunderstanding that Alex has
Status withdrawal lay down with
He thinks the rules say the church's can't talk about politics or social issue
But that is not the rule
The amendment specifically about partisan political activity
Churches against abortion
They can be against abortion
They just can't use their Church to support a specific
Or attack a pro-abortion
Or replace candidate with
Measure or whatever
Use it for political
Advocacy
Strictly
Right that's the other thing
This isn't the rule that ever been enforced very strongly pretty much
Ever
I've been to a church where partisan politics have been engaged
Yep
Small instances of it or just kind of ignored by the IRS because they know that strict enforcement of this rule is way more trouble than
It's an important rule to be in place though so they can go after organizations
Exploit
Political machine
And that kind of thing it is important
It never enforcing it
In practice
Churches legitimately almost never get in trouble for Johnson
On May 4th 2017 Trump signed an executive order the Secretary of the Treasury really enforced by the
C3 rules
Which most experts agree is really just a symbolic Act
Pandering to his base
Even the ACLU said it quote had no discernible policy outcome
Of course after Trump sign the orders started running around bragging about getting rid of the Johnson Amendment
Even if you wanted to
Xeloda performative bulshit
It's real
Is it in that clip Alex
Which is dammit
State phrase
No I mean nothing
So
The wall
Search reality TV show
That's what we have is creating a narrative
Play Watchtower
Reality pedophilia
You did say that I remember
Sherwin
Until
So
I don't know why Alex would even say to that
Our church
Speak out against
The bestiality
What
Why
Even Up For Debate like in the political
Partisan politics
Independence for some reason
Bring bestiality back I don't know why it needs to come back
I don't know why it was there in the first
Sure
98% of a man every Pole
0%
Republic
98%
Scenario analysis
Dirs goes after church cuz there again
Imagine what that would look like in the real world
Distraction
Twitter
Would love that
Yeah
We talked about this or touch down a bit earlier
Zoos that sort of like
Disillusionment moment
The cloud
You see what you actually
These next couple of clips
Really get to the heart of that for Alec
Yeah
Tenuous connection
Things to do Lyon
As a recording
Exclusive
Lawyer $5,000 to consult
Unindicted Associates firm
Get more money than
I've probably made maybe in my life
No worries don't worry about
I find
Juliati
Some sort of
Weird
Court jester
Trot him out like a marionette
Kinds of weird things
And everybody's like
He's going to get you guys
Killed why are you still doing this until he makes me laugh
Most
To say something
Totally legal
Well you always is that legal lawful action
Isaac is like Alex.
Young says that all the time
You Alex
You're now saying everyone's tired of the line that I've been feeding that
And so now I think
It's time to Pivot
Did you start to see
The early signs
How much is
This plant is it grows right I have no f****** idea
Play
I care about the president
Don't want to hear
I want to see destatis frog-marched
Now that's not going to happen
Nobody knows that
Freeze him to be like I put it on the line
I want to see cam
What the president's Valic of Americano whatever the f***
Masculinity nonsense ideas I have you know what it didn't come through
It didn't happen
We got to save ourselves
Exactly how many icing
This is does Trump have up his dirty
I would say point
We're happy we're half to little over halfway.
That's that
You got to get up
Is the family show
So Alex Goes further down this road
Squatting
Sandwich shops
We need you
Dropped
Do not
Oh boy
Lockup solidify Power by
Taking out his political Rivals that Alex is determined or deep State operative so
That's good
Right that's healthy
Convince
Fantasies
It's really frustrating like that that whole like her up and all of that
Your view sold them on something that is
Not real
He's really only serve in the real world they only really serve
To help someone who wishes to solidify authoritarians our kuso
Executive Authority
Calling for Trump to lock up all of his imaginary deep state
Like
Cool by normalizing Rise of a tyrant
ND
Get out of it
But I guess
Emotional
No satisfaction of watching
Somebody that you've been told as evil get
Treated like that if you're okay
F*****-up be all the policy
Cease that actually come
Yes if you're someone on the ground absolutely
Maybe the idea that I'll get back on Facebook
If we're going to have to control
Facebook production
In order for me to go
Got it
Yeah I just want
So Alex
Most of the he's canceled as guest
Cancel this gift he's canceled Nick begich hosting the 4th hour
Lizzie wants to take
The calls
He wants calls from people who disagree with
If you listen to how you setting this up
It really strongly implies did you call in
And you disagree with him
And no one calls in to disagree with it because they're too afraid of having a reaction
I'll probably going to be dealt with as if I'm a demon called
Real
Always and say I'm the government-run corruptor on build exercise
Tara from you
Casino
Weather
Disqualifies anybody
Start
Call treat us.
Like telling you that is Supernatural
Is controlling them making them the targets of violence
Talk to me what's up
It's kind of just like a preamp
Never having the
What
So Alex is mad about gender pronouns
Wanted to do
Known on the street
Yeah
He's mad about the political correct
Missive
I don't know expected to
You treat people how they want to be
What about that
But the things
Uses as
Example of times
We've acquiesced
Do these sorts of things in the past
Indicate to me
Simbad
Subway
Alex
Edward was the slipper
Freak slowed
Because then what isn't that you want
Apparently illegal
The part that I born in
The client should be tax-exempt
Next thing you know when somebody says they want to be referred to as
You have to do it right
No trying to draw a parallel between
Authoritarian
Parallel to that
They took away the Clans tax
Exempt status
Church down the street
It's just against the war against the war they have their tax-exempt status taken away
Yeah it's not
It's not real
The client should have kept
Which is
Yeah
I mean
Free speech
And tax-exempt status
We have to respect
I guess
More of this deteriorating
Descending into like being mad about
GQ people in general not really
Noting the difference between people who are drag performers might be
Everybody
Right
Disgusting
This
Combine
Always so scared now they're ready for the sexual conversion
No
In video after
Evil flows through
Touch some rides sit on them close to the spider come to me my
Okay
The only reason is to demonstrate
You spell August
Second
It's because
He needed to do that in order to get into that headspace
Headspace
And it allows
To transition into like
Just a completely f***** up weird character
The it's not gross
An incredibly fake
The Voice
Coming out of this
He's now embodied these demons
Get out of it
I don't know
If I were Alex instead I think he now needs to play
Play the other roll
Hero-guy
Don't want to talk it in my life
Trying to
I feel like you saying that means you are
Authoritative
Put somewhere back in our instincts
Build-A-Bear
What cereal
And it's about pronouns
Exercise
Notices voice my back to normal there
Voices
Anyways back to the normal conversation we were having
I tried to look into greyback
Old greyback
The only thing I could find was a term for like one of the currency
Before we had like inside.
The Union Army
But I don't think that's Wings reference
Blue
Don't know
What
It's got to be some
Reference to a western
Don't know what
The case I mean lost
Doing impressions of demons and then impressions of who he wants to protect us from the demons
Just like a guy who's
Playing out
Just absurd One Man Show
It's a mentally unwell
So confused
I apologize
It is so
Utterly
Beyond Paradise
Nobody would be more Furious
Avene mist
Then
If you were to call him
Over and over and over again
It would drive me crazy
You know what
Repeat over and over again
Just so how is it that
That's good they're trying to attack me
Jersey f*** off
Yeah it is interesting
Incapable
He has to recognize and with that lunacy
Is the message
Also it gets geopolitical to he starts taking calls
And he ends up talking to
Who has a little bit of
A bone to pick about how a certain politician is being treated there
Tell me how come Canada election simulator
Later this month and
It's really incredible
Do we have a
Classical liberal
That's come onto the stage and Missy the same pattern happening
What is populist movement
It's a return to
No just the classical liberal roots
Yo
Talking about Maxim
Well I'll be the first but I do not know everything about political
It's because his party seems to have a bunch of neo-nazis and fascists in it
Alright well
Okay
Find Wilshire for the People's Party to file with the Canadian elections Folk
Registration
Attesting that they are members of this actual political party
What was Sean Walker
Who was formerly the head of the Neo-Nazi organization
You want to know why you wasn't
Federal charges of orchestrating attacks on
John White Citizens in Salt Lake City between the years 2002-2003
87 months in prison
250 names
Alright
Only two strikes
Then there was Justin else remember these soldiers of Odin
A finland-based white supremacist groups
Vigilantes
Quite a long time ago
Which I guess is technically still before you sign the petition is member The People's Party
But not by very much
No that's why
Now
I've decided to change
Four track
I don't care about your rules.
It's because he needed to find 250 party members sign a petition in a Superfecta
Subway supremacist
I feel like that is a bad sign
Can you turn to your left
You're right there a lot of
He's around
You stick around
Yeah you're a nut
That's really weird
These are classical liberal
Classical liberal
It's weird interest
And had him on the Rubin report
Who do I like fundraiser
Interesting
These
Big dogs over here
Very interested in
He also has
Party members
Create a
Global associate
Right wing
Nationalist
Classical liberal
Control the world it makes a Global Group
Madeline
Do well
Seems like a good idea
Alex
Feel like it's still time for bed
Shutdown
I'd like to start
Park Hill Tunnel
For Destruction
Is totally fine the idea of trump and his family behaving like
Chosen enemies globalist
You can have a kingdom
Going to me what could be more American than creating a dynasty of
Fascist leaders
Who have total political enemies
Address for that power
Logout political enemies Rivergate
Cancel
About absolute also
Theme to wish
To control
Media
Punish
People who report
I want
My dictatorship
I don't want
My imaginary enemies
A what
Will live under this
White tyranny
Multicultural
Revealing
Find with him
Yeah no
I'd like
Well then I'm taking my ball and going
Home
You think we're going to add malt
That's what it's supposed
To be about so I'm going to get rid of democracy
How do you like that
With the democracy
More present
To completely abandon those ideas about like Posse Comitatus
Let him run
The Damascus flip
Everything else before was pretend
Yep
Identity guy
Former
CIA guy who went on
MSNBC or whatever
Who spies are going to kill the president
He was obviously talking
Annabella Schmidt
Lights out
Go to examples of people actually being like
He's just making s*** up
Sure
Does it
Jealous supporters
And that's where the expression his name is mud
This goes back to dr. Samuel injuries after the assassination
But the jury is still out about whether or not he was in any way involved in crime
There's a pretty high chance of not knowing
It's unclear what he was doing
Regardless
His Name Is Mud is absolutely not
Lincoln was assassinated in eighteen
Trace the
Expression his name is mud
At least as far back as 1/8
23 book from Britain
Call Daddy
Canary of the turf
Which includes the line
Exclusionary rule
Spell differently
Mud a stupid swaddling fellow
The expression of a circle even predates
Public Storage
1823 long before the
Comparison
The pawn on it
Mud itself is
Linguistic
As well like everybody has been like that guy is like
I'm at the center.
I'm just saying it's not necessarily.
Sure but it wouldn't help with the mud situation
This version of the story that Alex is telling about the root of this idiom
Of course
Particular I remember the story that's told in the Book of Secrets
Find Cage's character Benjamin Franklin
Favorite very strong suspicion that that's where Alex got the story from National Treasure
It's a very good Nicholas
Performance
It's very good
I am a fan of the National Treasure movies
The first one
So many times
Is that
Might've worked at the theatre when it came out but I just thought it was so over-the-top and ridiculous
Dawn story
Nicolas Cage is awesome
Historical revision aspects
Nicolas Cage
Such a great line Book of Secrets wasn't nearly as
Delphine
The increase
Parts for a WhatsApp
And Harris was the first one
Still pissed
What would what would you
The plot for it
Clue to a treasure or something
Buried in Arlington Cemetery
In the place where presidents are buried so in order to get the clue he has to become the president and then faked his own death
Get buried in Arlington Cemetery to find the clue
I don't know
But it's me
So anyway
Pretty sure that that's where Alex
He gets everything from movies
This is absolutely not true
It is in that movie
That's where Phil Mudd being the great great great
Phil's pretty private
Available.
Tree or lineage
Still doesn't matter either way
Yeah you'll hear the clamp reported over and over again on message boards and tweets but there's no sourcing
For whatever
And even if it is who cares
Alex exactly zero.
Confederacy
Whether or not he was in on the plan
You know every
Jefferson Davis
He's got very little yachts
Strange feelings on that subject
The bottom line here is that Alex has one hundred percent wrong
Historical fiction movie
Four treasures
Did the Knights Templar hit around the world
He's further just making up any nose is Phil Mudd is related to Samuel B cuz they have
The same last name
This is the level of shipping
Everybody everybody
Sure
Bright but he uses this idea about film
In order to justify
He thinks
Gets to do now
Chocolate
How to change user
No
So we're starting to think about how we guard ourselves
About yourself for real
Parts
Brain
Everybody tries to keep
In the warehouse under
Under sheets
Are we around the f****** campfire right now
Scared of
Never actually did anything like that again
Don't know history
History
Alex
He thinks that
Okay with horses
Is him he is worth
Alex
Earlier like Alex saying that as long as he takes out the globalist
Great chest seems to be against literally everything you stand for
Do you need
All that you need
Still pay attention
The present
This verse
Some
Very
Ideas
God Hates a Coward
People have their way with your
God damn
And you're very genetic
Playing that song underneath that
Yeah it should be against the law
No
I'm going to give you a nightmarish
I hope scape speech with
Contacts entire world
He's talking about white
You talk about
Yep like that's
In terms of
Danger if he doesn't start using his bully pulpit
Declared national state of emergency
Liars and cheaters
NetSpend
Entirely his life
He's
CreateSpace and a show in and advocate for Congress
He's done such a poor job of teaching his audience
Anything about the reality of the
The Advocate
Everything that he talks about superficial
Stupid and So based on
That he has just a bunch of radicalize listeners
Pinkberry
And simultaneously
Congress
Two arrested political line
Where to go to
Secretary of
Whenever somebody has said we must
Destroy the Republic
To save the Republic
Is it historically donwell
I know that there is one
Great
Literary historical stores
George Lucas
Is George Lucas dead
Wendy's has this imperative
22 facts from your audio
You have failed you failed miserably
Lady
Do you
Have you
If you hate America
Really hates America
So it is exclave Alex said something this is the closest I've ever been about to talk about us
Stop
So I thought I thought
Don't know what that's about
But by the end of the episode he hasn't made it clear what this is about but I think it's a
Are coming out
I may be on Netflix
I don't know
That might have something to do with framing Alex for causing violent
Don't know he's very nice
Specific about it but I think that's what it said reference
Might be in production that might be frame
Far more sense than him talking about
What's a very real
So
Unfortunately it got my heart
Guns are drawn
But alas
Dog collar
This is actually happening
So you got the Great Awakening language
I think you did
I might have my Enclave
To the key phrase
Cuz they've been in the concubines or whatever
Roosevelt big
Common Man
I think there could be like a Rico
Knew that he has
We sold our country
The Federal Reserve
Hobart
Absolutely
Portland
You said that
I don't think you use that high of a number right
Now these things
Keep talking about it and never come
So Alex
Because it's a no
Episode of the show
Day of the week
It doesn't stop him from talking about
Please prepare to
Can you turn your ringer off
420 Club
He in the fourth hour at this point this is the fourth hour of his show and he's going to get to the news
Maybe I'll show you haven't done any of the work I meant to
Do on my own ever identified without
Him be like
I'm going to go do the thing that seems hard
Alex
Clips of Trump's rally the night before
Trump saying if
If Hillary would want China would be number one in the world right now
Baby the greatest
Sure and Alex talked about what the plan
So
Great
Saudi Arabia in the world
And you'd still be lowered
Saudi Arabia
Exports of crude oil have definitely if you're looking for someone
While President Obama
That bad
Responsive
We're OPEC countries placed an embargo on oil sales
Indian Kippur War
The price of oil
Royal
That wasn't vulnerable to those sorts of action
End. The export ban was put into place
Much to the Chagrin of oil companies
They just wanted to sell their oil for the highest
Prophet
And because of that
Jimmy Carter
Being an exporter of oil now a net exporter of oil
Not still buying tons of it
Important
It just means big oil companies are taking the oil refined domestically and sell some of it
Well we're also
You and I
We've still end up paying for
Imported oil
This is quite frankly
Unless you're making money off
Probably everything
Involved
Shity develop
Play some clips of having an argument at an abortion rally
Great
On the street interviews
Super important
Relevant
Hard-hitting news
Relativism
Riveting radio
Abortion route
So now playing clip Alex. Editorializing
Is not attract
Social worker
Good money
So I just decided she's a social worker
Where is Ike I don't know she is I don't know she's not I don't really care
But he says find out who she is
He's asking his audience the docs
This woman
So
Caution you Alex
Doing any
Anything like that
It just seems like your
You can't even help you
Yourself
These protists station
He's making about the accusations
There's a million examples of you doing exactly the behavior last Friday
This girl is a video
Discourse
God Barnes
So much
Shmoney
Just more advertising America
So Alex
Jumps from
Insulting the abortion rally
And then jumps over 2 videos
Of whites
Being attacked
Outside the Trump rally by Somali
Feel like that
Well
There's racist attacks going on around Trump rallies Jordan
It's time for all good men to come to the aid of the party
Successful when playing is Cliff
Really
Mostly the racial attacks.
So again just
Everywhere
Flash
He's real mad there
Why is it that every f****** time
Furious
You're right you know what it is
I
If I had to give a theory highlighted everything that knows how to do I think people
I think that he has a crew that is not nearly as smooth and you pretty
Causing hiccups
Pull the wrong clip
I can't prove it
But it would be exactly what you would see
Is Alex is working with
A thinned out staff
Which is exactly what I would have predicted after he doesn't must go sale
Yep or any of these other sales
Or is it
Competent people are going to leave
Ferb
Just had to leave my old job
What was my old job
You don't let's not talk about that
Okay so there is a
You would rather pretend
How to make
Has found
A new source of Revenue
I think that he's found a new sponsor
Because there is a saying and neutering your pet
No you're about to hear
Is
Paid program
I have a very strong sense
Cuz he's being paid to
Freespeechtv
To be able to talk
About
Eonline TV 40 boy
Call wow
Notably not you
Worst Harrys Razor at you have a hard-on a podcast
Seems like ad copy for ensure
Like that's
Classic
Turn off my lawn
Like you
Bad
Which brand himself a little date
Hold on to anybody who might be inclined
Come along with his new adventure
I don't know
Yeah no
Surprising
How
Obviously
It was like
I get here
Maybe they were trying to do that like
Content that goes in there and it's
Kind of like buzz
He's an old-fashioned
He's going to read
Commercial
In addition to that as a new source of Revenue
He also has the Everything Must Go sale on right now
Please remember we have to do everything
Christmas
Everything
Is 30 to 70% off
Appreciate
It's amazing
That's explicitly false advertising
But if you're advertising for you to 70% off everything at 30%
That's the misleading advertising
Nobody
For that violation is pretty small.
Which is parking
The show with a couple more calls
Trying to take pretty quick
Try to get the calls and realizes it on
And the first guy is
Absolutely
100%
Member of Christian
Hi Alex I really appreciate your appetite
Fraction today
Ancient American scripture clearly states that the son of the Living God
Jesus Christ of Nazareth is the God of this plan
The author. Constitution for the United States
He gave us all the tools necessary in the Constitution to restore the Republic
You know it look at those people need
I don't know if that's right. Siding with you on
Don't know I don't know what that answer awhile
Your knee-jerk reaction of like you got to re-educate people is what I do I know that that's not necessarily A
A good solution
But I don't know what the solution is
I'm opposed to your solution but I don't have a good one
Beyond that
You know you individually this would be able to be handled by
You're going down this path you believe the Bible is an ancient American scripture
We need to talk you'd hope
People support networks that are able to
To help with that
Just gave Florida
Play just give it to him
That's not an answer
I feel like that will lead a war against these Invaders
Can identity people
If they try and come down to Florida
One last call
Another guy
To promote Max
Russian here not sure if impeachment is inevitable but of the vein is 1736 worldwide
Freedom
Okay promoting
Liberal
Seize the new Wilder's or for bolsonaro
That is one hundred percent in favor
How can you
Canada's Trump in there
Going to be
I pushed on Alex
The show
Control the collars or anything but you got it
Is there is this much representation of the people who call into his show
Bitters
Message out about Bernier
Then that means something
They know that
He might be somebody that appeals to the Infowars audience
That lets you know ever
Infowars
Tumi
I got a red flag
Big red flag
Like I said earlier I wanted to try and cover more ground couple episodes
Mike Adams
Get out suck off
And then I turned on Mondays listening to it was very clear
Keith new stunt right
Responses
Spend more time doing another one of these
Like it's just
He's answered that sort of rarefied air
Jacob Wohl
I'm so went out for 2 hours today
Like I'm not listen
His other was about that
Meme Trump
Cutting off people's heads
Defense about that
The year old and we went out that doesn't really address the fact that
This was
It's just who cares I'm not going to descend to the level of bickering about
So I just
I heard that
I heard that and I was like
I don't
I don't care
I don't care about this Monday episode it's very it was very bad
Much more interesting
Completely sucked up
He talks a bunch of nonsense
Oh yeah
Like these real
You know it's fine
Callers advocating
Victor
Congress
And I just flies on the show
And educating the election of this
I guess there's real-world trouble here
The insanity of The Three Little Pigs
Unprofessional laziness
Combined with
Mood swing down there
We got it
Pretty much
Making those sorts of messages so if you
Specifically about Trump
You could
Conceivably think that what he means is executive orders
I know that
That you could use that as a
But that's
Weird
Sometimes it's
It seems like just his mood swings are enough
Like just to know the inability to
To handle any
Adversity at all
Absolutely
Tanner and tone of the show
And that's like
I don't know
Should exist
Butts
It's knowledge
True
Go to bed Jordan I'm pretty sure we're on Facebook
Word on the street
We are also
Astrolabe Searcy
Download please
Will be back but until then
300ZX Clark I am Benjamin Franklin Gates
Alexandra Thurston color