Air Jordan X swetik
I have great respect for knowledge but I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
MoneyGram
Stripe.com
Jones
Jordans
You ever played a likely place
Lot of people from the area
One guy in specifically Euchre I don't know I don't know if it's
But there was a card game called Dutch Blitz
Card game
Join.
Colleges where they bet
Kenosha
East high intensity game
Card game where you trying to
Stack numbers on top of
It's crazy
Winning hands or anything like that it's really
And it leads to fights its
It's really there's a lot of accusation
The cheating
It's never a good time
No good
I resent
But
The Box
It does say that is a vonderful good game
Death Race
Check it out
The crises come from playing it
And I do lava rocks
We are in the present-day a little bit
Figure out what we're going to cover on today's episode
Wacky Wednesday
I came up
I considered covering
Publix
Noted anti-semite Owen Benjamin
Good things about Hitler
Alien versus Predator situation
So I consider listening to Owen Benjamin live streams about Alex and I realized
Play him like a drunk and an idiot
Which is fun really f***** up stuff that
So I figured like that's no good let's stay around in the present
So today we're going to be looking at October C
16th 2019
Isaac is a really messed up
Episode of Alex's
Worthwhile for us to go over at even if it we just did do a present day episode on once
I don't think there's a different to dinner by the bridge
Hungover
He may be a little bit depressed
But
Real dangerous trend
To pay attention to
Lupe is suggest makeup
Portend
Butter
Books are signed up in
Purporting to show
I'm a policy wonk
Jared thank you so much right now
Next job
Frederick
Amapola
I'm a policy wonk
Yeah probably
So first of all Peter from Denmark
And second Mary Catherine
You are now both wonderful technocrat
The business
Heroin
Is freakishly large from Denmark
Mary Catherine
Specifically singular heaters
Nothing
Conspiracy of Peters
No no it would be
It would be a plus repeater
Good thank you so much
If you're out there listening as hey I would like to join the conspiracy of Christmas
Famous Chris
Peter I like that
Sports
Alright Jordan let's get down to business
Today Show
I only have one question for you
Despite its stupidity because I want to see how this show is going to end
That's the sort of mode he's in at the end list
F****** around nonsense
Circle like a sort of b*******
Not far off it's mostly important
Because as we get started with the episodes
Completely different
I do know that that's where it's heading to value
Grandiose
About
At the beginning
Has like this real sense
You're very serious
Message
And purpose to
Just minutes ago
In the control room standing over one of the Riders
Today's live show to put a page out everyday that has a life
Feed
How's the right there
Infowars.com easy to share that way
Tennessee magically says
What the broadcast
Bill's where there's a quote from there
This will be the most important
Broadcast
Most important
Levi's
Ken Jost
Execute
Laying out the information of calm
Recent weigh
President
So much for the days after the Boston bombings the most important broadcast I've ever done
Am I pretty good
Self-immolated
Episode
Nopi just dicks around with Sargon of akkad
So that's again
Where we Envy episode
The most important broadcast ever if he's able to focus and execute his plan
Makes it
You might ask why
Is this day so important
Eventually Alex does have an answer
I've been very frustrated last few months on air
And affair
My mind's been working
Like a splinter
Inside of it
Wanting to
To defeat
In Plainview
Conscious mind simply
Couldn't grasp
Longhorn
As I was laying
For Westerville Ohio
I just had
Great restful sleep
I woke up at 6 a.m. this morning
New
Mission
Need to be carried out
This is
Real weird
Alex is the globalist
Figured it out
Who you know what else could feel like
Maybe he has a tumor
I don't know
What we got to do it's been in Plainview I couldn't
Except it would like whatever your plan is
It's either going to be the most disappointing
Right thing ever
Wade Hughes the getting into the subject
You know what it's super easy but we just couldn't bear to see the
Dissolution
You know what I realized I realize that we need to live in the now guys we spend too much
And the now says
Murder everyone feel like it could be anywhere on that Spectrum front right self-help too overt
Play like
It's wartime
Good or whatever call Dad
I didn't know where this is going to go we learned that I guess
Defeating globalist
Involves a ritual or something I'm not tired this is a little confusing
10:00 this morning
My brain when I was working out
That vision of understanding that I knew
Carry out this ritual
Realized
This is what the enemy fears more than anything
And this is what
Night and day they work to make sure you never discover
We're not specific at this point at all
I am on the edge of my seat
Because like
This is I'm so used to being
Disappointed
Me too much
But I was like
What is he going to
Advocate for
Because the way he's building this up is the most important show I've ever done
I had the piffany on the easy way to defeat the globalist
It's a it's a ritual and the globalist are afraid of talking about this ritual
I called this could go bad directions
Probably saw something who knows
Scorpio most of his career
Child's Play compared to what we're gonna do now
Is Child's Play
Nothing Preparatory events
Setting the stage
And whether Abdullah
Answer
You
Like a plant
I'm starting to think maybe it's just about acceptance
This is all just like a really dramatic
Call today to come down in
What do they call them
Set a reminder
It's just that where my head's at now is I'm listen to
More like other regular
It must
To be clear by headset
This is just you didn't have much to talk about
You probably weren't paying attention to the debate so you don't really have
Anything to cover their other than your normal stuff about
Elizabeth Warren and Bernie and
Blah blah blah
You have a different job
Supposed to be
He's just rambling about that week I had an epiphany that we could defeat the globalist by accepting Jesus
Isn't that something you would saying for a long time it doesn't seem like this is the fruit of a
Very much
Just performing
Gravity putting on
Is it tree in the river that covered in blood that we have to do cuz Thomas Jefferson but
Yeah
From contacts
Lead me to believe he's just going to be like so we accept Jesus but he's not been
Specific
Another
Whatever
Anything's possible but he's still not specific
Break
Butox a little more
I have been spending the last three months or so very very frustrated
With an idea that I knew was hiding in
Front of me
But my subconscious
And my spirit
What's hiding from it
Responsibility
Also
I am ashamed of myself
That's really the truth
I tell you this because it's important to understand that
Understand why all of us
Who don't openly consciously
Still
Chad Duvall
And it's a riddle
The answer to
Keys
To Eternity
So you're still not clear starting to get those
Sort of
Echoes of the other day like a couple days back Alex saying God is calling him to declare
I don't know if that's necessarily the way he put it
But I'm starting to get little
Little kernels of that feel like
Alex are you building up to declare yourself a religion
Just l
Specific I don't know what he's talking about
Text Cliff Alex
Admit
But all along
Please don't have to defeat
In a raises the question why haven't you text me the first question I would ask
I have known
How to defeat the globalist
Claim
Vibrate
Defeat
Satan's world
You're all going to say well of course text
Fontspace
Asia
Speaks for itself weaponize rare
Is truth
But knowing
What's true
His only
Ben wants to know that true that you hide from
Shut the fuk up on the phone responsibilities
Place
God's will must be done
So when you start talkin like that must be done eating from what must be done
Birthright is involved a b word
Also the connotation of like
Claim this leadership role
Days prior about God calling him to declare himself a leader
This quote-unquote epiphany
Exist Within
The context
And that's troubling
Yeah
Going to be like
Now
What's the Holocaust
So bad
I mean you're using exaggeration but like
Talk especially people of the sort of
Inclination
Did Alex
It has
About done
It's generally not like positive things
It usually has like we're pretending we don't want violence for a long time
Our enemies are demons so f*** it
What must be done is going and getting ice cream
He's not going to
To go into that direction
He's not saying
Overtly or explicitly like
Got to do this violence or anything like that
But these tone these these
These beams that are coming up in the ways of presenting this religious
Are just
Trouble
You usually don't see them outside of the really negative Conte
We should not come
Wink wink
So Alex
Now gets to a little bit more specific
Like if you really listen to
What he's saying here about these
Demon anime
That he has
I think I think you're fine
I'm pretty troubling
The Enemy by being abused as children or having genetic
A lot of different ways
Themselves
Operating system
Spirit
To be able to throw off any connection God
And you willfully
So far from God so they can be with
Willfully
We're switching to Linux
We have to
Consciously decide to be with.
Okay so there's a prescription sort of that we have to talk
The same thing you talk about all this
But as soon as I like started talking on this episode was just going to end up being an Evangelical
Everything is
His big Revelation this breakthrough seems to be
And so his buddies have to be that much more
That's a huge disappointment
You know but it always rebuild something off at all it's never not a dud
However
And this is not something I've heard him talk about in the
The least interest training and loss
I've no idea what that means but I assume he watched Eyes Wide Shut recently
The other two examples about how people prepare and willfully doing these things to get into Satan
There's super f***** up
Sincere about what he's putting into the world I think
Just makes me bigger monster than even we give him
Credit score
Cuz apparently being a survivor of childhood abuse is preparation for being into Satan
According to Alex
Callous and cruel as Alex
Steven from him
That's a shocking
Statement that tube really really f***** up thing 22b
Part of preparation to go away from God
That is troubling is that idea is
I think his other examples probably worse
What's a genetic
Predisposition for getting into Satan
Exactly just Jeanette explain to that at all
There's no way that what he's saying isn't it
Sorts of people are just biologically susceptible
I would love for him to clarify exactly what sort of genetic link
Discovered here but I think
Haven't listened to as much of his show as I have I already know that
See them right away if you know what I mean
WinCo
Fatima three ways you given here for how people become part of his enemies are completely out of their can
Being the victim of a crime
And the other is based on
I don't understand
Yells about free will all the time and all that is just
Lumping people around like this
The guy I just
I think it's really sucked out
Well I mean I guess the idea behind that
If they don't have any choice
To do it then
Not their choice to
You stop doing it
Same way
I think everybody's a d
He's removing
Agency from all of his enemy
So they do know
Do anything
Disposed
When he's
Press to the wall
In the middle of his bizarre religious Tran
At the beginning of this episode
Slow rap
Irrational
The three things that he's able to come up with examples for like rituals that
People willingly willfully go through it
Those examples
And I just don't I don't think
You can
I don't think that you can live in
Well
And hold those sorts of beliefs
What's up
Euchre you get hit a lot
While you have to recite
I'm pretty sure that's the names of cereal you know that pretty sure that's how it
Yeah
So Alex is talked a little bit about this like
Why if this answer is
Easy why won't people go for it
And it's because of
You feel ashamed
Because you're in the presence of God
Fall program
That I remember
Manipulate you
To feel like you're not worthy
Communion with God and that you're not worthy
Christian the person
Something
Because it's so magnificent and so time was
And so powerful
You want to crawl under a rock
The coaches just want to get
Completely
I just hear their Alex talking about like
More or less a rationalization
For himself declared himself a religious
Because because of
Presence of God because
Like it it feels like he's talking about things that held him back
From declaring himself a religious leader
Feeling like s***
I feel a psychodrama being played out for Less
In the context of projecting it onto
Believers in the audience
Right right right
It's obvious
If
Like 90% +
Evangelicals
Voted for and support Trump
No matter what
The average Chris
Is full of s***
In League with the Devil
I think he's
He's a saint
That's right
I don't know
Mexico
So you talk about Solutions just on his face
Is the solution
Close to God
Yeah but what's the final
View
And should lead you and guide you enter Direct
God is in you you will go out like a heat-seeking missile
You will go out and you want
A Magic Touch
Enemy will see it
And will
Absolutely
Sing
You should not have any fear of Satan or his minions and his slaves
So Alex's
Given the idea I guess
Can you get magic
Anti-corruption powers
Which is
Is good what is the Bible was just
Old Testament in the letter to Thessalonians
What we're looking at right now
Jesus sucks man he's all like don't
It's strange
I don't know how much I believe necessarily
Magic antique Russian powers
Whatever
Alex Goes break
Any comes back
Going Whole Hog
Just Breathe
And he's just
Now greetings
Rue
Because they are given over to strong delusion
The other doesn't sound like you
Saying unhealthy
Yep that's Gaslight exotic pretty hard
Reading scripture on air coming out of commercial breaks
Which is a great development
To use Magic anti-corruption Touch
A day and you only
Have to rest one
2nd Timothy 1:7
Which is part of the letter that Paul was writing
Paul was in prison for Assurant
Don't worry about it
How do I get because it's fun here some other quotes from 2nd Timothy that Alex should think about
Recent more ungodliness
I can't think of a better description of The Three Little Pigs
Wednesday is Ben's trophy bowling
The servant of God but not strive but be gentle
Patient and weakness instructing those that oppose them
Themselves
I can take a few things
Describe Alex
Gentle unto all
In chapter 4 of 2nd Timothy Paul instructs Timothy to bring him his cloak
It talks about Alexander the coppersmith
Just talks about the coppersmith he doesn't like
I don't know anything about Alexander
Uniformly douchebag my question is largely
If Alex is so ready to cite this verse
Why is he silent on the matter of Alexander the copper
That's a good question of the coppersmith
Does coppersmith Jones
I'm a coppersmith truther
Portsmouth
I think he's in the bar in the pocket of yoga out
Just been a Prelude to him trying to
To get his audience
To accept Jesus
And it's the realization that
You don't have to have all the answers your will not defeat
Show me what to do
It will all follow and you will
Experience and intensifying relationship
I'm not against people who are
I am not against
Christianity I am not against Christians
Muslims
Not against
Anybody of any faith
I'm against
I do not think
The distance
I think this is
A guy
Pivoting his Khan
I think what you're seeing here is somebody who's like all right
I'm not making money doing this anymore
The ship is falling apart
Even if I get sued out of my entire existence
How's it going to be
Play Lee worried about that
I'm so if
You know Alex recognizes
Even if I do completely self-destruct on that path
There may be a future for me and televangel
Oh absolutely Baker go to prison
For defrosting people come back and now has a compound in the Ozark
It's still make tons of money doing this is a safe Refuge
For me
Despite like
The answer
Suffocation of it just even in the last
Has been pretty severe
To declare myself in a leadership position
The first
F****** hour of his show being this bizarre
Religious
Like I don't feel like
Anybody should
Feel ashamed of having religious
Believe
Or anything like that
And it's not my business or interest on the
The podcast to be like
You're stupid if you believe in God
And their religious beliefs
I don't respect people using it as a weapon
Against their audio
Yeah and that's all I see
She going on here
It's not critiquing somebody who wants
Someone to accept you
That's
Like I could be easy to get that twisted
And that is not what I'm respond
I'm responding
True Religion be used
It is as far away from what it is
Possibly
He's just
He's just like
I made all this money
If I become a cult leader
I can make the same amount of money and I don't have to work
Probably still do some of the
Steamworks
His work is just yelling
He's technically still work
Bright no totally ends I think it's a smart move on his part I don't know if that's what he's doing
But it's the feeling
That you get from listening
Feel like I don't know what
This has to do with the Democratic
I don't know
You're just
Trying to get
People
Your
Version of religion that
Yeah
Haha
Pivot
To religiously
Organization
Would he be able to
Who created Twitter
Count for that organization
Probably not
Oh yeah well I mean we learned the Tommy Robinson and Sargon of akkad when they tried to get
Twitter accounts for their runs
4 Harlem
Right so I probably wouldn't be able to
Rebrand
Comeback
Easy like a lot of
Just be done in a purely religious
Just contact
Do you know they're just demon
There aren't they already are
All the time even hybrids
Steve Quayle
He's been on Jim Bakker Show like you could just
I made it wouldn't be hard
Yeah closedown Infowars laylow for 6-month
Become a religious
6 months
He does have the actual lawsuit
The trial
Get enough money to weather that storm
And then come back
In some form as
Purely religious
And then any kind of like
Answering him become even more compelling
Skyblock
My religion or whatever
I think if he was like
Legitimately
Trying to just
Say hey
I believe in Christianity
And I want as many people to
To know the joys
And the love that comes
From Christy
But the issue is
Trying to
Proselytizing
God and Jesus
He's also say
Don't go to church
The Falls churches
Them Shazam
Control
Because you have the real why didn't you
I want to send you out to bring other people to them
Flip it
Control of that whole flock
People and lead them
Into a spider
That's how this works
Most churches churches all these golf glitterbug churches out there
What exactly falls under that
Not specific enough it's probably any church you might go to
Absolutely
Did you go to what do you mean
Cuz it's a spider
What you're doing here is trying to get people into a specific
Your extreme right-wing
Possibly
Christian identity leading religious belief
That's what you want people to
Subscribe to with a religious fervor as opposed to just being in
Interested in
Bringing people to Jesus
Write the problem is f***** up
No matter what anybody else says about
Right
Assault leader at all stuff conflict with stuff
Spider trap spiders
So Alex.
Monster
Torture you
God wants you to marry
Into
Life
Is creation
It's a
Love affair
Once
Torture your soul
Because it's
Is a loser
Another joke
God did create a new one
I can't stand
Watch
Football
Universe Works
Freeway
That's what free will is about most of these people are Satanist
Because of things I had nothing to do with their free will
So I don't
I don't know if you don't know what f****** contradiction how he's able to get around that is mine somehow
Being obsessed with Free Will and then
Maligning people because of
Being the victims of crimes or their genetic makeup
F****** stupid
This is all incredibly dumb and
Kind of transparent on a certain level like
I don't know if he's going to pull the trigger and actually go through with any of those things that were talking
About like
Whatever
If you were to do it this is how you would start it
This is the kind of
Behavior you would expect from somebody
Who wants to make that pitch
Dial
I'm not predicting
King shitt cuz Alex is a crazy for
A good that prediction could it be entirely bad and maybe he's just in a weird mood and felt like preaching today
Yeah
You know couple days ago you wanted to l
Volume declared himself a leader then a couple days later this
Popping up on the show it just it just
Field
Messed up all the way
But if I remember my Bible
Seems like
God made it clear on multiple occasions
It was blasphemous
To tell him what his
Reasons for doing
Or even try and tell other people
Why God does whatever he
And apparently Alex
Is a direct line
To here's why God does
You think you think
I would say it is
It would literally be remind me of taking the lord's name in vain
Another thing that I think is really funny is that
Yeah was from seconds
I'll ask him
If you wants to declare himself a religion
Just l
I think you should read 1st Timothy also
Because in 1st Timothy
38 discusses the
The requirements
Someone who will be uprooted considered to be a bishop
From 3:2
Must be above reproach
Married only once
Temperate
Not quarrelsome and not a lover of money
Those are qualifications
It's almost it's almost impressive how all of those do not drive him
Bishop
Hilarious
1st Timothy Timothy Mathers
Great
Go talk to Alexander the coppersmith
Right the wrongs of Paul
So anyway
Commercial with that sort of
And here's how it comes back from come
He's hit show
Episode
It's a special report
No
I don't know what
Just airplane
That requires that
Go from
Weird religious Tran
Into special report about how there's a TV show about awesome
Hit the ground running when it first started by premiered its first
17 million viewers early on
But that did not last
According to the Olsen season 2 of the show which started in September 20th
Ended in March 20th
18th
The show average
6.7
131 million viewers
And was never higher than seven points
Fractured
Season 3 which is currently airing
The further drop-in rate
6 million viewers for the
Four episodes are
The reason Alex is citing the the higher number is that
Numbers at least 2 years old
And the reason he's doing that is because it's you know the idea that the show with that many
Alex
Elevate
His stature
Pure and simple
It's less impressive
To say that a side character was a parody If you want to show that would be easily in the ratings by The Voice
With the Stars
But that would be more accurate
Also I would be remiss not to point out how this special report gave me whiplash
Alex spent the first hour of his show basically this
Disturbing religious Tran
Then he goes to commercial the show returns to show
The super high ratings
It shows disjointed as hell
Like I don't know how whoever's working the board come up with something it wouldn't appear to be
Largely contradictory of the
Selflessness and that the religious
Tone of the first part of the show
Hugo going straight in
Into I don't know
It's just
Hugo s***
With the Stars loser
Sean Spicer
So Alex comes
Or something like that
Just wasn't ready more about this
These characters are based on
Movies
Can create this false
I regret to inform you we did this new site
Go back when there's a character that was similar to Alex on homeland
Globus could kill a man
If there are actually doesn't
The characters based on Alex and movies and documentaries
Explanation been there all day
Based on Alex
A possible explanation being that there are way more people walking around in public who sound like Alex.
There used to be
Characters on the show involves relatability
It seems like there's more people know somebody who's a bit like Alex
Is there more characters on shows like this
It's less likely that Alex is super
Popular and relevant
It's more likely that this stupidity
Champion
Is become more Main
People could be getting the same sort of bulshit from Fox News
As opposed to usually being
Those folks would be ashamed the level of
Rank overt stupidity of bigotry
They use the code things a lot better
Tiny little
Puzzle piece away
Tucker Carlson
I'm just saying like
White people are the best let's kill everybody else
We all know that the Bible is
Ancient American scripture we're not far not far
This complaining about the media demonizing him is just sort of a diversion
Sidetrack for Alex
He gets back to religious
Is
And then tell you you got to go through them to get to the metaphysical that you knows
The disinformation and craziness comes from
Within
Generations
Two horned devil.
Where was the ancient world they found the pyramids
They're finding pyramids in China
Whatever
I guess I can't look into it then
The black pyramids in
I'm almost there
I'm almost certain he's just talking about that
So whatever
Los Angeles
Libertarian
None of them live around there and they can't stand
What is 1 B
Blood
Everything
Sure
Most people get really scared
Decide to serve it
Wouldn't that be those Libertarians that you're talking about
And if they decided to service
These people are bigger than Charlie Sheen major Stars
People who are like 8
Okay well crew would have to
About vampires
Just b******* if you've ever read the graphic novel American vampire
It's very good and it just opens in the 19
1820s with
Vampires running Hollywood
This also suspiciously like the s*** Charlie Sheen probably tell Alex in the middle one of his Coke binges
Yeah
There's demons everywhere they've taken over
All this s***
Defeat them very either by believing
Has God not destroy.
If demons are taking over there running amok
Is God not destroyed us like Noah I want to know the answer
Is because God
Loves our ancestors that prayed for us
Becoming
Quietly
The future
So God is only not destroying up cuz we have a built a bank of prayers because our answer
Preyed upon
No one pays into it
It won't run out as long as we all need to pray like
Crazy
Great
I don't know what to say to that
We're not being destroyed because our ancestors prayed enough
Very very weird
I want a number
I want a number what
The correct amount of prayer if you have a situation where there's a no
Enough prayer coming from your Aunt
That means there was a
Point where enough prayer like right over under for how many prayers you need it also implies
It also implies on some level that there is a need God has for prayers
Why would there be a line
Very weird
He's actually talking about ayahuasca
A bit about DMT and how if you take it yours
Because the only thing that's going to contact you
I'm taking it
50 years
How's that 45-minute trip
Dementia
I guess 5 minutes I probably is.
Outfitters alternative explanation
It's completely possible for a bad time
Really has nothing to do with literal demon
From everything I've read or heard about the experience taking p.m. to your Ayahuasca puts a person into a state where
Struggling
Conscious level of baby trying to ignore
Become very
Clear to them
A friend who taking it said it was a challenging experience with Air Force 2
Confronting work through a lot of stuff that they've
Been suppressing
I want friend who's a super happy-go-lucky type
The person who took it said it was just really interesting
Make a good hallucination
Kind of Xperia
The point is a lot of what you experienced in those States depends on what you bring to
To the table
It's certainly not the case for all Christians but I would guess a lot of a sort of Christy
Listen to Alex's associated with b b a particular sort of Christian
Put on the fire and brimstone
They might be the sort of post-tribulation rapture
They might be the sword we're stuck in the part of Chris
Belief that emphasizes that humans are deficient fine
Take me to certain beliefs into hallucinogenic experience
Is Austin going to be bad
Experience these beliefs don't really stand up to scrutiny
They all that well
Your beliefs
It's about this stuff yeah that's no good I don't want to take DMT and then start reading sinners in the hands
To give you a bad trip all
Security about the idea that all loving God would create exist
The cruelty
Your subconscious will do the rest any kind of feelings that you've been sick
Depressing about your beliefs
You'll be confronted with
Fight it
Like I know from taking acid in mushrooms
In the past
Blue whale
One of the way
That you can end up having a very bad time
Is by
Fighting
Thoughts
You'll end up like a trapped in
Weird
Conflict with yourself
You can go on
Anybody who works for Alex
Would not be able to handle being
Confronted
With subconscious
Things that they
If you work for Alex you know on some level that you work for a liar
Taking a hallucinogen would be at nightmare
They always empty
Exercise having a guy
Anytime you go on any of those strips
You want a guy there too
Comfort you in
Keep you on the path instead of getting lost
And you don't want
I'm sure they did
Around Alex
Oh God he would turn into a demon
So fast
To be said for like
Christians being particularly tormented by
Did sorta Kristen's that Alex probably hangs out with probably have a lot of unresolved
Stuff they need to work through
Brought up
The state of Illusion
Magenic trip
And experience that as demon
Torturing them for their beliefs
Call bunch of bulshit
But Alex has one other citation
And it's a guy that I
Play this again
Eric Muller
Joshua
Costa Rica
$50,000
All saw the same aliens come out of the forest
Just were there to help
Tell folks it was feeding time
Mankind
Duck-fat on
And here's a few
Reasons why first involvement Kouts 02
Got paid $15,000 for an Ayahuasca retreat
Costa Rica
There's a group called soltara that offers
Most expensive package
Is just under $7,000
And that's for two people
You could stay in a private couples
Covers all the costs for the week that you're there
Food everything
Kind of affordable
Not at all.
Doc.
There's would be able to
$2,000
3 week Retreat for
Two people
At Vicente pretty like Resort
High-end
Right I wanted to know more so I went to listen to an episode of podcast
To the guy who runs the return
He went to a place called rhythmia
If you look it up it cost
$300 a day
Have to been there for 50 days for $15,000
Jesus was only in the desert
440 manman count
Is there for a week
So it's like
Which is pretty standard for people who go and do non-luxury
Trips like this
The entire episode of Mancow show is about how Ayahuasca is a medicine that helps people overcome trauma
And reconnect with themselves
There's no conversation about everybody scene
Aliens there's no demon possession
Talks about recovering memory from
Beautiful
He asked me about the guy the Clockwork elves
Advance Auto explicitly says quote
See any of the
It's all bulshit
Listen to podcast with this guy it's one of the more
Like I was
Because he wasn't
Being
It's very unlike the experiences that I've personally
I've heard him
Was having a really really hard time and needed to go to this
Retreat at exactly if it was like
A friend of his went
Before and that's why they went together
Experian
And the guy who's on his
Just talking about it in the
The context of
Are you go
You're shown
Important moments
In your memories and your path
Places where part
Of you became alienated from yourself
Offers you the opportunity
To confront those things
From your past
And move past
It's shockingly
I don't even know what the right word is but just
Find Flamenco episode
There is Easter
There's even a conversation
Between him and this dude and runs the resort talking about the difference in belief of like
Whether it's a mystical thing or chemical thing
I don't really care if you believe
If if you believe that if
The chemical thing
Then that's your experience and that's great that's awesome if you have a chemical Experian
Allows you
The same benefit as somebody else who believes it's a mystical experience
What's the reason we should argue about
There's no Orthodoxy
There's no
There's no aliens
You would think there's no Keebler aliens
Medicare does a half-hour episode talking
Guy runs the retreat
Everyone's are salt the same alien and got taken over by
And I don't think I was the kind of person to shy away from that out of politeness
This m*********** made me see alien and I got
Right
If I do Mancow repertoire
The only thing this evening
Close
Is that the guy who's on the podcast
With me
How does mention that you had
Experiences taking
Ayahuasca
Where he and somebody else
I quit taking it
Had a shared
Experience
Is
Subjective
So even if it is both of their subject
I don't know
I don't know if that's real
I don't I don't know I but I also believe that if there's a possibility that
Could be maybe
You hear similar stories when people about like meditation and lucid dreaming
You hear that
Shared
Subconscious
Experience
In other avenues
I think that that's something
People we might learn more about as we
Get a greater understanding of how our brains
I think
Part of that like
I don't care if you think
Chemical or mystical
That's cool
Did you hurt yourself did you hurt somebody else
No you only benefited
Well then find the subjective experience
Far as it goes
About
Aliens
That's why they aren't
Open pallets
And if that's the case then Alex you think Mancow is evil
Because the functions that podcast just to get more food for the alien
Or whatever the demon
So would be an active promoter of
Feeding time so
Mexico
And I think Alex
Just making s*** up knowing the bank how is going
I agree
It gets back to talk about
Germany has been transitioned
The news of the day it's a little jarring
Questionnaire with our memories light
Send a text
Oh no
Autograph
Computer memory
Tulsi gabbard
Anti
In which war
This is too much
Timer a long pause
Romance
Maverick
Chose
Sparse beard
Really
Get into the debates though and he doesn't
At this point
Really at all except
Endless war thing but I think
Did she is just there in order to take
Takeout Trump
She's the Dark Horse or whatever I don't know I don't know what he's doing
Little bit
Cuz he's got to get back
The talking about the good doctor
And how they're making fun of him
Turns out he works for the Nations
Funds a lot of the shows on ABC really
Dreadlocks
I will be in a shareholder document
That's the first entry is Bill Gates
Research
Don't be digging on this and by that I mean he's gone to Gordon's Wikipedia
Redirected videos for the Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation
Do you want
If we're going to play this game let's at least make it fun
Seth Gordon also directed the king of Kong that documentary about the Donkey Kong world record
Conspiracy
Donkey Kong Gaga
There you go there's no citation on his what work he did with the Gates Foundation
I guess it has to do with the six months
She spent teaching in
According to an article about him and Reuters promoting his upcoming film
Should I quote after discovering the Canyon in
Infrastructure leaves
School building to the locals
He helped get philanthropic you and financing to finish up a rose
And then film to students
Residences be experience
The ensuing
Change it
His work was abused work
Towards a documentary called building Shimon yarrow
This is where the path intersects with the gates
Do you want
Either that or Bill Gates movie starring Gordon
Also Direct
Everybody knows only Satan believes in more than one Christmas
Any evidence needed has Alex that he works for the Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation or the UN
But
Just passed Pat probably enter
Intersected with
There
The Development Council
Might get involved with
While he was trying to help build schools and Kenny
Years ago
Is it like
What right
You know another problem with income inequality
Is there a never-ending amount of billionaires
Is to update your b*******
Conspiracy theory
Like you start with the Rothschild or whatever
Avanti
Name of
And then you wind up with Soros and then you go to Gates and then it's never ending
Blame the government
He won't have
That might not be a great
Development for his rhetoric
I don't know
Right don't care it's just like
This is the same thing as saying the good doctor has 1718 million viewers
Who's making
The attack on you
This guy to direct a video about
The Gates Foundation when he was trying to help
Smoke Canyon School get built which was in
Intersected with a wrench
He doesn't work for them
It's just crazy it's the only ate all it does
Is it serve to make it look like on me
Hey look at how powerful the peace
People are who are reality
It's probably just like hey here's something we could put into an episode
There's an archetype that's Goofy and ripe for parody
Yeah not hard
Nope
You're not hard
It's not hard
To book don't guest on your show and Alex has done just that
Carl Benjamin Sargon of akkad is back in studio whether she is a Smart Cookie look forward
What do you want to cover first
So Carla
What is a first date
Navigate to that Unabomber
Alex
Behavior
Which is
Have already left
And the
Putting the baby to bed
Ending the war the Deep State started
I don't know
Support
Blank is a few
All roads
I guess so
Sargon has
Is a little bit of an interest
Sing take on this
Carl
Carl has an interesting take on this
You're taking the troops out
You know
And Carl realizes that well I mean they also sent troops
What's the Saudi Arabia
Which is true
Now Mike down for this
How this exchange goes
Because I think is one of the most revealing
Clips that we maybe have ever played
What do you make of what you just saw cops
Trump is doing what he said he would
Living Desert
In the middle
People essay well he sending xmod troops to Saudi Arabia
Igtools
One of those things where it's a homogeneous
Yeah yeah
So
First of all
Arabia is our Ally so Trump has to send troops to support them over there
There are more real than Saudi Arabia
That argument for his evolved 11
Fall completely apart upon any examination
Strike one Carl
Carlos
Now ignore for a minute that Alex was convinced recently by Joel skousen that Trump taking troops out of Northern Syria with
Because this goddamn show exist
Outside of context
Obviously
Intentionally ignored
Trump sending troops to
Saudi Arabia
From everything I've listened to visit just pretending it didn't happen
Because he knows he can't justify it at all
That's why would Carl brings it up
Alex first tries to pretend that what's really happening is a trump is better than missile defense system
But Carl doesn't realize that this is not a welcome talking point on Alex's
So he tries to correct Alex
Compromise
Namely the only a couple to man the missile defense system
You see how that works there that back and forth is so revealing
That's all he's doing is AAA
An uncontrolled variable entering Alex's
Controlled
And then you see how it's mitigated
You see it
Leave the conversation that's happening
Is very clear the message that Alex is because stop it
Stop
MMA
Knows well enough to be like oh yeah okay
You can tell there's pushback on this
Is very real thing as it all why would anybody push back on that do it kind of hurt a scenario
Alex is lying because he can't afford to tell the truth
The missile defense systems were sent last month along with a couple hundred true
Saudi Arabia
And that was a response to the attack on Saudi oil interests the drop is blamed on a run
In October on October 11th the New York Times reported the Trump is sending a proxy
Smiley three thousand additional troops
Which were not just people to man The Myth
Defense system
Alex is so full of s*** that clip is very special
Because it demonstrates Malik
Carl has no idea what things from The Real World are okay to talk about on Infowars and with her.
Intentionally protects his audience
From some information about reality that might lead them to realizing that he's misleading
So Carl thinks that he can just speak freely cuz I was healed by free speech
Create a new reality to explain away the verboten information
It's just been introduced
Without putting that stuff never come up
The goalposts are on ice
But please
Come on man we outside
He talks about
Like he knows that
More troops of exam Saudi Arabia
And you just pretend
Talking about this
The situation
Troops out I thought they were into leaving the middle
Middle East
To hear them screaming about how we should say that
Is
An amazing
We have the moral Monday to impose allegations of Human Rights
At least
With what we consider to be
Human rights
A really interesting perspective the car all this putting forth
The idea that people in the Middle East don't see much of an interest or at least the rest of the world
Who don't have as much
Right
What we would call the people
They're really into it and they're against
Gas by there only
I suppose he could be talking about the number of poles that have been done to show a trend in countries in the region of not believing in equality
For women you can see things like that is unsalvageable difference
Or you could realize that the polling numbers would look really similar if you did them in the US and then
1950s
A lot of history seems unfounded
Cultural hatred towards Muslim
I really don't see any other way to look
Cuz I kind of get the sense that we're Carla's doing is just a
Assuming that the terrorists and extremists
Are completely representative of the people of the region
And it does not seem
Fair
It seems like this is based on feeling
Also
F***
You Carl
Carl
Are not defined differently
Earlier this year Secretary of State Mike Pompeo and Elsa
Formation of a commission on unalienable rights
Would you said would revisit the most basic of questions
What does it mean to say or claim that something is in fact a human right
He went on to say quote How can there be human rights we possess not improve alleges we're granted or even earn but
Virtue of our Humanity belong to us
Is it true as our Declaration of Independence assert
All of us every member of our human family are endowed by our creator with certain inalienable
What the f****** monster
Is this a state department or an undergrad philosophy class
If you hear someone in Trump's cabinet floating questions about whether or not people have rights just because they're people
You better prepare yourself for the answer they come up with to be maybe not or worse
I found it when people insist on asking long ago answer question
Already came to
A commission like this does not exist to strengthen or celebrate human rights
It exists after completely different question
But High
What can we get away with
Yep it doesn't make things look
You better when you learn
Glad I protested the
The commission haven't found over anti-lgbt
Statements made by seven of the nine members appointed to the commission
And there are a whole ton of anti woman's right to choose
In there too
That's what this is about
Jesus Christ
My point is I guess
Is human rights issues all over the place
I don't know what Carl was talking about what he says the Middle East isn't into human rights like we are
And since he doesn't give me any citation
Chance to go on it
I just have to assume
Feels that way
And doesn't care about other ants
Human rights issue
Around the world
You know what I
Very funny
Where is Elmo state
Suspicious
Just parallel between
In the seventies and eighties
Russia-us right
Because Iran
There was a far more open and a galuteria society and then we helped install a repressive
F****** Theocratic nightmarish
Regime
And Russia is
Basically
Did the same thing.
It's very fast
A book about it okay
So
Sargon of akkad
AKA Carl
I is
He's up on things he knows about
Struck me as weird and why people are talking about him
I'm not even sure what the grounds for impeachment
What are they even saying that should be
Buddy reads his divorce files it's really amazing
10-4 it's also
Shane Boldin there's so many better ways to attack you
Also mustache
For the longest time
Hadn't revealed his music
The only picture Alex had of him was from the 70s
It was a pretty big bust at SoDo
Maybe he's onto something
Didn't like
Until blue blue
Wasn't a big fan of
So Alex
This is all about
Warriors and
He's doing all this
Great
It's so annoying
Like
Because it's
So start
They have to go so far in the
Like if it was just a little bit of that
It is just a little bit of that phone call and there was no other information
They can be like oh well you're all blowing it out of
Proportion
Democrat Lisa
Knowledge that it
Because it's so obvious out criminal
They're just like
Never heard
Like it's just
So hard today
To the delusion
SMS
About the debate and Alex
Who's kind of Pro Tulsa
Which is weird
Considering
By his own definition
She's a gun grabber
Which literally
Anybody who indicate in favor of red flag laws
Everybody anyway
That they're interested in guns being
You take it and or
Restricted
Weird
In this clip you speak
About her positively
But also brings up that
She wants
Grabbing
Just blows away everybody else
She said some terrible things I disagree with
So I mean
Some good
Everybody else
Ever
Who's in favor of red flag laws for gun regulation
He's a f****** demon
I don't get it
I'd
It's probably just because he thinks he's hot
Yeah
But they're just shattered
She's a dark horse they're holding
Interesting thing that everybody's got to be kind of aware of
And that is this world likes bird
Andrew yang
Universal
I don't know why
WinCo
But it's strange
It's very strange
Are the candidates that people Envy
Extreme right-wing like Alex
And people who are more
I don't know what you call Carl
Quite frankly just a s*** head
Pieces of s*** head
Kind of far right is Alex
But he is certainly
He certainly should
Yeah they're all they're all on board
Which
Is weird AC same thing from Robert Barnes
Weirdly
Why
Don't know
Obviously
So clip earlier when
Alex and Carl were having a little bit of a negotiation about whether or not Trump is second to
I was really illustrative
Of how this works on Alex's show that you cannot counter his narrative
Push like Alex get there
And if you don't
Fall in line
It'll probably
Interview
The route of acquiescing to Alex
The interview
And now Alex pull the power move
Where he makes Carl report on an article that he hasn't read
2D platformer
Dosing child sexual exploitation promotion cell phone
How did works
Reporter is a joke
He already did that and the other band
There is
No reason to for Alex to say hey
Carl why don't you report on this article that you haven't read you can hear the hesitancy in in Colorado
This is from RTI
I guess it's right I'll look stupid
Right and then he's reading it and took what why would you have any issue with Twitter having rules where world leaders can
Zack list of things
Clear
World leaders should not be able to do those things
If your
Open Lisa
Most active
They're banning
Outright calling for violence against someone specifically right
You're saying that Trump outright calls for violence against people specifically
Which iPads
Carl has allowed
Alex decides to start speaking in a British accent
I want Kamala Harris
I'll show my friend
Noticed
My good man
I would be terribly offensive
This is bad riffing
This is a disaster Carl's laughter is probably just like
Slightly discomfort and laughing at like this is uncomfortable as s***
Breath of Life
I would be terrible at fencing
That's not the actor somebody was like I like what's happening
What a boot
Bootlicker
That is exactly how Starman
Untreated wormtongue
Glad you are a
Little booty
Licking
You are nothing
Have fun with that
Car wants to talk kind of
Right, Harris head
It suggested the trumps
To be kicked off Twitter
And car wash
Talk about that
Alex
Wants to
Fill out his character real
What
Sam
I think you have any coffee
This is not good
That's good stuff
Universal healthcare that people there's a lot of people
Because of inability to access appropriate care
We should be living in a society where people are using crowdfunding in order to
God dammit
God damn it you are talking
King to a child
And it is so funny
Exactly
I didn't have to succumb to his whims
Very poorly
Clip of Kamala Harris
And Alex has
Some criticisms
Elizabeth Warren
Sure over the video
His info
Kyle Brandt
5 million Twitter
We saw in El Paso
So you know they're not supposed to
Children
Development supposed to make it through pretty early
Genius
Against Elizabeth Warren
By saying he's doing it because people say he shouldn't
This is also what you expect to hear like from a rebellious teen trying to justify how they started
Smoking not from an adult who spent the first hour of the show rambling about being on a mission from God
It's all good
Bryce shame the people in Alex's life for not recognizing warnings
But yeah
It's true that a lot of things
A really troubling about what Alex is doing
They could be elements of a performance
But I would rather err on the side
Taking Dysteria
These symptoms that he's mad
Indicates that he's putting on an act than all that happens is I look stupid for being
Concerned about a con man putting on a show
If you sincerely operating with this kind of diminished
Levels of
Functioning
It's only a matter of time before something goes horribly wrong
I guess I hope I end up looking stupid
Like I just like you can't
You can't you can't
Be around this
And not stop
I just can't
It's just pathetic not Lisa
Even if we're talking about him putting on it
This part
Him talking
Over Kamala Harris
About
Does Warren looking ugly
Just because
Fourth grade
They're all in
Into his friend while he's a f****** child
It's something that you act
That's just him
And it's obviously intended to make people dying
How to get negative attention from people from like
The pyramids
I'm sure that's what children do too
They thrive on this negative attention it
It's the pastoring again
It's just
He's operating on an adolescent level while at the same time
Saying that God is
Asking him to declare himself a leader
Hey going on this
Religious
Quest
Open children
It could be something to children do but it's also something
Is very difficult
Even adults
To pull off response
I just
It isn't like it's going to probably get annoying
It ain't our present-day episodes be given
Little speeches
It specifically directed to anybody who might working Infowars who's listening
Guys
Ladies
Call the.
Someone can help him
And they should
Because this is not somebody who's well
I feel like all those jobs are people riding this horse until it dies
Like
Dies
I hope you do have you ever heard of
I think you guys might
Find her
So Carl and Alex are talking about social media
Because of Sandy Hook
And in this clip
And Alex
Straight up lies
Carl's face
About what he did
I want to be clear
I always thought I should make that video
You know supposedly.
What I said
Shelly here
Hurting family
How to get the
This is a complete bulshit wise Behavior
So I mean this is just rank disrespect to it for his gas
Which would be a perfectly acceptable out for him to
Granted it might be tossed because it being sued right now
Fight for him to say
I did believe that I was wrong
I was misled by a number of people who I believed to be credible sources at the time
There's no shame
Unless you're out
He can't be wrong about anything
Ever
Enso
It just makes allies
Build on top of it
Each other
You just do not they're not having a real conversation
Like Alex is just
Insulting him Force
Propaganda
And then lying
Disrespectful interview
And I don't have any
Care for Carl
No
For somebody who has a lawyer
4 days a week
Continuing would be my first
First bit of advice
To Alex's life
Don't
Don't say anything
Stop you're not home
You're not helping your case by creating a
Completely fix
No backstory for what you did
Pretend that you
F****** a behavior that could only hurt
Because
This isn't
True
Truths about
Not true
And the more he says it the more the audience has an opportunity to be like
True lying about your coverage
That introduces the guy that possibility maybe you're lying about everything else
Feelings
That is not why you were
Hurt feeling
Are not white
What part of it.
Play a video of a woman
Oprah's
Network I show on Oprah's network
And Carl's there
Alex is there
Italy and back
Kid out visiting though
This is Lady
Music
We really shouldn't
Feel like that's all gone
Now Alex is trying to
Chris Carl
Side of the the show
Capri racist riffing about a video
A blaze of a black woman discussing obese
Going to say that that
We know
The strawman version that they're attacking is that this woman in the video is blaming Trump for getting her fat
Because they set this up as
They've become free to goof on how stupid she is
Super awesome riffs about racism is just an unhinged
Crazy person
Because they created the false argument
And this is all the rage with media
All the outlets have their own articles about this clip and they all have the same
Gender studies professor says black women are fat because of
In reality
This is a clip of a woman named Brittany Cooper and she's discussing actual issues that Alex would rather
Discuss fake versions of
If you actually watch the Clipper read anything Cooper's put out
You'll see that
Insurance and worse Healthcare
The issues that
He is pointing to
She also mentioned the theory that racism makes diets not work as well for black women
Intercourse
This is just
The stupidest show nonsense that Alex and Karlov ever hurt
But in reality there's some indication
True maybe not racism
Exactly but the experience of
Dealing with races
Cooper is specifically talking about research that has grown out of a paper
American Medical women
Association
This paper was looking at the racial inequalities in women's health in the country
By one of the focal points be excessive levels of
The Chronic morbidity and disability are widespread among f
Can American women regardless
Who's socio-economic position
Because the trend exists on larger
Spectrum it's harder for them to check that up solely to having to do with access to healthcare or poverty
Sunset across the socio-political economic
Spectrum
Does the author proposed a model called weathering
Which African American women experience early Health deterioration
Consequence of the cumulative impact of repeated experience of social economic and political exclusion
This includes the physical cost of engaging actively to address societal
Structural barriers to achievement
Wellbeing
It'll be really hard to defend early prove this
But a number of peer-reviewed studies
Suggested it might be on.
This might be a model
That explains things
Much better than other models that you looked at
Restrict poverty models for class model a strict model that looks like just a genetic
Physician for things
Seems like this works
Better
Explaining the phenomenon that we
Easier to lose weight if you don't have the
Russian gravity of
Daily and dignity
Weather
It for everyone
Super is arguing
At Nueces articulating a day
That's something about
This experience that we
We have
It leads to
Bodywork
I'm so
Things that would work normally
Diet
Doesn't work
Because of the metabolism
Them changes
That stress response
I don't know if this is 100%
Proven
But
Peer-reviewed studies that have been done
Have indicated that there might be some
So I'm calling not to write this office
Some kind of just
Stupid b*******
This might be it
And I would imagine that of what also contributes to it is
In the same way that women
Don't have
Heart medication
Conveyor
Far less likely to work for women is because there
Tested on
Like always said about
Certainly Focus
It's entirely upon
So
It's simply
Something that people are
Or studying is
Is also very well be the case I'm not totally sure
She specifically brought up at that did very well could be a factor
I mean that could even be applied to weather
Sure
The point here is that this woman is talk about something real that affects communities but Alex is not a part of and doesn't care about it all
Instead of engaging with what she's actually saying and recognizing
Specifically even
Bubble and greatest
2 attack
Pretty racy
So anyway
I mean it's just it's just
Believable
Like
The elements of it are like
Real stupid
You know creating a strawman to attack what she's blaming
Trump for being fat
Or something
Is stupid
It's just all over right there's an article about it on the blaze
Fox News
It's just like this is a talking point
This is like Alex's just doing like
He might as well
Riffing on stupid right-wing news
It's just pathetic
If it's sad because
I need this
To be clear
The show opened with an hour of religious fervor right then now he has f****** Sargon of akkad in studio
He's trying to impress him with racer
Like that's what it needs on the same episode
It's crazy
So now
Listen to this
Stress-eating Issaquah
Is what happened
Racist
Man it's really nice
Of him to have
Lee Ann McAdoo on
In order
To ignore
That's really kind of him
Better
For the wrong
Conclusion
She would be able to actually cover this a little better
It's like I have made you been to my well we're now in this place where I'm the alpha I have a dominant in the
Curry your favor
Spy
Making fun of sjw is like you love to do bringing you into my
I'm giving you these jokes so you will feel more comfortable and then I will you won't be like
I have dominated you and now I will make it all better
Magnanimous in your
What's going on
I just gas-lit you now let's have some jokes
So Alex Costa
Commercial there
He comes back
Play Baby Got Back
Because
Of course not.
We just make that against the rules for him
Wait stupid actually works out being really funny basement what happen
Subway
Continue making these
Cheez-It
Because they just did that whole she's got a big fat ass
Commercial
Clearly is it going
Song right there
Go to the races Chinese video
Where is have him say racist s*** about black people
Let's Play a clip of him being racist towards Chinese
Great family show in Alex
Broadcast hear sound
Furious
Broadcast
This is our breaths just f****** so mad
Yeah he is
He is. She has work trying to broadcast
I really think
It's a strong indication that what I was saying might be the case screwed
Maybe a lot of butter replacement
Besides it's time to go to some calls
Call and it also.
Does not go well
Warrior Princess
In California
It is amazing isn't it
That's good
Alright well she probably in like holding too long
Oh my God sorry sorry
Mute
This is an arcade
Age of the narcissist
Gaslighting
Was a rerun of the negging
Taking aminu the baboon
Throwing their boomerang
Classic archetype
That's all wrong
Every part of that
She's creating new racist things to say it might be I don't know enough to say what info Warrior Princess
That's where she's coming from good
I'm so
Complaining about how Warren has no fashion
Alex's response
Is pretty normal
Sweden
Apathy
Hillary up there with her mouth Mumu on Everett
So we do see Warren with that black shirt
45 years
For girl and got no Style
Scholars it keep talking about
I was going to say once it once I heard them laugh I was like
She's killing
She's going to get a shower she's getting a job old man house phone
It's not real
Actually got around to doing it which I don't think would be wise for him to
To do giving
His listeners actual
Like authorship
On the Shelf
I think that he knows enough
I mean
He knows it's like some people might seem like they're right on and then they might say something about
Is it dangerous
Call there's too much freedom
But if you're really smart thing for him to do if that weren't the case because their work for free
Freak
I think that's why
Keeps thinking
I got to do that
Earlier Alex was doing a big butt wrist to
Chinapress Carl
Complaining about you know men demanding they be called ma'am
Potshots at me
Again just to impress Carlos Behavior SquarePants
I have friends and I have a DE
Yes ma'am
That's a mean he said that multiple times you like that
It almost reminds me of what
Almost reminds me of like people at open mics the right a b i q
Go to punch this up I know you're the king's yelling about sjw
Please call
It's I think it's just her being there
The fact that he has not listened to her one time
Is self-defense
Eclipse that I'm not playing
Accurately portray the field scholarship
So f****** awesome
Just
Goliad
Call people here
Absurdly disrespect
Both of them
It's crazy
I think you are
Leanne
This
Series of Clips is living proof white everything that you have said is wrong
So h w Carl's validation
Charles has an idea for what Alex
You should do
There's a clip playing underneath that they didn't set up in any way there's just weird audio playing under it
I have no idea what it is I don't care
You want this sort of thing is already be
Been done
Like his fellow internet propaganda Florence Southern already did this gender prank
If you want to call it that
Knows full well what the result is
In 2016 Lauren did it start when she legally changed
Your gender to male
I guess is an attempt to demonstrate how easy it is to
To get that change on your ID card in Canada
Obviously this is just a temperature
Community who cheap made a large part of her career victimizing
That's all
Have to do it most of the coverage it is I can find it doesn't seem like people took the bait
A lot of responses that I found more focused on how sad this kind of stock was and how it demonstrates a fundamental disinterested
Ultimately most people saw this for what it was
Intended to make money off angry people who care about social justice
Lauren works for Rebel media at the time and already had a career gone nose full of sad offensives.
Anyone who knew what you was about knew what you was doing
I saw some responses
Question did the little by doctors day
Consult
Probably the best way to take a note 4 propaganda
Stop and take the power away from them
All in all it was a flop for Laura
Group generation
Intercept boats of refugees in the Mediterranean Sea
Subservient
Cracking up
People quitting political stuff into 20
Get the
Response the Carl's pretending he would
I suspect people just see it as a pathetic desperate man trying to get attention the only way he knows how
By acting out and try to make people angry
Is what children
Yeah I wonder what
Carl stinks
Reaction
Really
Thanks
Pikachu
Do not understand
They just absolutely have no f******
Conclude
No it wouldn't
Baby a section of people
They would be well within the right to be mad
But the responsible most people would just be like
If you're sincere cool
And if you're not you're a dick
Especially since
Alex
Most people respond to it
Wow
This is what I really need
How the mighty have fallen
October
16th episode is one of the weirder disasters I've seen and Alex's
Present
Libras are religious
Fanaticism
Nothing
It's a meaningless
Probably
The genetically predisposed yes
They nonsense about TV shows making
You fond of him
Then turning into a pageant of
Trying
Sargon of akkad into liking him racist
Establishing
Power dynamic
By lying about the real world
Lestat enter the bubble of Infowars coverage
I just think it's a terrible show
And you add into the two
Back problems
Just awful
Right unfortunately Alex has a different position
Credible
Marisqueria
Focusing on them
Your energy
They have nothing
Just trying to ask this overarching question
And after
Pretty much publicly apologizing for screaming at the crew off air
Between commercial breaks
If he's
Bringing it up on air
If he's bringing it up on are then that means that he did something real f*****-up affair
I would assume
Navigate through
Maybe
You know
He's trying to ask overarching big question of like how do we deal with
Throws death throes of globalist
Can do is make a joke
Like a little dismissive joke referencing back to the
This is nothing
This show is terrible
Disabled at this point I doubt
There's any purpose in Opa
That all
Jesus
This show sucks
I think that there is value in
I need to at least in some fashion
Keep track of the fact that Alex
In the early stages of pivoting in
And to being a outright called
Yeah
McKay's
Yeah people to take that seriously and even if it stopped
We will take the other things that he's clearly manifesting
Seriously
If sincere and real
It's only a matter of time before something really bad had
If not sincere
Still if you care about him
You should not be allowed him to
Yeah
What wouldn't surprise me at all
Based on the trends that we're
Is as
Like the Maine
Stream
Quote
All right
Media
Transit
A Transformer and Alex
I wouldn't be surprised if next year
All of their shows are apocalyptically religious
Sand
Openly racist
I think a number of them already are
I don't
I don't know what to say
Expect
I don't think there's a lot of
Ways for me to know what the
Does the larger right-wing media is going
To do cuz it seems Maybe
If its history is Prelude that maybe that is what we would expect but also I think there's a possibility
That if things get bad enough
They could course-correct a little bit
There might be
Especially people who
A come-to-jesus moment no become good up and up
But there is a possibility that
Start hiding a little bit of this stuff
Do it right
Sponsors
Who made
Do exactly what you're saying
I don't know none of it
Goodfellow will see what happen
We will see
Website
Knowledge fight
You bet we also route Twitter
Underscore
And at Goats
To bed Jordan rose on Facebook
We are on Facebook
You would like to download
The show
Intuit
ITunes
Review Oracle listen to it whenever
Castrol application
Absolutely
I'm Sargon of akkad
Thanks for holding
Alex