Air Jordan pipes sweat it
I have great respect for knowledge B I'm sick of him posing as if they're the good guy
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Little bit about Alex Jones
Authority
Shut up
Keep bringing that up excessively
Jordan is inside Jordana Brewster
Movie
No that's Soleil Moon Frye
All right so that's
No
Let someone else
Fantastic
Shoes in the thrilling adventure hour she's she's in
Controls the universe come on you ask yourself a question
I was thinking about this
Cuz of news of the day have you ever had a conflict of
Supposed to be theater back in my younger days I was friends
Some of the employees
Adventurous
People who are you
Who's your friend
Friendly relations
Projectionists
Alongside these people that got promoted to manager
CR 2 weeks ago I was just
I never really got that bad
Crisis of conflict of interest
But certainly a thirty-five-year-old man now I can look back on
How I behaved as a nineteen-year-old the movie theater manager
I can say I probably was far more people differently
My friend never got to never fired anybody or
Or did anything like that
Just because I didn't like
Somebody but
The idea that likes
3 people who weren't even
Out of college
Age without a general manager for a
Couple months stretch
Showtime
Bizarre
That's great you guys are like hiring at firms
Get Don Draper pitching you sit
Brother made a corporate level reordering
King supplies and electronics
The companies
Play
It was a lot of admin it might have been
Or we can just burn it down Loki they might have been
Challenge
Take that
Is the other conflict of interest was like
Corporate
Let's see that's pretty
Google manager
I know a little bit about Alex Jones
Of the show
Little bit of an apology maybe I'm not
Entirely sure if it qualifies as
We got a present a episodes in a row
And I should give an explanation for
Everybody likes it when I'm dumb
You know it's
Is fun to celebrate when I do something dumb
My mind that's the last 2013
Episode that we had.
Was the night
So when I sat down to prepare today's episode
Bailey
I'm so unprepared the wrong episode so obviously
Record we didn't have the
The right episode ready
We've got ready for you
Angela
Is Friday of last week real fun date to look into and check
I was because
The night before
Thursday
For his rally
No.
He's a pretty
Pretty messy
So first of all I apologize
Aimh
I'm a policy wonk
She ran out
I'm a policy
Maps
I'm a policy wonk
And finally
So just thank you so much you are now a technocrat
Money off at heroin
Freakishly large
Appreciate
You have been looking at me like I'm a little bit loopy
I don't recall looking at you like that baby maybe I'm just getting that since because
I might actually be a little I think we might both be
Tough night sleep last night so that
And you yourself do yourself for loopy battle Factory
Let's Ride the Lightning
Alex
Almost
Feeling like I'm peachment probably going to happen
If it's going to happen
We buy we weirdo friends
Have to start dealing with what happened next
I don't want to know
Definitely
Trying
Remove the president
Right now
Yeah no s***
The aftermath
Especially remove him
A lot of nationalist
Conservative
Christians
President
Tell you what
Subject today
Mario
Stories that
Trubbish
So you can see Alex has now started to recognize the shift in drudges coverage
Dare you acknowledge reality
How dare you say that break the fourth wall. Recognize reality
Too much
Too close to home
Is stories in order to wake up Trump
So he's still living in a little bit of a delusional
Hedge it as like
Drudge it's still a hundred percent on the don't worry about it
That's why all these that he's right-wing blogs
Publications
Going through the motions of like had we lost.
Hairs
Anyway
If you think the Trump is invented
You live in a damp
You're right
He later gives one example of a person who he thinks
Thinks Trump is invincible
I'll give you one hint
He was dating
Jesse James
Jesse James is apparently he thinks the truck as a vegetable
So that's good
Transitive property that alphabounces words
You know a lot of conservatives live in bubbles
But you know who doesn't
Alex Azar
Not as much
Insane asylum
Sure
They do love their own Bible sometimes
At work
Nationalist Christian
Patriots
That's your issue literally something that he is said
Over and over and over again you are bad if you do not believe in an hour
About how God is the only way to defeat the global right
Event tents sermon
Alex Jones also by the way
Because it's still saying that like if you don't have the same religious beliefs as me that's your issue as if
Problem
Christian Cooper
Applied within the the phone
Which is great
Love it
Is it Trump
Like his rhetoric
I mean I don't know how you describe it
Bye
Did you get Lionel stores
Read his golf course
Really
Did what
That's not breakfast
You talk about
Sure
Play Store
Swiss cheese
Shut up roadside
Money got funding for new rugs
You wouldn't say all the other cow
Position
Total power grab the country
Short up power dishwasher
Russian Victory absolutely
Alex
I believe that
Crushing victory that would be
Interesting idea about the Customs and Border Patrol is being ugly
Hundreds of miles of fence
And that's why there's no more fence being felt because I know
Build the wall
On August 30th 2019 PolitiFact
Seeing as it was one of the two main things that people chanted at Trump rallies in the run-up to the 2016 elections
To be effective
Prison for about 3 years
To see how he's doing with the other
Before Trump took office there was about 654 miles of primary barrier along the wall like sensor
Now three years later
No additional miles have been built
Is replacing a
Approximately 60 miles of fence
Hundreds of miles that Alex is referring to the need to be replaced
But sexy
Customs and Border Protection it received 6.2 billion dollars
To supposedly build state-of-the-art
But none of it has actually been built
Alex should be against this because it's in
Third level of financial malfeasance
But also because a lot of that money
Those billions of dollars
A lot of it came from the treasury forfeiture fund
Do you know the money that's taken for people when they're arrested or seized by the IRS
Really thought he was super against that
Oh well
Strange bedfellows
What are you going to do
As we discussed a number of times even if Trump wanted to make this wall he legitimately couldn't
The Border runs across a lot of private property the owners of witches that they're not interested in
Be built on their property so you need to have all kinds of eminent domain cases that
It just never would work out
And that's not even to mention the 118 miles of border that inside Big Bend National Park
Could you get never get approval
How to build a wall
Allocate billions of dollars to fix
The couple of miles of fencing I guess that's his prerogative
If you do that you're setting the bar insanely low
But you're supposed to be this overpowered conquering Weider
I really read but he's considering this a victory
To be some sort of
Rhetorical referee
To have jumped in the moment he said that with a whistle and just
Moving the goalposts remove 10 minutes from your shop
Jumpers in Dallas
Because he's down there to scout locations
Alex
He speaks about
Briefly that
We're at the big Trump rally in Dallas last night
Spoiler alert
He does not
It was a shark
And I
A bunch of the security group
Armored vehicle
I don't know it's weird
Play The Fray
Rolling around in
Factors root part of the very exciting
To see Alex appearing kind of like what you would expect his career
It just makes sense
8fit
Don't feel like it's okay
Using a
And iterations of tyranny Crusher in the very representation of today
Around supporter
It's not really a tank
It's sort of an armed and armored Hummer
Describing with a roof
Doesn't appear to have
Offensive capability
Open it
Supervisor
It wasn't that
Honestly it's Saturday then anything else
I can think of liked it just near
Rarity levels of aggressive militaristic
Masculinity
Because it comes off is really that's very sad
What's the video that Alex himself put out of the bullhorn
That he did
The first is that while Alex is driving around bullhorn number of people with their phones
It's unclear if their supporters are just hoping he'll get stuck in that roof hatch and then video on there
However there's one person in the shot who appears to be presenting as a real supporter
He's an African-American man with dreadlocks pumping his fists in the air toward Alex
If you pay close attention employees
The host of Firepower
To the show I will never learn about
At all
In the video Alex himself release to help stress that he himself released this
Will Johnson is the only person who appears to be a supporter
Following Alex in the armored vehicle given MD
And he's on the
Of course
So
His blankie
African Americans
So what
The fact that there's just one
Really
So there's that
Is that actually part of your
Opening orientation
Echo Park
Very sad vibe
There were about 10 people around the car will Johnson is one of them so it's entirely possible a couple of others were Infowars
Employees that I just don't know
Some people are just walking
Past and stop for a moment
Spectacle that keep walking
At least one of the people in the crowd is wearing a shirt that says quote anti Trump Social Club
And they're just taping Alex other phone causing
Any trouble or anything
Pokemon
Alright somebody in the crowd with Alex yells at it he says they're MSM
Mainstream media
The Deep state is trying
Kill Trump
And Alex just yelled something about Phil Mudd
Any plugs infowars.com America is back
Chant going only kind of works cluster response
That's always
Yeah it always seems like this is a chain cuz you have a bullhorn
Look you only try and start a chat if you know you can
Get a chance
Really dangerous maneuver if you're not
Before the Cubs
Back in the good old days of
Before 2016 and also after 2020
Like trying to get a chance
But it's nowhere near the level of someone I'd like an open mic or even a show
Coronavirus
You just feel for him
Even if it well it's almost worse if you could do successfully ushe
Carnival plush
Alex looks winded hello he literally hasn't moved and is just popping his little head out of a roof hatch
It's
Cobb picture of a man with almost nothing left
It's just that there's no joy in him at all
He was being a douche like back in the old days you know like you do early
Do you watch videos in trolling people
Two 2016 that Alexa
There was a spark there
He really seemed like he was having fun
When you go out and yell at people and f***
Getting on.
Alex
That space
But instead
Website
But you look at it it's got to be miserable
The greatest moment for him
He should be
Still alive
He's in a tank
Yelling at people at a trump rally in Texas
Adam Sandler
Realizes that there's nothing for him at home anymore
Never go home
Who sell your soul
He feels like he's treading water
Job treading water
Now get ready to Dallas
To the hospital for evaluation
Which is usually a really bad combination
Might have an expectation that a shootout might be a likely part of your evening when you leave the house with those accessories
Oh he also had mace and against Mass okay good
Except that he was wearing an insult
Fun stuff
They're absolutely really awesome
Don't I might have been under
Okay well
A lot of shirts wrinkle when they're under body armor but not view high quality
Is Alex Haynes will work with him anymore so
It's got to go with another company
I don't know
Iowa
Alex is out there in full
He was tank yelling at people
Having a blast
But not having a blast
Alex
Really
Had to go to the
But you do
Trump rally
Been there
Done that Pharrell
Seems like you would get old
Yeah you're the first reason unspoken reason
He needs
Puppy are stuck around take Elena people is about as best as he could do right now
Absolutely
Good for that there's another reason
And I talked about it and
Love
Coming out
On
By the 17th
56 years later
Do not
All the other bizarre statements shut the fuk up
Cory Booker
I said
Everybody's got a
Real feeling of concern about that
I'm the one
Stop to Dallas with the crew
Did we stop Trump
The Big Show
The world will never know
I love it so much
How many years does it take to stop an assassin
My hero
World without never know the sacrifices that I made dumb dumb president
So this is complete
Assassination plot against
Drop schedule for this rally October 17th
This is more squarely in the genre of Alex
That I can get on
I love this
This is where I wanted to be
I do like knowing that in his Vine presidential assassinations have a certain kind of poetry to them
Anniversary boiler alert
Not
Presidential election
It's so important that we remove this man from office
On the 17
How many trails
There's no indication that he was saying the 17th
The number 17
Or is totally possible that Joe Biden decide one of those stocks
Call home
Whatever the case it's a
Is a bit of a stretch
Further Evidence comes from Nancy Pelosi
That she was wearing
Which has a bullet
As well as some orange ornamental beads
Just thinking if I safe
Stuff people wear
It's a statement piece of jewelry
Shootings
Butter
Special kind of idiot like Alec
See the bullet and put together
The TV
Is threatening him
Subliminal messages are being conveyed
Trying to taunt him that they're going to kill his hero
Right
She's doing everything I say
Infowars
Her body language seems unusually shaky during the press conference
Because she was telegraphing the presidential assassination
Could be because part of that press conference had to do with the death of her longtime Congressional coworker Elijah Cummings
That might Shake person up a little bit
Nancy Pelosi been in the House of Representatives
Hey, has it been there since 90
C96
It's 23 years the two of them work together to get legislation
Past perfect
Alex
That can't be true
Maybe they can all she wasn't out there
Literally only Alex
Picked up
I wanted to know more
I wanted to know more so I went over the Infowars article about this Theory
Amman
The evidence is overwhelming
Alright
He was killed in Dallas
Yes
Trump's rally rally was in Dallas
Falls Park
The only thing they get right on November 22nd 1960
C3
Don't worry about that Alex has you covered
Seems like it's not anniversary
So in the article which is posted before the rally the trumps life is in danger in Dallas
They have pictures of two calendars
One for October 1963
October 9th
You ready to have your mind blown
Okay ready
The 17th
The 17th is a Thursday in both years will freak out
Freak out
What
That's all but that's all they're gone
Yeah
No
Both ears
17th Thursday
Definitely
From the literal concept of October 17th
That October 17th was a Thursday in 2013 2006
1970s
President was either assassinated or attempt
Probably
This is stupendous stuff
This is
Is great
What
What an employee was like
Guys
Raiders page
October 17th is a Thursday
It's not okay
Not even 50 not the right match
Nellis Thursday
Right
Get some screenshots put it on the website we're good we're good it makes sense this is a good theory
Just so everybody in the writers room knows
By the way you're wondering guess how long
It is 8:45 clock out
If it got to be stuff like this
Calendar
Conspiracy
This is Bush League work
Just a definition of a zero everything not working
Something like this
I think people are leaving there's no byline on that it just says Infowars
Wrote that
Heavily edited
Calendars to look a very much faster than they otherwise would honestly feel like he would do better than that
I don't know I don't I don't
Just bad but I love it
I just f****** love it
Here's my here's my theory
They didn't even come up
That is totally something that some assholes posted online
And they just
Dejah screengrab 100% pop
100% possible but I still think it shows a lack of quality
Control
Going ever had good quality control to begin with
This being put in an article about how they're going to kill Trump
Is
Absurdly transparent
Situation here
Conspiracy
Keyboard
Project Camelot
It's sad
OSHA
Yeah
So we get around to Alex
Who now is
Favor of what Trump is doing in Syria
The Kurds
Yep is fully on wonderful
Find the Fab
First
Trump
Coming out
Animedia
Tannerite
British flag
Spitting on a getting a
Rally
The people who have Kurdish Flags
Although he was already
Already
He was already coming around to supporting whatever
That anybody
He was a
Pulling out whenever you talk Joseph
Right back
So he he raped
People with Kurdish flag
Antifa
Out of the
The Dallas rally
I'm not really interested in that at all Alex keep saying
Everything but the hours to bleep it all
Excuse for him
I'm not really interested in that I don't care
If that happen
Cuz I also don't think it happen
But I don't really care to argue that
Because as we
We hear this mix
Clip we find out how
Responded
They stunk
Like
I mean these people are
Surround the whole time
Call Shalonda the police
Despicable
Get out the guys I was with were either via former police
Like it was very
Despicable but it shows where America's gone
I don't believe this at all I don't believe any part of this story because Alex has spent
I don't know
When do they start becoming a buzzword
If they ever come up to him he's going to beat their ass
He has the perfect opportunity
He wants to kick the s*** out of that Pride
He doesn't
I don't believe any of this
He should take the s*** out of that person by his own mind just because
Think about all the publicity
Is bravado and masculinity
B
I did not just none of this track
The idea that you got hit
Spit on it he went to the police and please help us
Everything about him and everything he puts out to the world
Why would he be the person who goes to the police
Individualism and Nanny state
Bulshit
It's an interesting question
So a big big thing was yelling America's back at
Like I said he tried to get that Backstreet's Back
Alright
That happen
And although it's more believable.
What Alex says happened
8 demonic left
Watching people
From from
Boy looks like
Throwing holy water on Linda Blair in The Exorcist
Movie record
For the Democratic Party
Around
America's
What's wrong with
All I've seen
Video people suck
With Alex
I've seen
A couple instances of people like hissing
Lear there f******
I don't know
I don't think that
Has footage of yelling America's back of people's nuts flopping on the ground and hissing like demons
Debbie does
100% in Woonsocket
So
This is great
Coincidence
Grand mal seizure in history
Hideout
Probably not
Spoilers
Can hear about the situation with the Kurds and
Syria
Expresses that he's all for
Now it's well that's true
Public
Roblox
That place out
You would have any problem with that
Other languages
Cleansing
Root word
Those words are closer than October and November
But the 17th is a
Pretty f***** up to imagine
Alex
Is okay and supportive
More f***** up is he doesn't even really see
Seemed to deny the idea that turkey is going to go in and kill a lot of
He doesn't seem to
Care about
You get
He's only real response
And he makes this response
A couple times
Episode
And I think it is
And I want to spend some time
Done very well
Very very
And most importantly he's doing when he's shedding
That
Of the shower grape jelly the bunch of Clubs
The Curve
The media
80% of all religious persecution in the world
First Easter Christian
More than that
His only real angle on this
Isn't like refute or even
Seem to
Care at all about the actual situation
Why didn't you care about
Octonauts
Christian persecution around the club
I don't believe that it's
Nearly as high as Alex's saying because the reference but he's making isn't it
You and didn't put out a report on it and Catholic priest
Just said
Yeah
I think that's something that we lost track record
I'm not minimizing the idea that there are Christian
Into are in bad situation
And our being
Themselves
Absolutely
But
That is not a good
Excuse
I care about about what's going on in Northern
This is your fault
But almost a drawing a causal link between if you had been there for my perceived
Then I will be there for yours right here human rights is conditional
Its commitment to Human Rights is conditional
And that's a problem
It's not
Possible
No
At least it's not
Which is bad
So hook his behavior
In that time period and around that subject
He just lost another appeal
On that case recently
He says that it's not
True
Which is trying to get the case thrown out
And it didn't work so you peel the decision to not throw out the
Pushing back all of his stalling delay
Discussion tactics
To be like
Creating a straw man
Who cares
Even though he seems to be creating a
Completely fictitious version of what that lawsuit is about
When money falls
What
Basically those lawyers law firms
Izzy's Deli
Victimized by me
Which form of
There's an advertising formula
Haha
We covered that
How's the big news
Tom Arnold talkingshit
It's not big news
Do you know what else it's not the night
So
True Lies
Just, I don't care what tomorrow has
The issue with Alex advertising it's like
It's the idea that he profited off of
Slander
He doesn't understand
No I think he does
And he just doesn't want his audience to his best interest
Did this way I don't believe him for a second
In our 2013 when we got to the Boston bombing
The way he's so gleefully is talking about
Traffic
The way he's leaning so deeply Into The Sensational bulshit cover
Irresponsible
It is
Somebody probably
Could be sued for by people in those pictures that he found on 4chan
Is being led by the increasing traffic
I don't believe it he doesn't have some kind of a strategy know whether or not it's on paper or they have meetings about it
It's very clear that he recognizes when there are things that are popular
Eddie goes in that direction
Whether or not that's
Up to the standard of unjust enrichment I have no idea but
To pretend it's not a real phenomenon
It strains credulity
Big stories
You know
Big
Story yeah I'm pretty sure that was wasn't complaining that they were blaming
I tried to put out that book
Advertising
If you have
30hop
Yes Save
Pushed affect
Russiagate
Impeach
Trumpism
They are defraud
The General
Public as a consumer Flash
It's like that job famous Shabu
Great
So what are you talkin about is I guess
Trump
Demers
It's somebody
Trying to sue CNN based on James O'Keefe's latest stunt
I don't care I don't care at all
I didn't care to look into this
I don't have the patience
It's for it it's going to get thrown out
Today
Quite frankly I think I'm really interested in about this is Alex likes the idea of
A representative of the president or his campaign
That's not okay for him to control
Speech
Alex talks about things that are
Chilling Free Speech all the time
Have to think that this is falls under that
So you want to make sure that the media cannot report
It's not chili
Warmack is ice cold
He's complaining about us being in the middle
And shed
People Homewood
Direct contradiction to what
And reality that that too
Money that we saw
There's better ways that we could spend that
Yes and I don't disagree
Disagree with what
Talking about
Something that we could do
Okay
Bridges and
Remind Alex is a libertarian
What's 4
Not here
40 miles an hour
150 miles an hour
What the f*** are you talking about
To get on a train
Canon
50 minutes they were in town
Sam Houston
Go to the museum
Restaurants
150 miles an hour
70 years old
Houston
It takes 24 hours from now
We have had no infrastructure
Built
That's real
And Lasting
Since the 70s
It's Alex we're looking for president in recent times who agreed with him completely about shifting spending toward infrastructure to build
High-Speed Rail
That President Barack Obama
Really as big an advocate of High-Speed Rail
But if you said that it was Donald J Trump
Just made sure that there were stops at each of his hotels
34f
It seems like there would be so many good things that we could do if we just
Make our lives better too
He's game to every social progress that's still be terrible
Universal
Whatever
It's strange I've never heard Alex
Assistant efforts
The build-up high-speed rail network
Never talked about Republican governors in Ohio Wisconsin and Florida literally rejected Federal
Money being offered for goal
You see people like Alex want High-Speed Rail that they don't want the government paying for it
Or at least not Obama's government
They must prefer the fantasy of businesses building up his high-speed rail network the private sector
The government paying for roads
Like
Going
Never going to happen
Reasons why
Money is the root of all of
Without high-speed rate
Less money everything possible to keep
High-speed rail from
There's a reason so long to get somewhere by train now
Because the railway system this country has and has had for decades
That doesn't exist primarily to serve passenger needs
With the rise of the prevalence of the automobile in the greater accessibility to cheaper air travel
Nearly as much
And the commuter Focus rail Market became way less profitable and harder for companies
To justify starting is
Far back is the 9th
1830s
Most Rail lines prioritize Freight traffic
And this makes passenger rail
Subside sometimes you can end up having to wait for a passing freight train to go by at a Crossing
End up adding a bunch of times
Part and parcel of this is that most Rail lines are built to accommodate Freight traffic
And that's even though passenger trains are capable of traveling much faster they're Bound by the speed limits that apply to Freight travel
Because I operate differently would require an overhaul of many structural elements of
The tracks which again
No business has a financial incentive
Have to do
It just is no way
That this is going to become profitable for these busy
Operate differently
Freight traffic is what therapy
Business model is built on
That would be
So
Like
Part of this is just because
Oil and Automobiles
The 1930s
Bought up all the possible ways that a computer system could be built as a remor efficient and they would
They're trying to kill this
Think Alex might have had someone tell him about any
Durand
I think that might be what's up you got drunk at the gallop rally and someone told him about anyway
Cypress
Amtrak back to Missouri
Experience I really enjoyed
Being able to look out the side of its TV
Choosing
For the most part
Vevo you're on the train with art art Monsters then
If you're good even taking the metro to the like Milwaukee
United States
I think he's a real idiot if he thinks that any business has the kind of
Profit incentive
Ridiculous amount of financial losses
They would be required in order to pull it off
The only way we're ever going to have High-Speed Rail in this country is a massive publicly funded project
Sorry
Short of that the money is in Freight
And it doesn't seem like that Dynamic is going to change anytime soon
Advocating for this
So if you want to do that
Great
You gotta you gotta recognize
That you're drifting into socialist territory
Using tax money for all of this
Which seems to run counter
What ton of what Alex believes in
Concerned is love all of their closely held beliefs that were bought
But then when they come up against reality they have to find this weird
Push-backs
Weather
Let me twist my brain and
18 different
So I can get to you how the government
Can pay for it
But they won't
Add but they will but they're not and it's a good idea
Alex and I can probably find common cause
The ton of jobs
You'd have
An amazing thing that would come out the other side
Could get together a little bit on that
Right that's not what I'm arguing with
And then I can video of it later but I got to play.
I love the idea
The point I'm making isn't that I disagree with what he
I know enough about his beliefs
Never
Actually
Believe
Even if I guess you would have dropped presented it you just no matter what
Work
His brain around it but it's counter to
Just what he put the kids
We Act
Like he believed
I just I don't I don't trust
They don't know what they believe their
People pay other people to make them believe
Powdered milk
Kinko's
To do it
Absolutely
Chinese people and how they have braids
Subway
Somewhere
Miles away
It's almost a sacrilege
Is decided we're not going to have that anymore
Early in his presidency priority
Not all of them
Retire somewhere okay with
There was an impeachment just program going on
Well any success
That he had wood
Reflects poorly upon that
Yep we could have made this a priority when we had a president who was committed to it when he was pushing for this back in 2009
Massive progress
President with a communist infiltrator
They on we've learned that now he could have just
F****** got it
It might not have been the best thing to
To do though even though we now realize
Still doesn't
I still am not sure if
A gray top
It's a bit it's a bigger debate
I think it's
Probably true that
If you
If you ask
Actually do the things that are good for people
Even conservatives
Stay on the ground will be like
Oh yeah my life is better
Eventually some people come around.
Viewfinder
The result
If you're making
If the only people who are really getting mad or rich people then
You're doing it right
Images of potato
Seriously specific as to our current foreign policy
Primary thing is you guys don't care about Christian so I don't care about this child
Another reason why
He's totally cool with dropped
Perfect
Charge they've been doing
Since this war started 89 years ago they already had taken Arrow
So it's okay
Serie A
Western stereo
That's because the deal was made
20 mile exclusion Zone
Yeah did it so Alex is other defense
Is this is the other option
We didn't do this
There be more refugees
Right right
So that's good
Cuz he doesn't want to know demographic rate
It really does seem like foreign policy decisions
Trump this late
Either you lettuce
Kill all these people
Or we send brown people your way
And he was like
If that's actually the conversation that's happening as opposed to Alex's perception of it
That's f***** up
2-level I can't even begin to
Yep
He's going into the Plaza
Because of course
Want there to be more white people around
Relatively speaking
And so he starts talking
Going about
Fuji's bring
These countries
Absurd
The 40 girls in German
I go ahead and get yourself an adult
Muslim
Husband
Level 40
He is 24
My b****
Is a family show
The family show Jordan
Show
Hoof daddy what's cooking
Because it's just Alex saying that
I only care
If you cared about Christians account
Baddest
Mad Dog
Thinking about making jokes about Trump
Speech
And here's Alex
What is response today
Well Mad Dog
Islam
Because he's enough
Effete
Alright
It's so it's so
Pathetically
Consistent
Just anybody says anything bad about Trump
Just f****** the track
Just attack them
I'm honest
F*** Mattis
Fine like all of these people who come out after they've left the administration and then start talking s***
Right on board with the Nuremberg trials like you're you're the problem
I am so sorry I am part of the issue and I killed a lot of people and if it asks if it's not then people in the audience should have
A lot of points
Mayhem middle of their speech
I'm almost at the point
Listen
Just slink away
Well if we never hear from you again
Will all close our eyes will call it a day
You speak in public you going to
That should be the rule
In the hypothetical situation where he turns on Trump
It's like you go away
You slink away
Will never have to feel like you can help
Realized
The beginning no s*** but you can't so
Shut up
Administration
Scaramucci
Because I think he has something to bring to the table
You got it
Stitches go away
Turns out that the rally
Are showing up
And
And he wants
To do a challenge
Challenges
Call
From people who disagree with him
I think Trump should be in
How many do we get to
People that diss
Caldwell
The first
Rounded collars
What state
The first
Open the phone
To disagree with me
Really asking you
.
You know damn well no one who listens
A show is going to give you a serious disagreement about that
Anyone who disagrees with Alex is named
Yeah there's nobody at this point
No one's f****** list and if they are not calling in
This 88
Comical idea
So your question
We'll find out okay we'll find out.
Get ready to open up the phone lines and I don't know what the hell I don't know if he's like
His phone lines are like an old Camaro out in the cold we got to go turn it on at the house for an hour
Frost
You can do some serious damage
And then it is a long time
So he gets the rambling about other things
Have you found that there is a group
That has revealed
The climate change
Protest
It's not really about climate change it's all
A red herring
Just don't lie articles
Extinction Rebellion
Blocked everything around the world
Our sexuality app
Normal
Population
Stop
Normal
Climate
Them
And some weird
So get this group Extinction Rebellion
I don't know a ton about them I don't feel like I can say a pro or
Against strategy
Attention to approach
The video I don't know
There's a diversity of tactics
Six-letter probably required
In the world
First Extinction Rebellion is a Environmental Group it is existed for less than a year
And as best I can tell they have nothing
They were
They were founded last Halloween
The 17th wasn't on a Thursday last
Is it
Yap
Old medium post
Leandro
Activism isn't just about the climate specifically
But it's about
Fix astigmatism
Infected the way that we relate to each other as humans
This post is not a gotcha moment where the climate activist flips up and admits the climate-change concerns are real
Robin is just about forcing Alex
The kiss another man or whatever
It's about understanding the climate activism existed
Oven just being about climate
And honestly I think stuff like what this guy's talking about is really important
The path forward if we're going to take care of these issues and survives
Coexist
It has to involve greater social and class Justice
And equality
You run the risk of finding climate solutions that only serve to deepen
Between segments of society
It's important as Things become more serious too
To be deeply committed to solution
That don't Veer into Eco fascist territory
And that's what I see being
Expressed in this medium post
Straight people feel weird
The club of Rome
I think that it's
It's important think about those things
It's important to not view things
So
Granularly
Right you lose sight
Of the larger
I don't I don't know I'm not I'm not saying I fully support everything that this person
Believes are in
I don't see what you see
Sea hear now
You don't need this
And they don't need to have
Can you believe it
Okay
Watch The Good The Bad and The Ugly
Internalized
Travel to Faraway place
Alright
What a shock
Key lime tequila
I am being told
So that's good
Cuz there's not many people calling in
Which is not too surprised
Got drunk
Put a million-dollar bounty on the opposing counsel in my Sandy Hook lawsuit
Sure
They say that I encourage
Violence cuz I said I wanted his head on a spike
Encourage violence
You're slightly differently
Interesting
Suggestion of how the globalist
Can win
Alright
What's it there
Cliche I want this one
Patriots
Assaulting a ration
Is the violent one
And
Did
What I Hear here is a silly
Scary
Because I'm old enough to remember
When I do.
Hillary Clinton
And I remember that Alex
The false flag
I hear in 1 hour
Almost there wink
If someone kills these people
It's jumped the globalist doing it to set us up
Yep just so consistent in his career but it's always so
Jarring in the present-day and talk about hypothetical
Murders that could happen
I do most like a we got your back
Yeah I know that's not what you saying
But there's a way you can hear it that way a little trouble
If you did it though he would
But for anybody who killed one of his enemies
Volkswagen tempted order to make his day
Cover for you if you did that he's just saying that
You know he would
Cover you if you did that
You already know it doesn't
Deez Nuts
But you know it you know it
Right and I don't necessarily like
Persuasive or would get someone to
Do something
Put it is a strange thing to be like fully aware of
Show
At least on a subconscious level understand that
I don't know
And he was saying
Wait real quick
I didn't see the end of the rally
Doesn't happen
Anniversary
Nothing happened
But Alex got yelled at by
A leaf
Kurdish flag
This next wave is really into
Because
Deeply racing
But in a
Like it don't literal words
Are him he's trying to argue that he's not right
Right spot
In the way he makes his argument
He shows and reveals
A deep races
No
But it's also important to point out that I don't believe
No I believe it's an imaginary scenario that Alex's
Is constructing to tell his body
To demonstrate that he's not racist
Reveals deep races
Stop
Because this was
TitleMax
They really believe that
Local time to keep Infowars on the air
Cut off my break
Hispanic and black
Largely antifa
They're being directed by the higher-level smart
Call
I know from contact when he talks about this he always calls them like white meth head
There's a hierarchy
Structural
People are directing things around
There's there's a white supremacy and his false version of antifa
Is revealing that they are racing
Haha
Though because they obviously don't and he is imagining that that is how
Obviously would go that's one that's one part of it is the conception of these
Non-white
Being so dumb
White Overlord
Bucked up
So congratulations
Revealed
A insanely race
View of the world
Heard a racist
Once
Try to convince me that they were not racing
Without doing it
Racist Lee
It never happened does seem it doesn't never happened
Even when there
Trying to lie
He tried to be like
I don't hate black people because Bubba Bubba
And I never say the n word
Yeah.
Alex imagine that he was
No really slipping
Sound by minority antifa people over to the side of Liberty
Absolutely not
But also like I said there was a gun and
Hear about that and then either not talk about it or say it was a false flag
Orsay
Totally different perspect
And he was wearing an Infowars shirt
Sure
Under his jacket
But they sure
Deal the yeah
How do I wonder why
Guy with a gun and body armor it as Trump rally
I got I mean technically and text it's not illegal to have body armor on unless you're a felon
I have body armor
Sure
I don't think the guys doing anything illegal
Not good
Probably also if someone on the left
Without protesting in body armor
Like I would still say like
When you do that
You highly
Haley escalate the opportunity
And I I just don't think it's healthy I really don't
The only
That makes sense
This is when the escalation has already occurred without
You know like with the Black Panthers
In The Sticks
Steve
Around arms
Watching the cops different
The escalation was already passed long before they ever got there
You're just at a f******
Stadium
With a bunch of people who you like
Expecting
That's all that's going on
Primitive
Premeditated murder
Describe the clothes off at
It's not bad to scratch
Alex I think really get to the core of
His feelings about Trump
And that is it
I love Trump
F*** I want to get back on
That's really all I do
Buddy's not stood up
The persecution of acid
Beat up outside
Because he thinks that will scare
And he needs to speak out against
They don't do that
I want back on Facebook baby
You started it with I love Trump made me hope for just one second that he would then
What I want
It's all being attacked and that's just filler
Optics
So that is happening
To the point where he can use that in order to get more attention
Problems
But yeah so
Call still are coming in
No that's the problem
Got to listen to this
Remind me to supposed to be on and you never showed up
The 17th was a Thursday
Linda Barnes
In his rambling Alex
Tries to nationalize
The Drudge is having more negative coverage restaurant
He needs people like I said I I believe this
I don't know what it means it's going to break
But I do know that Alex
Turn on
There's just no way
Make the argument that
Which is rarely
I think it's pretty boring.
I love the idea that
Do you have the anime
Context of demonizing them to support Trump
It's a little different
B
I know people don't want to hear a radio show that is regardless of any circumstances
He makes at all my old positions
It is a little boy
Calendar
Conspiracy and Alex
Call cuz this is great
This is
Alex goes with First Call
You got say you want some
I thought initially that that might be someone playing audio of
Turkish
Nike Air Raid
I thought
Like someone
Might have troll Dalek
I wasn't playing at audio
Could be anything
I'm not sure audio Russia
Whatever you want
I realized
I'm probably overthinking this cuz Alex tries to go to another call
Oh my goodness you're welcome
No
Okay
You know what to do
Got to know when to fold them
When to walk away
You got to know when to run
No more calls and wow
Differently around noon
I love not being able to do my job
Too long
Without
Getting the phones
What episode
Maybe a couple episodes but this is too long
Yeah I am in there is that and then also you know you add that to like the not being able to play Clips whenever
They're supposed to be playing up and all that stuff
And then you added to the calendar bulshit
This operation
It's falling apart feels like if you turn the cameras around it
Just Rex
Running back and forth
From station to stay
It leads me to suspect
Possibilities
Is of him trying to sell off the warehouse to cash out
Steam light
Yeah
I don't know if that's the case but it just
Possibly
We have a full staff staff that was there six months ago a year ago
Like a different production
The alternative is
Whatever he was paying for like the phone
The experts
Run
Ability to take calls
He's now we can't afford
Or they decided
Occasion
Something here in Decatur
A deterioration of his
No I got it
Interference
That's what it is
That's why I can't take a pulsar weather we all know
It's just a glitch
Your calls
It was just hung up
Do the two callers who disagree with you think Trump should be impeached
Weird
Weird how there's a strange glitch while the people who are probably going to tell you to go fuc yourself
I don't necessarily Alex
Fake the glitch
In order to not talk to these people but it's weird
Unfortunate
Tell off some people
I don't know I've listened to the show long enough to know that whenever he gets it
Defending call is usually like your thoughts
You should be calling for Hillary to be hung love your product
Do I take them all every morning
And here's the thing
I agree with you
Yeah it's either that or like why do you dodge the
The Jewish question
Alright
Cell phone lines aren't working
Sommore
Play some special reports
Cuz he has nothing
How many Rambles but how you shouldn't win the lottery
Europe
How swimming pool dozen occasions every year
Combination
It's hard to find Chasers
Where people get
You'll never hear about those
And everything is fine. It's not a story anyone tell
You don't hear about it
A physical
Money and success
Will destroy you faster than
Black
Who's your daddy
Probably
Rockstar graphic
Helping
What about Trump
That's what we've known about Trump since his entire career
Nobody helps people
Donald
Jay
It's so amazing
Go to go on a little bit of a Jag that out on earned money is somehow
Even though he has no skills or talents
Very weird
Alex has mostly play special reports cuz
Really wanted to talk to callers cuz he probably didn't
Do too much preparing use out late at the rally and
He never prepares anyway
The other particular Special Report we're going to hear about in the
This last clip
Pretty much
But this is interesting because like
We've done
Investigation
No how he came
Support Trump
We've listened to a lot of different time periods of his career
And
I could hear
Somebody who doesn't know
Those things
Hearing this
What about this special report
I hear this
Galaxy
Go f****** f****** self
We got to get some bleach on this year
Brainwashed liberals
Brindle
Brainwashed liberals like Alex Jones in July 2015
Brainwash liberal
Like gangster
It's crazy
It's just like there's no
Sincerity there's no context
Text there's no through-line to any of this
It just is what it is
Bootlegging
It is
Rationalize
A hundred percent
There's so many there's so many things now where I
Can't
Albert
See you in my head
All of these propagandas reading anti-trump
S*** and then just
Crossing out bad adjectives and a damn good one
Not even not even that
The antonym
The exact opposite of what it is you know like I'm stupid
Cost it off and change the world
That means that he took his time thinking about it
I don't like f******
Whatever it's all just meaningless
I find
It's very little interest except for the areas where it's
Psyquel
This might be relevant
As things get bad
And then also
Bike
I think
Really interest
The CDs
Diminishing quality
Instance
Like that Trump is going to get killed at Dallas rally
Tech problem
Like I
Increasing inability to do this job well
Like
Bad propaganda
If he's still on air
Couple months from now
How is that
Deterioration going to
It's going to keep going
Naya Impossible 4
I just think like a cup
4 months from now this could be
Comically bad
And I look forward to that.
Does predictable trash
Whatever Trump says repairs
You can't get rid of them
I do have this question in my mind that it's impossible to answer
Necessarily
Howard Alex
Respond to Trump bombing
Getting drunk crying Trump shows Isis
Lakewood that happened
How is it possible that there's something
That will reach that point
I don't know
Maybe couple months ago I would have said yeah you probably would respond
I don't know now
I really don't
The idea that he could.
Fourth on that and so like
I lead me to believe that there is
There isn't
Now I think
Gone
Sometimes
To surprise me so I don't know
President episodes in a row
Apologize
You do not need to
Different on Wednesday
Vanderbilt website
Built it
Jordans
Into the show please go to iTunes
For sure send it to your friend if you have a brother
Goodfellas
That's a family shop but tell them I'm Neo
I have the Ides of October 17th
Alex
Kristen color