I have great respect for knowledge by now I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Aliexpress.com
Everybody just a little bit
About
Jordan Jordan
Let me answer a quick question
For you
Did you ever have a
Specific affect
Like a hat that you wore all the time that you would like when you tried to change
Your personality by some sort of outward appearance baby yeah I think so probably probably had a lot of
I did Little Things
Like one off
But what if things I did in high school was I had a lot of shiny shirts
Shiny button-up shirts and I was over my head like flaming dice something
Alright okay
Alright I don't know exactly what I was thinking
There was a it was a Guy Fieri before you existed kind of vibe
But also weighs
Shinier
New habitable arable weird beard
High School
I didn't ever weird beard
Small beard
Small tents will be rats also shave the mustache
Daughter my Mennonite heritage
I got called everleigh
Stop it
Time all around
Everlast
That is the guy from Smash Mouth again
Because that Guy Fieri
Proper place among
If timing is indifferent I probably would
Guy Fieri a lot but Sarah
Oh yeah I think I'm
I think you should be grateful that you missed that time
Yeah I did probably I'd I know that I had a bowler hat for a little while as well but I don't think I ever
It never really took over too much as like a part of my personality
You tried the bowl I did drive the bowler hat
And then the other social Gatherings or is like a work
I wore it to like a homecoming
School dance
Skyrim Rusty
Brewing tractor
Believe me
Rusty Drew is Dad on the car dealership in Columbia and
Use a big dick
I didn't really even know him he was a great older than me and he just
Got in my face looks like hey are you man enough to wear that hat
It's a fucken bowler talkin about
Why you got to pick on me what's going on
Arable
Are you mad
Shoulder bags
That was one
Alligator leather shoulder strap bag
You call that an affectation
Instead of wearing a backpack
I'm feeling a little bit about the stations that are unsuccessful and I know a lot about
And I only know what you tell me about both my
Rio cuz all your expectations have been successful every one of them I believe
I'm glad you had such an easy pass through LOL
No I tried I tried
The old
Fedora for a while cool
Kids books
Absolutely
Episode to go over kind of a Wacky Wednesday thing
Hello
All right kind of shirt
Halfway in the pool halfway out of the
Signed up and are supporting the show
Today we got in front of us
A murder of walks
Yes
So sign up and we appreciate it very much the first of all Scott thank you so much
Next Jodi
I'm a policy wonk
Next breath
Text David thank you so much
You are now a policy wonk
Text Kristen within a thank you so much
You and I will probably want
Make a piston with Tristan with an a
What
Read for the m
Christian
Alright
Next
One guy few thank you so much
Text Ashley Lynn
Next
Succubus Queen Amber thank you so much you an alibi was he want
And finally they don't actually
So she would be president
It's not a democracy through public
Exact
Then finally ghost
My Robin thank you so much
I'd rather listen to take inhaler like what these guys do like sport the show you could do that by going to our website
Show
Appreciate
Baby lovey
So Jordan
Today August
Sudo wacky 1
Yes
I was racking my brain
In preparation
So try to come up with what
We could do
For Wacky Wednesday
Episode number of possibility
Ever brought up a number of times in the past I think I've about reached my point of disinterest in Kerry Cassidy and project
And a couple of interviews of hers that I listen to to like train
Chart a course that we're pretty uninspiring
So I consider the possibility about doing another episode about Kevin Moore
The guy was making a documentary about Carey's best friend who's in prison for murder mark
He started releasing his new docu-series about people who Channel aliens and spirits
But decided maybe I should go
Give that a shot
It's called they call us channelers
They do not some people do
Not if you're interested in
Otherwise seemingly normal people do terrible alien Impressions and talk super vaguely about standard new age
Flash self-help ideas
This is the damn show for you
But ultimately it didn't feel like something Worth Art
There's not a whole lot to be constructed
Discuss about people pretending
And that would ultimately just to end up with us mocking them
Which is kind of fun but maybe not the best Bedrock for an episode
Yeah we it's it's kind of like a flow state
In the world
Frolic amongst
These people
You know things are far darker and more serious
Where in the where in the DC Universe we're not in the Marvel Universe and there's also a feeling of like
Alright
A time to talk
F****** till apples
10 years from now we'll look back on this and be like I wasn't this stupid
Whatever
So also I buy a mother Avenues
And I've said in the past that I didn't want to cover Skype
Kelly ever again
But I stumbled into a little video that he put out
If you if you were called this
The guy who claims those demonic forces that have a base underneath the
The Getty Museum
Killing children there to harvest
Whatever that is I recall loose factored heavily into that up
Episode and I would never adequately
Lowe's
So
For a while
Steven Kelly was trying
The Coop the qanon audio
Trying to get them into his side
I think he's moved on from that now and just putting out weird videos where he talks about battles he and his Jedi followers
Girls are having deep underground Wild
Sitting in front of us
It's all pretty disturbing
Wingstop
Baby clear I don't want to cover that dude ever again
And cuz he scares me
He looks like killer Bob from
From Twin Peaks videos of sitting in front of a sheet looking at the camera and rambling
Menacingly
About mindwar and also fairly often about how he's not so into
It's not it's not good
The premises that premise sounds fun but then you realize there's always the undercurrent of racism underneath and it gets
Dark but the racism in the anti-Semitism is like
That makes it
Relevant to possibly still talk about
Tendrils and where they go
But
I just
Now it's a mess
Add another issues that Stephen Kelly is a very small audience
I guess YouTube videos all hover around 1,000
Views and it just doesn't feel like a
Great use of our time to make fun of him
It just seemed
Again
Go to do your Jedi Mind
Mind Wars
And whatever
Hey Anthony. He's on the more successful side
The space weirdos that I was looking
Considering
A cover for the show that
The problem is a way we can't Frolic anymore so much
Similarly we can't really
Just that take any old video on YouTube and feel good about ourselves
So
I felt like I'd hit a brick wall
But then it dawned on me
Brick wall
Yes
Episode all about the manufacture of bricks
If punching down is concerned
And there's one obvious solution
That problem
How does this grab you Jordan
Gilmer rotor for you
Call me
It's a very common request
Listeners that we tap into the catalogue of coasttocoastam
And I've resisted the urge
To do so after this point mostly because I was perfectly satisfied with the Paranormal space weirdo stuff that we cover
Project Camelot in the rafters with all they really need it
But I thought well is gone dry and we've gotten a pretty good idea of what's underneath Kerry Cassidy
Mostly Sovereign citizen ideas
Is encoded racer
It feels like we need to move on to greener pastures
And there is no Greener pasture than post
To Coast AM
Will never need to worry about punching down
They have millions of listeners in the show is basically and it
Institution at this
We will literally
Never come close to the level of success
But they have
So we can mock
Freelee
That's a big
I like that
This will be a new Venture on the show and I intended to be an ongoing Series so I apologize if this episode in particular isn't going to cover
A lot of the background information
About Coast
The coast and George Noory in great detail
To save those for a future episode
Because I think the best way that we can make our transition
The world of Coast to Coast AM
It's by way of familiarity
As we learn to listen
Coming to Alex's shows on the days after the Boston bombing
Alex was a guest on Coast to Coast
On April
The day after the tragic
Now that we're equipped with a bit of the
Open understanding about what Alex is bring to the table on his own show
Thought it might be interesting
See how he was presenting
Take himself on a different show
A show with a way bigger audience
Ensign his
And a show
It's hosted by a Friendly House
As opposed to someone who is likely to call him out on his b*******
I think that looking at Alex's appearance
On the April 16th 2013 episode of Coast to Coast AM
Might be a perfect way for us to dip our toes into the water
And that's what we'll be doing
I'm here today
Sudo Wacky Wednesday
I know you put it very kindly
Broke up with Carrie
Yeah I think that's what I heard I heard you say it's time to move on
Damn this
I know
How is
Just like a man
To get a modicum of Fame and then leave his
Old girlfriend behind for the vase
Barry can't compete with that I don't know Project Camelot I know you got me through some hard times sure
Look look how hot coasttocoastam is I can't pass this up
I don't like you presented that way but there may be some truth to it
Maybe some Underground
I'll still check back in whenever she has Mark Richards on or let's say there's a
There's breaking news in the Eddy page world
Bringer of death absolute Archangel Abaddon news
Got to keep up
That's just our journalistic dude
I think I think
Might be a much better
I have a
I have a working
Theory about coasttocoastam
Pickle flash out over the course of
Not just this episode with other episodes with you about it that I take
I think it's a very important
Spoke
Maybe even a centerpiece
Of the wheel
These are cryptofash
We'll get into that as we go along
But let's let's jump in your this April 16th episode
George Noory
Host of coast to coast
Coast to Coast
Giorgio moroder put me in a great mood
Think about the previous day
Is bobbing
George Noory
Hi George
Law enforcement officials have no concrete information on hoopla
Finish Line of the Boston Marathon
Hospital
Situation
So you know you can already here like I just
Much better Brock
You can see the the the chop
The Voice
He has a warrant
Qm
Alex doesn't have
Yeah.
Never let
Oh yeah
What's this song
I truly don't know what you're talkin
Well I wish I prepared differently then I assume that you would have some
Familiarity with just such a cultural in
Turn on the radio for f****** ever
But one of the things that doesn't really difficult about
The idea of us dipping our toes in
I'm trying to do like an
All income
Episode about
Coast to Coast
Is the
It's had a number of hosts over the year
Okay like
Art Bell's era is very different than George Noory
There's a lot of complex
YouTube
And so that that's why I would want to leave
I got the gradual getting into it
Put all you really need to know is George always going to be
But I got you
Much better broadcaster than where you
Got you some of that is
Almost
Even more Danger
Because as we
Just hear 30 seconds of his voice
Come here a welcoming there's a there's a
Performance to his voice that is
Is there a Old School radio this guy is welcome you into the show when he's friendly
Your smile in his voice
I heard that and I thought of one of those old like
Big box
Radios then the family would sit around and
240Z
You know one of those Jaya
But I don't know what
Just Cabinets
Filled with
Yeah
So Alex isn't on the show right at the beginning
George has another guest
Who is a psychiatrist
Who they talk about hate
And the experience of hate
It can overwhelm a person not really that important
But I'm going to play Clue. And that is because
George Noory is sort of spitballing
About who might have been behind
This bombing
Okay no that's not that's not a good idea
Well it's what a lot of broadcasters and and commentators
We're engaging in
Perhaps Fair
Speculation
Runs rampant
Sometimes
They're big news stories
I don't think that his behavior is
Too irresponsible
But I do think that Alex would see this as very
Responsible
What's assume for a moment that the situation Boston was caused by
Individual necessarily a group
That has some kind of political ideology
Who's just ticked off
Innocent people
So you got George Noory speculating that it's a lone wolf
Okay maybe it's someone who's angry at the government baby
Yeah it's he's talking to his psychiatrist Peter breggin
About the nature
Like I said it's largely and unnoticeable interview and I don't have much
To say about it other than to point this part out
A leader in the field of the anti medications
Psychiatrist
Call God
You may not be as crazy dude is most of the anti-science guest Alex will have on his show
Guest choice
Is an editorial decision important to remember no s***
In that clip weirdest list
Nori is trying
Bragging about how person
I hate so much as to pull off a bomb in
But in the process
Nori's speculating that the bomber was a lone wolf and the example he comes up with his
Maybe they did this pic
The government
Which weirdly
He doesn't think as a political motive for they're not with any group
It's just a lone wolf who's angry with the
Tiger government's anti-government political
Very strange
That might imply a slight bias
Could could
It's it seems like
I can recognize this is a person speculating and having a conversation
Abstract
But Alex
Cannot
This is exactly the sort of behavior he spent days on a
Show claiming as evidence
Set the Main Street
BT is planning to blame right-wing Patriots for the bombing
Is Alex at any intellectual
Consistency human yelling at George Noory about I was trying to set up the paper
We don't hear that sort of thing
Imagine that's because Alex is welcome as a guest on Coast to Coast AM
A place like MSNBC don't have any interest in books
This is very
Tensional do this same exact behavior that your decrying in the rest of the
The media is something that nor he's doing and you're going to be on the show in 20 minutes and talk to him about how he's the greatest
I mean
Yeah it's obviously
But it gets worse
George Noory speculates a little bit
Would have been bigger
A little more
Well you know they're saying that they that studies pressure cooker bombs
You don't have to have
Come out of the
Pakistan
Yeah yeah so I mean not obvious
A little bit out of my ex
Expertise
But
I don't have the answer to that one knowing it's going to be important to find out I'll be
A military person I mean
What if it was somebody who
You talk about rainbow about hatred and
So Alex is also spent all this time talking about how the mainstream media is trying to demonize returning veterans
Hey could be our guy who people at Rainbow
I don't know
Guilty of literally all of the behaviors Alex's grieving about to be what if it was
Literally
Charles Bronson
Not the film version of Charles Bronson
Play the regular Charles Bronson
Chickenshit
Government
Nobody's hiring them for the Deathwish films anymore
He did it I would like
To say that
We could be bronze
Is he was dead at this point could be alive right now
Or he could have died in
What was it
The Wild Bunch
Movies
You might not have been in it might have been
A hologram for a look-alike I have no idea
No one besides me who's ever seen all five of them
He died
I could be wrong
Could be
So it's not only
Play George
Sing about the ape
Possibility
That's
Returning veteran
Is while he's talking to this psychiatrist
He opens up the phone
Takes calls
And one of his callers
Has a theory at this Jordan if you pay close attention
Is a really wild thing
Because
This caller
As best as I can tell
Fix that the motivation
For the bombing
Might have been someone who is angry
At leg
And I'm thinking what kind of person
Well I think it went like this
What did runners run with their legs
They fix the vines and places at the
People in Olathe
Ex-serviceman with an amputee
And I love all the servicemen God bless Amaya to chandan the service years ago
And about had to be someone with the love yourself
I got a view
And it's supposed to have have no conscience
I think he's a loner
That's what I think happened
George Lopez
We've got too many True Crime shows on right now that's what it what I'm hearing there is somebody putting together a Law and Order
It's almost supervillainy inmate search
Cartoonist
Do you sew
Positive with people every single things I got the great thought
That is his patronizing almost in his support of people's ideas
Hey yeah I think we should look into that lie
What she said that if you have all these amputations
Eddie George himself there all night
That was
My favorite he will literally talk about someone whose arm was a
Okay so
Is jumping along with okay I got a picture of George Noory now
I think I know what I'm getting into whatever picture you have Adam mustache and your goal
Alright
I got you some sort of husky
He's helping her build the argument
Yeah you know what you're
It could be a disgruntled legless man and hiding bones in a wheelchair I didn't
Consider that but you ladies you could have
Part of me thinks that would make him like the best dad ever
It's just so supportive
No
Baby supportive but also it doesn't it doesn't
The best equipped
To deal with people who might
Might have
Bad faith
They write become opposition of like
I want to manipulate
If you have someone like him who
It's just like
What combination is Steamroller
Wiwik
Fairly certain
Don't know for sure but we can be fairly certain that
She doesn't have
Some sort of
Anti a
Beauty agenda that she's trying to turn public opinion against specific amputee I don't think so
That would be crazy
Behaving this way and non-judgmental Ian on abusively towards collars
I think you have a pretty good
Pardoned by using the term O'Lakes
To stand on
For George
They cannot
Attacking her for this and being like
That's kind of being a gracious host
Keep the dick to your audience
When that behavior is so Universal and apply to all of these gas
That you have
If it
That's where it becomes a little bit murky
For me
But I appreciate that you
Use understood what was going on there and see that that is a perfect encapsulation of Joker
Doll legs
It's all lyrics
It's so easy origami it's all legs North
That could be turned it back
Just be like
They were all Jews like you can totally see how easy that that little transition is because
Cuz he's not trying
You're bad guy
If like after the Oklahoma City bombing
You know or 911 when they the rumors are going around the Jews were told to stay home from work
I have no idea
Episode
You could see that same sort of inability to
Push back
Yeah
Introduced
As you could see that could apply in situations
Then you'd like
To his credit
He does also seemed
Genuinely curious
I don't know about that
Maybe not listening
Then I guess I did not get a perfect encapsulation I think you might be. Actively listening to his guests
Point Mallard
You guys are real hearts
To pull out with they're all like no you don't get
You do don't you got to remember that they are tall legs and then still say that they are all a very simple to do while you're
Passively listening
So we get now to Alex's production
This is a little bit
A little bit glowy
All kinds of world issues
Department of Homeland Security
So we wanted to get Alex in here to talk about his
Propaganda narratives
Yeah let's let's really get to the bottom of it
I'm going to give him a real real tough interview are we
Proof
Because
This is not an unbiased energy
This is not like somebody who's bringing in Alex
To get to Greater truth
You can hear even from as this introduction goes on
These two dudes are compared
Is
Infowars.com
The foremost media
Alex is recognized
As the father of the truth movement
And that he is a digging reporter
Alex Jones
That's what I did when you come on my little show
George it is great to be here to talk about the globalist
Masterplan the biggest
The long-term there's lots of distractions going on
Lots of things happening at the media are hyping up
But you you look at the big
Be a big issue
So that doesn't seem like that. That's friends
Yeah Yeah Yeahs are at least
It's a supposed to being just like
Get his take on things
Yeah that's
That's a weird
Have not heard some
He's considered one of the founders of
The 9/11
Truth movie
In that kind of positive and loving total good long lines at the head of the foremost mean
Journalist
The f*** out here
So
And then you also hear Alex
Get it like on my little show
There is almost like a
Nothing compared to your van
He's learned lesson
Arab butter up in
Flattering person that you want something from
Namewee access to Their audience
You're just seeing Alex place.
Yes yeah yeah that is interested
Yeah
The kind of know what they're doing
So Alex Alyssa
Georgia
The show the night
Before and Siri talks about that
We probably do need to spend a few minutes
On the tragedy of it being regardless of what really happened whoever was behind it
After all of those I listen to you last night
Break that down eloquently with your gas
Of all the people there and then then and so many going to the trauma of just watching
So on the night of the 15th George Noory did a show that was just about the attack
What happened
I applaud him for having a large chunk of open phone time for callers to call in and just
Experiences
Just kind of like him offering up a public forum for his audience to collectively process their grief and let it happen
I think the radio shows should do stuff like
B positive
On the other hand I absolutely do not applaud him for his guests choice
I'm at night no worries only guest was Infowars regular Doug Hagmann
And a large part of his narrative on disappearance was about how this supposed
Bomb drill
Marathon in order to make the argument
This is a false flag
The headman was on on the 15th on coasttocoastam
Pushing for this narrative
Hagmann is a far-right and
Happy communist lunatic
Disseminates information through group
Started call Dean Dorothy
Least intelligent
Throughout the years he's been in
Entirely wrong about
Cowboys bombshell stories
These claims were based on unnamed but very real and very credible intelligence source
His career has completely Fallen apart by the present
And now you host a show on YouTube or as guest roster includes Coach Dave daubenmire
Appearances by Steve Quayle
The guy who Alex thinks is a prophet
Has written multiple books about how biblical
Giants are real
You can't prove they're not
I don't have to
The well then
The burden of proof is on the person making the extravagant playing
You'll be you'll be sorry when my Giants show up
I will I'll close them and they'll
Step on you I certainly will be sorry at that one
The day of the Boston bombing Was a Very Berry 10
And if you're a person who has a large audience
You have a responsibility
You can't just let them be misled by con men while they're in that vulnerable state
And to do so is to be actively complicit in
In the car on your self
And I'm sure George Noory a Doug Hagmann booked in advance
This was just bad timing
But I don't give a fo
If you have Hagmann booked
And there were bombings like this you got to say that something like eight Doug we're going to reschedule
There are 100 100 acceptable
Excuses and goddamn George Noory holds all the cards
These dicks
Almost donut
Exist compared to coasttocoastam when you're judging by Audio
Size and influence
What he says goes
What I'm getting at is that nor yet every reason to cancel Doug Hagmann
Appearance on the day of the bombing
He didn't because he thinks
Doug Hagmann
Is a credible source
And wants to help spread is bulshit far and wide
These are structural editorial.
Decisions that run
Under the surface of a show like coasttocoastam
And they're a big part of the reason why
As it exists with George Noory
This show is a trojan horse
For the very propagandist who are now currently running a buck
And have
Caused so much
Disorder
Is it like George
Story himself
Actively complicit in this yes I mean
Sorry
Open Agent on this or is it there or does he have some
Booking manager Endeavor collaborate himself 100
Yeah okay
Alright I have no doubt about that bass on every
I know about him
That's something we'll probably get into it if you
What's bucks up with this weirdo thanks
It's all legs
I'm really trying to push for someone
So just in the month of April 2013 George Noory lent his gigantic platform to
Familiar names
Alex Jones
Jerome corsi
This is posts
Boating I should point.
And soon-to-be Infowars employee at that point Anthony gucciardi
That's a lot
Guest bookings
Of people who are directly Infowars contributors and they also had
Sebastian Gorka
His family on
The song like what are what are we doing here
Welcome to Coast to Coast AM I guess today is a Hungarian who knows Gorka
You can do the next few months
After April 2013 you see appearances by Steve Quayle Webster Tarpley
Steve pieczenik was on
Weis
Catherine Albrecht
Who filled in for Alex
That when he went on vacation recently for almost the entire week shoes on
Auntie tax protester Joe Bannister
Bilderberg fanfiction
Expert Daniel estulin
William Binney
Mike Adams
And even more appearances by Alex
Jerome corsi
It would be easy to say that this is a radio show that has a very serious wedding problem
But that's absurdly night
These are intentional choices made by producers and Nore himself
To have these people on
Despite the very clear reason
Not too
They're Liars
Coast-to-Coast while Charming at times
At least it I am part exist
To mainstream
Invoices like
And to introduce them to a giant
Gullible platform
Either way that makes
Incredible
That alone would be really shity
Better be like
You know
But the fact that Nori would have Doug Hagmann on the day of the bombing
And Alex on the day after
Is inexcusable
Yeah that is in that says everything
End of that
Space
The game it's not like he needs ratings
It's not like he needs
Stunts for rating
You could do an open line
Show about ghosts
Or something
Did you guys see anything on the woods ever hit Millions
People love coasttocoastam
There's no reason
Start book
And be like hey you know what
There was just a f****** terrorist attack
Let's get Alex to Yellow
To get her
Yeah only serves Alex's interest
And that's an editorial choice
Sound like a broken record on this
Editorial choices
Are important
Whenever you
Have a show like this
So George Noory wants
On the bombing
Don't know why so much
Why would someone do something
He already had a psychiatrist. He said it was
Sure
Problem-solve
Seems like a pointless question to ask Alex
You know that Alex thinks is a false flag and you want him to soft pitch
Into the
Absolutely
Organized group
What would make someone
Focus on them
The loss to make trillions of dollars invading countries and selling robots every city 25
Nonexistent mom and there's a lot of issues
So did that
That explanation can't apply to
Anybody bout to go out
It's like okay I can see lust for power that's maybe maybe
Celeste at the media pants
Keno Lottery
People wanted
Reality Tea
Are there trillions of Dollars around the world that one is released
Invading countries of salad robot
They could be applied to let's say Al-Qaeda or from North
Carolina.
None of that is possible unless your underlying implication is that it was the global
So
Great
Alex
Talks about his
About whether or not
Conspiracy
And we know from listening
Alex's show on April 15th and April 16th
E.com absolute
So it's interesting to hear
How moderate he is
In another forum
You know I have the New York Times here in front of me
April 28th
Hatch by the FBI
And the New York Times talks about
Just a few cases but there's hundreds
The government going out and finding mentally ill people
Anybody could do that
And then giving them the weapons and and pointing them in the direction
Depart of Heroes and I'm not saying
That's what's happened with this case but I do know this
There were 4000 great National Guard out there great men and women
Not part of the conspiracy and there is one
Out there trying to protect people but violate the Fourth Amendment searching bags and running
Checkpoints
So that's interesting
It's an interesting
They're not part of the
Conspiracy if there was there was that strange
How can you
You don't know there is a conspiracy which means
By definition you can't know if they were or were not a part of it that's secondary
Concern what is that on his own show hours earlier
Coasttocoastam
Seemed a little bit
Right now I mean that's
That clearly obvious
Immediately wrote down my nose is how Brazen this is
Is knowing full well that nobody's going to be going back and forth from
Maybe Show 2 a.m.
For the being like
But no one's going to do that and I'll try to
He is to get as many
People from the coast to coast audio to him if you lose some
After that point
That's fine
Let's say you loses 60% of the people who come over
Yeah that's 40% is still going to be much larger than the amount of people that would come over if he got on and started yelling
No one's going to check into
They're not
Then right
So is it a strategic decision
On his part it's very obvious
Yes absolutely so about that New York Times article Alex wants to argue that the FBI
F***** up an inappropriate methods to generate terrorist arrest
Most likely to justify their funding I'm willing to listen to him
Loses me is when he tries to connect that to
To the very not very real Phenomenon with
Actual terrorist attacks
Have been carried out
Is New York Times article that Alex is referencing here is specifically about
Pretty much exclusively
Muslim ban
Who have indicated an interest in committing a terrorist
Worthington snared by the FBI who helps facilitate an artificial attack
In order to eventually arrested
Personally I think this is a f*****-up practice and a waste of resources
But it's super important to point out that these people who are disgusting this New York Times article are not people who act
Actually carry out
That's a bridge that Alex needs
To build if you want
See you this idea to support his false flag argument
Everything I could tell you spell to do that
The larger point though
Izzy you can see it
Wheatley different Alex
This show from the Galaxy song
Michelle from the same day April 6th
Hiiraan Coast-to-Coast you saying he's not sure if there's a
Conspiracy
New doesn't know if the bombers were put up to
Steve pieczenik wouldn't commit treason on air until the 7th
But Allison show on the 16th
On that show he was very clear that he thought this is
Yeah
Alex was yelling about radu's brother that manipulative lie edited
Family Guy clip you sending damprid on D2
Disrupt Boston official
Press conferences yelling about how this is
The false flag
He wondered on Airway right-winger hasn't blown up the UN bill
Alex knows what audience
He's speaking to a
And always tries to cater to what they need
To become interested
He knows the Coast-to-Coast has a huge audience in the whole lot of them aren't what we now call Red
His goal is to get more people to his website in the maximize strategy
G4 that easy to moderate
You can still be a paranoid f***
Fancy dumb s***
But most of the coast to coast audio
Isn't ready for raw uncut Alex
Yeah you can't go further then
They're all like
A like they're all Muslim
We're not ready to go there
We're still at just they're all legs
Part of this is just good business
But another part is clear evidence that Alex knows that what he says on his own show is
If you believed any of the s*** that he says
He wouldn't come on this show and that you didn't know if there was a
Conspiracy
He does that so he doesn't look
Crazy
Because he knows a few tricks
People that he's not crazy for long enough
Might just give him some money
Also they weren't checking bags
At the marathon and there were no on
And they weren't the National Guard was not part of the conspiracy if there was one
Which there might have been
And if there wasn't maybe they were involved when I get to the bottom of it
So are you digging Journal Jacob digging Journal
I told you that one of the reasons I thought that this would be
Good way for us to
Dip our toes into the
Coast to Coast
Canon
Is because
The familiarity
But little did I know
That this would be
Sofa
You cannot control
What are the persons good
Did he not say
Take away the guns from the
The only one who will have the gun
Is the Criminal Who plants
Absolutely that's a Thomas Jefferson quote right there your ride Georgia
Alright
Why
Why do they keep doing it
They can't if they can't.
To nobody's nobody
Checking up on him
So this is so interesting man any idea what Thomas Jefferson
Did or did not say
All them love Jefferson so much but haven't done a single
Seconds worth of work into understanding
His life for accurately discussing his
Career
Acopian reference deer is
The laws that forbid the carrying of arms are laws of such a nature
They disarm only those were neither
Client nor determine
The crimes
Now it is truth that line appears in Thomas Jefferson's
Legal comment
Place book
But it's a complete mistake
Meant to say that the words
Are Jefferson
They appear in his book because he was quoting a passage
Hopefully super influential legal reformer of
The time Caesar at becaria
His 17th
64 publication
Essay on crimes
Punishments
Becker Rio was a big
Inspiration to a lot of the founders of
States with
Complete sense for Jeffrey
Decided
Work later
So it could be fair to say this quote is something
The Jefferson most likely a
Alex's George were saying
That would be totally cool with it
And I just let it be
The fact that they repeat
Keep this as a Jefferson quote indicates that they don't know where this quote actual
Comes from
Nor do they care
Even if I once knew where the quote actually came from he's smart enough to know that his audience
Sonora have no interest in what illegal reformer from the 7th
Hundreds
Oh yeah
His words are pure gold
Alexis just a tribute to quote to him and move right along who gives
That's what's going on that's how that's how they interact with
And deal with that that these Jefferson
The prop
It's like
Rather than talk or engage with Thomas Jefferson at all
They're just
Holding up a Ben Garrison
Caricature
Listen to be like see whatever this thing said
Is imaginary
It definitely is
So
This is where things
Real f*****-up
But you can already see the
Princes and Alex's presentation like trying to moderate his his beliefs
Cannot be like
I know that this is a proper box. Screaming.
But this is what they were arms there too I swear to you
George said that himself later
This is where I think it gets.
Disgusting because it takes on
Assertive
Human level
Like Alex
Changing his
Form of humanity
Almost
I just I find this
There is no way to stop someone
If they're committed to something show
K show this idea
That we all better be afraid and again for the
3 people that died the hundred plus a 1/2
It's terrible I empathize with him if I see an old lady
Fall down at the mall
Breaker head which I saw once I heard it snap when she fell
I mean I still have your nightmares about that I have empathy you cuz I'm not a psychopath and a sociopath
You're the SheaMoisture letters are the same
Understand there are millions 15 million children starving a year
Close to 40
People worldwide
Most of them children
So
Cool
You know
You got him biting his empathy
A couple times in our coverage of Alex's immediate response to the bombing
Victims are survivors
Alex was singularly focused on building is
Conspiracy in Spanish centrally no time to even acknowledge
The people most affected by the tragedy
This is another instance of Alex shifting his behavior to suit the audience you speaking to
The Infowars audience has no expectation that Alex will even pretend to care about that
People who were hurt or killed
But for the uninitiated that
Comes office super f***** up
To make sure that the Coast-to-Coast audience doesn't get the impression that he's a real pile of s*** trying to profit off of tragedy
It's important for Alex to really Express
Country cares about
And yet
You can't even get through a sentence
Talk about caring about the victims of the bombing
Without qualifying
Saying that that's just three dead right thousands are starving
Is it to say that
You should care about this tragedy but keep it up
I think that's a dick move
On the day after a bombing
Probably a shity thing to say the people who care about the dead or injured or misplacing their emotions
My larger problem though is that in my experience
I see no evidence
That Alex cares about starving children either
I don't think I've ever heard him advocate for anything other than vague Notions of prosperity that would alleviate poverty or stay
Starvation
He's totally against the system
Program
And I'm certain that he's against Universal school lunch programs even though I have not heard him speak on that one specific
This is the issue here
Is your someone like Alex and you expect to get some mileage out of the
These deaths are bad but what about The Starving Children argument
You better make sure that you know you've made directly addressing the problem Starving Children
And identifiable part of your career
Because if you have it
It really comes off like what you're doing is trying to convince people not to care about the victims of
Particular tragedy
Because something else is supposedly worth
This is just
What are you talkin about the gun desert over 30,000 people in the year died
Car-X
Andover
What are you going to Outlaw refrigerators 100
Do people get killed by refrigerators where we going to do there we can't do anything and the primary function of that he's just
To minimize
The boss
You are going to do something about the other
No but I mean
Steve comes on Alex's show on the 70
Commits treason
Right and great day
That was a very funny
In that episode
He gives Alex
Motive
Which is that the supposed bipartisan committee showed everybody for war crimes and
Navigate it out of the news at this point on this
16th Alex.
Have that as a motive
So he only
His standard go to which is visible extraction
From something
Where's my phone
Because I want to hear your point George's this
Right now they're trying to pass total blanket open border and the standing of Homeland Security get some control over that and take
Congress out-of-the-loop that's unconstitutional they're trying to pass massive gun restrictions and registration or they can
Take your guns on the word of one psychologist
Not a judge not a jury not proof
And they're trying to give
Homeland Security other domestic powers and Hegel
Talking about
Basically soft martial law
All that
Is before congress with a razor-thin margin
All of it is failing
Because not all the House and Senate members are corrupt
So this happened and it diverts everyone in Old let's get behind
What the government wants or what the president wants
The whole thing is very
Very suspicious that's all I have to say
So this is standard Alex Jones Show
Oh no there's something that has to do with guns that people are talking about the clear that this is a distraction to push that through
We now live in 2019 we know that none of that happened
Now that idea about like
Immigration and open borders
Stuff like that is
Particularly ludic
Because as we
Come to know the do you know
Johar and tamerlan Tsarnaev
Did the bomb
Yeah
The idea that they would end up doing this bombing
And that the culprits would be the Chechen
People who came to the country Haviland wasn't even to Citizen johar was
But like
The idea that that would be what they would do in order to somehow distract people from
Pushing through it open borders package
It seems like
If any
An attack like this even before we know who did it
Probably lead to xenophobia
I know that does make sense
About what they're
To do is open the Border
Everywhere but
Okay you know that
The real plan.
All right you know
We covered up the hole Saudi involvement in 9/11
Of course but we just got to get somebody to
Get rid of the
That's what we've always wanted
Fine I just think that it's the globalists are having a grand old time
I just think that there is like
Such as
Standard Miss to this argument and such a like
It's just universally deployed to the point where it
Loses any kind of
You been feeling good it means any yeah yeah
Distracting us from
X
Know everything that happened
From everything else fine right and the part that super malicious about this
So manipulative
Is it now we live in the future
We know that like this gun Legend
Empath
Because I yelled
I-80 if it does
Past
I got it it's a it's a trap
Absolute rap
That he can profit off
No matter how it goes
So
George
Is a terrible terrible
Trash fire
I think he's doing
He comes in with you
Questions
Bat
In another setting
Might be
Good question
A lot of the time
I think that this question that he's trying to answer you want to order
That would be great questions of Thai
This question I think would be good if
The person asking
The question had any interest in the actual answer
And Hadley
Cassidy or inclination
To ask a follow-up question
These are
Neither of those things described George Noory
F.
This will end up poorly
Alex
Where do you draw the line
Between
The real conspiracy
Of the event
Weather
Sure
An end for you because you know you're you
Yourself
Picture
It would be a good question if honestly answer
Now we know from listening to this day on the 15th
Minutes after the bombing
Alex is talking to Richard Belzer
And their spitballing
Talk talking about how Rob dudes brother was in command of the army unit because he misunderstood running the race
There is no bottom
He was on like
Truth drug that would be the answer
But we know from looking at the actual
Timeline of the event
Come up with ways to argue that this
Do the false flag within minutes of it happen
There was no evidence that
That led him to suspect
False flag there's nothing it was something he was trying to build
From the jump
So here's his aunt
Which isn't good
The best question I've been asked
Steve pieczenik style flattery
Batman Forever
Because I struggle with this everyday and I want your listeners to know something I don't just look at an event and say
Hey what will be Sensational I got three children I've got a wife I've got a family
I try to with Integrity gets
And that doesn't mean that I don't make mistakes we all do
Historical
Spectrum of research it coz it's fact-checking it's
It's good she's looking at the
Events that lead up to something if she's watching for
Telltale signs
So that's vague it means nothing
I haven't
This is this is I want your audience to know that I'm not some crazy guy who just yells bulshit minutes after a terrorist attack
Determine conclusion that
Safe to come over to listen to my show you
Research
Historical
Context
It's the truth
He's telling him
South Georgia's helping it
I feel like I'm in one of those TV shows where
Like they have that episode where the longtime nemesis
Just shows up and acts like
I've no idea who the who they were before I do know I'm completely
Maybe I'm a changed person
You're going crazy like
No there
Does wearing a mask
You can't buy it
And everybody doesn't believe you and you start to go crazier and crazier things
That you're the one who's in
Say no and then Damascus revealed and it
It was the bad guy all along
Going crazy
George Noory is
A big bad
Because he has that folksy presentation
Oh
Whatever
When you really get down to
He is far more similar to Alex then he might like
People to think
There is no question in my mind
The elitist
Anything
Two controllers
To pull our rights down
For someone like me and you
Is that what events occur
Question the possibilities of one
Fortune
Is that
My frustration is it could be alone
Crazy psychopath just wants attention
Family Guy on the 17th or the guy bombs
Marathon to win right at the finish line
Maybe a crazy saw that one on did I do
What
That doesn't seem in line with his coverage
That is unfortunate
I will agree with you that is very
You know what that's a f****** problem though is that the same thing as does all the time like
People like
Kaitlin Bennett will go out and try and get people riled up
Can cause a negative reaction
Because I'm a conservative
Framing it as like you're mad at me
Because I'm a conservative is the way that you
Sweetly
Wharf
Whatever you're actually doing
Went Out in Georgia expressing
It's like we have to ask
The question
Could this be fake
It's like yeah I honestly do think that that is fine
Yeah that is absolute being
Very cynical and skeptical about things right I don't think
That is a negative impulse
It's fine
When you're actively trying to
How to build up argument
On
Like you're building a house of balsa wood
Yeah that is
No trying to demonstrate that this is fake
That's not asking question
No that's the same thing as like Millie Weaver Caleb Bennett Owen Shroyer being awkward
Because of that
No
Why why
F*** out of here
No one's mad cuz you're asking the question
You're mad cuz you're a liar
F****** talking about the Family Guy episode is your
This is why
Every episode 3 Palms the Boston Marathon
You know damn well that's not what that episode was he
Bulshit
It's just
It's just not
I've said it before there is it the way that they cheat
Furiate
In-N-Out
In such a like
Specific weight
Hit you right in
Eating so many
4 ways I'm fine with that but this little alike
You know what
I know it
Everybody knows what I
And we're all just
Shout
And if you can do to stop his imperator
Yeah and the end they won't have
Say it right to your face
I know I'm lying
You're like no but you do
Yeah
So you know the Family Guy what is things that's important about that
Line of rhetoric that narrative
Is
That
It demonstrates
Foreknowledge
Peter Griffin setting off two bombs
The Boston Marathon
Episode
Your manipulative lie edited clip
You got that that's foreknowledge of what ends
Happening at the Boston bombing
And you know what
Habitat Oklahoma City
The former Governor of Oklahoma
Rock or something
Oklahoma City
It was probably 6 months before yes
So do you know about this
This is
If you are host
It's like this
And you're supposed to leave the house of this
You can't just be throwing up
Was there a thing about that or something I don't know do you go but there was something about that
Right go ahead and fill in my life
Irresponsible
So the book that Alex Georgia talking about here is called the final Jihad when the best of the worst
Finally come for us
Which is a f****** unwieldy subtitle
Should I
Got that
I got that down a lil
The book was written by Martin Keating
Brother of former Governor of Oklahoma Frank
Conspiracy theorists believe this book somehow demonstrates for knowledge on the part of the government
What about the alcohol
City bombing
Then they knew you know they knew was going to
The evidence for this is that there's someone there
Tom McVeigh in
In the book carries out a bombing on a federal building in Elko
Oklahoma which definitely see
Seems kind of weird at first glance
It becomes way less weird when you take a couple more clients
Keaton had written the book prior to the Oklahoma City bombing but it wasn't published
The telar the middle of
Well after the bombing
There's literally no reason to think
He couldn't have gone in and changed
A few details in his manuscript to make it seem more interesting
After the bomb
Because it wasn't published until after
I want to sing is published six months before
It was not
Probably it was about it
Year after the bombing
It was actually published
Early manuscript could have been varied
That is
Brilliant
Pretty pretty good on him
F******
Brilliant
Said I look it wrong it wrong it's wrong
Evil 8
Wrong I know it's wrong
Morally I can feel it's wrong
But I do admire it be
You create decent sales out of a problem
Absolutely
So I found an interview with Keating from April 9th
Teeth 99
95 the day of
The bombing
I did it well what
He was talking to a reporter from the Oklahoma educational television Authority
And I have to say this guy f****** weirds me out
41 the anchor of the segment says the key
He's currently quote finishing up a book
Which really gives you the strong sense that he wasn't finished with it yet mostly because that's what those words
Yeah in the middle of the interview he says unprompted
Quote
I also predicted the World Trade Center bombing because that would be a gorgeous thing to bring down
He thinks for a Beat
Then says
From their perspective with a really weird face
Alright we're really getting into GoPro Isis territory
Me the f****** creeps oh man they would love to blow that up I bet they would false flag me blowing that up all I want to blow
He's clearly saying that he thinks it was a right-wing
Group
I even in that interview he's talking
I'm about how
The Murrah building that got bombed
Was the place where the
FBI agent
Office who was
In charge of the Waco sharing.
This was great
He's very clear that
He believes happened in the real world
Yeah but is also trying to
Betrayed in some sort of
Prophetic
Aspect
So this isn't alive TV show they had to pre-tape this just hours after the bomb
How the hell is this station goat
To dig up a story about an unfinished manuscript for a book that has some parallels to the bombing
Am I to believe that the Oklahoma education
Television Authority as a researcher that thorough on their payroll
They got somebody on the unpublished manuscript beat
Obviously not
This only happens if
He reached out to them
Note 8 there's a pretty good chance he reached out to all the other news networks
Anno ETA is the only one that said yeah
Bombing itself is not the main plot of the
The bookstore would have been really possible to take an already existing manuscript about a terrorist cell in the United States
Which is what the best of the worst days
In the subtitles on wielder
You can finesse a few details to make it mirror real-world event which it that naturally boost your sales considerably
And tell anyone could demonstrate otherwise the simplest explanation
For this is publicity
To be hunting on the part of Martin
How to Giorgio care about any of this though
They need talking points they can use to justify their anti-government position
And to create
Doubt in their audiences mine
Did all these horrible National tragedies are really
Lots of these evil globalist
Looking at them as if they are aren't acting
Possession of bad faith
You just see this as
Absolutely
You completely stupid
But I think that's not
Right
Doesn't seem
Yeah
Hang up to it that educate
What were they
It was actually really great
To watch yeah cuz it's so mid-90s like Aesthetics of it the people in the in the
The studio right it's public access my light grey table with the black background on it I don't remember exactly
Play but they had some like ads for other shows on that
Public Access Network
One of them there's just
It's the weirdest look
Okay dude in the world
Yeah yeah I'd like a Wall Street review show
Got to love it
Lubbock
So Alex that you bench
Family Guy said earlier you bring that back up cuz at this point
That is a
One of the only things he has to go on
If you recall on our episode about the 26
April
Episode
What are you yelling about for a lot of you that carries over
Family Guy
You don't have shows where
Where the cowboy joins the Taliban and blows up the Boston Marathon 2 weeks ago
I am in another expunging that off all the
DVRs and off of Tebow singing It's a hoax when it's not a
Very creepy that's happening right now
Not you got no exaggeration I did the math today
Current TV shows
For every episode
I mean I was talking to my buddy and watch Hawaii Five-O of initiation
Every other episode
Returning veteran is shooting cops or planting bombs or blowing up
Sporting events
That is a boring show that every other episode
Absolutely. Every other episode
That is a
Really top show to watch
It really is.
Every other episode it's
The same thing they changed it from bookem Dano to the veteran
It was weird whenever they just
Yeah I took the facts about evil veterans returning home app
For this episode I don't I did not have time to watch the
The entire third seat
FYE
But I did go to their Wikipedia page
And I searched
The page for veteran
Military Soldier
Right none of the episodes any of those words
Description
I don't know it was this the Hawaii Five-O with Scott cam
Jen from Lost
Oh okay okay
Remember who else is on that show but it came out right
After a little bit after lost
Sightings
People from Lost
Other bookings
I was I'm
I'm always happy when James
Sure that's just one of the weird thing Kenosha
Support Sports
I support
Who did you love that show
Tomcat
Yeah sure no way that was Gary Busey's son
Is great in The Frighteners
Is that unequivocally a true
Comcast
I'm good I only saw cuz I worked at a theater I never would have seen that movie otherwise
That's awful
Anyway
Position where we know a lot about
Do that that's not a bad Avenue to go down later
Oh yeah I would
I think it would make us to
That's true
Sodium
All this doubt there's 22 shows demonizing Patriots Family Guy all this
It's just Alex trying to build up the idea that there was a
Preexisting vibe that was going on
Don't let him to believe they were going to blame
About that a little more
I came out I wish I was still broadcasting in overdrive Internet only
Central for Eastern happen
And I'm usually shed watch my gut tells me we'll try to blame the Tea Party regardless of whether it stays or not
There were like Kim
Kim newscast
Right after that came on shed
I bet it's tea party that did this Michael Moore has said
Chris Matthews is shadow
George Noory has set at yeah
George noory's guest
She said it earlier
Tea party specifically
Veteran
Gun owners
Militia right-wingers
Download you are also trying to get
Trillions of dollars out of
Global
Yellowstone wolves
Yeezys using
Tea party is like a
Stand-in
For all of those groups
George
But earlier on this very episode
So the Alex is a Gaston George and one of his callers
Where
Bandying about the idea that
It was probably somebody who was mad at legs cuz they're returning veteran
Right Alex
Anyway Alex gets into more conspiracy b******* and I think this is actually really in
This low-key you might be one of
My favorite
Clips
Malik's cuz I think it demonstrates
Something
So damning
About him
You've got the marathon coach saying they were on the drill they were announcing the loudspeakers nevermind
What's happening this is part of the drill everything safe
Right before it exploded and Rob do my news director for my nightly news show
Rob Dyrdek
Brother-in-law cuz I've seen of arguments with him on the phone
His wife's brother is in Army intelligence isn't officer
And
He called
Rob's wife about
5 is sister and said
Yeah it's weird they pulled me out of the race towards the end
And I wish I was young pretty close to the lead
They said your dehydrator going to the hospital and I didn't think that made sense because
Normally they
People can crawl across
The hospital
For some reason
Talk to him since then no one will answer
The phone the wife hasn't been able to see him
And
That's something that actually happened
Coast to Coast
No time to explore got to go to commercial
So why do things that I think is the most
Interesting about looking at Alex's narratives forensically
Is that I can tell you when and
How they check
Based on new
At this point on the 16th Alex's heard the stuff about the coach
You mentioned the police exercise at the marathon
Which based on all evidence is likely a crowd descent
Station drill for the police dogs
Alex ran with that information
And you see being repeated here on this and that last clip
August 16th Alex had not yet found the pictures on 4chan from the marathon
So he doesn't know anything about Black Backpack
This narrative about the
Suppose drill becomes announcements on loudspeakers telling marathon runners not to be worried about men with black backpacks of later
That's how he is telling the one we looked at the 18th
The 17th
At least the 18th
That's what the narrative become
Because he doesn't have that piece of it
Yet his there was a drill narrative it's still in the larval stage
As he's talking to George
This is a really good case in point for how Alex incorporates information
Ninja has already
Narratives
He's already established with his audience that there was a drill going on and that means this was a false flag
Later on he'll build on this
Adding in the entire part about the
Supposed Navy Seals and
The white Patsy Alex imagined in the pic
Found on 4chan
This fundamentally has no relation
And do the comments made by the track
But Alex needs them
To be connected
So he goes on to claim that the track coach was talking about announcement about
People with black backpack
Which is not here
What are you talkin
George
On the 16th
If he doesn't have that information
But he should
Because he all he's talking about is the announcements
The track coach
Had this beat had was if this was sincere and Alex just repeating
You should know about the black backpacks from the announcement
Of course it's just impossible for this to be the product of good faith effort
Alex already has the information that came from
The track coach so if that information have anything to do with black backpacks
That to be a part of the narrative from the beginning
And it's not
That's
Suspicious
Yeah when I find
The mostest
How close to the lead was
Most interesting you know what I'm saying put that in
In the other episode brother get really good at Marathon
That's that's interesting it and that's exactly
It might be in there
There's added.
Details to Rob his brothers narrative that don't exist
As it's been told on Alex
Show
And I think what's going on there
Is it Alex starts down that road and then realizes he's not talking to his
Dum dum audio
Any dozen
He has to make this more interesting
Somehow a bunch more details
He starts
Embodying Rob dudes brother talking
King in the first person
Yeah make it somehow
See more compelling than it is
I hate when he does that he also
Pitocin
Some sort of brag
Rice
It's just that nurses
Cystic malignant psychopathy
He's close to the lead to why I think that's because I think that's fair
Sick that's life
Narcissism
And more trying to make it seem more egregious that they thought he was dehydrated
Alright people crawl across the finish line
Yeah it's just sick manipulative s***
And you can see like very clearly
The way this Morris
He's on a f****** jackass
If you had the information that
Supposedly
Has
It wouldn't come out
And I think
That's all they have
This guy is
So in the next clip Alex sites some globalist
Talking about how they want to take us all out
Then George asks another good question
In a different account
Be a good person and that's basically
But they're real
Straight Shooters
Socially engineer has
To make us pliable and submissive
Exterminator
Responsibility
Absolutely the White House signs are Road ecoscience bragging about the 70s
Bertrand Russell 80 years ago wrote about it
I mean this is their religion
And that's why they can find terrorists to attack us to scare us into submission that's why
Yeah they can come out and say it's either Al-Qaeda that attacked us
Orange Libertarians equation
That there is some
Al-Qaeda Middle Eastern people
There are real grip Shannon eget recruited under multinational organizations
To engage in selective control the tax
Compartmentalize low-level people
Don't even know what they're part of they believe they're fighting for you of the Jihad all I whatever
Everwell hobbyism
But they're working for a higher cause
Scare the West in the giving up
It's liberty in Freedom I mean
So your answer is no
There are no real terrorism
Started run by the global everybody is run by
The white ones are tricked into doing it because they think that they're pursuing their own
Pawns of the global
Driving like a punk-rock scenario for terrorism we're like
Do you get a good band together and you start out real small and then you start getting it
Remembers
And then the f****** record labels come in
And they stood they just only terrorists
Garage
Down in the lower level you know like
I know
DC shows
Right
Yeah it's
It's it's really strange
And again like I said I think that would be a real pointed
To ask Alex
Situation where you would actually ask follow-up
And actually be interested in an answer as opposed
To allowing Alex to
Just about his nonsense
And one of the reasons I think that this
The problem
I'm just it's impossible for this sort of
Interview to go well is that George Noory is not like
I think his perception of things
Is a little bit
Off
Call Alex
Create
Who became part of al-Qaeda
I would say all of them that would be pretty much everybody you act
This is some kind of information are you
Do you do you
Sincerely think that most people who are in the media don't know that
That's crazy
This isn't some kind of berry
Truth
This is very well.
It's one of the few agreed
Stacks of a
Treason committed by Republican president that we do talk about
Is there so many that we do
So widely spread it's almost it's
If this is
Is college dorms
Who's blowing your mind
Nonsense
Presented the idea that everybody who's not part of their truth movement doesn't even know this is
Crazy
Nonsense
Anyway here's where it turns that even worse
And they start getting attacked
80 Baxter
The globalist
As you know the talked about are pushing vaccines
Put on record and made autism go from 1 + 25,000
The one in
Chelsea
But I don't take
Flu shot
I had a vaccine when I was
That blew my arm up the size of a basketball
Was it for me
It's great to not tell people that they shouldn't get vaccines but do you think that maybe you were cheating the exact
Same outcome
But make yourself feel better
Because you say you're not telling me I'm out telling people not to I'm just repeating the story about the dangers of vaccines and hubby
Personally and I consistently say that I never get in I will never do it and imma trustworthy
Admiration and respect and I say that I never do
You think that this might just be a psychological crutch so you have to take responsibility for the things you advocate
Maybe
Yeah some contacts on this George Noory has been on the radio since at least 90
This time that you got a shot and had a bad reaction
Do it happen before then
It should be pointed out that vaccines
To come a long way in the last 40 years
The last time in or you got a shot with a Time
Before I even had vaccine for
Hepatitis A and B Lyme disease and rotavirus
Countless lives have been saved due to these medical advance
But George got a bump on his arm for decades ago so now he's going to let s*** head like Alex spread their anti-vax propaganda
And give them photastic port
Yeah guess who just booked their ticket to conman Island
B on their George
So I just
I got I got no time
I have no.
And George
Cuz nothing but time
You know my uncle is a Vietnam veteran I don't have to tell him about vaccines
On his way to Vietnam
That put him in the hospital for two weeks
She said I'm never going to get one of those
I was
Anecdotal stories
I will say in a very kind
Sending tone God love you I love you
Let me tell you about the time that I've gotten shots and nothing's happened
Valid is all of your apocryphal stories about your uncle and some stranger you talk to
I was at school and all of these
These kids got shot
And nothing bad happened
And any of them but
You're not going to see that being entered into and
Anecdotal evidence
Right that's why these arguments are made this way
Because statistically
The all the other stories are boring as s***
You can only build a case
For a position like this
With appeal to emotion and
Narrative
These these
Anonymous stories of someone who got sick because they got the vaccine or his arm blew up to the size of the basket
Ball and if you don't have one of those.
Make one up right now I don't know what this person was George to talk about
That's probably a Welfare Queen sauce it in there were supposed to trust him cuz he spoke CNC
Anyway why would you
This is very important
This is one of the
Things that make George Noory realshit
Is that he's pretty auntie
And
Is a lot of alternative ideas about science
As evidenced by the doctor
Did he talk to you
I strongly anti recycle
So
That's a problem and a problem it will
Continually
Will develop as we get more and more is Jojo
So Alex has a mad about people caring about
Victims
Android
You should know of course
Aubrey still mad
Wow hundreds of thousands die from
Flesh eating bacteria
In the US every year admitted
Hundreds of thousands die from Bad drug interactions
Hundreds of thousands die from Bad Medical
Procedures
We're talking
$600
In total or more
And no one cares it's not on the radar
But oh my gosh in high-def
Are three dead people we need to ban your Liberties because of this
How would I not be suspicious
Of the entire motive
Here let's sell every city
15 million dollars
A bomb
Disposal robots
Okay
Alright
Couple important
Hundreds of thousands people do not die from flesh eating bacteria every every night
CDC puts the number at between
700 +
1200 cases
Puryear
With about a quarter of the cases be
That puts us at about 300 people per year in the United States
Maximum dying from flesh eating bacteria
I'm not even sure that 100,000 people die of it every year global
I'm not even
Ensure 100,000
Probably
Don't die from Bad drug react
The number you most commonly cited as 100,000
Which certainly is a lot
Is a real problem
But also still in Belichick
In service of minimizing the deaths
Set the Boston bombing
Which is what a monster would do
Alex might be
Closer To Fine on the medical procedure one but there's a larger issue that he's completely ignoring about all of these examples
All of these things are examples of
Things that the federal government has spent money trying to attract
The CDC put that psa's and educational material about how to avoid getting flesh eating bacteria
Many of the drugs that people have adverse reactions to are prescribed
Stances that are literally called
Controlled substance
You're not going to last long being a license
Being lights
The doctor who can patch
Does medicine did you keep boxing surgeries
And procedures
Using examples like these in relations to guns
Really only
The argument stronger that all gun should be licensed
Register
Sure a lot of people to die from medical complications
But imagine how many more would be dying
If you don't have no license or governmental educational requirements for doctors to do surgery
Possibly a
Because from the dawn of a medicine that is always
The freeways never any
Hundreds and hundreds of years where you could
Call yourself a doctor
The free market would settle you kill enough people no one's going to use your service
You know what's funny about that it's the same argument I'm sorry
You know why people say guns kill people but cars kill people you have to have a license
You have to have insurance if you drive on
Public Road
Using that as an example to be like
You know hey
You do you say guns kill people that this does to think I absolutely think about how many more would be killed the government
Care of
Try to minimize the damage
Is that that does
Rude license
Something through insurance
In case you do get into an accident the insurance
Helps pay for the person that you harmed it in there
People only hurt
Don't arguments Adventure at 3 or God
I don't know you better believe it
Exactly what you were
What's
Inch of what what's fascinating about this argument
He gets that he
Getting it both ways
Because he's both
Setting the stage for it to be a false flag
It doesn't matter who did it
Except for who they're trying to
To blame for it
What the same time minimizing what
Silly means
Almost saying like
Well
If it is a right-wing
They wouldn't we wouldn't act
But they wouldn't just go after something
Mall like all only 3 deadbeat
Only under you literally is doing
We would have gone after
Exact
Yeah that whole thing
Utterly utterly
Fine
I want white terrorism to happen
And I don't want to be blue
Yeezys
Real real Shady
So they get to talkin about some other topics like that
There's a bit of Basa
Embalming talk they also fear off in other directions
Snorri has some news topics that he wants to
The head
And one of them is apparently
I just got shot
In about allowing people to have knives on planes
Right and this is
Well I don't I don't I don't care about my position
I care about their
And it's weird
Let me ask you
Wheelchair
Stuff like that is crazy
The judgment
Is Knotts
But allowing
To take
Is Ludacris
After all
And with a 2.3 6 in knife
Well yeah take
Via Lone Star College thing in Texas last week
We're 12-plus people or stabbed by a 1in exacto knife
My issue is this
England is trying to register butcher knives now
Because they took the guns of the stabbings
Exploded
I want to know
Why they make Pilots
The whole aircraft
Giant
Why do pilots have two jobs I've interviewed him he better be them
Oops
Daddy locked up in the shape of firearm
In the cockpit
But now we're going to let people take knives on a plane it's just not at all I'm saying George
This is crazy
First of all I have not heard alexeeff
Single word about that Lone Star College stabbing
When you first brought it up I thought he was talking about the shooting at Lone Star College for Becky
January 2013 that we covered on our show
If you don't remember that was the one where Alex
Feverishly covered live footage of it on his show saying the BET was covering it up
Thinking that he could turn it into his own saying
Sandy Hook only to realize that
To the students
At the school were black
If you lost interest
Well it turns out on April 9th
2013 there was another incident at Lone Star College
When a student named Dylan Quick-Step
People before being tackled
The Ground by fellow students
In interviews with police quick talked about having fantasies about cutting off people
Both faces and wearing a mask
Since you with age
And he also talked about how he was into necrophilia and Ken
Right right
It's so weird to me
That Alex never brought up this case
Until now and
Not on his own show
I wonder if that has anything to do with the fact
Dylan quick
A white male who went on a stabbing
Free at school that has a student body that's a proxy
At least 75
Not white
We can see it's a story the 5th
Perfectly into his narrative
Do you have an example of a non gun-related School attack
It's just sitting there on the TV
For Alex ready for him to use as proof that school violin
Isn't about guns
But for some reason I don't remember seeing
Or hearing him say anything about it
Which I imagine is this because I was a super busy
The timer
Tried to help Steve pieczenik
Can't be in Korea on clandestine business that could be
He had more important
Also shouldn't Alex police for being able to be armed on a plane
Doesn't Disney not realize that him conceding that there are certain situations where it's not appropriate for him to be armed
The really hurts his argument that the global
Monster trying to make schools
Hospitals
Disarmament zones
If he's allowed that some places are places where you should not be allowed to be armed
It logically follows that there may be some other places where the same
True
What is an airplane that makes
So you shouldn't be able to be armed on it
Well if it's that it's a confined space
And he shouldn't be okay with anyone being armed on a train or bus or any other form of public transportation
These are just simple and very Elementary problems of the way Alex can
Construct argument
And the term for this is
Consistency
Alex goes on and on all the time but no more guns equals safe
Because having a weapon and Powers a person to defend
But here
For some reason he's opposed to people being able to protect themselves
Because they're on a plane
His argument that the
The answer to the bad guy with a gun
One is a good guy with
Gunship
Still apply in this situation
The answer to a bad guy with a gun on a plane
Is a good guy with
With a gun on a plane
There's nothing and it's even worse in terms of guys cuz guns you could say while you might shoot out the window and so big
But not as you're not going to nice through the window
You don't know that you're probably not
Here's here's
His Witcher
It's all about
It's all about dementia
Alright 2.36 in
Is far longer than 9 mm
We all know what the real f******
Shut off
Appreciate
I appreciate your templates
Rationalization
But it doesn't work
He needs to provide
Irrelevant
Reason why he would be in favor of someone
Being armed in every situation
I didn't fail to do so
The fundamental problem is that Alex has an absolute
And he yells all the time about how the Public's right to be armed cannot be infringed
And that's
Incompatible with the belief that good law-abiding C
Shouldn't be allowed to be armed on a plane
They're not going to attack anybody while they're on that plan so why you worried about it
Because these positions are
Incompatible
It's a strong indication
Alex is
Really as principled as he pretends to be
Which I know is a shark
Maybe there's something else
Baha'i disposed
Now that he's just
Stop
B2 review
If you yelled at everyone should be armed and every single situation
Be able to have guns at
Stadium
The hospital in the waiting room of your kids being born you should have a gun believe all that stuff
You need to make a folder argue
About why you're gay
People having knives out
Right right
Probably
What is it
What if it crashes
Where did you get stabbed by the knife
That is a very serious consideration I hadn't thought about that I retract everything
So a long way on this episode we've seen Alex
Kind of minimized
The deaths at the bombing
And be a little bit
Dickish
Even while he's
Touting his
Great
Apathy
Picture of George tries to push back a little bit on the
About how like
You should we should care about these
Which I tip my hat to a little bit
And Alex
Tries to pretend
Okay let's hear this tone of voice
Chihuahuas scared
Whoever killed three people at the Boston Marathon
An immediate acting like it's the end of the world
There's giant issues going on I saw washer
Post article a few months ago that
At the headline
Injured
With her arms and legs
No absolutely not it's the opposite
The minute I mean I saw the photos of a guy with his leg blown off at the me
Bone sticking out with
Arteries hanging out
At the finish line for his father was in the race
6 years old
Marathon
To come up to his family is little boys.
And his six-year-old daughter has an arm gone
All the media
Appearances all week here so much over so sad
Oh it's terrible
But they're they're basically narcissistically
Drawing all the ratings
Alex wow
Crazy you're doing it again man come on
So this clip is super interesting to me because just hours earlier
You're on his own show Alex repeatedly done some Rifts about 8 year old child
Was probably killed because a cop told him to hold the bomb before it went awesome you got it
Alex in his own controlled environment spoken ways are outrageously disrespectful about this kid who was killed
And if I was
The parent listening
Think that I would be
Furious
But he did that and he was able to because he's acclimated is audience
Did I cruelty in
And inhumanity gradually
And now he hasn't convinced it in fantasizing about imagine scenarios about the globalist
Kill this kid is somehow productive
As a part of fighting the globalist
You can't do that on Coast to Coast
As I've repeatedly pointed out
He knows the audience is very
Any nose
Colors no one's going to come over to his show
But it's bigger than that
George Noory doesn't listen
The Alex's show
He doesn't know the kinds of horrible b******* Alex says everyday
Time for that
He's a busy dude he's got hours of radio to do is go up you got a Life to Live 3 hours
Is Alex doing b******* that it's actually very boring
He would probably be fine with most of Alex
Is political
Stupidity but this sort of disrespect to a child victim of a bombing would most likely offend
Even Georgia Sensibility
And Alex knows that that would mean he'd no longer be welcome on the show
Is way bigger than his
You know if you was
Joking about the
Is kid being handed a bog-witch
The stress was on the 16th
That was on our two showed that he did
This same day
This is crucial
Alex demonstrated a certain sort of behavior on his show on April 15th
And he's dead
Menstrating quite
Fred behaviors here on Coast to Coast AM
When will be wise
Ask themselves
Possible explanation
Other could be
Money
Yeah good
And we see Alex like just sort of rolling around like a pig and s*** talking about his ratings are through the roof
Talk about narcissistic Beauty basking in the ratings
And you did it again he did that thing where he's like
I know how to make the
Media sound
I'm so evil
I'll save they're doing what I'm doing right now
I'll be honest I mean I think that the criticism
Some of the media
Hunting rating
Call tragedy
Absolutely agree and it's again
I'm liking
This formation of this
How I say that
I'll accept that criticism
Anybody but Alex
That is a fine point that you don't get to make it
Can't be in the middle of
Doing it while judging
You can't that's a rule
That's where the problem
So they talk about a load
Of b******* Alex
Suggest that
Jay Leno is in trouble with a network
Sports Alex
They talked about her gloved
Alex's
Appearance on
A Morgan
It's just a bunch
Yeah yeah
You can sort of Hit the fast-forward button on that
And we get to them talking about how you need to get
Takeoff
Any moment now
Answer George
I think
Jokingly asked Alex
He's going to get chipped
Years old and I have a heart attack when I go get a chipped
That's fine
But even technology itself
But if it's a chip to buy and sell
Absolutely never
Are you serious do you think that these f****** evil globalist are going to
Tell you it's for a medical reason
What are you doing
You're saying that in some circumstances it's fine to get these chips
Well I mean Vince Staples said that you should never
He is very Adam
Okay
But also
That is such a fun
Trusting dumb things
Obviously
Play technology
He's not all leave
If I need it I'll get it
But if I don't need it then I won't get it you're like hey this one's going to be
And this one over here is going to
Control your heart
Choose
I know this one I don't trust
So I'm going to choose the one that you said was going to kill me
Alex I've listened to enough
Enough of him to know that he
He talks all the time about the globalist
Trojan
Trojan Horse thing things
In backup
Cancer virus in the vax
He went to picking at the medical thing in order to
If there's a medical
For me to get this chip
Such fantastic fan
Testicle like childlike
Thinking of the rules like they're playing by the fairy rules
You can't do what you have
Say my name backwards
Otherwise you got to heal my heart but it's also the same thing as the I'm against knives on a
Applying this is a counterexample to
What you believe or you express you saying there's a circumstance where it you're accepting this chip
That means
Not have the stuff you say his
Damn you can't hold the positions
You all day unless you allow people
Also what if your 50
Is there an age
Cut off for you where you like around 70 I don't need to worry about it I'll get the hardship
If they buy and sell me whatever.
Surge of Baltimore talk about the Family Guy stuff and Alex's
Pretty clearly expressing that he understands
Is that what they did was
Run with a clip that show different parts of the episode put together to make it appear
Peter was bombing a marathon sort of indication
He's aware of it I don't really care
Jiren talk
So much more about this
George announces that he's going to
Speech and Alex is going to be
Live stream
Skype and Alex have they talked about
Alex says
That's not verified whatever
Fuk up I don't know if Alex ended up showing up to that one but in 2015
George Noory gave a speech in Toronto and Alex roses
It's all built
It just trying to build up his Rebel persona
Well what it was he had enough
That really Siri
You know what you going to do
So this last clip
I think is
Interesting
And
Sad
In hindsight
What you going to do
I wonder what 2016 will be for all of us
What do you think
President
And if there is free Elijah to this country he'll probably win
Oh boy
So
That's why I just left
Could turn back time when I was listening to that just died hearing George Noory
His folksy ass voice and all of us
Oh no that is only you knew
Jumpcut
If only you knew and it's only you
Is it a lot of the negatives
Stop is a direct consequence
Reactions
Facilitate
The platform
Giving these people a much larger audience
It's much
More influence
What they bring to the table deserves
I would say you should look back on this George
Nvda
Deeply ashamed
And this is something that
I don't know if I can prove
But I think
George Noory
In that moment
Right
Genuinely wondered what was going to happen
So all the sudden we have a thought bubble
And then we're playing out
We're all living in that what would happen
George Noory
Continues on the say
Same track when we find ourselves at the end of the world
Explodes he's going to suddenly wake up in the middle of this conversation
They f*** you Alex Jones
Donald Trump will never be president
He's going to burn the studio down and run out the door screaming
And that's how we're going to save the world Dam
Not good that that's a better
Reality the day
I know so this brings us to the end of our maiden voyage
Going into the
SeaWorld of coasttocoastam
I think you can see
Some pretty good reasons why this is
Fits into what we do
This is ask
This is bulshit this is mainlining propaganda
White Wedding
Not talkin about big
Talk about it
At some point some of those
Make sure you end up going into
To somebody paranormal and weirder episodes of Ghost Coast
But what you see is a very
Concerted effort
Make Alex
Seem like a credible expert
And make
The things that
Sanitize
The things that he does on his show
By creating a difference
Moderate version of it resent your audience and then loud
That deep
Researcher
Guy who knows all this s***
And it would actually comes
What is this
Man between
Nouryon Rogan we got
Army of people
Soft
I think Nori is worse
Oh I agree with you
The what would I
The intersection
So many worlds
Exist on
Because we have
Space weirdo
So that has a lot of the Project Camelot stuff in it
You have Alex
Anti-communist
Extreme right-wing
Folk right Infowars contributors and what have you
And then also you have people likes
Quail in
Tom Horn
Who are
Pretty regular guests on Jim Bakker
Talk about apocalyptic
X step
You have the worst of it's like that book written by the brother of the Oklahoma governor
It's the best of the worst oh yeah you might be right these people exist
Within the
Gastly
Yeah
Coasttocoastam
And then you add onto that that
George Noory is
One of the sponsors
Is youngevity
Dr. Joel Wallach veterinarian
The f*** are those people have these
Thank you there's so much
A section that comes in
I think is weed to peel back layers on
The Onion
I think that what we what we'll see
Is almost a unified
A place where a lot of hover that youngevity is actually behind the f******
And all of this
I don't think we'll find that but I do think it will see
Honda parallel
Not just
Alex but to all these other topics
We cover and all these other stuff
Damn yeah
So I look forward to
I hope everyone enjoy
I will be back
Indeed we will
Until then
Great website
It's knowledge fight.
Better Days
Broussard Twitter
We are on Facebook
If you would like to download the show go to iTunes or wherever pot
Actual apps are still download at libreview do all that fun stuff
Yep I will be back on Friday but until then
Anillo
I'm Leo
I'm dzx Clark
I am Giorgio moroder