Holding
Alex
We're couple dudes like to sit around and drink wine
Pacific
Never again
Odd Squad Elie Wiesel
Cancel it
Sucralose drinking white wine before you got here that's why that opening was so off the rails
I really consider and drink red wine
Do
What would be more interest
Two guys
You both know a lot about Alex Jones
Have a back-and-forth
Know already know
There is no that would be not interested
I'm listening
I like a second option
Or one of us
It doesn't really matter which way
Probably the guy with the deep and comforting verito
What if he knew a lot
But are our co-host
Man he doesn't know nothing
I think that I would only work if the co-host was
Shocked by everything and screamed a lot
That would work
Joy Andrade
We've already spent 25 minutes on our in
Oh boy episode
Alex Jones
But today is going to be slightly different
And we'll get to that in a minute
But before we do
I want to play
Something from
Monday's episode
That isn't
Incredibly important
There is no joking around about that
God damn this is super super duper series
This is from Monday
May 1st episode
Alex Jones having an interview with Steve pieczenik
Now
For reasons that are completely unknown to me
Is in front of
What appears to be a diagram of all the genres of hip-hop
I will post a picture on Twitter no
What what else would Steve pieczenik be diagramming the man of the counter-coup
He is
Military strategist psychologist for the CIA in the past
In front of a board of trap
Crunk
Turntablism
I've no idea what's going on okay
That is irrelevant
Either he wandered into the writers room and VH1 in 1994
Kobe
A bedroom
Or
He is
Diagramming that
Hoover and 7th
I could give a very simple explanation I think might be right
I hope it's
They have all these berries about how hip-hop was made to lie
Popularize criminality in the black community and stuff like that
I could see it being something like that
But even
While
While but he's sitting in front of this chart
But I think
He's going to very seriously regret saying
Oh he is got so many different things to regret
I miss my dog knock
Safeway at the bottom
I'm going to kick your ass Adam Schiff you pack a pussies feel your hand
I was just up
But then you've got the guy who owns Chobani is importing rapist
I think this one's higher
Holy now it might not be legally actionable but I think you're going to regret this
Some good news
I don't want to get them obviously
But let's just say this
I know Mike cernovich the sources the government does his sources social
But it's obviously who's been retweeting him and saying he's a great guy between our stuff
Very close to president
Tell it's not a secret it's his son especially Donald Junior is a total Patriots and there's a bunch of other people so Trump is for
That wasn't a secret
I'll tell you it's not a secret government apparently
That's why this is a huge f****** problem
Whether it's true or not
Illegals
All of the illegal things that you can do well here's the part that's even more f***** up is it barely plays on All
Audio clip
Steve pieczenik responses right
He agrees
Kids are the sources
For Mike cernovich
Field propaganda article
Now there's two things that are going on here
Okay there's two pads
That are possible and one of them also
Path of this
Alex telling the truth
Here and if you telling the truth
Superfecta
If he's if he's not telling the truth and he's just making this up out of whole cloth
Like Donald Trump is never going to talk to him again
Any sources that he does have
He's burnt no sources should ever
Talk to clear most of his sources are fake
Fuel sources going to hear that and be like I don't know if I can
Can trust his discretion
His confidentiality means nothing he just on air
The children of the sitting president information to a right
Which information
Angelique witch again.
Telling the truth
Birds
Rights because now sirovich is sources out in
Trump's kids are never going to be giving him information ever again
You would hope
You are forgetting
Stupidity of all of the
People
That's a fair point
But this is one of the most f*****-up things I've heard on the show and I've listened to a lot of it
I don't think I've ever
Like fully witnessed someone out
A source
Like I've never seen a journalist do it in real time
So flippantly
Donald Trump jr. jr.
Bananas
For someone who claims to
It's it's right now I'll tell you what it's picked up on like Reddit
Picture
Screenshot from the Donald
God dammit now started getting more stories
We just kind of fairs
Think of the war games what happens when you burn a source but we've already established
If it's not
No he's losing it
But since losing it in the prison
Maybe it's time
For us to escape
Time for us
To take a little trip down memory lane but before we do that
Need to do a little shout-out
Like to thank our man out in Germany what's up Ian
Thank you John and
Supporter
Is it
He took us up on our offer is more what I should say
We offered on our last episode that if people donated $10 a month or more
That's a wee word
Take a day in history
Go back to what Alex Jones was doing on that day
So me a couple days is that the first date exactly was the date of the first
Nuclear test by South Korea North Korea
Which was in 2006
Turn on fortunately my archives don't go back that far so I could not find that episode
SAS for a backup
Date
You sent me
June 4th
What was June 4th 2005
What do you think's going on
You're a man of letters
June 4th
Ernest anyway
Did we blow something we didn't
Let me see if
Out of context
From June
This is June
Haven't been convinced there's as being right all the time
It was one day marriage
Bypassing the Supreme Court
Well
That's what was expected when Ian made this suggestion
Here's the deal
The actual Court decision was on the 26th
Unfortunately Alex name of the 25th
Alex Jones is in studio on the 24th
He doesn't talk about the gay marriage Supreme Court case at all
Maybe he doesn't talk about it on the 24th so I'm like that's not fair the subject matter that was requested
Quested was the Supreme Court case
I want to go to the next day
On the 25th when the court
Alex Jones is in Michigan
For his cousin's wedding
David Knight isn't studio and he's mad
So I'm like alright
Sunday episode Alexandra back to Friday
Going down
Nope
Nothing
Get nothing from him
David Knight still in studio
So we have to go
To the next episode where Alex Jones is actually on
Now you might be asking yourself
Does he go ape shitt
About gay marriage
I wouldn't so here's my
He does not go ape
He spends all of his time
Trying to straddle the line between like
But at the same time
I just think that
I think it's pretty reasonable
Yeah let's find out
Here's the first clip from the show
This is
A little Special Report
But Alex throws it to Special Report
And you're going to witness
Like right out of the gate
Minute one
The Alex Jones Show
From June 29th 2015
Something that is out of bounds
Hello explain when we get back
American flag
Now we'll get back to that
If it's going to come back
Butts
And it's no joke
Obviously called last week
Which is not a reasonable 100
Collapse
Front and so much more
Very important broadcast news on Isis
Really
For four years
I'll be so-called Rebels
Comes out August 2nd Amendment
Infowars.com now this week the Pope
Decided to go full retard
When he released a statement saying the gun manufacturers are not Christians
Oh I find that extremely funny to hear that coming from the Pope
Because here infowars.com we do have a Christian owned
Gun manufacturer as a sponsor
And co-founder releases statement
By the fact
Mmm saying bad things about the pope isn't really what is out of bounds
I do think it's funny to think that the pope who is an Italy is bound by the
Second Amendment I think that's absurd
But the thing that's way
Is the idea that Joe Biggs made it special report
The cookout the Pope
On behalf of a sponsor
I was I was a little bit more concerned about the reference
224r
Is Waters Downey jr.
Thunderbird
That was the problem
I don't appreciate
Majority of Manor.
Is that
It is exploited
Sew-ins
You did it again
Want to go to a
A restaurant called
Build it we're going to do that another idea
Noh8
The joke is that actor Zara
Voiding that in order to get
Yeah
In order to
Revealed
Hypocrisy
Stupidity
He's trying to use it
Min away
Also
If you're a Christian owned
Gun manufacturer
No Pope head
Wow I don't I don't know what that means
I'm so
The pope gave a speech that they're talking about some quotes from it
If you only trust
Man
You have lost
You told the young people in a long rambling talk about war Trust
In politics after putting aside
His prepared address
It makes me think of people managers businessman who call themselves Christian and they manufacture weapons
He's right on it man
That leads to a bit of a distrust doesn't it
He said to Applause
He also criticized those who invested weapons Industries
Quote duplicity is the currency of today
They say one thing and do another
I think a pretty fair assessment
Yeah it's
Cool Pope globalist
Yeah so I mean like
Out of context
I'll be half of your sponsor you're basically starting the show with an ad where you're committing
It's not God
No
You're just pissing on the Pope
4ad
Yeah that's awesome
That's one of my favorite things about
Mainstream Christians are
Mad at the Pope
Every now and again and then
Super happy with him
The cognitive dissonance
Of religion
Certainly
The
You can take that
Barely an Oculus
Hey if you're investing
Gunther used
So you're investing
You're profiting off the
That's what you doing I mean if you really get down to it
Joe Biggs goes on to be like you know how people use weapons to use guns to hunt
Feed their families Amato's money if it's made from
Killing industry it's
Staggering I guess
It's almost nothing comparatively
So when you want if you want to make that argument
Please debate the pope Joe Biggs
Go back and have a conversation with him about your
Principal Gunn stamp
Franklin
I don't even think Jason Biggs
Basically gone now
In modern-day already
So I'm going to break it down for you
Break it down this episode of 2015 is globalist heavy
Good
I'm looking forward to it
Classic
I don't know how wacky it is
If it's on advised at certain points certainly
The main narrative that runs throughout
Basically this entire episode
Is Greece
Degrees financial crisis
What was going on in
You mean the one caused by
Banks
There
Nanami and
Forcing them to accept
Steriti measures for
Zaire
And you have just made the globalist argument
Or at least you might believe in the global
Yeah but hit me up saying big Banks
His work
His version of it is far more Sinister than just capitalism out of control
Hillsboro
This first clip
Goodyear
Now that we're out of the advertisement section
Globalist
Are trying to
Architect will take up most of
He's just trying to sell out how evil the globalist
Now we know the
The origin of
Could be this is just about how global history volando trying
To change this
They've taken over almost
Real Drilling in
Announcement
To move the Overton window
Coins middle of the last century
They're slightly out of the Overton window
I think he is just described himself
That's exactly what he just did right there is nothing
In the world
That is more pushing what is
Decent
He is so like
Because he is so crazy the ID
DIA
Taking everybody's Healthcare away
Is though that's giving
Individual
And then
Listen
I think that just kind of
Subconscious
What would also is like
It's on air all day and is like Hillary Clinton is literally a demon
Like if you want to talk about pushing discourse in a certain direction you've introduced the idea of the demons are real
Influence our politicians
Now before you introduce this idea into our discourse
We just have to talk about ideas and disagreeing with them thrown out the window and now anybody could be possessed
So that your Overton window is way over here over here
Demonize your opponent when you just go
Literal with
With demon eyes
Smells like fire and f******
Brimstone never noticed that a fly landed on Obama flies Neverland on people
Anyway
Alex
As an example
Of them pushing
The Overton window
That I think is last relevant than him
In terms of actually doing it
Okay we'll see
What they're doing
Because their Vanguard is so far out
Jocelyn elders
3 years ago as a Surgeon General
Calling for the school to
Help children
Ages 5 masturbate
I don't know how to masturbate
I want
That's pretty good
We need we need schools to help five-year-old masturbate
For those young'uns out there you know where to round Jocelyn elders
Was the Surgeon General
The Clinton years
Prove it that you got fired after
She
Speak at the United Nations conference on AIDS
She was asked by someone there whether the appropriate
To promote masturbation is a means
Preventing young people from engaging in riskier forms of sexual activity
Aren't you replying quote
I think that it is part of
Human sexuality and perhaps it should be taught
That's it
I don't think that's
Genuinely do not see an egg
I honestly even before I was ten I did not see the controversial
I don't think I don't think my parents that is controversial I don't think there's anything Overton window we about it
Now the only things you can take away from that is that Alex Jones does not
I think that people should
Possibly
Hey neither does Jocelyn elders
That's not what you said
I didn't I wasn't in you at the UN when I was 10
Wanted people to
Something they've been doing
White Horse Tavern
Brevard
About the firing
The areas where the president does not agree with her views this is just one too many
Is 12 me
They did not see internet pouring
No f******
Or the next few years
Clinton's life
You didn't masturbate
Fair enough
He is already
Two clips
Which again is maybe within the first couple minutes of the show
Completely misrepresented with the Pope said in order to plug one of his pain
And completely
We completely misrepresented something to Jocelyn Elders said 1e f****** years ago in order to make his argument
About the Overton window
Example
23 years ago as Surgeon General said maybe if
People masturbated in that was okay
They would be less likely to come
That's not even what you was talkin about
She was
Kids young people engaging in Risky forms of sexual activity unprotected
Like that
Avoiding diseases
Watch it like that
If you masturbate
Safe
That sort of thing
Depends on where you are
Put her in the car at a friend's get in trouble
Cafe
Perhaps response was even
Perhaps
It should be taught
Yeah it's not even saying
I think this should be
Maybe
Banana
That banana
Less likely to
Ashamed and miserable ever
Hey this is okay
It's normal human behavior that
Everybody does
Like have you ever gone to the zoo
Sea-Monkey master
Kind of Cults that we grew up in
I'm so the next
Monkeys don't teach each other
Perhaps he's wrong
Yeah but they mature fat
Is Alex just blowing hard
Just blowing hard
Just I
The best
How old is he
So
How is Alex Jones
Never wrong
Donald Trump
How do I continue
Weekend
Because they told us what they're going to do and they done it over and over again world and old world
Apologist and sociologists
Launch file
We have accessed them
You would think it's a weakness that they're so predictable
Their responses hey
The public is even conscious
If you're awake if you're aware
Person that is for children
Who Coronavirus
I don't even know what you're talkin about
I just kept that to a positive review the long side at the end
I'm just grabbing things that are important to note are
One of them is that does not speaking a specifics
Information
Just proclaimed that he's always right
But if you really look into it he's wrong about almost every
He's absolutely just is
Is fax or Shawty
Value depends assertion that he never backs up ever
So much documentation
He's predicted that he's wrong about
But the other thing
Is this a beauty comes to the end or is like
Everyone's dumb
And you can't even communicate
Others there's two things I want to
Speculate about their
Is that because he has a very specific mental illness
She can't talk to other people
CiCi's crazy
Whenever anyone else talking to him he can't communicate because he just starts rambling about globalist
National forces
References to documents
Scientist who may or may not have talked to
And I can't follow you
Even the most generous of interviewer he's going to yell at them
It's impossible for him to interact with anybody on a human level
I seen him with his co-host
Mildly abusive
So I think there's some of that he's projecting
A little bit
And then beyond that
That is also
A mentality that is a spouse in the protocols of the elders
This idea that most of the masses are dumb
And the globalist
Are trying to make them dumb
In order to make them Ali-A
Well it also
Only trust your
Leader
To be the one who
The truth
That forces you to
To put everybody else
True
So he is
He is isolating his listeners
Yes
Yeah well he's isolated from everybody else they can only have him
Exact as a conduit the truth
Yeah yeah that is true
At the bomber
But the good news is
What's a good news
Albertsons off of special
Boston a bunch of thing
Alakazam
On certain matters
Especially
Isis
Show big specialist on Isis is going to walk you through
How evil Muslims are in
Home
It starts with ISIS
Generalized is the first of two times
He gets into really spotty animal metaphors
But I don't think are appropriate
Very not good
Analyze
The new Al-Qaeda and the
Al-Qaeda
Western governments all financing years ago years ago
Exactly two years ago
This is a real person Army
He has said that over and over again
He's not wrong about
At one point
Syria is definitely
We're doing most
And then you have
Muslim
Islam
Bright
Isis itself isn't
Created by us
Accepting a tertiary Cent
And any like the instances where there are
Like things that have
We have Supply that have gone back to them
Pretty accidentally
In the same way that you know
You give somebody s*** and someone takes it
Like how we
Sent a billion dollars in cash or whatever it was
Sure
Questions are you going to cash
Hash
Weird very weird
Hash in a
I've no idea
Possible
Western world and the Middle East
As a proxy for the under Saudi Arabia
Potion to use for the next day
Is the Muslims rats real
But it was manufactured
Accomplice to it
I put the rattlesnakes in the back
What's your emergency
Control
Where did you find
With 15 starving wolves
Run the World
Another
Three examples of the same exact a little accepting rhetorically unnecessary
Stewardship
10 million ladybugs in there
He doesn't another hour of just examples of ways he could accidentally
So I mean 50 at the argument that he's he's making there
I don't think that this is the way he would make it but there is a way to make it
Reasonable a
And that is that our foreign policy is so f***** up
We keep creating Terror
Through bombing churches
Through
Starving Children through killing civilians
And that is
Creating more and more people who want to hurt us
I think
What do you saying is
Is different
I don't know what he say
Well okay
Yours the interest
Cynical
I do have that
Inclination
Agree with that idea
Oh man what are what are you big Alex Jones
If I was going to conspiracy theories
Yeah
Nn
I think I think
He's not
Terribly wrong
Describing
People who judge
Incapable of thinking
Haha
Or even the potential consequences are outweighed by whatever immediate game you're trying to make
Terrorism thing
Is absolutely
2X
Like there's no other way to describe
What's going on
Now is that cuz there's
Globalist plot or is
Is it because
All of our weapons
Went over to Iraq
And we don't need the
And we Spanish
Kind of money on it so we want to get some of that
So we sell it to police
Isaac
I think that is definitely the
Economic
Version
Are there economic explanation for the militarization
Some of the police force
But I don't think that terrorism necessarily
He's creating that friend of militarized police
I think it's beef at the fake
Fear of terrorism
Actually not created
As much by the globalist
Edited by people like Alex Jones ironically giving away your rights
You need to
Yourself again
Yeah strong government with a strong military
Spell obviously
You don't want that cover
Control over
You want them to be able to
Military force
.0001
I put another death
But then it also
He's trying to have it both ways
With that Arch
You know it is that like
I think you nailed it we want this strong government but they're not strong
Stay out of my business
But don't give us anything
Yeah
I'm sick of having stuff from you
I don't want to be dependent on the government
Now admittedly I have a radio show
Flint Michigan where they don't even have fun
Can regular drinking water even though we've known about it
Any other method that
Outdoor
But also
I mean like
Did you make some money off of people buying guns from a Christian gun maker
Where are we
What is going on
Anyway I think
I think you're right
This sort of area there's a little bit more interesting gray area
I still disagree with Alex I think it's full of s***
I disagree with him
Tubidy
Like
It isn't
Tyson
Because
Your ears seeing that you're smelling the Tramp alittle more
It sounds like
Man
Then I go
Say that
In the government
Smart enough to
Polish
Right right right
Who aren't
Borderline
Moronic let's count of the charm of 9/11
Anyway Alex
Wants you to know
But he's got great information
You look marvelous
So this next clip Alex accidentally says something that makes him think twice
Never seen that before he's talking about how his information is rock-solid
He gets good information
But then he starts to talk about it
Since his we're in the past where
Other people's information
Is that this
And I think there's a moment you can see in his face was kind of like
Shoulda brought this up a little defensive and throws to break
So
I know this 20 years ago
Rockefeller
I read the opposition to it
If I was in a war which I am
Operating unquote attacking us
This is back when he may be couldn't skip as many breaks
For the Mercer money came in as I suspect
Is another idea that he has
It's based on
Illuminati beliefs
This idea of like
Sort of externalizing program
He got to show people what you're doing in order for it to be so mean anyting
Are a lot of times when you talk about these Illuminati rituals that they do the halftime shows and stuff
It's called a lesser Magic
Whatever you like
Eyebrow raised
Yeah
If this idea of it even extend
To like putting something
The globalists are going to do into a science fiction movie
So it like
People used to the idea
Magic game
Things in plain sight
End up putting out all their white papers that say these things out
Think they say
Don't
Is another part of that which again feeds into that
Little bit of that song
Which is like why they had
Pullman become
Independence Day
Paired
For him to be
Absolutely
Totally
Who else would we lost him
No we lost pack
Does next Wipeout
Get super condescending about how you need to wake
Fuk up
I'm really tired
AMF World part of them
Red Palace 2 we're going to fire you if you do anymore
Sulzer keep keep in mind that he said
Basically
That's it that's a qualifying word
It is
It is we say it a lot
Basically with you
But whenever you're not making a real surgeon
Stuff like basically
Betsy beers a freelancer
Federal
The third world
About how they would depress economies
Companies themselves bailed out by the country
And the public is true
Is the proper word
Totally literacy
When it comes to basic Financial system
MBC that's all
Within the Paradigm of the control
So that itself
I don't know
Trying to say I don't know what that the end I don't I don't I don't
You just
Every single thing he was saying up to that barzyk really even the world work
What are you what are you doing which button
The Big Bang
Did
They did
Cars
Them to get ahold
And then the banks themselves were bailed out five
Yes this is true because it's now
Not enough to sell your f****** huckster
If you
I think it is
I don't
I think it's enough
For me to want
Just fires all over the
IMS plan
Riot
And then when you're burning down cities the globalist
Can come in and buy everything up for super cheap let's get them
No but here's the thing so I did Google
Condescendingly told me to 2 years ago
Yes I googled this
I looked for IMS leaks 2002
And I found an article in the guardian by Greg Palace
Where he doesn't
He doesn't interview with a guy who used to work for the IMs
And got fired
Ugly
And he had some really terrible things to say
About the IMF and how they operate
I think a lot of it is
Spiritually fairly accurate
Stuff about like
You know
Beggars
Take it
Getting countries to borrow more
Then they showed him
Default on their loans
But you buy up like their water plants and stuff like that
And then you can even just basically f*** over a country
But there's nothing in there
Just the America
There's nothing in his article
And there are no leaks
That are out anywhere I couldn't find any primary documents
Right
Documents
In that article but they aren't anywhere
Republic
They never got
Put out or whatever but I'm not going to go to
But they're not
But
So
Nowhere in any of it has
Anything to do about trying to call
Collapse
Entire regions of the world
There's nothing in there like an evil plan that the West is neck
All this stuff is fantasies
From Alex's brain
Which is
The basic
That I was talking about earlier
The truth he's got a guild that s*** and that's where it becomes a lie
And it becomes propaganda
Serving
His globalist One World Government
Boner
Paranoia brain
Is that
It seems like an
Twisted in the
The current
That lead
Pizza
Seems like he's divorced from reality
Yeah
F*** that popcorn
I don't start at the beginning
Vulture totally given to me
Trumps
I told you I'm not supposed to have
But I told you before we started recording we're going to see if Alex Jones
But he's still a liar
He's still bulshit artist still obsessed with the globalist different dude
By this
I'm not Charmed
But I do
This way I'm I'm much more
Willing to enter
Then I am
You know
They're attempting
Sticks all over
He still thinks that though it is a point
Whether we're going to get to where I think you might
You will get to it Alex Jones
Shining through
Here's a clip where he is
Very he would never say this today
Number 326
I do not agree with this at all he would be
God damned if you said this today
Russia
Is defending its population
What is faultless
Shutdown
American
WikiLeaks
The New World Order frog
So there's nowhere to run
Russia
When there is no firewall firewall
A global government
LV Nowhere to Run
People running this world government
The world has ever seen
Maximum Alpha tyrant
Maximum
Alpha Tyrant is the sort of linguistic version of three examples of animals in your bed
If excessive we gotcha
Well I think that's a great beer to Great IPA
Country black widows in your bed
He would never say those things like he still says
Did George Soros is responsible for Ukraine
The uprising in Ukraine
But like for overthrowing Ukraine
Viciously
From his language
Pretty much since Donald Trump got around
These positive things
About Putin
And about how
The Russians
We're just protecting their people in the brain
Absolutely, people have a maximum Alpha tyrant
Sure he's not literally resembling
Episode
Yeah
Crazy
Still crazy
He's gone so far back
Forced on all of this
It's
Like I wonder I wonder if there is a step
Too far for him
Is it is there any
Anything that
He will not
Switching
Globalist
Yeah but the definition
That's great that's great point
Always ever change
Yeah if you can be a globalist one day
And a
Patriot the
Much like
The bouncing back and forth on WikiLeaks
Everyone
Right now
Where is like
No I I guess in that case no there's no
Second Amendment
Maybe
Because he
You didn't always used to be so into God as he is now so that's even like a little wobbly
He can't go back
His belief in God
What it is God wants
Sure esoteric weird God but
The twelfth dimension
That are out the
Didn't go back on that one
I think it might just be the Second Amendment
Like the only thing he has
If you turned against guns
You would lose almost all of his body
Yeah that's probably
Now there's a lot of weird factions in his audience that I think one of the biggest through-line
Wow so
Wait what
But it was cool to years ago
So this next clip he's going to talk he's talking about Greece
So much
Said about Greece
As all repetition
It's all just
The globalist they're planning
To take them down
Blah blah blah
The great people themselves
No
Globalist
Sure
The victims of his banking system
So in the end is next Clippers and talk about how
It's a bank holiday
Because on a real nice Ram
Real nice riff
On the idea of a bank holiday does a little bit
And then
Before we go any further
Right
What the f***
Is he talking about with his Barry Goldwater and Rockefeller
Who cares
Who cares where are these weird-ass roof
She's coming from
Books he read and didn't understand years and years ago that's all that's gone
I've learned not
To chase these rabbit rabbit down the hole
Reference and consistently they don't say what he says
Book by Barry Goldwater
I'm just not going to do it
Autotime
He had some good idea I got a lot of Philip K Dick's already alright sorry
I'm on my I'm on two voices from the street
The second novel
Published in 2000
Play after the eye
Bank holiday
Loses the thread
Right loses the thread
Starts rambling
I will get back
Meniscus
Closest Banks
Call Lil Jay
Joe Swanson talks about
Freedom initiative
Affordable
Entrepreneur
You
By Lesley house
Office Professional
Delavan
Celebrity
Closest bank
Do you have any idea what he's talking about
The reason Greece
Close their Bank
Ahead of the referee
Water skiing
Because
They didn't know what the referendum
There was a huge
Chance they would
Which is a natural human reaction to your money but if you're hurting ever
Everybody else
And yourself
And everybody goes
People for people to close bags but it's actually in everyone's best interest
Manipulative in like hey
During this time
A bit for like
Scholastic
Endeavors
Doesn't waterski I know that guy
We'll get to that in a minute. In 2015
Talk to you about it
If you were a foreigner you could take money out
So what he was doing and a lot of people were doing
Was that they were since they have foreign bank accounts
Helping
As though there was a bunch of resources on the ground
Independently
Of the people who couldn't get money out of their own bank account
Just you know very helpful
Not always Americans other European countries with a B
People
Hearing about
Diva Beyonce
Show me closing the banks of the right thing to do
Yes bottom line
Now he goes on to say
He makes a great point
Username
Patriot Act
It's bad and it's called The Patriot Act
Right
That good point
Are you laugh
Almost no time having Goodwill
Then goes on to rant about men in dresses with mustache
Who's Leslie
You don't know I don't know who Liza globalist
Picked him to be the face of things still don't know who that is
If your
I'm going to tell you and the listeners who Leslie is
But before I do
What you just use one name
Leslie Nielsen
Yeah
But also if you don't know who Leslie is or you do
I want take a little Pole
Before I tell you who he is
Go ahead and buy sound off
Now I'll tell you
Leslie
Leslie was a homeless activist
And Austin TX
You homeless for many years and was a huge advocate but headed up a lot of causes
For homeless rights
Police brutality rights these sorts of things
Ultimatum ultimatum big spectacle out of himself
I wore women's clothing crossdresser
Wear women's clothing around 6th Street
And go and hang around get the word out
He'd also like to party
He party around 2 if that's how I ended up beating him I was partying on 6th Street
Andy came up new super nice
We smoked a cigarette
And I we hug
There's a picture of us somewhere
After he got the s*** beat out of him in 2009
He was I who found unconscious Outdoors
I was transported to University Medical Center
Critical condition
Does October 3rd 2009
Within two weeks you regained Consciousness and was transferred to a rehabilitation
When he was released on October 23rd
That's a vibe
Reported that he had been attacked after commenting to group of people about the dangers of drugs
Just reasonably responsible
Believable that's within the scope of
Yeah sort of
Active
Sure
Also
Not outside the spectrum of reality that he was beat up
Because he is an old crossdress
Yeah there's a possibility that these people beat him up for that after he said something about truck
Those people are there
Kicked out of in 2009 and suffered head trauma then
Three years later two and a half years later
I just deteriorated from that
Ended up
Trying to get some brain surgery
It was successful.
After that okay
Tragic story is also a very empowering story someone who
I did a lot with his wife
Depression on millions of people
And help the charitable causes that have helped
Tons and tons of people
F*** you for minimizing him in such a way
To say that either
Trendy
In addressing a mustache you piece of s***
Was
Would like
To the point where
With all of his support
If he had asked for it
People would have
Made him not home
Correct
The towards the end of his life you may not have been home
I think throughout a lot of it
After that I mean Alex Jones
He did
An immense amount
And Alex Jones
Has
Turn that
Ura
Meaningless
You've made money off your homeless app
Or whatever it was
Now which
Absolutely would gain you much more
I would also say that he ran for mayor 3
X
Does like that would run for office
Mystery novels about him and his crime
Yeah but like it's
Full of awesome weird personality
Anyway
As we discussed
They had what was it
Was it a balloon store
Pinata store
Pinatas
Next to a cat trying to shut down
Misunderstanding of b*******
I was like
I know Leslie
That's awesome
Yeah super cool
Alex come on
He should know better
Alex's the closed-minded
Yeah
How do you
Hero the world
But
Probably also a drunk let's
Be clear
Mental illness
All of that
I have no doubt that by no means was he
Sure at the same time
I am not a saint nicer as f*** haven't done as much good as Plus
On that level
Like that
F*****'-a
I am from everything I could look up I see no evidence
Globalist involved
And his wife
So now you might be asking yourself Gaia
You might be asking yourself alright this is
Years in the past
Yes
Did Alex Jones
Always have his smooth as transitioning into a sales pitch scale
You might be asking yourself that I don't think
Before I go any further when I tell you stuff selling out
To his own kind of know
Yeah cuz he did also have a long pause a minute
So now he's not wasn't always as good as having an off-day
Now
He's gets into this sales trip
She's overly
Concerned with
Gay marriage
And getting sued out of existing
Two-and-a-half years
Listen to the sales pitch
Who owns me to place in its entirety
But
It's a good thing that I listen to Alex Jones everyday
The only time I've ever set
But if I did
If I did
I would not have been able to recognize this
Next clip
As evidence
Of Allah
In a clip
That we played
On
March 30th episode
He invalidates an argument that he made this March
2 years
This is very exciting for me
F****** Luna
Listen to this
But that is the
Craziest thing I've ever heard of
Listen to this
Survival shieldx2
Group
Is closed
Krystal's
But you have to go to
Contracts got a bid
Get these
Drill
Cuz you got to find the weirdo companies that are out Drilling in the right area that will do for them
We're the weirdos that the owner
Live.com
Now the clip from the March 30th episode is way too f****** long for me to play here cuz I'm almost
At the point of Tears drunk sales pitch
You do remember you saying and I will refresh for the listeners what he was saying
Is Hughes
On March 30th of 2017
He was saying
Set the globalist we're trying to cut off his iodine
Supply
And he was using almost every single argument
The cheapest made here for a while
He but he was saying that it was
Some sort of concerted effort against him
Listen not many people do they thread
Do wooden a******
No I can
I couldn't
TV argument
Okay
Know about his beeper
And the wacky
People
Who do that
Now they're going
I don't like
I love you I love you sweetie
It's not speeches its frustration cuz it's like
Yeah okay fine
Alright
Done
Alex Jones game is playing
Every single argument
No
I'm super powers
Super male Vitality I'm doing just fine right there
I don't have the
Whatever else it is unclear
I don't either understand any of
The deeper the iodine
That according to all of the scientific
Research that I have read
There is
Plano
I have read some reviews of some of his product
Recently
I don't know if they're jokes
Or not
Like they're so bizarre that I don't know if there's someone making
Like just trolling
I have no idea but there are a number of them for caveman
His bone broth
She loves it taste like chocolate
There's a bunch of them though have the same sort of
Hatter they follow the same pattern that is
I
Can't not take this
Okay but it's not like I feel so good when I'm on it as if I feel so shity when I don't take
And that to me to me in the cave
Like I know
From
Pastor cute that you get into an elevated state for a long enough time
Normal feel shity
Really sucks with all your heart rate whatever bone this
The chaga mushroom and all this b*******.
I don't know what the f*** else is in there it's about
And s*** like that trucker speed all of the all of the GNC
Vitamin
Regulated by the
Spend billions of dollars
Sure
Millions of.
Yeah but
It makes total sense to be like
The diesel joke review
Yeah
Totally I would believe is that it really sucks you up
In a good way
Basically
A couple of drinks
A couple of or even like
Once this goes off sale I'm not going to be able to afford it
And I'm really going to miss it
I need it is really a huge bummer which actually could
Bring into focus is
Economic model
A little bit tougher to sort of habit forming
53 /
It totally makes sense as a model
If you tell
You got a couple more clips
And then we're going to delve into two
Adventures
Adventurism
What happened
So is
Really
Really unfortunate
Alex is walking
What I would describe as
Tightrope of a metaphor
And I don't think you succeeded
I love his
I love is in village
This is dangerous is like
If I threw
100 black widows
Into his Studio
Them in their own separate
Okay
Great metaphor I'm going to say because this is such a tightrope
Let's put the mic down and enjoy this because
I think we're going
To hear him make
Something that borders on a very racist
Metaphor
But now it hits my ears
Very racist because I could see it
For what he's trying to say
He's talking about with
The globalist
If you work against
Good
Because instinctively
Because they're jealous
And they have historical
Over and over again
Them
Corruptible
Talk about genetics
No
You can
Oh no don't get dachshund
It comes from really mentally ill biters
That's really a screwed-up breeder they got problems
Dog
You got a race between good health
Think about power
Do you want the power
You don't work 95 and put the kids through college and then go out to the
Get the latest Mark Dice video it's one of the worst ever
I love I love that plug at the end
What I agree
It's terrible so what's this a metaphor
Sourate more races that he couches it with me I'm not talking about a black bloodline
Immediately went to I am protecting myself
Coil full on I'm not a racist
But perfectly absolutely
The reason I said it was on the border is because what the point is
Trying to make I think is that these globalists
Come from different stock than
We were genetically engineered
I think I remember the five percent
Sedation.
I'm glad to have another induction
I don't think
You can never you can never make that argument succinctly like that he's trying to make
When you're using genetic lines
And stuff like that there's less and less and less
Full hog
And you are saying
That the elite are made up of then like
9 powerful Bloodlines it existed for blood
Then
Your metaphor is fine you're not being racist
You're being an idiot
Yeah
So
The way I understood
He was trying to
To say
As Alex Jones's pop
All humans are
Genetically
Good
But
People who are genetically
Bad
Like the Ducks
There's a biter spider
There's
And now now if you want if you want to pull the the Dachshund transcend race in this metaphor
I'm fine with that
Except
A very specific
Genetic
Staying
Like the Dachshund
In particular
Is more like
Idle
I don't see any way to get out of this
Without you at least going
Alex
You know
You're being racist right especially because it is white
Somebody was in the bucket Buckley was at the potentiometer lights
No Alex
Alex
Crystallize this deeper crystallize
I think the reason that it comes off as racist
Is
Is because this argument has been made by races
From time immemorial cider inferior because
Is of the shity blood by
Argument
It has that baggage
That comes along with it when you're talking about something
You know
Like from the start they were like
Their terman 22b
Left
Right
Relates directly back to the protocols of the Elders of Zion
Zionist cabal has about humans
Alex thinks that the globalists have about us
It's a direct mirror
Through this
Racist
That's racist
And I think another reason that it is raises I have to stick
This down is because
The idea of the behavior of being a biter
Something like that
That is something that is in your jeans
That is not like
Instead of learned behavior
Yeah it's
It's just
It's really troubling
It's really troubling for me
To hear him
Make arguments
Especially because if you are a rapist
And you hear that
Did you get it
That is also like a
Smokescreen
For you to say you're not ready
Because he
Preamble that way
It's not about
White black
Asian
Peter
So you get to like hide behind
It's not that I'm racist
Talking about
Natick
Yeah
Skin color
Phrenology
Good
And maybe the
People that I think are bad
At this point Alex introduces the fact that he's going
Start taking calls
Yes I am
Introduce
Topics that he wants to talk about
Want to talk about Greece
For a dark but how
The world is
Being overrun by right
And then
Poses this question
That I think is poorly frame
Will Smith
Bailouts
Greece
Seems like neither of those options
WhatsApp
I don't know a third option
I can't say
Either this is going to be the great Global meltdown to be another thing that the globalist have orchestrated
Brett so it's going to be the Great
Not quite it's like
It's either going to be the worst thing ever or just
The worst
Yeah
He also doesn't really end up taking any meetings
Call
One guy about the
More about Russia and its exact same
Yeah but
No calls were worthwhile it sucks
Cuz I take up a good amount of the Shelf do we lose like a good 40 minutes
Of usable materials
Garbage disposal Falls
But
Before he gets to take phone calls in Earnest real quick
Were there any
Did any
1 grandma
I'm already on board
If she wanted to talk about how the bond market
If it falls apart
That is a bad way to Sally if it falls apart
Then people
I won't get paid
And Alex
Tries to talk like you understand
The situation
She doesn't do it
Third party
I don't really either smell bulshit
Hey there just dancing around Alex's using $5 word
She's like
You know you always talk about this
This other ring thing you know you got the divide-and-conquer mentalities
You always talk about black and white but you never talk about in his eye
Talk about it talk about it more
Generations
It's kind of nada
Lenovo think he does
A bunch
Episode
Is introduced Topix
He's going to get to and dumb
He keeps having like plastic
Never gets to in Pittsburgh
How about
Is the band The American Flag for about 2 in a minute
The first thing where I was like
Phuc yea let's get into this Alex
So I actually have a lot to say about that before we get
Religious freedom speech
Open Society to where we accepted all this
Now we're not going to be tolerated
Yes don't want anyone
Don't want to have a Catholic Church
Finger shut down no good
This is the opposite of Tolerance immune system
No one is forcing a church to pay for abortions
Know everybody was
No I remember I remember the most important thing that I talked
With a lot of people
Hey
You know what I want
Forest churches
To pay for Maya
Having no give me money
Catholic Church
Also
Nobody
To pay for those aboard
So
You have a right to put on a dress
Yes
This is the great joke of social engineering
Where they made mean trendy
The new religion and now people
With the new
Until they only
Puritanical
Surface
The door up to whatever
They want
It's Politically Incorrect
Let your washer out the window
Six-years-old across the street
So
Spoiler alert you talked about going to the
Sparks are like 4 minutes you really lost the thread in terms of complaining about the ACLU
11 year old kid who got arrested for
Authorities
Oh that was
There were neighbors who thought that the parents weren't
The kid was always home alone
Since I got off work much later zielinski kit
Nosy neighbors
I believe I looked into it and I think it is like
Guys magic f****** business
Their motivation was protecting this child cuz they're concerned with
For the time that the parents were or didn't have access to a bathroom who's locked out of his house
So
To make the matters worse the mom
By whatever she was being questioned about it was like
The officers themselves said he had a big yard he could have gone to the bathroom on it
The right you know I left the dog alone in the house
Be super
Into what people are complaining about
Bishop had the kids taken away and they did get them back
Yeah it was it was a f*****-up
Situation a little bit of talking about
He's saying that it is like this big regret
Destroy the family
Always reason why
Dinner
A right-winger tells me one of those
Anecdote
If you look in
Google it
All the sudden you start finding
Yeah
But in reality
Unfortunately there are a number of people on the left to do that too but
If usually not as a like
Obvious
Or at least not as awful
Yeah I have their agenda is generally to create more
Good I feel bad for you lies and propaganda but it's not
Usually like
It's very dark
Yeah if
Sort of left-wing
Do you mean now
Left-wing
Duboku
When he got his way and Trump was elected
Let's let's say like if entire
Congress
Is Republican
It's okay it's okay
Well there'll
There are saving grace is
These people
By virtue virtual of what they believe
They are already revealing themselves
Dumb
So again I are saving grace
Is we are being run by
People to dumb
To enact the dumb s*** they won
There is that like
That that upper right quadrant of the evil stupid
Yep
Yeah g herbo
Yeah yeah
But today is it like if you take someone like Keith Olbermann
Who is kind of
Left-wing propaganda
You could possibly
If you got his way
You better have more social programs but might be better safety nets for people
Have you built that on Ally I'm not super thrilled with that I don't think that's good but the end result is way better than us having
Mentally decaying
Bigoted as our president
That is
Probably for the better
Totally scaling back
I mean every single day
New f******
Anyway
Perfect summation of
World we live in
Me Clear My Throat
It's a new fuc
The new thing rolled back that's a school lunch program for going away
Let's privatize it
I swear to you
This is the
Ultimate frustration
I would
Absolutely live with
If he had the most aggressive anti-climb
I know we've been over this
Because then the human race would
Continue
Incorrectly
Global Society
Yeah I know
Stay Rihanna
A boy
All right so now it's time for us to get to the phone
Policy policy
Battle Cry
It's very bad
If it ends on that kind of
Minor key in the very bad battle
June 24th
Episode
Chaka block
We'll talk about how
It's evil and wrong the people are trying to get the Confederate flag taken down
Places
You if you think
Their argument is that the free speech
I don't I don't want to have that argument cuz I don't care
I don't care if someone has a Confederate flag in their car in their house
Publicly I don't really even care but if it's like a State Building or something like that
Play very much care
That's bad
If you're if you're
If you're not a horrifying
No I don't even try to answer that
Subscribe to that
You doing it
Things that you could point
There's a foot that is the smokescreen argument for
I want my racism to be left to celebrate Old Dixie
Who are
Huge racist
Yeah but that's not all of them
And I don't think it's right to ban flag
To have it up and say buildings
Some stuff like that
And I think
For the most part
That's the argument that people of had
I don't think there is
Legitimate or widespread group who is saying
Let's ban the flag.
Federate flag.
But
Is Alex's possess
Alex pink
But that's what people are saying
It's the same thing with the Ten Commandments in front of the the court
Nobody wants
Reading the 10 f******
10 commandment but I don't want those
In front of the
The courthouse
Because
Is not
Implies that it's Christian just
Exact time magic show
I was going to say Christian Okoye
Football Christian Okoye
Another team
Alex
Extrapolate
11 bayham
Alex on the 24th is going hog
Wild
About this
He is just going on like
Next on the American flag
Yep
So that's what he says
Like Rush Limbaugh thing
Here's what I'm zapopan.
Mark Dice
One of the worst
Special Report
He goes out
And does one of his Fieldpiece
We talked about Mark Dice before
Alyssa
You are
Reports before
He's very ineffective as a man of the sea
I think has some kind of
Personality disorder
He's unable
He's unable to make eye contact with people as he's interviewing them on the street he looks past
Upset
It's it's not fun
It's not good
Alex Jones sent Mark Dice out
Around with a video
It's possible to get people to sign
People on the beach
Society
Trying to get a new flag
Get rid of the Old Glory
And get a new flag
In order in honor of the New World Order
Arabi a pyramid
He's buried with Hulk Hogan
No I wish
Too sweet I know it's not that one it's like I'm at the back of the dollar bill the All-Seeing Eye on the pier
Pyramid
Chico's hours
And does this video
Alex posted on Infowars
Drudgereport link to the video
Epic
Alex
On Infowars
Starts reporting
But people are calling
For the American flag to be banned
She has made
Loop of b******* it's a complete Ouroboros supplies
Is insane to see it like
Just literally this is exactly what's going on
It's amazing
They're making the news they're commenting on the news
And then they're commenting
Becomes news
Exactly model of right-wing at the at the bottom
There is no like
There is nobody who's asking for the flag
To be bad
There is only Mark Dice on the street
That is all there is
And now we're going to listen to Mark dice's report
And I want to tell you
I'm going to pause it a couple points because I have taken notes about all of these people that he goes and talks to
Excellent and it's good for him
Here we go
Cheerios that report
From Mark Dice
American flag
Is first
First person is already against him
No I'm out of here
Even Fox News edited that guy out
Put it in the middle somewhere
Make a funny face to the camera
Drunk
He's not staggering around Alex Jones style drunk
He's having a good time out there on the beach
Stanford football
He's looking for his
Nevermind I don't want to ruin it but he also does not send
People are offended by the American flag
In racism
New American flag petition
New American flag
When you don't want to sign something
You're a weirdo
Charges into the shop
His face is never shown
He comes in and he aggressively
Petition
I don't think this is a real person
That's a meat like
Exactly what I said
To somebody who is
Do you want to help
Save the Dolphins
It sounds like a great idea
I'm going to leave
I got to go I have other non dolphin related activities to do right now
A good idea
Hugo
You're with you because you're weird
Why aren't you looking at
Oh my God
Scares me so much
He has so little charisma
Like I've said this about people like I don't know the Jerome corsi is of the world David Knight
I would I would
F****** go to
Across the world in a balloon
Before I said.
What's a metaphor
So here comes the guy who who just charges in
So you think you can understand a lot of people are offended by the
American flag imperialism
Think it's about time we do that when she agree maybe something with an All-Seeing Eye and a pyramid
So as he's trying to get lucky
As he's trying to describe what the new flag would look like the guys
Just walks off
Signs Aries man
Just something to represent the New World Order
This guy I don't know if he speaks
He doesn't seem to register awareness of the things
That Mark Dice is saying he's wearing like a muscle tee
I need to sort of like
Is this little looking at him confused
Signs of saying n word
I will admit I also like the reaction of the guy who signs it and then just says f*** yeah and then walks away
Whatever man
Yeah I might do that
He's just talking to this guy who doesn't say a word
About Alex
Goes on a
F******
Just teased off on this guy with a muscle shirt
American flag over the capitol to signify the new world order but we just needed some more signatures thanks for support
American flag Confederate flag
Modern Talking
Wendy's
101 variants
Those how to act
Guys walking around acting top
And they don't want
To know what's going on
I just want to look cool. Other people
And put on a front
These guys eyes every time
Finish up this week looking
It's up with that
Do you think those guys white or not
Go with
New
Bingo
Prayers to the old American flag and
Forgot to put up a new American flag
Over the capitol to signify the new world order but we just needed some more signatures thanks for supporting the new American flag
Confederate flag in a lot of cities to end the era of racism in
Who cares
It is so boring let me walk you through
The American flag
I like
The American
Mark shut up
Flags
Person he talks to is a really nice girl
Who
I think she's just super excitable and happy
Oh
Either way
Next Thursday talks to his lady and he's like hey we're going to try and get a new flag of she's like now I like the stars
You guys walk up
One of them is a chubby dude
Probably
Because I think you're tired
It's him and another guy
They're too skateboard dudes
It's like tie-dye shirt never guys like in a muscle shirt
Yeah go to the beach
Because
Do that dumb people are there don't want to answer your question
He might not be allowed in
Only open-air areas
Yeah
Deirdre only open areas
20ft outside of any public
Who may or may not be high and they both sign it but they're also like
Whatever
Said they talked to break it off is two dudes who are
Straight up
Baked out of their mind
And one of them is just
With his mouth slightly open
But has a backpack
What are you doing
Mark Dice
I don't know what point you're making but if it is that people want
The American flag ban
Haven't most of them
People we've heard I've just been like
F*** off
There's
One first guy
Who likes my group of two said absolutely not
The second guy said
Is the lady who walked away
Everybody
Everybody else was ambivalent about it
You're a random dude asking
Don't be a
Dick right now
That's all I heard In that clip
And it's not even like the the shity
Leno like man on this
Where he gets
People that actually talk
Answer
If
It's just a bullshiter
Prank
It's not a prank there is nothing here
Cuz if you sign that
Then
So what
If you a violently politely sign that for us if you want the American flag ban
That just proves that you're a decent
Person who doesn't know how to
Have boundaries here like the old just like
Like the easiest way to get
To go away
Zionism
Exactly come from it because that's such a
Wild
I've signed
Hundreds of things I don't agree with
Matter there's no
Possibility of that
Like even if you hate America
Which is
You're not you're not going to actually
Genuinely
Regardless of Americas
Horrific Acts
Throughout
Are exist
Stars and Stripes really is a symbol of what it is
Like
Play Fire Woman
Yeah it is everything that America wishes it could
It is all of the all of the states represent
It is all of us
Together
It is built around that idea
Of either we hang
Together are we
Alex Jones quotes
Okay alright so actually
Will Shakespeare we're coming towards the end
Hour-and-a-half of the show
Yeah he has an interview with this guy named Lionel
One name like Madonna
Lionel
Land
He is a fast-talking New York do
Is it something else
The show before
I strongly disagree with him about almost everything
But I don't hate hearing him talk
Gas
I would be in a hot air balloon across the world
Take a short trip
Miles down the road
Maybe
Depends on the speed limit
Yes possibly
So they have a really long interview
Where
I caught out
So much
So repetitive
At one point
Lionel
Starts describing what his plan would be
If he was going to
Destroy our country
Interesting
Already cuz two years later
See if you see any similarities to what's going on
I'm going to destroy this country
Here's what I would do
Informal
I would distract the bread and circuses
The people more than ever
I would have a foundation for much of the economy
This tissue thin veneer of cotton candy
The derivative
You say what
Dollars
Alex of American Express
Ronald Reagan
Accidentally
I can't believe it 40 episodes in
I don't know what that is
Perfect
Trump rally rally Trump rally
Weather
God dammit this man
But he's saying it is this what the globalist are doing
Not what
Unless
Recently come out
As an international
Well Alex's
F*** off a battery
Not really
He's a good guy
Ignore
He's just saying that because
He has to
Impenetrable
Are never going to be Puerto Rico
Iceland or Portugal where is the United States
Strange language for vaccine deny Airshow
You would that is exactly what Trump is doing with us we're going to renegotiate these deals because
Go to be immune from Alta
Exceptionalism
Perfect summation
Like if I were going to destroy the
Fireline
Because that guys f****** on it another phase to this
Obstruction of
I'm a big fan of it
Mission where we had
Split up into
And then we're going to confuse people
Settle for something
A full lemon juice
Flagger battleflag controversy
What else about the globalist in terms of externalizing their plan
Literally
Like we've already Illustrated year this idea that they took
The
For a cross-country trip
I want to know where he's at he would talk to us
That's the dude
We've already shown this
Fake story about banning the American flag going from an Infowars video to an article on Infowars
Garage to something it is reported on the Alex Jones Show
That is creating fake outrage
Now he hears the bulshit first
Sing me out right here in a
Because what he's talking about is
People who are
Legitimately offended
Bye
In this case
The Confederate flag
Which is denying people their feelings
About the history of brutal
Racing
So that part is what he's really talking about when he said something
Give people something to be mad about
It is
A complete
Perfect demonstration I wanted to bring this up earlier I can't remember which Cliff it was in the hole.
Has the eggs
Jackson history of brutal racism
You're not wrong but you're off on the wrong the wrong direction
What I'm saying is we need to ban the American
It's not about that
He's talking about all of these politics
Kinds of things
All these ideas about trendies in
Wedding dresses with mustache
All of the stuff is parceled within that it is
A perfect expression of this
Angry male privilege
Expresses
Everything that is like
Black lives matter
Globalist
Cityalight
If this anytime that you're pissed off about these things
Divide and conquer strategies so if you care about the Confederate
Or if you care about is he even says I remember which episode was in one of the other ones
We're not covering please talking about like
Yeah sure
Cop shoots guy every week
I see articles about them guys too
Hope you're not right right understanding
Shooting white guys too
You can be against
Both the point of them the fact that he
Is that
Long history
And it is something that is
Targeted
That it is Paramount
Isaac
Definitely says more about your priorities
When you're mad
People who are complaining about cops
Shooting black people because no one likes
What if we had a Father's Day
Your Mother's Day can always always about celebrating women like what if what if we had a white history
But nobody talks about
It's not missing it's missing the mark and they frame it as
Society is confused
Society is being tricked by this divide-and-conquer game that's the way they can Elevate themselves in the same way
Play the Daleks inoculate
It's all from that doctor metaphor
By being like it's the global divide
I'm not against your point
I just think that it's so inconsequential compared to buy
This
The issues that I a very smart
White man who figured out
Right it's very stupid
It's a bummer
Pressing
It's one of those things
Over and over and over
VI
Idea that
They're doing
What weird
So we can do
Like this is just there doing it
So we have to fight them
Which justifies
Yeah
Always it's always the
Playbook like oh they're playing the victim
Whenever they say that religious
Freedom is
It's exactly what your you're
F*** you
That's why we're so great because we don't play that game
Without
Screaming at the
No
So fresh
It's very obvious unless you have an agenda
But the reason you have that agenda
Him so you never really have to look
Is
Lionel also being an a****** again
And this
Biscuits into
To the world being run by bankers
Which is
Well
What episode of a let people understand
The what and who run the world
Very very at the top of the pyramid
Delete
Gangsters in Illinois
Yep you guys are being Jews
That's that's anti
When you say the banks are powerful yes they are but they don't
62 people own more than the bottom half
Entire world
The bankers
Why are politicians people with the 62 people that own
Call of the Wild Art old getting together around
Mark Zuckerberg
Some of them are people like that or like Mark Cuban
You're like he has billions of dollars
Right but like they're not Central bankers
Like you understand it's not like
No I bet argument Falls flat
I agree with you in that
Bankers here is
Is code for
Banksters this is purely do we not bleed
Like
It's that whole thing
But
That there is again
This is an area where the
The kernel of Truth isn't
Because
Again
Bankers are
F****** everybody
That is a thing
Yeah but I still will not die
Because I know what they're saying
They're not saying the same things that you or I or someone
Right it's dog whistle e
It can't be taken outside of the context of all of these other thing all these other
All of these other like
It's insane I understand that I
Keep bringing up
Call
I have a pretty well but like literally
Multiple things that he says
Directly mirror
Parts from that very debunked
Anti-semitic book
It is
Clear that most of his velocity comes from
Understand
I think that is something
Most likely
We waffle
But most likely cuz I don't think
He's more of a and out now White
Nationalist
I agree
But like
Did the point I'm trying to make is that
Within that landscape
When you say something like the world is run by
A small group of elite banksters
You can't say that
Alex
Resoundingly agree with you
Without it being taken
Heart
Of that
Cosmology
Part of that world
In philosophy
And anybody who listens to his show
Whether they're consciously aware of where they come from or not they know that philosophy
I want may hear stuff like this
Where there is a kernel of truth right help
Further into
Big part that's not true agree to Part B is this evil racist bulshit
So that's
Here's my
Kind of
Question
Okay do you think
We could ever co-opt
Protocols
So so they're antisemita
Is
Still
Targeted towards those that idea of
The bankers who run the
There's more absolutely the whole fake media thing is a big part of it too and
If we could like
Just
Deep Earth crystallized
Into that I
I think
If we if
We really did it
PetSmart I don't like where you're going
We could on one particular
Situation
Utilize them as
A kind of enemy of my enemy is
So you like
Arcata man it's
Chris they wouldn't work
I know that problem with Coraline I could never align with Alex for any common cause that we have
Yeah but you moved there is also that part
It says
We don't make
With our friends we make
Right
Is one situation
Where
God because
Because the
Conservative anger
Is towards
Like the tea party
Out of the bailout
And Barack Obama being black
Well yeah
Apps
The bailout
Mad about
Great
Now
Mad about a black
Is there a
No
There's not
I just have this hope you know why there's not you know why there's not it's the exact same thing
Agreement about the bailout
But agreement that we might have
Hair actually be in agreement
Because the reason that you have it is different than the reason
The reasoning
What got you to the point that you're at
Doesn't exist in the same cosmology is
What house they got to wear their
And because of that even if
On the surface agree about an issue right
You absolutely don't
It is
I'm against the war in Iraq
You're against the war in Iraq
Taking it back a few years
Yeah our reasons for it might be different
And if my reason is
I'm against this war it's based on false pretenses
With no reason
Is
I'm against the war in Iraq
Because
A lizard person who's under the swag
Blah blah blah
Don't want people to die and that's good
Really
Work together
I think your your analogy of
As propping up out
It's probably
The
The question their wood
Could we
Like
We don't agree on
But
Say we actually can agree
To break up the
Sure
Now I would sooner side with Bernie over on that van Alex Jones okay
I'm on the Bernie win
I don't know if you guys have ever listen to me talk
Politics
Borders on the the IRA more than anybody else your
Your past furnace furnace trying to catch up
Music
Where I would love to be able to use that
Anger towards the back
Even though the
Deep-seated heart of it
Is Aunt
Anti-semitism
Could I use that anger
And co-opted
To act
Break up
My answer is no
You end up destroying yourself in the process
Yeah you're
All of your principles go away
You're probably not wrong
Bums me out but
A God there is that part of me that
Victor thinks strategically that
I say sleep on it and you'll realize in the morning
Do it's impossible
I know but this one Lionel gives us a very nice visual and that is Alex
In the future
But he doesn't unfortunately in the contacts
Really just
Kissing Alakazam
Real hard
But
Away we go I'm going to then as everybody is being distracted by the three card Monte of
Turn
Why we're looking this way
I'm going to little by little cake
Everything from this country
Before you know it is going to be
Maybe with a rumbling
Run the World
They thrive on disorder and disaster
Window screen
When we turn to the government in Azalea dielectrics
For more power more Authority
Then one day is over
Maybe
Your word your finals valedictory hours
I told you so
You thought I was just somebody who is conspiracy theorist
It's going to be too late you thought I was doing this trip or some kind of
You didn't realize that what I was saying and what the world was say
Was there the whole time and you didn't listen to me
I told you I tried to make it as simple as possible and I brought in guest
Explain in different way
So hard
God damn it I was so close
So close
I've been
Look I hate that mentality of like
1 year dad everyone will realize
You have the s*** has gone down and we should have listened to you
Premature profit status kind of really f****** dangerous
You're depending on
Like an outcome and
Status quo
Probably never will exist
In order to justify whatever you're saying in
Impreza
Classic logical fallacy
Just
Reinforcing Alex's need to spell iodine
And actually immediately after that clip Alex is like
Kiss your ass
Right
Of course
We took a time-traveling trip
Here
The 2015
Right
The things that were mostly talked about we're globalist
Destroyer
Lionel accidentally spills
My truck game plan
Is a little process
Was going to be
His belief
Three major things that were
Were American flag being bandwidth
No beers later has napping
And even there even there outside
Mark Dice
It's not going to happen
Greece's economy is doing better
It's that they're not all the way back
Lipstick
They're good sign
The end Tommy has been improving
Yes
I mean it's not
Do you understand it like this whole argument that they're making of like
It's part of a pre-planned down slide
Blah blah blah
They talked about in this
Is bunk everything is bogus
Kernels of Truth are there in terms of like
Yeah these
Dunno
Banks are shity but all of the other stuff is
Absolutely not true
Planned collapse of Greece
Has not happened it's on the upswing
It's coming back
It'll take awhile to telling back
The IMF
Adequate info
Maybe we'll come back
Possibly
Beyond that there was that the family who had their kid taken away playing basketball
Also maybe they were being neglectful but maybe that also wasn't necessarily
Nosey neighbor
It wasn't it wasn't a globalist
Actuation where somebody you saw a dog
Hot car
Broke it out
Yeah because that was
For the dog.
Yeah there was a crack in the window
Maybe that's not a
Big enough
Yeah yeah
I was a great man
It was like a hundred bucks
So if your car has black widows into it
Bruce Willis
Kind of like it's unfortunate you didn't like it throughout the episode about gay marriage which is the main event
Legalized by the
Supreme Court Nationwide
Takeaway from this
Time travel up
Is
Before he
Himself to the
Praying
Didn't have to do as
Mental gymnast
You didn't have to
Makeup as much
It's true
Like before that
Without supporting anybody
Cuz he's not coming out
Supporting a
A person saying dumbass
He's just anti-globalization
He's just in a nebulous place where you can
Pick and choose whatever
Fairfax he wants
Spiral out
Yeah a group that doesn't really exist so whatever you wanted no one can ever prove them wrong
But now is with his
He doesn't have a choice but to
You make things up haha
Because Trump
Frankly
Disagrees with him on
Well I would say this here's how I would describe it
Does Mike bare truth route
To our future
Time travel
Due date for you
But I will say is I think
Before
You hitched his wagon
To Trump
When he is like he is now
There are no more good day
He is all bad days now
Just
We're spoiled by current Alex
Is this is mostly low register Alex this isn't like
I'm still in stillwagon do
It's crazy but it's like Al Pacino you want him screaming
All right version
And that's kind of what a lot of this
This is
Heat output
Phuc yea
I really appreciate it
Thank you very much I'm going to do something crazy
I've never done this before
I am going to
To plug a show
Now
The facts
This fact that I've never done this before
Maybe why I
Hopefully this will be so uncomfortable you'll never do it again
Brutal
The globalists are going to come find you at the show you know that you out
Not the only reason I'm plugging it it
At the theater, too
This Saturday
Saturday
Terrible
Brutal
Yeah wow wow wow
Not important
Holyshit
What day is today
The second okay
Unplugging it is because Timmy
Whittle
Runs and does everything for this theater
Successful as possible I will be there one of my old podcast
Also if you want
If you want to find out
What I'm not what I'm like when I'm not screaming into a microphone and it's dead
Screaming into a different like
Microphone
If you want to if you want to come out and be boil I can't actually cuz I'm I will be
Kuykendahl
Well then yeah if you can come out we'll do that
Wolfie
Where can I edit this entire plug in a half hour
Knowledge underscore fight
Twitter
Confined us everywhere
Nope I can email us if you like knowledge fight at gmail.com and if you
Become a policy wonk
You can donate if you'd like to do a time travel episode
We can do that
We might have some shirts coming in the future get big shout-out to our friend Chris
Awesome designs
Guys that's my plug
And then I stare off out the window like a
Mark Dice
Let me ask you a question
What's up
The people who donate
Our policy
Does that make us
We are
Controlling
Alexandra Thurston color