Air Jordan pipes sweat it
I have great respect for knowledge babe I'm sick of them posing as if through the good guy
MoneyGram
Stripe.com
Little bit about Alex Jones
What's up Jordan
Really
This is weird
I want you
A big part of me
It's a very specific question
But I don't think you're going to have
I'm going to go with
An infinite number of questions
But
Look directly into my eyes
No I have no idea what do you want to talk about
And told them to their
Probably
Yeah probably
Texting story
This is a foregone conclusion
I need to just tell you about this Jordan
Yeah probably
Friend in the morning before we record
Waiting for you to show up Studio
And
A few things
I think I've discovered genre of music that might be
The right in my wheelhouse
At this Jordan
Probably
Reimagining the Phil Collins
The cannon
It's fantastic
Disturbed Land of Confusion know everybody is great
Take me home
Really feel like I talk
It might just be a rediscovery
Who's real
Disturbed
Fusion
And then Bone Thugs-N-Harmony did take me home
He's in the video and walking around with crazy lazy and wish
Rabbit hole
Good as I remember
Pretty good stuff
Man I started me going down the road of life
C-Murder still in
Prison
The new trial
Anyway
Surly
Alright
Another look out
Another look at it
Hurley
No longer Simard
They claim that they did not see a murder
The questionable musical taste
And I know a lot about that was just
And I regretfully have to participate
Addresses record this early in the morning we are we are
But snoke
Better Business
I can't do Mondays
Between episodes
To do all the required
Aldi's Normal Day episode
Narratives and silver pretty easy
Especially
The bombing.
That is stuff that we're like
Might take me an hour and a half
He'll lie about something that requires a
So
For Monday I consider the coast to coast episode
Episode of the week
Is that does
Ivar understanding
Wednesday
Stuff going on
Both of his lawyers
I'm not sure I've seen an episode
Pat's calls in
Norm
And barns
He's even more eager for The Fray
Not busy
Although
I do
It's
We're going to have
On way
Underscoring the show
Jackie
What's Montello
Brent podcast
Brent
Appreciate it
You took up the people who signed up on an elevated level
So first of all Josiah
Reverend Peter anomaly
You are now attacking
Heroin
Freakishly large
Thank you so much
To the both of you
Sounds like a Phillips
Character
I'll be right there listening
Going to go website
Perhaps one of my contacts
Drops going to be.
No this is this is a rare type
This could not be better
There's a microwave
Is the ideal form
How to say
I'm just stating the facts I own a chainsaw
I'm just stating the facts
To fight
I know
Who owns one
I'm here this is
The old ball rolling
Predictable
Oops I just
Give me back on Facebook
We obviously have the latest developments taking place
A lot of different fronts
And we have the latest rerun of
Whistleblower dogs
The ambassador to
Heard somebody say
Was quid pro quo just like the other fake whistleblowers whose names we can't know
Why'd you said that as well
Justified
Bill Taylor
Had to admit
We got a call for the EU ambassador
Beterbiev
You may notice that
Ukraine business specifically
What are you open to
The show like that
We are the new doesn't start off the show talking about Mick Mulvaney press conference
Trump asked for a quid pro quo we do that all the time
It's the reason is that
Really hard to go
Mulvaney's
Conehead
Maligning Bill Taylor
Diplomat
For the u.s.
House committee members privately
Hasn't been released
Page opening statement is very public
You give your first indication that Alex
Dismissively calling this testimonial bobsheaux
Alex is very scared of what this guy
The first application is on
It's like me saying hey.
Our national security
Remain strong
However in August and September of this year
Increasingly concerned that our relationship with Ukraine with being fundamentally undermine by an irregular informal channels
Policy-making
And by the withholding of vital security issue
For domestic political
Bill Taylor was the u.s. ambassador to Ukraine
Situation in the country
He's absolutely no slouch
Testifying on official foreign policy
State Department
It's a real serious charge
And it becomes even more serious when you realize the charge Taylor is making is it this second unofficial channel was contradict
Real official Channel
Of US foreign policy
Namely strong support
For Ukraine
Taylor's opening statement involves very clear
Like the following
June 27th
Ambassador sondland told me a phone conversation
The president is a queer to President Trump
President zelensky wasn't standing in the investigation
I don't understand
That doesn't sound like
Taylor provided conversations with ambassadors
Resilience
Need to say you will help him
Asians and address personnel
If there are any
You can play
Sure WhatsApp
On July 20th the representatives olenski
Told Taylor the u.s. re-election
Calls into question the idea whether people on the Ukrainian side were aware
Of the machination
Put that
Question
Taylor Skype conversations with ambassadors
Explicitly tells them
Zelensky
Publicly saying
They were going to do
Investigation
President zelensky
In a public box
Shirts
You can't trust
Sure
The inability of any Us official to respond Ukrainian Ukrainian
Question
Security systems
Problems m
LED idea that they ask what's going on
You don't sound exactly like how Trump
The operate like a mobster you know what you're supposed to do and you're not going to get me to
Say it so just do it or they'll be problem
Criminal
Enterprises
Iverson
Call I would like to buy some drugs
Illegally
I drive over with cops behind
And then I buy my weed
That's how it works
By the books
It is true that Taylor's opening statement does include a passage about a conversation that he had with Tim Morrison
Security Council
Morrison spoken with Trump
He was he was not asking for a quid pro quo
Go to a microphone and say
Election interference
And the president's events
Should himself
Right
I guess the Trump did technically pro quo
Describes
II
Now you have
Otherwise it doesn't count
Magic
It's very hard to read this opening statement and get the impression that there was not a quid pro quo going on
You could read it and take
The parts that say there was no
Those are
From
I am the evidence
Dmkc
Contradict
There was no
So I am offering
Actually
I am withholding Aid
In order for you to do something that I would like you to do
Yeah and then when you do that I will give you that a
I don't understand
Arizona
A big deal
YouTube ideas
It's hard to know precisely what
But if this
It was very like
F****** damning stuff
Just from this one person
In this opening statement
You have multiple named people like vulcar Sunland
Among other people
Who had Direct conversations with Trump
Just from this there's a clear roadmap
Do an investigation
The people you need to ask questions about to get on the road
Furiously
Seriously thinking about turning on Trump
Right now
Now is the
But I'm not going to do it ever has
For a while now
And if you're about to enter an area where
There's nothing you
Good luck
But look man that's just assuming that there's openings
Was real
There's a possibility
Expect
Is that going to
Discussed here
Rizal
Open Patel Schiff wrote this latest statement this guy put out of it it's so obvious of the fake letter
Chef redhead let's do that
Chef
Reading the fake
Letter
It was supposedly the fake transcript
The last month Adam Schiff read what you might call a parody version of the restaurant
Where
In the mobster quality
Some boneheaded move but others might think it's a worthwhile strategy
Creatively make
I've noted the matter other than that when I first heard about shift doing that I knew immediately that Alex
Layout quotes
The essence of what the present
Do you have to be an idiot or Shameless propaganda
Set off as a real doctor
How about both
Did the big pizza
Kaiser like Trump
Defenses are real
Easterby
We get through that little segments
Real serious
Teasing
In major Wars
Try to stabilize their economy
Trying
Reboot
American Spirit
But under Trump's nose
There's some things going on
I think you should know about
I think we should talk about
To do that
On the other side
What's going on with Bono
F****** it's not going to be I support the homeless and we should
Socializing
It's not going to be Let's help people get access to
Like to discuss what the best options are for public housing
For mental health assistance
Or
None of that we don't know what he
Take on it is going to be at what the story is
So Alex
Leave that alone in ghosts
Break a promise
To get back to it later
This isn't going to be good
Whatever it is whatever your Alex bring up a vulnerable population
You know it's somehow going to be
You know it somehow
Adding to the possibility of them being further victimized
Exploited
Pretty confident in saying
If that is the case
He brings up something to do
Distract
The larger
Issue
And then
Pepper's it with
Cruelty
So people get that
They don't
Sure
Dehumanization
Just started
That kind of mentality
It kind of lead
Towards
Criminalizing
Possibly
Rounding up
People are not homeless
Because they failed
They're homeless speaker
Because the rest of us
Because Alex Costa
He comes back
Is it a real weird
Broadcasting worldwide
I want to let you know
I am aware of information going on inside the Trump campaign
That is very very dangerous and very very scary
To the president to this country into all of you watching
And listening out there
You may have noticed that the Brad parscale
Earlier this week had a huge lavish cover story in the Sunday New York time
About what a wonderful person he is and what he is
Well
There's better things going on with Brad
Parscale that I'm going to reveal
Later the broadcast today
He doesn
Relationship
Administration
I'm starting to notice
There's a trend where you
Seems to keep
Finding out about how certain members evolve
Working against the resurge
Legends of America
A lot of this Falls squarely into the genre of what you might tend to see in a Thor attarian system
Where the media bootleggers
Dwell on Palace
Where the storm of Suspicion
Is always raging
Threatening
Appeared to be loyal enough to the leader
Without some starting to notice a slightly different character
Particular type of Paladin
Namely that all the people he seems to think our threats within the administration
Or specifically people who apparently don't like Alex enough
We saw this generals McMaster and Mattis globalist infiltrator
Which was how Alex communicated direct messages to Trump
Which is weird on its own
Similar problems with
The former Chief of Staff
And now the crosshairs are fixed on Brad parscale
It should be mentioned that Alex has recently complained about
Who is Alex Jones
Hard to hear Alex now uncovering
Some kind of scary and dangerous information about Park
You're not thinking maybe his bruised ego is somehow involved
Really wants to get back on Facebook
Publix
Demonization campaign
Essential Personnel in Trump's Administration
In order to get there which is
Funny on one level but really just sat
Really wants to get back on Facebook
The context of the testimony from Zuckerberg yesterday
Yeah
Give us
Clearly a happy
It is strange
It is
Yeah but you know what whatever
Alex doesn't think he's
Brad parscale butt
Quite frankly
The man he is
Not the sharpest knife in the drawer
And as a serious weak link
So is dumb
I guess
Doesn't get to talkin about what is dangerous and
Scary information about Brad parscale
This episode
Huge gap
Coming up on Friday
And later in the show he does so to connect these two things
That this Gap has some information
About
And the Trump campaign
And I was really Alex overselling Friday show
He's going to get killed over this interview
Again I probably got butterflies
10 times the 25 years I've been on air
@donaldtrump
Butterfly
I got sick
I get butterflies when I think about
I guess we're going to have Friday
It's a big gas filter Rogan had
Edward Snowden on
Yesterday but they released a few hours ago that's Graves
Wards.com
This is a really important big interview
And it's it's an emergency message to the president
Listen to
Interview where I'm looking under my car literally now for bombs when I
Interview
Coming up Friday in the second hours work schedule
You're going to want to tune into this
And if something happens to me interview still got to go out
Hotel by the way I don't hide stuff
I tell you how big something else
Straight up deliver
Before that
The only make us interview large
Anybody would do that
Nametests
Snowden Edward Edward
If I know what is life
He does later like I said give a few close by to it is to do with the Trump campaign to Brad parscale
In a normal world
It could still literally
Idea
It could be
Sure
If you weren't in custody I would say that it could be
Rogan Vega Alex that have snowed in on
Assange
Outside of being Augustine is not above going
He may have been
A few years ago
I was trying to think of a big name Alex
Could get who's in
Need to pretend
And I just couldn't think of anyone really
Like Rodger Stone coming on is only a danger to Rogers
I thought it could be Steve Bannon for a second
But I could never pull that off everything so much time in the past, Steven
Trader
Possibly a globalist
Just started a podcast called war room
Clear infringement of copyright
Let er Rip
Yeah that could be a breeze coming out
I thought possible place where he could have
After their unceremonious falling out I thought they probably never speak again
Turn on it
Steve's YouTube channel has been coming along
Gathering
Justin trying to poach
And I could see him trying to put water out of brass
Now you know he was wrong about the Las Vegas but he's one of the greatest
Are beneficial
Patriots
I will give up literally anything to get 1000 more listeners
I could I could see him
Trying
Rehab
Yeah for sure possible
People who ICS
Fraternity male
Listen to As Much Alex as I have
He teased that he had the biggest gas ever coming on later the week and it turned out to be the Obamas
So I do not know where Alex's
That one
That one was brutal
Flushing
So Jordan here's a random list of people that I think it might be and I'm mostly putting this list out there in case it's one of them
Turkish prime minister
Joey salads Congressional camp
John McAfee I think that one might be like a real FrontRunner
Just for Longshot points
Bubba Sparxxx
I'm just putting a dollar on that
Interview
And it's hard not to get a little excited about
Could be
Everything I own this is going to be
The Obama Phone Lady again at two possibilities
Yeah
So
Right back
The news about people experience
Alex
That's good operation
They've already or wired up
Let me tell you something
I did some digging this morning
Austin for it
Is doing it through a microchip
The homeless
Austin I'm already done it in Mexico
Guatemala and now
It's here
Took my first thought about this is it
Strange of every nefarious
Same area Alex lives in
Eddie's
Just keep coming up over and over again
Keep happening in Austin
Likely
Almost
Proximity
Novels are set
Statistically doesn't make sense
Plus
If you are the globalist
Crusade
The thing that keeps uncovering your plots
Cities home City of Austin
Looks like you might move your operation somewhere else
Go to Cincinnati
Austin give a s*** about Cincinnati
Globalist
Talking about
Twist just making
Stuff up
There is an organization that
Working with people experiencing homelessness
Implantable form of
Application
The argument goes like this
In order to access many of the benefits
You survived
In order
Need identification
However these same people are precisely
Is the store these documents
Yeah what are they going to
Carry around
If you live on the
Out of a backpack away from losing your Social Security card
Possibility that just living in the
Elements Mike Destroyer
Jason card without any incident
This leads to people in that situation
Having
Constant state of
Applying for the
Which becomes an awful cycle
You end up in
And you can only imagine what kind of like that would cause a
Horrible psychological experience
Trapped
Been unable to get to the next step
Constantly
Reset
These sorts of barriers are a frustrating part of life
For people in these circumstances
And a golden problems like this one in Austin
Is to eliminate some of those barriers
Getting back to heaven
Secure life
Right
I don't know how I feel about this program as a whole
Obviously I scored the goal behind to be done to help
Homelessness
And that is developed with input
Is something that is worth being a
Explored
There's some concern about data security
Programming promise
Technology
In order to
To service
Yeah so
Curly under the control
The individual
Call only to have access to that medical
Information
There is some
Compartmentalization
The data
Blockchain
It's very interesting
The way they're trying to set this up
And like I said show some early promise
On that front
If those are took
Considerations are adequately
It's shown to help
The community at the
Whatever your position is on the issue 1
Presenting this like it's breaking news
And that's because Mike Adams just ran a story about this on natural news
Sound the alarm
But don't get it twisted this is not news
I've been stories about the beginning of this program dating back to
April 28th
26-28
Harvard's datasmart law Grand Apizza
The Austin American
Statesman covered a new grant for the program back on August 2nd 2019
Local news in Austin
KXAN
Covered the program on July 31st
This isn't something it's like
It's just been developed in secret
It's not hidden
Plain Sight
It's a program that aims to alleviate the
Under-recognized
Apple's of
Homelessness
Many outlets have covered
Disgust for a year-and-a-half now
Alex's team is just super bad at news
Let no idea to Pismo
Microchipping program was
City that they live in in
Opera
Who's just embarrassing stuff
The severity of like
Crack the Case on
Is is a mass
Discovering we didn't know about this for a year-and-a-half
Key issue for them
Like it should be squarely in their wheelhouse
This should be something we've been talkin about
I mean it's literally
Way that he describes the mark of the beast
So if you are adult
To news that is not
Local news
Susan Austin you should definitely have been aware of it it suggests the really bad news.
Considering
All sorts of other places have B very openly
Is Joyce's
Disallows
Possibly have a better chance of breaking out of the cycle of a fly
In order to
Get the ball rolling
It's one thing to keep them trapped in the system
Which Alex's
Whether or not
Function of
Supporting
Based on everything I know
Pretty much active
Supporting
Well
His conception of people who have chips in them
AI
We can take over them or something like
Not even people anymore
Minions of the globalist why even bother
Crushing leaves
People who are
In a very vulnerable state
Enlight
Because of their circumstance
I did the ideas if you would want to approach that
Situation
Social problem
And look at it to make it worse for them
Let's make more suspicious
As opposed to
How can we work together to
Rise
We could
Homelessness
Or
We could end the homeless
Those are the two out that is a good way to put it
At least at least it seems like
Prefers that
Approach
Profoundly spot.
Play bulshit
I don't care to hear him over and over again
Fluoride
That's also kind of boring
But I wanted to play
Because I think
This is an interesting rare
Good
Pivot
He's in the middle of talking about fluoride
Bulshit
The actual content
Wonky
Kind of smooth
Fluoride
Good halogen the iodine
Can I get up here and Sensational at all out of the government document the periodic table
Add
Try to launch a movement against it
Tell the people understanding before I doubt that's a good idea
We sell the best cleaners
Relationship
Get the best packs to the best x-33 braids for kids
That's a little smoother is because it is just
Normal content in the same spot
There's there is an A to B
Before you know it
He should be doing
It's almost a little scary
Because on some level that is like
You hide this better bothering to try and hide
Manufacturing stories
About specific product but I kind of do
Demonstrated that a little bit in the past
Line by line I going down your Victory job
Ugly
Energy
It could
If you were smart
Much better plan shows
So the break is at 16 of the hour
So bye
Bennett 40
Of the hour I've got to be in the middle of a rant about fluoride
I need to be able to
Make it appear him
Right
Commercial
It goes to commercial
Alex
Has a weird commercial for his commercial
Cover the commercials
These days too much cuz they're mostly like this Alex
This one I think was a little bit worth
Checking in on
Again
I'm not talking down to the Infowars audience but I've been banging my head against the wall for a long time
What's the old Glastron boat have a lake to put
What is a gentleman bad halogen is fluoride that's why in every Western Nation they put in the water
Precious light on a Dodge
Because it's the good outweighs everything else
String of commercials
That is weird
I'm not talking down to you I own you need water for a boat
Never heard
Professional ads
People going like
Let's play
In
An overly comp
Placated
Doesn't actually make any sense
It's not if not I want to talk about
Comparing the human need for oxygen to boats need for water
Hind
Like we need to be in a Knox
Enriched environment to survive
Needs to be in water to do what
Supposed to do with a boat
Take a submarine
Apparel
Metaphor working for iodine in the body
We do need iodine like you know
Atmosphere
We just need to take a little bit of it
Function properly
I would say his metaphors has been
They take the fuel of the boat needs to run
Food is food
Mineral that helps the body work
Who be like
Antifreeze
Are babies a piston or something
That's all
There's more important
Alright
My first comment is today that the global put fluoride in the water in the West
Is maybe making his Christian identity ideas a little bit to over
That is not a dog whistle that's a f****** siren
Keep in mind that this is how Alex is trying to bark
Products
I don't feel like it
Used to be the early that blunt
I'm trying to sell to a specific audience
Edward Edward
Maybe
Alright
So
My first glaring problem with the
I'm about fluoride to their water
Austria Belgium Croatia Estonia France Germany Greece Italy
Fluoridation
Are plenty of Christians in those countries
Considered
Well parts
Do the problem 4 oz narrative
The teachers Christians to lay down and die
Put fluoride in all the holy water.
Answers for China and fluoridation Alex's correct
Contacts
China and India both don't have fluoride water partially because they exist on top of it
Naturally occurring fluoride
This belt contains 85 million
Tons of fluoride
Has the expected effect of making their water supplies naturally high in fluoride
There be no point in naturally occurring levels are higher than any place in the United States
Even after we've added to the water
This is a public health problem that's cause increased rates of dental fluorosis and even fluoride toxicity
The world it's very heavily discussed issue and the real issues in the world related
Would understand this
All Alex knows of the China doesn't add fluoride to their water
That's all you needs to know about a big butt
I could find I can't find any information about China adding to their water
Elations in 1995
Iodine
To address the high prevalence of iodine deficiency
Population
Well us hasn't made a law about it we've been to table salt since 1924
Anchoring test
About 70% of all salt iodized
Probably be higher but we don't have as big of an iodine deficiency problem
Most likely due to varying
Natural water supply
Who cares
So what you're saying is the globe
Time and put all the fluoride in the Earth
In order to get rid of the Chinese
I guess Alex good make that argument
The time-traveling Patriot web
Globalism
Fluoride
No Bridge Too Far browse to go
Why not just the world issues
This is an attempt to attack
Little Alex
Kind of mad that
Hasn't in
Globalist
Perfected
He should be there by
I think it's implied
In stupidity carries over
Starting to sound a little bit like an open appeal to White Christian victimhood narrative
Way more than normal
Yeah
Is new line of Infowars branded
This indicates to me a bit of a lack of interest in any other demographic
Which kind of makes sense
Like when you talk to your marketing that selectively it's not a good sign for your business
Because you're alienating people who are outside of that possible
Market
When you're doing that while you're also running an Everything Must Go sale it kind of feels like you're circling
Would you really go in these with it trying to
Theoretically make it longer
Surprise me if the only people buying it
So why even bother
Like is it really nice or is it just his
Sort of touch.
In the same way that like
Sort of content
Hidden
Is we should have been doing all along
He's built like
I have a broader appeal
Do you imagine your casting this why
At least these are the indications that I started
Christians being under attack
In the commercial
The number of commercials
But I don't remember hearing
Little bit
Surprise
Previously
Like back when he was on
To pretend
You know in order to in order to
And that he is only speaking
Even though he knows he's only
He still has
In order for
Wear all-white Nashua
Let's put on rogge Lane
Go for it
So I need a news headline
Reinforced
Doughboy
Alex is muselk
Excuses for their beloved all they want but
And doing so
All they do is reveal what they really support
Alex can get on his show and here and Report the news these two proud boys are being sent to jail after being found guilty of
Gang salt
Brawl in New York
You can say all know that all they did was defend themselves from an antifa attack
True
If you was in any way
In reality
You know that
Alex is operating off of 1 videos widely-circulated better
Pure to show one of the victims of the
If that's the argument goes the Cowboys are just defending themselves antifa started it
Subsequent videos of come to the surface that shows very different story
Is a water bottle thrown but the person who throws it is doing so in response to the proud boys literally charging
Hiscox
These are children
One of the men who is sentenced
39 years old
And he joined group
The only way to get the name cereal
I'm kind of sick of the bulshit so I'm just going to put this simply
The organization that is based
Environment
Ritual is based on
Gavin created the game with tiered structure of membership where the only way to get to the fourth level of initiation
Is to get into a violent confrontation
Temptation with ants
From the second you join with the proud boys
Your way up the ranks
Everything is centered around either
Implied or real political and physical violence
If I had a leader who had said specifically they created
The fights guess people are politically disagreeing
Inmates
I made submitting to an active group violence necessary to join
And create a hierarchy
The Climb
I promised you I would not find that acceptable
Even if I come to
Completely agreed with what they stood for and we're working
For in the case of Gavin in the proud boys stand for repulsive
And their entire structure is indistinguishable from a gang
Mostly centered around misplaced feelings
Nonetheless
Anyone carrying water for the proud Boys in 2019 knows exactly what they're doing
Extremely right-wing white men have free reign to assault people they politically disagree
That is what Alex wants
And that is why he's presenting
Their incarceration is
Pureed
Make America great again
About what
We used to always have
Roving gangs
Hurting and murdering
Defending
Proud boys
Is only like
Protecting
That's the only thing
Being,
Like I could see that as
That and not actually wanting Road and kings.
Alex
If
For him
He needs to get off air
Because he is so stupid
So unable to
Present information
He's doing is
Accidentally misleading literally everybody listen
Well you know I know
I know he's not
I know he knows we
Cuz that clip
The guy throwing the Water by
Obviously
The right-wing
Edited
What they did was
They started it
With
Peter Griffin
Running shirt
Yeah
Very self-conscious
Phil Collins songs
Me for a blanket
Jordan 14
It's fine
We all right
Easy Lover is a great song
Easy love
What are you at
Kidville,
For sure
Talk about just got another
A big
Story
Fetty WAP
Literally talk about this too much but it's definitely like a touchstone
Also trying to pass laws the word b****
Manchaca Wes is going to be f*****
No one is trying to ban the word b****
Actually that's not true there's one person who is
A random person
Massachusetts
In the Statehouse in Massachusetts representative Dan Hunt
Introduce spell Outlaws
But it was because he was trying to censor people or overturn free speech
Most of the right-wing media would have you believe
It's because he was following Massachusetts law
Massachusetts has what's known as the
Built-in
The state constitution
Predates the founding of the United States
Which allows citizen
Send bills to the representative
It's the responsibility of State reps to give their
Constituents
Government and that's exactly what happened to you
An unnamed Massachusetts residents that Dan Hunter build introduced that would outlaw the use of the word b****
Did what he was supposed to do
According to the guardian at least 6,000 bills get introduced through the right of freedom
Massachusetts
This is a kind of a perfect example of why Alex Jones f******
Sucks
It's so interesting how Massachusetts has this right of free petition
Yeah never heard of that one of his listeners I'll probably get a lot out of learning
Country state government
There's a lot of opportunity for some much-needed Civics education
The perfect way in for that
Alex could talk about how this Quirk of Massachusetts boys allowed real direct action to take place
Like how in 2013 and 8 year old kid with pushing for a bill
To put restrictions on shark Finning
Or else could go the opposite direction and talk about I went 2011 someone tried to request their representative do something about how
Football games were pre-empting Jeopardy
It's the yin and the Yang of people actually having a boy's I think about it the more I realize I know why
I don't know about this
How many how many how many of those 6,000
Petitions are
Buck Dave
Discount Pascal
If everybody knew about this
Circumstance
Maybe not
Known
I want you to send a bill to your representative
Make knowledge fight the state
Podcast I lived in Boston for a number in Cambridge
We don't need to be the official state podcast but I would like a parade
Like this is this is the sort of thing
Maybe we're abusing the system a little bit here but there's a lot
The conversation
What is behind this clickbait story
Civics Works in one of the great States
He just ignores
You can see the headline about someone trying to outlaw the word b****
And he just takes it that's good enough and building it outrageous
Cycle
Free speech in the global storm control how you talk
It's pathetic in Trivial
It's pointless to even critique
Because
What he's doing is uninspired
Except
Movie hopelessly lost among his audience
What makes it so insanely dumb as to imagine that what he saying
Is true
Imagine if he's right
Imagine that someone in the Massachusetts state house was trying to ban the word b****
Who gives a s***
Bill would never pass
Massachusetts ACLU
Would get struck down so fast
This is right wing Outreach clickbait pure and simple
And what you really get down to it that's most of what Alex has left
Right
You know
He was bigger than this
The earliest you pretended to
To be bigger than this
Tireminder
It's just
Too often
Reality is
Starkly against
F******
Headstrong against
The concept of reality
Itself that what else do they have the
They have to make it up I think it I think it's one of those things we had like a really good
Good but you have a sustainable balance
Between the Yukon
The rest of the world
It was a kind of
You know adversario like alright close to the Sun
They took the game
To too high of a level where
Is it like everyone is now like
Okay you're a problem
Good plan under the radar for quite a while
$10 a day
Easy
60 of 100
In one day you'll get caught
You wait
Spread out over 10 days
Ecco hundred dollars
Noticed
Every workplace
Like they could have kept
Stealing $10 a day
But they wanted that hundred
This is the consequence
One last job
You know you're you're running the the you're robbing banks
You know you're not going for the you're just going for the cash
You're doing great
You do the one big job in the
Atoka
So you know this is the only free
Free Speech issue that Alex has to talk about words
He's got another headline
Short clip
Who was shot by the person that complained
Dangerous for Americans once
Are walking along
Weather
Verboten word
Navigation
All right now.
Mountain said the okay symbol that law enforcement uses the
Divers used
Mama dishwasher
Okay and of course the NBA there's a proper
Clothing line
Your symbol
380 eldercide
You're going to lose your house going to go to jail
There are boxes
Arrested for speech
Couple of white students were repeatedly yelling the n-word on the campus of Uconn
Student dorms
Illegal to say the n word
Be taken gear
Who's on campus property
Such a public manner that someone on the in one of the buildings
This does create an environment if you're black student in one of those
Like it not making you feel unsafe
Make you feel unwelcome
It doesn't even
If you are they were out there just screaming
The same
You be like that we got to get you the f***
Well yes.
But it could be some other
You're not a priority
It's V
Factor of is less the word itself in the behavior
The word exercising the word is bad
Behavior is the problem
Just problem
The big problem to
If you're the school administrators you have to do some
If you don't do anything you're sending the message
Unwelcome
Because of their race is okay
Very dangerous normalizing
The fact to just let students run around campus Edward from a school admin
Perspective
The real option to either kick them out of school or in for some kind of punishment
These records were charged with ridicule based on race
Which is a crime
Connecticut
According to the general statutes
The punishment of up to $50 or 30 days
These kids will definitely not get any jail time for this so if I had to bet I would say that they're going to
This is really actually what I think
And maybe I'm wrong on this and willing to be told that I'm wrong
But I kind of feel like this is a good processor
For dealing with a point Behavioral
Particularly in a college
There needs to be a Punisher
But it shouldn't be overly harsh
And the door needs to be open for them to learn about why they did this thing it's awful
What do you have a punished
Not like this
It's a negative
That's good
And it also opens up the possibility of
People who are different
Perspective miles for conversation
To become
It is
Healthy
Process
They can go on
And that process is
Completely disrupted by people like Alex
And all this
Outrage driven right
Because of their framing of the case people like Alex have created the illusion
Two kids are involved in a very important
Free speech
Case
If they're so inclined
Just because of the exposure
In essence what the right-wing media does is create countervailing forces
Against the process
Run its course without people like Alex
Call
It's not to save these kids are going to do this
No
Start a GoFundMe
$50,000
Easy like that's f****** capitalize on this
It gives cases like this
Is that possibility of another path to go down as opposed to learning
And I think it's some people might say like a you should kick them out of school
An egregious examples
In this case
I think that you have the opportunity for
Conciliation
Have the
This is
I know that they were screaming the n-word on
An examination of it
Circumstance
It seemed like they were yelling other words as well
Targeting black people
And we're just trying to
Play a game where they yell defense
Okay
Sure you guys just keep
Did the issue
Okay
Given those circumstances
The effect on people who are in those dorms
Behavior is not change
Yeah but the possibilities
They
Could learn from
And try and terrorize better erase
So you need to make it so
Isn't Sosa
Severe that it inhibits the possibility
Learn
I don't know I'd be interested in other people's perspective on it but from where I am looking at it like trying to imagine
How you would handle this from
Superintendent
Perspective
That seems like the most
Likely to get the desired outcome
What you want
By my lonely
Like
What you're looking
Forest
Something that's
You want something that
Equally
Treating
The problem
And
And that kind of stuff
And that's another thing that the right wing
Media is
Right
Treat the problem and also honor the people who are being Behavior
You need to balance those two things
Yeah that sounds good
Pregnant
Taking those two
Considerations are looking for the best way forward
In
Possible white like actually
This behavior from the right wing
Media is not
Particularly
The right-wing media is
Participating in
Protecting what is a
When they f****** love
Galaxy S8
Tyranny
This is it all runs
Track
About this because of
They just wants white people to be allowed to yell racial slurs and create hostile faces for non-white people
Let's be doesn't think that that's a problem
Norm pattis
Amazon
Connecticut
Norm
Be there lawyer
In talking about why he wants to be there
Norm Norm music
Oh no
Because I think this paste is right for a constitutional challenge
Which country is always had
And the n-word is one of those words with B contact brick
If I walk up to a black person say yo n**** what up
And so what makes this word offensive is the contact
Offended the ability to
Norm
Norms
No more
Really just trying to shoot an arrow at a bar and he doesn't miss miss to the side
Never going to
They just never going to get it
Supposed to
I hate him
It's
It's so stupid it's very weird
It's very
There's no need for Norm to say that earlier
There's no reason
Hey hey
Well I'm not hitting too hard
Come out
I'm
Elementary
Simple most language
Does work
Circumstantial
If that's not any kind of like
Interaction
Penis head
Text of what
Absolutely
Are you serious you don't understand that Norm
It is funny how he's like
See if a context
And now I'm going to use it
In the precise
Use this word
Oh yeah yeah
I may be a verb
I don't know if I've heard the n-word on
The show
In the past
Yeah
Could get him in FCC trouble
Like I really I do
Messages
I don't know
I don't know what the rules are
It seems like that
The rules
Say that and preferably
Stop speaking in Pratt
It's wild
Might be a false
This whole thing
Probably
No no you shut the f*** you're being willfully obtuse
Accused of anything bad
Norm just false flag event do we know these guys didn't Jesse Smollett something
Pentwater folks to do this
Muji
What
Tigers are people just trying to tease folks
False flaggers
Damn he's trying to pronounce
Albany
Don't look or act White
Yeah
Holyshit Alex
Totally fine send a text
No larger meaning whatsoever
After Alex has like his lawyer said the n-word a couple times
Which implies there is a way
Leaving alone the entirety of like a being like they don't look white
No not that
Angry meme
You guys
You guys are gone
At the beginning because
You know it's okay to microchipping Alma
Cruel
Holyshit
Wow this is
This is unbelievably
This is such like
This is two white dudes who think
After a show and tell him like you want to hear a joke
And then tossing and racial slurs in the joke cuz he's like
Your white-on-white we know how funny
It's like dude
F*** you Alex
Kicked off social media
And all that one of the things that I speculated was a possible outcome
A lot of the stuff that might have been there
Subtly
And under control a little bit before going to come up
Goddamn
Alex's adds this fluoride
News about attack in Christian
See little bit more this is coming through
Allowed to speak freely
This whatever all social media for this long
What time is it
But whatever
Alex's just like a cool font truth-teller
He's entertaining it's like that
The stuff
And also remember that
Norm is also the guy who posted a video or a picture
I mean
Of like A3 white beer can
Surround sound
That's right Crewcuts
Corzo router
Yeah
Truly
I just messed up
Computer chips
We can always know where they are
Norma's gone
Alex wants to talk about why
He wants to stick around on air
And I'm so glad my lawyer drop and Edward
I'm so glad that we've been around for as long as we have doing this show because like this
Ambitious
If we had no idea
This takes on as mayor of hilarity
Berlin Wall
Show me big story. A lot of corruption and told
Broadcast shutdown
I don't want to just
Continue on
Bureau
Nothing will go wrong this where in reruns
Right after the election year Jerome corsi setting up a DC bureau there's just in his f****** apartment or whatever
Euro with Jerome
Of course
Let's do this again
Alex let me tell you why
Jerome corsi
I think
First of all
I would assume
He did do that it was why he was at
Right after the election was on top of the world
The audience
Outlet
Rentals at the White House
Like profit Drive off of that
I think he probably wants to see if he can do it again
Not going to work
Nope
Second
Whatever
Ribeiro
Would be
Very easily achieved by having
An enterprising listener indeed
That person
If there are
If they were insane
And had a flip phone
Even if you can record on you could have
In a second
Yeah or let's say hey I don't know
6 unpaid interns running the show now so why not you got another one of your audience members would
Do it for exposure
Yeah 100
100%
Maybe an iPhone is
Good enough to record
You're special reports on
Yes
Dollars
It would take almost
Nothing to get a dumb listener in
Step Up 2
Play conference
You don't need a DC Bureau
If no one listens
So
We already had one
That's my that's my reason
I do think it'd be really fun to work it out
Infowars
Just as Lief
Contrarian
In d.c.
I don't know my parents live in Austin
Physically around
Really fun for it to be like Courtney
Like the fairness Doctrine comes back
Alex you could do your show but Darren has the co-host
You're so dumb
I would take that job
I really believe there are
That is one of them
I would absolutely do that
At this point Alex already had one
Knock it out of the park
Edward doorbell
Edward Paddock
Edward Asner
Another gas
Is the guy who was
Whistleblower project veritas
She is in studio with us
Information last week
More and more is coming out
What's sorts of news stories
Actually really nailing down the CNN Styles down
Care too much about that
You were saying
Alice 44
I love me
Let's talk about you
Want to talk about
Name the song
Toby Keith
What
Girl don't want no maintenance
I really don't like this
This is uncomfortable and I'm more uncomfortable now
Whiskey
You are singing the n-word
Song
Why do a lot of my karaoke
Yeah should have been a cowboy and ride
No it is not
Anyway
Project Veritas video on everybody knows
Early hopefully
Toby Keith
I do like
Oh that's nice
Carry the porch
I'm not sure
Bright House
You carry the porch
Is Kerry the verb
Porch
Him
Who's on first
I thought the noun you were talking about is the thing that you sit on
Lakers
Right
Can I record this
Alex
Even
According to his own telling of the story
He is not
An important person
I'm again
I wasn't a journalist I was just on the back into things very low level
Musica Uplink satellite
Guy
Start talking around
Alex
Oliver Darcy
Here's a guy tried to work here and now he goes to see in and joins the dark side
And it literally goes around
Police
Everyone on the internet
You know it's f***** up
It be true
I don't know if it's true it's
Seems like I would still need
Conservative-leaning
Dude years ago
Amazon
30 under 30
Conservative
Media that he was on
Years ago
Complete and total
I don't I don't know
I don't I don't know if that's
The truth I don't know I don't know I don't know
Do you have
Automatic
Someone position
Or the third
Artificial reefs
I think that's
Totally doing that but I think it's
Just saying someone used to be
Conservative
Invalidating
I find that to be a little bit
It's a dangerous lies
However
If it's
Are you working at 4
Conservative that he tried to work at 4
That's a little bit of it
Yeah possibly
But I also think that if it's like
Has as much awareness of it other than it being a
Conservative
Ron Paul type
Libertarian organization
It's
It's tough because we know so much about it.
You can make a better argument for it not being damaged
Right unfortunately if you didn't realize that the only way to get hired there
Cell
You got screwed that one up
I don't look at any of the f****** resumes the people sit
You got to you got to save Bill Clinton's a rapist on TV
Cover letter resume
Complain some more about
Is old girl singing reporter used to mock Network
He's a big boy
Can we say
Bright
More instances of Alex picking up people's physical appearance in applying for
Not good
What do you talk about yours that like Fox News.
Old tweets of Oliver Darcy before he work
CNN's coverage
I can't remember the last time it was
Breaking news
But it's also important
Media criticism
Oh really it's almost feels almost feels like what he was doing
No I don't know
Nowadays
He doesn't
Critique
But I don't
I don't know if that's a dragon
Decreased
The company at all but a little bit
Basically I'm doing
On the job
He's a company man
It is just sort of like
We've got to have a
We got to have some
Moratorium
I get it
Let's let's start from here
We start now any b******* from then
Now
Undercover Journal
Lying about your identity or whatever
Needs to be
An actual reason
Xxxx
Ethically
Use deception
In order to thales
To get a new story
Story is such important
The public
Withhold
I think that there is
A public interest when it's like someone who's
Trying to Rebrand
Used to be like
Fascist
The public
Take out of context
Joke tweet
Cedar Fire
Those sorts of things are all just like
You need for the moratorium
But
I don't know I just suggest
Everybody
On the planet
Should delete all of their old
Everybody
Sure
Self-destruct button
Just built in
Your tweets go away after a week
You can
You should
So anyway
Sponsors
But that doesn't mean he's not going to give some companies
A free ride
Is it your first time
No I've been through Texas many times over my life
I can't say I have
Okay
Supergirl
Play unpaid plug for Topo Chico
Probably don't want
Baby
Send Alex
Booze
When was that
Champagne
Yeah
Come on Alex
That's about putting together
There were just too busy watching videos
It's ridiculous he was like I'm going to go pee on that tree or when he was out
Cupcake
Wrong
Drink
Even if
Super irresponsible to do Alex
Gives a s***
But they don't pretend
You don't as if
Maybe he's not drink
Now
Great
I bet you will soon
You're going to get so drunk and have another breakdown screaming on
Abusive dad
That like
Tell me when I get drunk
Don't make me Hasselhoff
Jesus
Christ
Yeah so are they discussed this
This video
The Carrie help
Project Veritas
And
He was
Still working
The first video was going to be
Be released
He was going to
They put
Easy route
He was there at work
Project Veritas
And flee the city
Overly dramatic
Least
It really overly dramatic stuff
So Carrie talks about that you're a little bit
Experience
Project Veritas video in the van
He articulates the word very well
Trust the guy the CNN nobody's down they know that
Now they know that I was the only one there
So there was
Are there people there on Ark
Accrue
Yeah we just found the back of the
An old ass U-Haul Van and just washed it on iPad it was kind of cruel
Got a cruel cruel
Cool cruel
I mean it's kind of crew
Project Veritas on an iPad
He was
So Alex has the guy carry porch
Whistleblowing
The pizza project
Carrie is not the chatty store
He's too into Alex's sense of humor's kind of like
Cast deep mud
Carrie is trying to be humble and accurate
Constantly refers to himself as a low-level employee
Perception
Betrayal has to keep correct
View a bird's-eye view from the ground
Rhapsody
It's a mess
And to be on board with Alex's worldview entirely
But the two of them have zero
Preoccupied
The carry that your light bulbs
Respond
And the Trump was probably being spied on by lightbulb
Carrie's impolitely interested in looking into it like
But Alex because he's such a dud
Because hyper focused on proving it to him
Goes off the rail
Yeah that sounds
Watch the project video
About that
You know it's really crazy
Part of this interview with their doing
I just don't understand
Covering up this project
Maybe history
Sure
It's a four-part series but I only watched
The first one because that seems focused on Carrie
The first one
That is enough
This boils down to some employees saying that CNN's
CEO Jeff Zucker doesn't like
Personally
Editorial decision
Negative stories about Trump
The entire Institution
Profit-driven news or political commentary
And probably needs
Please please
Don't think that I'm here to go to bed
These folks deserve plenty of criticism
It's just that the valid kind is never going to come
James O'Keefe
If the main criticism your primarily lodging
Is it a head of a company.
It seems like the situation.
Is if everyone liked the president
Which sounds pretty authoritarian
If your criticism is that the network is chasing rating
But then why is your whistleblower going on Infowars
Website
But he's so much more guilty of this
No one else
Yeah
Honestly all of James who keeps expose the complete trash and embarrassing
Particularly
You have a guy who works at CNA talking to his co-workers about stuff like
The election
They think they're just having a conversation with a friend or an acquaintance
They have no idea you secretly recording them so he can give the tape to a s******* propaganda
It's a pretty messed-up violation of their trust
It really doesn't reflect well on the character
It's just kind of bums me out
Like I can't even begin to quantify the number of times I've talked to him
The workplace has an environment where nearly everyone is something
Complain about
Everyone's got something
Say about what's wrong with the bosses
Coworkers often build rapport with each other off
In order to
Make this video
It feels dirty and invasive
But I guess it
Cary poarch
And the right-wing media
Useful to his dark money
Patron cell
I hope it's worth it
I bet
So hard to real bummer
That is
That is dropping a bomb
That's now
Every time I
Is somebody
Videotaping
God that's
Question like now every single time that you talk to this guy before then would be just butter
A state where you can record without the
New York is a one-party consent state
Be having this conversation
Cuz he couldn't just record other people
He actually had
Google order for it to be legal
There's another layer
Negative
I understand that you think
You're doing something big here and showing
And all this
And in order to do
You have to really violate
Peoples
I mean just
It is. It's the sort of thing that like
If you sit back for a second and think about it
But you should be so ashamed
And this will never will
This is something that can
Shity person
Who believes lies
An amazing person
Is actually
It's it's
He's willingly
Can salad like listening
Interview
He's not like
Some guy who got rope tonight
James O'Keefe
Couldn't get
These
People to say what they say in the video
Someone who you think
Your friend at work
You might talk to
Just kind of s*** around them
Such an invasion of privacy
Engrossed
Like for people who can't like
Is turn around and act like this
Is just
Stupid
Guys just don't get
Set the grift
More important
The new and you will be
Alex
In a much larger
Oh yeah
Even if trumps
Even if Trump solidifies his power becomes like a dictator
Doesn't matter what circumstance
You will be chewed up and spit out
Is
You don't want Alex
You want somebody who gives the veneer of
Reality
Alex could make his brand
Continually
Worth Wildwood Beach
Opposition
To whatever
Choosing to go along with Trump
Is the
The second he just died
It's all these consequences
We're inevitable
We set it on like what
Second episode of the podcast
Yeah I guess you could make it drop had lost
Everybody
The decision to support Trump
Supported Ron Paul for all those times again.
Portal
Years
Material
All the same narrative
In a much more effective
You can make excuses for why you're not getting the changes you want to see in the world
Everything works better
I'm sorry for like
Cardigan
Do that
It's kind of backed into a corner ownership over the election
Made it happen
That's a real
Bucked up box
Cuz you think you did
And if you check
And if you change that
You have to admit
That you were wrong
Great at doing
I guess
So this next
Because Carrie claims that used to
He discusses his f*****-up political alignment
In this that next question
Is this doesn't mix
Can you call yourself a liberal in
Fourier on the inside of the
So yes send
I use that term loosely with liberal and everything but
And I supported Bernie in the 2016 election voted for Hancock it's for him in the primaries and then voted for Gary Johnson
And the general this cuz I didn't like Hillary and I didn't like Trump so
I just went third-party and nobody said my vote mattered until obviously the next day
But I would actually say I would mourn the term of left sister far left when I got to CNN
And then
From what I saw the two-and-a-half-year journey I basically
Basically got the red so myself on YouTube while I was in the bureau
And I would say
I mostly center-right libertarian, right now but definitely leaning more and more conservative with each passing day
I spoke at a turning point
Aventon
College Station last night a bunch of great kids they're great people and a lot of fun to me lot of people that
You know just wanted to know
Know what happened well you'll get
Scarlet Letter
Put on you
Of course
Smartcom
Stuff that a guy who's his parents cuz I want to work
Just makes me think that maybe I
I could get that job
Call Jose
Buttermilk
Alex
Describe
That would be hard
Barely sweet
Yeah this is sad
I think that what you see here
Expressing
You know like you just watch a bunch of dumb
Propaganda videos on YouTube
Oh my God
You probably over
Estimate house
If you were to begin with you can make it seem like I came out of the cold
Compelling
Looks like Alex
I watched a bunch of food on YouTube it warped
Hannah under
Launch videos on YouTube
I just don't get
It's strange it's just
Crazy
YouTube videos
And the algorithm will will do that
Yeah yes
Waldo
Takes too much effort
Comprehend well
Well
Possibility
Time is a block
Alex
It's offering him a
My lady and I were entertaining everything that's coming our way we're not
Ruling out anything I'm sure you'll appreciate
More people for 2020
How are you going to hire people you're having an Everything Must Go sale
Your shows falling apart
Live radio
This is a mess
What kind of ideas do you tell me what kind of ideas
Here's an idea
Used bikes
To steal whatever you got
But here is a clip
That I believe invalidate
His credentials
More of is Project veritas
The only group
Well that's just a testament to James and his team like he is very
Very particular with who he hires and vets and everything like he and I talked for almost 2 months
December wedding me
Quietly making sure that I wasn't a CNN Plantronic herbicide
I mean even when I was a leftist i
Didn't like James
But I respected him because
Habitat
Do you know a corn in this that I'm like
You know my people at the time of them like you can argue with tape
You can't argue with a man that is
Either you were Alexa
And you're the dumbest
Still the dumbest human it is it is a possibility that he was inclined towards the last
He was just profound lease-to-purchase. James O'Keefe was actually people who don't read also
It's not like
To Alex's
If you're somebody
Incline
Towards
Last position
And you think
Is accurately portraying
Videos
Quite frankly
Because otherwise
You would look into it
Complete b*******
Masks to protect
The James O'Keefe was wearing the pimp outfit
Alex
Even
Doesn't realize the manipulation that you
Subjected to
So
F*** all this s***
I imagine
He considers him
Self
Are you considered himself a left
Because he had basic human
Then chances are you're going to say you're
It's possible that in hindsight
So he watches those videos and he's like well this overrides
These are giving me a reason to ignore me
Maybe there's some perception that he has
That was accurate but I don't
So he's already said that YouTube videos
Got it
Skyrim
Able
Even Satan ran playing but at least
Yeah so he's
Complain about people who sing
That YouTube radicalized
But he's already
I mean I went before I torched my Facebook the morning of obviously but you know how they do the memories thing like 8 remember this 5 years ago
With me doing like some
You know
Crazy far-left ideology post and what not like that unlike
A total crankshaft sound like
Process
It was this process of where you coming to work in DC
I'm kind of seeing how the sausage is made slowly but surely you know watching an ecosystem of videos here and there and just being open
Start you actually entertain other ideas
You know what
Accepting of that time but just being open and it's okay let's see what the other side has to say and there was a whole ecosystem
On YouTube where I could go from one day to the next I know they're going to take this out of context that see this YouTube radicalize of people you remember
New York Times article but it just got me where I can start watching pieces
Several different people's videos
And was slowly but surely kind of
Red tailing me in the process
I did
Is he the manipulation of the self
Yeah I mean
This is
So woefully transparent
Somebody who fell victim to the algorithm
Probably started watch
Like Stefan molyneux videos
Dave Rubin
This is a story over and over and over again
And
Good luck
That's listening
Pluck
This isn't
Yeah the problem is it
So
Like they do it's okay
Cuz you know if you were talking
Somebody and you hadn't been
And they took a big swig
Say you are as somebody who voted for Bernie
You're like
Consider myself on the left
YouTube video where it's
White people are under attack
You're going to be like
Just like
What's the function of people like
Man
You need to raise the temperature gradually
That's why people
Lancaster
Steven Crowder or
People down towards
More radical ideas
Terrorism
Why you have people like that
Katie Hopkins
F***** up
Any presents
Leads to
A greater ability
People to
End up considering the people
Kill all the Muslims
Genocide
Whistleblower
For a long time
And he finally gets around to it
In the shower
Call
Immediately go to a friend of Carrie
Call Dad
Overseas
In the service
Go to Carlos, go to Johnny solo Ryan Michael and Chris
Let's go to your buddy Oz
Chinese dragon
Jordans
I was
Your jaw was wide open
I just
I just I can't believe
This show
Would also have a guy say the n-word a couple of years
It's it's
These videos where he does this
Offensive Chinese voice
On a Dragon cartoon
The audience response
They like
Laughing
Jesus f*** you
If you were on the left
We don't
It's a funny guy
This turns
I was talk to you
I talked to solo dance
October 14th ABC Air 2 footage from Syria
Nighttime machine gun demonstration
Confirm shooting range
Kentucky
Ever since this point right-wing media figures like Alex have latched onto this Esme
Excuse to pretend to Northern Syria
ABC apologize for the error and investigating how the mistake was made
Is it a big mess up appropriately
How do the operations are supposed to work
They f***** up
They apologized
Animator correct
It doesn't matter though
People like Alex can suck up in a million time
Never apologize never correct anyting
If you slip up on over and over to portray you as
Go party
The lame
Childish game
Yep
I personally don't care too much about the stupid game app
Truth is that ABC did fuk up and
The big one
And in doing so
Genesis justify
Potential genocide
Senator John cornyn
If he was planning on coming into Northern Syria
Liquid cleanse the Kurds
A US troops were caught in the middle
I'm not completely convinced that it was a bad idea to get them out of Harm's Way
Last week
Talkin about Northern Syria
Cleaned out
In the immediate aftermath of Trumps withdrawal Turkish forces moved in and started attacking
Tens of thousands of civilians were displaced
For their lives
On the 13th it was reported that turkish-backed millet
Executed 9 people
Including the secretary-general
Future Syria party
Who was the leader of democratic
Anita far from the only civilians
Overkill
Pointing to one video that ABC News got wrong doesn't undo have wrinkled ass execution
Nor the deaths of all these other people
All it does is give Alex a crutch
To feel right
When he all he's doing
Is supporting an unjustifiable foreign policy decision
But it's Doom
Countless people
The displacement life under a dictator or death
F*** Alex Jones
These are the sorts of moments that you need to fully understand when people say that Alex is
It's funny your this is just entertaining
Where the host of the rtlm in Rwanda
Was it just entertainment
Was Lord haha funny
Is that just entertainment
Is this entertain
Alex is carrying water for Trump abandoned while doing a racist Chinese
Funny
It's not funny
Not entertained
It's cruel and malicious propaganda
And the only thing I can really take solace
Is that I believe he'll probably live long enough to extremely regret his ass
That's the only thing I can really hang my hat on
He's at this point
Like there's just there's just no words for how
He's doing
While
Defending
A genocide
So
I don't know what else
If you can't
If you can't recognize
Is that is
Not just
Immoral but
Like some level
Next level is history
Understand
The problem that I have is I don't think that Alex is very
Relevant
Affecting famous
Nearly to the point that people like the broadcasters on the rtlm
Alex's
Is causing any
But not to the extent that
Yeah but his intention is very similar
These very serious situations that deflect
Anybody being concerned about it in service of
Supporting Trump
Isaac Hayes
He's going to be very complicated I actually
Take what he
He's doing
Seriously
Which is pink with a lot of people
You
I don't understand how I really am
Amaze
I'm not
And I do
That's the problem
Let me put it that way
It is so normal
That John cornyn will face
No
For literally saying
I'm fine with
Of course
That's how awful it is
They're like
And it said that that's what we got now
And you know it
10mm
What's been going on
For so long
Gordon should be
Literally
I don't want harm to come to anybody
But his knees
Should be blown out
Fucken prick
Support the use of violence
Political gains but I understand why you expressing yourself that way
Just trying to push back on your violent that's all I'm doing
I hear you I hear you
Hate to say
Haha our show is important cuz I don't know if it really is
Really is the balance
This is this like
This dude
Like way out of line
Here
But at the same time he's also running commercials where he brags about having a chainsaw
There is a farcical aspect
If he had the opportunity to
He would
Defender John
Because that's the behavior that you
Consider because should
Things ever get bad enough
In this country where we're talking about
Like let's say getting rid of
Country
He would be for it
Not not relevant
Enough
31 myflip here and Barnes
See this is where it gets into a really interesting conversation
Pataskala
Now we're going to hear with Barnes
Challenge
Answer me
Who is the worst lawyer on the October 23rd episode of Alex's show
Directions in particular because of the sort of
Thanks
Pushing us towards Islam
Askew
Richard
It is more f***** up
The guy coming in and talking about
Or the lawyer who comes in
And very bluntly declares were at war with a religion
Man
You know I want to say congratulation
Both our competitors
You guys you guys really left it all out on the field
Today
Anyway cause any kind of like
Worse
And there we have it I am and I'm going to
You know
Just pure number
But
I'm going to
While you're thinking let me give you my thought on
Okay
I think
Viscerally
Norm takes the win
I think
Probably we might be worse
Right it is much as
You sort of declare in the holy war is a lot more
That worlds
What you would be looking at is probably
Very least
Like a very
Very f*****-up
Campaign
Trying to rid the world of Islam
And I think that probably has
Far worse effect
Then
Nor being allowed to say the n word
Norm say the n word
Came out instead
The war against Islam
I applaud your honesty
A norm only
You know
Which which one you're going to
The Warriors
I don't want to
Position of relative
1 implies a World War
Guys are
I feel like a bar should be harder to pass
Is it is it normal
I've just really done a great
Illuminating
How
Every
I cannot believe how shocking
Episode 1
It's staggering
Just alone
Yeah that's crazy
The Shootist
Raising
Crazyshit
Indian word and the other declare in the war of islamophobia
Also
These two dudes
Perfect examples of why this show is
So
The the weekend
How many people
In their in their quiet
No one's listening
Just ask
How many people would say
I applaud you for
Public
In public
But when it's just us guys
It's good that
You're finally
I don't think it's too far off base from Alex's
But it's weird for his lawyer
Yeah I mean that's what I'm saying if if I if I heard Alex
Just say it
Exactly
You know
Alex
His lawyers coming on there being like I'm glad now that it's just us
We all know what week
Yep
I do believe that a lot of these signs that we're seeing means
Alex's Fox
So please like
Comfort in the fact that
This isn't going well for her
Still
He is circling the drain
But
Hey man
You know what that one day it will be a brag for him to say he has a chainsaw
Really think
If you had
And by Juliana as the two lawyers
This Converse
Laid out in the
It might be a little bit less
Same script to be played out by those three guys
At the dark.
We live in Thor the Dark
You didn't miss much
Good
If you don't go to a website
Our website
Browser on Twitter
We are on Facebook and I also
Hiiraan
I've heard that where you could download
Review
With your friends to the whole thing we love it
Until then I'm meal
Dzx Clark
This chainsaw
Holding
Alex