I have great respect for knowledge
Knowledge fight
Jordan
Let me ask you
Do you have a
Favorite gospel songs gospel songs
Why do you remember did you go to Hogwarts
Okay
Bug with red
Alternation
Woodcrest
Columbia Missouri
I don't know man I don't know about gospel songs but like
When you bring that up it makes me think of like
The Christian music that I used to listen to
Like DC Talk
To the Christian Scott
COC super town
Insiders
But there's a little bit of a swing / offer
To them
I like sauce
Yeah
Pretty lady
Just too cautious
My first two concerts but I went to live
Next one
Wu-Tang Clan
Little bit of time MP3 nose
Sure
Olympics
So I probably
Gerald
Undoubtedly
Like I'm sure I did what it just doesn't stick out
My memory weirdness Christian
Music One
Really stick out
I was actually into the
Okay I know everyone out there's rolling the damn eyes at me
A couple Five Iron Frenzy
Play songs I think
Hold up
Even if
You'd like
But you can listen to them almost outside of it being religious
FairPoint
I'll do other ones
It's big out to me
AR
Christian Reggae
Albemarle call christafari
There is a large
Safari
Terrible
Terrible shop
Who was the other there's a rapper name
T-Bone remember
Bedtime
Particular gospel song
Lot of Christian music ID codes
Except
Anyway I know a lot about
What are shows about today
Save the world
In the middle of the events
Of the unfolding
Of the aftermath
Of the under trying to stretch this out
Boston bomber
Which is the day that everything
Everybody figures it out
18th the FBI released images
We now know
Timberland
But
And then overnight
It just blows
Is completely
It's absolute chaos
Is everyone is
Shelter in place
People are staying indoors
Recovering today
I think this is one of her episodes
Show that I've heard in a very long time
You're right
I want to say
Weird can mean a lot of different
This was an unexpected episode
Exactly what US
Think you're going to fly
An apology
Auto.
Thank you so much
Next Alicia thank you so much
Silly goose
Untitled Goose game
Atlantic
Everybody was
Is overjoyed
You are now policy wonk
Next
Appreciate that very much
Steven thank you so much
Heroin
Freakishly large
Coyote has
Steven and Jimmy they were in the city
Saul Good
The button that says Sports
Things are on front
The United States
Everything is Everything is on President's Day
Exact
Is an interesting thing about the city of Boston being on lockdown
Call brother.
Months
Prior Governor Deval Patrick called for everyone to stay inside because of the winter storm
Could be arrested or fine
Talk about that
Our last episode covering this coverage
Tracy Bowden 4chan
Crack this case wide open
And at the media and the globalist
Stuart a mad scramble to keep their false flag operation
Come together
His certainty was naturally
His own imagination
But the effect was clear
He was blowing up
Open popularity
And he loved it
Is ratings through the roof
Traffic was coming into the website like
Like crazy
How to disrupt Boston officials press conference
Successfully able to calm
Televised events
Including the one on the 8th
Teeth where the FBI released photographs
The two suspects
Who are still at that point on identified
12 gal had the effect that
Is going for which was driving tons of traffic to Alex
That press conference had another important effect
Ultimately
We're far more relevant
To the real world
April 18th was the day that everything broke wide open
4 days since the bombing the perpetrators had every reason to think that they've gotten away with
They return to their normal lives
5:20 p.m. on the 18th
The FBI release their photo
The illusion of safety with gone
Matter of time for someone
And don't speak 24 hours of
Complete chaos
At 10:31 p.m. MIT police officer Sean Collier is murdered sitting in his car which investigators determined
These guys to get another gun
This murder happened very close to an armed robbery that happened at a convenience store
So early reports got the two of them mixed up.
People thought they were connected but they were
That was another
Thing that is stored apart
The conspiracy Canon but Alex doesn't
Actually
Diculous
How to make
Metropolitan area
To be another unrelated
Have you ever
The phone
Somebody was on the other line
Phone call at 8
Describe significance to it where there may not be
Convenience store
SUV less than an hour later at 11
10:20 p.m.
Holding driver hostage with them
They were
Pretty camera shopping for a bunch of snack
You later tell the detectives that their plan was to drive to New York and set off another bomb
This plan to be derailed by the SUV's owner Escape in the car
To a different nearby convenience store where you called
Police
You can easily find security camera footage of the driver run
To that store terrified
Hiding behind the counter and calling apps
Tell him that he been carjacked by men claiming to be the bombers
GPS system
You can also easily find footage from the same time of the older bomber coming into
The gas station
Tell the younger brother
That the driver had it was time to go
The younger guy drops all the snacks and they run out back to the car
Later in this episode
Alex and a collar will discuss how the bombers were in a Mercedes
And how that's really suspicious
Speculate
This money
They stole it from the sky
DeLand older
Sure I think that might
Are you sure
Pretty sure
The police track that SUV to address in Watertown
The first responding officer spouses
Disengage until the supervisor arrived
He follows the SUV then around 12:41 a.m. the driver of the SUV gets out approaches
Who's the star in start shooting
Approximately 8 minutes
With both sides exchanged gunfire
In one of the bombers throwing IEDs
Which Alex
Will later miss identify as
He does that in order
Do you like how they get their hands on grenades
They made
Which is well within the range
At 12:49 a.m. the older brother is tackled by police after he run out of bullets
The officers attempted to get him subdued and
The officers jumpmans
To jump out of his run over as it partners
Before 1 a.m. the shootout in Watertown who come to an
The older bomber is taken
To the hospital
Timberlands
And with this information to able to identify
Neutralizing one suspect is probably a good thing
Considered be hard to consider this night's event
A good result
What officer has been severely injured
Sustained injuries that would end up killing it
Approximately a year later
The one suspect was down please
Successful in giving Chase to Johor
Who appeared
From the site of the
Police went to work immediately
All points bulletin percent out and bomb squads were
Were called into duty lies the unexploded IDS
The brothers have laughed
Epicene
News of the flare-up broke real quick
And almost immediately the Watertown Police Department is
Suspicious individual
All of them look into inside unrelated
Do the search for johar
In the 24-hour span the department receives over 500 calls to 911
As opposed to their normal daily average of 30
These people were dealing with an overwhelming situation
And where communities
Protect them from a rogue
Individual on the loose
It's easy to look at the situation
What's the need for such a
Police response
But the reality is simple
At the time it was very unclear if this was just one kid
Police officer
When confronted by additional cops
He responded by throwing
This is a person who
Killed his brother
Maybe not intentionally but
It's just like
Probiotics
Up in the air about whether or not you would have died anyway
Viva minute that hospital
Yeah or he could be
Big thing like a
The Boston
There's no way that you're
Just
There has to be some sort of
Information
Oh that's
Up in the air
If he has accomplices
You cannot allow
Absolutely
Whatever
Which we know now there wasn't but that's
That could come from
If you're able to catch
The person before
There's a possibility
Disrupting the larger
You would need to
Worst case scenario
Terrible
So at 1:57 a.m.
The residents of the town
Asking them to stay inside their homes and Report
It might be helpful in there may
This obviously isn't given the circumstances I'm not sure there was a good option
Important distinction needs to be made
At this point the message to stay indoors was
Batory order
And it was very localized to the area directly surrounding the morning
Shootout
People could go outside but the neighbor
Police report was questioned and released
So it's not like that you'd be shot if you
Which is kind of what Alex would like
Unified command
Outlet shopping center in Watertown
Coordination between neighboring area Police Department
As well as the FBI in the Massachusetts Emergency Management
Over 1,000
Individual law enforcement officers are on hand
Deal with it
And by the end of the day more than 2,500 office
Been involved in some capacity
At 4:15 a.m. the Massachusetts emergency
Governor Deval Patrick
National Guard
Do deployed military police into water
This is another important
Come here because the authorization come from FEMA or the federal government
This was a state level
Decision which really punches holes
States rights
The governor's mansion
They can call out National Guard for
Situation
More likely would not have
Exactly
Group of vigilantes
Decision or the most epic
Not really my interest
All the argument
As the morning comes
120 military police officers
House-to-house searches
Again by the proper Channel
At 5:15 a.m. the governor of Massachusetts in the mayor of
Andesite
Suspend fast transit services temporarily
Effectively putting area into locked
This is the closest thing to martial law
We've seen in the United States for a long time
And it would be easy to see this as the Fulfillment of Alex's prophecies
This is a very severe but
Necessary law enforcement
Cuz what if Joe Hart been part of a larger cell
Or what if he wasn't being on the loose Legend bomb
Train the next morning
The worst case scenario of whatever
You to be down to catch him that night would be an unacceptable risk
The police did not do this how they do
Release that's my position
And it seems like the residence of Boston
WBUR did a survey a year later
April 2014
3% of respondents
Believe that the
Was the right to
Decision
In the United States
50% to be like
Whatever
Most affected by this
Agreed that it was
Police acted appropriately
Yeah I can see
See an argument
I can understand that
They can only be had in hindsight
And so we can apply some of those lessons
Futuristic
No one involved
Which is why
Is a good idea because everybody was really
Good
If you read the after-action report that the authorities all collaborated on
A lot of very valid criticism
Particularly about weapon discipline
Locate
It is particularly in the case of the water
Shootout when they were trying to stop his car
Possibility
Their circumstances
That the police
Definitely
Didn't
Operate housing
But at the same time
They weren't doing it
Because they were
It's more it's more expensive
Better training
They know not to
Create
Possible risk
Situation birthday
Learn from this I don't want
Get into
Storyville for this
Specific circumstances
Yeah
Operators.
Hunter tips during this
Suspicious person carrying a package
Intuit tax
The police end up finding out
The taxi driver
And this immediately becomes a
Huge deal
The taxi was on route
To the South Station
Which is a hub for both the mass Massachusetts Mass Transit
So taxi service is suspended in the city
It's determined
Misspelled his name
This will not be the only time in this story that appropriate
Which leads me to my next flight
Which is the data entry workers
Need to be respectful
And also she probably
Sprouts
The day goes on
And the police keep coming up
The previous night at Pinnacle
Completely chaotic
With a murder of a police officer
Request for a metropolitan area to stay indoors
The National Guard carry out their search
It's almost like a ball being set up on a t
He's spent his entire career talked about how fake terrorist attacks martial law
He's determined to terrorist attack
False flag
And the responses
Call Marshall Law
No it's not even close
All the details
If there ever was a day when it felt like Alex
Begone
It should be this
He's literally on air while The Manhunt is going on
Well Boston is in a shelter-in-place request
Select music
Alex
Constitution
Lexington Green
Bloomberg
Boston
And surrounding cities
He's bringing up the martial law so that's good
The Oath Keepers
Counter-protesters
And by definition counter-protesters
Need permit
Constitution Alex love so much
What a group plants
To use public space to hold
Because they're the ones
Use the public
Space for their own purposes
If a cat
Something green for example
This was the case with the unite the right rally in Charlotte
Where is harmony of the end of white supremacy
At Justice and McGuffey Park
Which are near the park where the right-wing groups
Permit
This is just simple Civic
The people counter demonstrating The Oath Keepers don't need permits because their event is really just a natural extension of The Oath Keepers
Not an event in its own right
I just heard
Million right
Scream
Intero in a
Understand
This is not an example of favoritism
It's not Alex's mostly Focus
Also
I'm not sure if Alex is ever consulted a map
Is not close to kinetic
I just heard a million conservatives
Scream out when you said map
Crystal City
Omni Atlanta
Other stages
Closest probably go with New Hampshire Rhode Island
Close to Springfield Massachusetts
What is martial law
Extending
He's really just saying something absurd
He might as well just say that all of New England
To try and apply
Nobody
Unlocked
You can get all of it but
Connecticut is because he doesn't understand to understand
It's 7:15 a.m. the police received a tip about the person with a suspicious package of the taxi
They were going to South Station which includes
If you allowed a bomb to get there
Ending
F****** transportation
Part of the investigation was believed that this person got onto on the South Station
To Norwalk
Which was the next stop if they were able to stop
So they stop this train in Norwalk
The Metro Police
Apartment search
There's no extension of checkpoints
The first time I've been on
Is all resolved by 9 a.m.
And use it to pretend that this shelter in place
Request the police put out extended past
Austin suburbs
It's a real on 4th
They really had enough
The moving train
And it just turned out it was
I like
I don't know
Good fight
So Alex
False flag
He's sort of
He thinks it's certainly a false Lash
It's weird but it's almost a meeting
Organic
Muslim terrorist
I'm all of this
Do you have the grill
This was real which is strange
All the stuff that he sang that
All of the reasons that you have for that 95%
Look
Baby 54
It's weird and it's weird to hear this
Unprompted
A greater possibility that it's a real event
It just got
5 times more likely
It's very strange
I don't know I don't understand why
Functionally
Keep your difference between they're being a 1%
And a 5%.
Of course not
He gets on to talk about how to use this whole time
Covering this
Add event
What does spectrum
He goes on from there and just Trails off
Could we listen to the episode from that Monday
When he was in overdrive
It was mostly a bit
Think this is a false flag and trying to find any little piece of information to justify
Patriots Day
Annabella stats
He was not right on target
Narrative
And he's doing it very sloppy
We just heard Alex's quote if there was a drill if they were military all around
The money Trail.
That part is of this offense
But we know what it is
Exactly
Every single person listening to Alta show knows that without
Xanax
Infowars
And this is where deception is kind of belt
Because Alex knows that his audience is internalize this if-then relationship
Shortcut to prove it
But something was a false
Proving it heavy cloud
Create
Perception
Understanding this Dynamic goes a long way toward understanding why Alex is so prone to accept
Bleep bulshit
Would it help them get worried
To go
He has absolutely no ability to prove that the bombing was a false flag
It's just not possible
But his audience is accepted the implied relationship between a drill and false flag
Which I would argue he still has failed to do
This context why you accept all this
Completely flimsy evidence of a drill and then extrapolate that stuff out
Or passed with reasonable
He's done this with
School safety drill in a completely different City to assert that Sandy Hook was a false flag
He's done this with a
Corporate training lecture he's pretending with a drill
Was a false flag
He does this all the time because he knows that the appearance of a drill
Is enough to convince
Most of his already
It's a shortcut
That's all
Long career in the
3 Bells is a little bit
Annoyed
Story
I'm telling you
You got some good ideas I don't know I think he was more the guy in the writers room was like
Fine
He gets a with with assistance by
Executive
Assistant executive producer credit at best
Sure
So Alex is a
He's convinced still no matter what they were planning on blaming right
Expresses
Crawdaunt
Wednesday
With three different host and yes it's going to be
Understand
You heard it here
Nowhere else
Aria Alexander
Snow people
Speculate stuff
TV news programs
You know the feelings a 24-hour cycle is
Is it possible that
Entirely absolute
So whatever
This is such an example of
It's like say that it was going to be
So they might as well
F****** you-know-who
Set all the stuff George Noory on Coast to Coast AM
Is also pretty worried
Facebook
Censorious
This is
Consistent to a concern of his
What have you
Pacifica 2013
Officially
Misinformation after the boss
Isolated incident
Infowars
In the absence of official solid information
Wellfleet
People like
There were cottage industry conspiracy blogs over trying to drive traffic we're posting the same kind of stuff
There were people creating fake profiles for the Tsarnaev Brothers on social media
Conspiracy theories
Could humans are f***** up
This was something is very much on the rise
Tons of accounts for Aurora shooter
I've been created
Some probably has jokes but some probably more malicious
NBC News reported
Many of these accounts are being used to spread
Conspiracy theories
Another thing it was happening at the time was
Reusing fake articles about the bombing
Spread spam and malware
Hoping to capitalize on
The public's hunger for information about
Cisco put out a warning
And warned that one of the attempts was related to an email that
From CNN
I know you want to make a phone
Biting your lip
You worry about you if I don't say something if you were under $0.04
Let me see that
B u
Looks like an email
With the headline
Explosions FBI benefits?
Censorship of
Conspiracy content around this time was related
Texting users from these botnet
We're trying to hijack
In a crisis like this people who are up to no good go to work
The public really wants to know what's going on and when they're not
To cyber-attack
Do you exploit that hunger for information
Get people to click on things they probably wouldn't otherwise
I'm not sure exactly what
The bigger picture of what Alex is talking
About
Definitely plenty of horrible things
There's a twenty-two-year-old brown University student named
PetSmart
I'm and he's someone who the internet decided to turn into a suspect in the bombing
In the days after the bombings
And then on April 23rd
The Providence River
With a subsequent autopsy the cause of death was suicide
I'm not aware of any evidence that the Witch Hunt was related
Incense before the bomb
Traumatized
Terrified family
Define their son
Facebook did not
Take down these posts that were
Think about
These articles about
I think he's also referencing this
Because
The manipulative lie edited Family Guy
Understand
I'm sure that Seth MacFarlane copyright claim
Wheatley distorting
You can use copyrighted
Material transfer
Recreated thing
Is representative
Play mix
The
Edward
CA is
Technically fair use all the f******
They are on the side of
Brazen
Commentary
So it's part of the Ark
I mean
Episode
These articles are you saying with these Navy Seals
Resume
These rossittos based on looking at some pictures you found on Fortune
I'm not sure what happened with Facebook
Thanks to this
You know what
I don't know
But if they were blocked
I fully support that decision
How much was engaged in targeted harassment of the people in those photos
It literally zero reason to suspect them of being involved in this terrorist attack outside
He was publishing articles speculating the
Is part of the operation
The left hundreds injured 3 Dead
I don't necessarily believe that Facebook blocked
News article
I don't care
They should have
This is as real as
If he blames
15 minutes
Touchdown current events in Boston
Nipsey Hussle Victory lap
Updates
Interested like this
Is a weed story
This episode
That seems weird
The behavior you would expect
Alex Jones
When the appearance of martial law
Is the get on air
Call Alt
This should be War
You should be talking about how good it is
Keepers are involved
Make the first offense
Deliberate
Alex's entire careers
Just coming
That's weird well I mean
Based on what we know now
I think you realize
Places that white people
Now that big
I don't I don't know
No I might be realized
This is that if he were to go
In his words
We might actually get a lot of
I think the possibility
The first
Completely legal and they do need to find the terrorist who's on the way
He knows if he doesn't
Key the carrying out of the investigation that God forbid
Like this guy blows up another building
Obstruction of justice
I don't think I don't think I would stay
Would just be a thing worth
There's a limit
Maybe I don't know
I like to think there's a letter
Glass quarterback
Possibility
I would describe
This is a point
He's been yelling about forever
Like you never have to pay up
Chickens coming home to roost
He's been millions of dollars rambling about how is the government ever got out of line images Patriot bodies
He was safe to do this because I'm sure he never imagined something like this would have
But now it is the appearance of it
And heavily armed police are searching houses door-to-door
And people are being asked
To stay indoors
In order for Alex to stay in anyway
He has to call for armed resistance
And he really doesn't want to do that
News ratings are way up
Like to keep that going
Resist
The police officers trying to find the surviving Boston bombing suspect
Probably your nose to spite your face conversation
I suspect but cannot prove
He found his narrative this is a false flag
Traffic
Descending on the city.
Play into his narrative
It's also too much
Do be very difficult for him to engage with the story how he normally would
Without it being too
To the point that I wear
I'm not something you just can't afford to do as a business
Because in his
Literally it is
Appearance of
Exactly these
Sequence of events
It is literally I
Grease police
There's a
That means
Blow up
Alex's
Globalist
Cannot ever actually start
Always be about
Always be making
Kinder move
They actually be doing the martial law
The in-between state
Because if the stories of martial law
Should tell that it's time to start shooting
I think Alex wants to
Foster this image but it's
Stave off
Tuckaway fraud
The only
Exclamation
Those possibilities
Because
Someone who presents himself
In every contact that I've heard
They only only
Possibility
Is that he realizes
Too hot
And his behavior
He thinks the negative effect is
That's debatable
Yeah
I see you being like
This is too hot
I could lose a lot of money
Movie traffic
Did now the time to get kicked off air is now
I do feel that
Sincere because
What he wants to do instead is just
Keep talking about
The same shape
But he found on 4chan
Change the game
It's going to come out
Forget it
What
Same
Obviously
Everyone listening to our show
Is just based on his fantasies
Constructed pictures.
None of this is real
It merits pointing out
Alex has no idea any of the people in the picture
Cuz you thought were actually Muslims
All he knows is that they're not white people possibly of Middle Eastern descent
He has no reason to believe the people in these images
Fortuner followers of Islam
DC's brown people in the picture
Which to me is bad
Yeah I mean
One good part
Like luxury of other ring
The other is so big
Just called the other whatever you want
Anybody in those pictures turned out to actually be Muslim is kind of irrelevant to Alex's
Assumption
If they aren't now they were
Narrative is based on
Imagine about people in these pictures
Easy brown people they must be Muslim
Easy white guy he must be a redneck 88 who's been brought in to be the Patsy
Guys in uniforms they must be Navy Seals mercenary group
Not one single thing about these people in these photos is actually substantiate
It's just taken
Because Alex is absurdity
To be true
When we talked about Alex not knowing the difference between reality and fiction it's usually in the context of him thinking that movie scene or
That's definitely place where the attendance
She is most pronounced
But it's important to remember that this exists in other
Here he's written a complete fiction about some pictures he saw that he found out 4chan
Any experience is that as real
It's almost like an author falling in love with a character in a novel
They're writing
He either knows he
He's doing this and willfully misleading
Accepting his fiction is reality for his own profit
Which would make him a psychopath
Or he has no idea
He's doing that
People which means he needs serious help
Regardless of the explanation
Someone should have intervened in Alex's like long ago
It's real
Balmert
These signs
These warning signs
Clear
Imagine
Someone in his life not being like this
F***** up
Now it's working
I can't imagine
I mean if you're anything other than
You could
Rationalize away all
If you didn't have a
Active life
Consistent point of view regarding everything
Can you Saturday
Tracking it over
Just be like
Coming in and out needs a nonsense like a movie and relax
I don't think the most
Like in that movie
That junk
I don't think that most people who would have any interest
And critically looking at
Write a lot of its life
People listening or passive or
You know these signs just get mess
Either a willful
Attempts to get people to accept an alternate reality
Inability to know what's real
Either option
Is pretty
Some little points that he bring
Wingstop
Again
Much
Going on talking about
Situation of the shelter in
He's leaving Lexington Green
That's the first reference to the shootout from the night before
Only
Referencing it vague
I can find no evidence
Definitely didn't but I'm saying that I can't find any trace of the story on the aps website
Archived versions of the sites
From the time
I don't know what the reality is here but I have every reason to
Believe Alex is just kind of
Later someone attempts to correct Alex that what happened was that the police were warning
Before at the shootout in Watertown
There was an active shooting going on
This is very different
Police threatening to shoot
Reporters definitely sounds like
Police threatened to shoot report
If you stick around
In this circumstance if Trump was
Police Commissioner whatever
I would still.
Because
It is a legitimate warning than 8 minutes
Ibiza police
Misunderstanding a misrepresentation of
A reporter that I heard of
Clip is a really good encapsulation
Is dealing with the supposed martial law
He touches on it for a second but only to use it as a way to amplify
Talk about The Oath Keepers can't have a permit
We're happy globalist want your gun
Those are safe topics
Turn to stay on
Because
The Oath Keepers are obviously still having a rally in Noah
Stop them
Taking anyone's gun
Totally fine to agitate
You're only
Creating
Hypothetical extension
Martial law
YouTube very quickly end up advocating violence of
The police
It's a real sign of cowardice what he's doing
Clear indication
If you believe half the s*** he yells about on his show
This would be a put-up-or-shut-up moment
Just decided to change the subject
But I'd be surprised
Nobody called in
Call Dan
The related to the shootout for the night
Before
Replace request
But it's not
It's it's weird
Crazy
It's if you're saying there's more
You said it's time
Start swinging
There are some crazy
Okay
So Alex
Stewie brings up the shootout
Before but
The gun stop
Stuart roads the head of the
Show
Stupid
Ceremony
In their conversation
Store Road Selma
Super f***** up there
Cupquake
Roses
Complete lunatic
Check if you think so
Please whatever preference solution
It didn't happen so we can only guess
People called 911
Authorized so the people who
You know they were calling
LaRosa's
Jesus Christ
Think about much more concrete version
Honda fault. Spector got floated by the internet
People felt emboldened
One of those people might have been killed
Absolute
It's almost a miracle that no civilians
Were killed as is
In The Manhunt and everything
The police after Action Report make
Makes very strong points
Needed
Was the weapons
And the late-night chudat Watertown
There was a crossfire
Situation that got created
After johar Got Away an erroneous report of a stolen truck was called
Police shooting at when they spotted it
No one was hurt and it turned out the people in the truck were off-duty police
Stride
Terrifying what could have happened but resolved as well
Signs of Life
You talk about
Resident historian have
I've never gotten a realize we set this up or lie cuz I don't feel good as a line pressure
These were
It strains credulity to imagine that would take possibly would be any more disciplined
I think this is a bad solution
Especially not one so f****** trigger-happy is
Oathkeeper
I want nothing less in life for Stewart Road style Posse to be empowered to
Enforce the law
Picking Lily up to the point of using lethal Force
That's legitimately the stuff
Contention that this was happening in Texas
I beg to differ
2018 twenty-three-year-old Mark Condit carried out a string of bomb
His first bombing was on March 2nd
Serial bombings
21st
Is Reign of Terror
Because I'm old
Keep a rounded up the boys and went hunting
It was because police did a thorough
Navigation and track
Their unsuccessful as he detonated a bomb
Bring a cop
Vigilante activity did literally nothing
Help
Nor did Alex's lunatic ravings about it all being
False flag
So I guess
Just proves Alex's we would have taken care of
Nonsense
Children playing
Cowboys in India
Got hurt
Probably
F****** group
Children
Awful
It is awful
I have so much power
Stewart
Advocating
Straight up
Vigilante Posse
You are as a preferable solution
I cannot imagine
A year later if you pulled that flavor
I would guess
You guys feel that
Handled the night of Terror as we know it now 17
10% says it was a good idea the rest of us
Did you enjoy the
Flimsy rationalization
24-hours
White people murdered
So keep in mind in this next clip the city of Boston
As well
Pretty messed up
Situation
Everybody's
Struggling
Is also having a
Like
You know that Noah was going to arrest
This is just
Milking it for all it's worth
This is that
Pizza place in the
Jakpus obit
I was just coming all over the place
F****** ID
Alex
And his belief that this is
False flag
I need expecting Stewart's going to be like yeah absolutely
Little bit
That's crazy
I don't like
Close this is why
Why I say that they're alive
There are unexpected line
People have
Never know how to predict what they are
Like Alex
It's probably would feel guilty if
A building be blown up
Now public
I never would have guessed it still roads it's been like I have no idea who these people are
You're literally Advocate going around
You know your neighborhood you know who's not supposed to
Be there
Are you talkin about how are you going to identify who's not supposed to be there if I don't
Why are weird
I don't know I don't know what to make of it
Please will you skin color
In this next clip we finally have the younger bombers
Alex
The first time that he says it
Under martial law
We just Incredibles
Like this is about a couple times
Cities under martial law
Do you expect
Getting into it
Yeah not just
Straight
Is on the way to other topics
Martial law
Entire careers
City goes under Mars
Signal
I'll take over the country
So far it's not just like
Oh yeah Boston's under martial law
You're right
Verily
Alright
Let's not panic about this
This is a temporary lawn Forest
Activity Beyond The Realm
Acceptable
What we need to focus
Is that this is a
The trial run
Or something like that
Martial law
And I'm certain that that is where Alex will land eventually
But you would expect that would be
Because he needs to cover this
It's just like I said
Aside I mean Trey mentioned
In the movie
He woke up early that day that the time to ruminate
Before it gets too
Right
His work is actually just reading negative articles
Demonic
Navy Seals
As a six series
David
What is this
Contracting
The people who backpack
Call Dad
Football game
Occupation news
On the internet that is now starting
Haseeb into Alex's
Conversation about it
David Knight is been more on this prior to the
Itself
Just for context is irrelevant
It may seem like a little minor slip up at Alex try to refute that La time story with the Washington
End times headline and he tries to pass off as a Washington Post
Edline
But if you know what these papers are that looks less like a mistake and more like sleight of hand
Washington Post is a mainstream media paper
Publishing an article speculating
These Craft International agents at the marathon
It lends things a bit more credibility
Which is exactly what
Story
But the story to make it to the wapo it would need to pass layers of Ed
Conversely the wash
Completely untrustworthy
The cult leader Reverend Sun Myung Moon
Boone said I found at the Washington Times
Expression of my love for America
Who seek to establish America in New Providence
That's that's
Formosa
The fourth estate
I'm pretty sure that's how they all started
These intentions
Concretely translator
In its early days the paper was mainly about how great the Cold War was
South America
You can see why Alex
It's a good source
He comes from an insane John Birch Society
Credible
He knows that most people look at the times as unreliable
Post
It doesn't make Alex look better to appeal to a Time
But it does
The post
That's why you said that the washing
The post headline
And lets out a big sigh
What do you realize is it the Washington time
Story
That's a sigh of disappointment
Doesn't have the msf
He was building up to
Telling
It's also pretty
Pretty brilliant
Reacting in the moment
To be like
Because that makes
Do you like all the mistakes
I don't have time
Now to pull up the post right
Times article
I'm just going to reference the one that I have
Front of me he doesn't repeatedly
The Times article
He's sort of spinning his wheels
Percent chance that this is a real terrorist attack
Said that it was a real
Then we
Hundred percent
I'm not going to do I don't know the number exactly
Nuisance
They didn't not guilty
No
Next
Some questions cuz he didn't say like we got the truth
When we plugged
Infowars
We plugged you should have seen them so scared when we plug
They were so guilty
It's
This is all
Just PR
That's that
Understand
But it's not a greater truth
Is out it's more eyes are on me
Beloved
So unfortunately he doesn't have a big
Staff at this point
Epson one of the other employees Wiki
Remember who it is
I wonder what that f****** thing is
Fewer employees
Fairly well
As opposed to not being able to play any of his clothes
I think he's running also
But you still doing it as a radio amp
Million-dollar
I think a lot of people
Alex
Like
Pretty confident you haven't
He's
Unfortunately because of the spin. Staff
California
Eric dykes
Melissa Melton
Just left
Just start their own
Offshoot
Operation
Paul Joseph Watson
Tired as hell
Play a special report of hers
Yeah it's really weird
Probably a number people to work it enforced go through
I think in the early
They're doing something real
30 plays that report is like
Damn that didn't feel like Infowars
The finger at Obama in a context that is
Sharks are bad
It seemed to be largely about
You're saying that we Precision Target at
What is going on here
That's wild
Eclipse
Demonstrate
It's very strange because
The day before on the 8th
She was the one who came up with the different color fact
Brilliant
Special Report
Different colored backpacks
We got a beat out the whole journalistic Integrity after overtime
There's no standards
Whatever
He doesn't have
To cut
Clips
But he's seen in the news
Is the beginning
Of the narrative
Eclipse coming up
Chris Matthews
Photos of baby seals
George Noory
Am Coast-to-Coast episode
I don't I don't know I don't care
Is normal
They were going to blame this white
Option
You saying all along
This is a
Fundamental change
It is narrative
Because that dude
Is not a military
Is route
Pictures that are necessarily
Well you know what the
Mistake was
So they only said Navy Seals
In order for the Navy Seals
State five times
Whatever is going on is a fundamental shift
On does a lot of the
Baby seals
2 take away
I need to get the military in line
Call whatever
Sure
Listening to the show is like how
Disjoint
The problem for the earlier days
Certainly
Different narrative
Being sold
His narrative
Amorphous
Is blob that is
Just like cert
Parts just expand
Come back in and then another party
Expands images
Rolling around in roustabout little holes
It's like that shows that Stephen Colbert
People with no bone
Bonobos
Stop playing to setup
The Marine
He's also decided that the people that
Blippi talks about how they should reach out to craft International
He claims that they already tried to call them he's discussing this makes me think he has not
Minecraft
Officially
Doing all this work right now
Can you say again
Haven't called
Before they were just giving him a nice call
See if they want to go
Officially say we are
Is every would like
It doesn't seem like they've called
Get to the phone to call craft but they didn't even make it all the way to the phone you could say that
Tried
Formality to life
Return call
Alex
Express
It doesn't feel real
Alex
A comment
And as we learned from the last time you tried to do this. Raise its really fast
He tries to read
By saying I really agree with it
Ghana
Weird
Weird, I got weird
Weird the case with pretty much all,
I don't agree with that
Write off
The combat
Find his comments anymore they're all gone
Everyone
Ethiopia
No it we we don't know
Big B
You can be you can hear that and hear him say I don't agree with that
Indicative of being like they're going to be
He's disagreeing with the fundamentalist some
And this is part of the pivoting of the narrative
Because
We need your help
You need more staff
The thing about this is planning to blame the fields or at least they talked about
What do you base
Baton
Conversations with anyone
Of course
He's trying to say that he's
Conversation
Because I didn't hear them
Which means
Obviously
If you reverse engineer it
Six months ago they said if we were going to
What age is
Brilliance
And I think it's probably accidental
But what is brilliant
Is putting it on his
Audience
Put those clips together
Instead of
Having to do it himself
If you don't get it
And if you do
Play those clips in that sewer working on it
We can permanently be like the audience
Kansas putting it together whenever
It's now they're playing
Just put the pieces together and we are moving forward
Call
That is so horrible
Which is setting it right now
So physically sick
What's your name
What's her name
Expert
Erin Burnett
I will say that I can neither confirm nor do
Deny that Erin Burnett
Listening to right now
The night before
It seems very unlikely to be discussing the possibility
After the photos
And they're clearly both pretty young
That's the type of
That you would do on info
I guess it's
Impossible
Maybe I'll press conference
I don't know if
What's a sarong
Anyways
And
AR
Wild
The first guy that you talk to you want to talk about the white packs
And pictures
Poor looking guy
Actually matches his straps that he's got over his arms
Right right
If you actually had a bag that you brought with you
Terraria
Thought experiment
The marathon
Do you think for a single second that Alex
Take a second look at a picture of a man carrying backpack
Do you think that rises
Level of Suspicion
Man I'm really trying to find a funny way to say yes but it really doesn't it is nothing
There's nothing realize that the graphics one
Split-second into consideration and doesn't tell you anything about what happened
If there hadn't been a bombing you just see that
Any number of innocuous explanation would make sense
Maybe
Friends also
You prepare to take something out of your backpack
Maybe he just seen that Lionel was trying to
Stop the video.
Taking off his back
There's literally nothing suspicious about a person caring
Down by the police
Could we imagine Alex in this alternative reality
These two guys are talking about the single
When is it didn't happen they do most certainly be opposed to it
Books
Weird
And you're going to search him
It doesn't make any sense
These people are still
Sprite very very
There's more
These guys apparently Maybe
Community College entry-level psychology
About psychology
Because they decide to psychoanalyze the guy
I would rather than
Body language
Exactly
Not good I don't know he looks ashamed
Your honor I was not ashamed at the time and this is
Harshly earned by Sia
Said that I looked at
I think the larger picture of what they're doing with this guy is death
Currently not appropriate
At least a third of a judge
My call like I think one look
Ashamed
What
Dick is
Wild
Okay babe
Another
It comes up with calls
Is a new piece of
The narrative
The Marines were going to
Not blaming
If you just think that there's a hundred different Patxi's there
Mint Marine
He was there in case they wanted to go with the redneck
Purpose in case they wanted
Crazy the Old Country Buffet of Patsy
Yeah
Prioritizing
The Marine
He is under lockdown
They're on the shelter in place order
There's a new there's a new wrinkle that's going to start development
TV Guide
Theron pictures everywhere
They're saying that just in case
Can make a difference actually speaks out
A look at all these Navy Seals everywhere
That's another way for me no mainstream media to cover their butt
Yeah
Beginning of a colonel
What's going on with these
Cease right now
Appreciate that
A certain kind of stupid first
Can have a conversation that I would have high sober
Baha'i
Is under martial law
It's not
There haven't been so many passes
All imaginary
Throughout their how many people died in the internet decided to blame for this
Which makes you think
We shouldn't have a bunch of
Don't like all this stuff again
Roads on earlier
Vigilante
Justice
I got
Complete without
From gunownersofamerica on
Support himself
Perspective
Martial law
Surprise
Boo
Good good stuff Larry
It's
That's broke
We assumed that it was going to be
They were going to plant
So they could
Steeler
But what
Oh my glob
Cuz they just do that
F*** are you talking about
Friday episode
No that's awful and it sucks
To hear it sucks that people act that way
You go back to 2013
These are the same ideas
That has been underlined
Gaston the people in Alex is orbit
Totally totally totally practice
Coming on here
We should have a Muslim just blow stuff up
We shouldn't have a war with them
They just
Weather schedule
It's a very
Locked up
Position
The ability to episode
Begone
Euro
Exile we're going to
Wants to build up more this idea that the Marines and the Navy Seals were there
People who work
You know what
I was looking at those pictures
They looks
Apprised
Maybe it's a former military
What is that
It's shifting everything is change
This is where it really comes
Together
Alex gets a call
From a guy who thinks
The shelter in place
Request
It's very weird
Unusual
And we need an explanation for Wyatt
Actually have
No no no no
That's what they want you to say
Globalist
The city of Boston effectively shut down all the transit
Everything
Something is in place
Yeah
This is
Thrown out
Suggestion
Whistleblower
Bald eagles
No you're right
Around killing all these people
That could blow the whistle
Vigilant
Now when I heard that
Crazy
First of all
Suggesting
We'll see how it goes for the rest of the show
Becky has come back
It does
Weird movies
Oh my God it's
It's introduced in the context of being
As we go through
Through this episode you'll see it become more like
Bad idea
But he hasn't
To give a shout out
Dan badonde
And Alex reveal something
Look good for him
Release the Kraken
The fact that is not funny at all
The movie clash of
It's a common catchphrase that people use
It is always
The context of sending it
And an offense
It's a weapon
Is twofold
The first thing is actually pretty in Port
Baby covers
In his deposition about a Sandy Hook
Official
But this clip really seems to suggest that he is an instrument
They have a Target and they sent him out to do what he does
The second thing this reveals is it Alex
It's tantamount to releasing a destructive weapon
Going out to ask question
He's a mythical Beast who's completely uncontrollable
Is letting loose on people
Namely the citizens of Boston
Hook
He's not fake laughing bear
He has his collar about calling
The Kraken
He loves that he can throw a grenade at these people explode from a safe distance
This illustrates a cruel and sadistic streak
Can Alex give a s*** about the
UNIF
Alex
But not somebody who he really
Capacity
I really hate that bhadoti and I hope
Really ashamed
I'm sorry for what he's done
But you trying to can't help but feel a little bit bad for him
Hughley using
I don't feel that bad though
I've lost
Alex come on
Candy when they're not enabling you there
All of this is awful and then
Somebody else
I'm just like
Betty's
You know it's like these people just do
The game
Play Choice it's not like some kind of ingrained
Behavior that they've learned
Absolutely
To it it's tough to feel
That bad
But at the same time you know you got to still stay in touch with your human insta
And someone being used
Is not good
So
I would I choose to do in a case like this
Instinctually
I feel a little bit of
The pity for Danica.
Because he's
Queenly willingly
An awful way towards vulnerable breathing people
I choose to transmute PD into disgust towards Alex
I hate batondy bad for him
Haggar
Realign
Call from a guy inbox
And Alex wants to know if he thinks
False flag
As a Bostonian what's your got on this
Probably not
But I'm going to be
Obviously
Part of the plan, but I'm going to Badger you
I'm not sure if it goes that far but he is going to Badger the people who disagree
Not fun
Next clip
Just talking about the
Amex
Crucial mistake
And how we discuss
Happy family
Interested
So here's another weirdo
His main complaints
Scale
Jordan that's a huge problem
Regardless
Any sense
Naturally raises the question of what size area is
Too large for the police
Alex says here that he thinks it's okay on one block presumably because the police would have narrowed down their swords
Good reason
Suspect that the suspect is in
What's the substitute of differin
Used to justify and the other not
I will I will give you a very clear
The suburbs
And we're not going to worry too much about the
Inner-city black
If you know what I mean
Actually introduced another issue is it different
Rocks will be different
Your
Arbitrary
The definition
This being okay
Miners are with just made
Like what type of block are we dealing with
And they've split up
Can you send brought in the area
If one suspect being traced justifies one block
Being locked out
Police telling people not blocked stay indoors
The two suspects justifies an additional lockdown right
It has to be one terrorist per block
Okay
Set off bombs
What if you're not sure if they're working with
Qualifies them to be considered
Linda Bostic
Extreme Measures
My point is made of form of martial law
And from that point
Completely lost
Any kind of grounding
Can stand on
If you were against the police acted this way under any
I could disagree with him and say that I believe that there are occasions where the public could possibly do things that are uncomfortable to
Themselves
Personally
But I couldn't say like Aur
Made a mistake
What's Alex
You completely
Now he needs to answer so many questions
Absolutely can't answer
What's the diff
That's a pretty big fart
Like listening to him I often find things he says that are lies things that are stupid
But it's rare to find such an unforced error like that
No one's asking him to like
Make his message less extreme
Or like the moderate
No one
For whatever reason he's just decided to moderate this anti-police a lot
Downstairs
You just made his job way harder
He's accidentally supported martial law
It's almost like
By accident to be
Reasonable about this
Lesbian light
Sing like
For no reason he goes off brand
Write the whole point is because unreasonable and is stonewalling in his absolutist is possible
You if you
Text one moment of
Reasonability
It's magical does a couple times
Understand
I don't think he understands what
He believes or what
You should be saying
If he believed the things he believed
I think it's just a glaring indication that
He's making it up as he goes along at all based on feelings
And whatever
Banks in the mall
Like
Actually getting down
Who he cares about
Living or dying
At that point
Like sooner or later he's going
You know everybody has a heart
There you go you
You are arbitrarily created
I think that the arbitrary aspect is very
Okay it looks like six blocks isn't
I would love I would be fine with
You're welcome to make that argument
See him making
That argument
If one is okay and the other isn't
Because otherwise
It is arbitrary
The basic idea behind that argument is
More comfortable understanding that these people have
Target that it's not just a wide sweep and that they are
Narrowing it down in a very specific way
And by having it only be a block
I feel far safer
Exactly
You got it
Crowdsourcing
Erin Burnett
From the night before
I've heard them say it's probably
Whoops
Why would you do this
I don't know
Transcript
And what he experienced
What's
Absolutely that is really good inside information
That's really bad
Even weirder is that he
Specific
Goody said Erin Burnett the night before interview too easy to trace down that it doesn't say where you're at
Leg with a lot of his specific references
He can be like that's not what I was talking about
I think that might be
Goodbye
You get the call from a guy
About this
Alex
You'll see how it goes
Wisconsin
I expected to get cut off or is my house drone strike before I even get on there
Okay you don't want your kids to die right
I got kids to I don't want him to die
On Facebook you want to know about the guy with the hat or the hair
Guy with the hair
Blue shirt
Backpack
Two hands
Okay
Facebook Sean
Small to go hide behind the Red Cross
That's why
Give me your money
What specifically what you're talkin about
Alex knows well enough
Knights of Malta
Hiding behind a Red Cross
George Bush
That was
Spectrum
About right
Protect
You know like he needs to make sure that that
Appearances
Lest other listeners think like
People who have
Processing problem
But the thing is
You and your staff
Put a cog in the wheel
And you presented them online
It made them delay
The news brief
It delayed the conferences
And they had to change your story because of you and your new staff
There's no
Alex has sex
This is all just Alex's imagination being reflected
You're only saying that he's stopped
Or the puzzle Alex
It is enough
Is fun
Alright I believe
Man also wants to compliment
Other caller said that he has a stack of Steel
I think it's a meme that's going around
And I got to tell you
Without a doubt
Before and after
PR all of it is about the publicity
Baby from the stunts
You sent out their causes
Y'all infowars.com
Same thing he ends up doing in the 20s
16 election
Is this his arm out
What is what he does
When does serious issues going on but other people are trying to deal with
He's trying to get a 10
So
Cool good job
Another caller and here's where it goes from Vista
Suggestion
Cleaning up at
Seriously suggest
Martial law
Now
Obviously
So now that is the line
The whole situation in Boston that's going on is just
Streets whenever
And there's a big problem with
The first dated
If you go and look at pictures of Boston
From the 19th
It's
Weird
Because
Streets are fairly empty
But if you go and look at those pictures
Almost everyone has a few
You'll be able to see a few people
Because the shelter
Place request
Weather request
It wasn't it wasn't like you have to
Estate of your home
If you wanted to go out and
In about
And enjoy
I don't know Longfellow Park
And I just like
Take a risk
It was multiple Dunkin Donuts
Places we're still open
The Dunkin Donuts to the goddamn
The Google Street View car
That was that was a real weird that's for that track a lot of miles
No cars on the road
But there were people out and about it's not like it's it's
It's not like it was
Strictly enforced
Stay in your homes or we'll shoot you
That's nonsense
What we talked about earlier
The warning that there's an act
Active shooting going
Those controlled explosion thing that I was talking about has to do with the police find what they believed to be another device
In a home that they were searching
Where the Tsarnaev Brothers had
State
Also the media wasn't threatened or anything like that
You can find her the police
Like there's a place called Hutton
Photography
If you just Google the Boston Marathon week
They have tons of pictures
Of the police
So there is no there's no
This is a 0
Anyway
I mostly just played that clipped illustrate
Did they're just trying to clean up happy
Narrative
Broken record
Everything in this coverage
Is stuff Alex's imagine
It's none of it is real
Really that that caller
And Alex both
This is a
Cleanser
Or whatever
Saying it's just
I can't
Really comprehend
Like that
That is just
It's not
Real man
We cracked
Code energy
Like I don't
I can actually explain a little bit of that
But I don't fully
The feeling that people are having
Alex's
Instilling
I think there's a funk
But before we do Alex
You should be talking about MIT police officer with the night before
Any of this stuff could be discussed
Instead
It's like there's another there cleaning up
Troll in there
Acevedo police of Austin
Gun confiscation
I choose you on Twitter to show me guns
This is absolutely ridiculous and
Jocular
It really makes it seem like all of the things he
He's talking about her jokes
My gun
Nrsv
Look
You talkin about
It just ate
It's so deflated
To Alex's
I've just
Goddamn you very well
Set the answer Alex
Was really going to give you from the beginning
It doesn't matter
Doesn't matter if you say yes
Or no
I'm going to say you did whatever I want to do whatever I need to do
Soy
Because
Started trying to get him to fight
Brodnicki
Pretend coming together
Like he did with the sneaky snake with Joe Rogan does this all the time
So he did that with her
I understand
That's far funnier than
I understand confrontational strategy
You coming by
If you understand that
His family did flee Cuba to the United States
Like telling him to go back
The Cuba
Or even just like
It is a country
To say that part of the motivation behind that is
Believing
You don't belong
I don't think it's a hundred percent that but there's two
Pictures of it that make me on
The way that he's bullying people is
Involving the police response
We think it's 41 guy we don't have all the information
I'm sure they have good reason
We don't know really what the situation
We can't be together
This interview is completely fine
It's mostly Alex trying to bring up his gun talking points
Bernard being like
I think the background checks are very reasonable thing for citizens to submit to
It's not a huge deal there will not be any comps
Application
I would never go along with that
I've not heard anybody suggest that seriously
And anyway
It's just pointless
Absolutely
With you caliber Barrett
No you can't just pull out a gun
Find
Define
It's not loaded
Alex
Get in trouble for going shooting
I know you're good
I'm not worried about
It's just nonsense
Goddamn
Really nice guy
Since you weird
Needling
Make him angry
Exhausted by your
Do you understand
But he's clearly at least aware of like
He's full of s***
Pictures of Becky
The f****** car
Putting it
Subway
But not
It's not worth
What happened
Which is weird
Alex is back
Is gone and Alex's
Killing the Patxi's
Narrative
Is the most probable
Scenario
Illogical Behavior I've seen from
Spot-on
Toyota Colorado Springs
Imaginary razor that is exactly what month
Narrative
Completely shifting over the course of this day you're on the 19th
Are the Navy Seals
Military men
The entire lockdown is
To sweep Appaloosa and
Then kill these
It's just developed over the course of the show as opposed
To talk about anything real
Because
Alex knows the stakes are too high
It's a f******
Shout
So we're now into the fourth hour
Of the show
What's interesting about this
Overdrive
And I'm still taking calls
Listening to the police scanner and watching the
How's things going
Police officer shot
As far as I know this is the first mention of that
In the fourth hour of the show caller brings up the cops
Alex reference
And I missed it
Maybe that's possible
But from my listening to this that was the first time I heard
Which is
Crazy
Yeah
Cuz why not
So yes but dandi call and it's all just stupid about how
I've done stuff like he's doing now.
President
And most
Visitors
A minute for hours
Infowars.com
100,000 visitors
All roads lead back
To publicity
All roads lead back to his bottom
What's the saying is not
Something
That is actually
Actively important
What is John is pull off a bigger than any I've been able to do in my career
2 million downloads thanks everybody we couldn't have done this without your help
But instead of that second part they said download
Because we lied about 9/11
Fryst
So instead of dealing with the real issues going on in the city of Austin
Surrounding
This bombing
Alex
Decides to spend a good amount of this fourth hour
Complaining about Bill O'Reilly talking about
Bill O'Reilly talks about Alex
Play this video from
The Family Guy
Wright Bella was like
No build is not like
Against what Alex is doing
I don't believe that
Baby
Furious
This is important
Call Shawn Christian
Boston Marathon
It never happened
Blurb
Very
Big piece of Alex's obsession
Many many times
Pretty sure
He plays the clip of Bill O'Reilly
Bill is right
Boston Marathon
How do you do it
The people didn't see that clip on
Because it's additive
Cuz it's doctor
Is not
Engaging with critics
The part of this
People take issue with
Is taking the part of the body
To the part about the marathon
Is a distortion of what this episode
When Alex says he blows up the marathon blows up
Not true
The blowing up with other stuff
He's on the right side of this one
Nitpicking
Being like
How do they do this
How to edit videos
Confused
We know that he loves to do it live
I don't
Don't understand why
Video and splice it together
Alex is really serious about this
Bill O'Reilly
But before he does
He gets to this
Is Central
Do a lot of his ID
He's trying to explain
Conspiracy going on
Could literally come from any month
Of any gear vouchers show
It's a constant refrain that uses
Convinces audio
Except outlandish conclusions
This bombing was a big set up by the government
What are the reasons that line he's selling it
Except for people is because of
Most of Alex's conspiracies are presented as being really simple
What is staggering amount of protest
The question does seem to ask itself
Why would these people all agree to something
Whatever else needs to justify something he's running out of options
Is default
To say that the globalists know that they've committed crimes
And whatever conspiracy he's selling that days they're only
Themselves out of prison
We seen it over and over and over
In the present-day this is explanation
The Deep state
They're all going to prison
Explains how wide
Conspiracy would have to be
This narrative crotch also serves a second
Which is to make every single
Conspiracy that Alex
A matter of immediate life
If a global its needs
Pull this off
In order to make sure they don't go to prison for
Just bring the truth out on this one
They might just
Globalist want
Brawl
Every half-cooked
Every fantasy about a picture he finds on Fortune
They're all elevated to nearly absurd important when their frame
And what's so crazy is that it's so consistent in his career
But I really thought some of this stuff that you could we hear this a lot
Increasing desperation
Canada Post 26
Here it is and Rozier times
The 2013
You just constantly f******
Like this is our shot
Every single time
And they fall for it
Does
Cheerleader
His imaginary world
Like
Unaffected
Buy reality
But it absorbed
You know like what's going on in the real world
His imaginary version
Informant bubble reality
Space
Information
From reality
The main thrust of the imaginary
Universe will always stay can
Call Alex wouldn't say cleanup Patxi's if there wasn't shelter-in-place request
Right
The bad guys would always be
Be willing to go clean
People up
No matter what
And that's what I was referencing earlier when you said
Why are these people feel so intensely
In
Yeah I'm part of the reason is because Alex is selling it in such a way that they're like to believe
We can just pull this off
If we can pull this all night finally be rid of those global
Little B it's game over
Like I said
Play to fight
O'Reilly
Jesus
I don't like turtles
Like being the Survivor of child
Especially on the same
Episode where some
Offer to fight was on earlier
Patterns
We need to talk
Engine from somebody who he believes will be able to help
As we get towards the end of this episode
To David
To do a couple more hours
Sure you keep that
But
He starts to realize it
Dangerous Game
His life is in danger
He wants everyone to know
Let's
If he died
Keep the fire
Yikes
That's a weird and
Is that the end of the show it's supposed to be
After that break
What are those
Nashville Mental Health
E-bikes
Interesting
Comet
Cartwheels
And probably go on vacation 408
Around
Because I really want to believe
Start cartwheels Alex
He's going to apologize
Alright
You know his
Argument
Just prove it
He is saying if it proved it's not
So I guess you would never accept whatever evidence
Because whatever evidence you have is only ever
That it is more up
Just move the goalposts
You sort of responding
To a little bit of
Insecurities that he didn't
Cover the shooting from
The night before
Articulate
Address
Alex
I need money
Why didn't
She talked about it earlier
That's a good question
Question it's like yes absolutely
There's no reason why you needed to cover that at 3 in the morning or earlier than
It doesn't explain why it's
Almost not addressed
At all
On this episode
Is that I can only talk about what is happening in this area
It is impossible for me to talk about the past or the future very serious disease
I don't know what the
The f*** is going on
I know that I suggested at the beginning of this episode
It feels like he knows that it's too hot
He's being
Daytona get a lot of P
I think there is a Feeling.
I don't know
Maybe he just didn't want to cover it
I mean it really does
Seem like he could also
Attention span
I don't know I don't know
He's just like I I don't feel
It's no worries
It's no fun doing
The Second Amendment
Now they're killing
Hundreds of Patsy's
Maybe hundred we don't know exact number
Play story
Two loads
This b*******
Very
There is a there is a shift
The only real difference
Between
What happened on the 8th
What happened on the 19th
Up until the end of Alex's show on the 8th
The FBI hadn't released the suspect's photos
Abstract
Concrete information
And on the 19th
An official story
Unfolding situation
Actions being taken
That's the only difference that I see in between the two and Alex's behavior is
Completely
Now granted he's still lying and making up a narrative
Born looking
Your disease already established
The cleaning up
People
It's just different
I don't know I don't know exactly how to put my finger on it
Like
It's like you
Play
With a specific actor in mind
The run for a good year and then
Keeps going but the
Can be the same play you're putting different characters
Do a play written for
They're coming for our guns
Play
And your throne in Navy
Seals and it's just not the
Second time
Express what
Cop out
Images of see how this develops
Slightly
This feels much more like normal hours
I think the fever has broken
As for the city of Boston
Tonight
In the evening
Finding Zohar
I mean I know that Alex will probably just return
Kind of more normal
Conspiracy bulshit
Real f*****-up
This stretches
Weather 5 days
The 19th
It's been awhile
Michelle
You've been so irresponsible
He's done
About is bad
The job is good
You should have a parade
To be so thrilled
You've broken the case wide open
No one is ever
Failed as hard
Well dessert
King they deserve
It's
Literally
Boomers Vista
It is
That I feel right now that you can feel that you can do that stuff
Kizi
You would think any
No
For him to guess like this level is
What is
You expect that from me
Please
Remind me of that I'm always
Behavior is way less becoming
From someone in his
But don't talk about
It's it's like
Like you can really see the intention of crafting narrative it serves his purposes
The behavior and then the goal achieved
Almost
Exactly
Spinning
A yarn
He's post-coitus
We have a website
Twitter app
At go to bed Jordan
If you would like to listen to the show go to iTunes
Review with their do all kinds of fun stuff
Neo
MDX
The juiciest Ice Cube
Holding