I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
MoneyGram
College vype.com
Everybody
Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
What was the last Halloween
Costume you wore unironically
With Aurora
Pure joy you do not like an adult. I like the note it's like I'm just going to The Regular Guy
I don't like that kind of thing I'm talking
You know I dress
Set up as a ninja turtle and
My f****** loved
I probably talked about this in the past but I have a problem with over-committing
Two things like that a guy Halloween costumes always been a problem for me
Because I'll just go too far with it the big time there was sort of like the break
Chicken point for me
Was I went as a monk
1-year okay and I shaved a circle on the top of my head around the side
And I went around with a jug of Carlo Rossi
So your party
And maybe people take drink
Eggs when they did things that were again
The social order
A blessed people who were behaving well and everything
The character super drunk the next morning I woke up with a
Terrible hangover I walked into the bathroom and like oh my
My head
It was
Gatorade and a hat just like that
Just are walking away like happy Halloween you know what's up
Yeah but that was when I was probably I don't know
Early 20
I don't. So I don't really
I don't really get into that too much
Care for the Halloween
Not really a Halloween guy
Any good ones when you were can you trick or treated right you were super pour like growing up my parents
Make our own costumes and we weren't very crafty so I know there was nothing no there's nothing good
The only time I got to eat candy in my entire childhood around Halloween and
Candies good but it's just a sheet
You're wearing you know Alexa
What can you do with cardboard
It could do that much
The memories are good
Sandy was good at Candy's
Except that what those want those Taffy's
Just come in like
Rob Brown
And orange oh yeah it was like a labeled
Piles of garbage
And that
Candy corn sucks
I don't know why there's like a
Vishnu
Effort to rehab the image of candy corn dog on
Over in his grave right
Is he dead
I feel like there's a effort that I'm seeing online
This year more than
Pastors to be like
F*** you I like candy corn candy corn stop making me feel bad for it
Polaroid
Polarisation
I don't like the idea of like if you like
But I don't feel like we need to feel bad for not liking it and
Declaring the objective fact that it stinks
That's my position
I thought that was one thing that was the last thing the America
Can people could real iCarly YouTube or
No that's not no Americas
Record to own the libs
I do appreciate though that it hasn't yet extended to attempting to vainstream
The pumpkin
Yeah I know that would never have
Did accept candy corn in a tiny little thing but not that big
Bulbous
Pumpkin
I don't know too much about dressing up for Halloween anymore
But I do know a lot about Alex Jones
And I don't know anything about either
Is correct and today is actually a spooky Halloween
That's not a fair way though
I want earlier this week where I just felt like I was kind of not interested in
I needed to take a break
And so I was thinking about a great week
It embarked on this Coast
Coast AM
Do a lot of s*** about wacky
Crazy paranormal topics
But that was like okay forever year-round Halloween they do ghosts
To go well
Ghost ghost ghost
I don't blame them
To close
Right but a lot of that is just taken
Calls from people have ghosts
And I don't really want to make fun of that cuz as much as we
You know can focus on George Noory and some of this
Like toxic platforming
But he does I don't want to spend a ton of times being like look at these dumb College
Crystalline
I've liked what I think is probably a
Acceptable for us
Talkingshit about the colors over so I can the other guys talking then yeah we're kind of that song
Is politics
And some of the city stands for
Possible
Maybe not maybe not something I'm going to do but possible
Household are you didn't have to
Search out a collar
Ghost seems like now that's a non-starter
But like
We could do that
I found something
I found a notch
To go into
I'm pretty excited about it
Here is not a contact drop
In the case of the mermen
There's a lot of
People eyewear misunderstanding it in
Oh yeah
Yes
Encyclopedia Brown The Case of the mermaid
Something to go over that I might have something to do with the Birdman but it actually does not
What are you talkin about
Murder man will not Factor heavily into this conversation
But before we get down to business
Talk about what we are here to talk about
Forgot to give a shout out
So first of all Alex
Thank you so much you are now policy walk
Brazil
Next Chris asked thank you so much you're now a policy wonk
Conspiracy
Text Chris B thank you so much you are now apology Wong
Text booty thank you so much
Journal policy wonk
Hell yeah buddy
Clown shoes thank you so much you are now a policy wonk
Thank you
And finally like say thank you to a couple people who signed up on an elevated level
Appreciate that very much
So Cedric
Thank you so much
And James thank you so much you are both wonderful technocrat
I'm a policy wonk
What's the business that heroin
Why you pimp so good
Freakishly large
Thank you so much Cedric
You're out there listening I like this show I like
Do that by going to website
A sports show that's on knowledge right.com what's going on
Real foggy
Today I don't know what it is I'm in a haze
We're about to talk about merman
We are not I can confirm to you that we're not about.
But a couple things real quick before we could go and I apologize and there's been a slight
A little bit of sound issues on our last couple episodes
We are shifting up some of the recording
Technique
Working in a new workflow and there's a
Pancakes along the way
Apologize hopefully this episode sounds up to our
Regular standard
And we're working on it
Appreciate
Patience
And
A special shout-out to
Who sent us that might be Alex's
Intelligent source
Alex slept with a couple of shirts of a band
He found out about called the titty baby oh yeah yeah thank you very much appreciate it I have
Make it one of my gym shirts
Okay
Getting swole
H2d unfortunate
Nobody else
Nice sticker
They put up out here in the studio
So thank you very much is actually appreciate it
So Jordan today
What we're doing
Is we are going over
Episode
Of
Kevin Moore
So Kevin more for those of you who have not kept up with
Tire projects
Camelot Saga
Is a gentleman
And who believes he can Channel
Intelligences
Maybe maybe aliens
Maybe other dimensional beings who knows
He does not have
How to do
He's absolutely doesn't have to do with
Boys because they have confidence in him
He also runs a psychic hotline
Probably I'm not sure
He runs a psychic hotline and he has decided that Kerry Cassidy over Project Camelot
And Mark Richards are running a scam and so he is in the process of putting out a document
Country about how about Richards is a murderer
And he is not hung out with raptor alien
And this is all very delightful
Is furious at him and has decided he's a part of the game Mafia
Mortal enemy
Probably involved with the Illuminati on sublevel to discredit Mark Richards
Right is friends
The space Raptors
And they're trying to help yumanity against the Illuminati it's all very complex
Yeah
Anyway I
I know that we were shifting away from Prague
Hot stuff
But I can't
Not be
Intrigued by this mystery
It's surrounding it
And one of the big things that I find
Mysterious is
Why is Kevin Moore doing this
Good question we talked about it it's supposed to be money it's got to be money but I don't understand why he would get it at
Mentioning himself in such a way as to be like a critical voice
I am within this paranormal community and I'm offended by these charlatans
He's like Kerry Cassidy
They make us look bad and that is what the voice
But I am channeling right now aren't telling me
And you
Break so I feel like
I want to understand a little bit better
This guy right
Trying to think
Take that as
The his motivation that he wants to be
A thorough GateKeeper
Hey I'm a trusted voice
I'm going to say this is
School
So I know
Look around a little bit
He's going to be a Spaceman
You know what
Because it's honestly because my
Rhythms are all complete
We we f***** up
With my YouTube
I got suggested a video that he did about time traveler
Of course you did so
Of course you did I figured he did do some stuff about ghosts
Like channeling dead relatives
Kind of feels
Greeley yeah
Death is not going to be fun
To talk about
Indy grow Time Travelers
Possibly
No
Are any of these f****** time travel is merman
God dammit
No alright bourbon will be mentioned
Empath
So here is the introduction
The Kevin Moorehead
He's talking to a guy who runs a website or it gets the YouTube channel called Apex
And he is on video and he is just almost completely obscured facial
On purpose
Yes
So here is
Kevin zinter.
Hi guys and
Welcome to another Edition
Turn off the cabin motion out
Today Show is
I've got the Creator
Tampa to solving a pack
TV channel
From YouTube
This YouTube.
Channel produces
I interviews that you pretty much find anywhere else
Okay
Interviewing
Whistleblowers
Time travel
Levin interview
They've been known internationally
Play because
Interviews
Made it songs
2 News Channel
Throughout the world
And they contacted me they office run into
To view on Amazon
It's too happy to answer
View them as well
Because I do enjoy what they do
The alarm
I do appreciate that caveat there you got to make up your own mind on this one
If I'm going to be completely clear with you Jordan I like this episode is a little bit bent
Okay
There's really nothing complicated going on nothing to adapt there's no real like a lower to sort out or anyting
The subject at the heart of this episode
Yet
There's no floor
Yeah I have bad news about to start driving
Took the subject at the heart of this episode is this YouTube channel called Apex
The channels run by an anonymous guy who appears on camera wearing a hat
Big sunglasses and headphones with his head mostly behind a big microphone
They mostly post videos by people who claim that their time
I don't want to make people wanting super clear right off the bat
I'm not mad at anyone for engaging in online immersive
I know a lot of people really enjoy the titillation of stuff like that
You know the clearly fake stories presented as truth
And I don't necessarily believe that a lot of people who take in this kind of entertainment
Actually believe the things that they're watching
Just kind of fun
It's not my
But I'm not going to spend a lot of my energy judging someone for liking that kind of entertainment
Another extension of that I'm not go
Don't spend too much of my time card
The person who creates that kind of
Themselves
To the extent this is just a YouTube channel that lets people send them videos where they pretend to
3 time travels
Travelers which they then
Post and make
Money off of
I'm not going to make too big a deal out
I'm not going to get all like I self-righteous about that
Yeah I'm going to go with this one's fun
Tell me that there's some secret racial animus beneath it
I don't know I don't know if that's the case
Okay
There is a difference though because
Between that
Kind of thing
And you know like online immersive
Eviction and a hoax
I'm not quite sure exactly what the difference is but it's something I wanted
Explorer with a corset
This episode
The only reason I'm even doing this episode at all is because like I said I needed a break from Alex
And my YouTube
S***'s f*****
And it accidentally revealed this episode
David Kevin Morris
Time travel guys I got to listen to this
So I did and here we are
It's completely blocked up
These characters in mine
He's got to put out that documentary about and I feel like that will be the
Alright bet I feel like that will be
What is it
Third Act of our projects
High tide
Just my two cents
I don't think he's ever going to a
If he's smart he probably will
Some of those like trailers that he has a
It's clear he is getting interviews of a lot of people like a lot of work.
CC
Anyway apextv started out with your standard-bearer of paranormal clickbait videos
Headlines like
10 haunted dolls caught on
Okay I like it
It wasn't really successful Enterprise
Since there's a lot of competition in the
Videos mark
Then in September 2016 someone sent apextv an email claiming to be a time traveler
From 21
This guy agreed to film himself talking about time
Apextv posted it and over 1.5 million people have watched that video ever set
Really can't be traits crazy I really don't like that
I want to go back to 10 f****** haunted dolls that are real
Yeah
Shirt and then
They claim they got contacted by another time traveler who told them that he
Holborn.
Define
NSYNC had flooded
He tried to fix it
I had to crawl inside the cabinet and as I did so
I discovered
Continue
So I kept on crawling
Further and further into
To the cabinet at the end of the tunnel I saw a light
And when I got there
I realize
I was in the future
Okay John Malkovich situation
I love that
So he caught this guy claimed that he traveled to 2042
Read met be 72 year old version of himself
He proved this with the video he shot with his older self
Sorry
If you watch a video they both seem to be taking this whole thing it's dry
Put their arms around each other smiling like not freaking out at all of that time ripples
Well one of them knew we was going to be there eventually
The other one is fine
Good point I guess you would have to
That explains their blase attitude
Baby I met you a while back so they both shows they have the same
Tattoo on their forearm
But honestly that makes me believe this either
Unless
This dude is supposed to be 40 years older and his tattoo looks
Just as fresh as the one on his younger self also it looks slightly bigger in size and the positioning on the arm does
It look identical but who knows that could just be shoddy camera and
Looks like you just solved the case of the mermaid I didn't mean to
Cuz in reality the video of this guy whose name is
The cotton orchid
It was actually a viral marketing campaign created to promote the pension plan
Sold by the Swedish insurance company AMF
I want
What is it that pension plans are doing better commercials that anything that we've got going on here as I understand
Stand at the advertising campaign was meant to be like you can feel secure about your older self
It all makes perfect sense the moment you described it as an atom like no I got it all.
Stop is a time traveler by
These guys over at the Apex TV
Matter you know that it's all clearly like bulshit 5 million
Everybody everybody wins except I guess
Oh yeah Provident reportable
YouTube viral
To the extent that anyone knows that it was a viral campaign
It might not have had the follow-through that you need to keep / Swedish insurance plans but
Are also in the Swedish
But whatever the case
You got these two incidents
You know you were making these listicles and it's doing whatever traffic if you doing you got one time traveler
1 million
And plus reviews
Swedish insurance commercial presented as time-traveling
2.5 million views in later but that is
Time travel is what you do
So from there the channels just put a tons of videos featuring people who are claiming to be Thai
Many other stories are contradictory but that's okay
Because apextv wants you to decide whether or not these people should be believed
It's the standard paranormal
Outlet line
I'm just passing along the information
You get to choose
Believe it or not
And I think that's where the Victoria pot policy is floppy an idiotic but whatever the world has room for sloppy idiots
As long as they're not actively creating this content then
Tending their just passing it along
It's all just kind of been good fun
What is Ripley's Believe It or Not except for you
Really
It's embarrassing
For Kevin Moore to be interviewing this guy I'm not taking no more critical stance then we will see
By the time that they have their interview
It came out that the person apextv was suggesting was a real time traveler was just an insurance
If Kevin's trying to Rebrand
Himself is the guy who calls out frauds in the
Community like marker
Richards
Is a good place
Work that muscle a little bit real Prime opportunity
I mean
Ears ears
Quickest
And dirtiest way of figuring out
That
The Time Traveler's giving an interview
To you
So
He is not actually a time frame
Very simple talking to Kevin is the time traveler himself okay
I apologize to all the time
Stave time traveler situation
Of course
Yeah so you might ask yourself how did the
This interview,
How did
Kevin
Hooked up with the guy who talks
The time travel
Maya probably at some point during this process
With that thank you for contact
When you did
I really appreciate that
That was a bit out of the table but was the weird thing about that is
I had just been looking at your channel a few days ago
Before that
Yeah I was actually going through the
The people who were a subscribe to my channel sorting by the most popular and you were just only a couple down so I'm just and I went under your Chan
I saw you have a bunch of interviews with people
That I'm really into and I'm really into the subject set the videos that you make
So I thought hey I mean maybe he'd be interested in having me as a guest on the show and it looks like a cool show so
I'm glad to be on
This was the first indication to me that something might be up here
You know I was looking for the people who subscribe to my channel and you were there in the most popular so I thought I
Reach Out
Bananas yeah that kind of gives me a sense of like
This is this seems to be driven by public
Sounds to be like
First indication of like
Crass promotional concern
And that's like minute one of the
The interview
Yeah that was trouble it's almost being presented as like
You know we running
Circle
Quiet
Because he is still saying that I was looking at the most popular of my drivers you got it
That was kind
I mean there's a
Refreshing
He's like yeah but you're putting your nothing's on the table.
What I got for you I don't know what to
Hetalia hobnob with people who know the
F****** secrets of
Subscriber
I like there was a little bit of a troubling
So also traveling Kevin is subscribe
Knowing that this is all like
Cheats for children
I watched a couple of their videos yet
What is this b*******
That's why I'm saying is is kind of pretty that says like it does not take any critical thinking skills to deconstruct what
This is mostly interested in anyway
It deserves to be talked about Siri
The more I find out about Kevin Moore
The more I'm like
F*** are you doing yeah
I have I have a couple theory that
I want of them is just as bad
Underlying Theory
It'll be hard to talk meow
There's a second theory that I have
About like
Why you
Against Kerry
I'm not sure it can't prove it but it
I'm working on it and it's developing we'll get to that probably couple episodes down the lion
Navigation continues
Butts
What are the things that like I said
I'm concerned
Primarily with the fact that Kevin is talking to
Treating it
Seriously
I think one of the things
I think we're going to see
One of the reasons
Why
He's baby
That way this is the kind of weird is interview I've done
Play interviews today right this is the most fun one even though it stresses me out right
Have no question
But it's still kind of car
Yeah I've done a lot of interviews where I don't have many questions
Prepared and
But yeah
I got to say that this interview is not starting off promise
Kevin just outright said that he hasn't prepared for this interview is no question
Who's ready which I find
Troubling
This is where the whole thing becomes really interesting to me cuz like I'm the one hand this apextv is never something I want to cover
It's really just amateurs clickbait bulshit targeted idiot some children naturally which I'm not particularly interests
I feel like it would largely be a waste of time to critique it and
Insane way I don't have time to tell you about how that link for that one superfood that'll save your life is not on the up and
Dude I've got this
Is one weird trick for you that will do I don't even know how many
Right that's not a good use
Frivolous
But Kevin Moore
Journalist
You trying to establish his brand is this gatekeep
Like a trusted voice to guide you through the good and the bad of these
Paranormal weirdo world
He clearly has interesting calling people out who he feels are giving the community a bad name
You'd expect you'd have that more broadly
Avenger singularly applied to carry it Martin
It would make sense
Unless there was something
Personal unless all s***
Is Mark
Actually his real dad
No
Are you sure I can't prove it but no
He's trying to present himself like we talked about like a Tesla
Some sort of a gatekeeper you think you'd apply this prospective more Broad
Opposed
Singular Focus
Like if he wants to get any mileage out of the
The perception that he takes this stuff seriously
People who are out there scamming people
You're making
Serious researchers look bad
He takes on certain responsibilities
Namely that he should be trying
Kingston Pointe
He's starting this episode out framing it is if Apex
Stevie is talking
The time-traveling whistleblowers
Which is meant to lend credibility to their videos
If you done any preparation he could ask about how exactly the
These people ended up promoting of viral insurance at is if it was a time traveler
Whistleblower that would be a good place to
Start
I feel like that's the first question that needs to be answered
Before you can even proceed with the inter
At least
It would be if Kevin were an interviewer who is X
Play interested in upholding certain standards
In the Paranormal world
He's not
So anyway I don't know this is bad
What do you start off at like I don't have any questions for you guy who talks to Time Travelers
How could you not have what you have
So many
I have a car YouTube
I just ate but even better is that he commiserate the long with him he's like yeah I don't have Quest
For interviews all the time to we are both bad in our jobs
It would be what do it like legitimately
Let's say
Out of the blue
I get it
Big Bang message it comes up on my screen right and it's like hey
I talked to Time Travelers
I will allow you to interview me in 10 minutes
I would still have
No there's no amount of immediacy
The interview could come that I wouldn't have some sort of like all right imma gather my past really quick
How do you time travel
Can answer that one all right next
Why do you time travel
He's not talkin to the time traveler but you know you still could ask those questions
You clearly if I still question
Better half
Although on the other hand
And you just told me that a lot of times you don't have any
Any questions
The best insurance
AMF
All right I don't know we'll know in 40 years though
So
The questions that we do get are at the beginning of
This are like
Hey why you hiding behind that microphone
So why are you name is to
To begin with
Oh well I don't want to give out any personal information as of right now cuz
I've been refused A lot of people who
Who've expressed
Concerns for this
Security and I think those
Biot Distributing their messages if they're telling the truth they could
That
Concerned for their security could translate over
Intimate
And in the team here at 8
Text TV Soho
We want to that's that's the reason we chosen to stay Anonymous as of right now
Another possibility is you know you're scamming people right right
That could be why you don't want people
That's another possibility
Another reason could be he works at home.
Deebo
Fired from home
There's a lot of reasons a lot of people use anonymity when they're f****** around online
I don't care I didn't do too much looking
Going into trying to figure out who this person is cuz I'll respect their anonymity to the extent that they are
I don't think there's anything
But I can tell that they're up to that
Elevates past the level of like
I don't know
F****** around internet nonsense
Of course you would
Like in that line of work it's just a good idea to say you have
Have to be anonymous
Just throw it out there just in Subway's whenever you're engaged
Did this sort of like LARP
Or whatever
You have to it's by default you say you need
Need to be anonymous for protection cuz if you don't it almost raises too many questions
You should
We have to be anonymous if you're saying
Mark Richard
No I was off-planet but they're giving you a difference
Store
They know I'm crazy goes fine
Right
So glad we get to a discussion of Apex
Stevie is greatest work
They're they're really there's a Swedish
No that was big
But what really put them on the map
Was this one time travel
They talked to
And it was a younger gentleman
Okay and that ended up getting them a bunch of mainstream
Coverage
Really not quite you know CNN
Still likes
Foreign news outlets
Yeah alright
So recently you got it you was on
Don't talk shows all over the world
In some cases in Australia that was
You was over here in the UK on on the
Magazines and newspapers
Was pretty impressive
Yahoo search
Surprise Daddy
BR the reception of one of those interviews we did with a man named Noah
Who claimed to be a time traveler from the year 2030
And it was actually him that went on a lot of those talk shows and everything I did I did go on a couple but
I'll miss it's amazing the reach
Into the mainstream news that this is God in because
Ironic thing is that the p
People we've interviewed say they've tried to contact the mainstream news and they haven't
I've been receptive.
To them and they haven't taken up their stories
And then buy us taking up their stories and it actually reaches the mainstream news that's a
I'm really surprised me and it really gave me hope
The dirty mainstream news and there
Covering up
Got this is just another attack on the beach
Time travel buddy is a bad year
That is way too
Oh yeah that is only like 10
Embellish a bunch of stuff if you
Is 20/30 I would have gone with it
What year would you choose
I don't know 7582
82 makeup everything
Right so far in the future that like
Like an hour
I just I don't we don't even breathe anymore
Kirby Ross evolve out of breathing because atmosphere will be destroyed then why do you look like
Well because it we also technology to revert ourselves back we could digivolve
Airtight
So one of Apex TV's biggest claim to fame was their work they did with the person
Play Noah who was said to be like you said
Set a time traveler
From the year 2030
Search for mankind
No I've been recruited
Into a time travel program
P5 where is job would be to go back in time to help
Compile a compendium of all history
So Noah travel back to our time
Euro 2017
The time that he showed up in
Would be a mysterious time for the people in 2030
You think they'd be more interested in figuring out what was going on in ancient times of checking out that Jesus characters
Or something like that
You could make a good argument that the 26th
The election may be historically relevant for
Galatians but I would suggest that they will not be wanting for information about it
Been pretty well-documented the things that are happening in the present
But maybe would have
They lost the internet
And games
Just do the one the one don't know if you know this is still out of books
Publix
Things in stone
Sentient
Sure
So anyway Noah came back to our time
But ended up getting fired from his job but this future time travel organization after he got into a bar fight
South America
This trapped no in the present
Today which was his
We had to create a new persona and trying to do the best I could
If you consider for one second
The story that's being told here you have to pause and ask you. Follow up
The first is what kind of secret time travel program is just going to recruit someone who will then know all their secrets
And fire them for something as trivial as getting into a bar fight
Automotive
Throw up
I used to work at a movie theater and one of my co-workers showed up for a shift with a black eye and a big cut bragging about getting into a bar fight tonight
Before and they didn't even take it tell him to take the day off
Seems unlikely that a time travel program book
Consider this termination worthy as an offense
This kind of moral Behavior
Reflect poorly back on the
But even if that's the case why strand the dude who knows all your secrets in the past week
Control it then
Budget any half-decent secret time travel Outfitters going to kill this guy
Very least bring it back to 2030 and lock him up there
Or lock him up here find a guy who
How do you think
Wonder how much time travel detritus
This is left behind by these
So anyway that glittering time carbon if I were the person doing an interview with this guy
Rubio
In the story explanation for
Yeah
So no I had some fun stories
Tell about what life was like in
10-20-30
41 informed the world that m.l.k. Jr Martin Luther King
King Jr his granddaughter Yolanda Renee King
Will become
In that year that's one problem is that Yolanda was born in
So Riker 21 years old 130 when you lower
21 years old to run
What's lower than the minimum age to become president
Understand now right there we go
No explain to buy that point of law will be passed that allows younger people to be
The president
He doesn't seem to understand that this would require a full-on Amendment since the presidential age limit is Article 2
Section 1 of the Constitution
I feel like if we get to the point where two-thirds of
The House and Senate pass an amendment lowering age required to be president
And then three-quarters of the states ratify it
I think the fact that 21 year olds can be president is not the headline
The big story here would have to be the
Massive political realignment
That would have to happen in the next 10 years
Get us to the point where these stuff
PS Washington political class or tried to get youth into the White House
Headlight 2025
What the f*** is going on
Like really from a political science perspective what could bring that about
Like really think about it
One possibility would be that we see a trend of high levels at like we already are
High levels of political engagement
In the you for sure you don't have to
Continue to the point where they be
Become the only political relevant voting Bloc in
As more and more people cannot control the vote they could vote in younger senators and representatives
Boogy event incline to push
About a month
I guess
But this younger voting Bloc wouldn't
Be single-issue voters just based on lowering the age you have to be to run for president
Derby ripple effect
But polling shows that the user pretty overwhelmingly in favor of Subs
Pretty left
Position
Particularly ones related to civil rights issues and climate change
Is a pig
Their Wills to the point where they got that kind of Constitutional Amendment passed
You have to assume their presents
To be felt in so many other places
Like this amendment will be a side note to the bigger news that fossil fuels have been outlawed
Right I mean I feel like it would be a side note to the bigger news that everyone over 40 died
See that's the other category or a plague the dislikes
Illness
The older population
Do you know everyone's got a grow up real fast
F-35 there can be no President Dan something like that is possible in that case
It's not due
So he says that Yolanda king is president
She says that she's elected at the age of 21
There's another problem
And that is a 20-30 is not a presidential election
Of course he's a little wiggling washing about her actually being elected in 2030 but he does say that she's elected at
21 which you would be in 2030 if she was elected in 2028
She would be 90
Being at that point
This makes any sense and is honestly completely disqualify
Anybody who'd
Consider this s*** for a second
Idiot or the running app
Right so this is
This is the sort of
Work that apextv is doing
Clearly
Not good
Otherwise known as the Lord who cares
They're having fun
To the best of our knowledge there having fun
I'm not going to be grumpy Uncle Dan over here being like you internet kid
Play All Around the World
It's clearly part of some corner of the internet that I'm not a part of it I don't fully understand
So I'm not going
Steak
My effort on being like
Shaking my fist
At the same time if you look at it it is still like a guy trying to present him
Himself as
Like where do you know you can't decide whether this is
Real or not but why don't you help people decide a little bit by asking the f****** question
Betty White
You put also Noah predicted that multiple US cities would be completely destroyed by snow storms in February 29th
Which I don't
Think happened
Pretty sure
What year is it now
2019 that's travel that's that's not going well
So he revealed this information in a video where he was holding a piece of paper purporting to
To be a page
My book that lays out our future history
This page is labeled 2019
Re-edit just has six entries on it
Boy this is apocalypse written all over it seems a little minimalist
It's just a crumpled up piece of computer paper that's been slightly distress to look weather
Looks like something a Junior High student would make if they're trying to come up with
With a prop
It's hard for me to really put this in this into words
It's
Accept paper and tea and then baked it for a little bit and I got a little parchment feel it's good stuff
Know what made the rounds on
Talk shows and got a bunch
Felicity which was largely filtered back
Apextv
Sent to you as a
Appearing with his face obscured
Depicts
Dang it and it made the altered his voice
They made it pretty much
If you don't even know the other name to him
Sheriff
In one interview I solve his it was a split screen with the news anchors
Inside
His chest on the other
On his torso he was wearing a wellframe
Apex
Eevee hoodie
So you was wearing their logo it's all free.
This is one of the more low-rent lazy scams I've seen in my time looking
Paranormal
Wellspace grifter world
It's remarkable.
To me to imagine that anyone would look at this s*** and even give it a sec
Quite honestly
It's even more insane because apextv would promote their story that's so
Clearly full of
Basically unless they don't care
Hey did you like this is all just vulture who cares
Get it out the door will get the money
Then on top of that
Bananas
The Kevin Moore would have such
Chabot standards
But he's doing a softball interview with the guy who's promoting this
Clearly full of s*** nonsense
But that's what it exactly what's happening all right so
The guy that we're talk
Yes they Kevin Morris to us
Guy
I'm probably just going to refer to as Apex
Apextv dude
He is obscured
But his voice is not alter
Yeah now Noah is both of Steward and his voice is also yes pixelated over the face
Now
If I'm Apex guy
Why am I not both guys
You have to be both guys
It's definitely not
It's definitely not we'll get to that later okay
But yeah.
I thought about that as well why not
Yeah yeah I mean if you're already Apex
What course you're going to jump into
The time-travel why not
You got nothing to lose Nick you got to be worried about the possibility of
Like raw footage
Someone
Getting her hands on that I don't know
I don't know exactly why you wouldn't do it it seems like you'd have
One less loose string
Yeah well they only thing I was thinking
Is because
More asking
He says
You went on TV all did all these interviews all around the world and then he goes like
No I did
Some
But it was this other guy making me think that more knows that it was all him
Kevin
I should I should start from that operating position always
Fair enough
So in this next clip we get to find out the Apex
Talk to a lot
Eventually we got contacted by this man claiming to be a time traveler from the year
2026 I think knows our first interview
In which we actually sat down with somebody in person
And he told us an amazing story I think he really believed what he was saying
Whether or not he was telling the truth is another story
But it was a really interesting
Really
Nursing interview and I
I think of yours thought so as well to reach
To that was
Incredible
And
Ever since then that like
In my inbox
In the last in the last week I've maybe 20 people claim to be Time Travelers
From various years
So it's it's getting hard to
To interview all these people and be going through each one one by one
It's a
What's a challenge
Right right
If you thought any of them were actual time travelers you make the time
Also 20 is not that many
It's a lot of knock
Vet 20 Time Travelers
Is in a good two or three hours how do you write a time traveler
How what do you do
Sure did it pop up
Yeah but if you're back in time you could make a Facebook page
Sure very easy
Okay
All you needs an email address other information
M20 showing up in 2017 and their Facebook post from 2015 that does
State of Decay 2 problem
See what I'm saying like I was not going to be the case for all of them
We're going to be using aliases
Don't say you got 20 I say in the first 10 minutes you can knock out at least 45
Yeah so now you got 15 and you got a whole day to go through
I bet you could
Maybe no problem
You're under estimating
The workload
Would bring up
I think that you probably imagined just everything
I mean time traveling
Specific for Real where I can prove somebody
Traveler in 10 min
Alright listeners
Pretend to be a time traveler email Jordan
20 if you just wanted to knock it out in 5 minutes
You know that now you can just say none of them are
You probably should
Anyway
We got an indication earlier that there is this the sort of like
Yeah this guy is coming on Kevin show cuz he's one of his more popular
Sky Burger
The sorts of it interest
Silly sort of like motivation
Come up a bit
Well I'll just set minutes
You know I mean
I can beat this out but I mean you'll making some
Some serious money from this chat
As well
And I think the figures are quite right on socialblade cuz the right for my
So evil
I stayed congratulation
I understand we're employing people to transcribe all the videos
I'll putting them in.
Text form so we can put them out on her website
I'm we're making the videos into formats will be acceptable for Instagram Facebook
Already translating the video sound other languages including Korean Espanol
Spanish
Couple other languages IO
Hindi
We've actually got the
Those channels launch
I already sold out of the money is most of the money
Going right back in a peck
Text Steven by-nd
Into
Employ more people to
To spread these people's messages in our goal is just to make an environment in which p
People aren't afraid
To tell their stories
So make a lot of money but are just going back into running the business
There's a lot of deflection errything
Like that
Entire
Theme of like
Where did you know AIDS
Stop saying this is true or not not saying this to make it place where things are comfortable for people to come forward with
Weather
So I guess fine kind of enabling in
Is but it's a really wild
Space weirdo
If you already at the gate their break
Working a lot of rules
Talking Bunny
Yeah it's weird you said like hey I know basic
Typically how much money you're making because of how much money I'm making you congratulations
That is a lot. OK Google
Not good
Very good job
No
I guess I'm the one hand you could look at it as like
We're just talking about it in terms of
The financials but we're really actually talk about underneath is like
How many people have seen the message
But that's even
Anybody
I'm sure that would be kind of the the way that they were trying
It does seem like that money
Promotion
Is much more
The currency that they're they're trafficking
I don't know I just
Is very weird and also just that
Constant refrain
Of
Like I wanted to
Put it back there they're out
Their stories out here I don't know. I don't know if it's true
That is so can
I just weird
Heroically bringing what
Maybe truth to the people and the mainstream media ignores they can't do it right there too afraid
Without me
No I would have never been on television
Fine then again neither would be 20 other guys who were lying
So Kevin gets around to talking about how like
Weird
No Time Travelers talk to
Oh my God
I don't get these people come
Coming to me
Right I've never had
Well maybe one
Maybe Wonka
And it was it was about what the real story of the John
Cheetah story with old about
And it was jumping
So crazy pan out there that actually did almost did sign
That was some truth in
It was a love story mixed in with it as well I don't good over-the-counter
Yeah
Yeah yeah
I'm never really talked about this I went all the way down to London
To interview this lady who would met
This person
Many years is
Kia.
Edit
Destroyer in some ways because she fell in love
But this guy
Random
And the whole
The story is not what we think
It's actually very different
What they at 2
Stories that sound
So I want to come across that one
Why didn't you do anything with it when I was looking at that is like I've never
Seen or read The Time Traveler's Wife
Sounds like it could be the time travelers
You might right if you've never seen it it was her the title
Yeah
John
Peter is the classic
You know that is wrong
I don't want to get too in-depth on it I think we'll probably end up covering it
If we keep going with coasttocoastam
I'm just going to be huge thing and
I don't know I'm just terrible with me he's a guy who claimed to be time traveler
And made a bunch of s***
And then other people have claimed to be the real John
If we talked we talked about him the last time we talked about a little bit
But I just
Do not remember.
It's we haven't gone in-depth on it because it's it's a gigantic
Body of work online
Time travel Theory
There's like
Pretenders there's the original fake
But yeah I found that that
Cuz I don't know what he's actually talking about
I think there's a time traveler
Or did he talked to a lady who got
Conned by someone who said they were Time Travelers actually in Mexico
The fuk you stalking
I know somebody didn't make any money off
Alphabets and somebody definitely lost
That's all I haven't decided not to do anything with it might be an indication of good judge
He could be both
So
I don't think that if our
Listeners email you
And try and make you
I don't think you're going to do a Time
Like I said you'll just ignore all didn't say none of them
I look at the positive approach
That would be your approach
Sure now we get to hear a little bit about Apex
Approach
How do you how can you vent
That's the best the issue is with
Like we've had a few who we go through as soon as
So you see we don't go if we don't go
Straight to do an in-person interview for a software you a couple Skype interviews
We ask them if they have any conclusive
Approved for anyting
And if what they're showing us seems to be holding up we we sometimes do goes far as meeting them in person
What we've done it a variety of time traveled all over the world
Actually had some the best experiences of my life
Example we went to Armenia on several occasions other European countries
Through interviews with
These people
So yeah that's that's a major issue it's like
How how do we know
Yeah end it end
What we're trying to do is
Green environment in which
People aren't afraid to tell
Their story so I think
Almost
The last wedding the better but if someone's obviously
Trying to pull your leg
Like we had we had that many times like we we going with interview with somebody and they're wearing
Ski mask
And they'd
They they seem to be making a joke out of the whole thing he looks like he's five years older something we've had that a couple times
Here's that you know someone's trying to pull your leg
They tell you there are time traveler
REI
So what's the lion-man use the two things that we learned
For that clip
The first is that the answer is how do you let these people at we do
Yes that's the that's the number one thing
I believe you but you don't want to do too much we talked to him a couple times see if they're just yelling at me
That's just not going to be good for the brain
5 years old
Is there
Clearly just mentally ill
Walking to work for us
So we do a couple Skype interviews to make sure that they could coherently say a couple lines
And then we move forward with it
So that's the vetting process
It's just an audition almost
Right which is great
I love the second thing we learn is there making enough money to travel to f****** Europe repeatedly
That's good really not like
So this is work at you are f******
Bumming me out
Happy Halloween
Bonita's
Also
We're broke
And they are flying around and having the best time of their lives
Sam play the critically disc
Them
But they're not irrelevant
They are
Massively popular in the world that we're not apart of
Yes it's still have punching down even if this is
Profoundly stupid stuff
I am
Not Furious more Furious that we are punching up at the
FedEx Express
We don't need no Vedic
Maybe
Visitor to do is better
We're doing it wrong apparently
Some people end up being out of his liar
And we've had some people actually come out as being fake
For example we did an interview with Michael Phillips
Who claims to have been
From I forget what year
But he talked about a third World War end
Kid here she came out a couple weeks ago he posted a video on his channel saying it was all
It was all fake
To see if we would take his
Story and everything
And
I think that
Deb soompi
People might see that as
I don't know but
I think it serves us good in the sense that they can see that we're not part of these people we're not
We're not telling them what
To stay there during the ones coming to us
And I saw in the comments section A lot of people are asking him did apextv pay you because that's that's what everybody's saying online
And
He responded to all the comments
Say no I I was
Just trying to see if I apextv would
Good takeout by story
So
You know that might be
Be the case with many of these people but
If just one person is telling the truth that it proves that
It proves that things are going on that the public doesn't know about behind closed doors
But what if no one's telling the truth
Brabus
Correct
There is one time traveler
Then the whole game is up
You know there's just the whole thing
It's all over
Right now we start from zero year zero if there's one time travel
However
Proven that there is one
Is
It should be easy
It's berries
It kind of a kind of should be
So it turns out Jordan
Michael Phillips
The guy that he's talking about
Let's Phelps he's not the only time traveler who's been promoted by apextv there's come out and said that what they did was fake
So this video that he's doing this interview is taking place in
Remember that guy Noah that we talked about well in July 2019
Video revealing that the person claiming to be Noah the time traveler got all this means
Stream news coverage
Was actually just a guy named Jason who faked the whole thing
Right
In the video put out by Apex
Jason
Claims that he was an egg
Animated kid lonely and bullied who stumbled into Apex
He really
Got into the whole thing
Decided to contact them claiming to be a time traveler
The entire message feels very
Curated though
With lions like quote
Just because I lied it doesn't mean that other people aren't telling the truth
The video feels like it was created in order to address the fact that this story was bulshit
But also maintain the perception that everything else is
Probably isn't
It also feels like it serves a very specific purpose
Namely to put the blame for the lie on Jason
He was socially isolated in a
Insecure so we can
Did this plot
Apextv was just a media outlet for a
Tell is why
And they did everything in their power to
Check is Dory they
Detector test
So what more do you want from these people
This feels
A lot like media relations
Not like an update to the
The story
Another thing that seems weird is that all the Noah videos are still up on the Apex
Channel oh yeah
None of their titles have been changed
Just something like a guy lies to us about time travel
Stillgoode content
And just cuz it's not true doesn't mean it's not good contest and should be at like parentheses
Debunk
The guardian now this is
Apextv debunked yourself they still have titles like quote time traveler from 2030 reveals future
The Philippines
And quote time traveler meets his future
No disclaimers
Jason revealed secrets of 2030 also that video where he meets his future self who apparently is comeback
Back to 2017
Theme from 2070 that's the pets how it goes right
20-17 70 version his comeback 2017
They're going to start a band he was big
Tunnel problems now that we know that it's all a lie
How did that happen
So you have no align completely separate person who decided to
You know the why
Apex TV set up a meeting between the two haha this is supposed to be true
How can this even work with the story
I thought Noah got fired from the time-traveling job and gets stranded in 27
This guy from 2070 would have to be like
60 years older than him
He's clearly not
The keys just
How old
He would be a
From 2030
1227 you wouldn't have the additional 13 years
The knowing
20/30 is no longer in the future
That's the time that he comes back
So that version of himself shouldn't exist
It's just embarrassing showing but you know Apex
Is there still people
Stories
It's not their fault that the stories that they're telling our lies
They fell victim to an elaborate fraud carried out by a socially isolated
15 and a forty-year-old guy who wanted to pretend to be his future self
It could happen to anyone
The salon we all play a go and
We talked about this
It's
Weird
Considering the logistics of how this would end up happening yeah it doesn't seem like it would end up here
Happening except
Bye
A guiding
He is he was at
Absolutely right when he said it's a good idea not to do too much wedding like the same way
It's a good idea not to worry too much about whether or not your story make
Yeah otherwise if you start putting that effort into it then
People are going to recognize
The Craft
Where is if you have no f
People are just going to be
Think you're lying
And some people are going to think you're telling the truth doesn't need
So you know
They're talking about this and like I said Michael Phillips
No he was
True true
Kevin
An interesting question in that is like
Have you ever been talking to one of these people and just be like
I don't know about
No I have not
Is that X in an interview but you
Just think
This is just a load of rubbish or this
I just caught
This isn't
It's something I can't swallow do you know what I mean this is
I can't go down but
This direction but
You know
During the eighth mermaid interview I remember when he
When I asked him if he could
Speak mermaid and he started making those sounds
That was that was on the hardest I've ever try not to laugh during an interview I don't want to be disrespectful
Respectful of this man really believe he was a mermaid
But
Yeah there aren't there are times like that
I mean looking out I do with little shows that way
With people that channel
You could say the same thing for them
Do you know what I mean
Ian so
I mean I never
I'm heading back out to the
The state soon
Finish that document real cool
Butts
Come on we can't be
We can't have both of you commiserating on Alexa
I know some people just lie to your face
Right well I mean it's really interesting cuz here what's going on is Kevin is ask
What's the most laughable thing I've ever seen is a quiet guy pretending to do a mermaid voice
You know that's kind of like whenever I talk to Chandlers put two and two together a soft and they're both they're both
Moving on
Just moving on yeah I know it
Isn't it weird that some
People lie
But oh well
The most liked one
Interpretation you can take of that is the Kevin Moore is saying like
Oh that's very similar to
The b******* that I deal with these ridiculous
The other read
Meaning of it
Could take is Kevin Morris believing that the Chandlers weird voices are sincere and genuine
And that being like what you know maybe that guy was talking about
Yeah
Anyway
They don't talk about it much but he interviewed Geico claims
I believe the
Direct quote
Begin with during the mermaid up
Which is something that I
I don't hear often enough
That was not something I decided to look into for this episode
Leave that one well enough alone
In 10 minutes I can debunk whether or not you're a mermaid
Send me an email through your water
Computer I love the idea that maybe you're going to get a bucket on it
Emails from the
I'm so he also Apex
Stevie have another interview that's
Coming up
This is a context
Conversation where Kevin's trying to ask him about like do any of them have
Technology
I bought some of them say they have
Good good sign
One of them
Has a top
Spinning top
And I did actually go watch this video
It is just a
Any claims
They tied it something to do with like it connects to his brain and endorphins or something
I know that you won't
Your technology but people in the future who look back
Can see this video
They will know that I was a time
Who cares
Okay anyway that's the least of bored
Something about this guy there's another
Indication that I get
Something might be up
Send a couple days where we're going to do the interview with him and he's going to show it to us
That's on Skype
And I'm excited
To see what he has to say
Sound like an Australian man
Who said
You said some Empire never win
Dang I forgot the Empire but he said
One of them Neverwinter
Got overtaken
And they
The Ottoman Empire
He said they never fell
So they've asked
She existed throughout time
What we have here is possibly a slight indication of some bigotry creeping into the
Proceedings
It's entirely possible that this guy who you talkin to his just a weirdo resume historical views and so
Revisionism
But generally when you hear someone in the present-day talking about the Ottoman Empire and how it never really went away you're listening to a rang
Bank islamophobe
The Ottoman Empire is one of the largest historical examples of a widespread Islamic
And it existed until relatively recently
Only being dissolved after World War 1
In modern anti-muslim circles it's not super uncommon your references to the Ottoman Empire is what the Muslims want
Create
I know that I've definitely heard people express the idea that the Empire never fell and is actually still alive today in what they
They were described as expansionist Islam
All this really
Is deserve it serves to reinforce the perception
In the turmoil in the world is
Is easily understandable as a civilization level conflict
Between Christians and Muslims
It could just be with this dude is
Still writing some sort of benign historical fiction
But little things exact
I kind of hinted at possible underbelly
Things that you could accidentally give a platform to when you have literally zero editorial oversight or quality can
Control in what you put out and what you allow these
Supposed Time Travelers.
Could accidentally give a platform somebody who has like
Crypto f*****-up message
Yeah well I mean I imagine that it is
At the very least
We represent
The percentage
Are the ratio of out-and-out bigots
Versus
Non
In the space weirdo Community as
Is it is for the pop
Large baby higher if not higher
Do you know
So I say that puts us at what
The 30% chance
Any one of those space weirdos has some weird racial mean
I don't want to try in like a
I don't want to try and give a specific number cuz I think that's where we getting
The trouble but
But yeah you know there is some segments of the population
Of this population
That
Is your sublimating their regular racism through space
When you have no
Wedding when you have no standards
Of what you put for because you want everybody to be able to
Come forward
You kind of got to expect that some people might
Subconsciously or even consciously
Try to Trojan Horse those sorts
Messages through
And if you're doing no oversight no editorial process
You'll end up just airing
S*** that could
Possibly be
Space white Nash
Easily
So now we get to another
Boxer shift
And we could do a very familiar topic
In paranormal
Talk
And that is of course
The Mandela effect
With the
Swapping these subjects a little bit but the Mandela Rafi
Something that you
Covet on your way
Channel as well
Coronavirus
Dot-dot-dot Madara fight the little people are talking about
Not on YouTube
Explain to us what that is
Yeah the Mandela effect is
Is where
You think something happened in a certain way and it's it's more so where
A mass of
Will think something happened in a certain way for example at the
End of the Star Wars movie Darth Vader says Luke I am your father
It turns out he never said that at all and you can you can look this up on YouTube
I forget what he actually said
But but it wasn't that and there's been a variety of examples within mainstream media
Did you know that Jordan
What freak out
You didn't say Luke I'm your father
Okay
Hello most disappointing freakout ever
So this is one of the lamest examples ever of the Mandela effect but it's one that everybody trots out because although
Almost everybody has seen
Star Wars search your feelings
You know it to be
Be true
I am your father
No
Is that it
No okay people tend to remember the line at the end of Empire Strikes Back is Luke
I am your father but in reality
Quite the line
In the movie Luke's as a Darth Vader you killed my father and later replies know I am
It's really easy to see how this could be quoted as Luke I'm your father to the point
They're people just accept that that's how the line must
Have been
Discussing
Out of context
You're quoting the movie
No I am your father Luke
Have your father he never said Play It Again Sam
Let's move on
That's how it is pretty much all of these things
Music it cited as examples of the Mandela effect
They're all just things that are slightly off for what actual
We happened because what actually happened to slightly offer what your brain would naturally assume
The Berenstain Bears is remembered as barren
Einstein bears
Because Stein is a much more common Suffolk
The last name
Spain is just not as common all the people that are in Stein
Forbearance
And they don't have any
Stains or any
That would make you go like absolutely triggering your mind the demonic
Or whatever the
Associative device or in Reverse if they were barons
16 bears but they had they were covered in stains
Spend you remember this
Very confused
I've looked at a bunch of examples of the Mandela effect
And pretty much all of them are somewhere in between
Completely uninteresting and
Mandela effect shift is good and fun
And honestly if I think it's kind of neat to look at it as like a catalog in a little ways that we
We miss Incorporated
Information Network elective cultural memory
Almost like it's
The databases of times that we veered off
From integrating
Bison formation
Referring
Simplicity
But it becomes really serious bulshit
Seriously
I tried to presented as a paranormal phenomenon
Aldi
Please grifters do
It makes sense why they would
The Mandela effect
Its core is pointing out errors in
Cultural memory
And by definition we're all engaged with cultural memory
Everyone is part of the culture takes some takes on some relation to it
We draw
If we didn't we have a much more difficult time relating to each other without shared reference
Touchstone's
And
Easy ways to make metaphors
Because we're all interacting with this Collective
Did memory pointing out times when it was just slightly off
Is compelling to a large number of people
Almost every single person you'll ever ask about the Berenstein Bears
Will think it's feldstein
Because that's the way our culture ended up room
Remembering the name
Whenever you point out these little quirk
You will get a response
Out of most people
Ranging from that's weird
F****** way man
And it's that response
But you need in order to
Injector Colonel and of doubt in them
That reality Is Not What It Seems
To beat
You can take that visceral experience of learning that Darth Vader doesn't say Luke I am
Your father
And use it to say
You were certain that he said Luke I'm your father
So what else are you certain of that you might be wrong about
In this way the Mandela effect it is a really useful entry point for paranormal grifters
Do use to open their audiences mind
Possibility that other complete horseshit they're trying to sell them might actually
Maybe real even though
That's why it's such a Mainstay of these weirdo grifters count
So I'm not surprised to see both Kevin and Apex
Stevie you're interested
Yeah of course it's almost it's near Universal
And I'm not saying that everybody talks about it is by default
Engaging in some kind of Griff
This is a strange thing
You see it
But the people who are
Kind of really
Those are the people you got to really look out for
It is it is kind of an interesting
Collective neurological
You know it's like that that video where you see all those p
People bouncing the ball around in
Then there's the gorilla going through the
Back through it
And you're like why is it that my brain just
Cut that out
Why do I miss that
And the same thing is
Drew this on a macro scale like
I'm I'm rewriting reality for my
And then whenever you showed me that it's not
I my discomfort
Express
Stop in a weird mood memory aren't things that
Catalog things
Directly in concrete ladies
That is true on an individual level and it
It's true on a cultural level
And that
Most of what explain
I just
Would you look at it on that level whether or not
I do think
Intentionally
Deployed
And weaponized in
In some ways by the
These folks
For sure I do think that it is a
Recruiting
Kind of strata
Did the space
I think
I think it's weaponized
In the same way that
So many games are are optimized
Keep giving you that
Yeah like when you're playing Candy Crush
Like that they have psychologist
Who spent their careers figuring out ways to
Make you spend
$0.20 every time you need to
Press the button
They give you that feedback loop
True of this
Blade
The money they're going to find so many other things to the parallels of
Bike stuff in Alex Jones is
And the right-wing media strategies
Used to like with him
You can get a lot of people to like
Freak out by then like agent of the Federal Reserve is private
Like those sorts of entity called Federal level
Mima type-6 aren't they serve to open you up to the Grandeur and larger
Less
Believable
Right conclusion to they want to walk you
And you can go just
Just a little bit of
Oh I thought I was certain it was spelled
Berenstein
Bears
Well if my memory is wrong about that
What else could it be wrong of
Sure that's one of the things
That I actually I think is good and bad about
It is really
To think about these things that's fun to talk about
The ways in which our memories
To a certain extent
Right
I don't know
That's my field
Even more critical stance if you want to talk about it
Honestly
Yeah you can't talk about it
It's probably parallel Dimensions shifting you're probably
Pull up
Kazaam
So in this next week we talked a little bit more about
Is your Mandela
I think they called the Mandela effect because they heard that Nelson Mandela had died
Previous to when he acts
Previously when he actually did and then a mass of people remembering
He died on a certain day when he didn't
And yes she lived for a while past then
So there's a the end of the interesting thing is that if you go on Google and you go on Google Trends and search Nelson Mandela
You can see it you see a big
Spike
I forget what it was but it was way previous times actual.
I wasn't as big as a
Despite obvious
20 actually died
But the spike was pretty sizable and it makes you wonder why that happened
Wonder why
So I consulted the Google Trends
What you see is a relatively
Wii flat gray
With a giant
Spike in December
Which makes sense since Nelson Mandela died on December 5th 2013
Oh yeah that be
What makes slightly less
Is it there's another Spike
Smaller than the December one but it's still very
June 23rd
Now apextv was saying it was a long time before he died
Sponging things a little bit
There is still another Spike
In cases like this it's important to consider possible explanations
For jumping to conclusion
Thickness
Nelson Mandela died in June and then again in
December
Reply possibly alternate timeline
Google Transit only reflects what people are searching
So if they were searching for Nelson Mandela death
It's entirely possible they were searching for those terms
In order to find out if
He was dead
In 2013
Nelson Mandela was 94 years old
In an early June he was admitted to a hospital in
Pretoria with a recurrence of a chronic lung infections
The doctors initially put his condition
Serious but stable
But after a few weeks
In the hospital he was downgraded to being in critical
Condition
South
Can citizens held vigils outside the hospital and it became a really big deal with the media question
You think of President Obama was going to be able to visit him while he was receiving treatment
The South African press was reporting urgent meetings to quote discuss delicate matters
Which painting interpreted as signs of them preparing for his Eminem
Pass
Outside
December when he actually died
June 2013 was the month when the most speculation about is
Passing was done in
In the Press
Google Trends reflected
Research Drive
For people for his death
Airtime that makes complete sense
Unless you're willfully obtuse and wanama sleep
Yeah yeah
He was admitted to a hospital with a serious condition in June 2013
Other spike is and then he died
Fairly recently after that
Use for it and then
Unlike
And then it just pasta
To die down because
Still alive
So that big pushes everybody
Getting all he's gonna die soon
Right hand people writing articles about the possibility little passenger
His legacy there's a lot of media attention on it when
Heroic figure is 9
94 years old it is hospitalized in serious but stable condition you've got to recognize that serious but stable at 9
84 is back
That's too bad
Serious but stable
We're hoping for 94 and a half you could make it to like
Serious but stable at 94 is
Not
It's not a good product
You're still you still could die at any point
So people searching for you know Nelson Mandela death
Makes total sense
Trying to use that as some kind of a
A piece of information that helps
The Mandela effect look real
Is just ludicrous
Yeah that's responsible
He said that it was called the Mandela effect
People thought he died
I got that
Never understood
This was why
Not good because I sat from my memory
I don't remember this is
Exactly right
But it's my son
The people thought that he died while he was
Oh it wouldn't have been a couple month
Really
President of South Africa after he was in prison
None of it makes sense realized
Nevermind
When I last looked into it
It was my
Feeling
That people were theorizing
Figured I'd
Years
Oh okay this
This couple months
Before on the Google Trends
That's not even in line with
The furies
That's wild
I don't I don't know
Could be that there was some dissident leader that died in prison don't go around that and then
I don't I don't care to
Bully try and figure out what these people are miserable
Mandela was dead
Delta do I apply for
Universal negative
So at this point Kevin
I think he's doing a terrible
And
Rightfully
He starts to get a little bit self-conscious
The people will think this
This is a softball interview
S*** at it to my friends if they were watching this would be like being so soft in this interview is like
Is old
Cabinet also really difficult questions
You know
But the thing is
Well
It's not my pot phone to do that
Do you know what I mean I'm what
No I mean
This is what you doing and end
Whichever way this works out in the future is a fun interview right now
Now
What do I totally believe it
No
But then again I've come across so crazy
You stuff so I can't say no totally yet you know what I mean
I've had a UFO exist
I can't prove that too
Anybody give me to
So this is just
Sloppy
This dude is a f******
Psychopath
That is the crazy s***
You know it's not my
What channel to do
No it's your channel it's yours
I do it when you translate that to I don't feel like being critical right now it didn't work
And like you have a YouTube channel Where You Are
Have demonstrated the capability of getting Millions
Maybe
That's it son of your days
You're not
Maybe you're not
Averaging A million hits or whatever
I mean if you go to their Channel they still have over a million
Stripers
Recognizes
That very is a
The possibility of
I'm kind of advancement
For his game
That goes away if he starts being hyper
Critical to him
Channeling
Somebody who was
Traveler right
Hold on
Yeah it turns out as the mermaid
Channel to do whatever he wishes to do today
To do with it is not
Critical it's not it's not take any position then
What the f*** are you talking about
This video is it for children
Scampy's off kids yes
It does feel like the type of interview
Be aware those two dudes
Are like
Whereabouts
You're making money I'm making
Weirdo
You stealing people's money
Yeah you run a psychic hotline does not it's not help
You know you don't help disabuse yourself of that perception
I am
And I know Facebook is a
Is a growing market for content
Creators
Free sample I posted a video on there are either our first interview with no I posted on there
With no
Nope
Promotive in whatsoever that video somehow got six million views
Within like the first week just on just on Facebook
So I've been working a lot trying to
I'll transcribe videos cuz of the vast majority of people watch Facebook videos watch them without sound
So you're the one captions on it and everything
But yeah I remember Noah mention
YouTube will exist
He's from the year 2030
But I never I've never asked anybody
From farther into
Future if if YouTube's will still exist
Yes it is it's amazing isn't it
The Facebook just whooped
What they doing
Experiment
Yeah yeah
Yeah
But you almost see this
This way to monitor riser
I think there is four
Some yeah
I don't know how that works.
Saying amount
Followers or likes on your Facebook page be able to monetize hidden day and they only to certain people
But
Yeah that's how and YouTube and yeah that's that's the main attraction to YouTube and
Mostly like YouTube way more than Facebook
Obviously way better platform overall
Having a little bit of a business meeting about
Bananas
It's crazy
You can't do this do this
I don't even know what this is it's showing the cards a little
Ridiculous
Oh you do put that on Facebook
That's what's that
It does seem like a really good way
Drive traffic to spiritualist
Fortune tellers in the night
Twenties in a goddamn feeder telling everybody exactly
How they f****** lie to him
I mean without the admitting were lying
People watch them on mute cuz they autoscroll by then we got to have got to have subtitles on their good
It's weird when you have like an hour to talk to a guy who knows Time Travelers
It's significant amount of the time is spent like talking shop
Just being a YouTube video make
I mean
I'm not going to blow this out of proportion
Is really true
If there was a real time traveler the world would f****** X
Explode
It is over
Right it seems like it's a better use of time to
To discuss that
Stop
Over
How to
No use social media
It kind of feels
Like that is a toy
Tacit admission that what this guy does is Buzz
As opposed to
Yeah so I know this guy who
The collapse of five dementia
Single-spaced
How do I monitor
What's this song
And again
That's fine
For him
Do you know if that's what the game is
I feel like Kevin Moore would like to
To pretend that that's not what his game is
But at the same time
It takes on a different
Feeling
If you know it's not just a guy who's like hey here's a video some guy sent me claim to be a time traveler
If he's involved
In it it takes on a different feeling for me
I'm not sure why
I think that's important
And this next clip
Kind of bummed
I deeply feel sorry for Noah because I
We needed a light at
With him in the lie detector said he was telling the truth
On the
When when he said he was a time traveler end
If you telling the truth or not
It's clear he's in a lot of
It's clear he's very depressed season that he's in a lot of stress
And
I feel really bad for
Well then in that nothing is behind the family is
The
Loved one in a woman
He took it serious
At this
Point do like the ever come out with a video saying it like this guy's lying
Okay check the weather video that recorded
He's saying that
This guy misses his family
Well that's the from the future
This guy
Is coming around to being like well if he's telling the truth you know
Whatever and if he's lying no matter what I feel bad for him alright
Kevin is the one who comes in with the
Assuming that it's
They're separated from their
Jcvd didn't love being away from his love or whatever it was this is not a critical look at any
Kevin pretending to be doing an interview but honestly
Just kind of hoping for some
Clicks he doesn't have to work too hard for
104 still going on
Spell it's also interesting that Apex feel sad for Noah
Even if Noah is running
Monument
This whole thing up
It's clear that
He's in a tough spot
What an
In person
At this kind of thing you here and you just
Help but think that he would
Steer you wrong
See him in such a bad spot and if he
Telling me the truth or not
I still want to
Exploit his story
Remember I told you earlier that this guy Jason came out and admitted that he was lying and pretending to be no other time trap
Yes and how that video was put out by Apex
Stevie but also kind of felt weird
Yeah
That video where Apex announces that Jason had lied to them and made it all up was uploaded on July
23rd 29th
When Mandela died
The primary function of its
Need to be to put all the responsibility for this scam
I'm on this guy Jace
He was one who made the stuff up
But Apex was just passing along as information for you to decide what you think
Think about I got to somebody getting sued
I mean really when you get right down to it.
Fact that they put out that video
Is clear proof that Apex is willing to own up to its own mistakes
And that it will even
Themselves
If they've stepped in
In a completely bizarre and almost certainly unrelated Quentin
10 days prior on July 13th
Another person named Dennis Bell had posted a video where he revealed that he was Noah
He was sick of playing
The character no f****** s***
He was scared the people would discern his identity and Docs
So he decided the best way to minimize the threat was to address the issue head-on
According to Dennis cute when he was 14 years old he was a kid make
Comedy YouTube videos
Posting a pretty much daily
Who is channel he ended up meeting apextv who enlisted him to play the role of Noah
He claimed that Apex pressured him to sign a non-disclosure agreement
Which is kind of funny.
Even if they ever took
Come to court to enforce the NBA the obvious question of why they have an NDA active with a fourteen-year-old
Who looks a lot like their time traveler would probably
Like I'm up
It really only useful as an intimidation
Syntactic
Against a 40
15 year old
Ridiculous
Dennis alleges that he was paid by 8
And they when they recorded the videos Everyone was just laughing
Because of how stupid it was
It'll be really easy to just take this as a guy was trying to get into the scam and involve himself
Accepted his video includes
Clips of the original Apex TV videos on additives
Without his face blurred without his voice change
Walking sound exactly like Jason
The video of Jason
He was no I did not look anything like that
The unedited version
Put out what does look a lot like
Includes clips that Apex didn't release
Initially
It definitely indicate coach
One of the more damning ones is probably a clip of Noah about to shake
With his older self
It begins with an R
Camera voice saying
Action
It's kind of impossible for me to say like weather
Whether or not this Dennis guy is 100% the kid in the original videos but they look very very similar
Voice and manner is
Personally
Looks to me a lot like this kid selling the
And those receipts
Are pretty tough to explain otherwise
Although that you can
Okay
Your shot Recreation videos of it
I find that very unlikely
How many ghosts
Let's just be thing
I'm still not sure I care about you
Is there a big difference between soliciting independently created videos where people are pretending to be
Time Travelers
And creating videos your
South where people pretend to be Time Travelers
I'm not sure Hozier I'm not sure
In the first case you're just posting b******* and profiting off it and in the process
Probably enabling some Monteleone
Unwell people
It down this road validating this
In the second case
You're perpetuating
A fraud but it's also kind of in the realm of performance
I'm fine with it
I don't really know
I think the big issue is present
The fact that the channel portrays itself is just reporting on things
You know like I was passing this along
Welder in fact
Apparently orchestrating those things
Themselves
Intrinsically dishonest and manipulative
It'd be kind of like if we created a right-wing talk show host to say things that we wanted them to say so that we could cover the
Right kind of a betrayal of the format
Right whatever you're doing right I mean
I feel like this is
Ethical question
Yeah about
What is
Already demonstrable
Untrue
And in ethical I think from a very fundamental standpoint
A little bit
Weight of a gray area
In some ways
Seems like it there's some
It seems like what we're really dealing with
Is an in at the collector in a game of
4f
You know where it's like
Your you're
Too far
Yeah I'm fine with your
I would say it's an unethical actor inside a game apps
Cuz that's a good way around online
Whimsically in ethical or unethical
It's just
Is what it is
Your
Doing it right you're making me feel bad that's what it is
I think that there are added considerations when
The appearance
They are that you're actually running a hoax
As opposed to just being bulshit
Yeah
I don't know what I don't know what the internet difference but I'm
And it's there
Yeah I don't think I don't think Immanuel Kant
Never had to deal with this
Exact question
It's okay
This guy dentist
She comes out with these
Claims that he's making and the video in
Including the the footage
Which some of them are you could say our recreate
A video of him standing
Like
In front of line of trees
Saying something version and then the unpixelated version
But you could say I call maybe you just went out and shot.
Really tough to get around is the one of him like
Meeting his older self
But because that
Matches the video that apextv put out
Okay you put out the one with his face unblurred
Okay
It's tough to get around
And so he puts this out and then just a little bit later
Apex puts out there version
With a guy claiming I'm no I was lying
I suspect
Why they put that video out
It feels like damage control
Probably was
Cuz it's not that big a deal to the presentation
Show me the Channel with one of their source
Turns out to be a liar
No one perfect and we're all going to fall for something at one point in our life
It's a much bigger deal for their presentation if
The impression is that there just creating bulshit on their own and passing it off as if it could be
It's the difference
Gina you would pay and trusting
People and a hook
Exposes naive might hurt your reputation a little
But being a hoax or really destroys any possibility of future credibility
But again
I don't care that much
But the idea that like
A 14 15 year old is being put in this
Kind of position
Makes me pretty on
How old is he
When you made that video so I guess that's cool
Oh man
Yeah
This still kind of falls under the heading of like this is what lame grifter
On YouTube do
Yeah kind of the Wild West
It's not that interesting
Big picture
It is interesting to me that Kevin Moore is interested in talking
This guy giving it an ounce of this could be real
To him
That indicates a complete inability
Or unwillingness to critically engage with the subject
Discovering
And In fairness to him
The stuff about Noah being fake hadn't come out by the time he made this video there were list
Me too
But the stuff about the Swedish insurance
Commercial hat
There were plenty of red flags that would suggest
But maybe this operation isn't
Open up even by the almost non-existent standards of the Paranormal YouTube to me
Kevin Moore
Is not a critical voice
There's something else going on with his beef
I'm not sure what it is
But I need to figure it out
I don't know if we'll ever have been able to get to the bottom of it right but there's something rotten in Denmark
Thanks
There's nothing rotten there it's an insurance
If there's one thing that we've learned or I've learned from
We listen to a couple of his
As long as he has a personal connect
He will let
Anything Goes
Maybe I mean that is or or better yet
As long as he doesn't have a personal Vendetta
Or the door if he has a reason to
To think that this could be an Avenue for greater exposure
I know that does also
Is this behavior that he's doing here he doesn't know this
Not friends with him
Beer
What it comes down to for me is I think that this episode like when I said that it's beneath us
I think because this apextv s*** is super lame
The revelation of it being fake
First of all is assumed
And the fact that it's a hoax
Is likewise
Expect that
I don't know how much more unethical it makes it
Then then what
Did it originally is
Hoax video is
I think the hoax
Taking over the truth
That's the part that I think
He's genuinely
Morally
Bad that's when that's when we've crossed the the gray area into
You guys know what you're doing and
When you're trying to steal this
This story
You're creating a hoax
At your own hope I could I could yeah I definitely see that it like cover
Drop is worse than the car
Definitely intent behind
And I definitely don't think that it's not worth
Considering the idea that I can't
Dennis guy is
Telling the truth
Then what's going on is really inappropriate behavior with a minor
Uncomfortable he was as it went along and
He started to get harassed
Messages
People started to try and figure out who
Equation
Is probably legally action
I don't know if it is but it's definitely not something that someone with good intent would do for sure while I mean
It's a line past which you
You should not venture
Kind of what kind
Guardianship do we have going on there too
Did the guardian sign s*** did you know
Nmda as well that's traveled
You got to assume but like
If your apparel
A decent
Perine and like
Video
Yeah you're not
Go off at that
Batman technology just move too fast
You have no f******
Conclude I want to send her this
Mad when I was a kid all you had to worry about a fourteen-year-old boy doing
Was jacking off in the back
And now
Now now he's creating space hoaxes
I want to I want to refocus this because all that stuff
Is
Nebulous
I don't
Apextv is not something that I care to be on my radar
Except as
Away with
Which weekend
Kevin Moore more clearly
And that's
Really what I'm interest
I'm interested in
This
We are b*******
But it's not only that
Like Kevin Moore
To Safeway Richard Belzer was not a passive
Actors on the day of the Boston bombing when he was a guest on Alex Jones Show
He was a participant
Kevin Morris trying to become a little bit of a participant in this charade
What if you stumbled across
Excellent care that's not what it says
To be but it's
Yeah that
I don't know like
What would you say for example
I don't know well it's it's
What's that movie where they that they the people become the host of
Simon Cowell
The guest
Is that the movie
Thinking of
I don't know why
Okay that's putting out loud
But the idea that
You know
Yeah that that people have taken over by high for other reason
You know that major and again as you say
Yes possible right I mean
I'm trying to get
Yeah makes sense
I can make sense of it
He's trying to apply fake maybe it's demons
Play some other dimensional
Play Space little things that go in your ear Josh Hartnett was involved I guess meth kills them I'm not sure
Don't try any yes
You care about the credibility of your community
Your space weirdo community
You want to be like you know
Settling people we want to be we demand to be taken seriously
It kind of behooves you to not be like I maybe these folks
Right right right
I think your people are making this up
No
Very much like a
In in his own way it's like if your
Doing an interview on
Stalking Fox News
You answer one of the questions
And then you return it back with them
Oh well how do you think it's possible for us to
Isn't that he just comes up with a
The anchor comes up with a reason that
That your ship May
For you
That's that you f****** everybody over
If you are participating your escalator
Exactly
And enabling
Is absolutely
In this next clip Apex
Is talking about how people think that they're involved
With the people that they feature in their videos which they very well may be
Apparently that's a criticism
It some people have
I can't imagine why
And so he addresses that
And again
Kevin is enabling
It's been a lot of misunderstanding though people thinking we're in on these videos
And
I am planning on making a video soon explaining to people because
I don't think people get that we're not affiliated with these people that were interviewing
And there's been a lot of people
Who who don't really get it and I should make a video soon talking about
How we don't know these people and just explain things put things in your car
Where you can see how people would think that cuz I would think will these
The friends of yours you know these are people or actors that uniform other countries that you paid and
You know this makeup involvement
Everything cows
You know you don't revealing yourself
Can you can understand why they thinking
People but
Well I guess you already thinking along those lines
Volvo putting some account back
Real wishy-washy
A wishy-washy
You can see
Easy as nobody would think
Fat butt
I think you've already got that one under
The controller that's such a I got nothing
I don't have the nerve to say
Clear that's what
Your phone
The fact that you
Like he does bring the
A couple time
This interview it does
Indicating singularly focused with pushing back on that
Yeah in the same way that when they put out there video with Jason revealing that he had lied to them
Was also to serve the purpose of like
We were the ones who were lied to we had nothing to do with this
You push back on that
Maybe it's
Because you're
Self-conscious
It's about the fact that you're doing that
Yeah it's part of your
And also part of your
Layer of
Protection
The moment you're involved in making them
Alright guys get out of
Get the f***
It's easier to write off it's like if we actually had stay
Kubrick
Filming the moon landing
Then it's
We're all like okay get the f*** out of here
We know you're all
I don't know if it extends that far but I give you a call
So why we get to the end of this interview and we get to see that
Kevin Moore
Great judge of care
You seem to be a really nice guy right
Uh Manoa
You know you just easy to speak to you know you're you're
Did you get it all together and
It's fun right you having a little fun right now
This Is How We Do I would say
No
But I know very little.
Is probably a full-time job
Miss going
Yeah yeah
Making a lot of those bucks
So I mean that's cool I don't begrudge anyone making a living doing what they love to do haven't a lot of fun
Are people listening
People watching
Video
What do you mean
People actually watch that video
The video of Kevin interview
Not as many as watching the time traveler video stores like
Anybody watch that
Wasn't
Trying to find out more about SEO and f******
Viewers like this I don't know how this is a non-business
Video at all
This gets back to my point that I made at the beginning of this
Which is like
I don't really care to attack this
Online immersive entertainment kind of thing too much because I'm not fully convinced
That most of the people taking in
The time traveler videos
Actually think
But it's real so I'm
Super interested in
End
Like the idea that someone would watch this video Kevin talking
Dammit somehow like
Debunked
The time traveler videos cuz like
I don't feel like that's
Even a concern
It's more about Kevin I know I agree
I mean more like I don't understand
Kevin
Has no idea what
What an entertaining interview
No like no clue
Which might explain his lack of
Much more focused on hard-hitting question
About these
Even
Let's hard-hitting questions about the time traveler
Wild speculations and enjoying and having a fun time
Like on Project Camelot
Cary's great
Skill as an interviewer is
Ben Wilde along with everybody else
Not like being okay Eddie page
What's your hit count
On an average Twitter post
Right right
Would be less energy
To say that Carrie is very entertaining.
So yeah
I don't know I'm going to skip this clip
Got a sad
It's just that Kevin talking about how Apex TV has a
How can you trust them
Repeat
I have to work alone
Really hate Kevin I really hate it
Out of deep and abiding level he
I don't
Yeah I mean there's there is a pastor this to him
A real slipperiness
But I also think
I think there is just a huge
He's not very good at this
Right he wants to do this
And I think
Mickey's dumb
Yeah I think that there are those elements of it
Lot of it lot of that
Could explain some of the stuff
Comes off as slippery today
There could be a lot less
Evil intention
They could be explained by incompetence
And kind of being gullible and dumb
I don't know
I I think though
Even with those qualities
It's very clear there's also a naked
So yeah One Last Cry. It's just how they sort of
And things but listen I really appreciate what you doing
I think it's fascinating
And stuff
You know
Are good on you for doing it that's all I'll say
Good on you while I appreciate what you doing good on you
Talking and everything is like
Yeah there's a lot
Well I mean
That's part of not preparing at all
That's fair
I would say
That is a terrible showing
The identity answer with like I appreciate what you're doing good on you for what you're doing.
In this
F****** interview that he talked to a guy who claimed to be a mermaid
Some of the people who are Time Travelers are clearly lying to him
I don't understand
If you want
To just be like we are doing
A large
Scale
Immersive
Entertainment thing
Where people lie to us and then we pass it off as truth
I'm not all that mad at that
Kevin's trying to
Play that game
Yeah
So he shouldn't
Taking somebody who appears to be
Be doing
LARPing
Yeah bulshit I was just I was just saying it's almost like a
Channel vet
Should exist in an alternate universe
You know what I'm saying like where where this s*** is
True that's where they're LARPing
It's Unbecoming
For Kevin
To be this
Uncritical
Whatever judge
I'm at the side that I have
For whatever Apex
I have strong judgment for Kevin
Because like you can
Can't do both
Trying to take down Mark Richards
Because he's an affront to the community
Appreciate and applaud
What are fake
Time travel bulshit clickbait nonsense
It leads me to believe
B something is in
Sincere
And based on everything else I have all the other info
Information of Kevin
Between
His weirdo channeling video
Other videos that I've watched it his where he is woefully uncritical of other people
Is the being critical of Mark Richards and carry
Because
We have a long-standing
Interaction
Project Camelot
I feel like I'm the only person
So Jordan
I would like to Wenatchee right now
I am going to make a documentary about Kevin Bull
I'm not going to do that
You are absolutely right
I'm not going to do that but I'm going to look into this
Much further
Who is
Fukkit
Deep In The Weeds enough to really get to the bottom of this Feud
The only person who has
Any kind of grasp on reality
Terry her friends are too busy trying to say that this guy is working for the spider leadership in the Illuminati
That my friend is a non-starter
We'll talk to a time traveler maybe he'll figure
I can't go down that road
That's not going to happen
Let's not going to be good
So this
It is
Something that I need to get to
I'm going to get into this
I'm going to try and solve this mystery of why Kevin Moore care so much
About this
I think that's the fun part of this
Far more than any
Kind of
Proof of them lying or like
Carrie's b******* about
Getting to the bottom of this weird
Personal or professional fight
The two of them
Has a far greater likelihood of like puncturing there
Their Mystique bubbles of space we're done
If you just go down to it you're like
Oh his
Mom
It's her dad like it's their stepdad and montagues and capulets
That's
Real
Reinvigorating my entry
Things a little bit because it actually is something that like
Maybe you could get to the bottom of what the f***** going on here
I'm never going to be able to tell you whether spider aliens are real or not we can
Safely say
No evidence for that right but
This is this.
Seem like something I
I can maybe Dig Inn
Yeah I do feel reinvigorated
About the Project Camelot / Kevin war world I do not about the Project Camelot Studios
Very distant
I'm a goddamn Hercule Poirot mustache
So that's something else I'll be engaging in
I hope you all have enjoyed this
Halloween
Spectacular
Nobody
Mermaid
Yeah
I think somebody dressed up as a
Critical event
Instigators journalist
Oh man
Is costume might as well just been all cardboard
Trying to channel
Person who asks a follow-up question
That would be good
All you can go with Dan Rather
Sure
When did Mills
I remember it being last week
So we'll be back on Friday Jordan in modern-day Alex Jones episode on his dumbass
Do it now it is moving along
So we'll see but until then we website
His knowledge bike.com is right we're also on Twitter
We are is at knowledge underscore fighting
Go to bed George can find us on
Facebook you could find
Who's on Facebook
You can go to iTunes
Download reviews
The show give us all that stuff you could go to other pie
Go to the places where you listen
Yeah for sure but I was back but until then I'm Neo and Leo
I'm dzx Clark
I'm a mermaid
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color