I have great respect for snowledge b b
College vype.com
Hey everybody
Novelty Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Have you ever been trapped in a snowstorm
Yeah actually I have a couple times
Yeah like like trapped outside not like crap in your apartment by a lot of storm
A I think I meant like
Snowpocalypse Chicago for that
Right
There's one time there was a really
Terrible blizzard
Number of
Is back
And I was like
Real f******
I wanted to get out of the house
And
Good buddy
Neighbor has worked at a bar called
I believe it was
Dukes
And you know.
Everyone's
Snowden he's at the bar all of the buddies are going over there to just drink at a bar
I feel like it was the day of the Super Bowl
B b mixing up the memories
The bar it'll be
Be great
And so Mike yeah that's it I'll get stuck in there
5 Steps outside
No f****** way
Nah is my back inside and
Aniwatch
YouTube
Yeah I know I don't know I don't mind the idea of getting snowed in
You're mentioning this because we're having our first
Real snow of the Season here in
The Chicagoland area are the kind where the
It is it is
Believes having fallen off though so all the trees that were like
20 ft tall and I'm 5 ft
There's a nice view out my window.
Tree covered in
Snow
Very idyllic it looks like like
Box boxing bags
Celestial Seasonings ass
I blow out the window
It looks to me a little bit like there should be.
Teenagers throwing snowballs out there
Play before they go fight in World War 1
I was outside met up with a friend blast
Last night for a drink
Uber
The guy was talking about
I was telling me about how like
Going to snow tomorrow I realize I'm so out of touch
Like whether the world
That was happening
Like almost
Iocus
Snow in inches of snow a foot I don't give a s*** come home at all
Very strange
They strange
Anyway I don't have to be
Concerned about snow that much given my normal lifestyle now but
Fbe concerned about Alex
And I guess I have to be concerned about
A little bit
Looking into the present-day of Alex Jones
I've have been Talkin Bout Time Travelers APAC
Ogive time-traveling ourselves
This week
Mindy and we've not checked in on what Alex's dumbass is up to
So
I assume he's protecting Deadspin writers that's all he's doing right free speech
Curiously absent
Doesn't seem to care at all
I wanted to cover a wider
Span of time but it's
Not possible given
The Bangles
And I'll talk about that a little bit here in a moment
But before we get to that
Jordan
Say thank you
Some people signed up and are supporting the show
So first
Jim thank you so much you are now a policy wonk
Chris B thank you so much you are now a policy wonk
Join the conspiracy
Next Chris W thank you so much you are now policy walk
It is getting out of control we are full up on Christmas
In the show
All of you call the Chris's
Next BART
Thank you so much you're now about to walk
Next Kelly with an i e l l i
Next William thank you so much
Ewok
Next Anthony thank you so much
Anthony scaramucci
You're out there listening and you're thinking I'd enjoy the show I'd like to support the show with
These guys do support if I go to a website knowledge.com is Betances for the show we would appreciate
So Jordan like I said we're doing the 30th
Wednesday of this
So on the 29th Alex's going on about just trying to
Like basically get estate
I thought about covering
That Anna I looked into
Do a lot of that
What I realized is we talked about a lot of that alright
Yeah it's very
The same thing
Talk about over and over and over and over again
And so much as I think it's important
Keep an eye on that
The way that you use
You know increasingly and
Consistently calling his enemies devils and demons back to the same things that happened
In the early to mid 80s
Martin
Preschool casein
Now these things again about it we never ever ever ever will not ever
Is rhetoric and other stuff
Is very the same
I think it's important to
Make a note of
But this is a lot of the stuff he's doing
But
I don't know how important it is to really
Dwelling it
I mean I think I can sum it up usually with just hey you know those marginalized groups
Not only should they remain marginalized but it's their fault they're marginally
And we should marginalize them further or Satan
Yes exactly
That's kind of what's going on in on the 29th
A.m.
Keeping an eye on
It develops if there's a change
Escalation
Worthwhile to
The point out but I believe that the 30th
Is X
Actually far more
Irrelevant
Do Trenton
That we are seeing in Alex's show
That are are much scared
Okay
I meant so
Will we get over the course of this
Episode is
So pretty pretty f*****-up white nationalism
To surprise you in the room now
Just you and us
Iuc
Some things happening on this Epic
Episode that I think are
Exactly what would you predict would happen on Alex's show exactly the directions
He's been going in for a while
But you still really
Don't like
Yeah they're going to start here in this
This first clip
He's addressing these new clip
Should have come out of Barack Obama
Saying that's a hey you know wokeness
Advocacy
Oh boy here we go
Here we go about that
Would be completely different because there's also a clip of
Michelle Obama
Let's come out
That is only rule of the right
So here is the first close
That talkin about
Clips from the
And they're also telling you that we're on the verge of a global race war because white people
Are inherently evil and bad
But everyone's trying to get into countries
Founded and that were Ryan
By the dreaded
White people
Very interesting
I'm fact here's Obama
Telling us that wokeness is not activism and then
Maybe he hasn't heard his wife's out doing
Spilling some of the biggest black KKK stuff you've ever heard
Obama talking about families
Is being
The same whether they're immigrants or
Akka
Cool talking about the one where she's like
White people moved away from Black
Yeah yeah yeah
Because
That was literally
White people moved away from black people against the law to move closer
Studies have been done about self-segregation
And the phenomenon that's a happen
About you now
Do white people on a macro scale
The way that Society
Cities have readjusted a lot of it is
White flower
But bedtime
You know
The countries founded by white p
People is little disingenuous
Oh well
White always has been in
Exclusionary light
The idea of whiteness
Has always been used
People out in the ways that label was applied
The inlets are the late 1700s
It's certainly different than it is
Today
Concepts of whiteness of
Revolved
Svr
More or less
Spoke to the people wielding those ideas right
Kind of silly.
To say that
Well well dream of bounded by y p
Before they found his car
Protestant white people are Catholic white people
Because they used to kill each other all the
Time where they routed by the Irish founded by the Italians
Zach even later periods of America's his
No it seems like the white is a is a term that includes
As the exclusionary Group Change
Yeah and whatever you needed to be that what it is
So it's always a little bit disingenuous
The heaviest like
Everyone wants to get into the
These countries founded by white people
Alright whatever
Anyway he's mad at Michelle Obama cuz she
Is black KKK no different than the Immigrant families that are moving in the families in Pilsen the
The families that are coming from other places to try to do better
Because we can so easily wash over who we really were because of the color of our skin
Tell because of the
The texture of our hair
You know that's what divides countries
Artificial is artificial things that don't come on now
Call the world with no skills training
You're pushing is a anti-white anti-American agenda
Everybody knows what you're up to you evil witch believable
Broad anti-white anti-American agenda
Interesting phrase anyway that the those two being so close together with
Appoint any larger issue
Very over I can understand which is very over
Strawmanning of what
She saying
Changing it into a
Yeah you see this
In the
Beginning of the episode
And it's
Yeah that's how we hoping yeah I was listening to this I was like
OD
Dear God what is going to happen on this episode
This is
Really f***** up and it's not even like
It's not even like as anti-American
, anti-white cuz that means
A whole different than that means very similar things
Anti-white then, anti-American is very much like
White purse
That's what's important
And then naturally
But thing is it like Michelle
She knows what used
Evil
Evil evil evil evil
Did you go back to
John D Rockefeller the first you go back to Margaret Sanger Planned Parenthood
The Colgate family
And others are public
Paris letters
And she was given billions of dollars billions back
I'd be Huntersville yesterday
So it's not
Not true of all the black leaders and black colleges
The Christians are set up they hijacked
The madman what you see this
Is the plan
Everybody
So you can look at the master black communities in Bible
I get mad at a butt
We're smart enough to really know the full gameplay
And I buy into this race war crap
How about we do that
Because the whole thing
Is a
Shut up
You could easily hear this very similar rhetoric being used as anti civil rights
Ciara
These are black people who want to be able to eat at the same counter is me and I was white
I just don't know we're above that kind of whatever it is they're doing
I know you and I the whites
We're above that we're not going to get down in the dirty with all that jazz music
Haven't we talked about them are grits
The number of times
But at least the dollars is a billion dollars Sanger with hundreds of billions of dollars they needed to pay
I heard to come in and co-opted all this stuff we learned me because
Things to help Empower people butts
But they are all susceptible to billions of dollars a payoff putting an IV evil
Genocide
Margaret Sanger
Oh yeah
Anyway Alex starts rambling
Some more about towel
Like his body
They have this
Supernatural
Right and that's what the enemy is jealous
Okay once you get the big agenda
The same thing
To the same thing you say like an hour later
You tweeted this
For speech
They said exactly what you said he said during the speech
We're simpatico
And that
Globalist looks at me and he just shook his head.
Works
They're mad
We've got a sixth sense way more powerful than them
Do you serve evil you lose the gift-giving
You get staytonville Twista
Yep
The literal superpowers
The god-given
Superpowers are literal
Right2know which one
Subaru
Super 6 in all right so I'll pass on that
I'm willingly given that one up Ono
I'm just going to let that one go
What next
What am I missing out
Magnises cuz I don't give a s*** if I can tell you what Trump is going to save 5 minutes
Yeah that's a bad power
I would rather Bruce Willis no dumb thing
Oh I know what a white racist is going to say
Yeah I would if it was telekinesis or flying
Hell yeah
I believe in any God that lets me fly predicting
Because Alex has believe it
Power
He's talking about that you know the big
Agenda
Continuation of his thoughts
About Margaret Sanger in this
Does Eugenics plan the globalist have
Once you see all that you see
See you at all when you get superpowers that God gives you the ability to talk about Democrat
Demographic replacement
Call you before another guide rate superpower
So
Like you know like we have these
Powers and then Satan gives like full super powers
Alright
Man I wish I was high for the
This is really entry
Because I would argue that the things that
He's talking about here
None of them are gif
Okay I'll explain the other side
By the way
We're all pretty equal in God's eyes I agree with that Russian dependents equal in our skill
I don't have to get to being a long distance Runner
But I do have a gif
Fortitude and focus
And the gifts that nobody's ever knocked me out
Couldn't get in the habit
Lead pipe
Handles
Call got
Different gifts
I do not believe also
Alex's head trauma
Have a very thick skull
Avakin
What what familiarity with head trauma that I have been
Laminated 2
Had abuse
Even smaller than it was before
What he's saying
R-Truth
It's not a gift
Also
Long distance running isn't necessarily A gift either you work on right
Cracker
I could get much
Better at longest
Distance running then I am right now if I applied myself that's not necessarily a gift
Maybe some people are
Just like by their butt
Their physical like we all have different bodies
Airborne
Yeah it's summer maybe more conducive towards running
And other I try right but Michael Phelps
Clearly has some sort of proportions that make him Swim Good
Now if you had
Praying that no he had the gift of swimming
Dad
Whatever
It's 88
Discounting of the process
Yeah just pretending it's
The gift not the other thing that I would say about this
Alex does not have fortitude nor does he have folks
The both of us staying Focus
Is
Furiate
Yeah
Reading week
UE
I don't even allow breathing on the way
That's that's too far away
I could
I would also say that those are
Practice behaviors to
Like focus is something you can get better at if you apply you
Yourself fortitude
Fortitude another thing
And will is something that you can get better at
By making
Brave decision
I think he's only talkin about fortitude in the sense that he can take a
I think that's mainly his idea of fortitude my basement where he goes with
Ahead
I'd like
8 that he has to have a really good saving throw to make it through that without getting
Ridiculous
So
This attack
On Michelle Obama
Is
Icon
Necessary
And stupid and it's being couched in a lot of like a very
White identity ways
Sure it is absolutely a reflect
I'm sort of an insult
Security that he feels about this
Very powerful popular black woman speaking the way that
Yeah when she talks he might as well just Screech strong black woman and then hide in the f****** corner or whatever
Something
Do that that you can hear that
Feel it from his
Response
And because he's very stupid
Any lacks fortitude and lacks Focus he has been hit in the head with a lead pipe
The only way he can really
Experience this and move forward
To make
Personal
Bigoted
Yeah there we go on Michelle
We're going to talk about
The real rabbit hole next segment play Somebody's clips
From Kanye and then that Wicked devil Michelle Obama
That
Sakuraba
Wife
Dollars in advance
Going to be talkin about
Mrs woky Wok
So it's business going to descend a little bit it's a human flying B
Michelle Obama secretly a man
Over the years
Covering it talking about it a bunch and then being like hey we're just joking
Just joking around and then doing
Sirius special reports about it
It's disgraceful
Disgusting
And very dumb
And we'll go see a little bit more of it as is
Reveal
A big Special Report
That he is made
Don't know no no accents
No I okay
But I told you already
Okay
It's still happening
Cry don't worry about
I'm there's a News special report Vine
Final yes addressing the age-old
About flattering
I want to be completely clear I do not believe
But because the
People have been lied to so much and they know they've been lied to now
Most people don't know what's true and
They've done internal polls and actual survey
$20,000 is a few months ago doing one
What color shoes to find out example
Going on
What we thought
What
Question where the earth flat
Something else
I don't know if you saying you spent $20,000 on a flat Earth pole or if it's a different pole like
Sandy Hook related
Public
Ian Pollard
I don't know what you're talkin about
But the legal issues leads me to believe it has to be related
About legal issue
The law is it who is it
Help you could help guide your like
How you would behave in the Press
Court of public opinion
Okay for me to say
What can alienate literally everybody
How could I bring you some Focus
Get any
Semblance of focus
Guess yeah
But it's the way he's talking
You did a f****** survey about Flat Earth
Hilarious probably not true but based on his life
The focus in inability to convey information that make it that's what he's saying
Anyway I don't really care about this stupid
Flat Earth report
It's just basically about the idea that
Government slide so much that it
It's rational to question whether the Earth is flat
And I would say
The opposite
It is probably true enough people have been
Baby conspiracy
B******* so long
Okay the government does lie
And having a healthy amount of steps
He's a healthy
But it's a healthy distrust
As opposed to an unhealthy distrust
Which is what we see manifested over the years when Alex
Right I don't understand
In what
Possible sense
The government is at fault for
Whatever the government does
Has anything to do with whether or not the Earth is
I think you need to look in the Flat Earth theory
Is a little bit you'll understand what
That's not
I think you need to educate yourself
What isn't flat your revealing the you don't know shitt
So
It's goes down over the horizon
Off the edge of the world
Slowly
I don't really care about this subject and really well versed in
So I don't really even want to pretend to argue for the others but I do believe that the
People who believe that the Earth is
Is flat think that the government
Has invested in Macon
You think that it's round
Sure sure that's the part of it the
Yeah I don't
Anyway I think Alex is just trying
How to reach out to
So cool good luck
I wonder if we could turn those into white magic
Easily
So if Alex addresses the elephant in the room
The big issue
And that is Kanye West
Does new album
To really talk Kanye West on this show
I assume we're going to get into the music we're going to get into some production elements
He's going to talk about the opening track being an accelerated version of it
Has gone back and forth on the subject of Kanye West
Depending on how insane
He's behaving
When he's talking about slavery being a choice Alex is like
Kanye is a genius
Where do you sort of walk
Slingback
Doesn't agree to go on Alex's show probably
Opposition
But now Alex has finally made a determination Kanye West
Is For Real
Yeah I'm going to go Alex Jones level on you
What is he talking about
I said Friday
Hippie comes out against the
Genocide of black people to pick her up my Planned Parenthood
Margaret Sanger
Rockefeller Foundation
That spent billions of dollars in 19
2034 East
The target black people first termination
Black person on Earth
Hillary Clinton said black men are predators have to be in prison they're like dogs bring them to heel these are quotes
T.i. on this podcast the millions and others
Hey quit telling me about Trump and racism all day and that dog whistle
When is the Democratic party that founded the KKK
You gotta talk about that
The next day he did
Let's talk about Alex Jones level
And the next day he talked about
Today
Multicultural
Today I don't want no attention on the weekend now
So Kanye is come outside anti-abortion and Allergy
This is proof that he is
Completely for real he's legit
War
Kanye mentioned Alex Jones and so we're going to talk about
Well that is interesting that you say that
Because
Alex is saying that Connie you think he's going to go Alex Jones live
Here's the actual clip
Wake up wake up mr. West wake up culture
Supposed to be we brainwashed out here bro
Come on man it's a free man talkin
Democrats how does Bolton Democrats have food stamps for Years bro
Was you talking about taking a plan B
It was the same shoot
But they don't want to even more of it
Planned Parenthood and the purposeful Target
What really is the reservation
Okay good for you
Even Kanye if the state that he's in now recognizes that Alex Jones is crazy
I am not a Luna
Like Alex Jones I am specifically saying I'm Alex Jones
Crazy
Sample of what
I am not doing while people accuse me of having a bit of a
Episode
Then again he is doing it
Yeah it was going out
It's debatable exactly what going Alex Jones level meaning
And what he means
Hair turns gold and his Aura goes from RedTube
LiteBlue I would suggest that I'm not particularly interested
Posted what's going on with Kanye West album
Great I would say
Is that
I find
Some of the
Surrounding element
Of this album
2B contradict
Some of the
Consumerist
Elements
Of this
I find it difficult to find
Verity
In
Someone making an album called
Jesus is King
And the last album was called
Yeezus
And that one of the songs
Cuz I am God
Play God thank you very much
Hold on one moment
Maybe that's just my hang up but I find it to be like
I don't even want to dwell in this
I don't care
Absolute there's nothing to care about you every literate like
There are zero reviews of Jesus is King that I have read that have not been like
The music Here's a review of the music
It's pretty good, he's a genius
And then it's been a thousand words on how it doesn't change my opinion of Khan
Kanye's personal or public
And like okay
Great
Still some good tracks I don't know whether I don't know what you want
No
I mean it is on one level I guess you could look at it as
What is
Rashes
Like artistic
Move you could make
Yeah and it's to become
Kind of Fundamentalist
Aggressively fun
Kind of something
Put you in a
The corner
He's going like
The Prosperity Gospel like what's your
It does feel that way
Had a really really good producer and was not married to a shity
Like that's what it
Keyboardist
Not shity
I don't know I don't particularly care but it's awesome that Alex
Alright maybe I can
Can get in on this
He said he said Alex Jones
Granted it was in a I'm not
Going Alex Jones
I can weave my way into it
So anyway
In Spanish
What time on that bud
I'm certain he's trying to
And
I don't think it's going
Probably not
But Alex needs
Get back
Michelle Obama a lot of time
Insulting
It's only place this short clip
Talking about the like our families are the
The same
Just be superficial differences of skin color in hair
Texture
Alden Arizona
The division
Until Alex plays that clip again and then
It starts mocking
Because of the the texture of our hair
You know but
Millions of black people
Oh mother sick which I'm not kissing your ass anymore
She wears a big old silver dollars
Some kind of big old giant king
ATS
It's better the family show the real
I don't I don't
I don't know how to engage
That's too far that's that's
Two races
To transfer Robux
It's just too everything I did it's just beyond anything that you can engage with
You're just like
You're crazy man
If that's a nonsense you're going to throw out
Yep
There's a absurd and
Disgusting preoccupation that Alex has about this Michelle is a man
I'm kind of thing any value in playing this is because
When
Press to the wall and when he needs
To make like criticism
Do people like Michelle it does seem like
Things that he ends up eventually having to playoff is like our just joking around
That's where is buying two ghosts
It's because he's a cruel bigot
Yeah
So when he's talking about Michelle one of the criticize
Vicky
Rises with her
Is about
Like you don't say anything about the
The rest of the world
Problem and I find this to be an in
Interesting
Primarily
Because it's
Super white identity-based and secondarily because it's
Absolutely not
Michelle
What you think white people are really bad
When the truth is modern civilization
And the end of slavery is white people doing
We have the moral Authority if you want to talk about
Africa
Muslims are still selling humans in four nations in Africa can you don't say a damn word you evil
Jesus he is angry
And that is because she said that immigrants are like us
Or I can be very comfortable in saying that he's expressing overwhites
Presentation that white people have a moral
Superiority
Slavery
States is
This kind of mentality absolutely whitewash
Is the hard work and sacrifices of
The people who are in the abolitionist
Nope white people on their own
With no other Christmas inspiration
Many abolition
It's too late they gave their lives today
And this you know
It presented the
Slavery it
White people realizing it was wrong and deciding no more of that is there at minimizing their financial struggle
Ancestors World turned and looked at each other and they were like guys we got a not do this whole slavery thing for and nobody
We just learned on her own this also seeks to minimize the brutal racist system
Brought in to replace slavery after he was 10
Technically abolish
Slavery under other names like convict leasing program
Continue for quite a while
I mean it's not like prison labor isn't still being used
Exploitative Lee all over the place
Today
While these programs are running
Strictly on racial lines they are extensions of a legal system that disproportionately affect
Non-white America
Enter pretend otherwise is
Their inmates being used to fight fires
Yeah right now for
$2 an hour We're reminded of that every time there's a fire
Yep ever
Seems to think that just because slavery ended in the United States white people did their part and everyone should just shut up about this race stuff
Leaving aside for a minute that Alex f******
Heats Abraham Lincoln
And Alex's family literally thought on the side
Did the Confederacy during the Civil War who would have absolutely
Continue play free if they've got in their way
We've all had stuff on the side of the Confederacy that wanted to end slavery
You forget that that side of the Confederacy was there right right
Even leaving all that aside without you saying isn't
Incredibly stupid
But and likes any kind of nuanced understanding
Sanding of history or the
It also seems like one of the issues that Alex has years did Michelle Obama dares to speak about race issues in the United
Midstates but you won't talk about slavery related issues an African country
Did Alex not remember how in May 2014 Michelle was very active in the bring that Bring Back Our Girls campaign
Does he not realize that that was about 300 young girls in Nigeria who are
Kidnap presumably to be traffic
I understand that I was only operates on sound bites he gets from White identity leading right-wing publication
We can't possibly be expect
Did actually know the work
It someone like you
Michelle Obama has
It's done but he really should do is research before launching off on completely unhinged
Racist outburst
Like that I've never seen any Muslim leaders condemned Muslim Terror
Like maybe a good place for Alex
To start would be the July 2014
Speech Michelle Obama gave it to Summit of the Mandela washing
Fellowship
Young Africa
Can l
From that speech
Quote
When girls in some places
Still being married off his
Sometimes they even before they even reach puberty
What female genital mutilation still continues
In some countries
When human trafficking rape and domestic abuse are still too,
And perpetrators are often faced in Oconto
Address for their crime
Then we still have some serious work to do in Africa and across the globe
And well I have great respect for cultural differences
I think we can all agree that practices like genital cutting for child marriage to Messi
Violence are not legitimate cultural practices
They're serious human rights violation
I have no place in
Any country on this Earth
Alex is creating a fictional version of Michelle Obama turns turns a blind eye to Human Rights issues
It's slavery in African countries because she's too busy trying to demonize the white people here in America
But that doesn't match reality at all
Put simply
Being racist is s***
It's this isn't the valley pretty now you could make a criticism that she maybe could do more
If you want to have that conversation
Fine but pretend pretending that you dozen
Do anything or
Why you talk about that that's not true
And the reason you think
Not true
Because you are very
Angry about your white identity being
And what she does is in some way
Castor the same eye that you does to the African countries
In this sudden the speech a throughout her career
Upon you and your buddy
You f****** can't
Yeah
It does seem like
The only people that I hear talk about how
Somebody is saying that white people are in
Apparently bad
Are these people
The people who are the people who bring it up as a strawman about what other people up at the conversations that other people
I'm Not Lisa
It does have some of that like weird sense of of guilt trying to escape out where it's like maybe you guys are the
The only people who think white people are inherently bad
Well I would say is I think they kind of do don't they any based on all of these arguments that begin with
See they're saying white people are inherently bad and then goes on a Litany of all the things that white people have done and they're like
Oh just cuz we did this doesn't mean that we didn't end slavery a****** and
Yeah yeah I don't I don't know I I don't want to come
Because I don't actually don't know what I think
But what they
Perceptions are
Because also it could be very easily
Plantable as like
Wow their criticism
Coming our way that I rather not a dresser discussing any any meaningful
That makes sense
Just as much as
I'm having a
Deep-seated feeling that they're evil or whatever
Probably own slaves
So he probably has some guilt towards that
Maybe I don't know
I don't care
So not only is Alex being
Completely
Disgusting monster regarding races
He is also pretty deep in his
Anti Trans
Stuff in lgbtq
IQ stock
Which is always at least
MedExpress
Pretty solidly
Through conflation
People in
Various communities the drag queen Story Time stuff
And and what have you
I don't care too much of that cuz
Mostly just
Calling calling trans people pedophiles
Variety care about that too much I just want to point this out as like a really
Example of how sloppy is f****** work
And this isn't a religion of the elite and they're really into this you see I'm pushing on your kids everywhere
If you guys go
Men in Drag
Normal right
Another speech
I was a very very
So that arrested Alex is talking about
Have nothing to do with what he's
Pretending it does
This is a case of a person who is wearing a wig breaking into laundry rooms
Stealing women's underwear
As best as I can tell has nothing to do with trans issues
You said has nothing to do with children
It's just someone using a disguise to steal underwear for laundry room was he reading the underwear
No
It's an invasion of these people's privacy and
Insecurities and it makes sense
Did they arrested the thief but trying to make this a part of
Some sort of an Anti Trans narratives
Seems a bit pathetic
Like the guy who is setting off Bombs all over Austin a while back he wore a wig when he went to
To the FedEx store to mail off one of his
Explosives
Criminals often employ disguises to avoid
Detection and that seems to be what this case is
Now I don't know cuz the stories I read I don't know anything about this guy particular lady
To do with the larger narratives that Alex
Constantly
Yells about from from what I can tell it has nothing to do with drag queen story time
Which he's trying to
Conflate
It's just a
Creep who's breaking into laundry Road I mean he has a problem
Since people because
There were these bank robbers
Bunch of surfer guys really really f****** out on the edge there and they wore masks whenever
Break
It was arrested with 50
7 pairs of underwear in his car
Now that's a Johnny Utah level amount of underwear
Also you can't get arrested in California for using the wrong pronoun
The bill that was passed there that they're all lying about has to do with doctors
Care providers not being allowed to willfully use discriminatory language or behaviors with their patients
In assisted living facility
Alex get absolute absolutely misgender someone all he wants and have no consequences under the law unless that person where an elder
Really Resident Inn
Does ologist
The classic right-wing Bolshevik
Strawman
Man eyes
You're going that hard just to be
Addicted
That's our cue really want
So Alex
Spent a large part of the beginning of this show really being pretty
White identity
Yeah and really screaming by Michelle Obama talking about how she
She's the Man
Going real hard on this
People do right
Even though
I felt like
There was an intensity to at that didn't
Field that normal
You know it felt like he had the spirit in a little bit
Off the rails here today just because there's a
Here today
Stage one from the dreaded
That's right
Never got to this Sunday or Monday or Tuesday I'm going to do it today at 6 a.m. for next hour very serious news
George Soros
And we said that he could
Ben the will of God
Close to you
Public defender of free speech and trumpet Alex Jones are hurting our free speech
Total
Inversion
Reality
So he's back on his b*******
Anybody could have
Some sort of
You know Russian
TV is here but it's more important
Yeah yeah why is there a little bit story about how he's crazy
And who knows what even me
Independent YouTube channel is come with a camera
International news
But whatever the case is he's
He's a little bit more juice stop than normal because he's
He's performing for an audience
So you see that that like screaming about Michelle Obama
Compassion
Then he might normally be although he still would be worked up about those
Yeah
But that you talked a lot about
And it's sort of my position that I don't really care about his
No absolutely not interested
Sing to me whatever he's bringing up is
Bulshit
And I don't want to get
Nope but he talks about
Including this clip
Assertive tertiarily
Involved in it
I just because he makes an accusation
I think
Okay
The children
But who's Dracula
The Duke
Girls
There's a certain famous black woman is the only black person allowed to attend these meetings
Does she like her little girls
Redbox they weather
What you talked about Oprah
It's all about Oprah
Gotcha
Clear Opera of being a pedophile
Yeah that does sound like that's what he was trying to say
Yep that's a hundred percent ready saying
I don't
Eventually he's got to learn the less
Nothing about what you can and can't say
I don't know people
It's a it's a
Pretty wild
I think this is deeply
Possible I think he's like a dog you have to have
Your negative feedback has to come immediately after the X
You know that he's being punished too long after the fact he doesn't understand he doesn't
Put the two together is being like
I was saying this like if he just got whipped
Yeah I think that's the line
Yeah there's no kind of Behavioral modification possibility even with him getting
Consequences
Cuz now he's gone
Too far
Along with the
Everyone being like whatever
Yeah that's a problem
Why we're Where We Are
Marla
So he starts doing this he's talking about the Dracula and
And all this s*** and he starts becoming preoccupied with the globalist
Working for Satan literal Satan
Yes of course
He dissolved devolves into a bit of a described as a wrestling
Promo
About Satan
There's one way for the globalist to get out of this Mexican
Because you're already slaves to the devil your father you can't do it
So there's no way out
But it's still important
For you
Why
Cuz your boss has to get permission
Oh
The even
Blank is I
Your boss is not in charge of anything either of you
So you may have a bunch of slaves
Bowing down to you all along but
You don't run anything in this universe you don't even run this planet
You have just been given a little bit of power
To test the faithful
You know that
Can you imagine being a film crew in there and trying not to laugh
Are you doing this I mean
I can I'm at years at here's my I'm just looking off into the middle distance wondering when it
That's my face
Why is this show is long as it is
What is listening to this
That's people who out
Totally scared
People who are running
Themselves
In the next clip Alex
I have no other way of describing this
Then just like Alex
Freaking out
About trying to scare his audience into thinking people are coming for their kids
Okay big fat man
Assaulting Christians in downtown Austin to go out and have a demonstration with family because
Rosemary man are going to go teach five-year-old how to have sex with him
Official Austin
Five-year-olds are different gender not having anal sex
You know why because that's their food
What the
F*** as great music choice that really swell there at the end
Like I'm really
You scared of the idea of someone taking
Event at the other on the other hand I was just like this show is so f******
It's stupid there's no way there's no way what kind of
You would have to be
Way too far gone if you were to hear him say that it's the official curriculum
Teach five-year-olds about anal sex would be like that that's true
And some sort of a metaphorical way
Kind of sex
Yeah this is spiritually true they are coming on our kid
But I'm exhausted
Jesus just listening to him be that performance
Totally fake
Angry open
There's a there's a film crew here sir
Probably why
It's absolutely why it up for the camera so anyway
Also found a clip of Rashida tlaib
And yet you take some issues
Share with her
What a shock
Talib
How many of you have trouble breathing oleifera wo your old guy I'm trying to help you breathe
Super clean air compared to China and places
Where are the jet streams it'll happen to dump over
The Midwest and Texas
That's the truth
BMF
Preying on children
Uh-oh
Palestinian Johari alright cool coco
Rashida tlaib helped organize a
Campaign called we have the right to
To breathe in response to a billionaire in her District flaunting
Environmental Protection laws and refusing
Cease operating
Semi trucks
In residential areas
Which is massively polluted those neighborhood
According to her official page on the House of Representatives website quote
When large piles of black
Black. Started showing up on the
The Detroit Riverfront
Blowing into homes
The parks in the Michigan Department of Environmental Quality told residents everything was fine
Rasheeda collected samples and got the
The testator
She found that this was a carcinogenic
Petroleum Coke
And she started this organizing
Campaign to address
Problem
In the political climate were living in there's a real danger that environmental regulations
Will be rolled back or just not enforced
I want that ball starts rolling
People get hurt
We've had relatively clean air and water because years ago we put regulation
Place a big business polluters
The follow
Alex is a hacking a liar
So there's no real need to explain why he's doing what
Drivesense that rank
Vile everyday people who could be persuaded of the
Environmental
An argument
They just don't realize the situation we'd be living in if those regulations
Work there or wanted Force
I suspect they just take for granted the relatively good environment that we enjoy
So all of this came up recently with
Rasheeda because there's a Chrysler
Plant being built
It's right and she's been vocal about the
The company take
Taking the responsibilities to the neighboring community
Chrysler is getting massive tax benefits to build the plant and as such they have a very real responsibility to not f****** the lives of
The people in the surrounding area
And that's all she's talking about
It's irrelevant concern
To the Detroit Free Press spoke to a couple that lives down the street from where the plant is being put up and they talked about how their house
House was shaking
From the construction
And said they quote
Keep dust out of the house
It's awful
Also
It'd be wrong to bring up this topic without addressing
Studies that show
Clearly the air quality is not a consist
Something in this country
And their demonstrable pattern
According to research presented by researchers from the Ohio State University at the 2019
Keep beating of The Americans
Logical Society quote
We're seeing that these pollution hotspots are the same year after year
And every time they're in low-income communities
Auburn communities of color
This has implications for a wide array of Health
Disparities from pre preterm birth
An infant mortality to developmental delays in childhood
Do heart and lung disease later in
There is a cultural Gap here
And low-income areas are hit incredibly hard by polluting companies
And the research tends to show that this disk
Proportionately is
True of low-income
Predominantly black
Quote
We found it for everyone percent increase in low-income African-Americans living in an area
The odds that an area would be
Become a hotspot gruesa
Significantly
This was also true but to a lesser extent for increases in low-income lifepod
So yeah
I'll keep rambling on about China's air if you want
But that does nothing to address
The situation the tons of America
Where their health and rights
Clean air and unpolluted environment are being neglected
Did for the sake
Of protecting corporate profit margin
People like Reseda are trying at least
To address these problems head-on
In a way that serves the people's interest
But I guess Alex
That's just what Palestinian
Jihadis
The idea that
Well see we're better than China
Irrelevant
Okay one child
Less
Died a f******
Poison in their lungs
Great we're better than China
Like makes you feel good but I think you're comparing yourself to something
Terrible then
So I don't know if keep playing that f****** dumb game if you want
It's it's just of it's just a f*****-up thing to do this if which cuz that's
It's such
It's such b*******
Cuz that means that it's fine for us to slide
Back
Closer to China as long as we're still a little bit better than China
All the people who don't look like me better than to the worst
Worst case scenario is not good
Don't compare yourself to a terrible example of something like air quality in if you want
You consider yourself trying
Right
Ridiculous oil spill wasn't as bad as the Exxon Valdez so we're doing great
You're basic we we are heroes actually yeah
It's silly
So anyway accuses her
Rasheeda of terrorizing
Children Rashid Talib
I go into classrooms and
You know the second and third grade classrooms to read
You know Grace for president to end at the end I try to explain what my job is in
Before I begin I just asked how many of you all have asthma have a hard time breathing and a third at the class will raise their
And I tell them
I'm my job is
Protect your air so that you can breathe
And the kids are like eyes wide open I said sometimes it's really hard right
What
This woman
Looks like
Great another powerful woman of color
Target
Snake
Snake know how
In order to be a snake-like person
Right wouldn't you then have to have knowledge of your
Get stuffed
What's your forked tongue
Just a clear pattern
And how Alex
Interacts with
Other
Now I'm just
Rereading
Metaphor Metamorphoses in my head where the guy just wakes up and
He just goes to work like
Normal day in everybody's fine
You're a butthole
Metamorphosis
But with that
Metamorphose
That's the sequel
I was trying to find that punk
So anyway it's keeps getting worse
And Alex
A second and third grader sometimes I wish they can be in this room
And make these decisions because they're you know they know what's right and they know they don't have any kind of
Political strategy behind of these no it's just the right thing to do and I wont.
That you support
Mother's Day
You love
My God is big
Myself
Wow
Is that legal action
I don't know but I mean like it's just
Gross
Ask you support child suicide bomber because of just the fact that you're Palestinian
Don't forget to also wants you to be able to breathe
Sure so that is what is more like
Isis
Then
Like legitimately Allina are all Alex's responding to is the possibility of Greater regulation
For businesses and this is the response
Pretty f*****-up
And realize is really bigoted position
We're scenes very consistently
Play throughout this a
Really really f***** up
It really is amazing
How
Complete
The the propaganda wall really is whenever you
Convince people
Go to vote against their own ability
Yeah you know like there are people there like no we can't regulate the
Those those company bring Jazzy can't regulate them or regulations like
Okay then choked to death I don't know what to do I don't know what to do for you bunch of kids have asthma and we know
Ways that we can
Help this issue
Unfortunately
Going to cut into
Corporate profit
Can't do that at least we're better than China
So there we go
So we've seen attacks on Michelle
That were very white.
Exxon
Rasheeda which of also
Center around
Him
Taking issue with her at
You do a lot of white guys don't like it when black women have power
No would you know that was a trigger for a lot of white dude
It was like a crazy number
And so now we get into
To what do you do
He's promised he's
He's going to go over
And that is some Soros
But as he's trying to
BC
The pesky head of Tech problems
Oh hey
George Soros
I want to be clear we are going to hear this sort of tech glitch this is not your phone f****** up
This is from Alex's raw audio
Big paws
Finding where Jews written
Stealing
Getty warehouse for 60 minutes
Our Father stole it from Susie was supposed to say
So the situation with Madeleine Albright is a little different than what Alex is presenting
He has a lie about George Soros that he always tells about it working with a notch
Making a true story about Madeleine Albright
Fudge the details to make it matches false version of the Soro store
Madeleine Albright was accused by a man named Philip Armour of being in possession of things that were stolen from
His family's apartment
After WWII
This was apparently done by Madeleine Albright's father Josef Korbel
Who was the Diplomat at the time
I need check for a minute
They enter the other ended up
In that country after finding refuge in London during World War II
I say Refuge because many of Albright's family members were killed in the Holocaust
Though she's a Christian she had many Jewish relatives
Who's investor family was it rich
During the war if they do
Didn't get out
So they went to London then
After the ending
Hostility
Prague
Philip Armour was not a Jewish man who had his things stolen in the Holocaust
His family was German in the post-war years over three billion German
I've been expelled from
Backcountry
That that they were in
The ventricle
Waqiah
To be clear I don't know if Philip Armour himself is Jewish
And I'm not
The saying he's not or is I have no idea not because of the Holocaust
But because of anti-german
Did the post-war years
After that point
It said that Albright's father stole a bunch of there
If this is the case
That's shity and they should have their stuff returned
I don't know the ins-and-outs of this case
But it's nothing like what Alex is presenting
Even Harbor said that the confiscation of his family's items
Quote
It was understandable considering what the Nazis
He's did to his family
But it was not necessarily right
Yeah
Nothing to do with
What Alex is
Presenting
He's only using this story in order to reinforce
He's completely about George Soros
And like rounding up Jews during the Holocaust under the guise
Coming
Stop or whatever
That's just such a funny
Clip for the wave
To get into
Like to do
And so the Jews were all that
It's almost like you just wanted to keep going. Bulshit
Weird non-sequitur it like it might as well just been like
Rectum damn near killed
Dentist next flip Alex denies George soros's
Is identity as a holocaust
George Soros is really mad at me
But I covered this and I talked about it
Any puts out the pr
And the
Disinformation
That
He's a holocaust Survivor
Well I guess that's kind of like
Hitler is a holocaust Survivor
I guess he was someone that was around during the Holocaust and he survived
Please true that what did you say
Sickening play on words
Manipulation illegal
So we know that Alex believes that Hitler didn't kill himself
Okay
Where in Boys from Brazil Terra
Position for him to have
And I don't really want to get into it as much as I would say let's stipulate that Hitler did
Now Alex is saying that
Similarly George soros's
This. It's similar to Hitler's experience in war
Is Holocaust revision
You're engaging in minimizing Hitler's Behavior
Turning whatever Soros did into the level of
The person
The fuhrer
If either of those things is trivializing
The Holocaust
And I find it to be a
Yeah I think
He's really
Arundel Aranda that you shot the Moon
If this was a game of Hearts
He got all the trip added for the cycle got the white identity
Rashida tlaib is a Palestinian Jihadi was trying to terrorize children
And now we've got Soros Holocaust revisionism
You see you guys don't talk about that I think you can
Maybe understand why this is an episode that
Should be cover
Jesus but also I really just want to gloat about Alex's horrible
Sound quality
Issues
And far be it for me we've had some sound issues to lately
Yeah I don't I don't mean
I don't mean to begrudge
Hey we recording my bedroom and he is a millionaire
Play changing qualities
If
My s*** sounded like this
I would never put it out
AccuWeather hiding place
Small 47
Remember all that run out at night
They called the Bloodhound
I will completely making that up 100%
Nothing that's there is
Said he has no proof
Did Soros answer you
Went and found juice
Hiding places and then brought the Nazis back
This is one of the worst
Kind of Slanders
You can accuse someone else
This is
Disgusting
I don't even mean this just because like a iluv Soros or something
Play Let's Not by angle on this at all
This is
Cognate
And it just absolutely trivialize
The Holocaust
When you use something like this
As a political cudgel
Against one of your enemies
What you're doing is
Making it okay to commit a holocaust
Alex
His family eat he should
Have to worry about this
Cuz his family
F*** Hitler
Alright
And now that man has the ATL until they're probably lost it or say I'm a Nazi
That is obscene I almost don't exist
And time and space
Because
Hitler
And then a monster that served him and rounded up shoes
Fun swatches
Me and my family to live
And I'm just if there's Justice in this universe Mike
Can't we
Do something about George Soros and his son out
Standard openly funds
Antifa
Republic those documents are fake and what you're doing there is calling for someone to her
You can't interpret it any other way on Alex's show like you hear something like that
And like
Should something happen to either of them
I ain't like
The person who did it there's a listener of Alex's show that is a clear-cut example of
Like he is just been like
Oh there's any justice in the universe ain't God's will can someone take care of them
Meanwhile
On a show like within the last month Alex's said hey
Vengeance is God's but sometimes
You got to be God's instrument you got it. Cause you to do things somehow that makes sense in both Direction within the
The Canon of Alex
Does work you have all the pieces Nessa
Siri to think God is calling you to kill George Soros
Alex
Not saying we got to do something like
We need to
Institute of wealth tax
He's not he's not trying to solve
That problem he's not trying to solve any of the
Even if
Soros did do the things he's not saying let's send him to the f******
Hate to stand trial he's not doing any of that
That's f***** up this is unacceptable
Alex has a guest
Sure a lawyer
No that's nice for once it's not one of his lawyer
Turning Point USA
And so that Alex wants have a conversation about it
And I hear is that little bit of an in
Is being censured and targeted
Bye
Turning Point USA
All this why are there best people
Being shuttered
So Alex has a guest coming up who's on the outs
Turning Point USA for the interviewee mentions that turning point is good organization as a whole
Candace Owens
No
It seems worth mentioning that Alex just got done with a
20 minutes segment of Holocaust revisionism and lying about Soros rounding up Jews during the Holocaust
Tootsie
When you been transitioning to an interview by saying it was wrong for turning point to part ways with Candice probably relevant to know
Why they did that
It's like we're at what you said recently
You are not more important than the
Every functionary in these operations as usual
I'm told they're not
Even when you make quite a name for yourself if you go Main
Streaming some sent you can reach a point where you're just too f****** dumb or too toxic
Property
Continue being associated
That happened for Candace Owens in December
2018 when she
He said at
Turning Point event
I actually don't have any problems with the word nationalism
I think the definition gets poisoned by elitist that actually want globalism
Globalism is what I don't want
Whenever we say nationalism the first thing people think about at least in America is Hitler
You know he was a national socialist
But if Hitler just wanted to make
Germany great and that things run well okay fine
The problem is he wanted he had dreams outside of Germany
You wanted to globalize
He wanted everyone to be German everybody to speak German
Everybody to look at different way that
Not to me that's not National
Leaving aside how this, definitely seems
Implied that it internally operating genocide would be totally cool with her
Sing something like this publicly you just f****** embarrassing
It demonstrates a very shallow understanding of what happened in World War and what Hitler was up to
When someone says something like this
You consider what other completely idiotic and
Profoundly offensive things they might accidentally say in the future
And if you're smart you decide to cut ties with her
Yeah it's important to note
This has nothing to do with the substance of what you believe Turning Point USA
Probably probably exactly
Add Griffin
You don't say it out loud question of what else might we have to do damage control about a future
Get her out of here
Yes
The most generous reading of her comment is that she knows nothing about the subject
She's talking about the Holocaust
Both of these are bad for the brand
This is a holocaust
Supporter
Within certain borders I got both these are bad for the brand and turning point USA is all about that grip
I think this is important to recognize however because Alex is saying that they were wrong to cut ties with
In one of the motivating factors was clearly this comment
Easily be interpreted
Minimizing of the Holocaust
That's really f***** up to here after Alex's just Rewritten elements of the Holocaust
His purposes
It's also really f***** up to here considering that
Owen Shroyer had the host of Red Ice Radio is guest on his show
This week he did what ya man so they're going full throated
And it'll be even more f***** up or just dropping the hoods on when we get to who the guest
He's introducing
Well Nick Fuentes really appreciate him
Coming on Nicholas J Fuentes
Oh really you're really familiar with his work
That's going to be a problem here in a minute who's this guy so we briefly mentioned Nick Fuentes in a recent episode in relation to him
Working with that Network that also employed Joey salads the racist hoax video guy who peed in his own mouth
I kind of hoped that would be the only time this dude came up on our show but apparently I don't get what I want
Nick Fuentes is a pile of s***
But he's also clearly a troll so talking about him gets into murky territory where you
Can really never know how much of what he saying is
Jason Sierra
How much is Just intentionally provocative strangle people angry protest
Doesn't matter f*** that guy he has a show called America First that is just
It's really terrible green screen backgrounds Lobby bulshit
It's terrible but I've listened to enough of this work to know that they're definitely something
But he's very sick
About and they're all bad things
For one he believes that the United States
To the country specifically for wife
You'll generally resists the title of white supremacist or any of that stuff he pretends that he's just wanting to uphold
Hold the intent of the founders of the country one of the country
Be a place
Typically for what
Now
I'm going to go out on a limb
When does
Right
It's an issue
I don't care though
Don't care I'm just saying it's there everybody to know it's there and then we can move on that is
Interesting consideration whenever you have these sort of
Escalating
Exclusive
Miss
Position
Do you not think that you eventually won't pass
The test you are at
Skating in that Direct
It is
It is one of those things where it's like
The further on the edge of the in-group you are
Seems like the more aware you should be that the in-group is going to
Slop off those they're going to shed their skin Whenever there
It does not go the other direction
So the other thing that's very consistent
Nick Fuentes work is it strain
Hatred towards
The Jews and Holocaust revisionism
In this clip will hear Nick on his show America first
Complaining about Matt Walsh
The crying white nationalism
After the shooting in El Paso
From a little white Waze
And please be advised listeners he's going to use some language
It is very uncommon on Archie
A kid
Is very refreshing
Some people say
And I'll take a selfie
Deposition March
Digestive iwaste
Notice how the clause
Sorry for the late
People like as a family
Matt Walsh
Guy
Baguette
And
He's always lie
And when a white person
Suddenly is a big top
Scumbag Steve
People
Yeah you're real
Sorry for the language
Pictures of all the Lang
Yeah that's what it is
For their own pee
Matt Walsh a busboy
What it is
I know some people don't like
Use that expression
Nobody else
Nobody else talks
White races
Hayden public
Brutal about it
Keep typing on
Twitter.com
Faget
RaceTrac
You work for
So that's the kind of things that he
Espouses
Familiar with his work
So if you take that for what it is you have a guy was offended at someone not supporting white nationalist
In his responses to call him a race traitor
And then talk about how he works for Jews
Interesting
As for Holocaust revisionism
Nick engages in a crypto form of denial is
That's pretty popular in neo-Nazi
Which would they do is they talk about the killings in the Holocaust
Using the language of bacon
Cookies
I know it
Sounds weird but you'll see what I mean in the
Mac says
As if I take
One hour to cook
A batch of
Cookie Monster ice
15 ovens
Working 24 hours
Birthday everyday for
For five years
How long does it take Cookie Monster to make sick
6 million batches
I don't know that's a good question
Certainly
Are those really sound correct to me wait
Takes 1 hour to cook a batch
And you have $15
Probably
Four different kid
Doing 24 hours a day everyday
Day for five years
Here's how long would it
Chameleon
I don't know it certainly wouldn't be five years right the math dozen
So 6 million cookies
I don't buy it
I don't even care to engage with a sort of shape but I wanted to play that for you so you could understand that this is a guy who uses his platform to
Super taken explicit Olive
Holocaust revision
In denial
Nick is very young it doesn't know very much
But he has a good handle on really far right talking point
Is able to Rattle them off pretty quickly you know enough to
To trick idiots
He knows what he's talking about
Consider him to be like an anti-jewish been
Sapiro
A person a coincidence
Which probably has nothing to do with you
Shapiro's very public
I don't know why you would
What makes us absolutely unacceptable is that Alex's
Cuz he knows Nick
Nobody likes his
If you had no idea who Nick was and had him on then that's a huge f****** and assign that he needs a better vetting process
But knowing who he is
And giving him a friendly platform is that
Support for his ideas
And what are you staying
Mainly Holocaust denial and white Nash
So congratulations Alex you're almost at your true form
Yep
I heard that he was on I was like well this is progressing
Dim the Red Ice being on Owen show
Exactly the transformation that
You know you yeah.
It's basically what I was sorta predicting once
At the deplatforming came
And maybe took a little bit longer than you know you would expect like
It may be he Jump Right In but he probably had more cash
Before
No it was almost it's almost Admiral how long he tried before he just
Decided to become a white Nash
Probably trying
But all these people f******
The ND
This is how you do
Discuss
Assertive
Neo-Nazi
Holocaust Revision in a winking
Isn't it funny
Cookies
MattyB talk about cookies
Hey you know it's easy
The Holocaust was
Bad
No matter the number
You don't have to work that
Yeah
What you do if you want to have it if you want to come with it's okay with it then you really got to work hard don't you
So Alex is going to talk to Nick Fuentes
Which is how great
Answer what the big
Reason that Alex is having them on or so he
Yeah is that Nick got into a little bit of beef with Turning Point USA
Charlie Kirk
Sure I don't care about their payday,
But
It's interesting
Because they're having this
Fight
Alex's
Looking at things
Interested
Turning Point USA national events they say it's
We'll compromise in the left
So turning point USA is not a little left
Federally funded by right-wing billionaire cash
Infusions are absolutely 100% the two of the right trying to look cool in college game
So why is that likes hearing that they're a little left
I don't know possibly because he's now exclusively hanging out with crypto-fascist to me or not
A little bit left
They still say the Holocaust
Is real
Yeah
That is really what they're saying really is what they say
Country
If you have someone telling you to Turning Point USA is a little left
Baby but you're talkin
Someone who is
Emily on the far right
They appear to be a little leftist to them because their standard of where something falls on the political spectrum is
Wheatley f***** up
Considering Alex's Network as head Red Ice and Nick Fuentes on in the same week tells me
All I need to know
He's dropped any pretense
And this network is on its way towards becoming something
Very extreme
We're turning point USA is possibly on the left
The terrifying development but I'd be lying if I said I was surprised look at it look at these left this over here saying that Jews
You should be allowed to live
Come on budget lives
Lives
So
Alex believes this is going to be a thing where they talk about turning point USA being a little laugh a little
Whatever any please
Clip that I have to assume that Nicks
It said this question
This guy asking
Question at one of
Turning Point 3
Interspersed with
Charlie Kirk
Something directly contradict
And then
At the end
There is a clip
Charlie Kirk
Saying that Israel is special
Okay there we go
On the left indeed Alex
I think is a little bit surprised by the part at the end
Being about that just overtly
Not connected at all yet part prior to it
And just being about him saying that Israel is a Holy Land
This is not good
Falls apart very quickly as Alex should have known it would if you knew anything about Nick Fuentes
We're just out of that club in there to talk about it
There you go
2016 sprinklers talking about Charlie
Why
The fact they have contact with Trump
Yeah I know there's a lot of other videos online
Only telling Whoppers of lies or he has
Amnesia brain damage
Maybe maybe he's got a head injury or anything
You know I definitely think that's possible certainly he could be mentally retarded as you like to say or he could just be straight up lie
People get involved in conservative politics and maybe say one thing
Or send them they get people funding the organization I get some connections they rub shoulders with power
Purple people like the president or his son in the case of Charlie Kirk
And then all the sudden they're pennies start to change and then suddenly
It all their love for America becomes a love for
Another country so yeah I mean he could have been
Brain damage may be dropped out of
I'd like to point out that at the beginning of this episode Alex talked about getting hit in the head with the light pipe in an axe handle another talking about Charlie
Having brain damage
Real fun
That is exactly what you'd expect if you bring
Nick Fuentes on your show he's going to
Suggest
That he doesn't love America he loves his real
So Alex I don't know if he recognizes
By this point
This is where the interview is going to be
Be driven and he doesn't want any part of that
I know that this is what happened it's a good thing that that whole like dual citizenship right to return
Kind of stuff is staying well within this far-right Fringe
Call chicken
I'm glad that you never see people on national TV saying that
Somebody could be disloyal to the United States because they are
Yeah but I don't even I don't even know if Charlie Kirk is Jewish
I think this is even just like a
Surefire
I'd look throw it all in there
So in order to me
Make it not like interview that's going to be ended immediately
Nick gets into some of his other positions that Alex
B
Be more interested in
I'm 3xpress is his position on immigration
Here we go I bet it's
Very liberal
Do USA Style
Am I shall we oppose not just Mast illegal immigration but Mass legal immigration as well
Now we know that the demographic change
Stay in place
And so on
It makes into the uiy genocide mean
That's so cool
Illegal immigration of non-white folk
2 dni
It does sound like that's what his
Stated position
So it seems like I think like that one's he's wearing it on his sleeve than Alex
This
Sort of rhetoric about their look at the world the world needs more of that in the in the you-know-what
Let's not worry about the coke on our Shores Dan
Let's hurry about f******
Keeping immigrants
Great
Here we go here's some more
Chip that Alex will just have to allow on his show now
Patriot on legal immigration
I think he's anti-christian because
Degeneracy
Lady Maga some kind of make America great again theme drag queen supporting homosexuals in his organization
He's not a patriot in terms of his own country I think a lot of people suspect
Rightly so that he has a dual Allegiance or a Jew loyalty
Israel
Okay alright
Wow so yeah I mean associated with homosexuals and anyway is anti-christian behavior
Generous generous DeGeneres
Where is this f****** kid from
Chicago 1930s what is f****** happening
He's from that's a very racist part of Chicago
God damn it I believe that I have heard videos where he has expressed
Well I mean if you're if you're already
Comfort with a
Interracial relationship that you're probably against
Kind of a
Denigrate
This guy is so far past like what's what should be allowed in
Normal Khan
That I even find it
Tough that we're talking about
Like I don't even like the idea.
He's come into our
Spear by way of being on Alex
Yeah
Just like I did
You think we would see the
The day where
Alex is falling apart
I really want this and red eyes
In Auto Show
I mean
It's just becoming more and more overt
Yeah this is a white nationalist radio show
Yep they go
Uncritical interviews with people who are
So beyond the pale
I'm not just going to pretend to debate David Duke anymore I'm going to tell him to
Full throated screaming from The Mountaintop
I don't think you could do that because David Dukes
Yeah I think I mean metaphorically
It wasn't all about turning point USA campus
Associated with Candace Owens
Because of her
Gas
It's all about Optics as opposed to the actual car
So Alex
Seem to be surprised there
About Nick saying this
About that his loyalties to Israel
What have I done
If you listen to this
Text Cliff I do think that Alex has a little bit back on it
It's a country that we get support
I just about every way shape and form monetary support Military Support belligerent
I want to get you on
Be glad to know it's not videos about it
Where are the try to keep you from coming to those while saying they're open
They're doing this and they
Basically didn't stand up
Candace Owens
Personally I'm a libertarian
Until I like
The fact that Trump you know that his convention
Indian we don't hate you
Alex
The needs to redirect man
He does not want to have this conversation
Ocean ocean
As soon as possible in fact right now
When you got this
Hard right dude
On the show
Be constantly bringing up Israel stuff
Alex is smart enough to realize like
I
I've stepped in
I'm waiting for him to like
Artificially
Can't hear you good time for a glitch
He needs to refocus the argument or that the
Discussion into place where it's more about the
Trivial culture
Pop culture issues
I got
Somebody complained about something
And that's all he can do
It is it is kind of interesting that
It does seem we're really close to him having to be like
Right you know like you really all of his
For all of his free-speech b******* we're really close to him being like
I know
I know he didn't even push back on it no be with his
Don't do it later in the episode was we got a use those freedoms or else they'll go away
God
So Alex like I said the trivial issue
Kind of thing is he needs to refocus this back on the tourney
Greenpoint USA Petty drama is really what he wants
To talk about because
That's worth some money
That's where some attention is
Answer
Makes a little bit of an argument
I think is really in
Interesting I think it's really
Not Universal but it's very common
I'm in these world
This whole thing could have been averted I wouldn't be on Infowars right now
Yorkie no controversy
If he simply allowed me to take the picture
Are going to the event
I think a lot of people are now scratching their heads almost exposed himself he's made a bigger deal out of it than it is
What is he so afraid of why does he not want to stand these questions
So the sort the idea is essentially they Charlie Kirk Bain
Nick Fuentes from
I would assume that there's probably a good reason
I bet there have been some interaction
Between the two of them in the
Past
I know that I I was able to find some
Medication that
I got years ago Nick Fuentes was invited
At a turning point of
So there is some interaction between him and the organ
I wouldn't be surprised if
Naked Ben
Like critiquing
I'm saying like
You dumb Jew lover
Think that's entirely possible
You clearly an antagonist
Troll right why wouldn't he be behaving that way in the lead-up to Charlie say
Don't allow that guy in I see that is incredibly likely
But what are you saying here
Is a classic manipulation
To any right-thinking Observer this is more or less supposed to be stopped at Nick Fuentes
Running
Expensive Charlie Kirk
And ultimately there's no good
Solution for Keurig
What's being done is that Nick is putting Charlie Kirk in a situation where he has to offer
The first is to take a picture with an associate with someone who is a coup
Clear bigger than
Control who is outside of what you
To be acceptable disc
By that Association you'll be giving this voice your test
It support which is something you absolutely don't want to do
The second option is to choose not to us
With this entity
And based on
A very reasonable assumption
Reply format
What you doing
Keep them out of your
But this doesn't work either because now you've given this bad faith into the appearances
Can't handle their ideas
You're shutting down free speech
By protecting your space from a holocaust revising White
You end up giving the person precisely the fuel they need to
To get the publicity they were after in the first
This is a win-win situation for Nick Fuentes
And that's exactly why
You doing this and
It is
Evade
Like
You can feel Charlie BMI
Like I want to say
I don't want you here because you're a holocaust-denying
Nazi lunatic
But if he said that he loses
Half of Turning Point USA Spotlight wikiHow
Clear about like
No of course I don't want this
F*****'-a
Masshole anti-semite troll
Hanging around I think he has been cleared
Well good for him
What me there are limits I mean well he's on Alex's show
Charlie Kirk
Oh no yeah
There's still a veneer there
Whatever the case
Now after this whole thing
Other people in Turning Point have
You know come out in desk
Supported Charlie Kirk
In this
This kerfuffle
And Nick had some,
And you know what else is so troubling is after this whole event we see people like Turning Point USA
People are now standing up and calling
Everybody asked questions last night at his old is Ohio State University event
Last about Israel asked about his support of homosexuality so on
People working for Turning Point USA saying that if you opposed the Charlie Kirk
Conservative agenda
You're homophobic you're racist
I think Benny Johnson said we were the Westboro Baptist kids because we're Christians because we support the Bible
And none of the sexualisation of children
What does that look like
What is that pendulum going back to the other direction look like
Why do you think that gay people being allowed to exist in Civilization and it
It was just in the public is sexualizing
Children of the pendulum needs to go back away from them being allowed to exist in public they need to hide again so I don't ever feel it
Any discomfort at all for
My way of life not being
The only way of life that
More less what we're getting here
It does it does feel like
Like this
Fuentes kid
Is so much
Like I have to see these older guys like Alex Jones and all these people looking at Nick went
Buckeye made you
Yes
You are you are what I created and I can you do
And you don't know
No they do
Diving Nick
Made by Mommy doesn't know that he's
He doesn't know that the all of that Holocaust
Denial and all of that
Anti-Semitism and stuff is supposed to be about the Griff
First
Yeah yeah
Hates you know like Alex doesn't with that like
Iodized a x x I think we get caught up too much in how much
So much of this
The performance underneath that there is still some pretty freaking out about us
Muslims
A pool supply store Princeton
That kind of thing is
Still real for now
What I think is more
The point is like you see this me like I am
Partially responsible for your
Attract
That you've gone down
I cannot control
Anymore yeah yeah you're better than
You guys much more smart
Then Alex next generation is
Explore More compact
Then the past generation
Someone like
Nick could be really dangerous
With the level of
Exposure that Alex has more of these two used to have certainly I don't think Alex would ever have him on
Back when he was doing well
No I mean if
If he
Yeah
Like Nick Fuentes wouldn't have been there on the night Trump wins
Not at the height of Alex's power itself never going to happen also to even be too much of an issue
To even have his an employee
But now
I don't know I still think Alex
Vivid Seats
He threw a pretty quickly and realize this
The job offer treatment
Yeah I don't know
It's f***** up
Play one last leap year and it's
Nick Express
You watch them fall
In the day which goes to your point and
No I've been in this for
2 3 or 4 years now I remember watching when I was in high school
Donald Trump appear on your show and it was probably one of the coolest things I ever saw
Everybody believed in 2016 the things were going to be different
Donald Trump being insurgents in the Republican Party the hottest
It'll take over
Anna becoming president
Everybody believed that it was going to be a real America first movement that
The John McCain Mitt Romney George Bush conservative movement big tent conservative movement was done
To see all these people that wear the Maga hat
They co-opted Donald Trump message to Donald Trump look the Optics and everything
Use the same tactics of
Do you know they're really embracing this model party globulus mentality
So he thought that Donald Trump was going
To bring an end to the big
10th.
And what do you mean by that is
Non-whites
Are you mean by that is not
Y'all pretty means by that
Is anybody who doesn't think that the United States
Does a white Christian country
Weather is
Should be a power Monopoly
In the hands
Of those people because of
There's
And there
Choice of religion
It is fun to watch you hear someone talk about trying to get rid of the Big Ten
Ethiopia
Who has a
Expressed about like let's say a guy who isn't into white nationalism
Calling a race traitor who works for Jews
Yes you can't hear Holocaust denial and revision coming out of somebody
And not think getting rid of the big tent at the GOP probably mean something different to you give idea
Is what they're talking
Certainly it's the ideas that there
It's all about the free market of ideas it's just infuriating
Agates
It's a dating I don't really care I mean
I'm at Karen one-level but like
This to me is so expected
It's not like
I see this episode this 30
It's so
If you have the
You have the the s*** with
Michelle Obama at the
Beginning
You have the the receipt at slabs
Stuff but just
Repug
You have this long Soros diatribe
Where you going
Further
Then he hasn't
Oh yeah so Rose in these behavior in the Holocaust
In World War II
Revising elements of
Of the Holocaust
Then he talks about Candace Owens shouldn't have been
Cut Loose from turning point USA
And the reason that she was
Because it was
Because of
Deny around your show
Who you introduced as someone who you like they're working you're well right
Like this
Use
Bad
It's what you expect
Because of what Alex has
Been promoting
Throughout his career
But just not over yeah yeah
Coming off
A bit
And it's
This episode is a certain thing that it's just like well buckle up
Cuz
A month two months
Now who the f*** knows that the
The show is going to be
Like imagine
Yeah so red ice is coming on Owen show because they got kicked off social media
Because of the
Made a choice
Yeah
So if they're being
Put on
People who are being
Deplatform been censured
Like us
Alex has an alternative for that he has his own band
M.video site
Where people who have been kicked off social
That's where it's supposed to be where those the
Things go
Now is Red Ice going to get a channel on there
Racine the great merger
Infowars ice
Kind of see
The possibility
That this
Network that Alex's built
Infowars
And its tendrils
Like this new Band. Video
It could very easily be co-opted
By people who are
Far worse
Burnham
Fireworks
And also this
Yeah yeah
And that's so that
The troubling possibility but it's also I believe what I predicted might happen with the
Is
Video Endeavors that if he does allow other people on guess who's going to be
Take a look at all the replacements
Conservative Replacements to Twitter turns in
Into
Immediately your life
Yeah I get it yeah
If what you're if the problem you're trying to
Dissolve
Is a problematic
Exclusively
Almost
Exclusively applies
Racist
Nazis
Fascist
Solution it's going to be populated almost
Reply to roses
Crazy
It's because you're solving a problem that they only they
I really
You know it's telling
The disillusionment every generation
As their disillusionment with their with the president that they helped us
Like for us with Obama
Why didn't he close Guantanamo
Why didn't he stop torturing people hours
Torturing all of that stuff
That I was very deluge
Dissolute
And for this guy his disillusionment with Trump is
Why can't I torture people
Why can't I drone people why can't I buy murder people
Maybe not the life is difficult samples but like why isn't it this white country
Exactly
Why haven't we
You f******
Crackdown on the gays and non-whites
What is going on that was the promise you that I heard in truck
You made it to me
Don't you end up in trouble be like I didn't make it to you there's good people on both sides now you know what you f****** say
It's because
This side
Strong
Yeah they have a supernatural healer
So I do not appreciate the
So I think it sucks
I think that Alex is veering into territory that was very good
Quickly
I'm so far past the point
Social acceptability
That I just got
I don't think I
I mean any much further than this and I'm kind of the opinion that maybe we should
Yeah we shouldn't cover that show it all if it's
I don't know our responsibilities something maybe we should
The sky
It when you see this sort of thing
Like wow this
This is bad sign for the future but also good that you're also doing this
The shift in the middle of a going-out-of-business
Everything Must Go
Good luck Alex
Buck I wish you the worst of luck and I hope you fail them
On Monday
Picture of website
Acknowledge
Dot-com we're on Twitter or fighting at go to bed Jordan
On Facebook and if you would like to
Download the show please go to I2
Download or go to somewhere else where you can listen to podcast
Store leave a review or so on and so forth
Sure we will
But until then I'm Bo yo I'm Leo and easy acts Clark
I am the juiciest Ice Cube
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color