Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Stripe.com
Alex Jones
Long last
Sort of push goals I guess on our our patreon that I would get a show tattoo
And it is done
It is I went this morning to shop here in
Chicago I've been trying to get it for a while and I'm sorry there's a bit of a
The delay but
I really wanted my brother to do
Design it and he's very busy guy
It's getting the actual designs
Together
I took a little longer than expected
And then I don't you a couple places here in Chicago that I just did
Feel comfortable
But I just didn't
I got a feeling like
I rather feel totally comfortable when I go through with this
You had while you were in the tattoo parlor and you're the guy is making the stencil Inuit
Texted me just like
I don't know if I don't know if it's good
I don't know if I like this I don't think I don't think I trust this guy
That's not what it's supposed to look like he's freaky
Yeah it's
Here's the design
Here is a picture of an app
So we'll post a picture that on a Facebook group everybody who
Donated to the show and help me get to the point where we
We were
The Illustrated Man
Stupid Alex Jones reference illuminated manuscript that explains it
Propaganda
For those of you who aren't on Facebook
End up seeing this picture it's a apple with a bite out of it a glass of whiskey and the life is very fresh
Reference to his drunk
Hotel interview with Patrick bet-david
Indeed
In that same Spirit of thanking folks
Facilitated
Push my back into a corner where I have to get it done tattoo
Cute
So first of all Riley thank you so much you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
You are now a policy wonk
How one
Not 9000
Wright's how many houses are there
Apparently
Next Chris
Thank you so much you're now policy walk
Chrissy the ccs-r conspiracy
You're not about to walk
Get donations
Just pick a name and then everybody with that name
Yeah that seems to be working with Chris's
Thank you so much and I apologize
Next Molly
Thank you so much you are now a policy wonk
Untold aspect
Grinnell policy wonk
Untold aspect this last one I'm not sure if it's madku
Okay coop
Leisure But whichever it is thank you so much you are now policy walk
Or Co-op dead be like the Mad Hatter but it's a guy who makes barrels
Ultimate Koopa
Cooperative
Right
Great grocer
I wanted to do is also a
I feel like in the spirit of tying up loose
Very bad at taking care of business
Outside of just
Doing this
So one of the things we're getting this tattoo
Squared away get it taken care of
And something else I've been meaning to do and I have been
Just terrible
As I promised that we would have a
Play special drop
For the creator of our theme song
So very much
Like this is just the best
The theme song
Rave reviews across the board from everybody and it's
Shameful
Edit taken me this long but one
I'm very bad at this stuff at organization
And forgetting you like all right I'm going to get
Does drop together and I just
Is never do by sat down
Taking care of it today
So here is a special drop
Thank you DJ
Of Leo Young
Of the podcast
I love dolphin
Tigers
Machine
Prayers
Have ordered a Hitler uniform
The freeways were maybe four but
This is what they teach Integris
The official
Leo Young
Incredible thank you very much
So Jordan today what we're doing is we're going back to the past 2013 we will be
Talking about April 21st
22nd 23rd
Okay this is of course in the aftermath of the Boston bombing
Kobe
Survive tracking the course
The valix is terrible
Full coverage
The traumatic event
I think he's been doing okay so far
It's an interesting take
Directly counter to my position literally the worst job possible
I think if you asked me what could he be like what are
Ruin it further
Yeah what are you got opposite of like
What are
Where to go to the bright spot
I would look at you very
I don't know if there are any
So here we are Jordan Alex in 2013 he was coming down from behind he was writing
When there was a complete absence
The real information about the investigation into the Boston bombing
He was free to create his own narrative wholesale
After the Watertown shootout on the night of April 8th
The morning of April 9th
Which left tamerlan dead and his brother johar armed and on the loose
I want to show on the 19th was a
Completely bizarre
Up to that point he been in
System that the globalist plan to blame a white Patsy
You discovered by looking at pictures that he found out 4chan
But because Alex released those photos
The globalist were forced to change their plan
Then after the FBI released the images of the Tsarnaev Brothers
Alex pivoted the narrative
Since all the stuff he's been yelling about 4 days with literally no relation
Anything happening in the real world
Now the globalist plan all along have been to blame the imaginary Navy
Besitos
Alex also decided where they're at the
Where is not based on his analysis
Again
4chan
And sent Alex also somehow blue the up that
Plan of the globalist sad
They were putting Boston into a state of Martial law so they could go around and kill all the Patxi's
Who are the pictures that again Alex found on 4chan so they could get these people
They were cleaning up couldn't reveal that it was all the drill
Yes all of this has been confirmed is true
On the 19th
I'm magically just like that Alex has created a preemptive
Excuse for why no one has ever come out and confirm his dump
The globalist took them all out
As we've discussed already those men in the pictures that Alex found on 4chan that he thinks are seals
Are actually members of a couple of different states National Guard
Civil support
Goron seen it all large-scale public of
Events ranging from one of the largest marathons in the world
All the way down to just MLB
If you wanted to put the effort in the bottom of this list
I hope it's a smaller scale maybe than the Boston Marathon
Alright
If you want me to put the effort in you could almost certainly figure out who these
People are and find evidence
To them still being alive and working with their siesta
I'm not saying that I did that but I am saying if I did I would still respect their privacy you never
Augusta personal
Only show on the 19th Alex
Seems to have a keen awareness that is normal incitement Laden Behavior may be way too dangerous to engage
Why what city is in the middle of a large-scale map
That's not the time to call on citizens to rise up
Because it's the time when it's most likely to be taken
And seriously by the most unhinged of his list
Alex took a very strange approach and barely even talked about the Boston being in a shelter-in-place request
About how an MIT police officer had been murdered the night before
But how there been a shootout in a residential neighborhood
If you didn't know that these things are happening
You would not learn about that by listening to that days
Infowars episode
I can tell you that very
You learn about how Stewart Road there's a baby about permit
And how Larry Pratt hates most
That's about what you like
Better for everybody
So the 20th is a Saturday
So now Alex has no show on
Saturday or Sunday the 21st
By that point the situation is largely result
To get us up to speed on what's happened
Here we go
In the very early morning of the 19th Governor Deval Patrick put out a shelter in place
Request ask
The people to stay indoors to help police better carry out there man.
At no point is this Adam and
And it's not enforced by any coercion or any Force
Mass transit the temporary says temporarily suspended in the city
A Massachusetts National Guard is called into sis police
In carrying out door-to-door searches and targeted areas
As the day drags on though
The authorities
Keep coming up empty
At 2 p.m. that evening Red Sox game is
And by 4:30 p.m.
The command center is starting to wonder if there's any point in May
Maintaining the shelter in
Replace request
They've done their sweep and they haven't found johar and they're beginning
Keep the perimeter
At 5:30 p.m. service resumes on mass transit
And at 6
45pm the shelter-in-place request is lifted
Then
17 minutes later
At 6:42 p.m. the police get a 911 call from someone who lived it
C7 Franklin
Tell him that there is a bleeding man hiding in his boat
We just parked out in his yard
Gotcha
He did not notice those boats
It seemed to have been tampered with previously because he'd stayed indoors
Honoring the shelter-in-place request
After the request has been lifted he went outside to get some air
I already noticed that things weren't right
He looked under the tarp
Install person
Police immediately jump into action and they form a new perimeter around this
At 6:54 p.m. police fire on the boat but they're
Quickly told to
C-spire
The officer who shot at the boat did not have proper authorization
But you saw motion
And as the suspect was thought to be armed and don't be willing
Fire at least the last time I encountered him
You made a very bad assumption that he was about to be fired on
And then there's that sort of phenomenon
Contagious virus
Police
Hear someone shooting and one of the main points of the
After Action Report which is we need better weapons discipline
No it's it's a common
Joking
So many things were so
Some guy will fire off his machine gun and then 30 guys go off in the Commanders
Jesus Christ what are you guys doing
Yeah there's a phenomenon
Wasn't play
I almost an hour later the police place a flash bags but they're ineffective in getting suspect
About
Negotiators came in to try and convince him
Surrender and that strategies pretty ineffective as well really want I really want to caution everybody
Maybe we should start with negotiator and then go to flashback
You know the order of those should be reversed
That's its angle that I think you can take
And I would it like being
Instead if that was Alex's
Perspective but he doesn't
He doesn't seem to
Not positive even if you look at all of it that someone didn't
Like try and get him out of the boat before this was professional
What's bigger 2/3 to know is that it the rock paper
Scissors game
Boat beats flashbang
That's not always not always
So ultimately johar does leave the boat at 8:41 p.m. answer
Surrenders to the pool
The nightmare of the city's been living in for about 4 days
Come to an end
Four people are dead and wanted suffered injuries that will lead to his eventual death
And hundreds are in
Callous people's lives have been changed in ways they will be a
Impossible to quantify your numbers but at very least
The suspects are dead or in custody
And the people of Boston
Can can breathe easily
And begin the difficult process of rebuilding and
And healing
But that can also wait until the morning
That night people flooded the streets in Celebration
More less formal
Flash mob
Decompress and release their tent
College students got drunk and yelled USA in large groups
More adult bostonians gathered to applaud and thank the law enforcement officers were putting themselves on the line to catch
Call Britt
Watching the footage now even six years later
Later the feeling of unity in that
Catharsis
Palpable
By the time Alex gets on are the afternoon of April 21st
The chaos is over
The Manhunt is complete
The temporary deployment of the Massachusetts National Guard has come to an end
The city of Boston had already announced the memorial.
The victims and survivors
Plant to be placed in
In Copley Square
The suspects are no longer on the Run
And the details of the actual investigation
Took place over the preceding
6 days
Are starting
To become
The cement has dried but Alex has managed
Make a hellacious
Anton the surface and
As we jump back in here we'll see Alex entering the neck
Next phase
It is conspiracy building operation
When there was no information available he knows that he needs to lay the groundwork for his narrative
He does this by immediately insisting the event as a false flag
Displaying a
Confident knee-jerk defiance
The draws people in nubes take that confidence
Does big basin
Some kind of a wisdom or rebellious
As any information is come out
He's worked integrated into his narrative
And that's important
In this stage that we've been looking at so far
He doesn't adapt his narrative to match
Reality
He distorts reality to conform to his narrow
That Family Guy episode was actually about a tea party guy who joins the Taliban
That shifting reality to match
His narrative
CNN announcer
50 arrested been made not because they got bad information
But because they were scared of Alex
His coverage of the
Pictures
Downtown Fortune
The courthouse in Boston was evacuated not because of a bomb scare
But because Alex blew up their plan so they had to
Switch out there Patsy
Everything that Alex has been doing
Serves to use his overarching explanation
That this was a false flag that the globalists are not right
A cover-up to make sense of everything that happens that mites
I'm confused
Because of the absence of
Information
It's their rhetorical equivalent
A miracle pill
The cures
That he's trying to sell
That one weird trick for proper
Right now
Now that the suspects are in custody or dead Alex has to change
The next stage
Conspiracy building
We're just discrediting every piece of information that comes out about the official suspect
Send the story surrounding their crime and arrest
This is still somewhat aimed at distorting reality to fit his narrative
But it's also
Hasn't necessarily involves the opposite as well
There will be elements of reality that he just
Can't pretend aren't real
So in order to keep this going he does have to fine-tune his narrative along the way
There's a little bit of this
The shift to saying
They plan to blame the
Lucille's
That's an attempt
To jettison the white Patsy narrative
As being relevant to the conversation
And it all because
It's not
That's him shifting his narrative in order to better suit
The fact that are coming out
Are there two elements with Alex
She's doing that I buy
Find more lyric
I'd like to
Just say up front
The first is that this what
What this is doing is specifically in-service of creating an alternative
Alternative reality
Did Alex that makes money
It's profoundly disrespected
Full to the victims in
Survivors of the attack
As well as the larger community of Boston
He's taking their pain and anxiety and trying to turn
The Profit which is up
Abhorrent
The other thing is that if Alex has his way
He's trying to get johar's rnav off the hook for the bombing
Now in 29
It's very easy for me to say that I have literally zero doubt about johar's scale
It's been very well substantiated both by hard evidence
Circumstantial evidence
And his uncoerced
Confession and apology
There's a concrete reality
And it's that johar and tamerlan Tsarnaev committed this bombing
Alex is working
As hard as you can
Create a reality
We're either they didn't do it or they
Because the government was you
Which serve to shift culpability more than a little bit
In a very concrete and realsense
Alex Jones
Right now as we're looking at him in 2013
Is making money by doing damage control for terrorist
Sometimes it's easy to lose sight of that but
You say that with all this judgment
It's easy to lose sight of that sometime so I just wanted to start off this
Episode by bringing
Sharp Focus
And in this first clip we start
Toosii
Kitty is making a bunch more money off
Well ladies and gentlemen entire team
Has an incredible responsibility
Infowars.com
Quite a responsibility
We'll see how that plays out.
Greater
Careful this or attention to detail
Christy is going to
Increase his acting responsible responsibility comes great profits
I mean is traffic is up 10
On time so like
He's gotten to that point by
Sort of mirroring amplifying bulshit on the internet
And sensationalising and lying about an ongoing
So why not
That up
Market tests
At work
It's
It's just that
It's that thing where it's at
See that
Humanity
What are we doing
The idea that
In the absence of real information
Alex Jones
Makes 10
Great
Great Humanity we're doing good stuff just to be fair it's not
Concrete that it's 10 times as much money I would have definitely
Could be
So Alex
All of the
Stop his happy
Pandora
So Alex
Nose
The main
Beats
Of the resolution of the Manhunt all of this
And so he gets to talkin
About
Johar getting
Taken in by the police
And him
Coming out of the boat
Critical condition
So none of that ended up happening
So that's cool
Prescription privileges for amnesia pills for healthy on everyone
Doctor's kit that is ice
Is the special when I was James Bond license to kill every globalization license for halcyon
Alright fair enough
Every single time there's some high-profile event Alex immediately says the person who's arrested for Disney
Can be drugged-up usually on housing
It's a very important piece
Strategy because as long as he
Consistently argues that arrested terrorist
Drugged up
It doesn't matter if they confess their crimes
No matter I know do piece of actual evidence that they're guilty can
Penetrate this can
Conspiracy theory
Anything the police say is just a cover-up of the false flag
Anything the perpetrator says is just a result of them being drugged by the globalist to cover up the false flag
It's basically an insurance policy for his narrative that you needs to invoke whenever a suspect is not killed during the arrest
Leave aside for a moment that when
Someone who's suffering from a mental illness is incarcerated
UB Pro
Soundly in human
To not give them appropriate care
Including appropriate site
Evaluations
Just needed and also if needed medication
Where Alex is brainwashing an evil drugging the reality is generally just
Getting psychotic people on anti-psychotic medication
So they can ethically be put on trial
Yeah
Yeah it is it is just inhuman to watch
Somebody with a very
Serious
Mental illness
Spew their nonsense
Into the f******
Like if your
In his family are married to her
The same place
He does if you'd
If you keep a man from getting the medication that he needs to live a
Woolrich healthy
Play life you know I think
It's very trouble
So this tracheotomy argument that Alex is making
He was all the rage in
Conspiracy communities in the days after this
Stressed I guess what it largely traces back to an article that Alex posted on Infowars
The basic gist of this conspiracy is that after johar had surrendered
The police gave him a throat injury so he couldn't speak
And that's not blow the whistle about how he was being set up
Of course this Theory doesn't take into account he was still perfectly able to write
As he did as he was being questioned immediately by law enforcement
He was at the hospital
In October 2018 court filings were made public
Included 79 page
The johar had made Ian written while he's being questioned by the police
On notebook paper he wrote
Lawyer
And quote
Listen buddy I know my rights no one is at risk no bombs no one will die
Yes the police quote is my brother alive
A number of Thai
In a moment where he seems to be acknowledging his own guilt
He says quote
We're at War my
When he's discussing the US military presence
Iraq and Afghanistan
Even says quote America is at war is it not I did what is nessus
My people are dying
Other notes seem to be clearly indicating that he
He's telling the police that this was a conspiracy of two
Quote no one else was involved
Quote only
He knew
Quote my brother and I
Quote we told no one
He pleads for them not to arrest tamerlan's wife who swears had no idea what they were plan
Whatever would have been achieved by Alex
Conspiracy theory of the police injuring johar's neck would not have mattered at all
It's not like he was scheduled to do a press to a writer
After getting arrested and now couldn't be
Because he couldn't talk
The ultimately might not have been able to speak
But he was perfectly able to communicate
A box
Also
You was able to speak again by April 22nd
First preliminary hearing
Which isn't Stark opposition to Alex's narrative
Which is that johar may never be able to speak again
It is trial in 2050
Joe Hart
The standings of the
The following
Quote immediately after the bombing which I am guilty
If there's any lingering doubt about that let there be no more
I did it
I did do it
Get a hard dude
Do-it-yourself
Most of his trial was about how
Tamerlan was born
I did it along with my brother
I learned of some of the victim
I learned their names their faces their age
And throughout this trial more of those victims were given
More of those victims had faces
And they hit burden
Insoles
Who got up on eyewitness
And that Podium related to
To me I was listening
The suffering
That's how I was
And the hardship that still is
With strength with patient
With dignity
Now Allah says in the Quran that no soul is burdened
With more than it can bear
And you told us just how him unbearable it was how horrendous it was
Does this thing I put you
And I know that you kept that much
I know that there isn't enough
Time in the day for you to have related
I also wish for more people had a chain
To get up there but I took them
Now I'm sorry for the lives I've taken for the suffering that I've caused
For the damage that I've done
Irreparable damage
I ask Allah to have mercy upon
Me and my brother and my
I asked a lot of bestow his mercy upon those present
I'm here today
And Allah knows best with the
Best those deserving of his Mercy
He may have pled not guilty initially but his defense never really even tried to say that
Didn't do the bombing
Anyway about that naked
When police apprehended johar he was pretty Bang
He been in a shootout with the police the night before and then was inside that boat when officers were shooting at it
Not to mention the flashback
In the process of that he suffered some serious injuries
According to the trauma surgeon who attended to him when he arrived at the hospital Doctor Steven Ray Odom
Quote he has multiple gunshot wounds the most severe of which appears to have entered through the left side of his mouth
An exit at the left face
Lower face
This was initially thought to be a self-inflicted wound a botched
Suicide
But he didn't have a gun in the boat
So the more likely explanation is that it's
Stray shot happened and it was remarkable that he survived
Dr. Odom said that the injury cause damage to his pharynx
Which was treated in the hospital including
Help of a trach tube
That was done
At the hospital
Not on scene
No one would do that outside the boat it wasn't it wasn't like
Helpful doctor on a plane is like it'd be a pain and stab the guy with the throat
Alex's conspiracy hinges onto photos from the scene of the
One shows johar standing approaching the police surrender
The other shows Medics attending to him with his neck appearing to be wrapped in gauze
According to Alex
The first picture shows no wound
And the second picture is of them treating a wound
Therefore the police must have
Closed wound to silence johar
In reality the first picture of Zohar standing is very poorly lit
The entire left side of his neck is
Completely and Shadow
Other photos from the same release of images show johar and much better lighting
And that side of his face is almost completely covered in blood
The one image where the left side of his face is
Obscured by shadow
Look pretty suspicious
But if you look at all available images that argument falls apart is very
I like the idea of a person who is willing to accept
2 images
Is as all the proof you need
Call it a day guys with a wrap it up I got two pictures that's all I need
Many conspiracy theorists use that second photo of a neck wrapped in gauze as proof that the police are putting a tube into
JoJo Hearts throat at the seeds
And that's absurd just shows police using an assisted breathing man
Which is non-invasive
Everything that's provided as being suspicious here is exactly what you would expect to see you please
Encountered The Suspect with a wound
That was potentially
A Gabrielle
They are performing first
Sade
None of this is real at all it's based on out of context
Android soon as manipulative photos
They point so strongly
To the one with his face in
Shadows
I'd like you don't see any wound
So anyway if you if you dump
A bunch of photos
You don't get there should be a law that you don't get to
Somebody if somebody just uses to and drowsy
Conclusion it's like
Another fine
Find
You got yet that's a good indication they might
So that's one of his big ways to attack these
Nah that's why they put a tube in
Silence of a mediately
Part of the new
Strategy
The new
Manifestation of the
So now they've killed all of the Patxi's
Except for their final Patsy
Who they
We didn't succeed in killing but they wanted to kill him but Brett shelter-in-place order was rescinded
Media was able to see Sarah
Alex
Right
Yeah.
So this is
This is fun
This part isn't this next clip is actually like
All a lot of these are just dumb
Stupid and probably
Dangerous lies
This one is kind of fun
So much for joining us
Where should I start I start with this article out of a Hollywood Reporter
Red Sox player
He spoke from the Heart video
Emotional
But
Okay
But you cannot be so we're done anybody else
Program
As American As baseball and apple pie
Over at Grandma's house
If you're in the Gateway
Active enforcement
So in their first number one story out of Boston April 21st
Get the number one story out of the way and then we'll get to the H2 news whatever that may be
Hey this is how he like this
That's a good indication of him taking Like These Boots
Kind of like
Trivial issues
I'm trying to make them super important went like hey
The Boston bombing is resolved
But hold on
David Ortiz gets to say f*** it I don't I got to bleep it or I spent five hundred bucks or whatever
What about Janet Jackson's nipple where are we on that Dan
So in their first game back at Fenway Park the Red Sox are set to play the Kansas City Royals on April 20th
Before the game it felt appropriate to address the crowd
Because they had to cancel the day days before in the
Said he was in the state
And as David Ortiz is something of an elder Statesman
He was asked to say a few words
He thanked the governor and the police then said quote this is our f****** City
Nobody is going to dictate our freedom
Stay strong
Q2 the crowd going
I have no civic pride but I would be there being like
You get you get that one
Big Papi didn't get in trouble for this
Even though his comments were broadcast on live t
In fact the head of the FCC
See Julius Janikowski
Beat It Out quote
David Ortiz spoke from the heart today at the Red Sox game
I stand with Big Papi in the people of Boston
God can you imagine if the FCC really turned
The entire United States at her that no matter how much you hate bad language they heard that without
And that's like by like
My position is who gives a s***
Call Bob
So there's a very good reason
Beyond just be horrible Optics of like trying to find a more but they decided not to fine
One of them is at the game was being broadcast on cable
Which is outside the jurisdiction of the FCC
The game is also hearing on the radio
So they could have hit him with a fine for that but there's another Elam
Went to the story
If it's important
Previous to the bombing
Julius genachowski I put in his resignation
Can I be head of the fcr the doors
Phuc yea
Passionate expression of solidarity in the aftermath of the tragedy
I put in my two weeks whenever you f****** want
It's like okay so somebody take over the FCC in like a month or like you wanted
Go back
And do you have fun
So Bleacher Report did an oral history of the speech Ortiz gave
And here's what Janikowski said
I knew there would be people who saw that he'd use the F-word on the airwaves and would ask
Mio's that a violation of the FCC Rule and is the FCC getting punished at
That's an editorial tone of voice but
My first thought was no f****** way we're going to party stuff
In the same oral history David Ortiz says what he remembers the head of the FCC telling
Yeah
It was like
Look you said something that got this city moving
Forward it took the fear out of people
You have no idea what you just said
That's going to be in the history of New England forever
It was right when we needed
Don't worry we needed that at
Yeah you know what he also said
My last Act is not going to be the guy who find David Ortiz wrestling f*** yeah after
We caught the Boston Bomber I'm going down in history
After days of being on edge a terrifying 24 hours of this uncertain Manhunt at the city was allowed to breathe
The collective sigh of relief
Relief is good
And what David Ortiz did is hit a pressure release button
Providing a rallying cry
And no one not even the sensory sfcc
Couldn't see
At this moment was important
For so many people
Equal measures of rebellious and reassurance
It was
Big Papi would end up hitting a grand slam to tie game to the alc champions
Boston playoff playoff hopes alive that year ultimately leading them to win the World Series
Authorities taking home the owners of World Series MVP
It's really the stuff of Fairy Tail
And anyone who can appreciate the 2013 Red Sox
Is either a complete monster
Or just a die-hard yang
Yeah whatever still salty about not winning the World Series in 2001 after 9/11
God that would be
That's the only thing you could have done one thing
That's the day after 9/11 come out and then lie
Like fuk you terrorist I would have been like well at least we got one on the board
Said it was s*** all at all
From start to finish
Well I mean you just imagine a scenario where like I don't know a month after 9/11
You got
A-Rod
What's on the Yankees
Jeter comes out
I don't think
You know I understand the idea of selective enforcement being bad
But you also got to understand
Come on
Come on come on
Grow up
Tell Alexandra is is pretty much
I'm not anti profanity but
Or I just get mad all the time
Whenever I get back
Piss
Alex thinks that this selectively enforce
Signing Derek
David Ortiz
Is tyranny
Because any kind of selective
Enforcement is here
This is the essence of things are selectively enforced
Drunk spitting
Driving on the wrong side of the road
I empathize with that Alex is saying about selective enforcement but I also think that there's room for understanding
Extenuating
If you excuse was just David Ortiz was emotional like Alex is trying to preserve
You know is if you just hit a game-winning home run
Really think that excuses a little bit soft
Given that he was just asking
To speak before the first Red Sox game back after
The city was terrorized by bombers
I think it's probably okay to enforce obscenity laws a little selectively in that case
How to get my advice
Italics grow up
Yeah the only thing you don't get to say is
Man I wish that bomber was still free like you don't get to say that one after the other
The bigger rich
Now about this Austin
District attorney
Alex is talking about a woman named Rosemary
Who was arrested for drunk driving on April 12th after her car veered into a bike lane then into oncoming traffic
Allegedly
The officer pulled her over so an opened vodka bottle in the passengers
So this was what you call and open it
Chuck case
According to an article in the Austin Chronicle the officer wrote in his affidavit
Thought you was quick cooperative
Impolite
Which seems counter to Alex
Does characterization
The day after her arrest
She wrote letters to the county attorney and the court and said that you would plead guilty
Expected No Lie
According to a later Chronicle article she was sentenced to 45 days in jail and lost her license for 180 days
She also had to pay a $4,000 fine which is
The highest fine allowable for a DWI
She was charged with
That's a form of BWI
The strictness of the punishment is for
Piccalilli notables
First offense
I gets very harsh
Spotify
Kind of uncommon if you don't
Kill somebody or hurt somebody
To get any jail time
Time for a first of
DUI this was a this was like a statement
Nobody is above the
And she kind of asked
Yeah because
Recognize they would send a bad message we have to make us all look at
Aboveboard we have to do the whole thing
Never said that you was above the law and neither did she
They just felt that a DWI
Something that you should get thrown out of office for particularly when you take
Responsibility for your actions
All the details Alex's rattling off particularly her spitting on people is not
Substantiated
Video from Lambert's arrest has been released and I won't lie it's not a good look
But it's not too different from Hope just about anybody would be after getting arrested for a DWI
She's trying to talk her way out of it being a little bit rude to
The police but
That crazy
I would imagine a lot of people would look
Way worse
If you had video of them getting arrested
And still kind of drunk
Alex is using allegations that were put out against lumbered by her.
The enemies who were trying to user. I DWIs way to get her out of office
Then Governor Rick Perry which I use the DWI to try to get her
Step down threatening that if she
Yeah he would be fun
Her office
She refused he funded her office and then Perry got indicted by a grand jury for trying to coerce a public official to resign
Wait are you saying that you can't do that
Sequence of events
Play something that is enshrined in our constitution should be able to dishonestly and in Bedford
Precious
Did doing what you want in a public office
Perry fought the indictment and after he ended up leaving office all charges against him weirdest
Anyway this whole thing is a big two-sided
On what side you had a dat who got caught drunk driving last out a little bit then apologized and submitted herself to the process
Is it making things right
It's always wrong to drive drunk but if you do
And learned your lesson it's the best possible outcome
Short of not doing
On the other hand you had a
A concerted effort to blow the DWI out of proportion
And use it as a political weapon
To get a Democrat out of office
We see which side Alex's
Is just Towing
The GOP line
Trying to get a Democrat
APA RV
You know it's not that I don't want to say that it's blowing the event its
Tell about a proportion
I think DUI DWI
Very very serious
Like I don't think they're blowing it out of proportion I think they're using it in
Disingenuous and
Dishonest
I think we're saying the same thing
I agree
Maybe your phrasing
Yeah I just don't like that like
Blowing Auto it's just a DUI you know that guy I know trying to minimize
She's cleaning
Fair enough
So Forbes apparently has written an article
And he's not happy about it
They don't like us conspiracies
You have
Americans love
And you know what are police martial law
Lockdown
I don't get on your house I will shoot you
Important point
No point
Was there an understanding that if you come out of your house you'll be
That is absurd
That it isn't it was a voluntary shelter in place
Request because they believed like okay yeah
I understand like if you work some job you don't want to go into
Perfect excuse.
Pigtails
Most people
It's okay was it like a year later they did the Poland reference our last episode those 83
Still supported they behaviors
A year after the fact
You know that's that's that's like a
Casualty
You don't offer
Something about with Alex
He just can't
Be happy he can't be happy they caught the terrorist and you can't be happy
Because even care
Catching it is proof that they're still more work for us to do
Are there still lying to us or all that
Cancel
There is no wind
Except the imaginary win over imaginary and
They will never come
So if you said that last clip at this is martial law and he's
Some more about that
Your house
Exercising flag on the Republic
Posse Comitatus
Okay
So what happened in April on April 19th in Boston has all the opt
Necessary for Alex to call it martial law
And some very important points.
But he does not care to recognize
The first is as I've mentioned all the law enforcement action
Door-to-door searching the Dragnet
The shelter-in-place request
We're done by the state government through appropriate
All of Alex's martial-law fears involve the Federal
It specifically
FEMA
The situation doesn't match any of his tyranny fantasy
Cease at all
The second important aspect of this was very 10
Temporary thing
Alex always talks about martial law coming in and staying in
It's not just a couple hours when an armed guy who's already killed a cop and bombed the marathon is on the loose and unknown area
For the situation to match analysis paranoid fantasies
They would need to have not caught johar and kept the city and martial law in the state of
The fear that's not what happened
Finally
Most basically and most important
This was not Marcia
This is important to point out because the way Alex uses that term
Losing any meaning
But martial law is a real thing
It has defining characteristic
So let's discuss a few of
The first
Is suspension of civil rights
This did not happen in Boston in the aftermath of the bombing
No one's rights under the Constitution
Duchenne of Bill of Rights
Suspended
Habeas corpus was still in play
They did resegregate the
Schools during that lockdown
That was a really weird and not
Is a really weird day
They
Brought back probation and I got rid of it again
And then brought back a second time
The second characteristic is military coup
Control of civilian
This did not happen in Boston
Massachusetts National Guard were allowed
For taking policing activities at the order of the governor
Wheatley const
I think we're not in charge of normally civilian governmental rolls
The chain of command and governmental structure remains
I done changed
From how things were on April 4th
Before the bombing
The third feature
Is civilian being tried in Military Tribunal
This did not happen in Boss
They're plenty of examples from history of actual martial law and what happened looks
Nothing like the
And here's the thing that Alex whenever address
It's the most crucial thing
Like I said
No one had to
Stay inside their home
Is merely request the governor made
There's no punishment they would face they left their home
There's a bunch of pictures you can find that other people have posted of that day highlighting the Eerie emptiness of the city
But if you look at those pictures
They all are almost all of them have people walking around
There's the shelter-in-place was entirely voluntary most people felt
Made sense
To stay inside
This is not
You could have just said we're doing a Citywide Manhunt
Most of the city have been like
Cool
Hey there's some cartoons on
Dislike
Categorically what he what happened in Boston is nothing
Close to Marshall
And the way Alex uses that term cheapens the reality that martial law is a real thing and it's a f******
Scary Prospect
In 2019 there are literally people calling for things that are characteristics of martial law
And they're all Trump's
So I I just like
The reason I think this is important to like look at some of the
These defining characteristics
Martial law is Alex's brand is mr. martial law
And the way he uses that
Term is so not
Correct
Deserves it deserves a little bit of a foe
I mean the the
They
Secretary of Defense did appoint lieutenant colonel
Kincaid Topeka
Comptroller
Boston
So there is a little bit of a military
Examples from American history like
Chicago Fire
Like that that that was actual martial law military took over
That's crazy
Anton
Sure that
Sometimes it's not done in a way that's to oppress
The citizens B
It looks
Without what what happened to God
Score cheap
I did there
There's no way that you
It's one of those things where you can throw around
This is martial law all you want but
Listen through it is like
Probably not
So Alex has decided of course that there was a drill going on
Marathon which he has failed to really establish
One of the ways that
He uses that to
Approved
Was a false flag
Because these other time
Games in the past when there have been drills
That was also false
One of the ones that he brings other we haven't really disgusting
Detail is the seven
7 bomber
And Alex
Discusses house that was a drill in this
Next clip and then I'm very excited to explain to you what he's
He's actually talking about
Okay how full of s*** this guy
SWAT
2000s
I cannot stress this
Alex thinks that everything
Every major event in the world is orchestrated by the globalist to that take the
These drills make
Then go live in order to cause chaos and push their agenda
Every single one
In case the Boston bombing Alex has been making frequent references
The 7/7 bombings
London and how there was a
The drill that same
As a way to strengthen his argument that the Boston bombing was a false flag as proven by the drill they were having that day
As we discussed on the April 15th episode there's no evidence
There was any kind of a drill
The marathon
There's some indication that there was a crowd to see
Cessation exercise happening
Police dogs
Alex has taken that turned it into their being a bombing drill going on with literally no evidence
Except a couple pictures you found on 4chan
I waited a while to discuss the 77 stuff because there were more pressing
But now I feel like it's a real good time
Touch on this issue
And how foolish it
On July 7th
4 terrorists
Detonated bombs
Three of them in the underground train
And a fourth on a double-decker bus
Killing 52
It was a horrible attack
The deeply traumatized
That same day after the bombings
A man named Peter power
Who ran a company called visor
Consultants went on BBC and said that he'd been working on a drill that involved simultaneous bombing
At the same stations that the attacks
I taken place
From that
Alex and Paul Joseph Watson began spinning a conspiracy
It what happened is that these girls were being
Carried out by this consulting firm
And the global
And in the middle of the event things went hot and the bombings
They were the leaders
Honest Theory and we're largely responsible for it
Dissemination
And they did literally
0 fact-checking research
At all
Oz article on the supposed drill says that they were quote running a 1000 person strong exercise which
Drill D London Underground being bombed at the exact
Locations
The exact same time
As happened in real life
This is obviously meant to tell the reader that there were a thousand people involved in this drill to test
The response to
Obama
However this is a complete lie
And they would have held that if they reached out to mr. power
Or look into this anyway
Before deciding on a narrative
Here's a power actually say
Quote
And 9:30 this morning we were actually running an exercise for a company of about 1,000 people in London
Based on simultaneous bombs going off
Precisely at the railway station
Where it happened this morning
The Thousand person number was how many people worked at
The company for whom he was doing
The presentation
And there was a very low likelihood that all of them were even in his session
His lecture that he
This was a corporate seminar the power was presented
There were no people in
Streets there were no there was nothing other than a sin
Scenario in a PowerPoint presentation
Coincidence
People who have looked into Peter power of suggest
He was doing a little bit
Self-promotion
And this BBC presentation
Scenario did not
The events of the 7/7 bombings but it's
His business is best
To make it appear that the corporate risk
Lectures
But he gives all his clothes to
Prophetic is possible
That this is it
This is the drill that Alex
Approved the 7/7 bombings
Was a false flag
And attention-hungry corporate like
So this dude is on a self-promotion grift
And then he's used by right-wing propaganda grifters
In order to f******
Facilitate more terrorism
Cool cool interact otter incomplete
How cynical Alex and Paul Joseph Watson
There's literally no way they can keep doing this and have no idea that they're complete fraud
Can you imagine a Trane Macon
Like Alex getting on Aaron trying to argue that the bombing was fake because the guy was given the risk
Assessment seminar that its similarities to the bombing
Can you imagine it being straight up with the audience about this alleged to grill not being anything
Involved the police
Operatives or anyone on the
The street and only existed as a PowerPoint presentation
He never do it
Because he's a liar
All terrorist acts begin this PowerPoint presentation
We all know this
I've I've seen the Isis materials
They don't use Keynote
They try it at the very beginning but it just
That you couldn't pay it
Long enough so they
The Powerpoints
It's it's a very complicated
They still used
Sherp
I can't find the article that I was referencing when he says that are experts as The Mastermind of the 7/7 bombings
MI6
I searched Infowars website and I found a blurb about the
Relation to Guy on Fox
Snooze saying that Haroon Rasheed a SWAT
May have worked with British intelligence in the 90s
In Bosnia
That may be true but it doesn't prove that he was ever or is still in ma-6a cited 2000
Five when the bombings happen
It certainly doesn't prove the
The bombings were false flag at all
Also Haroon Rasheed a squad was not one of the 7/7 bombers
Summer
Suggested that he was The Mastermind
But this absolutely
Has not been proven
Whether or not is what was the string puller of the 77 attack
Whether or not he worked with British intelligence 15
Plus years earlier in a regional conflict
None of that matters to the larger Point Alex's Baker
Those things
Can be true and not be evidence
But this was a false flag
That's possible
So I don't really care
The Central Point that he's making
About to disappear
Drill and his version of that is
Also I'll swap is not Saudi Arabian he was born in the United Kingdom
Prince family
So goodbye
But he's trying to leave in Saudi Arabia a little bit it's a little more hot in the Boston
Common conspiracy world
By the 21st
Inez Brown so nobody's going to look into it
I did
So there's another piece of information that has come out that is that Russia
The Russian intelligence
Had warned
The United States
It's about tamerlan Tsarnaev
Okay
So now this is going
Become a central piece
Of Alex's rhetoric
Years ago
By the way
5 years ago
I'm just giving you the information
Sure don't
Attaque 77
Prove
Anyway
It's more like
You know
Everybody that was around in the 80s and 90s
They worked with the FBI the CIA and then they became terror is it there
The 80s like the Iran-Contra and that whole thing was like The Velvet Underground for Terror
Inspiration everybody but everybody who started their own terrorist
You know what I'm saying
Interesting interesting metaphor
So on the question of whether or not Russia warned the United States about tamerlan Tsarnaev the answer is they definitely did
The FSB told us in March
2011 that tamerlan was associating with known terrorists extremists and we should keep an eye on him
This triggered an investigation carried out by the Boston joint terrorism task force
They interviewed tamerlan but they were unable to surveil him because they evidence
They had didn't rise
The legal standard
Kind of a measure
The FBI's memo of their about their interview
This is just like
Come on you can stare at him anyways we do it what are you doing with your laws come on
Write the FBI's memo about their interview with tamerlan has been really
And the interview took place on April 23rd 2011
The readout sounds like a pretty
Clear-cut interview following up on a tip
Russian intelligence
Was tamerlan discussing that he goes to mosque once a week
Has no connections or interest in radical Islamic ideas and
Respect people of all faiths
Open note in the memo that he tells
BFDI battle someone he knew was approached by four men who claim to be
FBI
Who wanted to talk to
They left no ID or way of contacting
And them and he hadn't heard from them since
This is definitely weird but it definitely doesn't
Necessarily follow that these people were actually FBI or even with the government
Some strong indications of come out that johar was selling drugs so tamerlan could have had some second or first-hand contact
Criminal element who might want to try to intimidate him
With that kind of a stunt there other
Explanation for what this could have been
The reason I strongly discount the possibility that these
People are FBI
Is it the report which
Was restricted to
Internal use only
These four guys as an unknown entity
It makes Pacific note at the end of the memo that tamerlan was open to report into the FBI if these men tried to contact
Overall your left of the impression that the FBI doesn't know anything about these for guys
Little idea who tamerlan
Norbit
I've been following up on this fsp
By June 2011 they've done whatever investigating
They could do and we're unable to find any links to
Terrorism
Precise measure the additive to a Customs and Border Protection
If you try to leave or enter the country
Two notes
In this database
The Timberland
And neither were effective in causing his
Attention when he flew from New York
To Moscow
In January 2012
And back
In July
The first note
It didn't
Consider him a high-priority Target
So on the day that you was traveling to Moscow
There were about 100 other names on the watch list
Authorities were detaining
Questioning
And as he was a lower priority the resources available were expended elsewhere and he was able to go
Get through
Stopped
By the time tamerlan returned
That original note
Ionic
Border Protection
Profile
Tyler whatever
That is expired
But a more severe Note have been made in the meantime which was still in effect
This was the result of the second warning
Mfsb
Would you like to tamberlyn being
Considered a very dangerous person
And made his
Attention Bandits
However the agent who wrote that S Note misspelled sarnath when they were entering him into the system
And that's when he tried to return
The country that July it didn't raise any alarms
This is the second time
In the case of
The story when proper data answering trouble
Man
That's
That's such a bummer such a f****** bummer
Instead of an a
Hey typed Annie
Now it's now it's a Boston
I mean it's not a one I know it's not a one-to-one but man as far as butterfly effect that goes that's got to be
Brutal
Brutal thought
So this is a lot being allowed to get back into the country is been the rude and some people speculating the tamerlan with an FBI
Informant and it bent
Clandestinely working
Infiltrate Muslim
Extremist communities
On behalf of the government
Sure
As the theory goes according to Michele McPhee
Facebook maximum harm
Chamberlain wanted to be a US citizen
Primarily so he could box
The Olympics but he was on an intelligible for that because he'd been arrested
Did for domestic violence
The FBI recruited him to be an informant
That's his ability to travel while I was on the list
In exchange for approving his
Citizenship app
Location
Overtime as the promises Edition
Citizenship never materialized
Timberland became angry
Ultimately contributing to embalming
True
Well it's an interesting Theory but it's just that
If there were proof I can probably engage with this a little bit further
In write-ups for the book
Makita even admits that this
This is just a theory
From a Daily Mail article quote McPhee's Theory
What she admits
She cannot definitively prove
Was that a lion was a federal informant and then he turned on America after it's
Application
It's all good and well David.
The possibilities that arise from that theory
But the way her writing was covered with a b e response
The claims that the FBI was handling Tamblyn
14 years I'll add the story
And the disclaimer that this is just what she believes and can't prove or second
Thought he regrets later isn't that crazy
Yeah
In terms of Alex's playing with the government it handled these brothers for five years that's just based on a claim by Tamela
Mother who was arguing for her son
So I don't take that to be all that
I mean she's got a
She's got some Skynyrd
Yeah it was a little bit further
Later on
So Alex talked about that
Clip
His belief
Sort of the thieves 4chan picture
But he had
I still like
Really at the center
You're the headlines group
Brothers
Boston mayor
Remember
Propepper
But weeds
So that's all
But outages reading headlines on drudge and this might be a good time to point out something super important that I think we don't bring up enough
That's how drudge Works how do I get to work to that he takes
Existing news stories in Lancaster
That's the primary function of
Recite but that's not why I said is one of the most popular in the right-wing news
His sight is number one with these dumb dumb
Because he rewrites headlines
It's the fifth and narratives that the right-wing pundits are already
Disseminating
He provides cover
In the former taking
Sensational stilted link headline
The people like Alex
Can just repeat
And I'll under talkingpoi
Credibility
Princeton
Let's take one of these headlines Alex
Cuz reading quote no doubt Brothers not acting alone
That was the link on drugs
Which takes you to an article from the international business
The actual article's headline is quote bossy
Marathon bombing
FBI hunts terrorist Sleeper Cell link to Tsarnaev Brothers
In this article the international busy
This time quotes an article in the Sunday Mirror which is
Itself quoting an anonymous source quote
3 investigation
The credibility of the sources
Was kind of a question because they say the bombs used at the marathon were quote highly sophisticated
I meant call agents
Sleeper Cell has up to a dozen members and he's been waiting several years for their day to come
Both of these details have been shown to not be
Which leads
We believe that the Sunday Mirror got some bad info
Which is that being reported in the
International business
Which is that being sensationalized by Drudge
So we could be more easily used by people like Alex
This is the information pipe
Judges basically like a word cloud
Yeah it's it's like
If you go to that and you unfocus your eyes you can
Can see all the
White right-wing propaganda
Live pulling out like
Like one of those
One of those pictures
Yeah one of those illusion
Andre like it the boat
Sure
So is the next blinds even worse
Two from Tajikistan encrusted
What country is he trying to say there
Is apogee Costanza
The actual countries talking about it
Which isn't even close to what he said
Dial Tajikistan is not Kazakhstan
Very different
Alex is talking about johar's to roommate
Who were taken in for questioning
Their ultimate Lee arrest
Students at the prison for
Justice as they had gone to johar's dorm room
And attempted to help him
Dispose of Evan
Including a laptop
And a backpack full of fireworks
There's no evidence
Them having any involvement of the planning or execution of the attack
Text but they did to make Rhymes to help your friend evade the law
They both did short stretches in jail and were deported back to kha'zix
When they were released
I don't think there's anything too suspicious about this but the way Alex's
Reporting this
That's a
I mean that's a good roommate I guess
Sure
I think I would have chosen
Different
Such as
I'm f****** out dude by
Yep
So we get
Along the way
Spinning his is Yarns about you know shohar was
Trached on the CN rail never be able to
The talk again right
It's just exhausting
Tiger
And we know see that Alex is starting to
To Pivot towards
God blaming Saudi Arabia
Right on San Jose California
The Weeknd
Canary current
Off the coast of Africa
The canary current
America
Hemisphere
Okay
Australia
So he's doing a little bit of a riff on like Saudi Arabia did something so now we're going to attack other people
Is working the weather
You like it it's not it's not great been foundering
So he's established that there was a drill at the marathon
And you'll just
See here how he tries to link it to the 77 drill
Pharisee
And as we
Disgust
I was PowerPoint
Location
That's not good enough ahead of Scotland Yard
He's not the head of Scotland Yard
Aspired
I've seen how they do this
Over and over again
When you know what he's actually talking about this just a
Appears to be
The saddest b*******
That clip is so like
Like it just
State you see it clearly
The scales fall from your eyes when you realize this drill that he's talkin about 77
Is it corporate
Like seminar a motivational speaker giving f******
Performance goal
On a t-shirt
He's pretending that it's like actually people out on the app in the in the train
And what have you I didn't like
You can't think it's a giant Improv Everywhere bombing
Yeah yeah
Urus
That bombing
You have
Noak
Excuse to not know
Vest
I understand the day of you just see the CNN
Interview with BBC interview with mr. power
You could you could get it in your head and misunderstand things and then the next day a correct yourself
Think about this
In order to reinforce other lies
You're telling
It's just so clear I love his exasperation with like
I've seen him do it so many times
You said they've done it so many times
You're boring
You've convinced yourself so many times
So Alex now knows that the FBI did talked
2 tamerlan
In 2011
So
He's convinced now
That when they put out those pics
Of the
And they didn't know who they were
And they needed the Public's help identifying them
They were lying
Boston Marathon bombers
The brothers
We don't know who they are
Are these people
Oh you don't know who your little project
That's not
Shown to be true and like I don't understand why this would be a compelling argument
Somebody doesn't think
Too deeply about things
Like they did talk to them in the past
How do they not know who they are how many f******
People do you think the day
Have
On their radar and 3 per year
This piece
Entire thing
With are you like fsbank check out this guy
Could have been handled by like
Two people
They might not remember 2 years later in Tire FBI went to his apartment they all gather
Weather in around they all took pictures they said remember this face
In case something happens to years from now it's very understandable that they would not
See him and be like aha I know who that is
If you want
Any episode of
F****** Forensic Files you like a
Every
Every goddamn police department has their own database of fingerprints they don't even it you don't even know if somebody's fingerprints are in there for
F****** yeah there they don't remember everything on file they were able to find that out
He was dead
Exact
They did already
You know taking him to the hospital
So I think that it's very reasonable to assume that the FBI
Might not know who they are
Even though they talked to him before I do not think
That is some
But look dude
Leaders do false
Just established
Good luck man
Hey
L do false Flags you need an example
Of course government
Declare martial law
Can people
So his first
Example is Emperor Palpatine
Right
His first
Example
Is
A kids movie
Yeah any second example
Is
Fake
History
Good stuff
Okay got you
So those are two concrete
Yeah absolutely
It's this bad work
Alex's
Buick more toward Saudi Arabia
And that's where the narrative
And pudding
Some sort of blame that Direct
What's interesting is that there's another guy
I was doing that to by the name of Glenn Beck
Glenn Beck is going
Hard
Yes particularly on the
The guy who the police question
He was one of the victim
Come to the bombing Saudi Arabia
That we talked about episodes back.
Left
The realm of Suspicion about this guy
You someone Glenn Beck is focusing
Not very
Closely
No and Alex's
Seahawk
Mileage out of that lets
Let's throw him into my boat
Yeah
Yeah you do a good job with that I don't think two something
Thing until it didn't
In the news
What is that mean
What is that
Meme I don't know
Like what does that mean
So while Alex has been a bit more
Scattershot with his coverage of the Boston bombing and it's been shifting
Theories to accommodate a whole bunch of different
Suspect
Same can't really be said for his mortal enemy Glenn back
In between back segments criticizing Alexandria piercing in
Comparison
Spending a lot of time working up a
Conspiracy theory of its own and it centered around that Saudi Arabian student injured at the bomb
I've been very
Consciously trying to
To not name
Can people who are caught up in this thing
Except when necessary
Particularly victims
Both the actual bombing and the propaganda surrounding it
I don't feel like they deserve to have their names attached to this tragic
And leaving them on named it something I consider a small Act of honoring their right to live a normal life
After this more misfortune
Seldom
When where we discussed the student
Texted him being questioned
I stuck to that Stan
But now that Glenn Beck is involved I need to get more
In the days after the bombing
Glenn said on his show that they'd uncovered information about a quote very bad bad bad man
Reclaimed was involved in
It seems like it's a universal trait that right-wing s******* broadcasters
Really think they're speaking directly to the government on their shows
Because Glenn made an ultimatum
Ultimatum to the government
If the government
I deal with this very
Batman appropriately
Play he would reveal them on his show
He called them quote the worst of the worst
And even appeared on Bill O'Reilly show.
Despite his accusations further
Naturally the government didn't respond to Glenn wanted so you kept
Does word and accused Abdul Rahman Al harbi
Of being
Money man
Facilitated the attack
And if given the quote go order for the attack
Al-harbi is the study student
Who was injured in
Glenn Beck for all the money there ever was
Glen claim to receive
This info from
But he refused to elaborate or reveal the sources
It's super important to point out though that by the time
Glenda is making these accusations on are the FBI already spoken to al-harbi and it publicly announced
Involved
They would publicly announce Dan
So naturally alharbi Sue Glenn back in 2014
Good going to argue that alharbi was a Publix
Figure which would provide summer
Undertaker f******
Sally down the street from me Mickey
Story about her put her on the news 24/7 and then yeah
She's technically a public figure to provide him some cover for irresponsible reporting
It's way harder to prove defamation against public figures
The judge had no time for that
Andrew B alharbi was absolutely a private figure
And returned
Decision saying that back had to disclose his sore
Naturally Glenn wasn't going to do that
So he paid an undisclosed amount to settle
It's tough to imagine what the amount he paid out was
Was considering the person he was paying with someone he'd accused of orchestrating a
Terrorist attack
But I'm certain he'd rather pay any price
Then haven't revealed publicly that he just makes up sources Annabelle edges
What they tell him
To an egregious degree
Covering that up is priceless
If that suited proceeded
There's little doubt in my mind you would have never been able to go on his dumbass I'm sorry tour after Trump was like
I can find no evidence of the Saudi student had a bunch of relatives were on terrorist list
It is true that there are number of people named alharbi on the side Arabian watchlist but I can find no actual proof that they're related to
To the student
There's a bunch of dumb blogs like
I am not ashamed of the gospel of Christ. Com
The only evidence provided is that they have the same surname
Also returning
If you did have relatives
They wouldn't do s*** to prove it he himself as a terror
Who's in the show supposed to be about individualism and reject the notion of guilt-by-association
This is the sort of s*** I would just bring it to the table
Citing evidence that alharbi is a terrorist based on information put out by his arch-rival with which ends up getting his arch-rival suit
And the rest was just dumb right-wing blogs
Also
A pretty fun revelation of this lawsuit is that we learned some of Glenn Beck's
Employees names
Which are pretty strong Arguments for nominative.
Or the idea that your name
Determines what you'll do in life
The president of the blaze at the time was named
Joel cheek
Wood
I'm going backs producer was named
Joe weasel
Really
God
Dammit be there not nicknames either
Full on
I am proud of the weasel named legal in Ohio
Literal weasel
Gotcha
Yep so Glenn Beck get sued for this I think Alex is probably on the outskirts
Getting himself name
Suit butt
You know
It's still what he's doing is
Is the same sort of behavior that led to
Back having to pay a bunch of money
So anyway Alex gets into the drill there was a drill
At the bombing
Not here yet
Witnesses on record track
It's just a drill
Everybody
That's the Funk
Turn of the drill everyone's got bags so don't own a car
This here's the thing
The ol Switcheroo rudan the old hide the forest
Inside the tree yeah
So here's the thing
All of the evidence that he's siding for it being a drill is
Imaginary or deeply and Bell
So it makes it
Tough for me to hear this next clip and think he's being
And there wasn't
All the Alex is saying there for reasons he thinks something
Suspicious is up here is they're all completely fake
The evidence that he has that there was a bombing drill is
Completely blown out of proportion and he absolutely can't even come close to proving what he's putting out
There isn't evidence of a drill they're just pictures of Civilian. Civil support team
That's an ultrasound on 410 and written a mystery novel about imagining that they're secretly Navy Seals
There wasn't a cover-up of a drill
They're just officials who have no idea what conspiracy
Bulshit is flying around on the internet
Let me know really interested in the dumb picture
Fortune not engaging with your conspiracy is not evidence of a cover-up
Johar wasn't
Tracheotomy to me
We is Alex's suggested
And even if you couldn't talk for a very poor
Free time you still able to communicate
Also he was able to talk with them daisies
Just couldn't talk while your throat to Ben
Cuz he was recovering from a wound with ferrets
They didn't try to blame right winger
I was just
Feels like they were going to blame right way
I created an elaborate narrative surrounding those pictures
Fortunate
Where random person in the shot was anointed the white patches
Zero evidence of anything other than Alex
Good feeling
Literally
Nothing I was just saying to supported
Conclusion that the bomb was fake is
It's just absolute
It's the worst kind of work
A person can do
Also small point
I hate two people dance
Honey bees absolutely do not
Tell 200-plus people a year
Some decent numbers I have found said that Hornets
Bees and wasps
Combined kill about 1.4
Upper ten million
We're approximately 45 people in the
The United States
Also comparing the number of people killed in the bombings the number of people killed by bees is pretty UPS
Who won both people die from bees are allergic
Whereas we're all allergic to bomb
Perhaps more importantly
These are a very important part of our
And without them a lot of plans with Diane
The same as not
True love
People who bomb thing the Redwoods you know the forest fires clear off all the brush and then the Redwood
If we didn't have bombings then how would we rebuild our cities
It's the circle of life
Everybody knows it's just that
SEPTA
Is part of Howell
You know the things work
Sure I hate him so much for 45 a year is Hornets wasp
And
I really hate to be pedantic
I know you
I was going to watch over
That's not all bees
These might be like
It just so infuriating to listen to him talk
On a day like this
Because
All of the bulshit he said he sang with such confidence because you're like
Oh well I guess he must already
Fruitvale
Kyrie wants you to go for the past 5 days and then just came in on
And even though you had what watch the regular news the whole time
If you just suddenly walked into this show you're like
Oh s*** he must have proved all this s*** cuz he I must bring the episode
Absolutely
NetSpend
A hundred percent
I do not believe it's not in
No absolutely not
Can I can even feel my head just like trying to go towards their while
Give me like
This confident without
Something
He literally has nothing
Almeda
So Alex
I'm here this 21st
Is April 21st a
Episode he goes to call
And I one of these callers brings up
An old article from
From the Boston Globe
Arizona
Good job good jobs that is true human
So this caller is brought up this article and Alex
Just found it this color is a human
Yes now listen to Al
Talkabouttd
The whole situation
Negril
Now
Resume he reads the entire article from there
License Porton
You noticed that
The first time he read the actual head
Which is quote Marathon as a dry run disaster
The second time
He added the word drill
To the headline
It isn't there
Okay
That's intention
Alright
That is very intentional
Course it's against the weekend there's a
Flag on the field there's something
Go to a headline because you're trying to say this was a drill
If that is
Dirty pool
You should have him bleep that shitt I don't give a fuk
Buck if you saying
F****** did it it should be goddamn
So beyond his reading off his headline one of his collar sent him from the globe in 2008
Marathon is a dry run disaster
Could hardly be better tailored what he's been putting out unless you lie and throw drill on the
That one really helps that really help
However when this is
Conversation where Alex is arguing
The bombing was a false flag it's important
Discuss the content of the article not just
The headline
The Articles an op-ed
Where the author is primarily arguing that a number of public health and safety organization
Treat large events like the Boston Marathon
Or the 4th of July parade
As opportunities to heighten their Readiness for future
This is not about doing the dry run over bombing or anything like that
It's about her relationships between medical and law enforcement groups
Reforged at large events
Like this in order that they can work better together
Because as the article says you don't want to quote
Exchange business cards at
Scene of a disaster
In addition to this album
The marathon is perfect for collaborative preparation
Because it doesn't just take place in Boston
Extends through multiple cities
So by definition
It's an event where Intercity coordination is nessus
This article does nothing
Approve or even make more plausible any of the Arctic
Metallica's maker
But it appears to
Based on a few buzzwords in the headline and one Alex
Is faking putting a
So that's annoying that's like saying any of those simulations were they trying
Coordinate with different departments and act as though okay here's what a a pandemic would start
This is how it look like
Let's see if we can
Simulators
That's where we succeed
Something like that just those
Existing would be
Fuel for Alex
I see they're planning the new
There's nothing you can do
Unless you just understand how he operates what he's doing
You get the bigger picture of this b******* that that's the that's the way to hell
So Alex and the show talking about our God
Born 1952 in United States of America very very good great wonderful country
A lot of them
What I just heard last night somebody sent it
And can you know I got trusted source
Betamerica when was now number one the most corrupt Nations
On the planet
USA
Not very immoral people government and government back in 1952 you say
Wonder how it might be defining his terms on that one
Would it surprise you to learn that the 82nd session of Congress which included the year
Concluded that only to f
American representatives and 0 senators
Odd how about the fact there was only one woman Senator and 10 represent
Keep reminder 535 members of Congress
This is the one area where Congress is really noticeably changed
Since the 1950s let's say after the passage of the Voting Rights Act
One area that makes no sense
2.2 as a difference between the 1950s in the present-day is governmental corrupt
There are thousands of examples of Representatives and Senators behaving
Very similarly
Scandalous ways going all the way back to the
The founding of the country
But it's hard to say exactly what Alex consider
Accepting bribes doesn't
Now that's
The idea that there were fewer immoral
People in government
The entire
Government was by its nature immoral
Broke around discrimination and segregation
Tyranny of the government was a moral call Alex seeing if you liked it better with governor was wider
Yeah I think of that problem or I would ask
Ask him to
Explain what you mean that's not who's Borel
So anyway we can all do the 22nd
And when Alex comes in here on his Monday show
He lays out the canonical version of what
His narrative is
About the
The
The bombing
Let's look for
Let's look for setups
Han shot first
Our word is right
Xavier
MMA
So that's moving forward if it seems like is going out
Write that one instead
That's alright that's our final draft
Gotcha
So he goes along and he's
Denying that there was even a firefight
In Watertown
Expresses that didn't happen ever
That's largely based on like
Videos that people have
That are incomplete
Partial
Videos
Chico's
Is just strongly arguing the people were
Like
This is like
At gunpoint people forced
I just stay inside their homes
But it is you know you just repeat
He that over and over again
You know eventually people Arabic
So Alex talked about how this whole thing
Lockdown
Are the shelter-in-place request didn't really
Work
Because only after it ended was the person
There was a guy
Boatwright
And
He followed his orders
Your loss
Okay alright
You're a big boy
In his in his mind this dude is sitting by his back window just staring at the boat
Just like man I want to do something about this Blood covered boat of mine
But they told me to stay
Inside
And I obviously can
Can't use my phone from
The inside
I keep it outside of course so what you going to do until they give the okay to step out
Outside
Look like the guy decided to comply with
Shelter-in-place request
Then when he went outside you notice something
He wouldn't see
Unless you was outside
So Alex
This found some video of
The police shooting at the boat the johar were
And he
Plays the video
And I think that there's something really important
Video to TV viewers
In 308
Over and over again into the boat
There's even more of this
Word appears
Alex is absolutely lying
He is replaying
If you actually find videos of the the shooting
Your last
Very very short time there was a brief Outburst of firing
Stop fire hold your fire Hold Your Fire
The video that Alex has the audio you can tell they're they're shooting then there's a low then there's more shooting LOL
And more shooting
That does not happen
In the real world
That is an Eddie saying
This is about half of it as if to indicate that there
They were shooting for a full minute now he's not worried about a wild west shootout where people are in
Different f****** houses across the way and putting their heads out the window and Fire 3
Ducking back in that's what he
And it did not happen like
Nothing that I'm saying is to say that
Police wear it anyway within the
Bounds of good behavior
The fire on the boat
Alex is doing
Wheatley lion yeah
About it and he has to be lying
You could In that clip
He played
Shooting
It lasted longer than it did in the real world
There's no way for him to
Replaying that audio or video without looping
Or without playing
It twice.
Yeah it absolutely is and the only reason
And this is before everything was autoplay
Yeah the only the only reason to do that
That is to create a false
Presentation
What was being done there
Bullets Ark
What are we doing I don't like wasting my taxpayer dollars
I'm 30 guys firing
5000 bullets into a boat
So there was something
Happened in the night of the Watertown
And that is that
Naked guy got arrested
Who is
Sure
In the
Immediate
There were
Some theories that were running around that this was
And it was not
No one was going straight to time traveling
Turn off
Not that I'm aware of
Okay but this
I was
Assertive bolstered by Timberland
But that was he
It was not
But this
Family member lento this credibility to
Being like you wasn't actually killed there
He was arrested
Okay and this is not true but yours Alex
Pushing some of that
Full of holes
Brother
I guess you just said your firefight and then
If you consult the timestamp
Of the the time that people like wherever showing live footage
The guy being arrested
They do not match up it was after tamerlan had already been taken away in an ambulance
All this is bulshit
Honest
Understand they can be
Be made because there is
A superficial visual similarity
Between this naked guy
Tamerlan but he was just another
Suspicious person who was around the scene of the Watertown shootout
And
It's an easier
Sort of thing
Mistake to make when they say they filled him full of holes it what they really meant they force-fed him Shia LaBeouf
Right
Good
Man that was a swing I want for it I work for it a why you want from there
I'll be there it has to go
Wow
I thought swiss cheese might come up yo Shia LaBeouf
Impressive
Empressive
So Alex is narrative now is that
They were trying
Kill johar in the boat they were trying to kill him through the
The entire Manhunt and that is why they told people not to leave
Unloaded
Call him
No evidence they told that to the citizens or the media Alex is making all of this up
He's just decided that their mission was To Kill johar
And that's not
Anything that he has any reason to report
He doesn't have that from any official Channel he's just assuming it's the same way that he saw those pictures on 4chan
I created an entire fantasy
Nerd about it
He's just decided as what they were told
Everything is constant
Change it
On the 19th when we would listen to that episode Manhunter the lockdown was in order to
Find the
Fake seals for the pictures on 4chan
Now it's we got to kill johar
Ridiculous I imagine that Alex
Has to be a little bit
Disappointed that he
Secret used butt dialing
Giuliani
So is source.
Giuliani butt dialed me and he said you're over.
You can lie about anything with that
Believable now
Yeah
So
This next
Clip I believe is important
Pure because it's
Chose
Pivot
It's only these three people that are dead
Scare everyone
Staring
Very familiar at pivoting what are you selling his magazine cuz he doesn't have his line of supplement
Not yet
So this is bizarre
Viewing of development
Because he's saying that the
Same time that he's talking about the globalist using psychological fear and
To get you to do what they want
He's trying to scare you about
Globalist
Pikachu
Runaway Alex is certain that this is
The cover-up and a false flag
Here is what that cover up when we
Black powder
I didn't have any that's not
Call The Authority
And I didn't have any didn't have it so cool
Check that off the list
I'm certain this is going to be used Outlaw black powder
Didn't happen
So Alex
This is certain to visit
The false flag
Android stop just him it's everyone Alex
And he says that and then struggles to come up with anyone
People
Joel skousen
Very long pause
Then Steve pieczenik
It is
On the out we don't even have a Leo zagami
So Alex
It has a new wrinkle here on this April to
22nd episode that is
The story is come out
About the FB
Bi
Calling
Chamberlain
After the bombing
Oh no
Connections
Mother of suspected
After bombing
British media reports
So the idea that the FBI called tamerlan in the days after the bombing is supported by literally nothing other than a claim
By the Tsarnaev brothers parents
You are an active defense
Their interviews in the days after their children's photos were released could all boil down to
Something like our children could never do some
Which is a natural parental reaction
U-see-it commonly in the cases
The people your parents of people who do horrible things
Because it's very damaging to your sense of self to imagine that someone you raise could do something like a bomb a marathon
I tend not to give those comments too much weight unless they're supported by backing evidence
Which is just absent
This is a situation where proven this would be pretty easy
As investigators poured over Chamberlain's phone records try and identify possible accomplices
Even the channel for article that Alex is basing this on doesn't
The story is being
Substantiate
From this art
Quote
The telephone call claim raises a number of questions
On the one hand the claim could be false
It follows Suggestions by both parents at the FBI's been bothering Timberland for years
It could be part of efforts to defend the brothers
Another possibility is that the telephone call was tamerlan
Preparing his mother for bad news
Does Timberland told her allegedly
Yeah the FBI called
The article very explicitly treats this is something that might be true but there's no proof
It's all good while to discuss something like this as a claim being made by a traumatized mother but it's very inappropriate to treat it as if it
List Factor even something likely to
Be true and that is what Alex is doing
There's a very important distinction that Alex is trying
Play Both Sides
Then this very clip that we just listen
The headline from
Steve Watson story is fine
Cuz it's saying the Timberlands mother made this claim
But I'll explain goes on to say that a British
Report claims the FBI spoke to tamerlan after the bombing
And that is an absolute lie
The British report says the tamerlan's mother said it
It ain't no way claims that the FBI spoked
This is the sort of sleight-of-hand Alex does all the time
It's always able to subtly change elements of a story without people really notice
And you can pretend it's a minor shift in
In the story but it's not
One claim is that this mother made the claim
The other is at the British media is reporting that the mother's claims are correct
And the FBI did talk to Tamela.
It's an attempt to prove the mother's Claim by appealing to a source that doesn't
Prove that
This is a deeply dishonest Act
And you probably wouldn't do
So just just keeps piling up
Shifty Behavior
Really
Really bad
Yeah
Really really
Really bad like
Out-of-character bad even for
I think most
Today most of our coverage of Alex
Aggressively
Condenses a good way of putting
Is throwing so many lies
So many walls because he has the opportunity
Write themselves very alright
Rapid fire this
So Alex talked about that a little bit more about how that lockdown and the shelter-in-place stuff was really just
To find johar
This is all made up that's crazy
Is all just imagine
Narrative and a storyline out of disparate pieces of information I'm tired of getting cornered by the guide
I doing coke at the party what is he doing
That's what he's doing
Now what you got to know is you guys are afraid that they're going to come to my house and they're going
Never
Okay
Sir Alex has two guests on the show
On the twenty
And I'm going to say I'll chop
They're both pieces
First of them is Wayne Madsen
The guy who I told Alex that voted Hillary Clinton
Who died at Anoka Tech
That's Truman said call their neck
This guy now hates
Alex Jones
I think he's a liar and
Charlatan
That's great
So here's Wayne talkin about
Sarnia
A professional
Refugees
Including the families
Came over here and
Apparently
No no
So
You know
He's talking about like Chechen
Refugee
Yeah and he had another point you talks about how like he's noticed that they're all in washing
Canton d.c.
Boston
It's all bulshit
There are very few chechens
States that much easier to emigrate to a European countries so the communities in those countries are much larger
It's a complicated question as to why they're not
As many refugees of check
Descent in the United States
But some pointed to it being an expensive trip
To make to apply to Asylum here that's a pretty large
Another is that there were
Very many checks
Soca
Less likely to end up choosing
YouTube United States
Are there fewer fellow
Who can help them buy with the transition process
Of living in a new country
Yeah little self-select
Little
Economics
Whatever the case there are not many Chechen
The whole name
Some estimates
To put it as low as a couple hundred in the
The entire country
No s*** yeah but it's hard to know for sure since
What's many maybe identifying as Russian
Country of origin document
My point here is that Wayne Madsen
Got a dump
He says the DC
DC and Boston or cities
Without that
Chechens are surrounding
LinkedIn
They are cities that have
Now some Chechen population
But they're tiny relatively
Speaking and those cities aren't the only places where catching folks live
Their cities that he
You've chosen from a list of cities with Chechen
Communities
Because it's where all the FBI's stuff is
And where are the bombing
They're also notable Chechen populations in
Seattle York
Los Angeles
New Jersey the Wayne
Hand wave
Those away to draw Focus to the
He said he wants to build suspicion about
And here's the thing
This isn't perfect
Conspiracy
This is over at Cinetopia
Putting forth this kind of thing where you're trying to imply the refugee
This particular Heritage or something
Nefariously cluster
It serves to make your listeners suspicious of all Chechen
This is a very small group we're pretty vulnerable from a numbers and social capital
Trying to create the perception that they might be coming to the United States as quote professional refugees
It may be up to no good isn't it
Explicit active marginalization of a
Beauty based on their ethnic origin
That seems pretty f***** up
These Chechen Americans were just as affected by the bombing as anyone else possibly even more so
Some say the fear that
People would do exactly what Wayne Madsen
Is doing here
Trying to tie their Heritage to a terrorist
The strongest possible terms
F*** this
Wayne sucks
Yeah there should be a
Yeah this angle is
Real bad
So Alex is heads
China Crown who's given the
The motive
Of that for the polling office false flag is being the
Imaginary bipartisan
Congressional committee that
Yeah I'll tell you did Obama Penny Grimes
And has his own motive
That's word for word before and after
I call this the Patriot Act for the internet
Cardboard
Interaction
With anything electronic
Completely unrelated a guy trying to say
Set up an Elvis impersonator Julieta
What a wild story that was
The bombing was done to pass
Pasta spa or the Cyber intelligence sharing and protection act
Also known as HR 3523 in the 112th Congress
Hr624 anyone
Hr2
All these attempts
What's the pass the bill
Weather without any supposed false-flag bombing
In December 2015 the GOP included an amended version called Sissy
Visa into the budget
And Obama signed it in
You may remember December 2015 is one of the many times that the GOP under
McConnell had tried to force a shutdown of the government if he couldn't get his way
In this case there was a big hold up with them trying to put
Defunding of Planned Parenthood into the budget bill which they were unable to do
They were however able to
Slide in
There's no need for the government to Stage terrorist
What's the text to push through unpopular legislation
Alex's buddies like Ted Cruz are more than willing to hold the government hostage
Which to do that on their own
So now we got to bulshit theories as the motive for the false flag
Pushing through
Pertronix imaginary bipartisan Congressional committee that indicted bush
Obama war crimes
Noting that these people are saying means anything
They're just
Making s*** up
It's not okay
I know you probably get tired of that conclusion
You can't
Just do that
It wouldn't even a
Heard of me to just rip out the news and sister is your reality
I want my hair to Alex being a
But that's
Particularly against it as well
I think that's a solid position to have but it doesn't
Justify
This now
So anyway
Alex
By this point
Has learned that there's an explanation for the
People in his picture
Study found out for
And they were National Guard civil support team
Uniforms
Nope well that solves it not true see how it works it's not
And so I believe him
Now you take this entirely
Terrible work that they've done
Insisting these people are Navy Seals but in reality they were part of the Civil support team
I know everything is now taking the truth
And hand waved it away
Map
Of course not
You you're getting it wrong
This is how you solidify
Your narrator
From any kind of possible
Infiltration of reality
So
The Wayans gone now
And you can stay gone for all I'm
Besides take a little time
Plug a new station
Signed up
Two are his show
Call letters
Raleigh
Around here
760 a.m.
This hour
Family show I apologize
This is a family show all along
I love
The petty workplace
Office griping
Just coming out on air
Like that's
That is every office
That is everybody was ever worked in an office at least one day of been like
Really I'm getting
This many emails
Do you guys not know how to figure it out your goddamn self. Do everything ready
Episode the f****** radio
So Alex is convinced
The FBI knew who the Tsarnaev brothers were when they release the
Take photos
And then he goes on
Tells his version
Of The Manhunt
And some of this is a little bit repetitive
Weverton Cliffs like
But I think it's
Important to understand that what Alex is doing is
First of all being repetitive
Drive home
His narrative
I meant secondarily
You practicing hitting these points
And now it's just
But
After shooting
So this is all just
Made up this is
Again just Alex's imagination of what happened
I don't understand why anybody would
Dislike
I mean I do understand why people take it serious
Very convincing
Let me let me take that again I think I could do that a little bit smoother
Yellow lab dark yellow okay we're going to do this one more time only tell this story when I really want to get this story right
He has the emotionally
A compelling presentation
Someone who knows what they're talking
I'm about and it's very easy to be
Duped
Into thinking
This confidence
So
Some videos
Add Surface by the
Point of police
Taking people out of homes
And Alex has a position
And I have some great
What interface
So Alex is absolutely correct that there were videos going around of people being let out of their homes by police
There's no real indication of the police threatening them in any way North
He's aiming their guns at the
Civilians but the people do have their hands up
From the videos I've seen it seems
More likely
Orderly
Of a process
Lessor you know it's not their yelling at them to submit
But I can't be certain are these even actually from
Yeah
Alright I'm at my first my first instinct is like these are actually no
I wasn't there and I don't know what videos I was
Scene in heaven
I can't really speak
On those sorts of things I can just tell you what I've seen
Oh and I can also speak about one other thing
And I just that every single one of these
People whose homes were
Search during The Manhunt gave the police permission to search their homes
You can make the argument that given the fever pitch in the city that these people felt like they couldn't
Tell the police
He said they couldn't search their home
Eminem
Subway
That's a form of pressure for them to give up their fourth amendment rights
You can make the argument that they might have felt like there would be cops
Consent to the police searching their home
Like that might make them appear suspicious
And these are the exact order questions that a certain group was a
Exploring in late April 2013
It's a group that Alex f****** hate
That group of course
Is the American civil liberties Union
They cou
They've seen the same videos that everyone else
Latina babe very public statement they would like to speak
Any citizen who felt like they were put in a position where they could
Say no to a police search
Speaking to the Atlantic
Carol Rose the executive director of the ACLU of Massachusetts
Innovation head quote received a number
I'm concerned complain
From people about the searches that took place
Including some residents of Watertown
None however from people whose homes had been searched
I've looked
And I can find no evidence that anyone actually affected by the Searchers
Is ever lodged a formal complaint
Or filed suit
Claimed that their rights were violated
All the noise
It's been talked about this issue comes from people who saw the videos or look at the Optics
Then made their own decisions
These observers are making a joke again
And it's
Them trying to assume the decisions
Actual people whose homes are being searched or making
Many of them were probably totally fine with the surge
Some of them probably uncomfortable but understood it was for the best
Consented
It did
Right-wing virtue
Arrington
Battle other people
If one of these citizen to file the case and Alex wanted to
To support their claim and draw attention to it that's one thing
But he doesn't even have a particular taste
Only saying is
If that was me in that video I wouldn't be okay with
Yeah yeah
That's an okay thing to say
But don't help us establish that the police
Distracting on
Constitutional
So whatever
Are there like vampire
Those are the rules
Well that is magical rule
Greater Matt lesser Magic
So now we get to our second
You should gas to the day and that's Joel skousen
1010 here Alex is already
Said believes is false flag
F****** do thinks everything
Anyway ears Joel
It's very clear that the two brothers were involved in
False flag training and operation
And by the way we have video of the younger brother
What the FBI said about him dropping
I've been through
What a shock Joel skousen think something's a false flag
This guy is a broken record
Literally everything
Has ever happened in the world is part of some Grand conspiracy
Damn it's so
F****** funny that Alex presenting as an expert in any
Mayfield other than saying things are false flag
I'll concede that he's got that down better than anyone else I've ever seen
Everything is just after the bombing skousen was on his show on Alex's show he said that this at the signs of a false flag
Now he's upgraded its confidence
I don't give a s*** about any of that because here's the thing
Joel skousen is a goddamn liar
He said In that clip there's a video of Joe Hart leaving the area the Boston bombing
Still carrying his bag
There's no video or pictures of this
He is just full of s***
Actually know what he's talkin about everybody's trying to hide
On April 19th
The Associated Press release the picture of johar fleeing the scene
The picture was taken by a businessman from Florida named David Bowie
Finish the marathon about an hour before the bombs
Smite off
He hung around the Finish Line to watch the waves of Runners come in
But his phone was dying
So you went to a charging station and SE was
Turning to his friend
When's the blast app
Esau chaotic scene
So we took a picture and then immediately started helping
A friend texted him to ask if he was okay
And green replied
By sending the
Thank that he was right there
When the FBI released the pictures of the suspect
This friend review the picture
See if there was anything unusual in it
Any saw Joe Hart in the lower left
He told green who sent the picture off to the FBI
Event contacted AP who vetted the picture and released
This picture clearly shows johar without his
But internet sleuths decided that someone must have photoshopped the image
To take out the backpack
There's no evidence that they can't do that there's no evidence
If this is the case
The same original high-resolution image was submitted to the AP and the FBI
The conspiracy theorists get quite decide who to blame weather was green or the FBI who did the photoshopping
But the result was
A good number of Internet bulshit targeting David Green is possibly being in on a terrorist attack
It killed us.
Like for real this is repulsive
These f****** are like the eye of Sauron like once the eye is on you and it's
All of their power
Combined unto this f****** to the black hole
God that you can find out if it's Photoshop it's not even
It's not even that hard if you have techno
Chemical ability with it and it said they
Wave it away and just say like no it's it was Photoshop
At this is what's guy was talking about when he says that there's video of Joe hard leaving with his
His back there isn't
Yeah there's an unhinged
Completely unproven internet conspiracy
See about how a picture of johar without his bag is Photoshop
Coward doesn't even have the wherewithal.
Represent is b*******
Keep hiding behind lies of the weakness of your evidence doesn't
Show to clearly
Bulshit
I mean it feels like even if you pointed that out he be like a hobby evidences that there isn't a video of him without his
Like what what what are you f******
Video tune
Then fine magic is real whatever
Yeah so Alex
Is Ben
Sort of trying to softly and subtly
Go from
Timberland mother
Says that the FBI called Truth
Going to help out quite a bit with the
Cuz he's just reading that FBI call as a fat
I think it was interesting.
Did the police or the FBI called
A couple of days
And
I don't know if I wanted them
I'm still unclear Alex what this
MPI call is not establish back and guess what the carjacking and the murder of the MIT
Teacup make perfect sense
Outside of your conspiracy
They make absolute sense with reality
Why are you why are you conceal makeup a narrative around why that stuff makes sense within my cancer
Faricy Theory because if I were to like
I mean they're obviously reasons
That with those would make
In the context of what I'm telling you is true
Simply overcomplicating
Really got to figure out whether or not the the Moon
The mirror right
Set the MIT
He copped a killer
Himself and then they
So
Alex
Plays out
The config
Again and again I want to stress
I believe that this
I'm telling the story
House where it's at
Face
That's a question
Right here
So what we have here is Alex practicing telling the story what happened
He's going over the Beatles
The story and you can hear him connecting the dots as he goes along but there's
Problems
For one I thought he changed the narrative to this being a thing where they wanted to blame the seals
But now it seems
He's back today
That they plan to blame right-wingers
April 19th episode of bottle episode of Alec
What's the show where he throws out a whole new story line about how is all about the
Feels have a lockdown with the cleanup the Patsy
Cuz it seems like we're supposed to have forgotten all about that show luck it was it was so they panned out at the end
End of that episode and there was an autistic child with a snow globe
That's how that epi
Episode work you didn't
You didn't see the last part of it
Secondly Alex's never played those clips of the media celebrate
But they know it's going to be a lone wolf right-wing
Terrorist guy
This is the second stage of the you can look it up misdirection
What he says you can look it up
The Listener to never feel they need to look so
This other one
I've played the
Eclipse isn't attempted
Convince The Listener that he's actually played the piece of evidence that he hasn't
Eventually through repetition he can Gaslight
People into Assuming he's demonstrated all this stuff and they must have missed the episode
Like what you were bringing up earlier what you
Our feeling
12 benefits of list
Do this every day of his show is that I can see very confident
That I was just never said
Created this claim that the media was salivating that it was a right winger
But he's repeatedly
He claimed that he's played at the clips
Third and most interesting Lee
Globalist bad guys got trained out of false flag by delclos
The f****** think that these people are just up there improvising
Does he not understand how stupid that sounds
Alright guys let's do years-long cultivation to this tamerlan guy involving
Complicated operation to get him in and out of the country secretly
Culminating
Bombing the Boston Marathon
Alright sounds good then what
After that we wing it
I mean
But there's something to be said about a unique performance
Do you know that's like in like in theater you know there's certain things you get bored by the performance
Then yeah you have a fun mess up and yeah you get reinvigorated believe it all over
Anything that you can only have half
Bulshit this level of characterization of your bad guys is Carter
Like for real Joel skousen doesn't get enough grief for me on a regular basis
Maybe because it's kind of funny that he hates
Trump in the present-day and Alex has to put up with it because all of his other experts will talk to him anymore
But let's not lose sight of the fact that girl scouts
So we have two motives
Now for the bombing
Pertronix motive
And Wayne Madsen
Motive
Skousen has his own
Okay that sucks okay
Another one of these high-profile Terror attacks
Remember we don't have any normal terrorism in the United States
People coming across the border among the thousands of illegal aliens to come across
Maybe blowing up electrical pylons suicide bombers
Small non high profile profile
Always assign
If there is something
That's right
So as if you need more evidence this Joel skousen
The dunce. Asserting the motive the goblets I need to pull up his Boston bombing of the false flag us cuz we haven't had any Terror
Prison for a while that is a friedersdorf level take right there then it's been awhile since
We had one let's toss them on the
Ideas about real versus fake
Cuz it's racist to s***
Well might be there might be undertone
If it isn't
It's noticed
I'm going to leave aside also terrorist attacks
Same to other
That absolutely do affect our country's interests since that list.
B2 Gigante
And they probably wouldn't fit whatever nonsense
That's great. Joel's using
I know the definitions of terrorism
My very but what about Sandy Hook
What about the Aurora
What about Christopher dorner's Rampage
What about that Nazi who shot up a Sikh temple in Wisconsin
What about the attempt
Assassination
Gabrielle Giffords
That left six dead in 50
I would personally consider all of these we Act of terrorism to Summit
They produced are in the community whether or not be
Specific Act
Hadn't identified political motivation
I would say that in early 20
Circularly after Sandy Hook
No one needed to be reminded with Terror
Like I were there any trains in
No not Terror
I meant were there any just Telecommunications
Is this f****** dumb dumb not remember that we're like sick
Six months removed from the attack
Benghazi
6 months what the f*** do
Like what is it get off going on a nationally syndicated radio show and pretending
To be an international Affairs expert while he spouts
Completely meaning
Bulshit like that
Seahawks trade the bus Department
Terratech
A f*** out of here
It's the classic
Motive
It's been awhile
So dumb
So now we get to clip that I
Personally
Okay
And that is
It may be one of my favorite genres
Of Alex's
Coverage
And that is
When he's swimming
And he uncovers
Something
Detective Alex
At the swimming hole
I was swimming laps at Barton Springs
We're talking about
Show me more.
I don't believe anything about that
How to relieve out either
I was out the emojis that I was swimming laps I was like you're full of s*** I got to say though
To the pool bar and back away from this Alex's to be believed
Barton Springs
Is one of the
Biggest hot beds
Specialized information about casual it is amazing how
Much secret information is a block away from his house
So much secret apparently under a tree you're going to hear something classified
Walk with you can't throw a stone without hitting a classified piece
Information on also I love that his justification for the big special ops as they were
So they were clearly
School
That and they couldn't see me but I was laying under tree it was an oak tree I remember that cuz if I wanted a little achy
Corn fell on top of
Ahead
M8 but they didn't know I said
And then they knew it was me but that's when they
So this next clip is just just for posterity it doesn't really have a whole lot to do with
Steve
Current affairs that were talking about
Here in 2013
Alexandros cows
Or both
Pretty clear
That
Don't the bad
I want to make one point very clear that mainstream media continues to put out the propaganda
Assisting
This is absolutely untrue
Is that almost all of the check-in terrorism
Terrorism in Russia the apartment buildings the Breslin bombings
Of the school
So Alex completely does not agree with this in the present
Yeah you know where I got loaded with in like a year or two after this
He saying that Putin didn't do that
He must be happy that he does
That the news is not
Not focus on bolsonaro probably assassin
Nobody had to worry about that one
So Joe goes further down
And it is also it's pretty embarrassing
To hear that sort of thing
Considering the rhetoric that Alex who put out
I'm very short time
That the Russians have been running
The chechens is there false flag operations just like we've been running
The Middle Eastern Muslims that are false flag operations in this country
War on terror
In terms of
Bringing in more this false propaganda that Russia is our Ally in the world on terror
They're still planning on disarmament
It seems like our government is just insisting on proving to the computer
But there's no threat there that were fighting a common enemy
Well it sounds exactly like Alex is angle a couple years later
Weird
So are we going to Alex's run here on the 22nd
And I withdraw
Alex for
His great work
Course what you doing I know you're taking a lot of flak for what's going on
Attractive
When your Riley two or perennial conspiracy deniers or even
You know
Good guy
You're at the Forefront of this
So conspiracy deniers Glenn Beck
He has to walk very carefully because Glenn Beck
Some connections with like
He's a big
W Cleon skousen
Really he has some connection with the skousen family like
He's very into the skousen
Auntie,
Best work so
How to beat roll knows not
What do you mean
I mean
That I would man when they do background checks
But it shouldn't be drug conviction
What kind of questionable literature choices
Have you made about whether or not you're
F****** anti-government
Are you big into weirdo
What's your favorite book
So Alex
End
Any leaves
About three and a half hours into the
Joann
Has bakari Jackson the David Knight come in to take calls
For the rest
Today at shop
Another half-hour right you know there's no longer
There's no longer Wednesday going on so he doesn't have to do so
6 hour-long shows anymore Factory 4 hours
Ian Overdrive
And I just want to play a little bit of this because there's a
Going on in the world
And
Here's some of the calls
Here's the first
Constitution Bill of Rights news
Idea. I think y'all should run the Bill of Rights as a new sticker
At the bottom of your screen
But I wanted to point out something about the concert
Everybody's trying to mess with it and I'm going to tell you the Bill of Rights itself stairs in the first floor
The first letter
Play hell yeah man first letter of the first for sale
I don't care
I mean this is just an overall igigi level
Nicolas Cage Nicolas Cage on the other
So that's one caller is like okay I'm the guy who came up with the idea of doing the Bill of Rights as a ticker underneath
This next caller is a little bit more troubling
But you just wants to
He starts out the cold like I just want plugs
What I wanted to do is kind of plug
I've got a page on Facebook that I started a group and it is called
The Constitution alive
I know it's not living document but
Constitution Daiso to this country
I will say that this man is willing to admit the flaw in his title
Is like I thought it was a great title now I admit
Because a lot of people have pointed this out to me it's a very obvious problem
Late for me to Jade
I can't put some other option
Diversity is a constitution is pretty cool another one he could have gone with his
President and Vice President
Going to be elected separately since I hate the 12th Amendment
Another is a I don't like minorities voting
Any of those could work yeah accurate title so I was curious so I decided to check
I actually found this Facebook
It's been pretty dormant for a while now but the last post
From July 2013
Teen is pretty telling of the sort of vibe that this guy was putting out
Quote to all
5 l
Those who have gone back and forth
About the mixed race
Oh no it's in parentheses
He is not just
Black like you love to regards
Anti every religion accepted Islam White House
And the sad part is you still think his s*** don't stink
You are what's wrong with this country
That post
2 likes
Gotcha
I mean I think that's good
Sure I think I think only two likes on that is a good
Yeah I think that's progress for the living Constitution
Looking through this page
History it's so clearly so
Someone who's been completely a
Goodbye Alex Jones
It's a Non-Stop talk about taking off arms up
And showing the powers-that-be that they are not in
In charge
Follow dances insistence is not calling for violence
It's really sad honestly
Like they call into Alex's show and they're plugging this page
Best as I can tell it didn't do too much in terms of Engagement
They just lost interest in July
I would think that they
Just died
Maybe got arrested
But they posted again in March
From that post
Quote I still believe that we can see
Save our country
However I don't I do not believe that there's a notch
Available without blood
We all know that the corruption
Is well-rooted
And not going to voluntarily remove its
We've all observe how quickly promises made on the
Pain trailer left at the curb
We all know that the soap ballad injury boxes are
Tattered torn
Breaking into
We all know the only box still available is
The cartridge by
I do not want my children to grow up knowing what war is
I do not want my children growing up not knowing me
I do not want my children growing up not knowing what freedom is
I will not allow anyone the opportunity to
To take that away from
I will with extreme
Prejudice and
Anyone standing in the way of restoring this once great nation to her proper Glory
I heard you all to ask yourself where you're lying is
How much more will you
When will you decide to stop hiding online behind words and put your blood where your mouth is
The end of the post with the hashtag start the revolution
This is The Logical endpoint for a certain amount of people who internalize and believe Alex is b*******
They're angry the enemy they imagine they're up against a soup
Freeway overpowered
And every time there's a traumatic event in the world like
Boston bombing
They're taught a new
To hate this overpowered Elite
Cabal who were secretly the 12
Who carried out the attack
They're given no real guidance are Outlet
But no path toward legitimate
Political action
Only made him more Angry by outrage after outrage
And they never could change anything anyways since the enemy they're being taught to hate is imaginary
But they feel so real
A person can only live in that state for so long before it becomes a
Intolerable
Some could probably deal with it by supporting Alex Moore
Imagining that it's
The best way they feel that their they could feel like they're making a difference
Some probably manage to break free from the b******* and return to a normal life
But some are consumed with this anger Centric worldview and end up calling for blood-filled revolutions
Because they can't figure out any other way to deal with the imaginary enemies Alex
Just taught them to fear
I don't believe for a second that Alex isn't aware that this is something that he does too
He doesn't care
As long as they're out there plugging Infowars that's good for traffic
And if they do end up following through with their plan to
Kill
They'll just be called false Flags
Demonize the Patriots
Double used as a prop
To provide the fuel Alex needs
The terrifying outrage
The rest of his audio
Continue the cycle
It's good
So where we look at this episode and this this whole thing with the Boston
Embalming you see likizo vert
Lies
And this
This bike
This desperate
Need to take things
Make them fit his narrative so we can get attention which
We can absolutely
From his own words
Is paying off
Incredibly
10 times the amount of traffic
Victory is getting before
It just an insane rise
In his notoriety
Endwell
You can look at these
I think it's Uncle also incredibly important
To remember that there is
These people
One of whom who calls in on the show
Who are being
Guided down
Half that has no offering
At least no off-ramp with a sign that says hey here's a place to
F****** check yourself
This is
I'm far more
Concerned with
The people who are the
Targets
Of Alex's
Propaganda
And I are
I'm far more interested
Spending the bulk of my m
A fee on those feet
But
People like this guy who calls in
I don't think
That I in good conscience
Can't ignore the fact that he is a victim of a lie
Absolute
And it's harder to feel the ton of empathy for him because
You know he's advocating things
Things that will end up hurting
The targeted communities even more
Follow
His ideas
To The Logical
Conclusion you've gone to a
End up killing people
And that is unacceptable
Toptable
Well I mean to a certain extent
For this guy what I see
Somebody listen
Sing to Alex Jones
Is Alex Jones is
Is essentially
Has a f****** cattle prod
And he is
Living in a
Constant state of agitation
A bit like
It's like a
It's like a f****** you
Experiment
Of somebody constantly
Jolting you every time you're about to
To feel any
Comfort and about to feel like
You know what it's
It's really not that big a deal
Pokes you again
Can you get jabbed again in your brain
State of excitement
Drives you insane
Cruelty listen
Makes Alex Jones
Or if you have like the possibility of connecting with people on a larger
Scale like around
Shared experience
Insincere tragedies
You are let away from
The only people who
Same imaginary world YouTube
You can't process the Boston bombing
The way that other people
Will do because you
AR
Completely separated sublimate
So that's where I'm going to leave this a lot a lot
CB the second
Stage of Alex's
Is conspiracy building operation
Where are you
Any information that comes out
Solidifies his own narrative
Brumby they were blaming Seals All Along apparently
Stuff
And
You see the concert
I've said my piece
Will be back
On Wednesday
Cobia website
We will be on Twitter at we are on Twitter now it's at knowledge underscore fight not go to bed Jordan compromise on Facebook
Would like to download please go to iTunes review leave the downloaded share then go to other podcast
Best apps and do the whole thing all over again
Going to be fun
But until then I'm Leo I'm dzx Clark
I am at Martin's
Alexandra Thurston color