I have great respect for knowledge but I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
MoneyGram
Collegeboard.com
Everybody would like to know that's right I'm down like sit around talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Indeed we are.
Have you ever been forgotten in a mall or the
Yeah
Terrifying
When I was a kid I had like a real serious
Fear of being left places
Oh yeah and I believe it was based on
I like being
Lost
Supermarket
When I was really young boy
They drive away or was it just like the other day they were still in the
My parents are still okay but I would like it very visceral memories
I don't know where I don't know how to get where I need to be right all right
And like I've always lived or like when I was younger in Honolulu and then also in Columbiaville
Missouri I lived
Close enough that I was supposed to walk to
School
Answer like when we lived in Hawaii
My mom was at
You're at the school that I want
So you know what we'd walk to school together and then I'd stay after
After school while she wrapped up stuff and then we
You know walk back but then we moved to Missouri I was
In 4th grade
And it's a walk
To school
And I just had like
A really bad Sin
So there would be
Times when I would just like to try and take a slightly different route and just get
Weekly loss no and I have this
Real fear of being
Yeah very
Very strong fear that everyone was
To get me grown out of that
Walking home from school
A car that passes any car is like there are they're going to
It's over for my location
Awful
State to be in
Constantly walking
To and from school
Terrified of anybody and not sharing that fear because that would be that would be shameful as well
Oh man I was like probably 11
Or so and I was walking home
From school and I just got
I completely lost
Like II
I am now in my adult brain I can map out that neighborhood and I know exactly where I would have needed to go
Right
I don't know 10
10 blocks from
My house or so but
Because it was like
Is residential neighborhood
With winding streets
It's an offshoot cul-de-sac
What have you
I just completely lost I have no idea where to go
And I just started crying
And I like knocked on someone's door
I don't know how to get home
Looking for cell phones I don't have a cell phone at home anyway
GPS existence
Yeah it's a difference in there was there was super nice and I
Okay I'm 35 now it's still really appreciate it
Dental very just like oh my god let's let's get you where you get the wrong
And so on
I got homebodii.
Very very strong fear isn't as much as
Younger of being lost
I still I guess I'm a little bit now but with the Advent of cell phones in like maps and
Stop it
It's pretty tough
To be fully lost
If your phone is charged it really is
It really is it requires a bunch of things to go wrong alley.
Sometimes you could still end up in a place where it's like well I know where I am
There's not much I can do about that really far away from a train station or are they lose your job
It's tough but
Lessened with a
Yeah I'm so this is like his Rhino bit about the other feeling
The being left
Did not very much
Jordan today we are doing a Wacky Wednesday episode we're going to explore a little
Something and see what we find but before we get down to business on that
Looks like a little moment
Thank you
Some folks have signed up and are supporting show
So first of all J thank you so much you're now a policy wonk
NextStop policy wonk
Next Captain Awesome thank you so much and I'll probably want
Captain Awesome
I'm a policy wonk
Next
Carpe donktum
I'm a policy wonk I like there's a real carpay.com Pretender
And finally like say thank you to a couple people who signed up on an elevated level we appreciate that very much so Amanda thank you very
Aaron thank you so much
And
Tennessee's baseball with a fat bat
Thank you so much you are all now wonderful technocrat
The business
Heroin
Freakishly large
Thank you so much Aaron Amanda and Tennis is baseball with a fat bat
Reference to something I think I said
Wayback on this podcast I have no idea what context
But I
I like being remind
I recall it was probably something
I like what these guys do I'd like to support the show
Website.com
Is button on there to sports show co-star patreon and you can help make
Fix your posture
It'll be lovely
So Jordan today like I said
Wacky Wednesday so it's been awhile since
We checked in on the world of the Jim Bakker Show and the main reason for that is his show is dumb as s***
It's so profoundly boring to listen to and it's so incredibly rare
For Jim or one of his guests
To say anything that I think
Even merits looking into
Like if he's going to have people like Steve Quayle or Tom Horn coming in talking about the giant Giants and angels
Baseball teams
Then Bang
There's not a whole lot I can do with
Stuff like that
But the reality is that the Jim Bakker Show is the media offshoot of a manipulative abusive money called
He feeds off his audience of tremendously cynical ways
And even if your show is boring
And half the s*** that said on the show
Can't possibly even be shown to be true or false
I think it's still important to check in for
From time to time
Particularly when his world intersect with
Reality
At the end of last week it was announced the trumpet appointed mega-church scammer
Jim Bakker associate Paula white-cain as to an official position in the White House
He'd previously been a spiritual advisor to him
But it was announced that she was now officially working in the office of public liaison
If you'd like to learn more about Paula's Fuller story we didn't episode about her called heresy and God
What you can find in our archives or talk about
Churches in
And all that stuff
For now suffice it to say that she is a Prosperity Gospel preacher
Who made millions of dollars by scamming her followers
She advocated
The principle of first
Fruits where you need to send her all the money that you make in January
To make sure that you make
Even more money the rest of the year
Which is cool
At that
Still one of my eggs
One of my most
Incredible
I got to give it up to you it's really hard to just say that
You know that's Jedi level just like hey if I say this enough I'm going to make
Millions of dollars that's crazy
It's a startling level of sin
Yeah yeah you're demonstrating
And it's one thing to say that you'll gain
Future blessing
If you give her 112 the money you making a year
It's shity and awful but at least it's
Just an offer
But in reality the way Paula preaches at the first fruits thing is a threat
She said quote
When you honor this principle that provides the foundation
Structure for God's blessings and Promises in your life
It unlocked
Deep dimensions
Spiritual truths that literally transform your life
When you apply this everything comes and Divine Alignment for his plan and promise
For you
When you don't honor it whether through ignorance or direct disobedience
There are consequence
There are consequences
The fuk Paula white-cain
Yes he's one of the most transparent scam artist in the field of
And the fact that Trump would give her a job in the government is so unsurprising
But so profoundly offensive considering he's one of the most transparent scammers
So in the middle of October last month yeah
Paula White Cain was a guest
On Jim Bakker
Again OK Google little bit of that here today
How it's going to be tonight we're going to get off in
Side topic
And what have you and
As we do just remember this is a person who officially works in the government now
So here is Jim Bakker
Actually his daughter
Giving the
And welcome to the Jim Bakker Show coming to you from the village of Morningside USA
Ozark Mountain senior pastor of New Destiny Christian Center Pastor
Paula white-cain are Cohoes today is Mondo Delavega I'm Tammy Sue Bakker
Now please give a warm welcome to my parents and the host of the Jim Bakker Show
Very very small point
Very small point
Why does Jim Bakker say thank you Tammy Sue Bakker
Do you not know why do you use your daughter's last day
Bizarre
Miss Tammy
Thank you Miss Baker
Daughter
I'm sure they have a great relationship
It just seems very strange
Thank you Tammy Sue Bakker
It's almost like you
Incapable of not doing an ad
You know like this is I am making sure that you get full full credits in the in the
Yeah I don't know exactly but I don't want them to think of some other Tammy I don't know why but that really was a hang
I was listening
I had to listen to that a couple times you like
Am I weird or is that weird
I've decided
Wright didn't even have to say that you fart right
I would feel like my dad did a like religious studies being radio show
Like in Columbia Missouri
And I was a guest on it
And if if you was introducing me and he's like I guess
Is my son
Damn freezer I would feel weird
My son Daniel
More
It's not like he's
Intro Youtube
Do 45 know
No
My son
Great, that works for me I'd be fine with that even if he was I would still feel weird
Formal
Anyway
So Paula White Cain is on the show primarily to promote her new book
There's a new book out called something more
That is probably the best
Yeah
FairPoint
GS change Laurie Baker's life
Because it is so damn good
And honestly I think there's a little bit of a vibe that goes throughout this episode that Jim
Is a little bit peeved
And how much Lori like this book
This is
I think your favorite
Talk of all times
I got y'all honestly we have a lot of
We have a huge life
Lori has already read this
But she loves it
So much
She's read it twice and she's told it to me
A dozen times
I thought she'd never tell this
It all in this book
Here's the only way I know
Is very authentic very real very open very raw
It was the hardest
Thing I've ever done
But the most rewarding
It took me 9 years
2 years
Why it took you nine years to write this book what were you liked it she was just on
Like maybe 9-10 months before this on Jim Bakker Show pushing her other book about Esther's
How do you have a time notebook
I will
Eat my own
I mean technically I don't have any evidence
I know I'm just saying that if she did
I don't know
Tobacco store
Let me see the f****** manuscript I don't know how she is the time
Quite frankly
She doesn't recognize
Fitbit
So in her book she talks about
Our path through life
Early childhood
Try and stay away from like her
Call stuff cuz I don't know if it's really all that into
Interesting or all that relevant
Tortured animals
I find her story
Has to be at least identical to John Wayne Gacy is but there was just like a different
I don't know about anything
Book except for what they talk about
And mostly it just seems like
I don't know
She's living in a trailer and then she got divorced a couple times and
Bada bing bada boom here we are to study two Bibles and
Who cares
So she gets into in this next five getting kind of emotional talking about praying at the inauguration
Eurasian
After the 22
16 election
When I got there
I
Stop
Can I just say
God
I looked up the heavens
Only
You
Boo
Stop everything I had
To do everything I needed
And I was so
Present with
That moment
Thinking it's like my whole life
Backsplash for me
Here's this former messed up Miss
Hippie girl
Lived in a trailer
Daddy committed
Pregnant out of wedlock
Been married
In divorce
Twice that mean all this
Not everything that
People said
Me every
Should I have called you
Shake Nation
And I'm standing there
The most powerful Nation
In the world
Invoking the name of Jesus
I said
Don't care what they say
Say about me
History
Did it work
The woman
God a female clergy
The history will record
An Impala
Came prayed for
The first time
A female
Sergio Verdin
It feels a little narcissistic that feels a little bit like this is about me as opposed to
Other thing
Why would you why would you think that
I got a
Strong vibe in that direction
And Paul is kind of getting out of this title of first woman clergy member to pray at the inauguration thing on a technicality
After he won the 2012 election
President Obama had Merrill
Evers-williams deliver a prayer at the inauguration
She was the former chair of the n-double-acp and was a noted civil rights activist though she was not technically a reverend
Preacher
Christianity is largely based on the idea that all people have access
What's the God and there's no need for the old structures were the clergy or interview
Media Aries to contact the divine
I'm not sure the Pollos claimed would be this big first
Billy means all that much
I would argue
That's
None of the things that she has said in that are true
A little bit
He's doing like
I'm sure some of the details of her life through and I'm shy I'm sure that there is like an emotional narrative Arc
The her life that I don't want to
Like demeanor
Because like
The idea that you did
They come from whatever humble beginnings however much
To that
Compared to how she is
Experience
That beat
To the point that she's at now
That's her life
And great
But
The other
It doesn't
It doesn't strike me as healthy
To have someone
Be like
But it's really just your life story
This feeling of of Narcissus
Isn't that runs behind the history books will have to remember the name Paula white-cain
That was the thing that I was list
Me to her entire little speech
It was like
Obviously fake cry
Probably and maybe better trained than than the Alex Jones School
A crime
Female comedians become right-wing commentators in
Bad actress can become
But then
Then it got real
It got very genuine when she started talking about how
History is going to have to remember her f****** name
Yeah and it was not emotional it was f******
I own this
Now I dominated you
World
Right and that is that I did
Yeah if you know you know that you had a woman who gave the prayer at the inauguration before that so now you have to like move
Move the goalposts a little first woman clergy
Which she's not
Technically
I don't know anyway
Hey wait the last
Right at the feminist
All they're coming
They should be
Thrilled with Paula because you was the first woman
Parentheses clergy member
Woman
The first clergy that a woman
Was like are you kidding me
The old ass all the women livers
Burning their bras eighty-year-old man
Expressing disdain with the the present state
Yeah
You think of suffragettes maybe rallying behind you but
They show their hypocrisy
Elizabeth Taylor
Won't shut up now we'll see
All right Jim
Calm down so Lori loves this book
It's going to probably shocked a lot of you
No it's it's time
Her
You mr. Non-Stop
Because that's who you are
And here's what I love
Variable
About you
If I laugh
Amen I love you
Amen oh God Amen
We had him amen
So very
Comforting thought Laurel and Hardy two-man game right there first banana second banana that was going I was going for
Pretty well
So all this is
Like the first
Half
Is Joe
Is just selling this book
Like I understand we'll make an
I suppose
Some of the presentation
Is that this book
Highlights
Biblical principles or something
And then you could say by proxy
You're being a religious program
But in reality in function and inform this is an infomercial for her book
That is all that's going on
You are truly the greater
This woman
Preacher I have
Ever heard
And I believe
With all my heart
I've seen and heard the best
You have a gift
I feel bad for Tammy Faye
Sojourner Truth
Doesn't leave you when your marriage breaks up
It doesn't leave you when people
When the
FBI comes to try to hit you up in prison she want all that by the
But this is why I want you to read this book
Did I'm really
Really
Angry
But what happened to you
Because I've been there and done a lot of that
God
Amen
He's talking about like
People investigating him for financial malfeasance
I've been there I cheated on a lot of s*** too that's what I'm really
This book is so good I mean this book is great
Yeah there is a real sense to throughout this interview of them being like
Yeah it look IRS and the FEDS are trying to snatch us up for this crime and
Look I commit crimes
They're trying to get me for any but I'm doing good
I feel bad about the sins that are b b y
So a lot in her life
And I'm not going to sit here and
Make fun of her for
Personal struggles
But
I am going to critique
The used
Of those personal struggles in order to sell her book
Jim Bakker Show
When we get
Attacked in every area that you can imagine but thought of giving prophetic word
And said everything around you will be Shake yes and everything around you will fall but you will remain standing in the merger
I'm telling you it is not over
For you you need this book you need the series
Because when you get it you're going to discover The God Who before you ever entered into your mother's womb at all
Already ordained all of your days
And your story ends in God's glory and I'm promising you different this summer you're going to find
Weather on your best
Trend your sister your Mentor your coach or Pastor they were going to hold hands together cuz it is not my story
Thoughts Tory
Through my life and through your life
How we can make it
Through it
This is like to me
Right on the cusp
Of like
What I'm uncomfortable
Because there is a part of it that is
I have lived experience I wrote about it and
You know if you buy my book maybe it'll help you with something you're going through
I don't really think it's that bad
Which is I know enough about her and Jim Bakker that I think it's bad
The surrounding context
Makes it
Prasser
And way more manipulative then it would be if
Just somebody else were saying those things
Because I think
You can't get a lot out of memoir
I think a lot of people
You've been through experiences
That mirror yours or ones that are far more
Stream than yours but highlight certain license
In life I think there's a lot you can gain from that
I just
I just don't
I think that this is
A good place for it
I find it
Incredibly disgusting
Cuz I
I've been to so many different places where people
Genuinely believe
So hard at all of this s***
They do not
They just don't give a s*** about
Any of that
I can't you can hear her
Words clocked in
Like
F******
Weird imitation of an
Actual believer
Now you know it it feels that way
Slimy
Every time she
Speaks I feel like
Who is falling off of her work
He's going to get roast
Groats
Say that I don't
Think that that
Behaviorism
Licitly
Grocer manipulative
But it is in the context
Of this
Because we know that she's somebody who asks for your January paycheck
Or there'll be consequences
Trump's spiritual advisor
And we know I know what's coming up
On first glance that doesn't
To be that bad
Yeah Patterson's going to drop in with a couple n-bomb
But this book like I said
Lori Bakker
Life
Changed your life this book
Yes Lori
Yes
You don't use get beat up
Yeah you had divorce
Shoe had
You know
I mean
This is
What she was a wild woman
Drugs Beyond any
If the Heartbreak
Centerline
And yet
When she first got saved they asked her to be an angel
That fly
And some pictures
But you are an angel my angel but you
Ashiya
This book
You tell women that paddle boards and women have had anything and we hadn't gone through anything Penny just booked is going to let you know
God
Does not walk away
Because not he's not letting Lori speak for herself that much I've noticed that trends
He seems to be talking over her a lot whenever talking about her personal experiences
Don't make me feel all that comfortable
He's very much talking about her like she's not there and then suddenly remembering the
Or not even recognizing there with you
That goes on throughout this
Drugs more than anything she did a wife
Did a
Heart of drugs
Hey how you doing you're an angel you're an
Angel she loved it heroin you name it there's nothing wrong with doing drugs there's nothing wrong with
Taking lessons
From
Earlier mistakes
Inform your future life
Anything like that I'm not interested in beating people up for reclaiming negative experiences
Isn't turning the positive
I don't like this
Mentality though
People don't value our Brokenness right but you're not even
Qualified into you walk
That's it you're not even
Karaoke in process
I don't know if I appreciate
The idea that you
She's putting forth
That you're not qualified
To be in a min
Ministerial role unless you have some sort of 8
Trauma-based
Initiation
Into being
I don't even know what
You'd like
That's if that's offensive okay so what happened
You go to the church
Yeah after Sunday service
About 23
And then the rest of the the elders the deacons in the like they'll circle around you and start
Can you until you gallon of cereal name
I'm sure you are eligible to be
Be in the clear if you haven't
Suffered
Some horrible trauma but you feel called to the ministry
Facturar trauma in order to become eligible to be a part of him
The cloth you could also just read a lot of Stephen King novels
Get really
I don't think that also
No
Not
I don't I don't like that mentality I do
I think it would
Trying to
Express is that you aren't your bat your past
Damages
Is your past traumatic experience
You like
Feels like what's intended to be said there is a reclamation
I'm being overly generous
You if you hear
Hear it that way
Good if the message is
Just because
I don't know I got divorced when I was younger that doesn't mean that I'm not good enough
To do whatever I need
To do or whatever I'm called to do whatever I trying to do
That's a positive message
But when is expressed as
In order to get to that role
It's a prerequisite that you have drama
If the inverse of what I think the message
Supposed to be
Right yeah all I'm all I'm hearing her say is like
Be
The only way that
Like almost again as though she's the intermediary
As opposed to everyone having an open relationship
It was God. He is the intermediate because
You are unqualified
You've you've been fine you don't have that
You can't really talk to
It's not until you have that serious goodshit
You know that's whenever you get to really f***
For him
Maybe
So they're selling this book and it's
It's not just work
Therapy
Okay there's pictures
Pictures of Bonnie
Rare color pictures
What are we f****** doing we're selling a book George this is bad for selling a book
And not just that
With this set of knives
We will also add in
And working out
Holler pictures
What's worse in the Halls
Power right now he's talked to presidents
Yes
Before he went further
And prison guards
I talked to both in the highest call Bruce Wiley was a cellmate in prison
He knows that a lot of
High-end people don't
Right
I know what
Real real high
I hate your type
Church people
They don't want to be around us
Charismatic type people
And so
Spirit-filled
Fire god
He would always watch your program
He would watch
The most on
Fire
Holy Ghost preaching
And the first word be watch did he tell you he watch my show over the years
Weather for the 1st
And I go on here so Robin his
Reception
It's on the line
And talk about loyalty
De Pere Boys Around
I've been with them the people in my building
Have a Trump building
Then we go into
What that cuz every
Boss thing that people think I'm going to the hotel
I trust you can't buy loyalty
God
Relationship Trump building
Really she has a home
One of the Trump building
Fake news and then say you can't buy loyalty but you have
Really expensive
Play bought the
There's some sort of I don't know how
Substantiated they are are but there are some reports flying around the Trump wanted to start a mega
Course
It's alright
Of course it's a great operator
Rate scale
Keepsake keep losing money
Working with properties
You didn't even realize you
You could just say you owe me money or you'll die and then it's fine
You didn't realize that so you noticed that
I think the exact thing
It's like the high-end religious people people in these Halls of power don't want to hang out with us
Charismatic
Well yeah there's a reason you you're embarrassing
But not just that mean
Literally described using
Charismatic type people
Confidence but it's but he's used he couldn't
Stop himself from finding synonyms for the thing that he is
Yeah I prefer a society where are serious people don't want to be associated
Did with people like this like it's
It's a better
It's better if that wall exist
Build That Wall
So Apollo starts talking about Trump going to
Are you ghosts these churches
Really
Batman he'll tell me like
To the church against Apollo
A boring
Egos
I went cuz I wanted to hear about Jesus
He said they talked about their dog and
About Jesus
I said there's a whole nother side that yes
Do you mind
See the public Persona he's strong don't don't get me wrong
I mean I would never get in the boxing ring
That's for sure
You know he didn't
He doesn't start the fight
But he probably will finish it so then I think we need someone like that right now
That's what's up
The Bible advocates for
Hey what's up with times get tough
Get a boxer
Turn the other cheek
Park Your Right Hook
Yeah it's interesting
To me they like yeah
Can I go see Church's I once talked about their dog
You've been selling a book for half an hour I wanted to hear about Jesus
No
Jesus is in the book
We're going to talk mostly about
I love that she has apparently been
Given carte blanche
To just lie about whatever the president
The Office of Public liaison because Jordan
Let's break this down
This is a
Crass attempt to appeal to Evangelical
All of this is an attempt to like
Really
Pull that bass
Back together
Because that's one of the only shots there is for the
Is like making the
Not end of Christy
Sienna T really really afraid of losing this election
Bike this is
Campaigning
There's no way around it this is everybody this is disgusting
You also sell her books she's brilliant yes she is male
About that book
It's written by a woman
Are there pictures in
There are color pictures which is very rare
It's right by one
Okay right
Change This Woman's life
Bright Corey Baker's wife
She lives in a comp
Here's the thing
Do you make Jim's like
Might be a
I don't think it's a checkbook but it's a checkbook
If I kind of say I don't know I really do
I promise you it's
The page-turner broken women should read it
I love the idea that he's saying that this is a chick book
He's not your it's a checkbook over Lori which he's trying to recommend the book
Very disrespectful
The amount that he talks over his wife
And introduces his daughter as Tammy Sue Bakker
Very weird this familial relationship
I don't I don't want to say that there's no love there cuz I'm sure there is
But did they have to be sure there
There could be none and I would be fine but I don't have any evidence of that and it's
It'd be very ER
Disrespectful and inappropriate
Here are like there is
If there is a very strong fan
Unit it doesn't
Translate to the show
There is a there is sort of a
Separation of on show behavior and Affair Behavior
That must be there or else
This just seems like
Weird people
Related
Relate to each other it is
It's
If you put it in this term
This is basically they're off
I know plenty of offices with complete strangers
Who love each other far more than beef
This is
Weird business
Situation
So I don't
Agree with
A purse
But
Paula White Cain
Does not believe
Leave the cheese in
The politics
Consider myself
New Politics
I do people
I Say Yes to God
18 years ago
Story
The Lord spoke
To me and said
Regarding
Trump show him who I am
This is how you reveal the religious conduit con man
Not fair
This is how you do like 18 years ago God said get involved with this Trump guy
She goes in that starts talking to him and through their relations
Zippy realizes like a man
Religion could be a grift
We made a gentlemen's agreements and nothing is in writing of course I debit I gave her
Proof-of-concept
Anyway
Cephalexin
And hopefully it goes
She's not into it's not her thing she does
She does people
Politic right
It's
Decades
Centuries-long
Spiritual conflict
It is a battle of righteousness and wickedness and it did not
Start with President Trump
This is Ben
Battle tried to take this nation cuz if this nation goes
Down I'm telling you this nation
Don't get me started see if this nation goes down
So we are the hope to this world because this nation was dedicated with little white
Crosses
That were marked along the beaches
Down my Virginia Beach then Plymouth that were marked that should we dedicate this plan to take the gospel to the nations in
Then once the gospel taken to the Neches we ushered into the return of the Lord and so yes they want this light to go.
Dim in America because if we do not be the Beacon of Hope to the world if we do not take the gospel to the world
Then
There's a Darkness but I believe that we are not going to go through a period where there is a 400-year of shut
Doors or windows were have perilous time I believe we are ushering in the Great Awakening and we will
See the greatest
Is Harvest ever
And there's a fight
You're going to get me started
I think you got started
Wow I hear they're just sort of a endorsement of religious Colonial is
I believe that this is a fundamentally Christian Nation
And that somehow our existence as a Christian Nation is a prerequisite for the return of
Yes
I don't like that she's working in the White House is working in the governor
I think that what she just said is something that somebody says a week before they start burning immigrants
Like that is a terrifying
Study different from Alex
Hairstyles long spiritual warfare between Good and Evil
America is a Christian Nation is very very close to what Alex
I wouldn't want him working in the white house either
For now
I get that people think that it's
Or that
I mean to us it's more important
But if you truly believe in God
Him giving a s*** about an election
Is the same as him
You should about whether or not
The Cowboys win
Yeah I like
It's infinite guys to an extent it's in the way that you get around that is
Is that you make the argument
In some way
That if Trump wins
He'll be able to
Italy reshape the
The entire government
And turn it into the Christian government that God
Wants to exist on Earth and has wanted for all the time
No but he doesn't
Well you would say that
Because he didn't say
Paula disagrees
Well
We could go in circles
But that's how you sell that's how you sell the importance
Do it like yeah you know in the next
4 years of trump
Stays in
It'll be even more Supreme Court Justices that he's able to appoint and then what happens then
Bada-bing bada-boom all these liberal laws goes or what go away Voting Rights Act is thrown out civil rights
Electrode out controls on churches being running schemes Johnson Amendment
Abortion gone
Absolutely I will turn this into a Utopia for a fusion
I don't know somebody
Got millions of dollars in the works in the White House
Yeah that's not to say that Trump being
In office
44 more years
That that possibility would bring that
The sales pitch
People who Paulo is talking
We can transform this country
Into a
Well let's not say theocracy
Because we believe that that has a loaded word chili enchilada
In in Form and Function
This could be
Christian theocracy
If
Do you have enough time
All I'm so that's why it's life-or-death
If
Trump loses
All the good stuff that he's done gets rolled back
Whenever the next person comes in
So that's that's how you turn it into something more important than a Cowboys game but yes
For you and me
It does seem absurd
That's the God Is A Thousand Years
Yeah
Wait
Okay now I got it I was heard that I always heard that the other this is the whole proof of the pudding is in the eating
Situations M the god of the Dead
I might just be quoting a Rizzo lyrics
Anyway
I'd like to read from Wu-Tang 416
But the big thing is like this idea that
Trump be in office will allow
Rollbacks of reproductive right
Essentially
That's one of the major selling
Impala get to that a little bit
They want to fight President Trump because of what he's standing for when you or the most
Pro-life president ever
So when you were looking at all at least others
The biblical
Pay attention ask God to download to you
When you are willing
To abort a baby at 9 months I don't like the sex
Skillet that called Murder
But yet if a person is pregnant
You can a double and then you kill them is considered a double homicide now watch him a spirit
Standpoint
You're only
To Nation
That would do later
Portion
In this world
And wontons lessening
You ready
So now you know it from a spiritual
North Korea
In China
Paula is a damn liar liar
She is a liar
Same
So that the issue that I come to the kids very
Differences between
Providing
Reproductive Rights even up to late-term
It in
Particularly where
A person's life
At risk or the the child would be on viable outside the womb
Those sorts of things are very different than someone murdering a pregnant
Thursday Elemento
The rights
Being violated by a murder
I bet y'all are not there in the conversation of
You going to let's say
Electively ending a pregnancy even if it is in the 9th month when if you give birth
The child doodle
Leave for a couple hours and die of
Painful death
No one's
No one is providing
9th
Month abortion for someone who's like
So it's going to be a boy I wanted a girl
That is that doesn't happen that is
Fake talking point
That she's putting forth here
But the big lie
Is the two countries
There are seven countries in the world that allow elective abortion
You just choose
Who get an abortion
Improper
After 20 weeks
And they are canada-china the Netherlands North Korea Singapore the United States
And Vietnam
She just chose to say China and North Korea because those are the two big Boogeyman
The anti-communist extreme right-wing circles which Jim Bakker is a religious offshoot of
So it's definitely not in their interest to muddy the conversation by bringing
Canada in the Netherlands into the conversation
No no no
It's much easier
To just pretend that the only people who would allow this thing that you're again
Are in these countries you've already established his code words
That's b*******
Well just listen to
Their reaction.
Those two countries
We're like that there is nothing
I
Appreciate more
Somebody
Who goes on
James the word of
Insta lie directly to
Over and out
Bright there is nothing
More in keeping
With the teachings
Christ Dan Rochelle
So I do know Alex believe that were fighting with actual demons
Principalities
So does
All white game
So now you're looking
Thanks 4 minutes
Spiritually
Wrestling against flesh
Can blood and I know I'll get a lot of backlash that's okay bring it on
Alright Ephesians 6:12
Says we are wrestling against
Principalities
Wickedness
Principalities power
Darkness and wickedness
There are strong men that we know there's a
The Jezebel spirit
We know that's operating there's a leviathan Spirit we know that top-right and get here by Bon just understand
Behemoth
Bilal
Abaddon
The Bible tells you what the principalities are
The Bible declares with the strong men are
We can do it but if we don't go in and war against it as one again Believers that have authority
Heaven and in Earth
That we have power through the blood of Jesus Christ is not a natural battle it's a spiritual battle
And when you look at the only other two that do late-term that is murder
I'm just dealing with one issue I'm not even telling you all the good things for doing the religious
Lower Court Supreme Court
You are so gross
That is
Discuss
Damn damn damn
Spiritual victories are he has appointed justices that's what she's got
For medical this is a religion
Completely
Separate political
Appointing a lot of
Justices to the Dodgers judgeship
Yeah I mean that's really
No no
Religiously appointment maybe the point that she wants to
To make
But won't make
Is the part of her religious belief is
Political
Maybe part of the the the thing that
Trying to express
But won't
Probably
Well what were you then
Is that there is a political dynamic
And advocacy
And in action
That implied in her application
Jennifer religious
Are you trying to get rid of it
I don't know she has it honestly
I don't know I've never I never look into those sorts
Because I think a lot of people just sacrifice their 501c
C3 status in order to act like your Baker does
I think I think that some folks
Like fuk it we're going we're going to go too far we're going to get in trouble let's just
I've already been to prison once
I don't I don't know if it's a little bit of a mystery
I would be I would be surprised if you
He pays much until
But I also wouldn't be surprised too much of
You just said
It's not worth it
I find that
They are
Cuz that's one of the things that they're going to
What is the fact that he
He is appointed
They're not going to camp
Doing anything
Cuz he hasn't smoke point
Are they just
I don't actually know but I don't know where's it at
Greater
Sorry I didn't
Get to the bottom of this alright stop episode
It's just so
Nakedly hypocritical
That idea of
Here's what we are proud of
We're proud of him
Appointing judges
Who are going to brazenly rewrite the law
Fit our religious Zack bialigy
You cannot if if you are campaigning on a pointing
What you are really saying is
I am destroying doctor democracy
Through the courts
One of the things that's so
Hypocritical in
And gross about this too is one of the things that
Commonly in these right way
Doing circles
As an attack on Islam is to say it's not a religion it's a political ideology
The political system mask deza is a religion
And I don't believe that
To be true I don't think that that is a
The fair attack
Back on Islam
And I don't think it's a fair thing to say about Christianity either
But I do think
Is it the way that Paula is engaging
With some Christianity
Lends itself to be also
A political
So when when you have these people who are attacking
King Islam with these
Pacific
Attacks
And are acting in ways that are similar to the
Depiction of Islam that there
Putting forth
It just
It's very tough
It's very it's very tough to swallow
It is
It's just it's the religious version of
So much
Up like
I know exactly how we're going to Moline my opponent
We're going to say they're doing what we're doing
And then no one will know incredibly effective
Such a universe
Application
So
Most of the beginning of this episode
What is selling policy
Trying to move this book
It changed Lori's life although Jim won't let her talk about it
I think that might have been the way that it
GIF it's no longer allowing her to
To talk so
The middle part in I get a little bit of trump is great I'm not in politics but here's all this political s***
Then
Towards the end
Begets
Big
News
God has spoken to me in the last
Last 24 hours
It was it's time to Launch
My final
Network
And
You don't have my 80th birthday in a few
You're not going to retire just told me you're not going
Guitar solo
It's fine
Give me strength to keep going
If you can keep
Hero
Paula going and keep you all of us going people
Amen
So today
On this broadcast I'm introducing
What God is
Please bring it to me next and by the way I'm
New Year's Eve
I want you to
Listen to me
A New Year's Eve
God woke me in the night last night
About this program a New Year's events going on
God gave me
A full download
At what is going to happen next
Oh God
It's so shocking I'm not going to tell you now I won't tell you this week
God willing
New Year's Eve
Will be my first major New Year's Eve
The dress
So he's
What is happening
God revealed something to him back in New Year's Eve
And then our next New Year's Eve
Gotcha
This can't be a very important prophecy
If you can wait a year
Well the fun thing about these text property
Is that he's going to announce something that happened into
December on New Year's Eve about what happened in
Convoluted nonsensical
But easy said that
New Year's Eve Suites week for religion
I'm thinking that you just
Mixed up that New Year's Eve prophecy and whatever God told him within the last
Well yeah because in the last week
I told him
To form his
Last Network
I don't know what that is
My will learn a little bit more
God
Spoke to me
That we were two
To finish this studio ever Studio
Under construction for the last couple years
There's the building
And inside that building
Has no
Equipment in it yet
It needs the walls and everything
Debate put in
All the
Lighting fixture
It could be done in 90 days
If I had the money
And it's getting so difficult to raise money because
Little people
You shouldn't do this you shouldn't
Sell items
You shouldn't do this thing
You know what
If you got a good idea that works out
I'll take
Exactly
The ridiculousness
So that is like okay
You going to go to work and work
For free
I mean Sears
Oh wow wow Paula
Boy
But follow in the footsteps
Jesus Christ
But I'm not doing it for free baby Jesus you better fucken give me benefits to I want good in
Jesus
Are they building a new studio
Yeah and he's pretty self-conscious about raising money because
Now people are making fun of the buckets
And all that is rightfully pointed out he's an evil being
Yeah might have flown under the radar for a while and then people started
No posting little clips of
Him doing this absurd bucket
Twitter is out
Look bad
Stop him
No I mean hey
Zoe's
These starting the
You need to build build his new studio
Because he's starting a network called
The voice of the prophet
He wants to run 24 hours a day very reminiscent of Alex
I do know everybody wants
These people don't
Nye's
That one of the things that's the biggest problem with the media
You nowadays
Is the 24-hour cycle
They don't realize that they will fall victim to the same thing
Be the worst thing possible
No voice of the prophets 24-hour
Add a prophecy Network
Be it be ridiculous if he sucks diminishing returns
Davida's Astros idea
But
You need to do this
Because
Prophets of things
To say sometimes they might want to say something at 3 in the morning
All right I mean that's a good argument
So anyway you needs you to give him a bunch of mice
The voice of the
The prophets
Network
Prison God spoke to me to build a network
And put his last night
Bugatti spoken to me to go
Major televised
Amen
Twenty-four hours a day
Where God moves
What are the prophets
Said
Jim
Is going to broadcast
The events of what gods
Healings and miracles take
Place up here on this phone
Add so where to go to
And we had we can do this we can do it in 90 days
We could be on there 24 hours
Richard day
Beaming
Loudly
That's our PTO means profit
Talking loudly
And so what the studio is there that's the
I renamed
The studio the voice of the prophet
Studio
And
In the
Entrance
The lobby
I called The Atrium
Event Studio
I have a
Picture
But my dream of it
This is the lobby
The Hall of the prophets
Atrium
And Jesus God willing is going to move
There
From here
Because this is the Hall of the prophets
And it's going to it's going to have a
Yep
A place we're going to put glass
Ibrance played on those who give this
$1,000
The gift
DeVille
Infinity
Open the network
Twenty-four hours a day
An openness Studio
So they can broadcast
Twenty-four hours a day
So you give $1,000 you get a plaque in the hallway
Is he forcibly relocating Jesus it does seem like that against the law
Jesus is everywhere and within all of us
He's evicting Jesus from the Morningside
Stevens with vinegar
Rent control Dan and then he's big developers come in trying to
Donate money to build his
I don't see a fundamental reason why he came
Just do what he's doing
Now like
On some sort of the streaming
Service
Like any kind of
Ikea's website has streaming capability
Like you could just
Get on
Nile overhead
He has a studio
He's filming this very episode in
I think one of the reasons
Can't do that 24 hours there
It's because this isn't his studio is state is in
Ballroom
Yeah yeah yeah but a long
DeWalt
This compound
Involves
Living quarters
Federal write-off
24/7 then people are going to be like turn it down out there
I think so
Icepeak
I think that's the fundamental problem I think that makes it so he needs to move the the shooting space
Right from that
I think
Ridiculous
F****** Transit
Parrot
Bulshit
80s
It is
Amazing
Amazing to me that you could litter
It's not Lisa
Because it's like
Purely Megalodon megalomaniacal
Like it is not it is not practical
It is not a way to make any
It is it is a it is building it
Asia mandamus
It is building statues of f****** Xerxes
So that when he dies
He has something to leave behind
I think that's part of it but I also think that the people like Jim Bakker in this scam
Any kind of community
They probably see all signs being green lights
You have gas you have Trump
Indicating that he's not going
Into an anyway
Encourage
Enforcement of the Johnson Amendment
Shinzon Church
Behavior
You have him putting Paula white-cain
Pain into an official position in the White House
You've got to think like
Now is the time we got to strike while the iron
Hot we got to do whatever we can
Expand this Griff
Amion
I get why you do that
That but it also
Woefully Tran
This is just like
All right we got to do this
We hacked
Have to get going on this year
We can make millions and millions of dollars
If we can just
Point we need to get to buy
That Windows going to be closed
Eventually I'm Amazed
How come from
Well I think
Terrifying
As if they're that
Well until the election
Right right
Right
Trump wins
In 2020 they have a real nice cushion
We're going to run rampant
2020 doesn't go their way they still have a year where I am
We can make
We can make a move here
Eminem challenges
People who commented
After Trump to
Tamp down
Explain political capital in order to
Undo
Whatever
Monstrosity
Rope horrific monstrosity is fair but I haven't seen him go but
I only saw an artist rendering of it
And it looks just like a
I don't know I wouldn't be surprised if it looked like Jim Bakker
Like that's that's the level of
Narcissus
Castleware deal
Yeah
So in the next clip
Jim kind of rewrites his own legal troubles
From the 80s
People do not
Stan
But I have talked to people
Boonton government
In prison and out
Believe me it's a lot of
They were afraid that I
I was going to endorse Pat Robert
For president
And they thought with his audience in my arm
They had no chance
Against
Pat Roberts
And he won the first
Yep primary
So they thought
Talk about
The
The president who
Ronald Reagan
I mentioned to him
I said I'm going to do everything
We thought the Carolina Broad
Everything to deliver 50 million votes
Political
Avenger
Brought into his home.
And we helped
When
That present
Tooth presents
Political about that
Temperatures along about understand
All these prints
Work
Political
So a couple quick points first
Pat Robertson did run
President in the 1988 election did not win the early Prime
He did end up winning a couple
He took Nevada Washington state Alaska and Hawaii although the Washington one I believe
If I understand correctly
You may have one because of something like manipulations of
Procedural
Thanks there was some there's a strike on Washington
He didn't even make it through the entire primary cycle and he dropped out of the race on May 8th
16th 1988
Jim Bakker wasn't indicted for his mail fraud and wire fraud until December
1988 mistrial wouldn't happen until August
The timeline for this doesn't really matter
If it all
Also I suspect at the
The person who told him these things while he was in prison was Lyndon larouche who was his cellmate while he was in the joint
Lyndon larouche
You'll find it
I do not care about the second-hand prison gossip
It's probably coming from the
You're supposed to lie about
About being the political wing
Just give me a lie.
Delivered an election is a fine thing to say
I guess so
So this is where we get to the point where Paula
Who is just been here
And selling her book
Now really
Active
It helping
Jim trying
Get money
For his duty
And this is
So important
Even at ATI
Keep filling my
Spirit because
80s of unit number to God
8 of course means noob
Beginnings
10 is the number of
And gods
Hey completion that I'm doing this
Going to New Beginning
That's what
The cycle of Gods
Completion form
To be released in
Into your life and that there's no
Hebrew word is Quincy
The we know that everything that's why
Eternity
Yes it purpose
Has
Eternal purpose
What's your destiny
To build this
It had to be
Watch when you're 80
It might feel like a
Delay but it was not
And right now
Someone is about to
Send you that million-dollar check in
Jesus
You just see play need to be obedient
Weather 100,000 weather alerts
$7
It's going to be one
That you have your plot
This is beautiful as blown away because I was like he's going to think I stole some of my stuff from him
Has God been downloading several things
Or Sosa
I'm planning the same scam wow f******
Wow
I I mean
I am a little bit in awe of her oratory prep
She remained her ability just keep talking yes
Jesus Inc
Marge Owen
She's doing the tent revivalists
If you actually listen to these longer clips
Everybody talkin
It's disconnected it's rambling
It's using
Rhetorical devices
Where you say like similarly framed
Fragments heatedly God is love God is well God is Faith is like what
Repetition trying to come up with the next
Can you say I got done stand-up enough to know that like sometimes you forget where you're going
And you have just little things
You can say yeah to like fill time while I call that's my next day alright I'll get into
So much
A sort of rhetorical prowess
Is just those tricks
The same things that you
You do it over to be like okay I know how to make it sound like I have a point
And that's kind of a twelve-year-old kid
Thousand
There's these tricks work
So I find it
Tasteful
That she now has an official job in the government and she's on Jim Bakker Show saying like
Hey
You asking for $1,000 for a plaque Christian Prophet Network
You're going to think I ripped you off cuz I'm doing that
Do that
You work in the government
Now
This is distasteful
It's a never-ending
Exorcist 2
Isn't that that's that's so
Like
So much money
You got more money than you
Feed bugs and all you can think to do is
Try and scam more people out of
F****** dollars
He's not getting $10,000 donations
You getting
Five bucks from people who f****** need 5 bucks maybe you know a thousand dollars
Yeah absolutely but look dude what you don't
Is
That
This money
There's a ledger sheet
In heaven
Every treasure you give
If you're on Earth
Is being stored up in heaven
There is
Department of Treasury
Inhabit now I know mnuchin's over down here but I'm telling you
There's a department of
Treasury
In heaven that God
Is watching over everything you do
And you are
Storing up Eternal treasure
It will go so far beyond I think that we can even begin to imagine
You are mandated by God
Willimantic I know I'm
I was supposed to come share my book
But I feel a mandate to help
You build this
And gods
Has removed the pressure
Move the burden that you are not
Kerry burden
That would stress you out
It would make you physically
Yogurt to live well over 100 years
I'm telling you in the I know this spiritually because there is much
For you to do and it
Does not spin
Stretch your body stretch your mind and listen there is no stress on him
By the spirit of God is hip trying to get the gospel out which means that somebody needs to do their part and
You were that somebody and when you step up your life is about to be revolutionized how do you think I got out of that
Trailer God is about to make a supernatural wafer
For you right now and your obedience to standings
With Jim and Lori because it's really not your dream and all gods
Just shows you the best
Is God
Scream because he knows you'll be obedient
And that's what God wants it so you're not watching by coincidence
God wants to heal you he wants to bring you into yourself in Greater but you got to line up here when you line up your something
Greater gets really a man
That's wow
Insane wow
She's talking directly to the people watching
Home wow
You need to obey
Wow
Fuct
What's so interesting about this
Is that there's a
Believe that
He's expressing the people like Jim
Shouldn't have to feel stress
You'd be relieved of the stress of the
Millions of dollars that they're trying to make in order to operate exactly how their operating now
You should be relieved the stress of having an extra thousand dollars that you don't know what to do with that's the
I mean that's a fun way to say
In reality she's
Not
It all
Recognizing
The stress of
Everyday people who they are targeting
No
Cruel
Imagine.
If you
Imagine hearing that
And not think a like if that's your brand of
Christianity or if that's the only brand of Christianity been exposure but imagine listen to that and not coming to
Conclusion that Christianity is a fundamentally corrupt
You know like just
Man
Hayhurst
It's so much for
Making me try and defend the ideal of what
Text Bots
Or whatever I don't know
Through these sort of
Minute examples that
Good versions of religion become very
Clearly identifiable
I think maybe there's some value them exist
Sing for that but I also think they do way more damage
I think there's value of them existing Animusic
Maybe there's an interesting
Something that she's bi
Presenting here though that
Did you know
If you're the person who believes
Nothing and you're watching this
And you have Paula White
She is someone who is a luminary
In the Evangelical world
To the point where she now works in the f****** whiteout really don't like you say credibly credible person
In this fear has political clout
She has religious cloud
Jim Bakker Show he's one of the Legends in the game
He's talking about how God his
Called him to
To create this new voice of the
The prophets Network because prophets need a place
God is golden he must do this so he has to do this I came on to talk about my
Book by field
So drawn
To helping you pull off this
Miracle
To you out there listening
You need to obey in sending this money
Because Jimny
Dresses of these Financial things
If you're in that position
You're listening to this year
Scented with
A couple of possibilities
What is that I don't have the money I can't do it like you literally don't have the money then you feel like what I can't
Be a part of this
Religious thing
Or you do have the money
Going to give it then
Your
Not just that you're killing Jim Bakker
Your disobedience
T'god
Right or you have I don't know
$1,050 to your name
I do this
You have to do it or else or else your will punish your creating
Dichotomy
Choice
Abusive no matter what you choose to do
It's just a trap
This is a sick trap that she's putting people into
Who have gone far enough to believe
The virgin
Of religion that she's putting for
And I just
I think it's gross
It's so sick
It's cynical and in
In a really abusive
It really is
Play f****** parasite
Siphoning off
Worshipper for
Mind-boggling
But
It's not like Polly won't put her money where her mouth
If they can go get my check and write a thousand dollars right now
There's the obvious
The first movie The First One
Going to need a receipt for that
Tell somebody to do something
So she's all run get my purse
Can you have a second one
As
Will you run get my purse in the back.
They already put on the screen the $10,000
Which is the profit
Armor Bearer
Those are people
Not only to help me do the studio
Especially
Going to be helping
Weather
The
Chamber you know the
The prophets chamber could you hear about the prophet chamber and
Hey Meghan King
But the Bible says
When you
Give to a prophet
You receive a prophet's reward
Amen and I believe in God
To folks that will say Jim I just going to join this $10,000
Armor-bearer we call it
For the prophet
This is so vital
People that I am bone way because
Cuz what you're doing for him to have a studio
In Florida it's almost
I'm sitting here going this
Just like God is speaking
This is exactly what I'm doing in Florida this is amazing
Still wouldn't be compelled by this but I would think it would be interesting if you know
I'll give you $1,000 and then Jim's like the $10,000 level if I did not give you something
I'm sorry
I can
A million of those but I cannot
In the 50
Revealing has stupid
We're like your your grandpa's armor level people were like that's f****** stupid
Prophets armor level f*** off
There's an interesting thing your we're like the conversation around this this network in the
Being obedient
Is Donald
Thousand-dollar level witches
Still a lot of money for somebody sending Jim Bakker
But it's
Not in the realm of
Comical
Kind of
You know it's not
It's not to the point where you're like get the f*** out of here
The idea of giving him this amount of money in the
Text of like
It's obedience
To give it to Jim
And then you escalate a little bit
So now this $10,000 level it's all the other stuff we talked about the thousand-dollar level it still apply
Still in there. You get bored
It's an escalation
So you know it's important
But there are profit
And they speak
And it's not just because profits are psychic
That's that small potatoes
It's because they are able to wheel words of God in
Existence is something I really don't think that's true this is weird
Without a
Prophetic word
Then the people
So when the priest mouth was open and the prophets mouth
People prosper
And prosperity is not
Got money
Prosper mean
To advance
Breakout to break through
Brake Force
It means there's no way you're going to be able to
Breakout breakthrough break
For without that purr
Prophetic word
It is not
Just
Foretelling but styling
To win a prophet in their many true prophet
It's in the Earth right now
When the prophet comes fortnite
Don't just for tell it's not just
It's not like a
Psychic or something I mean familiar spirits can do that
It has
What God
Do not only download the word of knowledge the word of wisdom Discerning of spirits
What is the prophetic word
So it's not just for telling it's telling for that shifting you into a
Which is what ecclesiastic
Stories of all about
The gospel eternity in your heart
To the will of God can come to pass
So when the prophet
Get the direction
Then the intercessors have to come in
I'm praying
Through which is why you got your
Have you got a chapel over here
So that the people can pray
What the prophetic word is and you say what
Is important because if somebody doesn't do it next
Actions are going to go down
It's just that simple to right now
At the PO box
Ovary number
Wow so that $10,000
And be a part of this
I feel at such an urgent
CMI Spirit right now
Holyshit
Wow
Holy wow
Wow that's an ad pivot
That is should be f****** a homeless
He should be homeless
Because she is the type of
The person who is begging for your money who would s*** on a homeless person
If they ask
She might actually in a couple clips
She's a f******
Yeah
You see so clearly there this
Like okay so you need the place where the
CrossFit
Can come and speak
We also need all the intercessors depraved well course that's why you have your compound here
What happened then the West is gone or whatever so please send me your money. Please
You better or jack-in-the-box
What uses rude for her
That is
F***** up
Not least because profits are apparently just
Chiropractors they're just going to align you better they're not going to bring anything they're not going to actually bring anything into exist
With what is
God
That was a
Big pilot.
It definitely is
So they can move on
From this poet does come up alot the giving the
The money for the the new Chapel
Studio
AMW
I think it's more important really to focus on what they get into after this
Which is some of the more like I know she's not.
She's not she's awful
But it's important to recognize
Is this through Pala
Jim Bakker has a direct line to the White House
She became the first woman to pray at the inauguration
Using the name of Jesus
And she
And your other
Ministries that you help
Doing it everyday and I was praying everyday and worshipping in the White House
When we Coronavirus
Hahaha
Orchestrating
August direct line is direct connection between
Kim Foxx like Jim Bakker in the in the White House
Yep this is
How you end up
This is one of the things it's like
It's so easy
For them now yeah it is so easy
Someone like Trump is so
Very easy
For them to
I don't know how much of it is
Playing him and how much of it
Just like
But whatever it is like okay
This is good there is the question that I have to recognize this is like
What's going on in the world right now is so f***** up
But this is like issue
Instable find X
This would be a very pressing issue problem
It will be easily very quick left
To its own devices this doesn't get better
Yeah and I don't see any reason
Why would stop
But like that that's what's so crazy about about the world right now
Is just like
I see this is a very very very soon
But I also recognize
But it doesn't
Yeah
So
You know again she's not political
But Trump is going to get rid of the Johnson to me
Super into this is where we get to
Can about someone
And that Johnson amendment in the buck
Which the thing holding a rat
Your President Donald Trump that you work with
Said
We're going to stop it
Because he looked down we were up 26 warranty look down he goes
That guy he said you
He gets it he understands the church
I said the church is the only legal entity and the Earth
It has the authority
To bring true transformation
And President Trump
What that
Hornet and the power of the Blood Bought Church of Jesus Christ
And he said you were the most powerful people
He's saying this to Pastor
Cuz he knows that Fitbit is the word of God that transforms a life
And he said but that guy down the street there that homeless guy
Has more
Power than you do in your pulpit
To make a change
And he said
I'm Preston is a. Not going to happen
And it has
Jesus
Or boy
Yeah that's not good
I wonder I wonder is
Like I wonder what is going on in those me
Like I wonder if she is cunning
Trump
Or if they have a
A business agreement
As equals
Do you know everything yeah I don't know I can't speak to that
Hey
You you deliver me this
Voting
Right I will say f******
Go hog-wild I have no idea I couldn't even begin to speculate about that but it doesn't it doesn't
Like either would Shock Me
Exactly
I think it's probably more likely that there's like an
Between between
Didn't recognize
It's not like you could probably be around Paula white-cain for very long without being like
Thumbs up
Even if you're oblivious
Kanika kind of get what's going on so
I would be surprised if
It's an outright Khan
And more of like a hey
There's a lot for you to gain
From keeping a Stranglehold on the Evangelical vote in the country
And
There's a lot for me to gain
If you get rid of certain regulations about how churches can operate
So
Let's
So look dude the issue is that she's not political
But why would you want to get rid of the
Wow because that's about God
The freedom is going to disappear
Sure as they get their way unless
In 25 the freedom of America soon if we don't
This election is so important and it just scares me what is going on
We already know
It is
Potential
Third one we didn't need the time
But it is very potential
We could have a 4:30 even if it
Now that makes
Let me tell you what that makes some people do
That's going to make
Dispense into it is a device
Toosii
Because it's going to either make you stand and have to look in your word and say what does the word of God saying where do I line up
Where do I buy not Impala
I might not like the personality I might not understand and get my book and you'll understand the personality and you'll understand
Person okay
You're not just a persona
But
Where do I line up
And you're going to have to make a decision that won't be just held accountable here
How things turn out for you your children or grandchildren
Stand accountable before 1-day not based on your opinion you're hurt you're wounding what you think what you don't
Educate yourself
Know the issues know the word of God
And then if you cannot align with the word of God
I just
I don't see it so if we can change the Supreme Court
Like we are already changing it and we can neither
Lifetime appointment
You don't think all hell is trembling right now
I am traveling right now
Is it freedom is going to disappear unless
Trumpkin fundamentally reshape the Supreme Court towards more
Extremist religious Christian views
So she's not political
Neither weed it's it's
Interesting
For that to be such a
Such a
Thing
I understand
A place of like not owning your
Place
Your place in the system
Please find really
Layman
I want to be involved in advocating
Fundamentalist religious
Positions
Vet spillover in
Politics
I now work in the White House
I'm not into
It's just
Lame it just lame
And here she drifted apart
Takes a little more in a very dishonest
I can tell you things right now in certain States they've already passed lunch
Just like Shannon state
It says the Bible is
The book of hate speech
It is only a matter of time
Laws already passed
People are sleep
In my opinion
Do you think this next election
Could change America forever if
The wrong way
No Doubt
Absolutely
So when people like Paula say things like that when they tried to save their laws being passed the declare the Bible hate speech
Really important to get down to what the laws actually are that they're talking
Because I've seen other sermons that she's given I know that you
Pacifically talking about a law in California
Sensitive very common talking point
For her as well as other dumb dumb television
The law that she's talking about is assembly Bill 2943
Which was written
To ban conversion therapy
A segment about the bail on one America News Network
Place that employs jakpa Staubach
Argued that this was going to make the Bible hate speech and Outlaw the sale of the Bible
From there it became a hot talking point with
The evangelico crowd
Confirming their worst fears about the state trying to oppress them
Conversion therapy has been shown not to achieve the desired goal which is a phrasing that I'm uncomfortable with but honestly I don't know
Know how to express that point any other way
These people believe that they're able to change people's fundamental Identity or
Or persuasion are sexual orientation
But it doesn't achieve that goal
Nope. I hate I hate
I hate that I can't find a better way to say that
Because even the phrasing
Imply that there is a goal
It's a brutal practice
That often involves trying to attach negative stimuli like
Nauseate shanor electric shocks with homosexual thoughts or feelings
And I don't understand what the difference is between that
And like you said torture
Yeah that's good
If you read those things
Oh that's A Clockwork Orange
Describing A Clockwork Orange and that's not always the case
But it does
Enough very well worth
Mention
A recent study published in the Journal of the American Medical Association
Lynx quotes of your psychological
Distressed
Made it subject
People took
Conversion therapy
The co-author of that study found the quote
People who are exposed to conversion efforts any time in their lives
Have more than double the odds of attempted suicide compared to those who have never experienced ever by professionals to convert their
Gender identity
Study also found that age is really important
And the people who are subjected to these things
Even earlier in life
Have a four-time
Times higher rate of attempt
Suicide
Very serious issue
Conversion therapy as applied to things like gender identity or sexual orientation or barbaric
Humanizing
An absolutely cause severe problems for the people
Subjected to those
But Christian fundamentalists like policy conversion therapy is just part of their religious out
It's what the Bible would tell her to do
So if California is Banning conversion therapy
Then that's actually
California banning
Her following the Bible
This is extremist s***
She may have a soft lilt to her voice
She may not be saying that she wants
Kill people who don't fit her mold of religious beliefs
Apologize not give a f***
About living in a free Society
She knows that she
Can't really make the argument that she wants to make in reality
She can't say
I want lgbtq
Atq youths
Subjected to brutal therapies that don't work to make them more likely and make them more likely to kill themselves
Because I see
I think their identities are wrong
She knows that argument doesn't play in a free Society
Socialize
To move the goalposts
Turns it into an argument with California
Trying to outlaw the Bible
Because that achieves the same end result of
Put anchor pushing the radical extremists
And more importantly
Keeps the sweet donation
It's coming in
You can see how this easily could like this exact same logic could be
Be used by anybody who wants to push some
Form of religious
Yeah I mean switch it out with
Female
Like just stay in the realm of the Bible
Like you could say we should Stone adulterers
California passes a law that you can't text Outlaw they're trying to outlaw the Bible
Yeah I mean
The fundamental logic that's being used
Is sewed
Deeply
Disturbing
I just
I can't handle stuff like
It's missing the forest for the trees
And the forest
Is
Deep
Abuse
People who don't fit your mold of what you're the world you want to live in it
Well I mean the
Basically the they're trying
To save it
Torture is religious
I guess if that's the argument that we're having
That's what we should be talking about is it okay for torture to be part of your religion
Where do you come down
With you okay
I don't know how much this could be
Kind of a slippery slope
B
I don't see it being
Too far of a leaf
For her to then
Like apply this outside of just
You know
Lgbtq
Tfue related
Conversion therapy
Type laws like
How
Big leap is it
Vertu be like well
Muslims
Who don't want to be Christian
The Bible says go make Fishers of Men spread the gospel like
Putting people into
Or
Centers who don't
Convert to Christianity
I love that undergo conversion if you want
To do that
To let's say Muslim
And someone says you can't
You're ruining my religious freedom. It's outlawed
People whenever they hear the word Allah
Fine you hate religion then
I understand that that is
An extension of this logic
Maybe
Maybe too far of a leap but
It it does follow from the
Precept she's putting forth
That that would be considered somehow a Banning of the Bible and saying that their Bible is hates
Yeah it is it's nonsense
It's
What should be is the draconian
Gay conversion therapy should be too far out there to make as a slipper
Not
Pull on genocide
Is too far out
His work is bigger than a
Jared Taylor
Yeah
An Impala
Is just
Actively trying to get people to say
Doing this
Is bigger than me and it's so much bigger than made it is which is why right now you better write that PO box
And not just get the book and not just
Get this which is exclusive to Jim and Lori not just send in 35 but you need to send in 3,500.
You need to send in 35,000 you need to send in that hundred-thousand-dollar check because you know God has blessed
You know what a blessing this ministry and now there's a launching of a network
I'm telling you in God has mandated to in the world and their right mind
Would build a network at 80 years old
No one unless they had a Chihuahua or
Yeah I guess so I mean he's old so you can't be slamming
He's a liar
I like that sort of like
The argument
Well he's going to be dead so why does he need money
Okay
Alright
That works cool
Weapon Applause line so we heard it's a very
It's very much
Kind of been couched in do you like there is something to gain by giving him
Which is
You know manipulative I still think it's wrong but at least it's
Hey like hey you want to support the ministry
So you should give him $35,000
$100,000
In his next
And last clip
I think we're getting into the stick
You know that did the threatening stick
Where it is changes
Words now if you don't give him money
Negative things play and you and your son might be getting ready
To eat your last
Cake and your Crews might be failing and your barrel of meal might be failing but I'm telling you if you do not write that PO
PO box and you do not call that toll-free number and you do not become a Ministry of sustained or you will never see sustainment in
In your life and your dream will die your call will die because God sets it up that way that what you may
Make happen for this ministry and is used to stain it. Says your cruise is not going to fail your bear was not going to fail
Your son might die but he's going to be resurrected because the enemies going to come in but I'm going to cause life
Sustaining to come to you
I'm going to cause your life to be sustained your son's life to be sustained
Your money to be sustained your massages. The saying your business to be sustained because you are doing what I have
I've said to do and I am telling you
You are so right on right now because we know
I hate to call this an interest
But we know in the industry so straightforward you probably never going to have me back
They want to stop they want to keep charging us more and more what we want to do get the gospel
We know that we want to preach
Uncompromised
We know that they are closing that window Tighter and Tighter on us and if we don't launch our own network
That we have the ability through technology to control our voice
A come together as the body of Christ
Then I'm telling you they are trying to shut down the word of God
They're trying to shut it down
Do you know like if you don't give Jim this money then nothing that you want is ever going to
To come to pass
It's so gross and if you do give him this money your kid might
Might still die but he's going to come back and have him buddy
Department of Treasury One More Time come on
2 gross things
The treasury Department in heaven will recognize it on The Ledger and they'll pay for whatever restorative Health Care is made
Better if he was good or bad
They're going to pay for
Medicare for all in heaven indulgences are great I think everybody saw that
That worked with the Catholic Church
And it was
This is gross
Like it's just
Disgusting levels of
Cynical
Money
Grabbing death
It's going on here on this show like whether it's through
Trying to get her book
Sold me know that you're Baker's already talked about a by the ton of people's books
You've already made the money call Pamela
So you know
You're trying to sell this book
And then trying to get hundred-thousand $10,000 donation
To build his f****** Studios we could do a 24-hour prophecy Network
Just it's
And the way that he described the problem
Vertu's like
There's going to be healing there you see who's pitching the TV show
We're going to have a healing
I know that's hot on YouTube
Yeah it like
To put a button on the
I mean I know that
Baby you've brought it up a number of times but like
I find you so immensely boring
It's a plant
Parent cash-grab it's disgusting
What he's doing to people is abusive
And I resent it entirely
Brahma humans
Point and from a person who doesn't believe that religion is intrinsically evil
From both of those two endpoints I find this
Tubi
The works
But it's also super boring and I probably wouldn't even cover this episode where he's trying to raise money for his
New film studio
If his guest didn't work in the White House
Like this is the connection between the
This world is so explicit
The connection here is Boracay
Explicit then Alex
So
He's guy in the white house has Miller
Like Steve Miller's not coming on the Infowars
I don't even know the words to I'm speaking in tongues
The word I want to use about this
So if you would like to hear Dan speak in tongues more please
Donate thousands upon thousands of dollars to our new Foundation we're going to do a 24/7
Where to call a Tongan with Dan I think we should change it just going to be rolling ours
Pictures of the whole 24 hours
Endurance tongue roll
I don't I don't like it that I don't know the word but this is the strongest possible terms
I
Vacaville
It is it really is like
Oh man there is no bottom
Isn't a bottom there might be a bottom but it'd be interesting to know what it is I think
I think the bottom for people like this like a gym or Apollo or a Lori is just like
Being allowed to run all scams they want to run
That's the bottom
What
Removing any
Anything
Gets in the way of them fleecing
Gullible and vulnerable people
Is the bottom
Yeah I don't think they have any interest in going much further beneath that
Like I don't I don't know if these people are ideologues
They might be they might be but I think that their ideology is far more about the scam right is
About extra look like social issue
Right now granted
In pursuing
Pursuing their scam
They end up hurting a lot of people in political ways I mean a lot of these people also
Go insane
And start to believe there
If they didn't
At the beginning
You mean people like Jim or the people like they're listening
Does L Type Stone
Don't usually
Have
As they
As they continued
Popularity and you can see a lack of restraint even involve the way that she
These long
Diatribe
I wouldn't be too surprised even issues like on
Atwoods
Anyway I find every time
I take a look at Jim Bakker to either be
So bored as
To just be a waste of my time
Or so just disgusted by what I see
That this is one of them
This is this is one of the ladder types so
Achievement of sorts
It is impressive
To think that I listen to Alex Jones
Bentley and this is still like it raises the needle a little baby
It's a dubious distinction that Jim and Laura and Lori and Pollock
Can have the even in my unshockable state
Jaded mystery listening to Alex Jones
You have disgusted
Congratulations
A wolf
BoBoiBoy
So
We will be back not as well
But until then we website
World's on Twitter
We are is that knowledge underscore fight
At go to bed
We're on Facebook
We are in a few would like to download the
Show please go to iTunes
Cheerleading reviews
Or some other
Yes but I'll be back next time
But until then I'm Neo I'm Leo I'm dzx Clark
I have the keyboardist from Journey who we forgot to mention in any way on this episode is married to Paula White Cain
Holding