Damn important
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
MoneyGram
College fight.com
Everybody was fighting
Indeed we are.
Have you ever had an
Circle Appliance
Low.
I mean when my house burned down a few years ago when I went back
To the apartment
Like we're able to
To go in like my oven head like
Oh really yeah that that's the only
Yeah you never had anything like actually happened I had a blender over like
Top of it cuz I was using it wrong
I don't know I don't I don't think so
Took out my hat nothing like a man
Because I had a toaster oven that
My grandparents bequeathed
That was from that was made in like this
And I used it
2 years ago
I just moved in with
Just exploded into started a bonfire I thought everybody had likes
I got nothing nothing I can remember
If it didn't leave a mark on me
Right
In conversation so I'm going to Pivot
The subject I want to talk about the I started playing the new Luigi's Mansion
Why did my question
A lot of thoughts about it
Luigi's Mansion 3
It's been very
Emotionally resonant
I would say what kind of was like one of the first games that I played
As an adult
Sonic video games
I played like Megaman
The Mario games of Donkey Kong Country
Yes there was a little bit of a break
From video games
And like when the GameCube
Came out my buddies had it
Luigi Mansion was one of the launch titles
And I f****** love ditlove run around the vacuum sucking up ghost naturally it was a lot of fun
And I wasn't able to play Luigi
Listen to cuz it wasn't on a system
Write anywhere to make
In any shape to get
3DS
So I never liked was able to
Play I heard the third one was
Who's coming out of like
I'm so excited about this
I am so I got it
I plan it I started to realize
Aesthetically pleasing out no tell me you're having fun and it's absolutely
Fun enjoying it quite a bit
It's low you know Alexa
I just played in a day or two
A lot of replay value in some
Some games like that
But it dawned on me as I was playing at the like
I am
This is a lot about money
Okay you going around this Mansion is haunted you got to like suck up a ghost and everything right
You're like banging on trash cans
You know trying to vacuum up the walls because sometimes dollar bills a fly out of you and coins
Super money
Interested game
Kind of like at the end after you beat the game it rates you based on how much money in
You probably and that's
Determines what
Seismic
Can you end up with a review of this video
Just kind of Forgotten
How Deeply involved finances were in the illusion
And I was like this is a strange
Video game
All the Mario games run around collecting coins
There's something weird about the dollar bill
That is true bars of gold
We have coins
In the real world
Disiena video
You're just not programmed
Well because I think it what you're thinking
Is like someone had to print these dollar bills but at the same time those coins have imprints on them
I want to know I want to know who's in charge of the treasury and Waluigi
So far it's not running to Waluigi I don't know if he's in the game but I think he needs to
Perfect opportunity to throw Waluigi into the mansion
Stalinist you go to there like money is very evil
I thought I had along the way play night we just match
I know a lot about Luigi's Mansion
Alex Jones
That's the fun we have on this year show
Imbalance
So Jordan today we're going to be in the present we have been looking at November 5th and 6th
2019 cuz I was just got Buckwild did some stupid s*** even haven't been able to avoid
Pretty much all over the news as everyone knows Alex Jones
To be a juror in Rodger Stones trial
The legality question surrounding it
No matter what the situation is
He's still f****** stupid
And we'll get to that hearing about it before we do Jordan
Take a moment to say thank you
Because signed up and are supporting the show
So first
I don't know if this is the celebrity I don't know if it's the celebrity
No it is not it is Taye Diggs
The most handsome man ever thank you so much
Jacob the second most handsome and ever you're now about to walk
Next professional wizard thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Are you very much professional
Thank you so much
Journal policy wonk
What's the most Jack
Text Sarah
Journal about
Sarah finally likes a thank you to a couple people signed up on an elevated level we appreciate
Miles
Thanks a lot you and I will take
Blues thank you so much
You are also now a wonderful technocrat
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
Things about smiles and very much
I enjoy the show like sport these Gents
Do you can do that by Corridor website knowledge fight.com
Sports show we would appreciate it very much
Lovely so like I said the big news will get to as we get to it that Alex Jones is trying to meddle in the affairs
Sports
Classic
Texting on the Infowars
Circuit
Let's say
Every time there is a big
You think that Alex Jones does
Often times if you watch the entire show
You find there's like other things guys probably should have pointed out here there's a whole lot of things
Debatably are worse yet
Alex Jones caught committing a crime and then in the same episode he starts peeing on a
Checking into like a why is not going to talk about that
What is llamas in the studio
Arab talk about the goddamn Mama's alright
I will see there's a number of things that are like really important points
In his coverage
Over the course of the
Nothing to do with Rodger
Don't naturally
I thought that's what the register
That is absolutely important you know that
We'll discuss it all
They're going to start on November 5th here and Alex begin to show searching for the top
Story what is the top
Story
Don't know if I agree with where he lands
Ladies and gentlemen I said here this morning cuz I got here at 9 a.m.
Pondering all the news all the clips all the guests all the information
They're about to be covering and just
Thinking what is our top story because it's more important than just what is the biggest news what's the most interesting news
What out of the spectrum is most important
It said an advertising if you go with the worldview of advertising that perception is reality
Well if you're on 10 hits of
LSD
And you think you can fly like a bird you jump off of 20
Balcony at the concrete below you're going to die
Now your perception is that you'd spread your wings like an angel
The phoenix like a lark
Crow
Is Amanda.
That's the only Birds we've got there going to be
Cheating on you
Perception is not
Reality
What actually
He is and what works and what replicates and what succeeds
So what's the top score
Lice
Israel
Universal rally
So is top story
Appears to be that there is an objective reality
Big news that was that was good stuff
Reality exists
Good stuff man
I needed that I knew that I was listening to that like this show is not going to go anywhere good
Admitted one of his
Where do I begin what let's establish that reality is outfit that exist
Okay
Good
Joe Alexander gets from there
Reality unless you're taking LSD
Yes but no but then reality is still real bigger perception will be different than reality show Perception
He's not real
Do advertisers say hello
Alright I was stuck on the birds eating
Is teaching class
The student
So Alex goes from there any jumps to some stories that he's got about cartel murder
Their offense of US citizens that were killed by cartel member
Recently
And the Alex gets
The story and he believes that it's a cover-up
Then I'm going to discuss what my initial theory was about that
With the caveat that everything I'm about to say is not correct
For you at least nine people including six children were killed in an ambush by Mexican drug cartel
This happened in the northern state of Sonora police believe the attack to be a case of mistaken identity
Members of the cartel opened fire on a convoy of three SUVs that were part of the Church of Latter-day Saints
There are 13 people missing as of news time while no identities have been released so far witness at the scene said
Some of the victims were his family members including his wife's cousin twins 6 month old babies and ain't you
Ten-year-old the national police and military forces are heading there to defend the area
Whitewash and defend
What happened
It was targeted
Including
Nine month old babies killed at point-blank range
So they were kidnapped
So when I heard him say that they were targeted
A hundred percent that he was talking about there was a story in the New York Post
It came out yet
Discuss how this
Group these Mormons that were down in Mexico
They had connections to the nxivm sex cult
How yeah
According to this New York Post story quote The Outpost Mormon community in Mexico is where underlings of the nixxiom
Cult leader
Keith raniere recruited young women to work as nannies
In an Upstate New York compound run by the accused called
So the Nexium recruited Mormons know they use the Mormons to recruit young women in Mexico that
I would then be sent to Upstate New York
To work at this
According to the New York Post is reporting that and that information
Who's coming from a man named Mark Vincent
Who was hired to make a documentary about next
So I don't I don't know how much
He is a fully accurate Source yet certainly
We had some exposure
The group that's wild if true
Oh yeah I'm not entirely sure but I thought that's what Alex was talking about
I like I just sort of like
I expected that to be the angle he goes down so
I had this whole thing
Prepared about why that stupid have to throw it out
You start looking into the case
You see
Something with somebody is reporting
This connection with the Nexium
Osteen one thing there and now we've got
Way for him to tell this story that you got to Angela
But it's not we'll get to what it's actually about here in the moment but after those murders pretty strong but
Possibly too aggressive
Response
He called on Mexico to declare war on the cartels to which Mexico
Can president Andres Manuel Lopez obrador said quote
The worst thing you can do is have War
We declared war and it didn't work
This is not an option
I don't feel like I'm in a position where I can tell Mexico how to solve its problems so I'm not going to try
At the same time I definitely understand transfer
Response where you have to take it seriously what u.s. citizen
Things are being killed abroad
Route to the extent
You might be doing that selectively
Maybe you can make an argument that that's the case
But I don't really care to make that argument
As a way to sort of like what about all these other people who were killed
Super
Worthwhile life
To go down
I don't really know what to stay here
I think this is an awful piece of news that's come out
And I don't separate
Particularly care to try and make it anything other than that
The tragedy
That we need to be doing more to try and avoid having repeat
Whatever the best strategy
Towards that is
I would say the
Probably have
All out War
With a cartel
It's probably not the best strategy
32 years and in that time
I can think
America winning every war that
It started I'm pretty sure that every war that the United States has been involved in they have
Completely one right
So I had it in my head that's like
Going to get into the snake
That's right in his wheelhouse
He starts talking a little bit more and I realize
The Mormons got
Killed
In a crossfire know if you watch documentaries about Mexico
A lot of Mormons went down
The forties fifties and sixties to proselytize
Add
They won't pay tribute to the cartels
And they get killed
And there's been Mormon Vigilantes not this group other areas that
Support the documentaries made
About it till they were targeted but brown people never target white
God that's that's yep that's your right
Chevy Magnum
Whites are inherently evil
I completely blew it with my initial Assumption of the Nexium connection
Somewhere else and then now it's just too obvious just a f****** race here
I was like holy s*** there were Mormon Vigilantes there's going to be a moron vigilante
Cartel War we're not going to worry about
Get the government about no pictures
Brown people killed what grade
One day I'll learn my lesson and stop trying to understand what you might be saying and just assume that it's all read it wrote it in his deep White
Really need to learn that lesson eventually
Don't see it coming I constantly give the benefit of the doubt that it's about something else and then got out now
Mormons didn't start going to Mexico to proselytizing the 30s who's more like the 1870
Many of them to go down there to do charity and missionary s***
But a whole lot of them also were running from the United States where polygamy was outlawed
Mormons have
I had a very healthy presence in Mexico for a long time
In 2014
TV reported having 24 missions and 13 temples in Mexico with over 1.2 million members in their
The issues related to the Mormon present to Mexico is complicated
And I'm not sure I can credibly discuss all those issues
But what I can do is say that Alex has absolutely zero reason to
Turn this into a race
Even if everything he's saying is correct
And that these people were targeted by the cartel because Mormons and
Mexico have a history of standing up the cartels
That still has nothing to do with their race
It would maybe have something to do with their religion but that's
It's not really a fair assessment to say that all Mormons are white
Well. Search with the number at 85% of us Mormon
Being white in a 2014 release
The same is not true International
It's a pretty common thing to hear from LDS folks that
Conversion rates
Did Europe in the United States are not
Growing
And one of the only thing that's keeping the church alive is
Is latinx converse
And eventually
That will be reflected in the u.s. Mormon demographics as well
From 2000 to 2010 the number of spanish-language churches
Went from 377 to seven hundred
It is a community that is
Massivelyop Norman
Yes yes
What Alex is doing here is equating the Mormon Miss of the victims of the
Describe with their whiteness
We just kind of eraser
Things to do
He can make the argument that these people were targeted because they were Mormon Mormon tour just disrupting the cartels
Ability to operate and we could talk about that is a possibility
I'm not really sure if that's true
It possibly could be
I don't know
But as long as he's discussing that is a
Siri and not proven fact
I'll probably just say that whatever
That's not what he's doing
He's taking the argument that they were targeted because they were Mormons as definitively prove
Then swapping out white for Mormon
In order to take the story of 9 murdered US citizen
And turn it into fuel for his white identity outrageous
This is disgust
It's super disrespectful to the victims of this crime
Honestly a very clear
Example of how racist is
Yeah yeah
So
Alex starts rambling around
About free will
We now know reality exists
And also as an option to that Free Will exists
I need to start stalking
Free Will exists and so evil exist
Because we have the power
How to make bad choices
God
And God's creation
The universe
Is a piece of work
Story tonight
Embarrassing
I was on The View
George W bush in the bush
Computers are so dumb
Legal Wars effect WM
That I was at
Leftist
Rcnn showtape show
She's an older woman
1235 14th
We doing later
You can tell this woman
Very interesting
Alex is mad The Joy Behar on The View said something to the effect of like
You know Beto dropped out of the race
Answer
Movies like you don't tell people to take their guns
Wait till you're in office that kind of okay
Comedian
Right. Advancing
Specific policy
As much as she is talking s*** on The View that's her job
The word for work
Straight up a think tank
Writing policy
Proposals the people just copy and paste
According to Bill of course
So he's offended at that so he decides
Man you know I
I know a lot of that type
A dude that's like
What's the name name any person and I love don't have like a story of like a time when I was
Almost
Yeah you rewrote that in your memory
It's a possibility that there's that rewriting that goes on
But it's also a possibility that
Alex just
Have to be case maybe every
Every person is trying to f*** him at every man wants
What's the fight him unsuccessful
So that's
The healthy
This is what this is family show where Alex is talking about Joy Behar trying to have sex with her
Sort of invalidating
You know that's also another album
Really f***** up
She came onto me
So Alex gets into now
Talking about
But he has like a
Almost the entire sect
Of the show
Do you know whole brakes break
A rant
About how
We need to reach
People who are against
Guns
And we need to
Reach out to them
Okay they're all fools
Okay
Takes us to a familiar
They've been inducted into a fraud and if they get deeper and deeper they get more frantic
But the fake degrees aren't paying off in
The system isn't putting them in charge they were supposed to be the ruling class
The priesthood
You got to explain to them
Email scam man
They get the first money and then the people don't but I bet they've been kind of a sucker for more money
Turn on people pay the Nigerians 1015 payments
They don't want to admit they got caught themselves or their neighbors are in denial
I think evidence just keeps mounting that Alex fell for that Nigerian email
That's it I didn't even know you could go to or more than to pay my
I never knew I thought it was one payment then they went away they'll come back
Yeah that's weird
I don't know if
The Nigerian scam Works in such a way where they do
Payout the first like the Nigeria the people running the email scam not that I'd off
They they give you that money
We need more money so what are you just send that money back
I don't know it's very strange
Whatever the case I believe Alex
Probably leave
It's so singularly focused on it like there's a there's a berry
It's strange
Oh yeah
So Alex talks
About those
Citizens
Circled
New Mexico
And then there's another story
But a New Hampshire couple that was found dead
My Padre Island
They were found
Buried
And Alex's
Connecting B story
And maybe he should
The fact a lot of Tourism go to Padre Island now
Because hundreds and hundreds are coming up missing including children
End up shutting down anyways I just got to Mexico until we stop it
What President Trump has declared
War on it
That's all these deceptions kill people
They don't want you armed
So you can't protect yourself so you know if you're coming down from New Hampshire I know it's pretty safe to go camping in New Hampshire
Camping in West Texas Reese Texas North Texas
You don't go camping
A few miles from the Mexico border 10 dangerous areas in the world
Unless you want to die
Public service announcement
We don't have a gun get one and learn how to use it and no we're going to be parked out
In the dunes
Next to Mexico
You better have your door locked and you better have an AR-15 or ready to start killing
Because there's a good chance you camp out
Enough time
Their common
And they're going to tie you up
I'm not going to get your bank codes off your credit card
And then they're going to put you down on your knees and they're going to squeeze a couple bullets in your head
After they rape your wife
In front of you but it's okay cuz they're brown
White devil
That is sick
Daddy
Do you told me this was a family ship
This is not a family show
So when I was talking about Padre Island like I said Cormac McCarthy
He's talking about James and Michelle Butler
A couple from New Hampshire vacationing on Padre Island were found dead buried in the beach
He's taking this story in a sort of combining it with the story of the Mormons killed by the drug cartel and unified story about Mexican
Killing white people in the media covering it up
As for the media covering up the Mormon story that's absurd
It's been reported literally all over the
If Alex's complaint is it the media isn't reporting a story of being related to his fans
Taxis of a race war
Then I guess he's going to have
Deal with that
They have reported that the police have said that it's a mistaken identity situation
And even if the reporter suspect
That's not the whole story
They have journalist
Journalistic ethics
Consider and uphold real journalist
Just throw around feelings and
Conjecture the police say this but I personally don't believe it
That's Alex's job
In terms of the butler's from New Hampshire Alex is very likely completely wrong about that
The couple's bodies were discovered on October twenty
Seventh time of this recording the case has not been fully solved
But
On November 4th police released pictures
Persons of Interest in The Killing
They were caught on surveillance cameras when they tried to cross the border in the butler's car
Which they had stolen
The driver of the car Pierce to be a Caucasian
Who the police identified as Adam Curtis Williams
When they put out a warrant for his arrest
The warrant is for suspicion of felony theft so it might be a situation where they just
Suspecting of taking
Car
It seems unlikely that in this case
The theft and murder wouldn't be related but who knows
I don't know what
It's going on for sure
I don't know that this Williams character is the murderer
Person
But it does seem pretty well established that he was photographed in the butler's car after the murders heading for Mexico
Man you know what that means
It has nothing to do with
Where you're from
It's where you are the Border makes
People killed
Dan it has nothing to do with their f****** ghost
People around that area I would like to remind you I would like to remind
Does not react alright well
I've got a hunch
So
What's going on is there zero evidence that this is a case where there is Mexican perpetrator
That's something that Alex is entirely imaginary
Based on his feelings that there was violence done against white people in the vicinity of Mexico that must have been done by Mex
This is a pure expression of his over traces
In case we're available evidence directly contradict
Does racist assumption
By the time he's on are here. We're listening to the 5th
And the photos of Williams driving to Butler's car have been released
The day before
This is entirely unacceptable
For him to be getting on are in agitated
You know it's fine cuz they're brown in your white devil
This is
Explicitly
Deeply race reminds me
So much of a
You're pretty sure of something
Myfaulkner
Where the guy is just
Reading the board
Paper and there's
It's like a
Man still on the loose thing and
Turns and looks news
Probably in Edward and then just moves on and do like
That's racism right there you got no information
Just like Netflix this
Supports my x-rays even worse
Because there isn't for
All right
Who's wanted that the police have put out a warrant for by the time he's on air
But he has every reason to
Not have
Narrative
Reality
Is not perception
Jordan
That's his top story
Is there is a reality
Unfortunately he's just trying to create a race
Trance I believe
Is profoundly race
Here's what happens directly
10 they're going to squeeze a couple bullets in your head
Your wife
In front of you
But it's okay cuz they're brown
White devil
The cartels write the
Porter's panics as well and everybody else to get their hands on because the evil is spreading
Is that we're here fighting because of your support have together
I want to encourage everybody to go to infowarsstore.com right now
I get great supplements bread products you already need
4/137 double Patriot Point 47% off
Gross
The cartels evil is spreading and they're going to rape your wife and then
Shoot you that's fine cuz they're brown your white Tahoe
Please go to my story
He's like a coin-operated races
Yep
So Alex
Saved starts complaining about how these
These proud boys
You're at your call this to Cowboys
He's got sentenced to four years
Prison
Forgetting other crimes
Sure Alex
Is pitching a narrative that they were just defending them
Themselves against antifa
Fair at all based on
Again reality
What does not
Perception operating
We've had hundreds upon hundreds of antifa
Quote people arrested and nobody's being
And there
Barely arrest anybody but everybody that every probably and all that
Whatever the case is Alex's found out that this judge
He's got he's been involved in other key
Does 20 do believe it's just a fresh judge what did he fight another judge
Judge fights another case that Alex pink
Indicates
That this guy is up to no good
You got the very same judge
Play The Proud boys all these years in prison
David admitted
Convicted
Pedophile
In New York
Almost no time
Inhale
There's a right here in prison for attacking
Rolling Stones
Water bottles
Protesters
Do they attack
Free Speech people
Total inversion haha
Who had Choice words
The proud boys
Did the Orthodox Jewish man
Has he had sex eight times
When a little boy
He gave him basically no
Shelton
Even though
He admitted it
To get this said right up top nothing I'm about to say should be interpreted in any way to mean that I think that this Orthodox Jewish man
And what he did was not as severe as what the proud boys
I'm not interested in grading horrible things on some
Some kind of an evilness scale like Alex's
I think they're both awful
That being said there's a reason that bruise
Leave it's received a lesser sentence
The proud boys
That has to do with the fact that
The proud boys plead not guilty and were found guilty
Which will always result in a longer sentence
For you
The two proud boys were found guilty were sentenced to four years in prison
But they weren't the only proud boys arrested after that game for fight New York
Two of them took plea deal
And only received community service
Others plead guilty and received sentences ranging
From 40 weekends where they're released
Go to work during the week
You can all that
I'm up to three months
Imprison
Like the people who cooperated and like yeah we were in a f*** it we're trying to find a ride
Generally speaking admitting your guilt to a crime you definitely committed is seen as a sign of pasta
It's often interpreted isn't it
Indication that you're on your way toward making amends
For your misdeed
Societal Stan
Sandpoint it's in everyone's best interest
To support that kind of behavior
In reality Bruce Lee prevent accepted a deal where he pled guilty
It was sentenced to two years in prison
He'd already he already served 13-month
So most estimates say that he's only going to be
Prison
A further three warbot
This could be interpreted as a 3-month cent
And spit in reality
You should already been about half sir
I don't know enough about the leave of its case to comment on it really at all or whether or not you should
Longer
But I know enough about these two stories
To tell you that the reason
Cowboys got slightly relatively longer sentence
Is because they took their chances on the trial and blew it
That's all it's going on here
Alex is trying to turn it into a thing where this judge
I love pedophiles and let them go fuc the proud boys
And that's just not the
Yeah I have no judge was the one who determined the sentence
I'm not entirely sure if it wasn't
Thinkware
So I don't know
But whatever the case I would
I have no interest in
Any right-wing arguments about
Disparities
They're all they're often
Ring false
So I don't know if you know this Jordan
Climate change
I know the ezine full recession we're finally getting back to normal
You don't know anything about this
Fair is that
Call Jaden
80's dress
Deploy in order to
Carbon tax
We all know that my brother told me that Obama Bots
Some property in Florida so we all
Alex's talked about that a couple times
But climate activism just back carbitex
Absolutely no
The consistent piece of Alex's rhetoric
You got it
Now
What's interesting
Is if you pay attention
Alex take some of his long-standing rhetoric
It completely
Will make you less lonely
Does junkie.com
The most
Alone in Jupiter not healthy and highest rate of suicide
I'm sorry are you quoting chunkys.com
Protest for carbontastic lovely painted the world richest
Stor-all exempt
And I will save the planet
How does the tide of the pedophiles where you're the globalist pedophile Rings you're involved in all this
How are you going to sell the public on letting them track everything you do
AI
Super removement you may
Exempt themselves
Jeffrey Epstein
Billionaires
Wall Street Journal
12 years ago 11 years ago
Groupon
By Michael blumberg Ted Turner Oprah Winfrey
George Soros
Bill Gates
Rockefeller run by Jeffrey Epstein
A secret world government group to save the planet
I don't want to put too fine a point on this but I've heard Alex talk about this very same group of globalist billionaires 4 years
They were definitely discussed as far back as endgame which came out like 2,000
In every incarnation of his narrative the group has been Oprah Bill Gates Ted Turner the Rockefeller
Keller's sometime Soros when he realized I got to yell about this guy
Times Bloomberg
He's not always
Included
It's a it depends on what stage of his rhetoric is it always Bill Gates Oprah Ted Turner and David
It literally has never involved jeffry Epps
This is a completely new part of the narrative that Alex is adding because he knows the Epstein conspiracy
F****** hot pics
Yeah they're the
Play Summer's new winter
I don't know who wasn't wasn't connected with Epstein but I do know a whole lot about what Alex Jones is that in the
And he never said that Epstein was involved with this group much less running it
This is a very similar behavior that we see
Throughout Alex's career
He'll take hot topics
Some current events Andy bolts his rhetoric to suit them and pretend that he's always been on this
Case forever
He's definitely been yelling about this group you insist is dead said Auntie population forever
So if you look into it you'll find that he did talk about them a bunch
But he's completely changing the story now
I search through the archives of Infowars in prison planet and there are there are zero stories
They include the words Jeffrey Epstein on Prison play
Plan it before January 1st 2016 and there's only one on Infowars
Which is just a 25th
London examiner article the paper
Repost it
Is Alex knew about him as being the big player in the globalist
Machine Esurance s*** didn't
It does seem to have left much material behind reflector
On the website
That Wall Street Journal article Alex's siding doesn't mention Epstein it all one of the sources for That Wall Street Journal article is enough
Their article in the times of London
Which also doesn't
What does tell us that the host of that meeting was Sir Paul nurse
Who is a Nobel prize-winning biochemist
Putting it very bluntly Alex's just making this s*** out of
What Alex is doing is a cynical exploitation of a horrible story
He's taking the story that is very suspicious
And twisting things so the suspicion matches his own narrative
In an attempt to reinforce
Susceptibility
310 steps ahead of the globalist it all turns
And I find this
Behavior
Disgusting
In better times I think this would be
Yeah like in bed like this has all the classic
Like
This is the conspiracy
Very kind of
Then you know that it's this guy and then and it's all run by Epstein
We just sausage
Justly died and that's
Slim Dunkin
In 2000
No.10 we're all like
Hahaha you're crazy
If it's a friend and you're smoking weed and I'll be back chairs
It's a little annoying but kind of fun
The Logical conclusion of
Mainstreaming this kind of
Dumb conspiracy theories
And this is yeah it is right
It is if we used to be something that would be fun.
Now it's like you pull out one of these
Conspiracy theories
You know 6 people
Jesus
F****** cry
Alex brags about his courage
Baby boy
Is very brave boy
Any discusses how he had a moment
And I think you said when he ran away from his problems
No I think that he has a little moment
That reinforces
Some of the theories that I've been
Putting forth
Something Beyond courage and I'm not saying that to active it's not courage it's
Driven
Divide these people at
Angry
If I'm not doing enough but I never get rest
I never feel any satisfaction just more more get them get them
The Holy Spirit pushing me
This morning about 8:30 I had like 10 minutes of ecstasy
Just Envision in their defeat and knowing we're going to win and just
The Holy Spirit was so strong that good
Good good now we're getting were supposed to go
Because you don't care any what happened to your mouth
Totally committed and you know we're going to win
And you're calling on my power
Come down into the Earth through the people and they're doing it and tell them to that more that's what you're supposed to do John
On the Holy Spirit and on Jesus Christ intercessor to God and we will defeat these satanists
You're on the right track Jones
You're going to be a preacher
Oh okay
Oh I thought he was going to re-record ready to die by Biggie but apparently no
No he is gone
To be a preacher that sounds great I don't know how much to put in
Fake to put into that like I could just beat him
Rhythm
Do we have
Pretty strong indications
Is that Alex's
Becoming
Well he's always been religious
Larry Moore
And it does seem to look like a maybe you would be wise to Pivot this into a completely religious
Grab
These made too much trouble in the can
Spiritually and politics world
It seems like you should hit that ripcord
I'm trying scam on that level
You can go away you got to go away to come back
You got to go away to come back
Yeah totally
He can do it you can do it stuff like that
Like yeah
You know God is pushing me forward yes Jones yes you're going to be a preacher
I have a difficult time knowing whether I should
Interpret that is like
Hey what's coming is I'm going to start ripping religious late or if it's just
Play hey whatever you're doing now is
Yeah I'm not sure which it is
But it's
The most clear demonstration I think
So far that Alex
Sees himself as a religious
Talk about that in the last couple months to do you like
God is telling me to announce my leadership role
I think so
I don't know
To me like when he says preacher he would mean
Like biblical Prophet that
Accurate
Pronouncer of my words
Yeah there's some of that but it's hard to know for sure right we'll see how it develops I could be both
He's got to be in his Bonnet about how everyone is afraid of devil worshippers
But he's not
Already started
He starts graphically talkin about murdering
Oh okay great people are fighting back
Everybody just a sell-out to evil
You got everybody scared of you devil worshippers
We're actually scared of ourselves
Desire to stop you want to make sure
We spend our will and our blood and our energy and our
Force
Making sure we eradicate your system
We don't want to just
Fletcher throats
But I want to just beat your head in with baseball
Put on just one ice pick senior
Socket
Lobotomy
We don't want that
You want to get
Your spirit
Safeplanet
And out of our universe
We want you to go be
With your own satanic
Forces
You want you out of our world want you out of our Lives get behind me
I just I don't know how he classifies as a
But this is exterminator
Like I don't know what Woods it all Democrats
Eradicate Democrat
From the world where everybody every everybody knows that ever
Delaware
Appointed that all people who believe in global
Which is a real thing as opposed to
The globalist
Globalism
As a
Market
Strategy
Eradicate them from the Earth
Behind me
What I mean when you talk about
Killing Iran
And stuff like this
You notice he's also not saying political
We're past that
That the day of that is good when you talk about
Killing your specific political enemies
This incredibly f***** up and totally response
When you start getting it
Intuit as classes
Is a folks
That need to be
Driven off the Earth we need to get rid of this from
The Earth
You are in it in a territory
Yvette
I read what was it in that New Yorker article was talking about W Cleon skousen
And it said that he was that people were concerned that he's
Is rhetoric was getting dangerously close to Nazism
I wouldn't say that you're getting
Close to
Some ideas that are abhorrent
So we just
Can't have that kind of mentality we need to eradicate
Like is especially and that I know that he's not
Saying that all of his enemies
Are juice
Right he's not saying that
But
We've talked many times about the ways that
Classifieds in characterizes it as enemies
Relies largely on a lot of
Medikpro
From history
Weather
The ideas surrounding the blood libel or things that he's craved directly from the protocols of the Elders of Zion
When you have that
In addition to weenie
Me too
Eradicate people from the Earth
You kind of got to recognize that some people who are listening are going to hear that way
Whether that's your intention or not
Whatever extremist you have in your audience
May hear that is a call for ethnic cleansing
On
Some level
Yeah you know I don't know
So when we talk about Danger
Usually close to abhorrent I think we're already there
For some reason
It seems weird that it's
Less expensive than
Let's target
Do you know what I mean like
Because most likely targeted then we'd be having a
Completely different conversation
That's
F*****-up he wants to
Kill this
Subsets of the pop
Population
His actual rhetoric kind of tree
Mayhem warnings
The Kill
75% of the world
So what kind of imply that there isn't a strong
Popularity for his ideas that would end up being classified as his enemies would be
A lot of people
So that is up
Problem
Like somehow
It feels less important because he's in
Equal opportunity once
To destroy the whole f****** planet
There is some of that but I think it's also
You know
You can't lose sight of the fact that be
Because of that
Serta vagueness
Because of the
Broaden
Open to interpretation aspect of it you run the risk of whatever your audience
Is bringing
Table that confirming
Something really bad in
Oh absolutely so let's say it's somebody who hates
Mexicans
Do you like Mexicans
It's not my fault have you seen their Halloween or whatever maybe
Really opposed to taxes
Have you seen the government that their devil-worshipers have you seen their Halloween or Christmas
I don't know which one it is
And then you could confirm the belief that we must eradicate all of these
It's just irresponsible whenever whenever you have
Apply for a like this
You need to be very mindful of the things
AliExpress
I want your expressing
We need to do more than kill these people
We need to wipe them off the Earth
You have
Can't talk like the
I don't I don't
How
I mean I understand how
I don't I don't get
Thank the person that can say
Terrorizing
Sing you like pee
They're going to
Rape your wife in front of you and then shoot you in the head twice
And then not find himself being the bad guy
I don't want to just
Bash your brains out with a baseball
Kill you I don't want to just do that like
You're the best
It's because his worldview is so
Such an underpinning of it is the
Constant
Defensive violin
He wants
To do only top 25
Carte blanche to do any
Bingo
I understand
Nonsense
So Alex also has James O'Keefe on the show on the 5th talk about his big new scoop but honestly
Drop-in
And it's just Alex Baker
For more details
That was James has coming up in James saying
Stay tuned not giving
No
Well it's kind of a
But in the sense that there is no information
As far as just a commercial for project veritas
And James is such a f******
Recently project Veritas released a video of ABC news's Amy robach
Saying that she had interviewed Epstein victim Virginia Roberts in 2015
But that ABC didn't let the story go to a
The way this video is presented it lends the appearance
People at ABC were trying to squash the story
And that this was a cover-up
It's easy to come away with that impression
But if you're listening to this show that you should know by now no matter what
You are a sucker
If you believe project veritas
After the video was released robot clarified your comment saying quote I was upset that an important interview
I conducted with Virginia Roberts didn't air because we couldn't
Insufficient corroborating evidence
To meet ABC's editorial standards about her allegation
My comment about prince Andrew and her allegation
She could see Bill
Clinton on Epstein
Private Island where in reference to what Virginia Roberts said in that interview in 2015
I was referencing her allegations
Not what ABC News had verified through our reporting
The interview itself while I was disappointed it didn't tear didn't
Meet our standards
In the years since no one has ever told me or the team
Need to stop reporting on episode
I can't tell you how many people I saw who I thought
New better retweeting that s*** saying well I guess project Veritas got one right
It's incredibly depressing the people don't recognize the bad faith actors
Aren't suddenly doing the Lord's work because they're saying something that's closer and lying
Do what you want
To believe
Or what you think is right or accurate
Project Veritas lies
That's what they do
It's their entire business
Miss model right-wing education based on taking things out of context
Conform to a narrative
I know that everything around Epstein is very
And further competent investigation
And Reporting
Has to be done on that story
That is just never going to come from James okay
There's another aspect to this that deserves match
And that is the James okay
Keith doesn't give a f*** about the f
Story
He's doing this to attack the media
This entire thing is about attacking the institutions that have rightly excluded him
I talked about how he's a lying manipulative she'll for right-wing
Billionaires
Ever since he and Andrew Breitbart got together
Nothing about what he's doing brings anything to do to the Epson
Steam story
Literally the only thing that comes out of this is trying to attack the media that is all he cares about
Also the stories that robot was describing were already reported prior to Rochelle dinner view by Gawker
You might remember that Gawker was destroyed after a lawsuit brought by Hulk Hogan
Which was paid for by f*** head libertarian billionaire Peter
Teal
Probably not important to point out the Peter Thiel has given James O'Keefe
Santa Bonnie far back as 2009
The very person who funded a lawsuit to put out a business one of the first media organizations that
The cover the Epstein story is also wanted
Easterly backer
Life's weird
So f*** all this s*** I don't care about James O'Keefe and his Nazi
Yeah what was it we we talked about it
On that day and it was Bass
Why would I
Don't listen to anything that they say ever
However at least ever at least
Don't take it if
I will if there is anything that they have to
Then it will be
Filtered through
Outlet that has f******
Yes
Why would I listen to them
Yeah you can just walk
I hate to say something like this but they have certainly deserved it
Earned the reputation
You can just write off but everybody.
Any information
In any way relevant
Some other outlet that has Juno Independence
Streaks do I will cover that story
And with actual
Affirming
It's just
The trash f****** Outlet
And you know that because every time he comes out
What the scoop goes on f****** Infowars talk about it any more proof that he's up to no good
With this white identity
The shitbag agitator
And that idea of like all willy got one this
Time Life
In what world does he
Picture story and then follow it through with reporting
Like there's no it is purely
Here is what we are going to say
Find us a way to
To say it that sound
Right
It is never going to be
He accidentally stumbled onto good report
So Alex jumps off from this topic
Kenny gets to hey another race story that he's
Is f****** completely lying a
Well we know it's coming it's on infowars.com and newswars.com it's so incredibly important
National Health Service to deny treatment
The quote racist and sexist
They control the jury of the leftist
Mob and media
They call you something
And now you
No jobs
Healthcare no welfare
I'm going to start off by saying that I'm not sure where I land on this story
Entirely
It's definitely not what Alex is saying it is but it does raise some moral questions that I'm not sure I have the perfect
Weather for
The way Alex is describing the story he's pretending that some board of leftists are going to accuse you of being a race
Then when you go to the hospital with a broken arm
They'll pull up your file and say sorry we don't treat racist
And that's not even close to the reality
I feel like if we do have that that week
Rhodes
Exelon
Leftist Overlord
Solutely
This is not close to the reality which again
Is not perception
This is a story about the North Bristol trust company that Services hospitals in Bristol launching a new program called
Aldi red card to racism
In the program if a patient is being abusive to a staff member in a racist
You're sexist way
I'll be giving a warning
Canary yellow car
If they refuse to stop being racially abusive they'll get a red car
And if it's safe to do so at that point they will withdraw from providing treatment for this page
The program grew out of a large Spike and racist abuse being thrown its staff at the hospital and a recognition that
No one should have to work in that sort of environment
I definitely support that
I think the program isn't Superbad
Given that there is a warning
And the fact they won't withdraw Services if doing so is unsafe for the page
If a patient like needs a breathing tube they're not going to jeopardize that person's health because there were race
If you have like a sprained wrist and you won't stop yelling racist s*** they're going to claim their space and refused to provide sir
Dude it's really hard to shout rachell
Pixel 4
Or if you're on a defibrillator pacemaker or what
If it's unsafe for them to withdraw services
Can't do that in critical condition
I'm at horn because my gut tells me that the medical workers should not make judgment calls about who they should help and who they should know
Best kind of based on some idealized feelings
I have about the profession
At the same time the more I think about it these nurses and receptionist
Some doctors their human being
Not unfeeling healing robots
If racist abuse has a problem that's reaching the point where it needs to be addressed at this Bristol Hospital
I feel like I would be
Be shity for my argument
To be that these doctors
Suck it up and deal with it cuz their profession as a
The higher calling
Is this weird thing where people who are known races
Let's say David Duke
I think they were being denied care even though he
Acted politely at the hospital
I think I would be against that
But this program as it's laid out what ends up happening is solely based on the patients
Behavior
And I think that's okay
Yeah I think that's alright
If you're if you're a server
And your table is hurling racist
Abusive
There are so many places that won't allow you to say a goddamn word
You know I think you should be able to do that absolutely
And absolutely there is a difference between a hospital and a
Restaurant there
But people are still the same people who were
Yeah so you're going to get
Rihanna
That's why I'm super conflicted because I'm on a human level
I agree with that 100%
Feelings about like
The Hippocratic Oath
Stuff yeah but I think I think
Reply I'm on the side that I think of
If there was no warning
If they could
Risk your life by withdrawing treatment because you're racist
I would feel very uncomfortable
But the way it's set up I think
I don't know it's alright
And it whatever
Even if I have
Some sort of like
Mixed feelings about it the air on the side of being a
In favor of
Completely dishonest
Based on his perception right
As opposed to reality
I like I was more comedy clubs
Galvanized
Two strikes and you're out.
Perfect yeah
So it's November 5th
Rodger Stone
Trial is starting that day
And Alex has a Rodger stone is sushi
Name Jacob angles on
To talk about
Ingles
Rogers lawyers on Isabel speaker
Tamia Brown
That does not at the tablet
Rodger arriving
Also folks were
Bullhorn in there that Rodger Stone
Did nothing wrong
Full disclosure
I believe that I've interacted with Jacob angles on Twitter before
Marathons are pretty drunk
While I was doing it so I decided to start weeding out some commentary
Okay
One of the people who came on Alex's Marathon was Jacob angles who was just there to talk about Rodger stone is
I have no idea what I tweeted at him
But I didn't add him I didn't add him
It was just his name please
Right right about 1
About 2:01 segmented I got a response from
It was surreal lose like the TV talking back to me
Anyway I can't find our tweets but I don't remember them being too heated or anything I don't have
Any like real memory of being like Oh my God this is
Bucked up yeah
I probably can't find our teeth because he got kicked off Twitter after you post
Some islamophobic nonsense
I know he's listed as a writer for Laurel Uber's website
The things look like they're going pretty great
Grant Hill isn't
Shut that window
He's also
Probably a member of The Proud boys
So
Anyway he is on
This is where the bombshell
We got there today early ahead of Rodgers trial
Immediately jury selection
Was Nirvana communications director appointee
Corrupt Obama era judge say
Persons
Customer service
On their ability to be
This is a sham
Excuse me
We didn't talk before you came on I follow a lot of your cupboards but missed last few hours
You're telling
Slow down and repeat Alex's completely caught off guard by this Alex
No idea what the
Start from the beginning was the word begin there and then
Catch me up in a few years
So this is news to Alex and he does not know what to do with it
Hellboy
Obama era
White House communications director
To be a juror
In the Deep state
You were there.
You're not allowed to say the names of the individual
But
All I can tell you this Washington DC 97% of the District of Columbia
So this is the generator
Small Point Hillary got 90% of the vote.
DC of the 20s
60 election
Even when the correct numbers still makes their point ridiculously hot it's like they're pathologically driven to
Escalade
Can't stop it couldn't be
It couldn't be 90%
Has to be 92
Be the right numb
Yeah
So Alex is immediately like
Got a f****** figure out who this
Person is
Why don't they just have Robert Mueller as the jury
Hillary Clinton
Obama White House
Communications director let's look up the names of who those folks were holy
Mackerel
Oh no that's
I'm going to sic my Infowars people on
Daughter and she's going to die I mean
We can save that pretty confidently or at least that's what he wishes
To happen prior Behavior
Offensive
Happened in the real world
You know I don't I don't
Find
Any plausible argument that he's not trying to intimidate
Play somebody for at least
Tamper with the jury somehow
Where are we're coming off Boston f******
Marathon him
Jumping into a story and releasing a picture of somebody who's not involved
Within seconds of course this is going to happen it is going to be nightmare
Now
Whether or not you could prove
In court that he's intending to intimidate
Is another issue
I think that I can confidently say it from my feelings
Am I experiencing studying
Yeah but in court I think you have a
Much more difficult time
Improving that in
You thinking a jury of your peers you would
It was Be Alright by 12 so Danielle
Wow that would be rude
So ankles wants to talking about how there was a bunch of
People there to support Rodger
And I just think that this clip is really funny
Because Alex
Interrupt
Ingles to go to break
But then he gets cut off by the brake
There's a series of interruptions that happened at the end of this clip that I find pretty funny
Communist train
Protesters
Came out to show sound
Ingles the reporter that Rodger tone trust to cover the trial for him or come back to you
Why
Would you like to get back that full head of hair from years past
It's insane
He has no idea how to handle this story that's dropped into his lap
So you have to go back to the Joy Behar
Just has no timing so you've got off by the brain
I love it
So you gets back and here's how he introduces Jacob angle
Central Florida Post
The central Florida Post is a name that sounds like a newspaper it really does I should tell you that it is definitely not
Okay it is a Blog that Jacob angles run
Witchy names
You're somebody else the headlines currently up on the homepage of the Central Florida Post
Poop taste good
Quote fake news Outlet Orlando Weekly is going broke
Weird Everybody
In this world hates them
Quotes American priority conference host
Trump jr. and Matt gaetz
This one's basically just a press release for an event
Trump Doral property
Quote Disney profit increases upset theme parks socialist
No idea what that one's about
This is blog
Good for Jacob for having some motivation and follow through
I respect the hustle of naming your blog something it sounds like a newspaper
But I can't give this a pass
Use the term
Theme parks socialist
And I had lied
This is not a serious Outlet
Everytime I go to a theme park I'm like
Socialist out of here
So Alex is eight he's had the break
To try and gather his
Is marble
And the story
Is that
This juror had been selected
For the jerk
But this is how it goes
Barack Obama's former
Communications director at the White House
Has been chosen as the first juror
Such a circus the judges appointed by Obama
First Church
Almost over there
So if your standard for who can
Preside over a case of anybody who was appointed by Obama is invalid that's a f****** b******* standard
You'll never get a fair trial out of a judge appointed by Obama it's
It's a nonsensical standard of jury of your peers
Partial judge
Get a Reagan
Maybe not
So
Also Alex is presenting this as the first jurors selected in reality what this is was Just Energy
Reviewing people to be put into the jury pool
Which then would be
I'm downright
It's a preliminary thing
Okay this is nonsense
Did you wasn't selected for the jury is the first round of cuts
Another round
You're going to have the jerk
Yeah and the reporting on it and Reuters
Was saying that the judge the reason
She didn't exclude this person from the potential jury pool
Was that they had said
That they could make an impartial decision
Yes bite their career despite the job that they formerly had
Baker
See this
Impartially
Right and that's the standard by which
People are excluded or
Included in the preliminary pool
After that point
You trim it down
The prosecutor and the defense
Attorney can say hey no on this person
Can strike it for no reason and I have to have a reason
So that's a natural part of the process
If you are a sane person
You would hear this
And you would think
Well
There's no way she'll actually be on the
No absolutely not
So even though she'll never be on that jury is release her picture
So a bunch of people can harass her until she
70 fun
But at this point on November 5th
Alex decides alright Jacob angles isn't going to tell me who this person is
So I'm going to pull up a list of communication
Director we're just going to be committing crimes today huh
Blink
Ellen Marano
Pfeiffer
Anagrams
Reveal games
Call Mary
2013-2015 oh my God
Genpak he gets on her huh
Wow you're so you not imprison voluntary God
Family show Family Show pissing all over everybody
So here's the thing
The reporting on this that was tweeted out by
Damn it I regret that I don't have the person
But there were people from like courthouse news reporters
Tweeting out things along with the trial
And it was
Reported and writers
That the person in question this juror this
Potential juror
Was a communications director for the office of budget and management
Or management and budget
Alex is reading off a list of
White House
So
Has the wrong position
Right and is just guessing names and has decided that it's this app on the Eyrie
Don't understand
How Humanity has gotten a
As far as
The list the real question
Pulling
Pencil people from
Cannot include the person because he's using the wrong
I remember number Sirius etterville numbers
Absolutely
I'm stopping for Poseidon he knows what's up
Balls
Call Mary
Obama's former communications director but I guess his lawyers what Rogers lawyers
More like how my God
What was the judge saying at this point
I can say is from what happened today
There was a
Obama Communications
Was allowed
To be a juror
They said that was no conflict of interest serving in the Obama Administration
Her husband is a member of the deep State intelligence community
Call Mary's husband
Okay
A lot of things but knowing other Wall Works
Recover doing this
What the hell you can't
Call Maryann
To lead the jury to convicting
So what
None of this is real
But yeah
Packing packing it called here what is it
7:25 is America's gone
Call it this is a ludicrous thing that's happened but it's partially because Alex got blindsided by this information and
DeSoto roll with it
He's decided it's this Jennifer Palmieri which it is not
It cannot
Cannot
Nobody didn't just not if Tim
Not he's building up with this case that it is
That's
Cookies rambling around a little bit and I really felt like he was trying to get to a plug
Yeah but he just couldn't do it I thought
I think that you'll feel the second wind
I'm just going to say this right now
Oh my God
Looks like she work for the bill Amana Gates Foundation to all know
They're producing full TV shows
The demon has been funded by Bella Monica
People girolamo stop for the room at our guest
That felt like you was trying to get you a plug I really thought that
Because all of it the good doctor
There's no evidence at all that I was in any way connected
So great
So stupid like that just the dumbest s*** I've ever heard in my life
Are you really
I shouldn't be surprised but
The swiftness with which he came to
One-hundred-percent certain
Is
Just kind of
Astonishing
Like right I've never gone from zero
Still regret cereal choices from yes
You know what I'm saying but you understand that this is partially like
This is what he has to
To do he has to stake a claim really fast
Because all of this
It really is
Like okay we have something we got to run
But this'll get a lot of attention
If we out this juror
Yeah I kind of feel like maybe this is one where everybody should have just
Ignore them
Yeah I think so too especially because from what I understand it's not typing
Quickly illegal what
Please do yeah it's disgraceful and also dangerous
I don't know
Actually know if I agree with you on the ignoring it thing because it is
A really good
Present-day example of the sort of behavior
To why he's a problem
Know for sure
And I think that there is maybe a teachable moment and it more so than a lot of times
I see things being posted about Invaders like
You guys should let this one go
Schleich
The thing there is
Seems like the only way that he is going to get
Enough eyeballs I
Maybe
We still don't know exactly what the size of his audiences
But it is far less
Then the amount of people who are going
See it if it's
Tweeted out by right-wing Washington
Retweeted and so on and so it wasn't my position on it that I know you always like I think that this is a story that is worth
People paying attention
Do and knowing about
Comparison to other times
F******
You don't don't like
Turn him into a meme
Yeah but this is
Worthwhile but I also think that there is
Responsibility to understand it in a fuller Conte
Yeah as opposed to a little sound bite
Of him saying that he's going to out the person
Fisher understanding it within like how does this fit in
Into his
Strategies more generally what is he actually doing what
And I think that those things are something that
I don't know if it's missing cuz I haven't read all the coverage
I'll be wrong of me to say that
No one is
Talkin about the larger picture
But I think it definitely is Miss
Jason from a lot of the
On Twitter
About about this particular
There isn't more important thing
That is part of this story
Without focusing on
Alex and under
More than
Most people care to
There is there is a context that
Okay
That's what I would say
Alright
So in that last goodbye
I told you he was
It felt like you was trying to get you a plug
I'm thrilled to announce
He definitely was trying to get to a plug
Put
Obama
Had Communications directors hell at the press secretary on there
Time machine to go back to 1946 to the Nuremberg
Trials I've literally
Political affiliation is nothing to do with a juror then let Nazi Party members sit
Judgement over the Nazis what a load of malarkey
But they're murdering common sense cuz they can't be, since I'll say this briefly
Oh
40%
That's almost whiplash
Man that was just after the last
Plugs
Snuffy's of the Year under a child's we're out of Common Sense we're about the Ender specials
Do you got to watch out he definitely just got distracted by someone in his ear saying Bill and Melinda Gates
In the middle of trying to get to a Goddamn
What an idiot
So Alex is pretending that the media is covering up
The fact that this a potential juror
I was formerly
The office of budget
Did management
Very
Very amazed
Yep
Not supposed to the media says they're not from Stella's
What I saw this treated and real-time writers at
An article that talks
About it like this is no one's covering
There is not behaving like
Yeah that's all
Cuz they understand
Reality or
Perception
So Alex is like this judges in your face this
Tyranny is so naked
Know why
It's because they're trying to teach you every single one of the people that are listening right now
Then you will be punished
You will be shamed you will be dragged for court
Your finances will be deflated your family will be ruined
Trying to do you know who the political
Rubbing it in
Yeah yeah that's what it is
If you
Probably committed serious crimes
They want to make an example of you.
That is
That is that that level of like
Why are we even trying to
Why am I trying to have a conversation with you at all about
AT&T in partiality or impartial
Potential juror
It's not doesn't matter what they are if I said
Voted for Obama he be like saying you can't vote for Obama and be a part on a jacket
I just don't you both are applying enzymes
And honestly I don't want to
Oversell this
I know exactly
What's going on here I think it's very transparent
If you watch
Through
The entire
Episodes
Things that he's done in the past
It's very very obvious
Yep totally so Alex
Besides
But he's going to go
Cover Rodger
New Albany hours to get here
That how we end the show
So that's a little bulshit but just to break up the 5th of May
I forgot to play this at the
The beginning so here's an
Text drop from
I have been in Satanic rituals
I got
Tricked into being out of twice
Rue21
Have you been fooled by the Nigerian
Which is which
Did the Titanic wreck
Sonicare
Stupid how do you get
Second
After that he clarifies our Bohemian Grove
F*** off
So we jump in here on this
And Alex
Announces that he's had a giant to pick
About how the global
So many of these
Research
And then I worked out real hard about an hour
While the blood was Papa
The brain
I was having explosive
Diarrhea
Many layers of its structures David more than even
What
Fractal
Design of it
Sickening art form that basically is
Critical
Piece the puzzle I want to talk about
So when I heard that I was like this is going to be disappointed
No matter what he says
He said 100 times
And honestly I wasn't the Restless episode I'm not sure what it was
Oh well that's that's actually refreshing New Direction for him to go say that it's a disappointment
But I don't know what the Breakthrough if there's any was I like that I like that
Leave me in suspense maybe we'll get there
It's very weird is that
I had an epiphany that I still have epiphanies sickening
Tactical system of Hannah
I don't know
I can't system is just fractally
And that's what is Epiphany
I'm not sure what it was but this
Next clip
Was nuts
Surprising in any way
Mention the first thing
In the next hour
When
Criminal lawyer constitutional lawyer
Several lawyers last night and was a Barnes this morning
41 on air
And George Soros and
Media Matters out fit are really upset right now
I want to pull the wool over our eyes as we all know
In the courtroom
It was completely blown away
When
A known Obama official
Department
Husband
As opposed to lawyer at Obama's apartment
Hugs
Pacifica
Lawyers raise this and tried to strike
The first girl they looked at she was waiting
Show me the jury Foreman watch
So when Alex is talking about this juror on these these two shows
He's absolutely lying about something very important
Which I've already brought up
And that is what they're saying that you was chosen to
To be a member of the jury that are not the case
I just stated that the trial is at
They were just interviewing potential jurors
This process would go on and result in a jury
After that pool is pick that the prosecution in
Advanced love you bility to strike people from
From the pool which is almost certainly what would happen if
All the typing is that the judge was in
Indicating that you didn't feel that this person
Past job was enough to
Preclude her from being a potential juror
Which I think is fair
If you end up trying to put in place a standard that a jury of your peers has to mean they all politically agree with you
No cult member or extremist
Would ever be charged with anything
In court ever again
Does Alex imagine that the proud boys for example all have to be tried in front of a jury of Western chauvinist
It's ridiculous
I've read up on this little and from what I understand
What Alex is doing is not
Specifically a league
What is a Deep Reach of what people consider proper behavior
It would become illegal
Very illegal
If you were specifically trying to out this person with the intention of until
Now we both know like we've already discussed
That's exactly what he is doing
But proving that in court would be insanely difficult
So Alex is probably legally in the clear on
Ethically though this is a huge affront to our courts this
Your identities are not something that people are supposed
Discuss until the trials Arkham
And even then
Generally only if the jury decides to come forward
That's kind of a crucial
Part of the appearance
Sublime just
That these jurors can feel empowered to make an unbiased decision even against
Powerful or dangerous person
Who are on trial
Because they know that they aren't necessarily their is themselves
They're representing all of us
In effect their individual identity is supposed to blur into the hole while they're serving as jurors
Outing jurors identity makes
This way
Santa introduces into people's minds
The possibility that what they do in a jury box
Won't stay in that courtroom and could ruin their lives
Now it's so easy to
Chargers for Mafia guys because they knew that nobody would put their name out and they would be
Say forever and ever
Ultimately I don't think that Alex's primary goal is didn't
Potential church
He wants to create a gigantic public spectacle that gets him
Which he is at
It's so sad that the only ways he can get any attend
These days it's a roll around town in a
Or behavin culturally destructive ways
That are right on the cusp
Albion huge Valley
The other goal he has his create a pre-emptive justification for why Rodger is going to be
Be found guilty
Alex
Because he's worked with Rodger and was around
Knows that Rodger is guilty he's so guilty he knows he specifically told Rodger to get in touch
Wikileaks and guccifer
He's the most guilty
Play clips of him talking about that on the show
He knows that Rodger was coordinating with his other employee Jerome corsi on the
Alex knows that Rodger is more than likely going to prison
So now it's important to have a narrative in place before that happens
This potential juror is
Perfect for that
Because now no matter what happens this trial is defective to Alex
It doesn't matter if this juror doesn't make the jury
Her very existence
Into the potential pool of jurors will be used as the talking point for why Rodger is a political prisoner
Not a criminal
Nixon tattoo on his head that is why it's what he's primarily
It's just damaged
But it's damage control this very dangerous
And could put this person through a whole lot of unnecessary trouble and if it does
I sincerely hope she sues
Because I think that is behavior here
Is
The sort of thing
Wow she might not stay in the neighborhood very long
I'm still on board with that she might have been a suspect
Look for a day cuz I end up naming the juror
And it's not her
Oh God he actually does
What an idiot
He's lying
About her being chosen
You talk about that a little more
She should be
And the judge said no she's unsure
The woman said
Do you have a dog in this fight for quotes or she doesn't know
I don't care one way or the other
He's first in line ready
Audien
And the judge
Laser scar cat pictures
On the Constitution
Family Show
Okay
So Alex Moxley idea that people might think that what he's doing
Easily
Because he thinks
But he's just being a journalist
Matirko Jones arrested for jury tampering and harassing jurors
It's completely legal and lawful
What time was the public figure
What was Chelsea Clinton
Yeah but what if it was Bo Jackson went Medical
We're going to release it
Because that's what the Press does other than war on the Preston
Alright
There's a war on the president your pleaded you're deeply involved
Warren
A couple of really quick point
It's 1 Alex says that it's legal and lawful which is a Barnes
Catchphrase
So I know that you saying that based on meetings with Barnes
That linguistic check
Is very specific to Barnes
So that's cool
Second I read the Media Matters article in a dozen
David Alex go to Primm
Ridiculous Behavior
He's just making that up as a straw man
Soul Fu think
This show is all
Just about
This a potential juror know Alex also has to get into disgust
Sing Rance
About drag queen story time
What why
Assault
Letting
Men dressed as women in clown outfit outfits have access to your children
In-N-Out event
Is a fully mark their territory for assimilation and destruction
McDonough City Council
We must have access your children's the beautiful thing we're going to do with them
This is lovely this is wonderful
We are here to groom them
Blind
Because they're uncloaking
You want to murder them they want them
Whale song
Pretty offensive and it seems really disjointed from our episode and it is a little bit
I wanted to play that
Is because like it's gross
It's sickening
But at the same time when I was listening to it one of the things that I couldn't
Help but think I couldn't
Stop thinking this is like
That is B that's was by the book
That's like it really felt like he was on autopilot just totally
Jacob Li the commentator
All of the little beets that were along the way it's a
This is
Boilerplate
Yeah that really
Juxtaposition of how like sickening
That rhetoric have and how wrote
It is in his just delivery it's just rattle off
No problem
Don't even worry about it you need me to fill five I got five
I'm sure that you've been there as well where you're doing along set
And you were you're doing a chance that you've done
For five years and all the sudden you realize you're thinking about
Something else while still talk
You were like oh s*** I'm still on stage holy-cow number stories that I told hundreds of times
Yeah and like I just could do it
Yeah absolutely and that's how it feels
Here
And that's
Gross disgusting
Really weird how
Normal
For him
Things that are horrible
Lahore
Alex get back to the
Like a fire-and-brimstone preacher in like the Medieval Age
Medieval era of just like
Oh you're just you're just screaming let's kill the Jews all the time and you're fine with it it doesn't even bother
Yeah yeah it's it's a drawing it's one of those things do that I always have to
Reconsider
Is like how inundated I am
With Alex's
That like
Nothing. It's kind of hard to shock
Give me whip is rhetoric
And that's that's
Like that clip
If you're introduced to that
Without the context of listening to tons of Alex
For us it's
Been out hey
It's just Alex talkingshit
While it's it's a it's a gross place that I've come to in my life
I think was
Interesting about that for me is that it makes it
Even more disgusting whenever I hear it from anyone else
Sure like from Alex I'm just like oh yeah f****** whatever you're going to drink blood and Gotti I Know This is your marketing
But if I hear from like a human being
That's just
Fine I'm like
You are
What are you doing your f******
You took a fade yeah
So Barnes is on
Sure cuz it's a day and it's Alex's shows at 1.
He has a
Distinct way of looking at
Organizations were pushing back
Saying that to the identity of the jurors could be disclosed its
Give me the media
What
1860s
African American
Precisely what took place here
That is not precise wow
That is not to place you upon for a big swing
Every time we've seen him on the show he has at least one big
Cut you know yeah that's taking it
Answer this is what he's bringing to the table
Is highlighting jury bias
Austin was only exposed when they
Information
What protects a trial in this country is open
Repressed that's right we're going to bring that power back
By sheer force of will we're going to expose
The first one
Brought up by the judge that work for Obama the Bill Gates Foundation whose husband
Deep inside the operation with the fake Russia Gatehouse On The Other Side
So now that Alex is spoken with barn
And Barnes is there he's being a little more careful
Because he is saying pretty active
So that is interesting
That is sort of a changing
Maybe it's just an updating of information maybe he
Sincerely believed earlier
That she was chosen
I don't know I don't know what it is
Conversation
Barnes is like okay
Here's what you have to
To tell the truth about here's what you can lie about
Things right but we can't say for sure is that Barn
Absolutely
Advised
Yeah he said
Absolutely
That is your right
Alex it's your duty
The name of the woman who's been picked as the first person
They tried to strike her
Wait till Robert Barnes
Steve lawyer
Rodger Stone
We all feel for we have empathy
Do we know where next
Literally
Yes
That is not a that's not how that works
That's narcissism by proxy
That's that that's
It's interesting though I mean like if you have that is his definition of empathy
Yes
Looking outfit hurts me
Yeah if this is an indication of
Something bad that's
Tumi
Experience it as bad
That is not empathy
Anyway on the last episode on November 5th
Alex said
Angles that angles was going to come back on as well as Tyler Nixon Rogers lawyer
Not going to happen or no
Stone people they're so scared they won't even talk. I said
The judge is going crazy
It's about an hour ago
That just about an hour ago
The judge is going crazy
We can't talk about anything
Well you know it's about this
We had mystery angles on
I'm going to show you
What he said
Be arrested for this
Jury tampering
Many batters didn't say that the article that I I read about this
I don't know what I was talking about
I would assume that maybe Rodger told them
To go on
I would I would assume that that's a possibility
Because
Rodger is I I know what Alex does you've done enough like we've create
Faded the piano of
If I found guilty that I'm little prisoner The Narrative is in place you can only do more damage
You bought you wrote there's only down for you to go the more you talk the worst to anybody who's actually associated with
Concretely my lawyer bias
Jacob angles
Just stay away from that for now is
Is too hot
Angles nail that here's what he did and he said that there was a juror that had that in
And then he winked
Yeah we're coughed or waived a little bit another f****** word you threw the bomb
Yep
Whatever kind of metaphor you want to make like
Is
In the clear of whatever Alex's actions are
He just said something that you started
Yep well again baby not cry
Crimes against civility
But the Alex
Now announcers
We're out there
Then they called the first match
Lawyers from trying to strike the very first one a woman
Who wants to
Excommunication
Director
For the White House Office of man
Under
Democratic President Barack Obama and his Husband is a justice department
We look them up
We're going to expose him as well right now
Next
He keeps teasing this out because obviously you want people to know he's going to yeah
Hey
The stunt stop in your car right now I'll roll down the window scream over Alex is about to reveal the
So he's now learned that it's a
Communications
The director for the office
Disadvantage mint budget
Which means that it's not Jennifer pompieri we said the day before
And keep in mind that he says that he's dug into this husband
End of her shift
Deep State operative
We'll see what kind of deep research is going to present on that
I like that
The Office of Management that's the important one that's where the money is
No one
Has ever described as being
The one where the money
Alex's got barns in
He knows that if this is presented in such a way that it appears that Alex is intimidating a juror
Yes then he could be in legal trouble
So he has to explicitly say that they're not doing that
You might argue that
The juror at already prospective juror at all
John Gotti son
I would argue that his audience that he's cultivated over the years
They're digging into things and seeing if things are on the up-and-up
Is
But you really identical to harass
Yeah
Historically speaking I do not trust them to be a Brain Trust of good researchers
That is what you call a disc
Barnett's Barnes throwing out a Alex if we're cutting wow
Wow
That's and that's if he even do it well he did it in I'll still sounded like a
Look
Nobody
Wants
Anything bad that nobody wants anything bad happen
Less than we do
We don't want anything to happen the most bad and that is why if you don't give us 100 grand
We're going to release your
We don't want
Nothing bad to happen
Yatso Alex's
Pretending
And announcing this as we have the person
We know this is the person who is the potential juror
Which makes it bad that this is
How is describing
Well by process of elimination
Pointers
Department
International Espionage affairs
There's only one
Public relations officer budget manager
She was there in 2000
Thirteen 2014
So he's gearing up
You knows what that guy said next segment we're going to do this
Bill is not going to f****** put up and say this person's name
Just yet
He has to
Make this even more
No Republicans are allowed on the jury
But
As he saying that
Barnes
Comes in
I don't know how to describe this
But I feel like this is a little bit sex
To see how this judge is not letting any Republicans on
Is professional class background
Obama appointee
Sort of looks like what Hillary would look like looks like you're iconic
Picture of Obama phone
People who would have otherwise been first grade teachers
With the power of the judge
Way to hear that I think it's difficult to hear that outside of like these women belong is first grade teacher
Is not in government
I don't belong in public office
Like I don't
I don't know what point he's trying to make other than that
What
Does
She looks kind of like what Hillary Clinton would look like
Even me I'm not sure
I don't care that much if it's just an insane safe it's just an insane sentence
Yeah
So in the next quit Barnes lies a little bit more about the selection process
Employed
Only people with a personal bias against Rodger Stone
We're going to be exploded
Who had a strong bias against Trump
Was going to be exploded
Robert Barnes is a goddamn liar
Allow me to read to you from the Reuters article that Alex's reference
Many times
On this episode
The headline of the story is quote longtime Trump advisor Rodger Stone takes ill during jury selection
A trial
Here's what it says
Quote
Some prospective jurors were excluded because they
Indicated they could not put aside their dislike of trump
Bias against Trump was definitely disqualifying for jurors Robert Barnes just made that s*** up to make it look like this
It was happening with Rodger it's some kind of a setup
That's because they need that to be the perception
Not to the reality that perception
Because they know he's f****** guilty as s***
And they need pre-emptive spin
Robert Barnes is not a lawyer he is a propaganda
If Rodgers found guilty
What does that mean for this entire operation
Rodger was working at Infowars app
At the time
He was disseminating his info information on Alex's show
His emails that involve the planning and coordination
Those were between himself and Alex's other employee Jerome corsi
If Rodger is found guilty that
Deuces some really hard question
For Alex that he'd rather not deal with
So the best way to do that is to preemptively argue to the audience that this case is a sham
So no matter the outcome it means nothing
It's the perfect strategy if your audience is stupid because if Rodger ends up acquitted then you get to say that they tried to Railroad Ave
He was so innocent that he still won
He's all just parlor
Who's all that Alex has this is all that he does
Which shouldn't be surprising
With a little more offensive is that he's a lawyer is
Complicit in this charade
I don't know how your ears many hats Dan on TV puts that propagandas had on its
Is Maga
Give me money
And then when it gets out the door and puts the hat on
It says I'm a bad lawyer I don't know how this process works
But I think
That
Barnes's license
Absolute let's see if this is
Becoming behavior of someone who is
Allowed to practice law
I don't know that it is
So it is next but we finally get down to business
And Alex Finally Revealed
The name
Of this
Supposed
Let's get to it right now
Here is who I'm that with the only woman that ran
This office in PR known as a husband
Sylvia
Mathews Burwell
Are there she is foundation
Government
For yourself
Ladies and gentlemen her husband
The justice department
I argue very confidently that Alex Jones by the very nature of his show in his entire career is attempting to engage in
Jury tampering by making a big production out of revealing This Woman's name on air
At the same time I'm not positive that that's something that could be proven in court
Maybe maybe within the realm of what's Technic
Illegal
This is an offensive display
Anyone who knows anything about Alex knows what he's trying
But there's a good chance you won't have any legal consequences
So whatever
There's another reason why he
He may not get in trouble for
He absolutely got the wrong person
Again
Jennifer Palmieri was the first person they decided
This
New
He's wrong again
Because the moment he said
Oh we we've narrowed it down this is the only woman
No you f****** didn't they were like 20 other women he's just f****** legs I don't know who the actual person isn't even if I did I wouldn't say
Say their name on air I'm only
Discussing I only
Littering bleeping out the person
Name Sylvia I was considering doing that but in order to demonstrate
Straight hwoarang Alex is
And he's already put this name out available by Jacob and goals
As well as the stuff that was tweeted out by other court reporters who were on the scene
The potential jurors specifically worked as a quote communications director at the Office of Management and budget
Sylvia Mathews Burwell never held that position
She instead was the director of The Office of Management
Budget which is a different role
Alex is so goddamn sloppy with his details
He doesn't recognize the difference between director and can be
Communications director
Because he's so desperate for attention
And to create a narrative that will invalidate Rogers eventual conviction
He's just completely f***** up his story
I feel like if Mathews Burwell receives any kind of harassment or threats because of this
She may have a pretty solid case
Alex
There's no reason for him to report that you was on this jury
Other than some identifying
Details that he got wrong and his alleged process of elimination
Honestly this order thing highlights why he
You can't understand that the ABC News video the project Veritas put out is
Bojack
He can't understand
The journalistic outlets have standards
Information that they report
The key to say whatever the f*** they want damn the torpedoes
He's making entire career off not being careful at all getting everything wrong and being rewarded for it
Couldn't see
I really wish that when you put it that way it's
It's so sad but that's why
Caution is proof of a grant
Spirit of course
Sylvia Mathews Burwell is not the
Potential juror but there's a further embarrassment
And it's
The potential juror Alex has been
Screaming about didn't even end up making
Taking the jury of course not
He's all yelling about how she's going to be the 4%
She wasn't so
Elected at all of course not I thought you were the judge the day after I would have been like well
We don't even need to have a strike
Nobody
Get to nobody needs
To say anything job
This is all nothing but it's potentially very dangerous
Spur Miss Matthews burrow
There's no paternalistic merit to what Alex is doing there's no further goal to this other than to create excuses for why his friend is probably
The jail
If you wants to create alternative realities like this
I mean it's his right to do that
But it's a point where his delusions become a danger
The others
It's well worth having a discussion about how he need
Be forced to get help
Even if this act isn't illegal it's the behavior of a severely mentally ill person
Alex Jones is completely unraveling in front of our eyes
Largely because of the attention
Support and Bunny
It had been buffering him has been decreasing
Exit access to social media is gone away
Everyone around him
Needs to recognize that this is the
But he's on and it does not end well
If anyone cares about him at all I am for you get Alex
Help
If you care about him in anyway I can't imagine
How you can let someone you loved
Act like this and not step in
It's disgraceful
It's it's it's I mean I hate to be preachy but like
This is
A lunatic
Who is now acting
In ways
That we've seen the consequences of his actions to the past has led to targeted harass
Fingered for no reason
Like we're seeing it consistently continue into the present
I just
I feel like everyone who has an ability
To persuade him or force him to get help
But isn't doing it
I just I cannot possibly
How are you would act like
He is
He is a lunatic
Who is
Lashing out at people
Enjoy you
Are making me feel like I'm living in Slaughterhouse-Five
How is it that week
Can just
Literally spend
A couple of episodes
Talkin about Alex
Pulling off certain behaviors
In 2013
And then do a present-day episode
Less than a week apart
And he is performing those very
Same behaviors
That's insane it's either that or he does it every single f******
He does a lot because you have to consider that the reason that were looking at these things
13 is because he
Consequences
It's just how we operate identify why we got why it's just that that's
Get raise
As his behavior
Erasing these ways I just I mean
I wish him
Bill
In the sense that I hope he
Feels
Consequences
This is what he's doing
But at the same time like
For everyone in everyone's best interest that he
He get help
No I would never want
His all of his fantasies of
This is what we want to do to the globalist and all that s*** just makes the rise more into Stark relief what it is
But I would like
That's like an empath
I just want to fire a bullet in you that make
You feel everything that you've
Like I don't know that would be
Fatal
I think that Alex I mean like
I think he's probably Beyond
Being helped quite frankly
But that doesn't mean that that's still not the solution
Trying to get him
Some like very serious
Psychological help because he
He is living
You know what if he's living in a fictional world that this buzard overarching
Communist
Conspiracy
All this b*******
I'm not particularly all that in
Yeah but to the point where he is
Disseminating
Information widely
Pretending he's an expert in anything while getting everything wrong
And engaging in a gigantic
Media specs
He's trying to pull off
Where he endangered
People who works with private citizen
Absolutely people who have no business
Being pointed out
And targeted by him
That is where it crosses the line to like
Every single person around
All of his employees
His wife
Everybody
Is complicit in this
Because there is a solution
There is a 5150
You can call will provide material
He is a danger to other
He really is and it has nothing to do with politics
No it has nothing to do with like political beliefs or anything like that
Who sang this and it was any other president or or political if he was on the left and he's
Reviewing jurors f***
Looking names in the hopes that his rabbit
Fan base with
Do some very serious intimidation
At
Best
Then it doesn't matter if there's a and ideology behind it you're f****** crazy
And if Alex were somebody who doesn't have that
History
That very clear history
Of this interaction between them
Himself and his audience
Where there is harassment
That goes around area where it probably take it a little bit different
Him saying adders name
Yea or nay
Imagine
I think it would be a little bit different I would say
Well that's just tasteful
But I wouldn't look at it as
A danger
This is
Danger
Kill this woman or anything
Yesterday
No one
Scared about her at all I mean
In anytime
Kind of I believe former civil service
Kind of potential Danger
From Alex is audience
Answer dumb s***
What is my kit reposted on Gateway pundit or would I write that Crosshair and now she is
Alex's brought that into her life and that is
Horrible thing
Yep so I don't know my basic point is
Someone take this seriously who can do something
A broken record
Cuz I said this many times before and every time he does stuff like this
If I go out this is why you need to get help
It's not like there aren't
Unending list of
People who have
Status try to Crazy Horse
Taking their cut
Let it die whenever
Steph you know
Yep that's that's a very
Common
Story about
Deal with that
People
There's an option
Anyway a stress whatever I'm saying these things about like he needs help I mean
He needs help I don't think that anybody should
Absolutely
So Alex husband
Is involved in all this stuff
To this is the only real evidence you provide
Husband here
Here is a photo
All she's being sworn in
Wheels
Joe Biden
So he looks like Eddie Haskell
On steroids
There you go what a nice
Authorized
That's the only evidence that he provides that
He's involved in the Mueller investigation used in a picture with
Biden yeah
The people who are the reporters on the
Did tweet out that he is a lawyer for the Department of Justice
AMV I believe it was in the National
Security division of Department of Justice
So there is a possibility that he was involved in some small way
But I don't I haven't been able to find any
Concrete evidence that
Cerenia anything in particular or that he was a player in any
In anyway and the only evidence
Is that
A picture while she is being sworn in until I get at least
Two or three more corroborating
I'm not even believe this guy is
I don't believe I was just like the important husband
I don't believe
He might have a tighter you would probably held up a photo f****** grimace
Like this dude
I don't believe anything
The media though Jordan trying to cover the song
I'm not we're not the meeting
The media won't even tell you that she was a high-level
Person with Obama and then her husband
Is he in the whole Mueller Witch Hunt I mean
We have a right to know that it's still America
So Alex is saying that the media won't tell you this stuff but at the same time he's quoting a Reuters article that says it
I don't understand what he's which is it
Which is the media covering it up or do you want have a f****** source
80 Folsom
That is such b******* is it is everywhere
Deeply abusive to his daughter
Article about it
It's over with for them it's abusive to me
I don't like having to hear that
I'm not entirely sure
Why I cut this clip but I do know that there's an ad pivot
Maybe pro-nazi
Would he not
Everything must go super sale
Appliance and
47% off
There's a whole lot of this on this episode
I think it's because he knows that he's trying to draw and tons more of the announcement of the
This person when there's
Usher Yeah
So you might be saying that Alex
Said this person's name and outed them is
Soldier when he was wrong about it because he's
He's bad at his job and
He operates
Knee-jerk
Badly
Yeah terribly yeah but it's actually because
He's a journalist
That really doesn't sound true
He is not a coward
Supposed to be random selection
Is the former
Budget management
Her husband works on the Mueller probe
American
I love the idea that like America is founded on not
Twice rewrites we're like El Ron Hubbard first
Alex
I'll miss Johanna sixties not even addressing the fact that for the 5th on the episode of the 5th
He was saying it was Jennifer Palmieri
He's not even addressing like what we got it wrong at first but now here's the real person who were left over
Was never admitting that you got it wrong the first time Dad
Actually that might be
When I actually made America great
What snake oil salesman
I want to slap Barnes
So bad
That that like that
Good selection of Judges is supposed to be impartial
Like
Really really the one thing that everybody on the right
A universally Praises Trump for is choosing judges
They don't do it because he's choosing them for their impartiality bar and certainly not
Didn't you know that
How dare you
That's a fence
He's not a lawyer
I mean technically is
But he's not a lawyer
Here's another gross add
Or lawyers
Or the people that are there are public
But now they want us all to be secret
We're talking about that
A lot more in just a moment you know speaking of the Grim Reaper
Horse plus Delmas closest
What you're going to find out there that's the fountain
I'd like to point out that he was not speaking of the Grim Reaper
I think he was saying that like these people are the Bringers of death
Like that
Wow
I was not speaking of the crib
This founder
I like that is a non-sequitur little bit of an ad for this product of his and then
He gets into talking about
No actually
Angel of Death
Was sent by God
My God this is
Have you put the Red Devil on the Lambs there
Pass over your house when
Establishment
It was about to be
Dealt with my God because of the firstborn son of every Israelite
Sacrifice
So there wouldn't be leadership
The crown
The boys were
Attacked
The Prozac in
The Red Lion in the Nae Nae
Conboy
In the past
It is again today
Then just repeat
Themselves
As Above So Below the seriously DNA Force Plus
Wow
Woodstock
My eye is bleeding from that punch that's that those pretty impressive
Oh God Putt-Putt me
A lot
A lot of weird salesmanship going on here
That was just
Free association that wasn't the old man
Alex has Owen Shroyer
Covering
Rogers case
Sure if you got the big guns he's got the talent over there if anything maybe
Laugh my ass off
It's probably this next clip
Owens out there doing a man on the street thing try to talk about Rogers
It's unfair what they're doing to Rodger Mike down for this because
You got it
Got to love
That's nothing
That's free speech that's truth
So this is kind of like the Tommy Robinson thing
Nazi coward coward
Space
Alphabet to be so hilarious
Owen Shroyer the middle of trying to do a rowboat and he gets into a fight with a guy
You know it's at
Another one of those situations where it's like every time Alex swears and he really goes for it you like you don't know
How to do this
What are you what are you doing
Owen does not know how to get into a fight with somebody doesn't sound like
Weird it's very stilted
This robotic yeah yeah
So the other problem is that he's also very stew
Owen Shroyer is very dumb
He knows to install
Punk and
Nazi
I don't think he thinks those are in
So he's
He's trying to talk about the juror situation
And how
Having her as a jury member means the whole case is f***
He is
Highlighting
A fundamental misunderstanding of how the legal
Every every member of the jury could sit here and be like yet Stone was railroaded this is a show trial this is
This was a kangaroo court
They control
So the first important Point here is that this woman was not put on the jury so she's not even there for the trial
Remote control Owens promise fails
They're just right off the bat
Button
He's also failing on a basic understanding of how our legal system
The argument he's trying to make is that because there's one person on the jury who's going to vote that Rodger is guilty no matter what
Even if everyone else says not guilty
Get Justice
This demonstrates a startling lack of understanding of the topic that he
Discovery
Well it is true that one person being skewed toward the defense could f****** a process
Accusation
That is true
The same is not true in the reverse
Because our courts are based on the presumption of innocence until proven guilty
If everyone but this one
Gerbo did not guilty
Rodger could not be convicted
A unanimous decision is required to convey
So if the jury reached an m
Impasse where this one globalist
Wouldn't budge
It would end in a mistrial
And then the state would either have to decide to drop charges or if they wanted to retry the case
In no way could one guilty vote result in the conviction
In a way that one not guilty vote
Preclude
Seriously Owen Shroyer doesn't have the basic
Understanding is required to have these sorts
Conversations
Are you putting this idea for
Well trying to correct
And allegedly very
Competent lawyer
You heard him at the beginning of thing Bob Bob Bob
Talking to Robert Barn who's
Supposedly a lawyer
These people have a lot of feelings
About what's happening in the world
And I guess they're entitled to those feeling
But they are just not equipped to have the adult conversations they're trying to have about actual topic I mean that's been
Yeah it's very
Now that they have one
One juror they have the whole thing
I was searching for something like maybe
Maybe there
He thinks that there's like it did it's like there's a swing boat
You know like
No it's no idea
Talking about a
You talk about a hung jury and a mistrial no idea how
Well what what is the name
Is the stories that you hear of people who like
You know 11 of the jurors they wanted not guilty and therefore you can convicted
He's reflecting that he's taking the opposite of that and imagining that it has the same
Sort of outcome
Yeah I know is idea is essentially
Hearing about 12 Angry Men I doubt he's
Well it's also assuming that like okay let's say there's a mistrial than that default means Rogers guilty
And it's not
Is it
It's it's ridiculous
So anyway we have one last
CLEP here
And
Alex has made a big spectacle of this
He said definitively that he knows who the juror is
Even though he was wrong day before and he's
Is also wrong again
And so it makes it really sad when he ends the episode like
Sort of waffling a little bit while still being hyper confident
Infowars releases
Obama official
Rodger stone jewelry
Wasn't turned out she headed up Health and Human Services on top of it
So what position
Politico and
Washington Post reported as a spokesperson for
Dopeman
Woman who had a husband images
Apartment 14 in the Mueller probe
Nobody else or lease it.
Appears to be what is about 99%
Probability
Ninety-nine percent probability why are you why you leaving that 1% dangling there out he used
Always at the 1% ends up being right and why is the process of elimination band and as mates
Silver and 538 of told us
I don't know what they say
You can't operate
If you can't
You just can't
You can't do these sorts of things with
Bulshit process of elimination
Misunderstanding various job titles in order to make this fit whatever you want to do
You just can't do this
It is I mean I guess you can but you should
And you can be rewarded
Don't forget about that part
It's just staggering
The extent to which he's wrong
Every single time he's like I'm 99% on this
There's a 1% chance that a real Attack
Always always the one whatever
20% yes but he might be
Oh wait I think
I think we're just experiencing
Sing Alex in the wrong Multiverse
Must be
Like in 99% of the Multiverse
Obviously
He's correct about every
It just happens that you and I exist in the one where
He's always wrong
I mean if that's the case
It's not crazy
Tragic
Anyway
I come to the end of this episode
What I'm left with is an overwhelming
Sense of
Sadness
I am sad
Because Alex
Is clearly
Diving deeper
Into the overweight Nash
Analyst White
Supremacist
Leanings that he has
As demonstrated in that coverage of the New Hampshire couple story where he's
Sayings that say you're allowed to do this cuz your brown and white people
You need to get guns get ready to shoot
People
Really f*****
Very step to Richie saying that his enemies need to be wiped off the Earth not just
Murder with ice picks
A street lobotomy yeah I'm sad about that that makes me really bummed out
I really I really think
That
The world's better without Roderick like that
And then I'm really sad
About
This desperate
Pathetic attempt
2 oz
Out this juror
Like I think it's I think it's
Static-X
It's very sad
Demonstrating is anything
Inability to research
The incompetence of his team
The sloppiness of his legal advisers words I can't go do this
I just
It's a bummer it's a bummer
In and further
It's transparent
Like as soon as I
Got through a listen to these episodes
It was so
F****** clear to me
This is the behavior of someone who knows that Rodger is
Probably going to be found guilty
That this is a behavior to invalidate the trial before it began
Because
That's what you got to do to protect
Whatever
Connection you have
That's not apathy
I think that when people cover stuff like this it would be wise to understand that that is the
Motive
It is
Possible
But there is also a motive of trying to
Intimidate this jerk
Tamper with the jury
It is possible that is somewhere within his mind
Possible
And it's also further possible that that will be
The real-world consequences
And it's not
Probably wise to ignore
I'm not advocating people ignore that
But
It would be wise
For people to
Lead
Any kind of story about this with
Why Alex is doing this is because
Like layout the connections
To Infowars that are very
Clearly part of
Rodger Stone case
And we like Alex needs preemptive
Application for when it's friends
He's probably found
To continue the perception V reality
I would guarantee that Alec
Never say doesn't believe like
Like in his perception is like
I am not trying to end
Tamper with anybody I'm not trying to intimidate
Anybody I truly believe that I am doing my best
Help these people
And I'm trying to
Invalidate the trial before it have
I'm not trying to hurt anybody but I've totally driving it but I didn't validate the child because the trial is just a kangaroo court
I mean
Alex's perception of what he did when he was super drunk and screaming about a million-dollar bounty on the opposing counsel
He doesn't think that is
Is intimidation or
And yet the real
Yeah it is
Right
So it all comes back to that
Alex's lead story on the 5th
Is damning for him
Every time he's like I f******
I've got some
Really valuable
Deep in the mirror
Can I see that everything that I do is
Is wrong and I mean
That to you as me be
You like Cheese's
Alright man
Good luck Alex yeah
So I will on Monday
Website
Itworld on Twitter
We are on Twitter is that knowledge of his
Go to bed Jordan we are also on Facebook
I'd really like to download the show please go to iTunes
Download libreview it's a Drago.
Tell your friend
We love it
I will be back when I'm near you I'm Leo I'm dzx Clark
I'm the director of office of manage
Holding
Alex