Air Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge B
Dollartree.com
Hey buddy would like a knowledge
Beverages and talk a little bit about Allie
Alex Jones
Giordano
Did you have
Did you used to watch
Late nights or Letterman weapons would let me watch
Stuff that late sorry I was younger not really oh okay
Houston sort of like
Saturday Night Live
The past year old Saturday Night Live
Like Monty Python
Or Blackadder that kind of stuff
Humor
Blackadder the lotto Rowan Atkinson the house
But that was all unlike VHS
The real time
It came on way past my bedtime for most of my life
Play kind of gravitate
Yeah but I would be lying if I said that I was
Super into it
To take on the identity of a lot of people in comedy who really were deep
Yeah I preferred it to other
Late night but I never watched it
You didn't have that
Affinity for the Smigel you
Sears on 9th
As I've gotten older and I've watched a bunch of the stuff
After the fact I understand why people would but I wasn't
Country lady
I was not
Not deeply invested in the Leno versus Letterman
Kerfuffle
Take a position on the average
Roll I know
Lino did nothing wrong hashtag
I have not heard MattyB
People expressive broletto visit
How about MSG
I don't know
I like to I like to
Enough like I liked Letterman in
Antonin that stuff I saw
But
Wasn't wasn't my main bag
Talked about it
Prior to this I wish it was Letterman guy
I wish it was on some level like I do think
Going back and watch a lot of that stuff
Is really hilarious
There's a lot of really good work that
It was being done Thursday night shows
But for me to pretend now is
35 year old man
Yeah backgrounds 12 I can stay up all night
But I have not a lot of respect for the crab
All that stuff in Minecraft
Watching late-night live
But I do know a lot about Alex Jones
Cool so Jordan today we're back in the past
We are going over April 23rd
And are continuing investigation of what the hell went on with Alex
Primarily
In terms of calling
The people of where the victim
Viruses
Actors of Tangled into the Boston bombing
Are we are
Coming out of that
And all of its result
Really
I mean johar sarna physics
I apologize I should have spoken more clearly
Still very much so on.
And others I know that there's more to learn about his response
The Boston bombing but I also think that we have now entered
The portion where it's like
In the same way that Alex has a little bit of a Comedown once there's official information out
I'm experiencing a little bit of that too
Just going back to normal where is we had a stretch of shows where it was like
Really dance lies in real time
And end
God
Excitedly
I just chomping at the at reality trying to take a bite out of it
That's mine now he's kind of
Back to a normal show here
It feels a little bit weird but I still think there's some
Think stuff in here but you'll notice a shift
You'll notice this feel a lot more like a normal Alex Jones
Be allowed right
Like what
TV show Stars
Groundbreaking moment you don't allow them to
Go back to
Exhaust
The World by breaking the biggest
You can have two different times
Different stories about the same story
All broken so we'll get down to business on this but first we got to take a little moment to thank you
People have signed up and are supporting
So first Andrew thank you so much you're now a policy wonk
Text KB
Dkay
Thank you so much and I hope all is walk
Damn thank you so much you and I hope all is well
Thank you Dan
Next to Jake thank you so much you are now by Lizzie Wang
Text Gloria that cuz I'm not sure now if I was you on
Thank you Gloria Gloria
Lisa thank you so much you are now if I was wrong
Robert
Thank you so much
Caillou Robert
Do that website, click the button
Indeed we would love a very
We jump in here Jordan
Alex is
Not talking much
About the Boston
Situation
At all
At the beginning of this show
He's mostly complaining about Janet Nepali
I know that seems to be what his
He's got some big grapes
With the head of the Department of Homeland Security which makes sense
Is an offshoot
Of his
Feelings about Boston The Manhunt
It's disconnected
Disjointed you never brings it all to
Together necessarily
But he's very mad about a couple of things
That she has done it one of them has to do with
The DHHS budget
You will not cut our funding
Dollars a year domestically
So this is a bad thing
On a number of life
First part of this is really terrible thinking is her saying hey you know if we cut our funding there's a greater risk of some
Some attack happen
You could hear that as a threat
And I think he's insinuating that what she means is
We're going to stage four terrorist attack if you don't give us
Well if we are able to fund our programs
We will
Leave area
Uncovered
You know there's a greater chance of somebody pulling something off
Great say Alex
Can read magical words in bulk
And the second thing is
That he's imagining that she
It's that 200 billion dollar
I told Isaac to the budget is a little too high on a 200 billion dollars I would Janet Napolitano
As she sees fit
I would say that there is definitely a fair conversation to be had surrounding like the Department of Homeland
Insecurities
And all these big the budget
I think I think that you could have in good faith
Albertsons not doing that
Probably not because any figure that
Time to site
Necessarily involves
So many things
Vettys pretend
Yeah I figure is a massive figure but it also
Extends to like outside of the DHHS
Things within the Department of State
Right like that budget is not
Just like
Janet Napolitano
You could save a lot of Terror attacks with 200 billion down
I suppose you cut
So anyway he's saying it's 200 billion
Then he actually looks it up
Enforcement agencies
Hundred billion dollars
Sammy what is he doing all of the law enforcement agencies likes OK Google glued like the FBI in there too
Alright Google
He's just a
Find Rihanna renderings of agencies that will eventually equal up to 200 billion
I don't care which one
Play so fast and loose with his
Terms
That's the sense I get it
Whatever you're doing
It's a problem to
Because
That is a conversation
Worth having
But when you do it. Disingenuously like this
Takes away from the ability
Have that conversation about the attempts to audit
The Pentagon
Nightmare where are you
Like everybody realizes that a certain point
They've done this over and over again
Over again
Nobody in the Pentagon actually knows where the mud
It's all theoretical
Besides he's been deposed
Like who runs what
So I think Alex has a little bit just
Because he went and saw a movie
Last night the night before
Let me tell you
He loved it
Will you pull up the
Rise of the Machines end of humanity October
Place
Nowhere
Nowhere online
I just tell you know where online do they show you
The bad guy
Obsessed with that obviously not a secret
The movie is on the cover of my
Out of my mind
So bad
So Alex Oblivion
Stop talking okay
If I were to do an epic if I were to cut a ton of Clips with this episode
So much of it would just be like
Oblivion spells out the globalist plans
It is a revolution it is a revelation of the Illuminati
And it's all because
He gets the bad guy well I want to talk to you
Okay that's that's what I was wondering have that issue
I'm not super interested in how the image on the cover of his
October 2012 magazine
Some similarities with the pyramid or the
The tat in Oblivion
There are some similarities but they're also
Some differences
One before minute Bolivian is not really a pyramid
It does have a triangular shape but then go out to
Also it's upside down
If you're trying to make it look like pyramids there's
I don't really give a s*** about
Here's why
If you look at that cover of Alex
2012 October magazine
You'll see a black pyramid with a red eye
If that's what you want to call it looks like
The pyramid in Oblivion also had a red-eye though the placement is dif
But this Stylistics.
Kind of secondary to the Mets
I know for a fact
The image on the cover of Alex's magazine is just a Photoshop of Hal from 2001 A Space Odyssey
I could say that with from his imagination with a hundred percent certainty
And here's how I know
On that cover the eye has the same
Three white lines on the top
Undercover Valley reflections
The lights
Deep truth or Vision when he designed that magazine cover you just stealing ship from 2001 A Space Odyssey
You can run around pretending that he has his prophetic Visions all he wants but the reality is that he's just seen a number of sci-fi movies
Thinks they're real
The makers of Oblivion probably added some sort of aesthetic touches
Bno Mars
Alex
Too far gone to understand that
Original by Soros
I got you
So you spent a long time on this episode about
And I'd have
0 it's not as funny
He is his
Watch
Ton of clips
But it does definitely shade
His mental state
Okay on this site April 20
Museums
Borderline obsessed with this movie
I really feel like
Just yesterday
He was crying about having defeated the globalist
Conspiracy theory that if he had uncovered
Then he did uncover the great autumn
That you never liked the drumbeat has
Have to go on until
Fired
Tom Cruise movie alright
Okay well then there we go
That takes up
A lot of his attention
Yeah
So he starts getting into talking about
So how you got a
Got to live
Globalist want to destroy you
I think he ends up saying something really Danger
Because
The fluoride the chemicals in the water
Go get drunk if you want to
Prozac type drugs
What I would say
When's art bats
Suggestions and I'll go climbing Hill
I have a dream two friends
Suggestions when when it's
In opposition to write taking care of your mental health I think that's where you get pretty dangerous
Children psychiatrist why not just live like Tom Sawyer that he wasn't depressed that was a good time
A great time tricking people into whitewashing things looking that guy has a little bit dangerous
Psychiatrist
You know what you can take Prozac
I recommend
That's great
Seems like an Alex Jones
School of Psychology is not subscribed to
But you know like
He
Is the pillar
Of Mental Health
Like he is the image of what a well-adjusted person
Would look like
Right
2001 Space Odyssey you believe
Magazine cover or they're both
Handling the globalist
Guy is saying you got it all
Yeah and I think his sanity is really on full.
Display in this next
Swimming in the toilet
I'll get you and your little dog
Your real powerful all you evil people
Will crush you for the Innocents
Doesn't sound like
Make sure you know that
So I'm not entirely sure what story Alex is talking about with the fetus in a toilet but I know I've heard him refer to it in passing
Multiple times
It's very hard to trace down exactly
What he's talking about since he's so vague
Probably a real story that he's talking about
But I can't credibly tell you exact
What it is
But I imagine that there's a good chance that it's just some sort of a disingenuous
Auntie abortion
I would assume
I think fetus in a toilet sounds more like a ween
Could be
But when you try to find out what story this could be
And like what I did is I went through
Through Google results with B
The end date being when this episode came out
Stories about people like Miss
Miscarriages
Don't in anyways
Support the narrative Alex
Trying to sell here
The rest of the stories I could find mostly head
To do with high schoolers
Like people who gave birth
In a toilet at their school the horrifying story
Even really get into
But these are the very people like these high schoolers
Who are in the most need
A better reproductive Health Service
If Alex is truly concerned about these kinds of stories that he's yelling about
The answer is greater access
The things I planned parenthood not yelling at people about the devil
I don't know also
Small point
Alex just went on that rant about taking no pleasure in killing people in all of that
Which is par for the course for him
But let's be clear about this
What prompted that rant is comment his own fans made on his videos and articles
These
Aren't the globalist
He's mad at the globalist
Start the abyss
His audience is
Accidentally
Post this video that says this article about 2
And his audience
Bunch of shity things
It's very strange
That's no good
So Alex gets from here jumps into
Tim Gunn fear
Cuz it wouldn't be a full day on his show where they're not too
To be gunfire
California
24 million
Oh man
Did you catch that he said illegally own butt
Like even he would be fine with
People who illegally own things having that being like should be
Stop using a legally own
That bill is exclusively and entirely by people have gone to or not legal
He says 40,000 guns that figure comes
From the bill where it says quote
There are currently more than 20,000 armed prohibited persons in California
Collectively these individuals are believed to be in possession of a 39000 handgun
And 1670 assault weapon
The bill has nothing to do with door-to-door con
Location of guns
Billions
It's about providing funding to improve the armed prohibit
Which is online database that gun dealers are supposed to cross reference when people are trying to buy firearms
Large part of it had to do with updating
Things so people who bought guns when they were legally allowed to buy them but then lost
Their right to own a gun because of a violent crime or something like that
I bet big sister would pick those
People op
And maybe that would end up involving a confiscation
But to be fair
Literally the only thing is Bill deals with his increasing
The state's ability
Enforce the laws that are already
If you disagree that people who've
Let's say committed a violent crime in the past shouldn't be allowed to own an assault weapon
We should make that argument
That's the argument Alex should be making
But I suspect he knows that he doesn't have the
To pull that off
It's super difficult to go on errands say
I'm opposed to this bill because I think the people who committed armed robberies or shot people in the pasture be totally free to possess gun
Change the Arctic
Alex creates a straw man this is about legal gun owners really trying to create the impression that that's what this is
Is about being targeted by the evil state for guncon
That's easier to sell
This is the trick that's how it's carried out
Alexis Roderick much more marketable and people buy into it cuz they don't want
Legal gun owners having their guns
But in reality
Doing this
Supporting violent felons having
Access to guns
Agates
I don't know
Easy even can't
Handle telling the story the way he means
Illegal guns
In the in the copy that he's ready to
I mean I think that
The murderer should be at
So we can be confident that
That somebody who has murdered in
In the past will use that gun only for Wrecker
Creational Purp
From here on out if you want to make that argument
And then someone would probably disagree with you and then
You know whatever was the best ideal went out in the marketplace of ideas
I don't like that
Because my ID is going to lose
Said yeah whenever you
It's just all disingenuous framing
That's all it's going
You should not
It cuz it doesn't even matter that he says illegally everybody who's listening is going to be like oh illegally is just their slippery
Slope argument
If need be it'll come to
It'll just be presented as if the story was about they're going to come door-to-door take all of your gun
Everybody's gone
What even like he's slipped up he didn't mean to say illegal down
About the story it's not in the context of
People who are not legally allowed to have guns
Law Abiding Citizen every one of you
Every single one of you
So Alex is trying to go
Get some news are
Besides he's going to Google
Little article
And well
It is this this this was a little upset
Americans
This is still not working is still not typing
Computer
I just
This is
Real childish
I'm having trouble with my computer so I break it to force people to talk
You need to go outside you need to go on a hell unit maybe have a drink that's better than Prozac or
You could smash this s*** out of your
Computer every time
Because as a minor function problems
He reads his typing
Like a f******
About somebody who
Can't re-up
Doing a improv scene about hunting packs
Is it a typo
I want to see
Dogs
Play
With
Lion
Quick all dammit I gotta break this whole f****** computer.
This is working the way I wanted it to
Ridiculous
Ridiculous that's it that's his problem
Wow
So there's no guests on this episode Alex is on his own
Just letting it all hang out
So he's got to take some calls he's got to open lines this thing
And he gets a call from a guy who wants to tell him about how Alex's taught him how to
Experience
The world
Encouraged
Information
It's become your formation
Freedom of Information in my mind
So close to a brain boost
Ditto
I don't know I could very easily be a real tall
You've taught me how to build a web of information in my mind that's all they call Alex's done like
Especially particularly in this
Post Boston bombing
Scratch that we've been in
All he's been doing is make
Whatever he feels like
Could be true
He just writes a story about it is true there is nothing supporting
He is ninety-nine percent of the time it is
Except that 1% that is always actually
True but 99% of the time it would have been for you learned on our last episode that Alex believes there's an objective real
So that is going to be a problem
R-Truth
You know he has this behavior that he is just
Do to your body
Is I'm going to make f****** s*** out
Area authority to bleed very confidently
I'm at so that behavior is mirrored by zombies
Freeze them up to make webs
Nevermind of infer
Information at
Might link here might link here
Of course not
Like it's bad what he's doing
It's really bad to imagine that it sort of
Give carb lunch to anyone
Right
Alex is a bad singer
But I bet there are worse
Absol any of them in his audience
I mean just by virtue of him being
Somewhat constrained
On the radio
Thinking only goes so far
Where is if you're just somebody quiet and alone
Watching f****** Raging Bull on a loop
You're going to be in trouble
Well he's constrained by his own success
Right like he doesn't want to lose that money that is a built-in boundary
That's at least at this point
His career he has we can't go too far left
Cash Stop
So
Don't like his caller or some
Dakooters has a Blog they don't have those constraints
Lulu's now
Like I told you Alex
Super into Oblivion
Sandy talks about it through most of this
This episode there is not a lot going
Just a lot of Oblivion thought of Oblivion talk
Handsome weird caller
Kind of
It's very surreal it almost has nothing to do with the Boston Marathon
That's okay
I don't either
Is Robert
That's what I envisioned in my mind when I stole the picture of Hal from 2001 A Space Odyssey
Concrete
Analysis I can confidently say to you
Satan's real and he's a Black Pyramid
Duh
Alright used to come to this
Alright Alex
Congratulations
It just becomes so difficult like
Whatever
I have my quieter moments
Of reflection
They just become so hard for me to reconcile the fact that like some
People like
Think he knows any
I know it's bananas
It's so weird when he's rambling about
I'm just going to tell you Satan's real is Black Pyramid
Okay
Then I'll trust you
When you say two pictures are
Yeah
Ridiculous
Give me sir we need to
You just get him at
Cruise movie ever
Nitro for the show and then we can
Can just hear his he's also conflicted about it so cuz he doesn't really like Tom Cruise
Because Tom Cruise Bentley used
Friends of Charlie
How much does an actually spell this out because pick it up
Apple contact
Tom Cruise tried to get your of the sheet to join Scientology wasn't to do it
Anyway
Really like Tom Cruise
So good
So good tomorrow it overcomes
The Tom Cruising
It's kind of the same thing that he went through an alley
Came out I remember hearing a couple episodes of that where he was
Really f***** up over it
He's a Sci-Fi nerd with a little bit of brain damage to also had some sort of
Inability to regulate writer
More or less
Ins and outs of
Another thing is
He didn't
Go to college
But you knows all about Recology
Now even
You particularly like in the president
Yeah you know
You know that they are all TJ
In-depth experience
World education
V
Virtuous
That does sound like
What is a robber baron
They are
You deserve it just like Kesha did you just to kill themselves
Political show
I don't I don't know if
Everybody
Secondary education
Talk to a human
Things are ugly and bad
Was that in your orientation
Did you have to take a 101 class
I did Skip Orient
Freshman orientation hung out in the kiddie pool
In the backyard
Bunch of assholes that's why you don't believe in population
Ice cream Gathering know each other
I don't know I took a pretty broad spectrum of classes
Anyone
Of them was telling me that Youmans
Their evil but then again
And it's years ago
Maybe curriculum
Change
That is true who knows what they're dealing with right now they're probably I don't know
Learning about climate change this just seems like somebody who wants
Too aggressively
Dismiss
And invalidate
Scholarships
They say they're smart but they're all secretly
By virtue of me Hinds Community College
I know no consequences
Play that everybody who gets a secondary education is evil
So
That right after the Marathon bombing
There was no reports of
The ricin letters
I got sent to prison
And as we know from discussing it it was originally believed to be an Elvis
Resonator setup
Buy arrival
A conspiracy theory rival literally one of the craziest stories I've ever heard
Story is unfolding in real-time and our first suspect
The Elvis impersonator is now being released
Rightly because the police realized this isn't their guy
Alex
Now believes that he
He predicted this
As well
Of course
They don't say the guy gets up getting arrested
Tried
Just worked out no patches no Patxi's got killed
See bodies
Federer match
Yeah
Seem to ever really very realized
Must
So this is just like circumstance again playing into Alex's
Perception
Yeah you know this guy was passing set up it was all
The fake
He was
He what's that up he was a patsy
We have a
Actual Panther
But it wasn't from the government it was fun
From crazy person
It was from a guy that you pissed off cuz he didn't believe in his
Guy who Bears so many suspicious resemblance is 2al
Exhume self
Wish you would wrestle with that ass
Janet Napolitano,
About
About the budget of
Mvhs
But another thing
Is there is
Immigration
Being discussed in Congress
And she is out
Support of this
And I Alex
Future
Our world over the very worst people
Immigration importance
And if you actually download
So the first problem with this clip is that I'm certain that Politico didn't write a straight news article that said added emigrate
Denaturalization would give Democrats Perpetual control of everything I'm not sure that
Will you political does at that end with most
Not something a serious person would really suggest
What does sound exactly like the kind of thing a propagandist like Alex would say people were saying in order to create fear in his audience
It does sound like that
Secondly even if that were true Alex's expressing
Exactly the same idea here
He's the crying with the Dems in the globalist want to bring a group of people who would vote in the way they want
Wow at the same time he sang that
The influx of people wouldn't be a problem if they had similar political ideas to his
Couches
Right-wing extremism by just calling it believing in the Bill of Rights and Constitution
That doesn't change what he actually supports
It's all these people voted the same way and believe the same sort of right-wing bulshit that I do wouldn't be a problem for immigrants to come in
Simple right
This is all I mean really get down to it it's all just demographic
Same sort of things a year from lightning
But it's been presented so disc
Ingenuous
That's all that's all that I can really
I don't know I don't know what to tell you about
The more demographics
Arguments
But there are the more
If you say the word demographic
Intubate
Your you've revealed exact
What your issue
Use the word
Do I know
That's when the word comes up
Only
So
Look
The most of this episode has nothing to do with boss
Alex.
Complain that they're under martial law
And then also brings up the people being
Having a home search
Once again we talked about on the lights.
Episode like he brings those up as little touch
Occasionally but that's really good
Get into a whole lot of
The only real
Kind of substance that I found that had to do with Boston is when
Caller brings up johar
And his back
Hey you guys
Did you look at the two pictures of Boston bombing suspects
Ottoman has a green backpack backpack
The backpack with the bombing it was black
I was just completely making up the both of bombs were in Black backpacks type that means just making
I like I like to call her
Giving us some
McAdoo news
So Alex is getting like he's doing some
Actually
The omni's
Pressure cookers
That was supposed to be in these back
And by research I mean he's trying to put a press
Cooker into a backpack that's kind of what I thought but I thought that was too stupid behind the scenes and
Don't know. It right now
You must acquit
Okay my right be the reference toronto-based
Situations
Clearly didn't
This is the clearest articulation yet of Alex explicitly trying to claim that the Tsarnaev brothers are in
Which is pretty f***** up
But at this point the case had gone to court
So it's totally understandable to be reluctant to jump to can
Conclusion
What to argue in phatic Lee for his innocence
Is a little bit straight
Alex was the only one engaging
Sort of behavior
According to an April 22nd article in wired
The whole community of Zohar
Supporters had popped up on social media
Pushing the hashtag
Free johar
People are posting all sorts of bulshit from your normal false-flag stuff all the way to in
The victims
Must have been fake because they didn't
You feel that there was enough blood around
There it is
A not-insignificant number these are
We're citing Infowars articles to help support their claims that johar was innocent
It should be released
Now in 2019
It's hard to look at that and not wonder if it was order
The way we've seen social media be manipulated particularly around hot-button issues and
Divisive event
Kind of makes me weary
I have little enough faith
Conspiracy socks that I could definitely believe this kind of
Campaign was well within the repertoire it could be a thing that they would do
I deal with it
Yeah that's not to say that I think
There's like a possibility of foreign meddling or
You know there's ways that people could games
Social media in ways that week
Realize
Maybe
Some people probably realize but we weren't super aware of
Being at least
Tested in
Shirt so it's entirely possible that that is
And outside
Situation
Come to bucket with strategies of social media manipulation and
Vacacionar thing
Things that people could have stumbled upon in conspiracy worlds like somebody might have figured out a good way to
Pusha hash
We have a bunch of
Connected accounts whatever all pushing it out
There is something here that could be very nice
All of that sort social media manipulation
And when I think back to Alex's
Earlier career he was doing a lot of
Not necessarily that I'm aware of.
Commedia but what if
Used to do
Was he would do Google Bob
Where he would tell all of his audience
To Google
Specific phrase
In order to make it rise up in the Google Trends
Dude show up in
Suggested searches
Like like false flag
That sort of thing
Yeah
I'm just I wonder I have nothing to base this
I can't prove it
But I do wonder about the organic
Of
That's sort of
Yeah
Only possibly organic
That is also the type of thing babe
They would do but
Now in retrospect with all the
I have about how the
The algorithm has
Exploited
Time and
How we weren't really paying attention
It is hard to look at
So many of the
Situations
Astronaut at least suspect ocean with that whenever it first
Weirdest ugly Hatter the light
Like you know or the
The Tea Party being asked
Kind of
Orchestrated media attack on
His is very similar
It's hard it's hard to know and I know that's kind of one of the reason
Discount
Whole Lotta social media
I think it's not worth really getting to
Up in arms about a lot of
Kind of thing
I'm curious I don't know what I don't know
What's going on
But
This caller that Alex is talking
We find out a little bit more
And it makes this interaction
Completely honest
Listen to almost every day and
14 years old
People
Annoying Orange
Now you probably have so many
People that hate you or make fun of you or call you crazy
Suspension for weapons
So this story is a little bit of a middle ground case for me
Is about a guy named Doug Bartlett who got suspended from his teaching job for bringing gardening tools
The school to show his students
I'm so and after you got tired excited
Got fired when you got suspended
The school
Is that punishment to the suspension a little bit
Excessive
Possibly
But also these are Sharp Tools that could definitely hurt somebody and it was a second grade class
You look like eight year old kids
Sensitive Sharp
Right you can't even have
The way the right-wing media presented the story with the Bartlett just brought a screwdriver in a wrench
The kids about gardening
But the reality is a little bit different
He also brought in a box
Cutter and a pocket
6 chainsaws that he also began to juggle
The flame unsafe working environment
The school review board found that while the discussion of
Tools is part of the proper
Curriculum he was a little bit outside of
Consider appropriate
The right-wing media also said that the screwdriver and wrench
We're kept in a lock
Box out of the Rita
To the students but this is directly contradicted by the findings
Came out when the case
In 2014
From the Cook County record quote
The imposition of a four-day suspension
For leaving such Tools in a place
Accessible to second grade students
Was within the discretion
School
These situations are always
Literally
Always more complicated than the way Alex
He wants cut-and-dry social crisis issues
Giselle
Nuance
He wants them to think that this globalist
I'm so out of control when in reality if you look at the Expo
Details of the case
Kind of makes
Play this guy might get to
Suspended for a few days
It's bad enough that Alex does this stuff
Generally
But to consider that he does this while talking to a fourteen-year-old
Child
Who listens to his show everyday
Is monster
Yeah that is
So inappropriate
Especially
Cicadas Clearlake
Expressing
Feelings of
Isolation and loneliness in rather than
Hey you know what you should still try and connect with people Alex
Everyone you know is lying there all crazy
No he went the kids
Pressing is I express the ideas that I learned from you and people think that I'm crazy because of it
I don't know they are crazy
That's
Abused I am yeah
Act like that you can't act like that you can come live with me
I can't accept that Alex takes calls from minors.
Inappropriate you should not be talkative
It's a family it is not a family
I think
I always talked about how you don't scream because you start Street screen your calls
About how you're not going to take joy in it but you're going to kill all these people or
All evil in the Devil is a Black Pyramid
Don't talk to kid he is he is
Definitely looking into the abyss right
Google
And it gets worse I mean as the call goes on this I think that it's fair to say that this call or this
Next clip of the call
Is Alex
Bucking with this kids
I don't understand
Rafael
Our Generation
Whose religion
Kids late like 14 year olds can't deal with this stuff
I mean I'm not trying to infantilize teenagers or anything but what Alex is talking about he's outside of the
The range
I might bake a 14 year old is not equipped
To deal with that being true or not
Use impressionable
You looks up to Alex
Steering
Come down a very f*****-up hat
Call Alex I'm at lunch I'm going to take this
Listen to biology next
Superior
And he's going to be talking about to f****** Gregor Mendel and I'm going to be like
Have you considered whether or not the overlords are dedicated eugenicist
Discus
Not good
Open wrestle with like what is the worst
Behavior I've ever seen
Tough
That's like asking what's the Worst Behavior I've ever seen
There's so many things
The denial of people
Personal tragedies be
The calls for harassment
That are very clear if not
Literal
Do certain things too terrible.
Profiting off denial of people's try to do right
Why is the
All really bad but in the running is definitely like
Detroit children's braids
Person who's under deepen 16 who I've heard call into Alex behaves this way to
As I recall there's a twelve-year-old I've heard
And like that you
That is a level with inappropriate that I can
Adult
Yeah he's an adult he have kids your parents didn't even allow you to watch f****** late night TV
What is this kid's parents do and let them listen to Alex Jones
I don't know
My parents were over Lisa
Censorious
Very much
Controlling on a level that
I could deal with a little bit less of that
My youth but if the goal is to keep me away from
Stuff like this
A good motivation
So another call
And it's a
The caller
Who
I don't know I don't know if this caller is an idiot but Alex isn't really
Do me a favor
I've been awake since 1 Seawinds George Bush
Junior
I got to wake when he wouldn't close the borders down when he's
The guy wouldn't close the border is going to be like
Okay there supposed
You won't close our borders
What a great prediction
Mass sacrifice of children coming soon
There's a 40
13 year old
Yeah yeah Alex
Great so we got another caller here who thinks the Hunger Games
Real which makes sense
That's because he's listening to Alex's believes that every thought the movie Inferno
But also with the movie Hunger Games
Timmy that's a movie that's just showing where they want the us to go
Population
You have to be to think the gladiatorial games would do anything to impact
That was really cut it really take us down one at a time I guess
The least efficient sisterlook lowest could ever come up with how many battles can we have in a day with the
Gladiatorial games
Let's say we have a hero to one-on-one matches in a couple battle royale's we get rid of 400a day
Hey Dad bye
2025r free
No no f******
Wave Glider toriel Games
Solution to overpopulation
Ridiculous
I would prefer a future where Battle Royale is real
Supposed to
That's my flavor of
Murder each other I would rather neither thank God they're both pictures
You're quite oblivious
That is true
So Alex is now f***** with his fourteen-year-olds mine
You said there's going to be a Mass child sacrifices in the very near future
The globalist want to bring back gladiatorial games in order to reduce population
So this is a good summation
This is a good summation of what he's trying to do on his show
What's happening what's going on
Massdrop sacrifices
For the globalist to worship the giant Black Pyramid that is
This is such a stupid show
I got it
I'm really struggling to remember that
Yesterday
Not. Like this is a week in the past and we've all kind of move.
The 24-hour news cycle and whatnot
This is yesterday that he was saying that full-on martial law was being declared
But everybody in Boston was
Held inside so they could
Hundreds of fake
Patsy
And then the next Aries just like
Man
Go to take some calls your 14 the f*** you up
What is this
Can't do that
It didn't say anything and that's what I mean this is a lesson that we keep learning over and over again that is like
You just never know what he's going to do you have
Spectations you know his patterns you know like
But one of his patterns
Predictability go watch Oblivion yet really f***** up the night before
Really freaked out about it
And then come in
Disaster
That's probably
Really really good
That's really good evidence for why he knows he's full of s***
Because if you actually were
On the greatest story in history of a major United States city being
Put under martial law
People being murdered
You would
Doggett Lake Houston pursue it
Daily
For your request
This would never go away what don't you understand about it in-depth investigation tried to put a pressure cooker in a backpack
What don't you understand that's right I forgot I forgot going
Exactly I forgot that he was feeling better
I apologize
So he talks about Oblivion talk about these authors of the movie
The guy wrote the graphic novel
Person who adapted at these people are like
Opposing parts of the Illuminati in the globalist plan
How many only has one other author you can really compare it to
Nope
Emergency
14 year old
About you and your children
Because I just want
If you do you find out that he doesn't
Know what he's talking about
Just bill Joyce article
You don't realize the only thing that Alex took from that Bill Joy article
Is a passage
It's quoting the Unabomber
Bill Joy hit put in the article
Discussing
F*****-up version views of the future that is all allocate knows about this article
That's what Bill Joy heard at this convention in the Unabomber
Okay so you go to this convention
Do they read the notes from the pre
This meeting or do they just open with
Should we tell
I've been doing Alex's presenting
We get down to business decided we're going to kill everyone
So exhausted
If you if you really were right
I doubt you would have to say I'm right
Twice
And your break down about like I can't be around people who don't share my delusions anymore
Yeah I know I do
People would be fine
If you were right
So Alex Oblivion
Keep bringing this up
Yeah
If I find a little bit upsetting
Because I think Alex
Legitimately almost starts crying talking
We are under attack
That is just
See something like Oblivion
Different archetype message
It was all positive
It was about
Children but also getting the genetics
And
System
Versus
And the soul
And
Compartmentalization
Is used to control everybody
Is just beyond insane
Overriding responsibility
I can hardly be around children
Because they're so innocent they're so good
It doesn't make me angry
Show evil
I just ate your hair clips like that
Should
I don't want to live in a society where people aren't allowed to
See certain movies you're I think you're blaming the wrong side of the media here on this one
I think you might be going the other direction I'm not saying Outlaw Oblivion
I'm saying
Football Alex rooms yeah yeah yeah I don't know how you do
It's just not for Alice
NFL NFL
Yeah
Can't tell the difference between fiction and reality you don't get to
See dystopic Sci-Fi warning on those
TV MA TV delusional just get the f*** out
I find it so upsetting
Pick it up
I feel such a responsibility to
Stop this
Oblivion in my head
Like when he was going through this whole thing I was
Kind of want to do a Sci-Fi 24-hour marathon with Alex and just see what he believes and what he does it
I don't want him to explain anything to me I want to watch his face if it's dystopian
He believes of course
If it's
Not dystopia any probably
It's ridiculous
Liberals
You know the rules
I've heard of them
They want to kill you
That does sound like us they want to kill everyone
But you are but if you
You try to kill them. You
Their total hypocrite
Don't take a good analyst
Kill yourself
So frustrated by this
Logic trap he keeps putting authoritarian liberals in
And they have no way around it
You think the human race is
Is bad and ugly and you want to kill him
Yeah well what if I tried to kill you you'd stop me right
Bulletproof bulletproof Point proven
F****** debate
If you have you've decided that all of your enemies are trying
To depopulate the planet
Conversation becomes difficult because they're going to need to clarify that first premise in order to
Go to any further conversation
And you're not going to let him your dog
Cuz if you say things like
I would like to provide reproductive health care for people in developing countries
Well no
That's why you want to
Kill me
But then you don't
I can't I got to go
I got to go
They don't even know what the
To say is like
Yeah yeah
That's the correct response
Because your argument
Silly
Not wear the hat hour
Earlier when I was talking about this immigration
Isabel there were shades of
Get some
Feelings that he he
He has about
Demographics
And all that
Didn't feel very comfortable
We talked about it a little bit more here in a way that I feel like it makes it a little
So I mean it's tough to hear that I did not hear some
Racial tingy
Votes Republican but then you let him
People who aren't white and don't vote Republican they believe anything take the Gringos sacrament
For Latin American immigrants to take white people's guns
That seems
F***** up
The idea that
There's something like
You're going to bring in people who don't know any who aren't used to Freedom is like a
Is a reason.
Keep people out
They're not they're not used to they're not ready for free
They're acclimated to like a halfway house where your little free but not all the way free
Because if they're free
Here when they're not used to it
Who knows what they'll do
It's it's strange his feelings are muddy
To say that
Put it as nicely as possible
There's not a lot of clarity
But it seems bad
So what are these big complaints about
Janet Napolitano
And her
Position on the immigration bill is that he insists she hasn't read it
And he's basing this on
Little bit of a Cuban a question-and-answer session
Ted Cruz
Who asked her who is not her
No he is pretty ass
Napolitano she's read the bill
So here's Alex's
Is Big gotcha MoMA
Said no one
Received
The text to this bill
At 2:25 a.m.
On Wednesday
April 17th 5 days
It is dealing with a very complicated child
And in my first question is it is
When did did
Did your office receive a copy of
Dylan
About 3
That's about right
In the five days since
It's obviously been
Heavily focused
Don't matter such as
The Boston bombing
Imater such
Have you had the time to read all 844
Four pages of the bill
Actually I have read the bill I know how many section
What
Also I was able to
But I had
Able to review the bill
Has been
A busy week
Yes sir
Very busy
Oh yes
So it's got your moment is Ted Cruz asking if she's read the Belgian I'm familiar with a lot of its was able to
Husky Parts but yeah I'm familiar with the Bell liar
What where's the festival
That's not fair not fair that is rude
I feel like I do
You can't just blame clip of her being like
Meijer
You can prove that you didn't read it
But let's say she asked
7 inch
In five days you think they couldn't
Handle the responsibilities plus reading
What's a 100 pages and giving a brief not just that but when she says I'm familiar with certain parts of it that's
Is the Bill didn't just
Written without her being asked about it at all at all 800 pages
Materialized out of nowhere
This is ridiculous
Stupid so Alex has
Complaints about Napolitano and this is the way it generally goes with
Especially with women in power
Thank you mr. Napolitano thank you for the
Making fun of women that look like men
This is
Good this is good
Analysis hard-hitting political analysis
All women in government look like women who look like
Yes that's
Unzip their alien suits and they've got a
Janet Reno
Janet Napolitano look
Underneath that me this is just particular
This is
He's so annoying
Whenever whenever we
Get back into
If if Warren is the nominee weird
They already are
I know but just so
Yep it's going to be rough
Yep so they're probably
Like people like nopales
Different planet Pop-Tart
This is reality-based Radio
General politano is from outer space and she came here in an upside-down Black Pyramid that I
Last night
Fourteen-year-olds Willis
So I was next up Alex does one of my
Are favored by
Of course
Hope the founding
Weird
Thomas Jefferson
Add reminder
Except
Not a Thomas Jefferson quote
Your paraphrasing Frederick Douglass
Ninety-nine percent of the time he is
No 99% ninety-nine percent of the time you start he's either making something up
Quoting a memory ride somewhere or somebody else's words he's attributed
How do I honestly
We don't know if I've ever heard him
Use a Thomas Jefferson
Quote correct
So we got one last like real clip from
It's Alex
Bragging about being psychic
Because this rice
Suspect
The poison
I'm sorry go ahead
No it's not a globalist
Handbook it's an incredibly f*****-up bizarre situation
Of a rivalry that got way out of control
Just such a more interesting story than some sort of globalist plot
It's ridiculous
You can you can propagandize so many stories but when you get a dynamite story like that you have to do
Just read it for bait
Yeah but
The Alex lot of that
We're able to know now hasn't come out she doesn't have that information
So he can write his own story about it a lot of the Boston bombing stuff in the days
Immediately after it
But when you do have the gift of hindsight you can look back
To be like you f*** that story up
Multiple times
The perfect opportunity
Make a correct say you're correcting yourself in order to do Cerita badass story
Would be
But I don't have to give up his mantle of the
The prophet January
Like I told you I was going to
Now whenever that case probably goes to court
Alex is going to just ignore it entirely
And just let let it sit there as a
Yeah
This episode is pretty short comparative Lee got a big reason for that is
It's so much
About Oblivion
And
Is it love that it's a preview is not
Compact you know like he doesn't give a like a fool like this is what I think of
Seeing with the Drone
Bob
No the other people in there the shipping
The Clones
Yorkie doesn't really get into
Vague talking about how great the movie is
And how it reveals the Illuminati
I've never seen it have you seen
No
I don't give a s*** you didn't watch it in preparation for this
I watch some clips
Myself
I think this is another thing much like childhood's end
And all these other sci-fi things that Alex believes
The real
I just
I wish I wish it was more interest
Oblivion review
Because I we could have played a bunch of clips of it
Fun but it's the
It's just I believe that this was
Globalist
That's no good
I want an Oculus Syfy
I wanted to review like
Gravity or some s*** like that where there's no like there's no secret alien plot or anything like that it's just
S*** goes wrong in Space the movie I'm positive that if we go and find the release date of gravity
He would have Johnny Longworth you
Along flooring reviews
Yeah I don't know I am this was a little bit of a disappointing
Episode in some way
But also
Of his show time I think it it's so fascinating
How
Cindy's
Sci-Fi movies
Blows his mind in a way that is very adolescent
Yeah very close
Yeah it really did that almost crying
It's not like he was
Fighting it
Crying that he would he would have tried to speak
Through it with like a
There would have been more perform
Stupid
Crying yeah it is subdued is not the type of
Performance
So he has this relation
Kinship with
These
Media things that
Like movies that I would describe is
Pretty adolescent
You see these movies and that there truth to you
Even if they are
Even if some of them do try to give like a allegorical or metaphorical
Message about the real world
You could watch The Matrix
And Come Away with some life lesson nothing wrong with that
Revealing secrets
Anything you see with like a Steve
He was talking about how this person in the
Media was writing articles that were to talk to him
This sort of bizarre thinking
That I would describe as
Bucked up
I'm kind of childish
Yeah and
When you have that mixed with
You get a fourteen-year-old collar
And you're just f****** with that kid
Like
I can't I can't not talk about that episode even if it has nothing to do with largely what we're trying to learn
That's it's a mess
It is weird
See this Behavior
So starkin
While at the same time like
Not applying that far larger
Like the weird s*** that people
Jamming to Children's heads
On a daily basis
Hey that reminds you so much of
Alex Jones like everybody around you is crazy
Like everybody around you as sex is going to hell
Like all of this stuff that
Hammer into
And you just shouldn't be left
Nope
That's abuse
I got f***** up for someone who is such a champion of the youth
The children
This sort of behavior towards
Children
Even if 13
Still not
Developed until 25 or some
That's when you can begin talking to me about
That's when you can talk to Infowars
Hopefully yeah
Anyway we'll be back on Wednesday with another episode but I tell them
Knowledge fight.
That's correct we're also on
We are on Twitter that knowledge underscore fight
And I am go to bed go to bed
Facebook to download
Do all that stuff
Absolutely
Until then
I'm Leo
Dzx Clark
I am a black guy
Thanks for holding
Alex