I have great respect for
Knowledge fight
Need money
College fight.com
Everybody sit around and talk a little bit
Alex Jones Jordan Jordan
Alright we've I don't know if you've ever done
I don't know if I actually like
Comedian
I guess okay in in junior high
Maybe not as I can high school
Like a lip sync
Competition
Okay and the class
Yes was
Female
Except for me and one other guy my drama
Yeah and so we had to answer this Lipson
A petition that was like
The entire School District
And the teacher hit shows in d.c.
From
Madea
West Side Story
I like to be in America
Girls in the band's going back
But there was only girls
And me and this other dude in the class and the other dude is like I'm not going to
Yeah and so I was friends with people in the class we were all like
Okay well got a long
So I was in for the team and all the rest of the girls in the class
Powerhouse choice if you're
But instead I wore a dress
Makeup and what-have-you in the
Lip-syncing we were I call
You're Hollow women
Vision
Someone who lost
Who would later become a friend of mine and you are sitting around smoking
Later in life
Discussing this very same speech tournament not knowing that we were both in it he was complaining about
About to guy wearing a dress and then hitting the cup
Kia
It's a Small World moment that I can think of it was I don't
No I don't want to offend be offensive at all like I don't know what
The parameters of drag
Specifically are I don't know if that
I have no idea it was a performer
I think
Respecting
Sure I don't I don't know the time when I want it looks like competition
I like to be in a mirror
Hell yeah
I did that
Denzel's I know that about Alex I didn't and I don't
So Jordan today on the show we're going over the present a little bit for a reason they will become very clear
Pretty quick
November 11th
2019.nfl little bit of the 12th
But the shop is mostly ignorable
Again once it becomes clear why I'm doing this you'll understand why there's
The twelve Ryan also it'll be clear Wyatt
Not that much of it
At this point
But what's not does
There we go
He's taking a little moment Jordan before we get going crazy thank you
To some folks who signed up and are supporting the show
So first of all ice
Wallow
Come thank you so much you are now policy walk
Okay
Journal about what you want
Eczema
Let's Ryan thank you so much and I hope I was wrong
Next Cara or Cara
ARA okay here could be
We're going we got you coming and going
Hbx
Thank you so much you are now a policy wonk
Mexican Jonathan thank you so much you are now a policy wonk
William thank you so much
William text motor sheep
Policy wonk
Finally
By-tor night of Darkness Centurion of evil Devils Prince gangster of boats
I'm a policy wonk
Because I'm about to buy Coronavirus
Centurion Boats
Thank you so much thank you if you're out there listening like sport it
Website.com
Support the joke we would appreciate
I think it's a testament to how great
Our fans really are
It took this long for us
Get so many jokes
Yeah
And they don't often drift into the rippled OR adult
This is a family show
There's one thing you know about this is a family show
So before we actually get right
Bully downtube is
I also have to say a very special shout-out
Thank you little bit of showbiz
To our dear friend been around
Such a long time
Hanging out loving the show
Being cool from Sweden
She got in touch with me
And
Sent overseas
It's Jordan
Yeah she reached outside over a packages
Candies
From Sweden
Am so I feel like they first of all thank you
You so much
That's one way we can thank you but another way is to do a little bit of a taste test
Pure on air
Avahi won't open this package
She Wrote
You're not in her little
Giuseppe little note along
Give you the description of these treats
We're going to be trying here
These are the
Jungle fry
I apparently I think it might be
Play jungle Roar
In Swedish
She explained that by law
In Sweden you have to if you're sending people can do you have to send licorice stuff over
Okay by long like this is an actual what are some of the Kings
And so
She sent over some that are what you do
Describes as the soyboy cook level of licorice
Haha and those are these salty cat
I want
Jungle monkey
Monkey
Equation
Alright these are the complete
Start level
I've licorice okay these are tasty to Sonia but not Everyone likes it right
So now we're going to find out Jordan
What I like
Stud level of liquor
I don't even like the soy version of liquor
I'm going to give them this is
Oh this is real this is real this is a man dying
Elizabeth dying in my face
Oh my God that's so salty
Subway
Alright here we go it looks a little bit like a pellet like this is what
Koalas
It's very startling
Womb
Sweating
It gets better
Just 10 minutes
The dead are chewing that's what our show is fixed hell yeah I will say that that is a pensive
Worst thing I've ever put in my mouth
That that's what that is offensive at the first
Stop B for sure
Whatever that
Saltiness
Frontier
Appreciate it
Wow
Is this is what Sweden's bring to the table I say interesting
But no thanks
I understand why you guys
To eat all that weird
Now it all makes sense
All the weird fish stuff makes sense now
Anyway we appreciate it I'm sure some of the other stuff that was in that other candies are in the package are much better than this
Complete stud level of licorice but
Atlantic most interesting thing to
Yeah yeah
The nothing has been even close to that Kip
Still dunk
Upfront that's salty whatever the f*** intense
Holyshit
S***
Genuinely have no idea how to handle that I can't finish it it's just in my mouth I can't stop
Anymore
I saw some the packaging of these candies in
I'm going to plan trips
Sweden now
Shrimp scampi
Anyway let's get down to business
Just so Alex starts off the show here on November 11th
Standing in front of his desk
As if you some sort of a real professional news
And he knows that this is weird so he decides to explain why
In front of his desk asking why lately I've been out
Front
When we start the show many times
Behind the desk
Probably years many times I've got nothing over the map wall or go to a video feed and
Pointing things out like a weatherman would do
Political weathermen
With only
357 days left to this historic election
I'm doing it because
I want a note
Visually
Everyone
We're not in Kansas anymore
The world is really on the brink
A total breakdown disaster if good people
Don't exert our full political
Cultural economic and spiritual will
Because if we fail with that we're going to have to exert our physical will because we have no other choice
Grandpa's coming at a show damn evil there will be worldwide massive
Civil war and violence
Until he got to the end there I was sitting here like why did I cut this clip this is so uninspired and boring and then I realize
We lose the election we're going to have to murder all of our political enemies
Clip to cut
There I think that would this is why I'm political weathermen
I know of other political weatherman that Alex hates
Yeah
Bill Ayers
But yeah so that's a bad note
Start the show offline
Yeah
His main storyline throughout that least the beginning of this episode is about to the revelations
Nikki Haley
Brought forth
About how
Rex Tillerson
And
Who was it
McMaster Kelly Maybe
They were trying to
Stop Trump from causing
Trouble
And I Alex describe
Have this
As treason
I'm going to lay out information here on the show today
That is of the
Complete Paramount
Importance
Nikki Haley
Former governor
Ambassador from the US
Battery issues my I've had problems with her
But she least understand that is treason
When you undermine the president
And try to set him up and when he signs executive order you take control and trash can
Or what he says bring me infowars.com articles daily
You refuse to do it
That is
Freezer
Quite frankly not allowing him to have Infowars articles is not true
Disobedience turned into trees and real quick right yeah yeah
An inability to disentangle those two things
Not kowtowing
2 and doing exactly what Trump tells you to do
A man who's made his brand on
Defying Authority and disobeying a every possibility
Getting headache while you're just replacing forwards articles with whatever
You're not getting a coffee
Who is this
Ridiculous
So they were trying to keep him for his articles away from
Because
They were on
To the mainstay
Early
High-powered
Billionaires
Drunk
I'm so fool
We hear the establishment under run things you'll be out in just a few months
Call the president
Couldn't even get them on the phone so they called Rodger Stone
The next day and so did I
We got told if you don't keep your mouth shut your dead
Ilevel CIA unit
Piss up a rope
Are you better
Better make sure I don't see you coming
I'll piss on you how's that sound
Family Show
You piss up a rope and don't act like I thought you was going to say if you see me coming I'm going to kick your ass not I'm going to pee on
Very strange
He's gross weird
How is it that we're on we're going to
Kill everybody could start a new Civil War and then
Backstage bulshit now we're peeing on people I don't know
Stuff happened for particular reason
That I think I'll
I'll be able to lay out as we go along
Also how is this supposed to work with that whole notion of like Trump's it's up till 3 in the morning
Just sitting by the phone
The people normal people can call him
Too busy talking to some guy from Idaho
Have a good day
I think this show starting out weird
Because
What Nikki Haley is bringing out does matchup
Pretty closely with what Alex has yelled about
For a long time
Assertive
Miniature version of he doesn't know how to win
He doesn't know how to take this and
And just run with it. There's got to be more
So Alex says starts talking about the plans to demoralize the
The country should know
You just see them everywhere
Receipt you can see them they're there their manifest all around. Let's see what they are
Because when you are conquering a nation and selling it off
Butchering it a dumbing it down
Psychologically demoralizing it and poisoning
Breaking up the family
That's how you do it from
There are the 49 secret plans of the Communist to bring down
Alma famous senatorial reports
What's the Russian communist
Started taking over Russia we're using the same poison on us we gotta
Read those lists are on air today that we will
I don't know what
WikiLeaks
Stuff he's talking about cuz he's always so vague with that stuff
I know that he's talked about those demoralize and
Divide and all that stuff
Relation to like the podesta and Clinton
And so I decided like I have no idea what he's ever talk
I'm about he never
I'm going to look through those emails
I didn't read all of them cuz there's words
If you so I
I searched around
For articles
About like the most damning thing
Things that were in those eat
Because
You know I'm not going to look through everything for the podcast there's just there's no way I have that time
So it's a little bit voyeuristic of annex
Exercise for me
You two like to read these emails because I know that
Then they weren't meant to be public
320 process feel like it's less like
Research and more like Snoopy
No that's to say that there isn't stuff that's worth the being covered in those email dumps I just think they've been covered pretty
Play this boy
And I can't really find any material about demoralizing
Society
Being the Cornerstone of some democrat globalist
Can't find any articles
Citing that
Well did you search for corn
Cornerstone
Globalist plot
Is there a lot of words
Demoralize only shows up
And completely unrelated context in the Hillary
And only in one
Email in the protest
Files
Email from May 24th 2015 with a campaign cable that served as a rundown of stories in the media about
Out Hillary
The word demoralize shows up in a copy and pasted Chung
From an article on real
Clear politics
With a headline quote why less competition
Is hurtful
The article is basically positing that without a strong rival from within the Democratic Party
She won't have an opportunity to defend her record in the prime
So questions about her controversies
Controversies will still be on the table
When she answers the general election
This Dynamic also means that all the media attention would be on Hillary prior prior to the general
The article says quote
Well media attention is
Appositive
Out for a candidate being it's almost Soul focus on the Democratic side has not been easy
And this could well serve to demoralize Democratic voters
They're already signs that in the Nash
National polls
I'd like to say that this is what Alex has taken and misrepresented but honestly I have no idea
That's Amore lies Democratic voters
Podesta emails
I don't know I have no idea he always just says it's in the Wikileaks and never explain to
Any further so
I don't
You know if he doesn't care to be more specific
Pacific I'm just going to Zumiez making s*** up until
Find
To the contrary
You might as well just say look it up it was on the news in the sky
Plane flew and it wrote it in the sky
What's be more specific look into it further but as it stands
It's now but I don't know what is you talkin about babies
Some sort of a
Like other
Email dump
Some other documents Wikileaks one of the lesser-known ones you know
Is the B-side
He's he's a real into the original way
So now about those 49 plans of communism
The first thing I should tell you that there's only 45
And I should tell you that it's b*******
On January 10th
Three representative Herlong of Florida took her to the floor of the house
He said that a constituent of his was an Ardent an enemy of communism
And requested that he read the 45
Goals of communism
Into the first official Congressional Record
Because a representative ready
These goals and it was recorded now all these people think that it's something real
These 45 goals of Communism were red directly out of the naked communist by W Cleon skousen
Jamaica capital
No that's his other book
He has
Fall Guy Tv the whole series it's just these to make a communist was about justifying
McCarthyism
It's a it's a misrepresentation of a lot of that communist
Right Red Scare s*** is about Carol quickly
And misrepresenting the anglo-american
Establishment
And tragedy
Anyway
He didn't even
Finish the trilogy
I mean I guess you could say the five thousand year leap was
Maybe that butt naked franchise going
Naked leap yeah absolutely so anyone who's listen to our show long enough knows that W Cleon skousen
He was an anti-communist propaganda Stew was probably too extreme
For the John Birch
Society in the late 5th
And his books the naked capitalist and naked communist are bedrocks of Alex Jones is stupid world.
These 45 goals of communism a part of a rich tradition of forgeries pretending to be Revelations
The secret machinations of the communist
They were yeah I mean to some extent a lot of the stuff is that is part of this
Literary tradition of yay
There was a list of communist rules for revolution that popped up in the mid-50s
Which was said to have been discovered by Allied soldiers back in 1919
Of course it was a complete hoax
But it served to give Focus to the fears and paranoia is that were popping up in the Cold War era
The Communist enemy was so mysterious
List of people that it became insanely easy to demonize your enemy
By releasing
Fake documents
The purport to show that's a wet Vista
40 secretly in line with the secret plans of the commies
We're basically commies
And therefore the end of
That's all skousen blisters
It's a completely fake pile of s*** you wrote to pushes politics
He disagreed
Number 13 being
Party hard was a
So this is a huge problem because Alex clearly think
It's categorically not real
Also it's
Kind of funny when you actually read the rules because Alex Jones himself is furthering some of these fake Communist goals
Number 24 is quote eliminate all laws governing obscenity and calling them by calling them sense
Shipping a violation
The free speech of the Free Press
If I'm not much mistaken Alex fancies himself a bit of
Absolutist these days
Absolutely would support getting rid of all obscenity laws that limit free expression
I guess either,
Number 35 is quote discredit and eventual
We dismantle the FBI
If I'm not much
What's Alex's spent the last
3 years of his on-air career screaming about how the FBI's completely infiltrated by globalist in Trump needs to
The clean house in jail all of them
Skwarkami would do
Most damningly
Number 42 is quote
Create the impression that violence and Insurrection or legitimate aspect of American tradition
If I'm not much mistaken In This Very episode
Alex's discussed the necessity of insurrection if his team doesn't win the next
Alexa
Goddamn catchphrases the answer to 1984 is 1776
Alex Jones is someone who is very very into making violent
Insurrection illegitimate
Aspect of America
Tradition
Just like a commie would we all heard it here first
Alex Jones is a,
To be fair the that rule about insurrection
Is in the contacts
Text of the rules
The fake rules that skousen road
It specifically about disenfranchised
Minority and special interest groups
Not getting the idea of its interaction is part of it
Anyway just listed stupid Auntie, this chain email bulshit Bay
Stupid to know
How many
Well you're you're forgetting the
4 secret gold
So Alex you know he's saying here that you got
Does globalist plan
It's being furthered by people like Kelly and
McMaster
Tillerson and
Nikki Haley at least you stood up against it denotes all to demoralize society as proven by the WikiLeaks
Fake 49ers
List of
Globalist
Communist plot
And how it's going to manifest
How it Hazmat
Manifested
Curses Upon Our Country
What the Alex Reid's coffee just starts
Discussing going to take these one by one
After this clip and explain
We already knew what Nikki Haley has come out and said was true
That they would come to her and say Trump is an idiot
Destroy the country
You've got to help us undermine him
A Nazi
Comporium
And block his agenda
When the globalist have sat here and presided over
The industrialization of America
The dumbing-down of America
Life expectancy Plumbing
Plummeting
Immortality exploding
And all the other curses that are upon the nation
Trying to undo all that
Yeah Saudi industrialization
First thing you brings up more complicated of an issue than Alex
I think and honestly I have no idea what statistics
To even look into to discuss his point
I don't know what he defines the industrialization is
I don't know what data point is going to be like and if you do if you do whenever he gets
Said he'll change his definition it's none do I don't care possible
I move along I'm not conceding the point now I'm saying irrelevant to the conversation
Move Along
Concession it is
The next is the dumbing-down of America
What does it mean by
Is it based on IQ scores cuz those are the perfect test of intelligence
And even if they were a January 2018
Paper in the journal intelligence notes that
While there were drops in Nordic
IQ scores that have been observed the US was on an upward trajectory Rising point three points.
Plus again IQ scores don't really mean
To demonstrate how dumb this whole conversation is 11
U2 headlines
From the Inc
The website
The first is quote
We're all getting Dumber new science proves and no one is sure why
That was from June 14th
Flash forward to June 27th 2019 and you get this
Humanity might not be getting Dumber after all new study suggests
A year apart the same publication and both articles were written by the same person
There's too much
Weird people just have too much, then you got to fill space
You just got it sometimes you can just let it go man
In 2018 everyone saw this study about a drop in IQ that was observed in the study of people living in Norway and
Reported it super response
When more data was in
It was all whoops
Dumber after all
Every single article I can find that the
Discusses me we're getting Dumber idea as being proven links to that Norwegian study
And it's all s*** or very least
Woefully oversimplify
If Alex wants to suggest that the population is getting Dumber he needs to
Explain what you mean by that
I'm almost certain that you just read headlines that came out in 2018 about this Norway study
You haven't cared to read any of the newer information
The completely contradicted
And I actually shows the office
IQ scores don't mean anything standardized test scores
I don't think that's early believe is even a good indicator of Intelligence on this on this scale
You get tattoo even have
A full conversation about the idea that America is getting Dumber you really need to dig into figure out what
What are your indicators but how do you define intelligence
And I don't think he's equipped to have that
The kids
He doesn't want to have a conversation with me like all kids with Tik-Tok I don't even know what it is so life expectancy
Plummeting according to Alex
Talkingshit
In 1970 the life expectancy in the United States was 70.81 years
In 2016 it was 78.69
That is not a plumber
Turley speaking life expectancy in the United States is on the upward path it has been for decades
Are there was a point 15-year drop
From 2014
And you can find plenty of Articles taking this very seriously
I'm not suggesting they shouldn't
But I think it would be a little bit much to call that a plumbing
Strong suit
A suspicion that Alex isn't talking about us
Expectancy
I think he's talking
About white people
A very specific
Group of people
I believe
Perhaps
Menor wine
A recent paper in the journal population in developed
Review
Observed life expectancy rates among non-hispanic white Americans
Increasing at a lower rate than the general population
They weren't able to pinpoint the exact reason for this but some of the prevailing theories had to do with the opiate crisis killing more Young
Rural White
People and with obesity levels
Yeah I'm going to go with
Whatever the exact reason for the phenomenon is you can find articles of headlines that are you know you could just imagine how easily they would
From Science Daily
Quote for non-hispanic whites in the United States life expectancy Outlook worsens
From ajmc quote
Study review reveals declining life expectancy among white America
There's some real issues behind this stuff for sure like dealing with what reach researchers called deaths of despair
Like overdose
Suicide
But from listening to as much Alex's I have IP very inclined
Please read some of these headlines about white life expectancy
Got really mad
Yeah that was excited life expectancy
Good life
That's that's my
Especially yeah
Infant mortality Alex is saying it's exploding
It's not according to data from the
CDC the u.s. infant mortality rate decreased 14%
Between 2007 and 2017
I have no idea what else is talking
There are no other curses that are abomination
Alex Jones everything you just said
In that clip means nothing
And for the most part it isn't based on any reality
At very best symptom headlines
Does using whatever they made him
Feel fuel
I'll just the anger that he gets for these
Headlines
I know a
Lack of critical thinking
Ease of lion yeah
Is that the percentage of that
Conway open
Soup
You know we got
These curses that are upon America which don't really see
Seem to be real
B
Even even if they are real
America's finally away
Finally waking up
We're weak
Because of all the curses
But we're awake okay
Getting clearer and we see what's going on
Define Ali
Finish this off
Shell Arkansas
The highest bidder
I personally
The only way I can do that is when you spread the word and when you buy the products When you pray for us you do that damn
Wow
Arisa just run
I can kill the Goblin
Spell I need your money
To kill Goblin I like his new
Candy Crush Market
Reading strategies
Like send me money and you'll get better at allowing me to kill Goblin
For you I like
Doesn't microtransaction
Goblin dead
So
That was pretty gross
This is how Alex goes out to break
Noticed a weird phrasing that
He keeps using
I wonder if you lie think you'll get I don't know exactly where that comes from
I'm telling you that this whole country
World is in grave Danger
Yourself
For True infowars.com where the defense of human Liberty
So he's he said guard yourself for True a number of times and like I know that's from something I recognize that
Salford
From Dune
Yeah that's what I like
It has to be from somewhere else
Is this motorcycle
Gird yourself he was using
Miss speaking but now.
Yeah the phrasing guard yourself for true so specific
Yeah yeah
And saying it's insane how many things are just like
Little little things he's ripped
From various sci-fi thing
Sergeant
And that was that
Frank Herbert
Doing some
Shakespearean ripoff
Noise right there
Sherp
So Alex did that shity I can kill goblins if
If you give me money
Money allows me to
To kill goblins
Thanks
Long rant
About the everything was ghost
It is still going on
Everything is not gone
Whatever
So much is selling out that he
He has to end this sale but he keeps not ending the sale
It just keeps going on
I meant and you know it
You got to buy his product
So you can kill Goblin
Right that's not enough
Local affiliate
Infowars
Give your money to local radio stations
Weekly or monthly
Civilization
Leash
Is somebody just tied to a radio
And just Alex in that agreement that they have to sign
A Alex to broadcast on there
Is it weighs one part of that if somebody X he gets a cut
No not what I would
Days that Alex's
Aware that almost nobody would send
Send money to a radio station
Play that errors
A certain show
And so if you are like working at the radio station right some people even if it's a miniscule amount
Send money as like I hear thank you for airing Alex's show
Hugely popular show
Much less inclined to take it off the air cuz it went like
In the same way they talk about how like one phone call is equivalent to 100 people in Congress
Congress members
View that as a as being representative of a much larger
Will think this thing but not
Follow through with it
You got to assume if you're getting off
Ifucking check
From somebody because they listen to Alex's show at you your radio station that airs it
And you're still making all the ad
It'll be like that's got to be a hundred thousand
F****** people represented by this one check
And that's probably not true but if Alex
Pinprick like
No no
5 people around the country to do that he's got five stations
She's far more secure
He would be otherwise
It's just it just good strategy
I mean it's sacrilegious
For sure
Wrong it's wrong
On a number of levels
So we get back to this stuff
About
Nikki Haley
And
So
Alex
Is mostly concerned about how people like General Kelly
And Taylor singing
They were trying to
Keep Infowars away from
What seems to be the spokes
In this wheel that he's most
Concerned
And it's because Alex
Broke really
Important stories
Long before anybody else
This isn't like
Claiming with a zeitgeist
Zeitgeist
Literally
With Kelly
New York Times Washington Post everywhere but I confirmed the inside the White House it was do not
Not let him have infowars.com
Do not let
The president
Talk to people
Dinesh D'Souza
Wow right they tried to keep
Using the truth
No
Avista
Until people show him and he knows we've supposed
Fiona Hill first
We exposed
Ciaramella
Hear simultaneously with Mike cernovich
And
The Deep state
I had the same sources we learned later they were
Eversource
I never outsources
He had quite a few
Still dies
It was public
That
Don Jr
Whatever Alex
Play whatever games you want
So here we have Alex insisting the general Kelly wanted to keep Alex's information away from
Chop because Alex was just so accurate
Based on the fact that he been yelling about Fiona Hill in the past
And apparently you'd mention Derek's your Mirella ciaramella
Which is the name that's being thrown around as being The Whistleblower brought up concerns about Trump's phone call with Ukraine
President
I'm not sure if that is accurate it very well could be
I didn't care to look
But beyond that
All this is bulshit
The bigger picture is
Is b******* and I want to parse through this pretty careful
In terms of Eric ciaramella I can only find references to his name being on the Infowars dating back to November 1st
And it's based on a tweet from Benny Johnson
Who's the guy who has found a job working with Turning Point USA
And forgetting unceremoniously fired from multiple Publications for play Juris
He someone has zero credibility
And whether or not he has the name right about this
This alleged whistleblower
It's unwise to basic reporting on his face
This is the source that Alex is pretending you some high-level guy
Just some dude at turning point
Benny Johnson Twitter at this guy's name
Old 2 days
Prior to Infowars even having an article about this
It would seem like if the globalist in the White House like Rex Tillerson were concerned about Rogue
Recording like this they would see
Keep people like Benny Johnson and turning point out
Not people like Alex or just reposting the shity days later
You've already put out
An interesting Lee
They don't
Turning Point USA has a very close relationship with the trumps
And in fact
Just the other day they host
Studebaker event for Don Juniors new book triggered
Which was disrupted by trolls associated with
Straight up white nationalist
Nick Fuentes
Very very careful about this
It's I hate to to use this sort of
Language
Necessarily
That's an important
Things pay attention to the phone on right now
Nick Fuentes
And his dudes
The way I would
Describe it is try to usurp
Turning Point USA
Disrupting their events
And heralding their true conservative values
Which are really just Christian whites
Christian
More or less
Took the like
We need to
We need to be very aware of that
Cuz it looks like a situation where you like I let them fight
Yeah yeah but in reality what you have is
A vapid grift
In the form of Charlie Kirk and turning point USA
Did that what they're doing is
Dumb
Also full of some racist
Yeah yeah for sure but the diversion
Nick Fuentes
Is involved in its Farm oryx
That version of
Conservatism
Is way more f***** up yeah
And what he's doing is trying to use Turning Point platform in order to increase his own
Right
And I think that probably be
Successful because
Well I mean that's why you
They were trying to keep Infowars and
Dinesh D'Souza inch it away from Trump
Is because you're not supposed to get high on your own Supply
You can't forget that you're running the game on the roofs
Because if you start to believe info worship
Senor
It's it over
You got that virulent
Conservative
I think this is one of the problem
That you see
Of
These things like
Infowars are turning point
Entirely is that they are really
Not so when Infowars exist
As this conspiracy theory
Bulshit
Entity for really long time
It leaves it the audience
And Alex himself
Pray
For someone like Trump to come along
You know you have Rodger Stone, and he completely
We validate it's not a hostile takeover necessarily
But you have this thing that's much more powerful than him
Common
In-N-Out
Alex has become that
Turning point is
Pointless
The desert of what would you call it even
Pseudo libertarian values that they express are not appealing
Two college kids they're not appealing to the younger generation
And so you have this thing
This entity that
That is just ripe for the picking
For someone like Nick Fuentes to come along
Ayan
Use is trolls
Whatever
I think it's actually I think it's a pretty dangerous thing
I think it's
I think I don't I don't know if it'll amount to anything
But I do think it's something that's important
For people to recognize cuz
When we talked about Nick
He was on Infowars because he
He disrupted HR guys
Disrupted the Charlie Kirk of
Yeah and
Waldorf
It's like you might just be talking
There's a clear targeting that's going on by Associates of Nick Fuentes
Vets are there trying to
Attack
Turning Point
And it's not because of some
They're trying to Annex
Turning Point
And then they're going to use that leverage they're trying to
Peabody of it but not
For some better reason
Let's to radicalize
The people who are there to be ratified
And that's dangerous
Because
Every turning point in
Worst version of the election
Trump
Entirely is Jay
This massive system that has
Has been
Praying upon people and trying to keep them inert
And
Just trying to fuc
I convinced them of all kinds of things that aren't real
Will be inevitably taken over by somebody who is simply simply
Simpling
Who is making the message
Simple clear and pretty
Tending to stand up for
The worst makeup
Doubt how like
What was it that you read some
Great
That was like
You always end up
The waves
Conservative Shirtworks you always
End up falling Victor
Jump to someone who claims
You're not the real conservative
And they are you're not standing up for True conservative values
Because that's what you said when you took over right
It's how it works
So I'd you know
Turning Point USA is very deep
Entwined
And get this
One of the places that Benny Johnson was fired from
What's the Independent Journal Review
Before he got fired the ijr was the only media Outlet invited to come along with Rex Tillerson on his tour of a
Asia
Seems like Alex's narrative doesn't make a whole lot of sense here because the guy who outed this alleged whistleblowers name
Is a guy who works for turning point
And
Tillerson was involved with the organization that he used to be at and now
The Trump White House is totally fine with Turning Point
They're not trying to keep that information away from him
That Justin for the wonder why maybe there's another reason
So now it's 4
Fiona Hill
That one's a little more
As you may recall Hill is the former National Security Council official who is testified
After becoming aware that there was a bit of a quid pro quo situation going on
People in the Ukrainian government
John Bolton told her to lawyer up
Angie's testified
About some stuff
And that testimony is going to be pretty important
In terms of this impeachment investigation
Because it's very expensive
She was in meetings were people like Ambassador sondland words
Discussing the ship fruity open
So whatever actually ends up happening on that front it's very important
Alex to discredit her as a source of any of her
And luckily for him he's already done that
On May 31st
Rodger Stone appeared on Alex's show and announced that he'd learned
The George Soros had infiltrated the Trump Administration by installing Fiona Hill into the National Security committee
Weirdly she was appointed by Trump himself
So I'm not exactly sure
I thought you were so many masks
I'm not sure how this
Conspiracy is supposed to have played out in the real world and unfortunately Rodger isn't big on the details
I wonder why
There's a couple important points
The first is that
Alex and Rodger spent the better part of three years calling literally everyone they disagreed with Soros infiltrate
Reince priebus
Steve Bannon Sean Spicer
Kushner
And Ivanka
Have all been in the crosshairs is Zoros plants and Globus meddlers
At at various points in time
Alex don't get to pretend that he was Pro
Prophetic about Fiona Hill eventually testifying about Trump because he said on-air Jesus or rose plant
Because he calls everyone a Soros
Doesn't mean anything that'd be
You should have one episode
An hour and
Reads off every single name in the in the executive branch entirely just be like
Let's see where we at where at assistant deputy director of the that's a Soros plant
That way 6 months from now he can be like I told you it was this one
Yep so probably the more important element to this is dating Hill's recent testimony she talked about the real life
Impact of Alex and Rodger Zack
My entire first year of my 10-year at the National Security Council was filled with hate
Calls conspiracy theories
Which has started again frankly
As it's been announced that I've been giving this deposition accusing me of being a Soros mole in the white
She went on to say quote I received I just have to tell you deathrun
Kohl's at my home
My neighbor's reportedly reported someone
Coming and how
Hammering on my door
Jonah Hill's life very
Well could have been put in.
Very least and insane level of harassed
What was directed at her
Directly because of Alex
And Rodgers on-air Behavior
According to her own resume
What you can find
It's very public
Do the member of the Central Eurasia project
Advisory Board
Of the open Society
Institute from 2,000
The 2006
A good decade before she was appointed to the NSA
SE bikes
Himself
That's the connection
The Smoking Gun that's enough for people like Alex and Rodger 2.2
That's all they need to risk your life
Because they're so desperate to come up with any kind of rationalization for weather supposed god-king
Isn't getting anything
I'm done
You people are vile irredeemable mans
No one should feel pity for Alex when he has to pay the Sandy Hook families for what he did to
We should instead feel for the countless other people who will never get any rest
Institution for the abuse David subject
Did you buy Alec
I don't I don't give a
F*** about this
Because I did all we pointed out that Fiona hill was a Soros
Plant
She works for the the open
Societies
Who cares
Who cares choose anybody on the NSC I bet you can find something 2.2 if you want to call them out
F****** b*******
Careers
There
This is how that world works
You just jump from weird position to weird position
And even if they
Yeah
And if you have a certain
Sporty's go finder
Play it your way somewhere
Like I I just
Think
It's so
Insane
To look at this sort of thing
And recognized
The real life impact
You never hear about
I do generally wouldn't hear about what Fiona Hills experience was after
Being targeted by
Thoughts or whatever you think about it because
He does this with so many
But
There are real-life consequences
She had to deal with
Clearly dachshund cuz if people were calling her home and have someone showed up at her house
Like
Ensure
A lot of other
Conservative Outlet
We're pushing that she was a Soros mole
The traces back to Rodger
So that
He better do.
There's another funny wrinkle to this but
Have to wait till a little
Alex Goes to break after yelling about how we broke this Ciara Morello what you did
You just
F****** posted a tweet
MacGyver
Point
And Fiona Hill staffing
A prune
Pointless
She goes to break
When he comes back
I think that I did one of the grocer
I've heard Alex
Sixth-rounder main funder of the
Helmets
So Isis
Al-Qaeda could jump
Force between the ambulances
Mortars and heavy machine guns
Just got found
Almond turkey
Show called James Bond
Found out the James Bonds just a fantasy
This is the reality
Pushing Daisies now
Wonder
Wonder what happened to me looks so young and healthy
Yelp set all that up to
He's not doing too well now
So
Your phone calls starting next segment
Gross
Buck
First things first the founder of MI6 died in 1928
The person who Alex is talking about is a guy named James Loomis CA
Intel was a former officer of the British army
And a co-founder of the white helmet
That's an organization that literally everyone in the world other than Alex and his weirdo friends
View as a humanitarian
At this point it's pretty unclear with the situation
About this death
Sky News was reporting that James's wife told police that she and her husband to taking sleeping pills and gone to bed
Then later she was awoken by people knocking on her door
She went outside to find him in the street surrounded by police
Haven't fallen off the balcony
As someone who's taking sleeping pills before I can say that it's
Entirely possible that he might have had a weird react
Sleep walked off the
That's paws
I don't know if that's the case for sure
But pharmacologically that is a possibility
His wife is also apparently told friends that James had just begun taking
Can
So the possibility of him dying
By Suicide
Is also not totally outside the realm of possibility
There's a lot of
Possibilities of what could have happened
But Alex is intact
Sing like those things are pause
He's treating this like it was a murder
And he's f****** gloating about
That's grotesque Behavior no matter what the reality is
Alex is acting like this is a murderer because
He believes that Russia killed this
This is based on the fact that three days prior to his death the Russian foreign Ministry tweeted Out quote
The white helmets co-founder James limit Serie A is a former agent of Britain
Am I sick
Who has been spotted all around the world
Including in the Balkans
And the Middle East
The proof Alex has for his claim that this dude was MI6
This is just a Russian foreign ministry's Twitter account
And because of the street Alex has decided that Russia killed him and Alex's happy
About this turn of events
I know that I sound like a broken record
These modern-day episodes
But Alex Jones is severely mentally ill
He's imagining a foreign government killed a man
And he's relishing it
It doesn't it doesn't get better from here guys
Likes get this guy to a
Yeah that's
And then just bring him then just bringing McCain up like
Okay
Alright
So
We're just going to
Gloat about people dying
That's what we're doing now that's he's doing
It's not so outside of his
No David Rockefeller died he was so celebrating a lot it's
It's grotesque childish behavior
Eve needs
He needs to figure out
Yeah he has a lot of work
To do on himself
While I don't think he has the
Emotional capital
Everything I read about mysterious
He's a cool dude
Yeah yeah hoo a cool dude
I'm not one
To pretend that I know
Lots or at like that I'm an expert in the sea
Civil War but everything that I can find that isn't
Ideals this is a humanitarian organization that rescued civilians
And we're caught up
Battlezone
So I don't
I mean even imagining that he is
A bad person
This Behavior still no good
I just
But
He's also needing me
Begging you
For yourself and your family's future
Commitment of this broadcast if I wanted to feed these people
Please
Please remember
But it is only Your Word of Mouth
It gets us around the sensors
Your financial support to fund the operation
And only your prayer
Dino
Two of us
That is your intercession
That is literally
Giving us discernment
It's
But
I need that
That
Absolutely
Explain real fast and loose with the Bible here yeah
So that first versus paraphrasing is Matthew 18:19
Which says quote
Truly I tell you that if two of you on Earth agree about anything they ask for it will be done for them by my Father in heaven
You can read that verse and think that you can get a buddy to join you in agreement about whatever you want then God's going to make it so and Heaven
Liza painfully dumb reading
A text
If you take the verses that come before this and around it and
Context for the book
Acts it's very clear
This is about the functions of the early church
This is what this is this versus
Has nothing to do with
You know hey
You know you guys get together
We can make my operation
Functional
Yeah we're like what do you want
A pool a pool
The Department of Treasury up in heaven
But what
What if we want
Haven't not to
The other one siding is closer
That one is proverbs
Going to be outside
Man chooses his path but God guides our steps
Well I was just looking that one up those we can make sure he actually knows what he's talking about Universe future times he wants to cycle
You should read the rest of proverbs
16 years versus 27 and 28
Quote a worthless man digs upheaval in his speech is like a scorcher
Fire
A perverse man spreads dissension
Anna gossip divide
It's close friends
Haha
I don't understand
Maybe he prefer proverbs
Quote
He who is slow to anger is better than a warrior
And he who controls his temper is greater than one who captures a city
I know I remember exactly why I hated reading proverbs
When I was growing up his cousin
Real judgy
We're judging who the f*** are you Solomon
Seems like that is a whole lot in this one chapter of proverbs that Alex didn't
Seem to absorb
If I had to bet I bet you saw that f****** verse on a mug
Oh yeah 100%
Cannot stress
Strongly
Enough
I do not believe that Alex's
Ever read the book
No
Not even close
In the same way that all his Thomas Jefferson quotes come from like memes and right-wing extremist
I bet a lot of
Does 2
Like and the weird servings of extremist reggae
Christian identity preachers yelling about stuff
So we got this this whole vibe
Going on man
Where you know why is everybody so worried about Infowars until like 8 and obviously answers the Alex's rhetoric
Answer is
Because we revealed
Fiona Hill sharing this whistleblower we we have all this accurate information it all
Now the real answer is because your behavior leads to
Two people's lives being a
Well yeah
That too that's the real reason the people take this seriously and are like this
Probably
We should be aware of this
So Alex
The idea of people being concerned about what
He's doing
And then he lists on some good
The people in Congress
Price of worried about Trump
You say
Princess Dave
Sold out the shy comes and others
Pretty easy to run
We're fighting back
Not a bunch of Yes Men
Kaleesh
Congressman Jordan
Congressman Nunes
That's Senators that are up there
But the senator from Missouri
Charlie Charlie
All those guys are fighting hard
Alex is trying to remember editor
Josh Holly's name
Got to feel bad for Josh Hawley
You're from Missouri
Weather at office when I live in
Hurly-burly
Hurly-burly I voted for Donovan the Hurdy Gurdy Man
Some people call him mellow yellow
Now as for the other people that Alex
Things are good in the house
Steve scalise once described himself as David Duke without the baggage
Hey come on now
That one's not great but Jim Jordans even worse
Just this week it came out that a man who was one of the victims of the Ohio State athletic doctors sexual assaults in the mid-90s
Directly reported the ACT
To Jim Jordan
Who is that the school's wrestling coach
And Jordan did nothing
43 man and filed a lawsuit claiming that they were victims of this doctor
An
Investigation that OSU did found that he abused at least
177 students
In the 20 years that he worked at the school
Consistently in the past Jordan is tried to claim that he never knew anything about the doctors abusive student
But this definitely seems to make that sound like b******* especially considering this
The second victim
To say that they directly told Jordan about
And to be clear this is a much bigger issue than just focusing on Jim Jordan
There's a whole system of
Complicity that needs to be held to account
And the plaintiffs in that case do not deserve for their day in court to be reduced to a political sideshow
Please do not
Let that busy images
My point
All that being said
When Alex has to come up with any politician season 2
All you can come up with is a dime-store David Duke
Thrift Shop Joe Paterno
Devin Nunes and a guy from Missouri whose name he doesn't know but remembers
It said some f*****-up things that he liked it
I guess Rand Paul doesn't make a cut anymore
That's not in there anyway that's not making headlines that's not he's not he's somehow a more moderate
Version of these
F****** Looney Tunes cat
It's so not that Alex is like he's going with the guy from Missouri hurdy-gurdy hurt
I'll come up with Ron Paul's kid
So I told you that there was going to be another wrinkle
The situation with Alex's coverage
Fiona Hill
And it comes up in this
Clip
Is Alex accidentally plays the wrong
But it's from the same
Today
That Rodger did the Fiona Hill
Okay
And it reminded me of something that a lot of people might not
It wouldn't
Jump out and other people's minds
Because I'm
Borderline obsessed with all this stuff it made me laugh
So f****** hot
Here's Rodger Stone
In 2017
Breaking down
John Kelly
Heather working with Steve Bannon to bring in the Deep state
Dolly saurus voice
Ciaramella
What does Bannon do the leaves in August
And by October he has a financial deal with qua
Finance Finance Breitbart
As of the Mercers who I do think our Patriots appeared to be ready to throw in Ontario
Trump a traitor
At the same time talking to a snake reporter that he brought into the hen house
And at the same time using National Security Intel
To them go basically get money off of somebody
Protector
Historical yardstick
This sounds like treason to me
Particular clip dealing with
The eclipse we have
Do you want
So on one level that clip was funny to me because once again out to staff can't Vonage
Play any of the Clip Clips that he wants
He sets up what supposed to be a slam-dunk of Rodger talking about Fiona Hill and this whistleblower and it's just Rodger from that same
So talking about Steve Bannon
But here's where this gets really
You might have heard Rodger say something about a guy named
Clock in that
And there's a reference to a man named Miles Kwok
Having nefarious intentions behind some alleged financing of Breitbart
You should know that Miles Kwok soon Rodger stone for defamation for this claim along with a few others like Rodger saying the Quan
Blockhead can be out with convicted Criminal
Answers for 100 billion dollars
On December 17th 2018 Rogers settled that case
Made a public apology and admitted that he repeated lies on Infowars
He had to pay for three advertisements
I can get statements in National newspapers
Part of the story that Alex is currently using to attack Fiona Hill is based on stuff that got Rogers sued
Invite to him having to buy ads in the New York Times
Wall Street Journal and Washington Post
Oh also I hope that re-airing the story doesn't end up getting Rogers settlement agreement void
That is hilarious
IPad
So funny
That is so goddamn
Oh God that would that would bring such a smile to my face
I have all the sudden Alex got
But man
A part of his narrative that Alex is now trying to repurpose because Fiona Hill is
Was testifying against
Trump
Impeachment verification
Part of the original context of it is stuff that got Rodger sued and he had to retract
They got to figure out a way to like
Quarantine
Thanks you know you should
Yeah well
Together exactly
No that's what I'm so now Alex Bri bring it up I think actually could put
Rodger in legal Jeopardy if anyone care
I think you I think you're right I just mean like even if it doesn't
Even if it does
Whatever Alex is repeating of Rogers stuff
Is all
Under the Umbrella of stuff you subtract
Yeah yeah
No that's cool enjoy
Just take all of the days footage
Be like a but a big red x on it with a circle around it
Jesus can't do it
If we can't put this what guys
One I don't trust you your s***
I you know it I know it we've been doing the show for a few months
Yeah hey you guys suck
Yeah so don't touch that no
Look at my eyes
Don't touch the red tapes
If you play this again Rodger might have to pay miles Kwok 100 million dollars so
Goddamnit will start
So I told you the beginning of episode about halfway through were so you'll get to like a very
Clear reason why I need
We have to do this
Here's what it is
Alex believes
That that book that the New York Times is putting
Where is
I don't know if the New York Times putting out there with the anonymous
It is about that warning about Trump
Whatever who cares
F*** off
Alex is convinced that John Bolton
Wrote the
Anonymous book
And
I almost
Gasp
When he told
The audience why he believes
We have the New York Times coming out
New York Times published
This Anonymous book the word is
It's John Bolton we know wants to testify
Against Z
President
Even though there's a separation of powers the president bylaws post able to keep from doing it he wants to go Bare The Faults with it because he's a mean
Neocon was always a neocon but lied to Trump's face
But he would try to carry out the president's agenda
The person that
We elect
Book review is a warning Anonymous author makes case
Against re-election
Dusty
I said the John Bolton is today's Benedict Arnold
Areas from his YouTube channel
Is it.
I want to talk about
Benedict Arnold
Holyshit
Does Alex expect his audience to legitimately have no memory of the side characters in his little play
How can you play clip from Steve's YouTube page after their unceremonious falling out where Alex decided he was still working for
CIA doing psyops against Infowars
By trying to convince Alex at the Las Vegas shooting
Needham happen
Legitimately what the f*** is this show
Some gases determined to be a
Deep State spy running operations against diesel
You just put them in time out for a little while
F****** insane know is going to Korea whether or not you actually did
Has he been back on the show and we will get to yook
It's not what you think
That is what happened back when they're falling out happen but Alex gives a little bit more detail
About that in a little bit
Before we get there I want to say this about Steve
Genic
He's a lunatic
But he's consistent
Steve pieczenik hates neocon zendesk
Consistently
You consistently tried to
Alex to be on the same page
With no real success
He was always there telling Alex
Not depressing neocon
John Bolton
But Alex didn't listen
He might Rogers don't talk him into being okay with those dudes
Steve pieczenik is a big old fraud in a con man but I will tip my hat to him for being pretty
He's crazy and a liar but he has some form of principles
Which is more than I can say for our
Like
How f****** humiliating is it for Alex
What to say on his show
Steven probably still working for the CIA
But you didn't
Actually work for them
Done with running psyops on his own audience
Then allow him back on the show
Do you think it's possible that Alex just doesn't even remember that he instead
Steve parted on those bad terms like you because it's not real
CIA watches right ones
That's the that's the rule right so you can
And still you know I have no idea
Alex
He knows that none of the stuff that he talks about his real so obviously the fight between him and Steve about like how he's probably still run
Psyops
Imagined it the way that I I saw the whole breakup
Was
Something behind the scenes where Steve is like
I want to say thanks for both legs in Alex's like we can't do it the heat is on me right now
Don't do that might be better was a false flag
I told you not to say that on my f****** show that might actually be correct and then they stopped talking for a while and
Then you know
He creates the whole I'm making up a deep State narrative and then
Possibly true
But Alex wants Steve back
Call Michelle
Why
Mole The Honorable person they are timeshares
Steve
So the collars really wants Steve back on he goes to a call this collar
Okay and then Alex explains
WhatsApp
It's amazing to hear Steve pieczenik on your on your program again it's been awhile
Alex
You want to come on he's refused to come on the show
He's refused to come on the show well I think everybody you know everybody should know you took a lot of sleep a lot of flak
Dino because doctor Steve was the one who originally in a brought up the idea that there could be
Some kind of ulterior motive with Sandy Hook and you know what
Call those press people that
You know that that say that they protect their other sources I mean you're actually that guy Alex you're the one
That didn't say put anything on Doctor Steve you know you
You protected doctor Steve in admired that about you man
I and
He's a coward. Put a lot of heat coming on
You can call it a federal court has been called into federal court
On other things that were said on the show so there's a lot of stuff behind the scene
Still speaking out and saying horrible things that I agree with
And so
Yeah he's been a source on many things we have a lot of mother
Sources
One day
15 minutes
Or whatever yeah
Come on I will make you holding up
But he's a good guy you should come back on the show that was wild
Bowser roller coaster ride right there stupid rollercoaster of a
I want this
This man is my friend I mean he's a coward
He's got a lot of great
Really good things to say
I mean he's a bitter angry old man sitting alone in his f******
House who won't come on my goddamn show I love them
He's been a great friend of mine for a long time
Jesus
I know from listening to the show that they they are fighting
Existed before the break
I want Alex called him in the middle of a hurricane
It started but that wasn't the end of it
Steve appeared after that
It was the last appearance
Was
That's surrounding the Las Vegas shooting
Alex
Haven't callers call in and say I think Steve's probably still working
In psyops and I was like that that's fair to say probably
I'm back on anymore so
When I hear that
I mean obviously none of the stuff that Alex talks about his real
Nor is any of the stuff
Steve pieczenik
Absolutely not
So what you
Her left with is they probably did have a fight behind the scenes
About whatever Petty nonsense Alex making him hold or or
Baby it is not letting
Play Everything is fake and then Alex on are the way he talks about it is
He's probably still working for the CIA
So you have that lie to cover up just a petty disagreement
Between two
Liars
And it's clearly now that shows that would have
Now that you put it that way then
Yeah it is 100% a petty
Bull Shed
Clearly it has something to do with one of them talking
On the phone with him having an argument I'm being like
You know what
I don't need you and Alex being
I don't need you
You know you want to kind of believe that Alex believes that Steve is working in psyops and that's like
It's more interesting but the reality is all of that is window dress
That's all just that's a narrative in it of its
Where is the reality is
Just got into a fight with this old man
That is not as much fun
Not the place where you
Shoving you have a bunch of people calling into being like where is Steve we want more Steve
You can't be like
No
Yeah
Coward bitter assholes who lives in f****** Florida A1A back on
He's got a standing invitation so anyway the reason that we have a little bit of the 12th is because Alex said open invitation
Steve come on tomorrow come back on tomorrow
Any dozen
So we just have a couple
You know what if I were better at
Maybe he does
Spoiler alert
We have a few clips from the 12th I thought were still like
Yeah yeah
So Alex gets another caller wants to talk about chemtrails
And
Not much like
I don't know how to set up this Cliff I just thought it was really
Insane
Remember you staying
And really
Even though
Everything more receptive
Frequency
Controller the cybernetic control.
Borrow
Ulf to everything
So what did I tell you in Transcendence with Johnny Depp
That is in the sky
Smart.
A whole computer system
Smartphone
In a single molecule
Will be everything and absorb us and that's the endgame playing where you can't escape
Already putting the
Binary weapon system in the Dockside
The other system
Binder that
I've been through the 678g they're already rolling out and test
Program
Actually kill you Friday
As we learned in
Why would you be working on
If you haven't got
Or five really
I hope you all just like listen to that and think 41
That's that's on the level of
They want gold was going to bring back Gladiator games to decrease the population
Johnny Depp movie I like papers
Transcendence
Starring Johnny Depp right ice I found that Johnny Depp DVD in the WikiLeaks
The f*** out of here
So anyway I was has a gas it's not Steve
Pieczenik
And it's
Also not Glenn Danzig
But he was a lead singer of the Mist
Oh okay well I got any Michael Graves
Later singer that's when they got they came back
Hyundai
I regret to inform you that this guy is very dumb he's not as smart as Danza
I don't know I've never heard Danzig on Infowars
That's true. So I can't really judge
For what I know about Danzig he's actually pretty cool f****** dudes
I don't know enough to say
I like the name Danzig
Its course sure
But this guy is
Wolf
Listening to him
Tough
So it's you prepare for 4 today and and
I went to infowars.com
And
There's the report of about Rodger Stone
Steve Bannon and and yourself and
He references and talks about miles Kwok who is this Chinese
National
Who is China's looking to
Expedite
Factor for his
For his crime
Steve Bannon Steve Bannon
Was it was basically infiltrating the
The Trump campaign for his for his own game
And then I started to think about
Chess board
This is legitimately look at Rodger Stone suit
Like this
Literally just talking about these conspiracy theories about miles Kwok
They get Rodger Stone soon hopefully Michael Graves doesn't naugahyde man
Irene
He was also talking about them in a in a manner of taking his sweet f******
In time about it as well
That is a long and
Obviously I have no issue with the stuttering at all but that was stupid
It's very dumb
The thoughts are very stupid
The exact I Was preparing for this episode and so I watched something
It got Rogers sued and he had to retract
So only reason to watch that is with that
Context of
The interesting element of it is
He got sued
Yeah like
Look for signs of awareness that he's lying because he is
That is so funny
That is so funny that you're
You're coming on the show and you're coming in pretty
It seems like he's coming in Fairly Bland
Like he's not a regular Infowars listener
Surgeon
He actually last year got kicked off a festival because he
Some social media posts supporting Alex Jones
Like really aggressively about like
When did the Nazi punks you guys not miss anymore
I don't know exactly why I didn't 100
Didn't care to look at that
His trajectory or anything but I did find a story about him getting kicked off his back
Asiana I imagined it in my head is
He's coming on the
Skyrim the business
And he just happens to listen to one episode to prepare to go on the show
And he just happened to remember the one part
That is the only part of that episode that is literally across
He's a fan and he still made that still went to the crime okay
The problems of Alex's rhetoric is that like
In Infowars World Rodger Stone didn't get sued for this
So why would the Ottomans
Read it in the f****** Wall Street Journal no they did not Infowars post an article about
Rodger Stone him to admit that he peddled lies
So anyway this guy again
Does misfit singer very stupid
Start talking about the lawyer for the alleged whistleblower
Ciaramella
And it's just kind of a thing that Alex has been going on this
This entire show
I think this is okay article
If you are everything that is on the chessboard and I went down the rabbit hole starting with
Mark
The whistleblower's lawyer
This guy that has pictures of of himself
At Disney World
Is clearly
Link to some sort of child
A hundred percent
And it's and it's still up on Twitter for everybody to see
So this guy Mark Zaid is the lawyer for The Whistleblower complaint
Against Trump
For most of the show Alex
Has been peppering in references to him being a pedophile
Based on a tweet where he says that he's has gotten
Security clearances for people
Who have c*********
Alex and now the former lead singer
Are the Misfits seem to think that he's just bragging
But they don't take into account that that's not just something he tweeted
It's a reply to another
The original tweet is from Slate
With that with it's a link to an article about how Rob Porter
Former Trump White House staff secretary
Was able to get security clearance even though he's been accused of domestic
By both of his ex-wives
In context
Clear that saves comment is about how a lot of things don't actually preclude people from receiving security clearance
It seems more like a
You think that's bad kind of comment more than any
Hangouts
So they're twisting that
So another thing that Alex points do is
Zaid made from August 29th 2019
And Alex is claiming it it's him bragging about knowing Jeffrey Epstein
The Tweet is a link to an article with the headline quote Jeffrey Epstein's little-known lawyer lands in the spotlight
Zaid commented quote
Not sure if being a little note a little-known lawyer is a good thing or bad
Though associated with Epstein probably a good thing
This is being taken to mean that Zada saying that associated with Epstein is a good thing
That's what Alex is saying
Which is a terrible reading of the tweet
Now he's saying that for this lawyer
If he's associated with Epstein being little-known is a good thing
That article in the Wall Street Journal is
Not about Zaid
But another lawyer I mean they're better
There's a better sentence
Alex Wolff
You know what maybe he's not wilfully mystery
Maybe you just is
That incapable of reading it's not a poorly constructed
If you it's very easy to follow if you're not a f******
I know
That's what I'm so
As for this guy taking pictures at Disney
Who knows
Maybe he's got a family ain't no f****** idea
I'm not going to sit here and tell you that this guy definitely
Isn't a major Cog in the globalist blood-drinking child ring
The evidence being presented here is not what I would call convince
I really expect more from the non Danzig lead singer of Vista
Yeah
Also the bigger picture problem for
Exist here without his narrative surrounding
Pedophiles in general
I generally try not to
How to cover the side of Alex's rhetoric too much because I feel even.
Construction of it is toxic
And I really really
Hey what he does
About this
Sore topic
However I need to point out one gigantic problem with
His beliefs
We know that I was believed there's a gigantic globalist blackmail ring where the evil blood-drinking globalist keep their politic
The media figures online
With threats of revealing that there pedophile
We also know that I don't believe that the globalists are trying to normalize pedophilia
Would you scream spot all the time
From lies about NAMBLA being a un organization to screaming about articles in
Salon two lies about the lgbtq community adding a p
Do his disgusting rhetoric surrounding drag queen story time
It's very very
Constant
As a thread of his rhetoric that they're trying to normalize pedophilia
Now the problem with these things are
That they both
Cannot be true at the same time
Is a globalist accuse pedophile blackmail to maintain their power
The last ever do is
Normalize
Pedophilia
The second they achieve normalization
Instantly lose literally all control they ever have had over Politics the media or the economy
To put it bluntly these two things are
Opposition
And no evil organization would ever pursue both
But you know what kind would know kind of organization would
Fictitious
I can guarantee you that that's no offense
Yeah
F*** this guy
Misfits just buy
Extension
Danzig
I'm not going to say either way
Danzig murder in
So the Misfits lead singer guy has some other stupid thoughts
And he's also connected to the James Madison project
It's talking about the whistleblowers lawyer show
Which
Also on the board of the James Madison project that's connected to John podesta
Which connected to the Center for American progress which is connected to the Southern Poverty Law Center
Connected to the ACLU funded by
George Soros
We got him
Not true but this is a fun game
We got this is a fun game so I want to play
So this lawyer right he's involved with
The James Madison project
Guy named David Kahn is also one of the board members of the James Madison project
Khan started a journal called cryptologic
Which is put out by Rutledge publishing
Which was founded by George Rutledge
Who distributed many of the writings of Benjamin Disraeli who is seen as the founder of British cancer
Because it will just let us to Boris
Johnson
So he must clearly be in on the conspiracy
I wish I could refute you but that checks out
I feel like that one got away from me a little bit so I want to try again
The Fred summer dragons
You need a better come
In between Israeli and John
Another board member is Thomas Sussman
Who is a partner at the law firm ropes & Gray
You know who else was a partner at ropes & Gray
Jean Willis
Who was also a member of the famous MIT blackjack team whose story was turned into that movie 21
Which star Jim Sturgess who was also in the movie
Cloud Atlas which store has probably had something to do with
Seems like a globalist movie Emmanuel a better
You got Envy's better than George Soros probably had something to do with cloudy like a globalist movie
Wanted to talk about Cloud at
Maybe not that movie this is stupid s*** and again I expect more from my rock band lead singer
I forgot I also regret to inform you this interview does not get better
Six Degrees of Soros game video
But
I do expect more from people who sound like
Eddie Bravo
Got to stop it
So this is pretty funny because Alex
He's like I got the lead singer here guy from The Misfits
Come back from break with a with a sitter
Hollywood Babylon and now Hollywood
Danzig
Yeah but it's it's a reminder that he's not dance
He did not help
There's no way in that arrows album
Probably
So anyway
Geico
Hates Hillary Clinton
Enza
They need to discredit the Liberty Movement remember what what Hillary Clinton said
Remember what she called us
Irredeemable the Portables
When you look up be redeemable the definition of irredeemable is is is not a distinct directions
And I actually and I I looked it up if you want no value can't fix deserving Strong-Tie
Condemnation shockingly bad in quality we were talking about Auschwitz were talking about camps before
That was that was when going to watch what's going to happen
When somebody like Hillary Clinton
And her minions
Get
Control
When they when they when they seed control back
And push what what they are trying to do
It really is camps
It's coming to get us
Has the word irredeemable I guess
Record that
So congratulations we made a lap and this guy still back on that so
I'm thrilled for him cuz he didn't get the earlier
Shows
I swear Alex
Onboard
Well for like people you're coming
We're not white people
Gotcha gotcha
We good it is good
Yes but only if he must do that to White
Conservative Ghana
It's good
4 people who were born a couple of miles away from the border
Be okay with a fever
Human rights are arbitrary
Veterinary
So this guy
Infinitely
He's read a lot about World War II
Oh no he's not allowed to which is a good start to a sentence
But where it goes this guy should not be allowed to read about WWII
I read a lot about about World War I
The death camps in Denver
One of the things that I find when you when you when you read about that history when you read about the p
People that were involved in that
It's always the same thing that people in these communities in the Jewish communities at work that were sort of falling removed from the
Concern next thing you know they were on a train
Headed to a death camp because George Soros
Was 14 he was a bloodhound he was able to find block
But he brought them out
Time in his life
The happiest time in Essex
I have
Like
Is it
Perhaps the most open-and-shut case for defamation
For Alex
Related to his Soros
Yep the fact that he is
Now escalated this
Strong like his original rhetoric which is just as vague ideas about he's a Nazi collaborator now he's
Turned it into very consist
Only saying that he would actually use a bloodhound and he had to go around and hunt out Jews and report them
The fact that he says this on his own show
And would go on Joe Rogan show and say
When you get to push back when broken
That's not true that's not what this interview that he did says
But Alex says on Rogan show
It's an open question
That is proof
Malice that is proof of actual Lounge
So if George Soros wanted to destroy Alex
He has him anytime he wants it
Please do it
I think that this is one of the
Examples of the benevolence of Alexander
Yeah
The world but
Towards Alex
He is living on borrowed
Time
1025 f****** years you know before you went on Rogan should I think will be very difficult
Go to demonstrate
He doesn't
Or that he knows that what he saying is
Ride like the fact
But you kind of have to prove
That someone knows what they're saying isn't
Right with public figures with George Soros definitely would be
Do not forget you have to reach that state
Standard
Matt
George Soros doesn't decide to do that Alex
You are you are f*** I think I think Barnes
2 Chainz I'm going to own Infowars
Steph so that's the end of the 11th step cuz it
It's mostly I'm just talking to
Misfits guy Morin
He is very dumb
So we have a little bit here from the 12th cuz I was listen
Cuz I wanted to see if Steve was going to come on
Cuz that is very relevant
Yeah there's no way we could have
Listen to this episode
So today and then been like well we'll try and see
What mean we're recording is on the 12th so it's very difficult for me to listen
To All of Me
And then turn around and have an episode
But I would have done it
Finally have to even
But most of it I probably would have just
Ignore cuz it's all just gone for yours
Paranoia
Alex
Some things are like
Map
I got to cut a clip of a
Because Alex
Are you saying that there's
Space wars going on
People just can't handle it
I was just shaking
Tell you that
This level of conflict is only the surface
Conflict is a Olaf
We even know
A lot more serious
What you say the universe is a variable
In place and there are some big Wars going on with John
Weed
Schrock know that's level because
Understand
That doesn't seem that different from Project Camelot s*** to me
That sounds like he's saying that there's space wars
Going on
I
I think God leads us in the space wars literally
Saying that there are Wars going on
In space
They are out there are space wars
He's not doing any he's
He said God me the
But if this isn't
This isn't him
Talk about
Like Heaven and Hell Wars
This is him being like
We need to get off this rock
The planet to join Wars
In space
The universe
So I'm going
Going to go with he believes
That his fictitious
Enemies
Know that he is
Pierce the veil of human consciousness
And is capable of let's say viewing
Remote
Wars happening around
The universe
And that they are on the side that is bad in the space wars
Much like the reptilians
Smells that we have Raptor allies in space
And God is involved
It's not that different.
And whatever
I'm sure has a telescope
I believe that too
So just after that
After he's talking a little bit about space wars
He talks to a caller
And this guy
This guy's f***** up
What else you think we should do I mean
Because it's a spiritual fight
It is a spiritual battle and end the reason why is because the Christian people
Permitted a lot of things to have
By controlling the language they
You think
Controlling your
Control your actions
Precedes action
Gullible
And then whatever you allowed to happen
It was a time in history of it when Christians control this this Arena so power
The Cockroaches like this
People have to live
In the shadows and do their business in the shadows and under the cover
Darkness now it is in plain sight
It isn't daylight
And there is not enough good Chris
Is that our calling and exactly what they are
Richard demon
And they need to be hunted
Pound
And a politically assassinated is what they need to be
Absolutely brother
Call Rochelle soon
Awesome thank you
So this caller is expressing political assassinations are needed for our Rivals
And they've been allowed to run around because
Is Christian
Aren't in control
Strongly enough anymore and I was just
Right on this diatribe
I want him on 24
I mean I also think that there's probably a mean there's really no
Difference but there is
A linguistic difference
Between these people need to be assassinated
Yeah
There's a contextual
That I think makes what this guy saying
I think he's trying to play Alex
Little birthday
But what are you saying
Credibly scare
These people are so f***** up
Cannot engage
Gauge with anybody
There was a time
Just like
F*** you give me
Give me specifics of go f*** you
So Alex does have a guest on the 12th and it was disappointing
Because it wasn't C4 Janik
But it was
The Misfits
Again
No is in Austin for a little bit
But Alex
Another guess
And it's Stewart Roads of the oath
Who is going to be the next
Cigarettes
Goodnight
So
In his appearance
Stewart is
Really expressing some ideas that are going to lead towards
Violence
Quite honestly
Express
Hear that Trump was the last
Peaceful option
No through the firewall the way through over the last was last you do last effort to try to do this peacefully
Is a firewall
But they can't let that play out here to remove him from whatever means necessary
24th Amendment he saw that were psychiatrists now
Ask him to testify in front of the front of the house
Under the gold Waterworld
Friday 13th
Warfare
You don't know that we've done all we can replicate it in some ways been having any restraint what don't you do this
Any physical response to look not your property
Stuart said there at the end
And we've done everything we can so we can not feel bad about having no restraint with our violin
Yep that but that's
Been there Point all along
This is a note this is what they were saying in 2013 to
Like they've always been right on
Cusp of doing so
Violence app
I don't I don't know if that makes me think that it's
Less likely that the
These people will do anything
Or more like
Eventually the dams got a break like that you know
Well I mean it's not like people who would listen
Link to this didn't
End up going out and doing things right
I don't know what I think
But I know that
This weird thing is
I read the thing that I'm
Getting so much cuz it
Ties back into
So many of these guys have
Well if we're going to do it we better do it while Trump's in
That's what I'm saying
Like that idea is that there
There's not going to be a civil war
If there's going to be a civil anything is going to be a civil f***
Manslaughter
And
The difference is going to be if Trump is in the white house and we start that Slaughter then maybe Trump will let us get away with it
And give us our f***
Can cover for it
Or if Trump is not in office
Then we're going to be in Insurgent
We're the ones who are going to get fuc
Yeah so then it'll be good people on both sides
Yeah yeah
So
At the end of that last clip
Stewart saying f*****-up thing
About like hey we can hope we're free to commit violence
We've done everything we can
And Alex brings up
They're going to pull false
Flags to make
Our violence
Look for something
Roy
And when he gets back from break
Alex says something that I find like
Deeply disturbing
Well obviously conservative would never going to Walmart and shoot
Innocent
White black Hispanic people
Could Adam Lanza
Patriots not saying do this wood would wood would go after globalist and Peep
It's not us
This is being staged
What Alex is doing here is trying to pull off some kind of bizarre no true Scotsman fallacy
The argue that any instance of violence not perfect
Score boost can't possibly be Patriots in
Conservative and therefore must be aunt
Fascist false flag into paper
The wave is basic fallacy works is to serve as a protection of a group
Purity
Alex you find a story about let's say right-wing individual killing a bunch of innocent civilians
It is responsible no true conservative would do something
So he would conclude that this person wasn't
Really are conserved
That's the basic version where the function is
To maintain the image of what a conservative is in his mind
Despite evidence that the group includes people who fall short of the definition
People do this sort of thing all the time
And on some level it's part of human instinct
To protect our own identities as being part of a group
It's hard to reconcile that you might be a member of a group that also includes people who you find morally repulsive
But that's sometimes the case
This line this line of fallacious thinking
That's how a lot of people ignore that internal conflict
But what Alex is doing is taking
Bad thinking
He's engaging it one step further than the
He's determined that because no true conservative her Patriot would kill civilians
Then there's someone who does isn't to conserve
That's already a complete disaster
Herbalogic respected but then
He insists that because this person is not a conservative they must be an anti-fascist pretending to be a conservative
Did demonize The Patriot
It's really hard for me to put this any other way than to say that this is not adult mental process
This is bad
This is really really bad thinking
Do you know what the other part of that
Okay
So prove
It's proven to you that it was a conservative you have to
To agree with it
What do you know who killed a globe
Wow
Now here's the issue
So
Did the simple reality is that there are absolutely conservatives and right-wing or to plan
And Carry Out attacks on civilians
These are real events with real victim
Thomson real loved ones
Who's paying Alex
Don't give a fuk up
About because it threatens the purity of his own self
The in his desperation to glorify his political side
He behaves in Calais ways
Sableye the fact that his side is nowhere near as pure as he likes
Super 10
But
Since you saying that any real conservative would Target globalist
Then I guess he's taking ownership of Cesar sayoc
B Baka bomber who sent bombs to the clintons and George Soros
Among other globulus Target
If he sang that accent
Can civilians or just antifascista Volkswagen the Patriots and any real conservative Patriot
Would Target the globalist
The truly that one was real
Whoops
Nope turns out Alex said that was a false flag to
Alex is worldview and narratives are childish
Instructions is propped up in order to make sure that he never has
Have to feel the impact of the rhetoric that he puts into the world
I used too much of a coward to even State internally consistent
Play by the rules that he's made up for himself
If it's somebody who doesn't fit his definition of what a patriot would do with the
Anti-fascist Volkswagen Patriots
Stand hey it's the Globus false flagging themselves in order to get pity
F*** you man
Your Heroes are Terror
Yeah just admit
So in order to reinforce his idea that these shootings are just anti-fascists who are coming out there and
False flag
Sure he brings up the Dayton shooting
And I find
His take on it's really boring and we parted like
They tried to cover up online
Stewart
Castellan
Texas attack that he was antifa leftist and that was confirmed
Pull up on his side
Who put that up
Who protected him
The question
That's I'm sorry I said dating I'm at the El Paso shooting
But
Diaz that response
I find
To be really
He doesn't want to be involved in this
He's just there to talk about gun paranoia
Saying that it's okay for them to
Boot wantonly murder their political enemies
I think he has a line though and as we saw in 2013
When Alex is trying to save those people in the pictures that you found on 4chan at the Boston Marathon
We're secretly seagulls
Stewart said I don't I can't say that based on
Just whatever they're wearing
I'm not going
I'm not going to go along with this
I feel very similar thing here he has a line of like
Whatever you're doing
Alex wants him to get involved
So that's about the end of anything with real Subs
On this episode
But I have a couple last
Clips and one of them is Alex get the caller
Who asked
About something very specific
And I think that this clip is only important
As a demonstration of
How full of s***
Have you ever heard of Carl Miller it was a Vietnam vet teaches about Constitution
He has some videos in anyway one of them
Mauriotto
Anybody charge
Any right that you have the Second Amendment any of them
Anybody can file a writ of Cold War against that judge and anybody connected with them
Trying to do that if you heard of this thing
So look
This is Sovereign citizen
But what's interesting is this guy asks have you heard of this Carl Miller guy you're going to talk about the concert again
I have no idea what you're talking about
That's Alex's music reaction
Denny's anytime anybody asking do you know about this isn't you but I do
I'm an expert on everything
That's a really good demonstration of his lying Direct
And then realizing
My name is last one Alex
He ends up playing a special report about how everybody is
The Otherworld
Olga's enemies are all demons
And I just love the way it starts it so just to end this on a softer lighter note then maybe Stewart Roads just
Satisfying
Political violence or
I want about the scholars calling for political assassination
Or
Alex
Deciding Steve Janik is totally cool
Yours just something
Straight up.
There is a shame
No one knows who first coined
It goes like this
But convincing the world
Okay okay alright
18 f****** with me
Has to be f****** with
I'm going to guarantee that Alex didn't look into this in anyway and he's just being a blowhard
I also guarantee that he's just quoting The Usual Suspects
And has no idea what that movie is reference
Generally people tribute this precise formulation of the expression to Charles baudelaire
The line traces back to a short story published
Before but the vague idea expressed in the quote goes back
A little farther than that
An 1836 a Quaker preacher named John Wilkinson Road quote what are the artifices of Satan
Is to induce man to believe he doesn't
Alex is definitely referencing The Usual Suspects
Which was referencing baudelaire
But from there
Line is kind of broken
Baudelaire was probably not referencing relatively obscure Quaker authors
It was probably just writing it with a creative poetic flourish
Of his own
Whatever the case is here that expression
Does not go back thousands of years that's completely
Unreal
There's a saying no one knows who coined it goes back on
Baby f****** with me
Yeah that is blood
That's the
Best
And only joke
He is ever so
I think there has to be a joke
There's a thin line between f****** with you and being a blowout
Yeah that line is something
I'm not sure where ever be able to really
Not with him
Clearly Define
God is that is that is
The most perfectly exit
Get a joke
Whoever wrote that
He maybe he didn't write it maybe somebody is f****** with him I could be
Oh man cuz that's so good
So are we going to the end of this then you know I think
I had to do this episode because there was
Steve pieczenik
Amazon
Scary s*** some really dumb
Stuff and hopefully
If I can do anything to bring to light
The fact that Alex is repurposing stuff they got Rodger
Just don't sued
I'm very happy to do that because I hope it's okay
Dorothy's to demonstrate that a lot of this whole new narrative about
Fiona Hill and this whistleblower a defamation against George Soros
That also goes in there
But this whole new narrative it relies on the same information that did get Rodger
I think that's a really interesting
Of this puzzle that
I don't know if anybody but us realized
So
Fun to be able to talk about that I know Alex
I missed a doona Wacky Wednesday
No I had some ideas
Maybe we'll get a next week
We we got we got
Johnny Depp
Just talked about the Mandalorian for
Alex's graduated to Wacky Wednesday
You might as well talk about the Mandalorian but strangely
About
Steve Miller's email hey now hey now
So we'll be back on Friday with a new episode
We do have a website
It's knowledge fight.
Yes
We have
We have Twitter's at knowledge
Dumbass
Ross on Facebook
We are on Facebook and we are also
Download the podcast
ITunes and other staff
Sure they're just listen to other podcasts
And then tell him to listen
Brother episode next time but until then I know I'm Leo I'm dzx Clark I am
Outrageous licorice
Holding