Airjordan.com
I have great respect for knowledge like I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
I need money
Knowledge fight
Everybody likes it around
Novelty Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex
Jones
We are
Jordan low top Jordan
Do you have any
Vendor like
Meet
Hot dog
You know like you by shift
But is there anything
Here
Anything that stayed with you
No
Traveled with no
My house burned down like 5 years ago instead of like I lost pretty much everything I own but events.
Me 5 years ago
You don't do this a lot of things
You don't keep a lot of things
That was even true before the fire
Books
Library
And I guess maybe some of those are like paperbacks I would buy
I'm not
Super interested in
Shopping number one if I'm walking around at somebody selling something I'm not
I'm not usually even considering it
What have you bought everything
Actually not outside of a
I think it was a street vendor when I was in
Like
I've mentioned the past that I like
In high school I wore shein
An extension of that was shiny robes
Woodside erodes marimba
They weren't really all that in play but I like that like
Robe
My some of my family lives
Lives in
Like around the
Yeah it's a one time we went to visit
And my mom and I think
I don't know why
And I got to Shawnee Road
That might have been
Street vendor perch
Yeah shiny like a reflect
Tavor like
Sequin sequin
Like light
A dragon
Games on it and stuff
Okay alright
Alright now that Cena that's what I wanted to get to the bottom I didn't want one of those soft
Robes
Like a bathrobe wanting something really gaudy
Over the top
That might have been but I don't know alright
That was probably when I was
Yeah yeah
Teen going on 12th century
Courtesan I called like that
I don't know much about either know I got to teach you
So Jordan today where did the present
Still I was hoping
To maybe do something different
But I was
Called into action
Okay alright
November 13th
And Ayana
Honestly think I would say this
Before we do anything
I think that this episode is a
Window in
A very perfect opportunity to
A lot of different elements of why Alex Jones is show is
Disaster
Any super terrible
Just perfect
The encapsulation
Of many different Elam
Okay I hesitate to call this a Rosetta Stone
Kohl's
All these
But over the course of this episode I am going
Highlighting
Particular
Behavior
Then Alex engages in
Constantly
I think they're all on amazingly public display
Alex commits
Every egregious error that he
He commits usually one or two at a time
Time-in other
Subway I don't want to put too fine a point on it because I
I don't think
Is any kind of a unique Apple
I just think that
It's some of the
Illustration
These Trends have behaviors
Really
Flagrant
They provide a glimpse in
Episode is a good
Encapsulation of why
Looking at Alex
The pizza state
So anyway before we get
Get to that Lexie
This sort of thing
Possible so first of all Jeffrey thank you so much right now policy walk
Tycoon
Thank you so much you are now a policy wonk
No longer
Come on
Ewok
Dennis the Menace the childhood prankster grew up chicken policy walk little known fact
Next
Three names
Okay
Loucreta and Zack
Thank you so much you are all now collectively a policy wonk
Next route
Next-gen
Because I'm hot you and I hope all is well
Is that short for Maximilian
I don't think people do this
Florida soul maximillia
That it might who knows
Could be good be a youth could be 80 years old
Strictly an armor for role-playing game
Pretend you know what age the walks are
OK Google
CVS 18th
Finally likes you donated
I appreciate that very much so Dougie breakshit thank you so much you are now it's
I'm a policy wonk
Money off that heroin
Why you pimp so good
Is freakishly large
Breakshit
All I can think of now is a hole dug
Universe like Doug
Iggy fresh
Breakshit Doug
Yeah you're a dougie something up there please feel
Able to do not a dougie something are you getting out of work so if you like we're going to website knowledge make that cam click the button that says Sports joke
So Jordan we begin today a little bit differently than normal that's early cuz I often don't play Alex's intro
Stride Rite but in this case
The way he opens the show is
Is actually different
I've heard in the pack
Leaving up frontal assault on the lies of the New World Order it's Alex Jones
So just right off the bat on the day that the public hearings for the impeachment inquiry
Our beginning
That's a real bad Vibe for Alex start officer playing a voice saying that we are gathered here to overthrow the US government
That seems like a statement of purpose
More than anything else
Do they
He doesn't normally
I have not heard of that drop being thrown in might be something
But I don't I don't remember it being a super regular thing
Yeah that would be funny but if Alex Jones
That's it that's like a
He's literally talking to
To the oath keeper
Well I suppose you can make the argument that he's saying that this is the statement of purpose of his enemies
He's fighting against that overthrow the government I guess you could
That's convoluted for him
Either way it's
Super interesting where that audio come
This is one of the most
Notable early fake voice recording
Spooked sound like someone else
In this case it was designed to sound like
Carl Steiner
The former commander-in-chief of the US Special Operations
A scientist named George Apopka
You took
A 10-minute sample of Steiner's voice
And created fake audio of him talking
About overthrowing the US government
That fake audio was so convincing that Steiner himself
I asked for a copy of it
No
There's
There's an interesting siematic in
Alex is trying to evoke fears of government overthrow in his audience whether it's
The globalist overthrowing the government and his audience
You know
To fight back again
Or if
What whatever it is there's something he's doing with
If you was over throwing
Audio that he's chosen to heighten that mood
Is specifically something that's fake
It's the product of misinformation
Whether or not it was benign and recreational in its
Construction it still
A direct
Fabrication
So he chose
What are the progenitors of Addie
Deepfake video
From the mid-to-late 90s
It's either that's very notable pesos
Know that that's fake
Yeah yeah
It's like a whole f****** metaphor for everything that he does
He said it's purporting to be real information
Absolutely. Who knows if it's because of the context of it being thrown in with this
Intro
Presented as if it is real there is obviously and I hope that somebody
People will hear that enjoy
Just it'll trigger
Where overthrowing the US government
I meant some people might know what it is
Who knows I don't know what the point of it is but it's fascinating to
To me that even Alex's
Intro choices are lies
Everything is
It must be somewhere
It's an antonym
Interesting things that I am not entirely sure what the
Performance
Poetry is yeah there's some
There's something
Dematic
A wrinkle that I'm having
Difficulty
Man I feel like there's some sort of foia request that we can have that will Revere Revere Electric
20 years of something Bowl on
Easter eggs of how
Full of s*** Alec
I don't know if the variable
Turn off oil can help with that but
Maybe these lawsuits
So the impeachment inquiry has begun in the house
And Alex of courses just dismissed
Very popular
For the right way
I wanted to check in on his show because of that
Cuz I figured that that's of monumentous thing
In the news
And Alex would have a take on it
His take
Is not all that interest
But
Something else
What 355 days out from this incredibly important
Election
And now they got the official impeachment proceedings going on
In the House of Representatives as we speak
Authority highlights of Chef
Congressman Nunez the ranking Republican member that is all going to be coming up
Today
Dr. Steve pieczenik
No Delta Force CIA overthrow governments
Really smart guy best-selling author
Call Ryder
Tom Clancy
He is going to be
Back on the broadcast that talk about the coup
No behind it and what he expects to come to help though
I worked out about that
Steve Outback nope
No refuse
I love it I cannot know
Steve is back about
Holyshit what they talked about
I would say
Headliner
Steve is back
Back is in all capital letters
Couple of videos from his
YouTube channel apps
Very concerned
Learned about his
Like I thought he
Deteriorating
He seems unwell. I'm not saying anything like
Conspiratorial like
Secretly got XYZ going on
Be pretty old his speech patterns are completely different than they are on Infowars
And I realize like now it's just cuz he's talking alone
He's back on the show and he sounds almost exactly like you always ask
He's eager for the yelling at Alex about stuff
Into webcam there's no photo for it I know it it doesn't have the same electricity
Yeah so I'm kind of
Happy on that level cuz it'll even if
I hate them
I think you sucks take no pleasure in the idea of like
I'm falling apart so it's nice to
To know that you still love
Pretty sharp my okay what you saying is people are still under estimating
Federer after all these
At the end of the day
The top five
He and Ant-Man
Steve
He's like
I can't I can't even like when he came on the show in 2013 and then
Episode we heard
Any declared himself in an open state of freezer
Yes I was pretty
Wild
Keys in that
Okay
Swinging okay so we got that to look for
But that doesn't happen for a while because Alex has got a
I Cover the Waterfront
Got to get
The news
CMP
Stuff is
And it is what it is it's all bulshit show trial
But there was a bigger story but
Alex knows what it is
What the big enchilada
Exactly as we said she would do it
Then we got to dig up potatoes from a year ago 6 months ago
A week ago
I I hit it
Perfectly hole-in-one I'm at just got to be honest with you
I just got inside the enemy Chad you can see Hollywood script
Hillary loses
She launches all the fake Russia investigation she wants to
Back out of those investigations he's running
She said she's not going to run while she collects money while she travels around the country
While he makes more appearances all this
Canada combined
All she still runs the DNC and runs those conference calls
Then ride is the impeachment starts of trump
Keisha the people are begging me
They're drafting Meowth or responsibility Trump so dangerous I don't want to do it but
Okay I am well she said that
She said that she said she's running
No she did not she said she's running
She said she's not running
Yeah she left it open with the never-say-never self
Yeah and that there was something that you said when she was being interviewed on the BBC as part of her book tour
Who's going to run again and she replied I will certainly tell you I'm under enormous pressure from many many many people to think of
But as of this moment sitting here in the studio talking
Sing to you that is absolutely not my plan
Also in March she said quote
I'm not running
Who knows no baby that's secretly her sexy
She's running
I've been pretty consistent in my position that Hillary is not run
But everyone f****** loves talkin about her running
People like Alex love talking about it because it Riles up their base
Something created the perfect
Easy villain and Hillary
People out on the last love talking about it because the idea that Hillary would run again proves everything they say about the Dems being
You stupid self.
Defeating party
A very small number of die-hard Hillary folks still hanging on love talking about it because
They think that Hillary should run
Everyone gets something fun out of entertaining the idea of Hillary running
But I just don't think there's much
Reality gear
I don't
Forget Hillary herself gets
Something
Out of being exactly
Yeah I don't think
Alex could prove all the other cities
Hillary Gary either I have not had that bouquet
Also
Why is it Alex completely freaking out about Bloomberg running
Alex f****** hate
Bloomberg
He's one of the globalist to attend to those meetings with Bill Gates
Ted Turner and Oprah
Why is he spending his time obsessing with a possibility that Hillary is going to run while ignoring the reality that Bloomberg
He's running
The Bloomberg doesn't really move the needle with the audience
Making them scared of the Clint
Move product
So
He does
If Bloomberg
Like
Do all of these me
Media organization
Clara Brown
President
Everybody on the
Just don't
Stop a lot of people don't care as it's
Some people doing it's good to pay attention
Did all candidates
Everybody
Oh yeah weather for Alex
Yeah you know you're right
Bloomberg no but it's right up there with like
Okay
He has not said a damn word about Bolivia about the release of his buddies
Stephen Miller's email Bloomberg running
Anti-heroes
F****** bone side down
Hillary
Secretly running
Hillary she's a has-been I know she's bi
Democrat nominee
Unless we expose her and get out of head of it and put heat on her
She wants me to self candidate with none of her corrupt past brought up
And once they get the impeachment they're going to say that's the conviction
That's just the indictment the house
And then she's going to run out
Before the end of the year
Time table
She is saying she's going to retire she beat him in 2016 or she is
I feel a sense of responsibility partly
Because my name was on the more votes but ended up losing
Also I think is
Really undermining our democracy in
Very fundamental ways
I want to retire him I want to see him retired
When you kill a horse basically
Okay Alex conveniently and Zack clip
Just the right spot
Yeah after she says she wants to retire Trump Hillary explains that means she'll be helping the Democrats I'd come up with the best possible
Plan the interviewer Emma Barnett
Then she's going to run again and Hillary says quote
No
Alex wants her to run so f****** bad
Think of how
Easy
Everybody's job would be if Hillary and
Trump rant again
We can just read everybody would post this thing called a dystopian
No baby horrible
I like the idea of Hillary being the Stealth cam
It's so she doesn't get any
Criticisms so nobody does any
Has any background
Go fuc yourself
I thought Rodger stone is telling you that was Michelle Obama what's going on here
Who's the self Canada
Whatever you need that day
So this is
Things happening for various
Some people are
One perspective on it other p
People have a different one
Alex is prospective
Seems to be that this is all Cuban odds Falls me
So that works is an interesting Tale
I like it a lot of people
What Alex
Reese's cake
Qanon
To me I can't really answer that question
It's buried over time
A lot of the underlying
BECU
Evacuation order things that Alex
And has
Prior to qanon
Right Alex has been
Okay with it at some point
Bitter about it at others
Trying to create his own version of it
At other times
But now in 2019
Hey November
You seemed a bit salty
They may have lost the House of Representatives
The impeachment hearings that show many said would never come
Are now officially going on
10 minutes ago finished up
Is opening statements very powerful that I'm going
Play
In its entirety this segment
And the next
He's the ranking Republican member on the house intelligence committee was the leader of it but
Thought we were Invincible in the 2018 midterms and
You told us we didn't need to even worry about it
Course we did
By the way we're not going to just have somebody that's
What's shadoweave today
Steve pieczenik of did co-found Delta Force with General
Schumacher and Boykin
So yeah I mean qanon gave a false sense of security to everybody trusts the plan
Feel invigorated to go and
Keep the house
For the Republicans and now we got in a
Angry at soggy bulshit here on the show no he's got the real deal
He's got Steve pieczenik
F******
Craziest wingding liar
This side of the Mississippi
Okay I love that alright
So great
Crazy you have no idea how crazy
Cute wasn't real
Neither Steve's backstory
This is wild so Alex has a radio show
A couple times
I will take you on
That's what we know about
The radio show
The TV show
But it turns out his secret plan behind the scenes
Maybe self candidate
Not sure what his secret plans are
He doesn't need your money to continue these secret plan
In talking about how we need
Snooze
That's your recall
The previous special
Been running was the Everything Must Go sale
That went way too long longer than he intended
Sale just before the Everything Must Go sale
Was the Black Friday comes early
Special
His new special is the Black Friday it's very uninspiring
We got a lot of stuff going on in the background and I've got
Plans and operations
That will keep this message on are no matter
How that railroad us
But it takes two things it takes Word of Mouth
And it takes money
And it takes a lot of both
Total War
People talk about all they're going to get their guns while shooting or someday
If you don't take action now you'll never take action of shooting war and we won
To avert
A shooting
Diamond easy to find this operation
Products you and your family need and I need
The majority of Lester's adult by-products in foursquare.com
To commit to the fight
And by their war bonds
And get things you
Need.
Infowarsstore.com
We already had Black Friday comes early a
3 months ago
Salata products on product came back in
We're launching Black Friday right now
Early as
As well got a lot of those legs for you
Free shipping
Double Patriot Point
But there are a lot of things
Sold out
We're going to sell out a list of them
I forgot to pull out
You said that as a joke
You said it's Black Friday sales then as a joke
With that actually what he's doing
Another early by Friday sale
That's what I would say
I appreciate
Preciate the willingness to
A lot of people on the right
You tried to bring Hillary back cuz I can reduce reuse recycle
The Captain Planet planet of b*******
I like it I think that's great
Y'all need to
Conserve bloviating die-hard
Again or some
What is he going to sell on Black Friday
That's my queen
That's a great question Cyber Monday comes early
That's real Bass
To me what this indicates is
Probably his staff in that area of the business is also finding out
Whatever marketing people you may have been employing before are now an internal right
You also your video editor
So I see these is all kind of like little
It's circumstantial evidence certainly
There are things you would expect
Jeffy
Crumbling as business
So I think that might be the
Yeah Jon Hamm
Is it working
Conformity
But you know what Hillary is run
She is on
Off the 10 TV and radio programmes a day
Armoire
Any speeches 7 days a week
He's running
He's collecting money
In our foundation
And you see that whole crew up there by dinar leeteuk
Bernie
Is gibbering
Why
They're all a big joke
Tulsi gabbard
Anywhere near
Why is she not a joke primaries are going to steal
Just like I did from Sanders
4 years ago
Alex I don't understand
You know he loves Tulsi
And whatever
Still kind of in a weird cult why is she in the dark
You can start that too much
In that area but it does seem to be very
Consistent thing among people I don't trust
Weird weird
Beyond that I think that Alex recognizes
He's in for a f****** world of hurt
Is Bernie is a candidate
Because he made such a big deal out of Bernie Havoc Beats
Screwed over by Hillary in the primary last election
Bernie before
Alex realized he was a socialist or whatever
Spent a lot of time talking about he was one of the only
Brave people in the Senate because he stood with Ron Paul in terms of
Alexander Realty
Any audience member of his with any kind of memory or actual concern about the issues that Alex
Rants about is going to be like
What about Bernie isn't the FED one of your big
Trademark issues with you on that why you care about this you know cultural
Nonsense let's say B presented
It's insane yeah he's going to have a really tough time with that
That's all I think he's
Really
Hoping that that isn't
The primary really love it if if if Bernie lose
It doesn't even matter they can
Hillary probably torpedoed in there too they can
Play that whole thing
Exactly
They wouldn't give Bernie a shot
So unreasonable Saudi heard Alex
Bring up a story about British Hospital
I am there making a decision that if you racially or
In a sexist way abused members of
I'll give you a warning
If you say
Continue
The end it's safe to do so they will withdraw tree
Treatment right
The two Edwards in your outro
Basically
Ya Ain't So Alex
Re brings up the story
But
Pay close attention to how he present
Because this is very telling
Last week
That article
I want to know about it
The NHS shed
If you're alright winner and that's anything they choose. Bad
You're not going to get Healthcare
We're going to kill you
Whoops
You really
You shouldn't say that
That's supposed to be the quiet fire
Right if I recall
Out-of-the-loop Bristol
In the UK
That's
It's just it's not even
The entire area it's just it's Bristol I think it's a system
Localize
Yeah that story is entirely about them saying
Their consequences were behaving and racist insects
Safeway store there say they hate the right-wing now huh it's about Behavior
Alex is reporting it is as if it's about denying care to right-wingers which is not a behavior it's a group identifier
You can kind of tell from this sort of thing the Alex believes that being a part of the group right-winger
It's some kind of connection with the behavior being racist or sexist
This is one of the more damning
Instances of Alex making an argument defending racist insects
Disabuse being cruel to people
Book framing it is if he's just standing up for right-wingers
Alex is a coward
He wants people of ethnic minorities and women to shut up and deal with whatever comes their way but he doesn't
We can make his place in the market work if he's an open race
That fun game he plays we complained about the media attack
Come all the time by calling him a racist unfairly
Doesn't work out quite as well if he's honest about what he believed
Pizza what he
So
So you see that sleight of hand
This is about denying care to right-winger right
No it's not racist
You are acting
That what
Wild
That he's
Still bothering
I mean
There's nothing bad going to happen
Stephen Miller and
Open Waze
He's been white supremacist
Forever but now he's just opened about it and he's free
I think that there is a acclimation
Listen. I think that Alex will be open
Wants
You realizes
If you survive
On-air long enough
To get
To the point where he realizes like
I don't think I have any other options
What once the once once other avenues
Of
Possible money
Aren't there
That's because that's what he is
Cute figure
It's not like Steve Miller
Get another job
Oh wait he Wilfred
Uni
Sure
Absolutely
So this
Kind of continued
Alex
Covering another culture
Issue and that has to do with the launch of Disney Plus
So here's Alex talk about this
Warnings being
Disney movies
Likely
Because of
Cultural
Just leaving
And with the
Cats
Saying where we finding maybe there is milk nearby
Samuel C. Shane swimming around them around
Maybe they'll be had for you
And tail for me
Something wholesome and fun and good
So Alex is really missing the mark
Is it being like outdated cultural norms are that there is a man and a woman and a base
So with the release of Disney plus the company realize that there were a few issues of some of the movies they put out over the years
Considering their first release
Lease was put out in
You got to understand that so
Some cultural things
1937 was 5 years before our government Force Japanese-Americans into
The camps during World War II
Do 10 years before Jackie Robinson broke the color barrier in Major League Baseball
It was 18 years before Emmett Till was murdered
18 years before the Montgomery Bus by
It's very hard to put into words how different the world we live in today from when Disney started putting out movie
A lot of those movies are beloved classic
But that doesn't change the fact that a lot of them are products of their time
In order to strike a balance
Instead of editing the movies
Offensive scene
Out
Just decided to answer morning so
Two people knew what they were getting into
Princeton
Dumbo features Acro character named
Jim Crow
Probably not a good look that one's a little bit on the nose
In Peter Pan they sing a song called what made the Red Man red I don't understand what the problem is there is Duty
We just thought people deserve a heads up on stuff like that as well as warnings about a ton of characters smoking
The movie
They were made back at a time when people talk cigarettes were healthy a Bugs Bunny used to smoke all the time
I love that shitt totally
The warning on the lady in the Tramp is because there were two Siamese cats
They're basically just racist Asian stereotypes
I wouldn't expect the guy Alex who's been putting out his own racist Asian stereotypes videos featuring fentanyl the Tiger
Dragon
To understand why a company might do this sort of thing as an embarrassing and regrettable thing of
People only
Wholesome entertainment like Alex's racist commercials I don't understand
I did not bring this up
But I'm going
Gaston Alex
Is furious that song of
Isn't done
It's not on there at all man
You can find it
On YouTube though
I'm glad they did that but also we should update a lot of movies
Like the movie American Pie should have a warning on there that it's like
There was that he was attempting to broadcast
The movies from like
A few years ago
That is
Twenty-something years ago
That was a 2000
I'm not minimizing
So you know the right right
Yeah
So Alex pretends here that this next clip better the problem with the lady in the
Is that there's a heterosexual
Couple
Okay presented
This is so stupid
Where job so right
Nice
We just played
The trailer
For Lady and the Tramp
Three released
The classic film
You're not allowed to do that
That is hateful
That is homophobic
That is bad
Again
Realtors you're really blessed
That you didn't just see
That level of bigoted
Nazism
And I'm not joking
21-gun salute your universities
People also Taylor offended by
Just everything
So in true Alex Jones fashion what we have here is a straw man
The reason is warning on Lady and the Tramp is the racist Asian depiction
But because Alex doesn't want to directly support things that most people recognize
Is part of an ugly
We passed he's pretending the problem is the movie is at with movies and tells a heterosexual love story
Is the complete s***
There's so many movies on Disney plus but to pick to heterosexual love stories that don't have worn it
That don't involve archaic racist stereotypes well as of Arden Disney fan I don't know if you can name one of
I don't know if their movies out the top of
This is such a gross
Powder Valley
He knows that he has
Have to defend racism
That's what he does
What are you just can't do that
I would venture to say that at least 30% of his Conte
That could easily be summed up like
Trying to find ways to
Repackage the argument racism is great
It's good
Let's not billets Nots
About that 21-gun salute
This is solely about the University of Virginia decided not to do a 21-gun salute at their veteran
Save that this
The reason was basically that it was disruptive to campus
And because there's a bunch of gun violence going on these days or maybe that's not necessary
I can hear argue
Events for people who love military tradition saying
Salud is necessary
And I don't think I agree with them but I'm also not going to argue too much with it
But in this case
It feels really weird because
This was a University of Virginia ROTC event
So it's kind of their decision how to do things
Is there deciding not to do the salute
Is Alex saying that
You should be able to
Force them to do it
Like if this were the government or even the University
Telling them that they
Can't do the salute
This argument might look a little different but that's not the case
Oh you're you're misunderstanding this is even worse than
Then you can imagine this is Android
The globalist
Have infiltrated the RO.
DC at the highest levels
Great all over the University of Virginia
Sure
Browse his position to make
Any sense at all he would need to want
Insane level of control over the choices of other organization
He is not a part of
He sees this eel in the world that he proceeded
Someone not wanting to do a 21-gun salute and he decries it
The only point he could possibly be making his
I wish they wanted to do that
Salute there's nothing
To fight here
This is just trivial gun culture outrage
Which makes up another 30% of his coverage
Entire career
Generally speaking they do overlap
Totally
So Alex is still mad about Disney
He complains about them quite a bit
You don't show Lady and the Tramp you don't show Dumbo Dumbo has a loving mother
Not good ladies and gentlemen
Stop
So again the warning on Dumbo was about there being a character named Jim Crow in it
Also in the movie Dumbo mothers and fathers don't create children
They're delivered by stork
So I'm not sure if Alex on steak this line of thought too far
Batman so
Counterpoint Alex
You know
You know the news is real bad whenever you're reduced to being
I guess let's b**** about Disney plus like an old man for 3 hours cuz
I can't deal with the fact that it's
Very obvious my present
They committed a s*** ton of crime yeah
Everybody's Talkin
I got to I got to do something
I don't have the luxury of Fox News where I can put real-time refutation Liza in front of the
Screen rather than
Yeah
So Alex now
Gets off Intuit
A little bit of a second
Would be
Accurately described as transphobic
But also
Is about
Performers
So it's convoluted on some level
But it is just
Outright
Bigotry
And really really
Gross
Say this first clip you talked about how
Trans movement
It's not about
People
Identity or anything like
What about
Is it somebody
It's about
Truly
It's just about say so called trans movement isn't
Bob Hope dressing up
Like a woman for Halloween
It's not even men that feel feminine
Okay want to be seen as women by their men
It is Satanism and vampirism
In total deception is it is what the movement is being pushed
And so a man six foot four man with vampire teeth on eating a baby is a woman the opposite
A woman giving birth loving a baby big nurturing
Demonstrate show
Simulating a terrific actor
Academy Award looks so satanic
When do Borat something on this
You call that a woman that's why number
And then you say that this vampire creature is an image of a mother
A raving lunatic
Scarier looking than It the clown
Still not named surrounding at the bar
Worshipping at like they're seeing some great goodness
Because this is a real spirit
So I heard this in his like this isn't going to go well
This is this is I'm not a I'm not interested or very excited about the directions
He's going to take this
Just got done yelling about f****** Disney movies
So you riffs around a little bit here about how trans people are anti-human aliens
I didn't I thought we they were vampires
Well that's part of
AOC
Yoshi
Queen vampire occult show
Again
Is that what they called in New York City
MC warships she put this big 6 ft 4 man
What are you doing
Party
More like some
Alien invading blood-drinking Martian
Actually
Is destroyed ourselves humans were here. I don't have children
Human world
Mars Attacks how do they invade the Hollywood Squares
The big blonde hair
Really
Are your friends
Whatever this is just anti-human
Woman to Woman
So when our two talking about that
Person who is at
Like a vampire
What have you few weeks back
He's really banking on his audience not realizing that a couple weeks back was f******
Halloween
Probably
Halloween is actually evil
Anyway this is about a video that Alexandria ocasio-cortez put out where she met Sasha velour I noted drag
According to their website bio page Sasha is gender-fluid and has no preferred pronoun in personal life
But the drag Persona goes by femme
Sasha was on drag race which AOC is a big fan of sushi was very excited to meet
Performer from the show
Is a big zero
Alex ends up like the video of this
He's just playing a 15-second
Video of a person
Drag sitting on a bar in a Halloween costume
It involves fake blood and a fake baby
There's no context to it and honestly I'm ninety percent
Ensure that person
Isn't even Sasha velour
The person in that video is a big tattoo on their upper right arm and shoulder which Sasha does not have
Alex just thinks they're the same person because they're both in Dragon appeared to be bald
The person in that video.
Actually have short hair but Sasha actually
Shave their head in
Order to honor their mother
Who died of cancer
Also in the 2015 interview the person who
Performed the Sasha velour was very clear that they're not tran
So whatever Point hours
Just trying to make you really just false
Flat
But that doesn't change the reality that by his conflation of all these different gender expressions and identities boxing it all up
Under The Heading of
He's hoping to get people hurt
Wasn't it some drag vampire
That was Sasha velour show smoke and mirrors
Also it wasn't a New York it was in Washington
Nothing that I went to saying is based in reality but it doesn't
Is it reality isn't the point
Demonizing anyone who does
I'm fitting to his rigid view of gender and sexuality is
The point
He wants to say that it was a New York
Because that video of the
The person on a bar is in New York
Conflating all of this
Together in order to make it appear that they're the same person
Even though later in the show he doesn't hate that he's not he doesn't know if they're the same
He doesn't give a s***
Smoking mirrors is A1 Queen show is Russia called
It's a Theatre performer
It's toward
It's not like some kind of a basement
Blood ritual like Alex is presenting
Sirius respected well-reviewed show
Has the backing
Dan that's how she gets
Do all of the the money to travel people pay Earth
Not put too fine a point on this Alex is trying
To get people killed
The issue of trans and non-binary people particularly people of color being murdered is very serious
Sushi right now to the point where the American Medical Association
It's called violence again
Since the trans community and epidemic
Is Alex Jones
Cared at all about people he could express his discomfort with trans people in more responsible ways
But he doesn't care
He act like
Grotesque
Act out about trans people wanting to
Eat your kids
Because he walks
This sort of behavior doesn't lead tour people having a greater understanding
Standing of each other it doesn't even lead to a place of like respectful disagreement live-and-let-live nothing like
It's quite frankly incitement
This is
Did this doesn't
You understand the point I'm trying to make
Yeah I think the only path that this goes down is towards
Targeting
Abuse
Harassment and potentially violent
There's no
There's no healthy outcome
To the
Brewer
They're probably satanic aliens bro I want your kids want to eat your blood
This from a human
No this is
So many people are going to be viewed
Not long
I'm from now and RV right now
Review
So many
During the HIV
How are you doing now just now
A hole
List of people
Just
Just basically saying
I'm not trans so I don't really give a f*** yeah or even you could do an outright demonization or mocking them
For Trans people get assaulted
Umbrella this out to Altamonte
Times throughout history people should have learned our lesson about what it looks like to be
On the wrong side
Yeah right for your cultural issue
With s*** that Nazi said 50 years ago I think you
You should probably take a look at you
Yeah Oregon
People
So many
What culturally moved
Many of these
As long ago now.
To be clear I don't I don't think
You know
You could easily call somebody transphobic or or whatever or bigoted you can
Alex is so far past
Yeah it almost doesn't
Even fit into the boxer
So just
Being pickle
It's
Where am I
Narratives
Call minutes certainly lines
Itself to that even if that's not the prescription
He's
Suggested I don't know every single person is the devil
That includes
Drag purple
Apparently apparently that includes people who are just doing the show but I would say
It's not
Overtly
Or calling
For extermination
It's compatible
Yeah that is a that is a
Fixing that I would make
I think it's important
Consider things like that
The ways in which the rhetoric you put out is
Compatible with
Something that you pretend
You don't suppose
Well it's hard to
It's hard to die
Divest
This particular calling some
Something the devil with
The other things that he's called the devil and the way that you're supposed
To act toward those other
You know so many other things get called the devil and it's
Your job is God's servant to Destroyer
You know if
He just cuz he's not saying
Destroy this time if you calling it
The devil there's in there he's going
He saying just Royce
You know somebody has been very clear about the idea that you can't really coexist
Raticate whatever the devil is
Seems like that's a logic
If you do it then the devil will be doing so
Something different you'll have to
That and so on and so forth
Until
So Alex descends
Screaming rant
About this Ranch
So this is who we're supposed to worship a six-foot-four
Open
Call Steve
Guys
Prison photos
Now I'm a woman
Gimme your children right now
I honestly don't know exactly what Alex
Just talking about it through a lot of that
If I had to guess there must be some YouTube video of someone wanting to be called ma'am and he's just losing his s*** about it
I really don't know and I don't really care
It's all good whatever it is. The same thing it's just more and deeper margin
Analyzation that he's pushing
But here's the thing
I don't know of any trans or nonbinary person who acts
Screaming and ranting with insane and unhealthy levels of unchecked anger
It doesn't ring true there but it really reminds me of Alex him
Where does
That doesn't feel like a carrot
That feels like Alec
Alex is a person who rants like that's it
Sincerely when he finds out about a gun control bill that died in
Committee 2 weeks
Prior but he thinks it's still going to pass
I went to the person who screams like this whenever he has to pretend like a white person didn't just commit a terrorist Act
This rage that he's expressing is not true of some imagined
Character who he wants basic polite
Not extended to
It's Alex's rage at the perceived crumbling of his straight white Christian male-dominated
Society
That fuels
Very real anger that he's
He's manifesting
I know I say this a lot but if you know Alex you have a responsibility to get here
And probably get him into a
Trans people are being killed at alarming rate
And he's acting it weighs on are the perpetuate and escalate the mentality
That make their being hurt far more likely
If you think that he sincerely believes he's fine to do this because he thinks they're interdimensional demons
That's all the oven
Did you need to get him locked up on a 5150
If you think he's just making it up
And doesn't really believe this but still saying it on there
Still evidence to get him locked up on a mental health hold
Anyone who gave a f*** about Alex
Could help him right now
And get him to care that he desperately needs
But I guess they'd rather wait until this whole thing reaches its
Natural conclusion
Howard's
The whole lot of you
Anybody who can't help it isn't doing anything
Like just
Watching this play out
Cowards
So
That's part of this is all particularly
Distasteful
Alex Goes To Break
He comes back
Something
John Cleese
Something completely different okay
Okay in a balance
Let me get to it
I have a message for
Contract
Whistleblower
Message to Joe Rogan
Talk shows in the world
And it's this
View art
Both of you
I know can research the facts
Or is this for yourself
Alex
Ongoing geoengineering programs
Putting on this plan
4 / 100
A research institute the US Navy
Air Force
Weather
Modification
Programs using
Alyssa Lies
And other
Particular
Put out
Jet engines
Using the jet engine to create the nuclei
Intensified ice crystallization the atmosphere
10 years ago and talked about this then he hosted a program
So what's going on here is that Alex
Is deeply jealous of Rogan getting to interview Edward Snowden and also Alex really wants debate Joe into having him back on his
Oh yeah that's the long and short of it
Honestly normally I would just let this s*** slide and I'll get into it at all but after that out right
Did Alex is coming with her earlier
I feel like we need to cool down
I think that would be nice
So even though Alex only child
Joe Rogan Edward Snowden
I'm going to rise to the occasion
And discuss why Alex is a f****** dumb dumb about chemtrail
All right but I really want to wait
Wait until Ed Snowden
It's on the line. You said on the Rogan show that you look for evidence
Aliens are chemtrails
The files again
He also said that if there is evidence of it
He's not saying there isn't
But if there is
It's crazy
CenterPoint
With all the acts
He says he had he couldn't
Sunkist
Stick to the actual claims in
Specifics Alex uses
Over the course of
Because I don't want to drift into some
Some kind of absurd goose
This is a topic that's so full of ridiculous stupid claim
But Alex wants us to be serious
So let's play it that way
Oz first point that he brings up his about the 1960s
Stanford research
This is a reference to an interview that he did back in
In 2005 with a guy named Ben Livingston who he credits as the father of weather weapons
Okay
Livingston is allegedly former Navy physicist who is involved in weaponizing weather in the
Bible A2000
Ranor was working with a couple
City called weather modification incorporate
What is a real company
But weirdly and apiece about their president which is
Discusses the company
History and founding
Livingston's name doesn't come up at all
This company is in the business of clouds
Which is a little different than count
What they do is they fly planes into
Clouds and release silver iodide
Which is Mexico's weather molecules
Come together and turn
Durant
It's a technique that's been implemented to try and help drought-stricken region
But it also doesn't really always work
They can't make rain up here were moisture doesn't initially already
Exist
Some experts
The pointed out the cloud seeding only really works when there would have been rain anyway
It's pretty unclear the extent to which cloud seeding does help but it's way more clear that it doesn't really have
Any damaging environmental or health
Too Human Side Effects
There's literally no evidence of this technique
Create
Get rid of hurricanes or steer them to attack someplace like Alex wants you to believe
There was a project carried out by the government starting in 19
T2 called project stormfury
Which hypothesized they could use cloud seeding
Need to decrease the destructive power of hurricane
By seeding clouds around the hurricane
It disrupts the inner structure of the storm
They changed the name from
Plan
What about supervillain
There was another name
M48 initially the goza precursor program to this but it's all tomato
Jesus Christ guy they found that this definitely did not
Well it seemed like it was a possible approach the
The science behind the high pop
This is about to be flawed
And the program was disc
Continue
Innocence of controlling hurricanes
Stormfury was a complete failure
What scientist actually learned a lot about weather patterns of the process
So we can kind of call it a win on some levels and
It's not a huge embarrassing
Surefire sight
Naming it
Stormfury might be a little bit
I don't like it
All this stuff is just faint
The rest of it delivered by Ben Livingston in an interview with Alex Jones a2005
I watched a bit of the interview and honestly
It kind of feels like Project Camelot
Hot stuff
Well there's a kernel of Truth in there do you know the cloud seeding does
Existing private company
Please do it I'll just take it
The extensions of it a bit too
Too far
Quite frankly
I have no idea you been living
Yeah the only trace of him anywhere that's life doesn't appearance on Infowars
There's no academic papers he's written there's no references left in the Congressional Record or anything like that it's all just stuff that he
He said and Alex's taken as gospel
It's impossible to know if Ben Livingston is a credible Source on anything
Unless Alex Cooper vide another source on this
These are claims that I can allowed to stand
So far all that Alex is bringing to the table here is a fourteen-year-old interview he did with some guy
I need better
Well I mean Ben Livingston did
Name later on
Does that
I presume
I'm pretty old in 2005 I don't know if you still with us
I don't know I don't know
Can't find anything else about him except for an Infowars
Suggest obviously that
He is 104
Correct they are scrubbing every bit of the record
Just like they did to keep it away from Ed Snowden
They've gotten rid of the files damn they're not
Well I would believe that it's possible although I don't know this
Could have been a pilot who was involved
Live with storm
I think that is
Not outside the realm of a possibility
But the
Conclusions that he brings
To the table and things he talks about are not supported by any available in
And I need that other backing
To the claims that he's making
Or else
I just think well this is a guy
Who may or may not have been
A pilot
Who now is crazy
Well I mean I think the I think
You fart
The people who came up with
What if we could weaponize hurricane
And we're a little bit out there as well but so I think he could
Very well be
Accepted by that group
Do they like if you are
People who have
Know what it's possible that we could create cloud
Hurricanes are problem they're very destructive
If there was a way we could use the
This technology with
Cloud seeding
Disrupt the hurricane
Blessing it's damaging effects
Why wouldn't you try it
Like why wouldn't you researched
Well I mean Government research is all sorts of
Yeah
Yeah I mean I would assume that
Much like the the how to know when you're on the right side of History the
Should we have
Control over the weather I bet it's probably never going to
But used in a evil horrible way in hurricane
Control plan is probably
On the like
Maybe we should leave that one alone you got a whole situation call it super villainous or you could call it just the inevitable can
Inclusion where human curiosity
If you could say that about the internet
Right
That's also a bummer
Straight to Grey Goo
Syrian you're like well I guess we're f*****
It's not so much that we're f*****
It's that the constant
Path of human evolution
Does involve a certain amount of risk
With the things that our curiosity will inevitably bring us
So the path
The challenge
Is figuring out a way that we can incorporate those
Really dangerous things
Into
Sustainable world
So I don't see any of that is being
Supervillain is or even
Doom
Yes you might look at it like we're inevitably trending towards Graco
It's
It certainly is like well that's something we should keep in mind
That is a
Gabriel - how come
What does it mean if that's the inevitable out
There's a way you can have
Inability to control hurricane
Which again
We do not
There is a way that
You can have that
Edit not be
Okay
Probably
I don't know why we've only talked to Nuke so I think we're good we're doing alright
You know with infinite
World ending power we have only dropped two
Set alarm
Destroy the world.
We have yet to do so
Yes you could look at it as Bleak but it also at there's a
Silver lining
So Alex brings back to the table and that's not a good starting point
All that stuff is just stuff that been living
Vincent told him
Until I got to throw that out a tiny bit cuz it's not really
I thought like maybe that was it
But he has more
Can I get it he has staked his reputation that you do
Going on the quote using the LIE term
Chemtrails don't exist
Haha
Altitude Araceli
Geoengineering
Programs
Show you
Smithsonian
Cfrb the CIA director admitting it
This is where I get
Tumescent
Jordan cuz you got something
Really sticky
Yeah this is where I'm like crime on this
Well whatever Alex
Really is like I'm going to
To prove something that's what I like
Time to go to work until like 3 or 4 in the morning last night
Knuckle
Okay
I don't think Alex is trying most
He's pretending he's trying
Right at least
This is
A time when am I okay
I have a worthy opponent
Give me very excited
So anyway here's worries.
And I want to be clear
I've not cut out stuff where you give good eggs
All of this is going to be terrible everybody didn't
Need that
I just wanted to be clear that's not like there's a Smoking Gun in here and I was like Let's ignore that
There are a lot of governments involved now at the secret treaty level
Fuel project
Two scientists won the Nobel Prize in 1992
Coming up with this plan
So right off the bat I can't do s*** with secret treaties
That's an unacceptable thing to bring into the conversation so I'm going to ignore it unless Alex can produce those trees
Level of secret treaties and neither is out as I get up
So you can easily look up Nobel Prize winners and Alex's lying
What is write-up
Forget about Nobel Prize winner so we can ignore the fields of literature peace and economics
Those aren't related here at all
And I looked at them for 19
And I do have another
That leaves medicine
Chemistry and physics
Is the fields of Nobel
Awards
That could
Bee-related
Who won the physics award that year for his invention of a particle that
That's not related
Randolph Marcus 14
For chemistry for his work in the
Is related to the theory of electron
Transfer react
Chemical systems
Not related
Two guys Edmund Fisher and Edwin cribs
Amino acid related research
That was two scientists
But it was
None of this has anything to do with secret plans to dim the world through geoengineering where the f*** is talking about
Didn't the Nobel Prize in literature go to a guy who wrote
Hey how about we build some other weapons or what now come on now hey
Long titles of 1990
G513 scientist won the Nobel Prize for their work understanding the chemistry involved in the formation and
Destruction of ozone
I assume that's what he's talking about because it involves the sky but also has nothing to do with Kevin
Entrails to make the Earth Denver to fight global warming
Later in life one of those three science
Who did get the Nobel Prize in 90
Did come out publicly in favor of exploring engineering
Solutions to climate change
Problems
But that's not what he got the Nobel Prize for Alex if he's talking about them
Eve conflating things
And he got the year wrong
Yes is making
Shut up please just talking
So none of the Nobel Prize winners
The Chemtrails are
Not in the way that Alex's
Joey gets on to his next piece of evidence he said that he's going to bring up
The CFR the dod all of it
Bring something.
Okay let's get into it right now
Overhead shot
US Department of Defense
Secretary defense Williams
Others are working on weather control
Control
Define 3rd is on
Right off the bat this can be ignored
His proof is at this guy in the DoD said that people are working
Weather weapons
That doesn't mean that anyone has ever successfully made one or that any of this is
Real
The statement that people walk whether weapons he's totally logic
Inconsistent
With the statement no one has ever made weather wise
Wanting something and work
Working on something is not the same as that thing
Being real
So we talked about this a little bit in the past but because Alex is doing a large breakdown and going to
Cover something we've already talked about
This was a news story about a speech that William Cohen gave it
The University of Georgia
On terrorism weapons of mass destruction in US strategy
Is entirely about
Connery in The Avengers
Baby might have been
If you read the quote in context you learn that
Bitcoin is talking about fake reports
And how they can really f****** at the park
He was asked a question about a false alarm about an anthrax
Scared that it happened at b'nai brith the previous week
Which going relates that sort of false alarm to the sort of scares
Can happen when there's a belief
There's a mole within a particular law enforcement or government agent
Quote
The mere fear that there's a mole within an agency
Can set off a chain reaction
Hot for that particular Bowl we could paralyze the agents
54 weeks in months
Here's even
In a search
The same thing is true about just
The false care of a threat
If using some kind of a chemical weapon or biological one
Their reports
Example that some countries have been trying to
Construct something like an ebola virus that would be very dangerous a phenomenon to say the least
Alvin Toffler is written about this in terms of
Some scientist and their Laboratories trying to divide certain types of
Pathogens that would be
Specific so they could just eliminate us
Ethnic group
Open race
And others are designing so
Some sort of engineering
Some sort of insects
Destroy specific crop
Others are engaging even in
Eco type of terrorism
Whereby they can alter the climate set off earthquakes volcanoes remotely through the use of electromagnetic waves
This list
Specific weapons like weaponized Ebola and the weather weapon
Examples of possibly fake reports
Can come up
The Cripple of depart
Mad because I have to respond to the report is if they're real
This is not evidence of William Cohen saying that there are weather weather
He's not even saying that anyone has one he's not even saying that I wasn't working
You think there might be false reports of these sorts of things
So far Alex
Has provided
Evidence of
Nothing
So
So if I understand correctly his evidence
Is William Cohen
Sad that people
Could be lying
Yes
Be very the very nature of this possible lie being reported
Can be devastating
And the money suck
Time-suck
Ford
Guys like that Twilight Zone
Write the context of this makes it clear that he's
Not saying
Anything
Concrete and the way that Alex want you to
So Alex gets to his next piece of evidence
Let's move on to the next thing
Other weapons of existed over 15 years testified US Secretary of Defense
This is an article published on natural news
So already not great
Burn It Down
Vertical ground so it just to be even you could just this message page.
The Secretary of Defense in question there
Is William Cohen of course
Exact same story as the fact that cannot be okay story
Publisher the b******* had to hang up Mike Adams website
Unacceptable
Alex's literally proved nothing
So anyway here's a bunch of it
In this folder IFC fr
10 running quasi secret program
Dockside
Corporate level
Eliza's it into
Nuclei
Artificial clouds I don't give a f*** about that folder unless you decide exactly what's
Alex can talk about Bill Gates
See how far until he passes out from exhaustion
Can I still won't give a s*** unless he gives me some specifics
At best as I could tell right now all of this is just a talking about cloud seeding
Exaggerating it way far past the reality
Yeah I think that's all he's doing is bringing up hats
But you can't trust that like crazy impossible possible
Trolls whodas it on thing there
Cooper little man maybe later on something will be related to Kanye
Time machines yeah yeah
Yeah
Any of them good though baby
Comes up right after this and made me worried that was
Get to these clips let's play Joe Rogan
Whatever Snowden
A few weeks ago
Is everything in the world
So like you jumping now
Clips of Snowden as if he's proved his case
All he's done is talk about Williams make a reference to a 14
Underworld interview
That's it
Cuz he is done
0 he went
Also literally his entire career is based on him being a guy who has secret government
He can't be that judge Aguirre
All you got RC
Secret government
That is a problem
But the reality of this is as we
It's very
He's just mad at Joe
Joe Rogan tells us it doesn't
Installed
Metronews
So
Everything we told you 20 years ago turned out to be dead on exactly right
We're more discredited
More discredited
So the mainstream news article headlined that I would slashes up there is about Bill Gates supporting a group that's coming up with solutions to climb
A change using solar Engineering Management governance
Initiative or cloudy
Give me Frank their plan does sound
Sound a lot like
Like what Alex has been talking about
About what was the release
Tons of particles at a high-altitude to block a reduce the
The impact of
That's all good and well but that's not a thing that people are doing
It's technically possible in their plans at this point in the unit at work there's a very good reason that no one would ever let
Let them do this unless there was literally no other option
That's because the consequences of doing something like this would be
Insane
Including but not limited to making
Biscotti no longer blue
I mean
You know I'm pretty sure that there's never been any movies made in the past about what would happen
You know Messi
They've done some modelling of the idea and found that it would be cheap
It'll probably be effective in reducing heat coming in
No way of knowing what other sorts of disruptions to natural processes the plan might have
And that's why this requires more research
Bill Gates has been on the table for a long time and we've talked about it before
He's not advocating that we do this but he's funding Research into
The things that we can do if we end up in a real serious crisis and the world is becoming uninhabitable
It's very possible that there could come a day
Where the ecosystem is so distraught
Goodbye something like climate change
That we would be absolutely thrilled to risk the Blue Sky in order to survive
And by that point
It's way too late
To research any of this stuff
By putting money into it now we do few Manatee options later
Which are super important
They would be helpful yes
Pick up everywhere
Likely to be
So that's the headline Alex flashes up on screen
So to reiterate so far Alex has done nothing to convince me the Chemtrails or secret geoengineering program is
All this evidence amounts to nothing
And I didn't cut things out worry drop bombshells
This seems to be all he's got other than whatever is in that super cool folder of is
This is the look like part of the episode where I could descend into a protected list of all the time
Suppose chemtrail science
Is the weather shift
Debunked every embarrassing
Attempt to prove this s***
But I'm not here to prove a negative
How to draw Bowser show that Joe Rogan and Edward Snowden were liars and wrong to say that
Chemtrails aren't real
You spelled in his task
Worse than project storm Fury
To be clear
I recognized that I was just do this whole cycle
To try and bake Joe at the heaven
Get back on his podcast
I really just wanted to read
For this episode so so here we are
I know you I know.
I know feels go
Alex is mad about Joe Rogan
Start screaming
Grapes
Podcast
Earlier this year
Professor
They just announced
But they're doing
Other dimensions
Sure
When I was 8 years old around dinner table
With people involved in the project
Okay
So I think I was talking about Rick Strassman who's the guy who wrote The Spirit Molecule and he's been this dude Strassman
For a long time
To prolong the DMT trip
Through like an IV drip
It's at least back to 26
Like there was an article in Vice
I'm not sure if that dude ever been on Rogan show by Betty what has how many would-be
The guy about beat DMT
I didn't look through all of Rogan's episodes but I was scrolling through them and
His name didn't come up
At least in the time frame that Alex's tacos
But I would bet
Anything that I own that whoever was
The cast was talking about Strasburg
This has nothing to do with the government thinking the people are talking
Aliens and getting their commands
The higher-ups in the Demon World
Honestly if the government were researching
Like why wouldn't they
Government grants are behind all sorts of scientific research
I have some people who take DMT
He think that they're talking to alien
Why the hell wouldn't that be an area worth it
Exploring
If you research that
It doesn't mean you actually believe the people are talking to alien
You could very well be in
Student learning more about the parts of the brain that are involved in hallucinate
They're plenty of research here that are agnostic
Towards the exist
Supremes.
Dimensional demon
Put simply Alex's f******
Stupid
I'm starting LSD
MDMA in the like it for
Possible treatments for p
PTSD
And all of those things
Why not
Add DMT
Let's figure some
Come sit out
Yep prohibition doesn't work
There are there are a
Great deal of applications
For research
And uses
Spray this other than map
Sing out a spirit world to talk to
Right right right
I remember her so I wouldn't take that off
People who were studying like loose
To Dreaming my God
There's some
Researchers were doing that that's the terms in which they were talking about that to like mapping out these
Subconscious world
It's sort of a way of
Contextualizing it in your mind when it's not like you're actually going in and maybe
Like doing cartago
Or something
If you if you have a scientist
Give you an exact
Chemical definition
Mission of what it is they're doing
Your eyes glaze over and you're not
If you have them give you a metaphor that allows you to
Expensive weather
Helps
Alex Jones will take it out of context
Destroy the world
You know
Right right
Alex is the crazy one that's
Oh that's kooky cookie talk to aliens
Globalist project
Even though it's all true
Welcome back on the play the eclipse but the Blood start getting to Snowden
So now apparently the entire chemtrail thing is about
People taking DMT talking to demon aliens who are telling them to
Go form the planet in order to make it hospitable for them to come because
I guess they can't breathe oxygen or this is
Yeah it is it that if you do not agree with that that sounds great
Motor standard business where it's gone
Call out Joe Rogan Edward Snowden because he has all the proof about chemtrails
DMT aliens are telling the government to go farm the planet
Okay
We are off the f****** rails
This is where I'm like alright
I looked weird and straight up to your specific
Fireplace your b*******
So anyway
Alex is mad
It snowed in
And I find something he says in this next clip variant
I'm refreshed
Should have somebody be mad at Snowden about a new reason for a new reason this is nice it's interesting
Mad at Snowden about DMT before
Well
That's part of the reason
But I
Alex says something revealing
But the main thing is
Conspiracy theories right everybody wants to believe in conspiracy theories book
It helps life makes sense
Just believe
Somebody's control
In control somebody's calling the shots these things happen for a reason
John Wayne when he first came out he lives for us
Okay Alex has been pretty consistent in his support of Edward Snowden because he revealed information that tended to help out
Let's create conspiracy theory
The stuff Snowden released generally speaking was well in line with
With the view of the US government was evil which job did real well with Alex's anti-government
But now he said that there's no evidence of chemtrail
And Alex has decided
He was right all along and that Snowden was controlled opposition
Man it's a bad day now what I find most in
Interesting about that is that
Steve has been auntie Snowden from
The job but
That actually works
Pretty well for my theory that Steve gets all of his information
From Stratford
The intelligence
Yeah yeah they would also be pretty heavily against
If you recall in our episode that were recovered Stephen Depp
We discussed her Wikileaks stratfor email.
Included a bunch of customer service emails from
Pieczenik where we learned that sense
At least do mid early-to-mid 2000
Steve has been a lifetime member of their privately produced intelligent product and their publication
A 2016 article put out by Stratford
Includes are discussing Snowden as an
Example of a quote
Internal threat
In 2013 Stratford founder George freed
Wrote an op-ed in Forbes titled quote
Keeping the
NSA in
Perspective
Where he argues that the spying programs revealed by Snowden
Nabil
Quote the revelations about prism are far from New or interesting in themselves
Beyonce was created with a charter to do these things
And given the state of Technology was inevitable that the NSA would
Recapturing communication
Around the world
Many weeks prior to Snowden
Show that the NSA was doing
It would have been more newsworthy if the leak revealed that the NSA had not been
Capturing all the communique
It seems like Stratford has a bit of a not super into Snowden
That would make sense
I think they
Just put
Together that I think the best argument for
Dissolving the NSA entirely right literally what he just said was
Well of course they were going to break the Constitution
Duh
They're essentially a private version of anak
They share common cause with something like the NSA so they would likely see Snowden
Similarly to how the NSA would
As an internal
It's possible this doesn't mean anything but this is
Definitely a position you'd expect to see from
I'm someone who is just regurgitating private
Intelligence company Prada
So
You know that's a little bit of a car
I did it fits in line
So now that Alex has dropped off into talkin about how the Chemtrails are really just part of it
Grands
DMT alien
Conspiracy
I'm still struggling to
Wrap my head around that one but we can move on I thought that he was done
Wright returns
They're simply aliens involved unless
Brennan
Right as he plays a clip of him here and this is a little bit of a longer Cliff but I think
If it merits
So let's play the
Of the CIA
Specifically repeating what we said they were doing 20 years ago
Another example is the array of Technologies
Poppin referred to collectively as geoengineering
Potentially could help reverse the warming effects of global climate change
One that has gained my personal attention
Stratospheric
Aerosol injection
Or Sai
A method of treating the stratosphere with particles that can help reflect the sun's Heat
How much the same way that volcanic eruptions do
An essay I program could limit Global temperature increase
Reducing some risks associated with higher temperatures
Provided the world economy additional time to transition for
From fossil fuels
This process is also relatively inexpensive
The national resource
Research Council estimates that I fully deployed sa-i program would cost about
10 billion dollars
Yearly
As promising as it may be moving forward an essay I would also raised a number of challenges for a government
Answer the internet
Community
On the technical side greenhouse gas emission reductions
We still have to
Company Sai to address other climate change affects
Such as ocean acidification
Because saii alone would not be moved greenhouse gases from the atmos
On the geopolitical side
The Technology's potential to alter weather patterns
And benefit certain regions of the world at the expense of other regions
Could trigger sharp opposition by Sundays
Others might seize on essay eyes benefits
I'm back away from their commitment to carbon dioxide
And as with other breakthrough Technologies
Global norms and standards are lacking
The guide to deployment
Implantation
SAR
Other geoengineering initiatives
But Edward Snowden said it didn't exist on the cool pretty show
You got him Alex
See how that works
Nothing to Brandon side In that clip can be taken really to mean that there is a program there is a potential thing that had
Been research
He's talking about this in the terms of this wood or
Implementing this would create a number of
Issues that would need to be resolved
He's talking about there's in a hypothetical
You can't introduce this as evidence that something does a
And you like no one no one can deny that research
Wright has been done on similar topic
It's right no one can deny that cloud seeding
Isn't something
That has been done
But to extrapolate it into the
A conspiracy that
He's pushing
Is completely absurd
I saw somebody with the
Slingshot so that me
Who's that
Control the weather
Sure
That's pretty soon
That's how it works here is the last
Clip-in are segments that I'm going
Call Alex Azar
Conspiracy dumped
I can show you the Smithsonian articles
Department of the articles
Program
Roll your sleeves up
You smug
A****** while I got all these things I could show you but I've already proved my case
Proof
So anyway that's kind of this segment
Doodle Alex has
Too much of it
Mid-segment
Yeah
So now we get to the the real enemies
Steve is back up boy
Man
So great
On so many levels
I could listen
Steve y'all italics
If you really rude to him the whole time
Dynamic and that is what I was really really liked him
Talk because I think that Alex has been humble
Bye-bye Steve
Inside of a galaxy
I don't know what the actual Dynamic behind
Machines is or how it's
Changed over the
The year plus that he hasn't been on
Yeah but Alex does seem
Far less willing to fight with
And
Steve is up to his old tricks
You know how whenever in the past Alex would introduce him he would
Flatter Alex with Akio the best
Yeah he's upped his game
A little bit
Going to get a real brown nose on this one no no no it takes a completely different form okay scism
Weather
Thank you for getting me back on the show
But you are an interesting times live
Summarizing 33-seat Jefferson
Call Jack.
In Liberty we will have
Have to sacrifice the blood
Patriots and Tyra
And that's exactly what
Steve immediately quotes Jefferson he is the best
No he's so good at all quotes
He's so good at manipulating Alex we've got a complete moratorium on
But that one is actually using it as close to accurately as any
That's fine but I'm still calling a moratorium on Jeffrey
But it's so fascinating that that's exactly what you do at Alex
Galaxy quote Jefferson all the goddamn time
Heart explodes with patriotism and he's like whatever you have to say next
F****** saluting Steve
Right now
So you know they start talking about the MP
My little bit the impeachment inquiry
And Steve naturally
Is millions and millions of dollars wasted on a
Access that will guarantee
Where Trump will be reelected in 2020
There's no question of it this is the demise of the Democratic Party
They are in a spiral of self-destruction
So why aren't you for it then
Why shouldn't you be so
Real Trump is getting impeached
Because it's the demise of the Democratic Party
Trump's going to get reelected
Cheerleading for this and I don't understand why he's so sad about
This is that he's really worried that the government is waste
Digging to school
There's
This few million dollars could have
Reallocate
Right
So there's a soft cool going on shore
Which there was in 2015
Always always a f****** sofcu
Who's like great-great-great Grand
I don't know if this is
Just restarted and it's a whole nother cool or whatever but apparently that's something to do with Yale
Anyway here's Steve
Whatever
But you had Jerry Post in your psychiatrist you are trying to claim
That Trump is not sincere
On the other hand
George Conway who
And is the husband of Taliesin
Conway
Call Leanne Conway works at
Straight East from Yale
Posters from yeah I got back from Yale
Woodward from bli got bushes from Miele I got Cheney from you
I'm trying to
Civil War or whatever you want to call it
It's it's a sock because we're using military forces and Military
Will not be in the business of
Using military force if we have
Play frankly now
That's what I was doing with my feet
Heather you've always been doing that you're doing on Alex's show and late
2015 convince them to get bored of trump
Who's all the ways that the narrative is the soft to going on and we've got a
Subvert democracy
Percy in order to
Yeah it's just
And when you say who's we
Always talks
It's crazy
He thought when he talks about the military he's like
I've got a hundred thousand men overseas
Nobody calling you
God got to get Steve on the phone
Yeah
So the Democratic party is imploding
Because this is
Pretty much the only reference
Prince to Bloomberg running
And the shell when it comes
So what you see in a sect is a very ineffectual of sheep
Party
Self-destructing in the midst of what really is a republican Revolution
The reason
In the Democratic
Democratic
Bernie Sanders is a joke
Warner New Hampshire
Is the Socialist he's a multi-millionaire socialist from book
Advances
There's a reason
Now she has no credibility
And then you have the light whatever you want to call it a migas
Work together and destroying the party so you really have nobody that has mentally
He has a problem with an aneurysm
All all of the people that he named beat drum
International Falls
Head2head
So did Hillary.
Fair enough but you understand
The squad
Because they aren't running for president
I don't care about is
Analysis
They go to break
And this is coming back from break I just make
This is so hilarious nothing to do with Steve but this is so dumb
Well Carpe donktum it mean world.com
Thomas released amazing New Meme
Infowars.com
The triumphant
Star Wars Museum right now
Dr.
Nothing says this meme grew organically like Alex Jones announcing it on Infowars
Christ imagine that swelling music Alex comes back on music
Carpe donktum got a new Reddit thread Cheese's I know right loading something
Just f****** stupid most insignificant thing I
Steve started out a little
Slow
He gets up speed real fast
So Jeffrey Epstein died a lot of people have a lot of feeling
I bet Steve's are really good
There are people who say he's murdered
Yeah there's some people who say he committed suicide right there's a third group of people
There's a third group of people who are very crazy
And Steven
I was surprised that
One General didn't do anything
When asked
Was Kill
OSHA
Can anyway slaughtered in another cell
Epstein was part of the CIA
And he knows well as I did William Barr that we take out our own people we send them overseas
Sebastian
Jeffrey Epstein the live out of the country
I knew it well you know when
Grand ideas of being a murderer or two popular
You need to go further
Someone like Steve so high
For crazy that like
You know what her to even
Feel it he's coming
He's got to go so much further than normal
He's like man I got to do
Three tabs ass
Get going
But that's my phone into percent
Yes but with b*******
Steve
Weather Consultants
Initially at the state department in
Roulette like 2 years
Until he British brought in as a deputy assistant Secretary of State
He was in that position
For a short. Of time
But in this club deserted rewrites history fries now what his job was
Is it was his job to come in and
Fire everybody
Most ruthless people people like me and
Job with the state department
What's the same thing in the intelligence community
There is no such thing not knowing
How to root these criminals
Has brought in a fired every day
Dumbest
Edwards people
Who are the ones who brag about coming in and
Firing Trump you guys are so f******
So you know he fired a ton of people and it led to a situation where the state department
That Steve was working people apparently
Alex the irony is he's not as tough as he should have been you bringing guys like me or you
We would get rid of them
Why do I need 75,000 people in the state
When I work for Kissinger we headed most 9 to 10 people
And Henrietta
What to do
Man the state department has list of employees you can find pretty easily and Steve's numbers are nowhere near correct
I have no idea what he's trying to express by saying the Kissinger had like 10 guys and that was a department
But I suspect it's a reflection of how uninvolved
Steve actually was in the bigger picture
Like I would believe that his office had like 9 or 10 guys in it but man
The state department is really big and it always has been
How come you never added
How come you never
Honestly as the question
Why does the state
Ambassadors are part of the state department
That's just one part of the state department you start to realize there's a ton of people working under that umbrella
Put it bluntly
Stephen Hawking
Straight-up b*******
This is nonsense
Why is what why do you need 75,000 people working for them
Cuz if there's a lot of s***
What to do but a lot countries
Is lot of intricate diplomacy
Call that
Says fire the state department
Irrelevant
I think even Alex is like hold on now
That
Crazy I hate you I hate big government but what you're advocating for is
At least it's like
It's not functional
The state department being like a couple dudes
What do you what do you need as a diplomat to know what it what are those what are those other countries called
China what do you need a diplomat for
I could see it working
No I can't ever
So you get to talkin about
You know
Rollie Rollie
Maybe enriching them
Steve Kerr
Can Trump be saved in your view and what are the plays they're going to use against him
They're going to use several things one it came out Jared Kushner Ivanka Trump have been south of grand
Deal
Saturday
A business name
A businessman
Does what he has to do
I don't care if he makes money
What
I think you might not be into that. Like
These guys from love the Constitution
Constitution
The businessman he does what he has to do
I would be
To be a fly on the wall when a music
Explain that to the entire intelligence community that he runs secretly apparently
Okay
Call Steve
So man
Steve
Comes out real in favor of Putin
Appearance
Which isn't too surprising based on some of the stuff you were saying in like 20
But it's a little
Very
Strong support here
We have National Security interest National Security interest means business so when anybody
Give me a break
Number one I was involved in the Soviet Union
We had an agreement
That was in writing
There is no such thing as the Russians
Baited
Crimea
What union Russia
But you not to tell me
Okay Steve
Wow so
It gets even crazier
Strong
Surprise
Control
The remainder of what was Russia
It's becoming clear to me that Steve pieczenik is a megalomaniac
While he presented world where he's been involved in literally every single thing that is that the stage for the world we live in.
Coming to exist
Yeah.
India Tea Company that's how we spread the road lot of China
Every piece on the chest
We all think we have free will but in reality everything is been
Steve all along
Awards
Universe I don't believe any of this yet
And I definitely don't believe that Steve had anything to do with Putin's rise of the KTV
Everything daddy the timeline just doesn't make sense
Cb&i
1975 and 1974 Steve just entered the state department as a Consulting
He wasn't even the deputy assistant secretary until 1976
This is all bulshit but it fits the
Fuse pattern Sowell
Kind of love it
I could listen to the Alex get yelled at by this grandiose old man for days
Yeah it'll when I was there at the
The Gulf of Tonkin
Okay god dammit
Go go off
So also in 2005 Steve Road and I paid for the American
Intelligence Journal title Putin
KGB
Forever
Which mysteriously doesn't mention him knowing anything about food before he became president of Russia
Also super anti-putin
You sure he didn't
Carve that into a tree
Playa bowls
Weather harder
Took from that quote what is certain at this point in time is the Putin has muzzled the Russian press
Sidelined rivals or jettisoned into prison
He's Cafe
Parliament prerogative as meager as they may have been
And once again like all good KGB operatives he's disseminated intimidation and seek
At once silencing domestic price
For security reform and political account
Possibility
Steven that op-ed literally argues that America doing nothing
Interviewing Putin's action
As domestic issues
Will lead to a quote
Serious problem
Did he describe
Russia's Neighbors in Eastern and Central Europe will be justifiably concerned about political destabilization of their region
What big country in Eastern Europe that was justifiably concerned about Russian
Destabilization their country
Maybe f***
Ukraine I don't think so
I don't think so I take everything back that I said the last episode that we did that where I said that
Steve is consistent
He's just consistent and hating neocon isn't that impressive
He's deeply in consist
Yeah
Pretty anyway he installed
That's pretty Dynamite that his
Psyops
Are still last
Years ago he fuc
The reason that he told everybody that was B
Assume that they wouldn't
Seriously
Because he
Chosen Putin
And of course as we know the globalist by law
Have to announce what they are
Doing
Before they do it people have to tacitly a
Green with that so dumb
Steve pieczenik
Cast to put it out in a journal
That Putin is going to do what he's going
To do years later we find we're here
And in order to facilitate
Continuing is power
Steve now has to run a psyop saying that he's not using his power
Perfect
Easier explanation
Steve
So
Alex
To some extent I guess Steve
Are pretty convinced that Mitt Romney is going to be the ringleader of the impeachment
Do the Senate
And do some real interesting
Ashley in the self-destructive mode
Who is a coward
I said it years ago when he was on break but I meant Romney is the guy that's been
So that's a very weird pairing of Santa
Mitt Romney is not a republican he's not a Mormon
Yep
It's strange
You know what it is
It follows
Next clip where
Steve is talking about how like we got
Got to get a Mormon
To neutralize the Romney
Threatened
Alright
Yeah yeah
And I would get rid of state and put in Jon Huntsman
To the president
At the same time he despises Mantronix I have a
Mormon
Romney
Can you sleep
Better than year Mormons
F***
So weird
Okay alright are we
We're doing Secret Wars
That's it we're doing a comic book mash-up event
Where we've got
Steve pieczenik used in the f****** Marvel Universe
The DC Universe
On the goddamn globalist side
We've entered is in this part of Steve's interview with Alex
He is
Fantasy Baseball any Administration
Guess what what
Steve got a job okay
ShopRite
And clean out that entire White House get rid of
Security Council
Can start coming into the state department and start cutting down on the 16th
And at the same time
You set in motion and incredible counter-revolution
People will say thank you
Mr. president thank you
Literally when he was describing it
Is I will go into the White House and get rid of any and every possible oversight into what anybody dance
Any possible to send exact
Calling 4:00 knives
So with all these constant talk of wanting to eliminate
The intelligence
Clearly screaming about their important to remind you that
Emails that Wikileaks released in their Stratford table
Steve breault
Customer service email
And said quote
Continue the great job
We will not need our expense
Ineffective bloated government agencies
In 2004 Steve wrote an op-ed for the journal-american intelligence
Arguing for a nearly complete
Pleat Outsourcing of intelligence operation
Do private company
He is an insanely huge supporter of business is doing spy work
Which I think is a pretty bad idea
But here's the thing
He never makes that actual argument on Alex's show
He always present this stuff super disingenuous
The goalies working towards is private intelligence company
Are you spying on civilians like Stratford taking over a ton of the responsibilities of the US intelligence
But instead of saying that on Alex's show
Still say things like
All these people at the CIA or doing nothing
Couches
Otis real motivation
Is very clear from his actions
It has been consistent over the years
He's using Alex's anti-government leanings to his advantage
No granted I believe that Steve is also fairly anti-government
But I don't believe that this aspect of his character is based on some small government prints
I have no idea exactly why you would want private
Companies spying
In the same way I have no idea why someone would take private armies like Blackwater would be an okay thing to have
I can't mail down the exact explanation
But I know for sure that it's
Not good
By elevating Steven helping him further his agenda
Alex's wittingly or unwittingly
Help move us closer to a world that is not more free
And privacy is not more protect
You'll just be
For-profit businesses that are doing the bulk of the spying as opposed
The government
So cool
This guy really is on the tip of the spear fighting against tyranny
That is
That is wild
Steve loves
Especially if they're
Multiple
Cuz it cuz
The idea thereof would be like privatization means that intelligence agencies welcome
With each other
And whoever gets the best intelligence
Is going to win out I can't see any problems with that that's that's
Sing the torture gives you the best information you're going to get what you want to get out of it that's how the
Booking
Consumerism
Picture of it
You're not going to get the best information you can see
Information you want
Yep it'll be it would be
Not good
End
Yep
Anyway
Steve seems to be calling for basically a
Of people in these places that are
Disloyal or oversight related
And Alex seems to be on board with it
24-hours all crime is
Are the founders of Delta Force
Jose Aldo Moro
Choo choo choo choo
Are you saying
What's going on but your message the president
And also your message to the president about we were just saying earlier
Action some real head starting to roll
This is going to energize everybody and it's going to guarantee I believe victory
Because they have gotten away
Would literally like a cat in your house pissing all over the furniture I mean these guys need to be whacked upside the head
I agree
Just a small Point as a cat friend
Cohabitate or with Jack
That's not how you
Want a cat now
That's that's how you create a very
A meme cat
You will break the bonds that you have with a cat if you discipline them through like physical violence or
Or something
Suggesting
Doesn't work metaphor
Doesn't work actually
And you supporting the idea that sea
Steve has a
Would you gets into a little bit more here just screaming more about how he wants to fire everybody in
Grandiose
Empower
Intern
I would clean out all of the institutions I do not need 75,000 people in the state
Department of the internet
You can just email over
Flat-side
Stupid I am
You know it's
A testament to
To Steve's ability
That he can
If you'd say that these are
Spineless sycophants
Who just want Power
,
What I would do if I had all this power
Is help you retain all that power
So the problem is
Steve would do all day
You fire everybody it'll be great
Sycophantic power fantasy
Trump
Whose catchphrase is your fired rise too nice to fire everybody
Solution to this problem
McDonald's
Because
I'm really worried you'll start screaming. Because this is infuriating because it's one of the most ludicrous thing
I think I've ever heard someone
Seriously suggest
I'm going to say something that most people don't really understand
Irony
Trump
Is it he's really a nice guy
Afraid of firing people
Ironically
Melania is the one I would go to because she's the person I would trust the most came out of a communist
System speaks fortified language
She knows exactly what's going on in the White House
So now we're going to have Melania fire everybody
This spirals out of control two levels
That I don't think anybody could ever imagine
In his neck
You were afraid I was going to I was going to your Starsky have your felberg of nowhere
Somebody just said that we should
All of this power to Milan
Talk about that a little bit more in this life
Please stop listening
Speak it with the kids call this is these dudes are being horny on Main is that the term
Some people use
Melania's 1in the most
Inserting a beautiful
Super hot women
Great
This is great this is great stuff man I just rather
These guys are so gross
Like at one point Alex is like
Yeah this isn't like one of those normal shows where people talk about that
Bulshit this is realpolitik
You guys are just talking about how hot you should fire everybody
Turn me on
But also
She's big
Halo mask
I could intimidate
Just get in there I'm not intimidated normally
Yeah but the issue is
Trump needs more Ruthless People in their viewing Melania is possibly a ruthless
Person
And Steve also brings up like she knows about communism
Whatever
B r b
It's kind of funny that it makes me think
Steve B B
I'm trying to get at is we need to have
People in there
It sounds bizarre
Supposed
Top Cash
No it's not he's he's sweet he's been sweet to everybody hehehe
My wife
Piano to congratulate
Couple years ago
Congratulations but honestly you and I
Whites are expensive electron to the next one
Yikes
Steve why is there expensive
The old crow Taqueria legere
Bitter bitter
Is the word I would use for that
Call boy
Oh congratulations wives lyrics.
Old creepy
These two guys together
I just Trucking gross gross old man there's no other way to put it
I think is where we get into like
Real Dane
It's real silly for him to be like you know the lawn you should fire everybody
Dumb
Whatever
This actually is advocated I guess you could say that like firing everybody of the state department and stuff
Should anyone ask
Act on that
Incredibly
Yeah but not this is all right
You are out of line
Is the Trump really needs to clean out his cabinet
And without any excuse I need an attorney general who can
Higher and higher I can't wait for the judicial
Great believer in judges I am a great believer in an attorney general
ASAP
Literally doodoo process is one of the defining features of the West according to Alex along with private property owned
Owning guns and Free Speech
The very idea that you would allow someone to come on his show and express a desire to do away with due process is
Incredibly tell
You can't be philosophically in favor of due process and the Constitution did not allow that she
The stand
But of course Alex has been completely humbled by Steve
And now Steve can do whatever the f*** he wants on this show
Stephen Alex didn't ever really agree on a whole lot anymore you think about it
Alex thought they did because he was f****** with him for years and blinding him with flattery
But now Alex is much closer to Stevens Point of View
Wanting to perform an internal coup
Usher enough of power
Now that Alex is reasonably certain that the president who would become the authoritarian ruler
Is primarily Sim
Sympathetic to heterosexual white Christian males
You don't really give a
That's kind of like
Fermenting a coup to create an authoritarian state
Kind of in line
With a lot of the
The stuff that Steve has been primarily interested in for a long time
Provided it's the right kind of ruler
So now they're far more in line than they used to
Alex has been brought to that level
We're going to Steve
You can come on if you like to process doesn't work
And Alex to be like
Made my career yelling about due process
But you know what degree with you on everything rid of it would defeat the globalist
You know you've gotten to this point where everything
Think you stand for me
Nothing
The more I think about it the more inclined I am towards the belief
Steve is very responsible for the situation Alex
Susan right now
Like I mean he completely f***** up Alex's life
Is what I mean
It was Steve who first gave Alex
The supposed inside information that confirms his conspiracies about 9/11
It was Steve was the first person to tell Alex
The victims and survivors of Sandy Hook were all actors
It was Steve who helped convince
Alex to support Trump
By telling a b******* stories of a coup in a counter-coup that
Needed Alex's help
If we're going to make it
We need your help
If you text
Steve out of the equation of Alex's show he probably wouldn't have made nearly as much money over
Overtime but you also never would be in this sorry State he is in now
He got f***** over by a manipulative psychopath
And now because I want to slow dance
Turn audience
He's got to go crawling back to that same toxic influences he managed to avoid for over a year
Then for what
Most of Steve's videos on YouTube get like 20,000 views
If that's enough for Alex to go chasing
And come to the point where you like letting someone be like
Due process doesn't work
Alex's in way worse shape than we were even
Yeah
Man it just
Ever
Say the time
Type of government that he would
Prefer
I mean you just call it a republic
Yeah you're fine I mean
Literally
A fascist
He's like a combination of the corporate spy Ajax with an authoritarian leader
Yeah what is the
What we should
To do is we should have a
Small group of oligarchs
Wauconda politburo
And will have them all fight each other for my approval
And if they lose it
Then I will kill them and erase them from photographs
There's if this leader that we have is a business person who's directly altering the way they operate in order to further their
Business
Nobody's ever seen
Corrupt billionaires
It's deals are mutually
Xclusive definitely didn't set one up and Rush
Cheats
Is Christ
Yeah I mean
Yeah that's the reality of like what Steve want
And yeah
Presenting it as there is this
Cool of the Yale globalist or whatever
It's such
Just serious thing that we need to do all of the
This stuff that's counter to
What Arkansas
The fusions are based on
Operating as in order to eliminate this threat
That's
Lasek
Dictatorship the only way to save the
The tution is to
Temporarily
Suspended entirely
Temporarily we just got it look we're going to put it to put a pause
And then we'll bring it right back once we get everything cleared up don't worry
It's just going to be a dictatorship
That works
The world
So earlier we heard
Steve say that the Epstein still alive
Talk about that a little more now
Anna
I think he's starting to swim
Didn't die in prison
Nobody
There's a big deal to have you cuz I respect you and you don't
So wow
Yeah Alex is starting to come around to that that which is crazy
You don't BS on air if it weren't for you I would
Know that
Osama bin Laden died from Marvin Sapp
All of the things that I can think of that were major
Gas
Analysis career a lot of them have to do with Steve same bulshit on air
But he hasn't been on the show in over a year because he said that the Las Vegas shooting didn't happen right
That's b******* that he said on air
Yeah his whole career is defined by bulshit that he says on air
I guess the family of apes
Aunt Sue him for
For defamation by
Listing that he's alive
And I suppose that's
Probably not
I suppose I suppose they're in the clear with that law
Fly
It starts out with Steve saying some slurs
About lesbians
In relation to Hillary so heads up for that
Any pivots in
To defending
Trump being
Incredibly corrupt
And is it that I personally couldn't care less she was highly complex
United Airlines
Again bonus miles
Highly compromised
Mainland Chinese
My CIA operatives came when he won the election against Bush
And said to me
In New Hampshire be able to be praising I Stay
And they said he robbed the election
Yep corruption
Permeating
He's a businessman he's a businessman
Those are the exact type of people that like
Happy corrupt
So now let's just say okay
Now what
Oh no
Let's just
Well then in that case of course it's okay the personal brand is a bird that is corruption on all sides
Dad and with trumpet
Fine if he's corrupt
It's with other people who don't have a white mask
Nationalist agenda I don't their corrupt I'm very mad about I don't disagree that there is corruption
All around
And plenty to go around on both sides
I don't disagree with that prescription at all
I take issue with
Top is cool with it.
Cuz he's a businessman
Go fuc yourself
That is such a flimsy lineup
We cannot have public servants
Be corrupt
But if your business when your business man come on we're just doing some business
So
Alex takes the opportunity of having
Devon to ask him a little bit about Q
Qanon
And they both
To have the
Impression that it's not good because it gives false hope
Which is interesting I hate
It's interesting because I don't
Totally disagree with that on some level
But the problem is
They are against this false hope
Because they need
Trump to be ruthless
Again is about firing all these people
I just
Don't like things
Everything's wonderful stick with the plan
Invincible they're all about to go to prison
And then it doesn't happen
And the things are true
When we're really working and really getting things done and exposing moles in the White House
CDs
Welders this nebulous
Imperial that you got about out too it's a 4chan board
That's all I'm saying is
People need to know that
Is in perilous times
And that he needs to be pressured to take action as you said because that you can take the action is the president
The mythical thing telling you that actions been taken
I agree with you because I'm saying that the following people were arrested and this is going to come out now
Alex
Alan wants to remain president and he's got to beat
He's got to be tough
He has to what he has to do because
She and I think a wife
What the f***
Steve has decided that he and Melanie are simpatico they're on the same page
This is the ramblings of a
I thought it was crazy before
I thought it was crazy but him just being like a
Fun like usual suspects kind of crazy words
Grab games and having a grand old time coming up with ways to try and like stop the news
Gioconda Jen do that
Melania
I have no doubt in my mind
Melania thinks like me
Is the
I don't think anybody says that
It's it's pretty trouble
Planet who has
Interesting things I never expected that Steve would come back on after over a year of being gone
And a lot of it would be about how great Melania is and how Trump needs to get her to fire everybody
Because he's too weak to do itself
He is really delivering on the promise of Steve pieczenik feedback on info
Yeah and here is the cherry on top of Melania story
National Security advisor
Melania
She would be the key point in that
Okay so we got
Melania in is a national security advisor we got Jon Huntsman and his secretary of state because he's
Richard boarman
Mitt Romney we got Steve pieczenik doing something where he yells at everybody in fire site will
This is not a good White House
I can
I can't think
Of a worst government
Then whatever it is
Steve pieczenik
What is the best gun
Yeah that's pretty bad
Yeah that's an accomplishment
Yeah yeah
In some ways to have the worst idea is better than two
Did just have a bad I
It's impressive
Yeah we have one last clip and it's Steve
Expressing with his expectation
Can was when Trump got elected
Doesn't stop
Control
TubeMate
Begging
Is
He'd be what he was supposed to be from the very beginning
Ruthless without any explanation or any rationalization
That's all we asked of him the minute he does he will come in on 20/20
If he has
Call Betsy Ross
We put them in there to be a strong man
Consolidate power that really is maybe they
The best
Explanation for his
Voter bases like
We elected you to be our ID
Yeah we are we elected you to be the swirling mass of hate and
Tents
May act as a wrecking ball again
That's the sort of
What we would call liberal social games that have been made over the last
5060 years
Rollback all kinds of protect
For vulnerable communities
Takeaway reproductive Healthcare you know do all of this stuff that we want done
Don't answer questions about why you're doing it yet never apologize
And if you do that we will be
Be totally fine with you sure enough all the power that you want Act
Chicken the most corrupt ways imaginable
Who gives a s***
And you know what the problem is always doing
Corrupt
I may still have to defend them that's a bummer for that
Steve are melania's NSA would certainly help quite a bit
The f*** are we
Yeah
Yep
After what the clips I want explain to you why I think that this episode is such a good demonstration
The holistic awfulness of Alex's
Throughout this episode we seen a very clear example of five distinct behaviors
Alex engages in regularly that are destructive to the public Consciousness and discourse
The first is that he creates narrative
Wheatley and
Totally out of thin air
That are
Separate from real
We saw this and Alex's insistence that Hillary Clinton is secretly running for president and is announced the
But she gets
This isn't real but Alex needs it to be real because it's
Easier for him to work against this imagination of Hillary
Beneduce room
Create a whole new villain out of Elizabeth Warren
Or to try and figure out how to thread the needle about Bernie
I guess just too difficult for him
Hillary Clinton
An evergreen bad guy
So he creates a fictional reality
People get to live in
The second is whitewashing and strawmanning for races
We saw this announced yelling about Disney
Putting warnings on their movies about racist
What you pretended we're just we're warnings
But heteronormative
We further saw this into way he turned a story about that Bristol hospital withdrawing treatment
Racist into a story about tonight
Care for right winger
This is a clear pattern that he has whitewashing
Strawmanning
Turning them into different issues
So the audience
Is comfortable insta
Supporting racism
Pretending they're doing
Something else
Yeah I with that one
What I
What I find
So clear now is
I don't even know if he's
Emergence
Be doing this reflects
Sibley and it may have been
At first but now I just
See him as like
Actually associate
Getting those two together it might be
Just purely like hey if you're not letting me say racist
Texas things
You are discriminating a
Right-wingers possible
The effective it is the same it really doesn't matter if it's so conscious
I think he just doesn't even know anymore
It's an academic question
I'm not sure
The third element is overt on hand
Understand completely wrathful bigotry
He's screaming about trans people or drag performers being so
Satanic aliens is a level of hate that is so far past what any decent person would consider acceptable
His claims that he's not a bigot
She claims that
What are you doing flies so far past just
It's outright in
Incitement
It's important for people to understand that element to his rider
The fourth thing is that Alex is a dumb f***
Conspiracy theorist
But he's super smug about those things everything that s*** up
He's a Wizard of Oz
Hiding behind imaginary folders full of evidence he'll never show you
Alex seduces his audience into believing he knows what he's talking about with that mystery folder and a couple of headlines
As it appeared to be in line with his conspiracies but
Definitely art
As a sub-point on this one we also see how Alex is very often using his conspiracy theories that he spreads for his own son
Selfish purposes
The only reason you did that whole dumb chemtrail segment is because he wants to go back on Rogan's podcast
To get more listeners we don't go broke
He's been so enabled and rewarded for this order
From tationil bulshit behavior in the past
Mixtiles
Nothing like this again
Absolutely
The last element
Is platforming dangerous lunatic
Steve pieczenik is completely insane
These masquerades around as an expert
Injustice episode these are the things he's put forth while being presented as a respect
Edible credible
Epstein isn't dead
Putin the super awesome and Russia should have Crimea
The entire State Department should be fired
Trump should eliminate the intelligence
Melania should be made Nationals
Security advisor
Trump gets to be as corrupt as he wants because he's a business
We should get rid of due process
And Trump needs to ruthlessly Shore up our overall areas of the government
A person advocating stuff like this isn't
Same extremist
They're supporting positions that are a direct contradiction to the foundations of our
Constitution
Enter the exact sort of things you B
To hear from someone who's trying to install attic
But instead of presenting the situation honest
Play It's presented as if the things you're pushing for her actually
Support of democracy
In the will of the people
This is very basic propaganda stuff
You install a strongman Dictator by created
The perception that a greater evil
You know they exist
The only strongman dictator can
It's literally what these dudes are doing
These are the five elements
Veterans so consist
Through Alex's
Career that are put on
Start display on this November 13th episode
And I recognize Alex Jones
Is not the most relevant person in the world
His reach isn't nearly what it wasn't past years and all indications seem
To suggest that he's gone bro
And that's fair
But I don't think that it makes this any less concern
These 5 bullet points
Are not unique
To Alex
And the thing is
This is
Like it's not like
I'm kind of a special episode where Alex
Decided to play the hits
Most of his jokes
Contains most or all of these elements
It was just particularly glaring when I was listen
Some of this episode today worthwhile to bring an added Focus
These are consistent and regular planks
Of his program
And they're all talks
To the health of public discourse
Alex Jones going off air won't solve any of these
They've gone far too mainstream at this point
And you see these same patterns
The countless other conspiracy in
Extremist Jose
I could be incredibly wrong about this but
Imagining that any single one of those Outlets going away
Isn't going to do any good you know
It's just not
But understanding how they operate and why they operate the way they do
Seems like it might be a way.
Take power out of this prop
So
I just wanted to put that bow on this in
Reflect
A little V
It's so obvious
On this episode
The thief specific
Discreet
Things that are being done
It's almost even segments
You know the khazar is the portion where he's doing the Race
The hospital or around the same part of the show
Then a whole segment of conspiracy theory
Bulshit
Steve pieczenik gets a good hour at the end of the show
There is there is almost like all right we're hitting these bases
And it's not always like that
A lot of times it too much more scattershot throughout the episode
It's a smaller but he did hire the program man
Colbert
So everything is really structured pretty well there's a
Solid situation there
Do you do your point about
Getting rid of these media
Empires creator
Solely to push this
Propaganda
I think that goes right back
To where we are with weather weaponry
That is The Logical endpoint of our curiosity
It is not going to it is not going to just go away the
Is there
There it requires last doing something
Where is learning
Control restraint
Constant watch
Parallel for what you were talking about with other weapon
Would be like outlawing
This kind of research
And that is the sort of things that I think is detrimental to
Humanity brighten the same way out or something
Dangerous
Kind of tone
In the world than good
Whereas
Everyone doing
Deep soul-searching about how you use x technology
Everybody doing some
Some hard work
Maybe maybe it's not that hard on understanding
How this manipulation
A long way towards
Allowing this to steal
Exist in the world
Increasing the possibility that it can be effectively used
DJ Lance
And maybe
That's not Eva
Yeah maybe
What is the position I'm living in right now
I don't know if that'll cheer
But it's the sort of conclusion
I find myself
Laundry list of things that he would prefer in a government
Is that
It seems like
If somebody else
What's gives you 1
Of those same
But they would desire you know if somebody's like I want Trump to have that too
Control and Fire
People in be more ruthless
You can guess the
They're also on board with a few of of the other one
Maybe not Melania Trump being at SC but
Call me also Imagine imagine the reaction that Steve or Alex would have if like
Some Obama surrogate
Boston process
If Obama nominated
Michelle to
Any position it would be
Yeah it would be an armed Resurrection right
To the
These sorts of things that are so far beyond the pale of
Acceptable
Become acceptable because you know you got your guy
Exact you got the guy who is going to
Your interests
Secure
Wow attacking
Or allowing a text
Two vulnerable communities that you want
To be targeted
As long as he does
You want him to do you cook
A blind eye to every
Even as he destroys you because
Con man
Same way that you're at
These people are
So stupid it's a mess
And fun as some of these Steve coming back
Is Dora's real f******
Messed up thing
That he's suggesting and pushing on the show and Alex's seconding
And allowing to be presented as credible which is a real f****** mess
And I hate it
The same time I would be lying if I said
That it wasn't way more fun to live
Listen to this episode
Not the part where he's yelling about trans people being demons
But like the part where
Steve is on is so much more listenable
Then
What are you saying
You put in poop
And here's a
It's dark
It's real dark and
Maybe if you took it if
You took it anywhere near as seriously as you would that f****** okay
A guy segment
You be like
This s*** is
Is terrifying
Steve
Interesting
Character
Pinata
You're calling for a dictatorship in the end of the Constitution to Tire lady
Crazy you're crazy for this one story
You keep it going
Welcome back Steve
Monday
Another episode but until then
Jordan website
Yes we are also on
Twitter
Can I go to bed
You betsworth on Facebook we are on Facebook
Download the show or share it with
Somebody please go to iTunes
And so on and so
Fourth other pie
Reviews
Sure
Emilio Emilio I'm PCS Clark project
Stormfury
Holding
Alex