Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
This is a podcast
Where me and a friend
Very
Consistently and regularly by co-host
Jordan sit down and drink red wine
And talk about The Life and Times of episode
And Jordan has a show
So I have brought the returning replacement Jordan
That was not grass hello good to be here
Thank you for great to have you back in studio
You know what we've each got our own bottle
3% 1
Yeah oh yeah it says applewine on it I love it says flavored Apple
On the casing has work
Google
Secret
They tell you a secret shameful stories
You are a very first one and you are one of the people who has actually done.
I have
You got
But that might be because I quit
I might be a part of it
Problem with you guys on the road a bit too
Leave your on the podcast at least one I think I said don't put those stories
Tell the story that may or may not have laps
In terms of the statute of limitations for I stole something
Stories are so good I just assumed that they must be out there
Alex motherfuking Jones middle name
We're going to be talking about it
I want to do a little
That we like to do it like to give a shout out to our new donate or what's up
Congratulations
It's just the word
Okay they are officially a policy wonk soufeel congratulations you're now in the weeds
Policy and
The world
The next time I come I would love if you had a button in the work
Yes absolutely work working this morning Zoo about Alex Jones perfect
That's what I want
Tyler a little bit of an update
I wanted to do previously on
I told you before we started recording that Alex's life is about to fall apart
And here's why
First of all he lost his
He lost custody of his children last week
That's going to
Slowly deteriorate is mine
Additionally
Chobani yogurt
Asthma put out a lawsuit on him
You didn't know about this so I put out a new story then the headline of it was
Idaho yogurt maker Imports migrant rapist
Which was about the guy who owns Chobani
Very big donator for Refugee, it was all such slander
Yo they're suing him
Very bad
Forever recording
On Thursday
Alex is
Just now wrapping up
836 hour or so live broadcast
Why is this a special occasion
AP need money
It's a 36-hour live infomercial it's like QVC bicycle
What is he in
Keeping him awake also caveman bone broth
That's a new product since you've been here and I kind of get into
You just desperately need money
It's clear he's going to get sued
So hard you going to lose every
And
Like
Couple days back
He accidentally let slip on are that Mike cernovich has sources
And some of his sources
Where Donald Trump's children
They were feeding them information
What is a crime
I can't believe Aaron was
Francoli
Flip on the air
Some pieces of it most of it was bulshit
I said Donald Junior was
Delphine crnkovich information at
Listen
I had it wrong like okay
Right
Right buddy
I don't know what to believe it's completely lying about the retraction
Or he could have been lying anyway
I have no f****** idea
Thunderdome
Cruises out the window everything is possible
Christine
So today we're going to be
A video that played during
The 30-hour broadcast
Who's the special report that Alex put out
On Monday
I'm a repurposed
I just played a bunch of time
It wasn't even a 30-hour live broadcast it just kept playing video
So anyway this video
Was it was
Special Report
Facebook
Is targeting trendy's and cuc
Trendys
Trendy
I don't know what that means
Well you're one of them cuz you got a mustache
We're going to get into specifically what the trendy's are over the course of this video
Incredibly pissed off
About Facebook
How many loses the thread and starts yelling about a bunch of other stuff
I'm pretty certain he's on some sort of amphetamine
He seems
Beats out of his mind he's shooting this in his bedroom
And it's gorgeous bedroom it's huge
He is very rich for now
Yeah for now he's going to lose that bet
Very soon
Getting up
I'm sitting down and like pacing around
He's on some sort of
It's crazy
Anyway
Millennium started off
Okay this is how it begins the report
My friends
Zuckerberg working with the CIA
Set up
Facebook
Google was also set up by the CIA
Search CIA funding
12 master
For social engineering
4 control
That's come out the Wikileaks Democratic party Republican Party
Globalist
Zuckerberg was 6 years ago
Set a conference I can't believe our users trust us they're a bunch of dumb
And then I see
The difference
Facebook acts like they're open and free and follow the rules
Libertarian are nationalistic
Target
Facebook to share your post
Force-feed
Are they cut off are you was going to say they force-feed liberal ship
So
Here we go this is the beginning the introduction of his promise
Facebook stock
You got to get out of Colonel there that I'm going to agree with him on
But then he goes on
That that whole thing about like Facebook isn't allowing us to share things
Misrepresenting how Facebook works
Post something to your fan page
You probably like
Couple thousand fans
I would assume
Call work
You post something on your fan page
And if you don't promote it
Only
20 people will see
Because they want you to pay for it to be promoted
Right they restrict
How many of your own fancy your s***
It's just how it works
It's an advertising platform
Right
Masquerading as a social network
Cher age
And you have to get multiple people to do it and if you do that then it starts to
Spiral
I am to get posted on more people's walls cuz there's
Organic interest
Right so Alex doesn't understand
That's it that's the feature
Social network
Make money
That's the game
So he thinks it's because he's spouting libertarian views
And all this put it
It just
Incredibly stupid
Some more bad stuff
About Facebook I didn't true
But
Before he does that man have to
I do think Facebook is bad
Facebook
Return to solitude
You spout like bulshit opinions
Often it's
Lightship the people are posting
The whole idea of virtue signalling that the alt-right likes
Throw around
The idea of like you really believe the principal Post online
You're just doing that
To Signal your virtues to your like-minded friends
Beyonce
Is that a crow
Critique of the left
Yes okay
They all of this stuff about like gay rights
Send
It's not sincere you're just trying to show your Bona fides
If your friends
I don't think that most of
Is that right
But
Facebook does suck it it's
Temperature
I've got no Facebook I love it
I think I think people should leave it
Your life is better listening
Alex Jones
Look
There might be a one-to-one correlation
I got on Facebook and immediately started listen to Alex Jones everyday
And my mental state has never been better I barely leave the house
I think Facebook is awful if I was not
In the
If I was not
A person who pursuing comedy I'd I wouldn't
Yeah
But it's weird to
It's weird to look at somebody be like
Yahoo Facebook too
You headed for the wrong
Globalist
I'm sick of seeing other people's
Head-to-head game
Yeah I'm psychodrama
Uncooked chicken cuz I might get sick
We're technically on the same side
But we're not on a team
It goes on to complain some more about Google and tell me about we talk about in the past
Hillary Clinton propaganda in garbage
Secret documents
Butter Google said yeah
We had Road contract
Multimillion-dollar contract
Delisting infowars.com
They said they stopped
Alex your fake news Sumi
Sumi I dare you
You're fake f****** news
I can prove it
And I have
Repeatedly
You dumb son of a b it's kind of the whole nature of the podcast
Fake news cuz they're afraid that he's going to put them
That's not true at all
Google has very weak lawyer
The streets further telling me about these documents we got from Mike cernovich
That were about
He is another one of these propaganda dickholes
He's a he's a guy he has his own
Call danger and play
Dynamiter and play
Oh yeah it's it it sounds way more like that than a right-wing bigots
That blog
But
It was involved in like
He was involved in gamergate
All the current date recently broke the story about Susan Rice unmasking peep
Unmasking Trump
Campaign people
In the intelligence reports that was the real story
That sort of s*** that's what he's on
Donald Trump's children
Yeah
One way or another
Beginning of
First clip
Recover your own trasar
That's one thing that you're going to be does this a lot and especially in this episode
Whenever he says this public
This is been Declassified
Everyone knows this
It's in mainstream news
Any of those four things you know it's a lie
Just a hundred percent is a f****** lie
He's just making s*** up that maybe a caller told him a week early
That's basically
Before we got started
What is a friend
Rice
I'm starting to feel
It's not a possum
Yeah I got
If this clip
Explains
About is mostly about
So many explain
On specifically what they are
I meant he gives a dubious
Historical lesson about proper
The Democrat special
Need to understand this really affects
Facebook
Has been caught with internal documents leaking
Systemcare
England and Australia
Young as the Press
As vulnerable and as trendy
Turn
What is a friend
We'll get back to that
First
Example of what
No not really
The report came out recently a couple days ago about
Facebook
Targeting
People that they
Viewed as sort of week
And
More impressionable more vulnerable
People
Alex is saying it is going to lay out is that they were doing this in order to make them liberal
Recruiting liberal
Vulnerable people on Facebook
The truth is
At worst
It's an advertising strategy
It's much like
Putting
Sugary cereal commercials during cartoons
City toy commercials during cartoon
You basically
So you going to make it seem really evil
Ears with
Actually was
The company
Facebook said claims made about targeting site users were quoting this
But his investigation would be launched into the matter
In the statement Facebook stock quote
The analysis done by an Australian researcher was intended to help marketers understand how people
Express themselves on
It was never used to Target
It was based on data that was Anonymous and aggregated
I believe that but I also don't believe them wasn't for Market
You don't mean right it's off
Absolutely helping marketers understand how people Express themselves if it wasn't for marketing
Yeah that's insane
So that part II believe them and I don't believe them
And I don't believe
Now he also said that they targeted 700,000
That is
Because that the specifics
But I can't rate
That is nothing to do with it
That has to do with Facebook what they did in 20
Do you remember that
So he pulled a number from
Disassociating
Well they're both Facebook things that are kind of weird
But they're not the same thing he's leaving issues
The 700,000 users
Was when they were trying to see if they could sway people's moods
By posting positive or negative stories
Without people permission
Weather
Based on
Keywords that could determine where positive or negative
They would take people and they would post
Primarily negative things on their wall and see what things they would pose
To see if it would affect their mood
Now the research was done
Technically isn't illegal
It's f***** up
Published
You know like research Journal
They were doing it for
Theoretical scientific reason
Bucked up
That has nothing to do with this
Alex is just an idiot and everything Facebook does is all one big
Kill people that dance
Those were
Muslims becoming radicalized
Shaklee
Procase off building stat is
Orthodoxy
He believes are the cultural avant-garde
Coolest people
What is conformist
Be a man Crouch
The system then puts out a plastic artificial in Crown and talk about this forever
Wall Street and Madison Avenue
Hollywood
Has talked about 4
Help
To merge
Government officials
With media
To make the Hollywood stars and to make the political Stars
About
And the media Mania like they're the upper-class
There's a beautiful people.
Once you feel like you're not part of the in class
Greek gods
Or
Elysium
And you just don't think you can attain it
This is Unstoppable
I don't know why that's why buildings are big
Another point though I kind of I kind of I'm cool
I'm cool with that Alex
Like I don't I don't entirely disagree with you I think celebrity culture is kind of shity
There is a whole thing about celebrity worship other ring
You know I'm I'm not as good as that
Instagram models
Tastemakers
Great
Something interesting about the trendy so is Bailey anybody
Is what he
Probably
What what I'm saying really to
Thing is
Are we so far it seems like
He has
Attack
Basic capitalism like marketing
Religious conservatism a couple time
Is it normal for him but he doesn't realize
Wealthy thing but loves the free-market loves capitalism
Love's Christianity
But hey
The church
But I don't think the things that you're picking up on
I don't think he even realizes
Are implied in his word
Must not be
Being
Like
People who gravitate
Towards
The mainstream thing
I'm 33 years old that is literally never been the case in my life
Cool are the people who break away right and are rebellious or have their own thing
He's like trying to describe
What being a hipster is
It's going towards
Radical Main Street
I think so yeah
It's convoluted
This is starting out a little bit slow
In terms of what Alex's say
I promise you the ball is going to start rolling and it's going to speed up
Standards of
What being
Trendy is
Yeah it's going to start almost immediately
Flip out
Get down to the brass tacks
Explain what
He thinks is going on in the world
Visa V trendy
Where they target
Young people who go on Facebook or who they see is alone
Christina is needing friends
Political systems certain products
We can bombard women
Larger puzzle
6 products
The list goes on and on and all I'm saying is
None of that is in any of the stories that I've been able to find about Facebook stuff
Jack Sharone Alex's Park
He makes all of his money selling weird supplements
Set reminder
Commercials about how you and this modern world
His bone broth can give it back to you
Like it's completely insane
What are you doing what are you doing
Do not be fooled by this but I really need you to pay for this nice bedroom with that
That's not your problem what you really need is for female vitality
What is a
Don't lick it so obvious
I can't imagine anybody watching this
And not being like
He's up to some
I trust this guy
Crazy
Anyway he goes on
Because I'm a little bit
People that buy in the trendy culture
Kitchen kapers
It's an
Augmentation
Changing
Body modification movement
Microchips in virtual reality
Initial programming
The funding of the whole body
To get you to accept that
In the sixties ugly are
To make you confused and think will you don't know what's beautiful art and what's what's ugly
Scrambling of social mores
Ugly architecture
Austerity collapse
There it is again
Murals of masculine men at colleges
The football team
Elementary School entry form
Seiji or Z because someone might have a mommy or daddy C
You can't have anything
Somebody else
He goes on to
Failing lie reference
Oasis to teach
Short story
Well he goes on to miss miss name it uses like herizen bums around or something like that
Butt stuff
The greater butts have to be impaired somehow
List there at the end
IR cockamamie
Turn on fan
I Googled a minute
There's no evidence the people are trying to band masculine murals on campus
Because some people are as a pronoun
It isn't
Like saying that he or she is bad
It's just
Offering a third option
For people who identify another way
If you feel depressed by someone else's inclusion
That's your problem
That's not that's not the person who wishes to be seen a certain way of problem
So
I don't know man
I mean
Progressive issue and that is exactly
You know
Call Jones's of the world
Is there's a new thing
It hurts my feelings
Learn about think there is a piece of it.
I wish I was
Not specifically because he like Alex wants to be a z
Or whatever
But because
He's like I wish I had that
Mention of being deaf
I think I was going to say either it's like
I desire to be different a desire to
Be included
Or
Where to
I mean clearly
Regardless of where he lands anywhere gorgeous mansion
People Like Us don't understand
My plate
Alex Jones in actuality
These aren't human
It's it's
Otter lunacy
Goddamn
Yeah the Trenton
Trump
Say that but he does get into
He's elated at what he think
This is about
Can get a little more specific in this next clip
I got to stay ahead of time I don't agree with him
I don't agree with his assessment
Here
This is the total oppression of the hot mine
Are these documents where
I won't let you leave Facebook if you want to
They're selling your data they're calling you a dumbass
Iowa Facebook nonstop me
That thing about them calling you dumb a
He brings this up a bit is that in their condolences email whenever you quit
No just walked up when you leave Facebook pictures
And they're like they're going to miss you if you leave it sort of
It's a little manipulative but if you leave
They don't stop you
He claims
Summit
Mark Zuckerberg said the people who use Facebook are dumb sucker
That's not true
What actually happened was when he was 26
Facebook was still sort of growing
Abet
He told a friend in a private message
That he can't believe the people trust him
They're dumb Fox
She isn't gone on record
I was young I didn't know what's going on I definitely wouldn't
Say that sort of thing now
And maybe that's just good PR
But
Sure
Of course you're dumb
If you decide
Dumbfuckery for being on Facebook
Most people wouldn't believe all the stuff out there that I do
Hey they know a lot of s*** about me this private business
Too much information about
That's why I
Again he's misrepresenting s***
Anyway
This moves into
We see what Islam
Really
So let me
Show me Australian
Facebook
When normally would meet
And some type of
Culturally successful group
To be successful
Cultural icons
Farms
Different globalist enclaves in the broken strategy
They're all scared
And always safe place your group
A lot of words
Oh yeah
What are you what are you really feel about that
Think think I've been cooked
Of course
That's the that's the overarching
You know conspiracy
Is being cocked by Islam
That's sort of a big thing is on
What is that I don't know what that mean
I feel like I know what cuckold
I know like it
The word
A guy whose wife is cheating on him and everyone knows it
How does a nation confrontation pornography
I don't care at all
That's the way he's using it more okay people are like white women are being taken over by mine
And the white man
Last time you were on you asked me if I thought Alex Jones was a supremacist
Yeah and I said I didn't know
In the last few months I'm pretty sure
Your is leaning one way towards supremacist
Yeah
Got shown a little bit of those flavors
He's referring to
You cock in
Fetishize
Finley ND
Specifically racist
Specifically
Yeah the other thing I forgot to bring us up
He keeps trying to say that Facebook is trying to make you into
Secure and all this stuff
And maybe that is accurate based on that 2012 study that they did
Pitstop
Stop doing that
That one
Fairly accurate
Vishnu
Obviously marketing research
Already Express insecure vulnerable feeling
But again
Not targeted at anybody
Aggregated
Anonymous stuff
Anyway
Cocking
Islam
These are important
Thing
Then we'll come back out
But before they do
Alex's got to get into his next point
Which
I did
Highlights College
You didn't
Alex Jones
That's correct
Do you want to I think about a year of Community College and then dropped out
That's important
Because this next clip Alex Jones explains what's going on on college campuses
Perfect as an expert on the subject and haven't gone to a community college
This years ago
Yeah
Major colleges in Europe
Scared kid show up from the countryside
Homophobe
Come to our group you'll be safe here
Disadvantage
Motorcycle game
Except
I mean your professors and their props and their assistants are the new boss
That's absurd
That's patently absurd
That's why I only have a few professors in my time at college that I interacted with in any meaningful way outside of
And they get no way swayed by
Political beliefs my
Sense of self
Inspired me and directions of that I was already interested
Didn't say ancient Greek
Or logic
These are things that I studied in college were because
Largely I responded to the teaching style of the professor
It was something I was already interested in
They have
Logic in college
Paul Wyrick
Was just an update an amazing way of speaking about something so Bland and dry
As formal logic
I got really interested in it and I took it took like three years worth of classes
From him and then went on to study Game Theory
Free classes that you taught
I really like this style
I had
Couple Greek professors an awesome I ended up translating The Iliad in college
I had no intention of doing that because
I really like the professor that audit and
They didn't they were
Bosses
My dad is a professor
I've grown up around
Academia
Professor
The Alex Jones
Is community college professor movie
Trump's doctor
If I'm lucky
But yeah
Experience with colleges Wyoming professors in
None of this is one of those Rings true
It's absurd it's fear
He's suggesting that like groups
Are the equivalent
If joining a
Race game
Yep
Missouri State University
That's the third most dangerous game
Yeah there's MS-13 up top does the blood
Lmsd Student Activity
And let me tell ya we
We killed some people over to Truman State and we threatened
Is going to come for you
You know what it is it all comes from
It comes from it he brings it up even people come from the countryside or whatever they go down
And when they do they shed a lot of their conservative values because they're exposed to diversity they meet people who are deaf
Different
It was a lot more
And you're now a rocket a trendy mustache
My main personality feet
This is the gateway to trendiness mustache
Oh yeah it's it's
Did the conservatives fear of losing your children
Well we would say reason
Different
He's not nearly done
With explaining what's going on in college
Of course not
Lisa liberal campus
Development
All the way up to that point
And then once you get to them at like 20 years old or so
You're allowed to develop
Don't like
What to be the wrong person system
Put them into the system
Take advantage
Bees
And who want to be part of the whole system you want to laugh at everyone is it part of orthodox
Are you starting to get the cosmology of bettas
Are going to become trendy
Alphabet
I I think there is a little bit of Baden this coming out in him
Shirt
Is an alpha being afraid of bettas
Right now it is just
Yap-yap
Ioi
I don't even know how to really
Address
His promise
Police let you
Beat up people and you go through a rite of passage according to their whims
He's just talking about Burke
He's just talkin about the bike
He's just imagining what happens
If you wanted a real case you should I mean
Something close about like having a jack off
He doesn't talk about that song
About as far as
Missouri
There was
Yeah
Teo Yoo
While I was there to hillbilly dude
Are they
What do the Legion of black collegians building
Had a whole bunch of bottles of Tylenol took all the cotton out of them
And covered their yard with cotton
Anti-racist gesture
That's how I was pretty pretty bad
On a wall
There's tons of stuff like that that happens
Not everything is fake
Is what I'm getting out of
Yeah there's some assholes
Yeah and I am people who
Like
Gravitate towards liberal causes aren't
Just mad about nothing
Right yeah
So
Alex you don't know what's going on on colleges
At this point
He gets back to his ideas about Islam
A little bit
Oh good I've been waiting
His hot takes this is very unfortunate
But he always calls
I noticed
It's I think it's very subtle disra
Respect
I think
But he has a lot of real
Thoughts about them
In this next treating you
Look at that
They put a
Symbol of resistance
This is a few months ago
Eddie's women
Control over my image of myself within my own family
My mom started wearing the hijab when I was 13th
He's playing a video of Muslim girls in hijab
Talking about their relationship with it
And then he's going to once it's over just here in a second
Get back in.
Which is the wife
Probably 13 or 14 at the time
Angel my mother did
This is the right to do this
You are put in prison or killed in almost every Islamic country
Iraq
And cereal you didn't have to wear them in women with a majority of college students doctors in science
Thunder
Leftist globalist Arab Springs
Again that's been Declassified
Also they're not implying that it's a choice
They're literally staying
It's a choice
Those girls in that video
Alex's is wrong on
Also I'm going to take their word
I think over Allison
Them
I think I think so
You know what this is been
This is not as wacky as I wanted to be
Yeah I'm passing
Fully
Disgusted
Shock
I think that's the problem is there's a little bit of disgust a little bit of
August there's a lot of Islam
Right talk is never fun
It's a it's a little bit
That's hot
Haha
Area
This clip
Is Luna
Complaining about how he's being censored
And then it spins way off the rails
Nothing but he says in this clip is true
Keep that in mind
I think you'll know very clearly.
We got more visitors than blisters and ever
Infowars.com
Exploded
Google
They are all tightness down
You've got a hand posted on your site
You got a hand
With a whole fake liberal cosmology
Your smocks
They're laughing you
They think you're idiots
Multiple people
20 years old boo-boo boo-boo
A boo-boo
Are Beanie Boos
Your hands already in the wood chipper
Million-dollar
Always thinking
Give us 200000
35 million
Then you can come to the capital of Nigeria
The trendy bars
Judge years ago.
Which is a weird old East Austin
I am free
Facebook's the coolest thing ever
It's all a con
That's what Trinity ism is all about Barack Obama New World Order
So there's a lot.
Okay so first of all saying if you're like
If I should have a Facebook
None of your friends would be in with that.
Hey Tyler you get it
They be like are you in a bit or are you okay with that
What happened
Are you not well
I love the idea that was a multi-phase scam
Where you give him $1,000 and he actually does give you $5,000
Did he say he was with Mike Judge has one of those weirdos
People like Joe Rogan hang out with him to this
I don't know if you likes his philosophies or anyting but their friends
Apparently
That's
About the fact that there were people pretending to be Rothschild going to Austin Community College
The hardest game in the world
Yeah absolutely what you get to look cool
Pressure to party
Drapion
Yeah I know it is a bummer
But any said Trent it he went to Trinity Bar
East Asia
Probably
Yeah probably
Anything
Heterosexuals are moved out
Oh yeah I don't know
Yeah
Like the Nigerian dude showing up at the bar if it'll be like
Robinhood
Bar outside East Texas
What do you Sauced and there's no way
No absolutely not
So stupid
What is like literally
Friend tells you happy
It is like a weird bar never been to and like the outskirts of Austin even though I do
Brother in Everybody Loves
Which is weird because in my experience
I don't know where this guy was probably wasn't even Nigerian
So
Goddamn stupid I love it that's the kind of Alex Jones I love
I think that he's scatting around like that because he's on some sort of speed
But he's on something inside of me it's hard to do that
Normally
It's hard to do that just
It makes sense
The only other possibility is severe manic episode
Full of energy
But if you
In terms of wacky you know I did not ever weird stories
Rest assured this next clip
Is Justice crazy
He's going to start by talking about this story
Where to go that FBI translator ended up leaving the FBI
She married a nice
Alex is going to introduce that story
Talk nothing about it
Dunno analysis of it into none of the details
And then skip onto another
Wacky stories that I don't think is true
Liberal educated
She still fell in love with the Isis guys that sell sex slave to the slavery six-year-old girls
But she had to go.
Realizes
Anderson Cooper
He pushed the whole system
You're the Arab Spring with Google and Facebook
Secular government
Olivia
In Tunisia
In
Egypt
Is Syria and other try in Syria
Sonic
Report
Bono's
Thanks he wasn't celebrating you didn't go out there to like tailgate
These
These revolutions
On the job reporting
Iowa
Buildings
I walked into Target today
Lysol
To really
Barney Rubble and
Fled
Save yourself or just people freedom
I could all this conformist uniglobal of stuff's really really evil and Corruption
You really shouldn't be so scared
Research
Military Warfare
21 years old
E85
What is listeners are doing
Those numbers are wildly
For sure
People are finally
Go to number website
Quantcast or Alexa
Track traffic to websites for advertising purposes
Infowars.com everybody is just watching The Colbert videos
Like if you go to infowars.com you're just going to be overwhelmed by all my tickets so much b*******
And the articles are funny and then if you watch the show it's not fun
Is kind of fun cuz I cut out
Like the
Half an hour
Right I just get to the
The juice
The world service I'll say it
So let me ask you something
Ask away what do you think the truth is about this running into two
Target
Well they probably were not dress
I think he was born
Their physique
Look like a The Flintstones dude
He's going to be there maybe Bears I would save their in the bear category
Gay or not
Who knows
He's just decided they're gay
Cuz of course
Anywhere
So they last
Yeah
Sizing in Subway
When you just had your kids taken away and I are buying one of them toys adorable
But I think it is
You got really self-conscious and probably
Probably didn't yell at them cuz his kid was there
I hope
But you know everybody
Continue
These trendy everything deprived from siggno
Play Know Who You Are
2 hours
Vitality
Yes
Japanese weird B12 s***
I learned I actually was watching this and I get
Woo because unfortunately we get to find out that Alex Jones has heard of the handmaid's
And
His review is not good
Based on the trailer the Hulu trailer
Play the Hulu trailer
Yeah it looks great
I want to watch the show
But anyway
Start by getting mad at friend
He then complains about some other stuff and then he gets into his feelings about the handmaid's tale
Yeah without having Reddit watched it or anyting
At all
Because we're
Globalist
Cool
Super crazy
I'd like to remind
Everyone about how mad job
The guy who just said I don't care I'm not obsessed with what you wear
Is it pointed out the Flintstones look like
10 minutes of this show and maybe 5% of his life complaining
About Muslims being forced to wear hijabs
So you do care
I'll complain about this more in a minute
Now what
And they make all of the
People
Only have one husband
Unwise and where do you have these gowns
Hamburger places little chips
First of all great
Great plot synopsis
Really really understanding the essence of what is in that
That book
The ultimate Evil that's going to make women
Not wear skirts and Anna just be slaves to a patriarchal system
Look at Ivanka Trump
Look at piceous daughters look at his wife
Got a different movie
New York movies coming out
Transformers
This isn't reality is the mark of slavery
So then he goes on to play the trailer right here for the handmaid's tale
Different movie
Nonsense action movie that Michael Bay is making
But in addition
Yeah and I I love this argument
Little boys with dreads
Give beauty pageant he's totally into women
Really into this
Especially on today of all days
When a plan
Pasta House
The only reason I'm not serious about that because there's no
I am I also said a number of
Other political predictions in my life that have been wrong
So
And if it does
We're burning the system
So it's everything a riot
You can sustain a system where you've never given people thing
Like before people had access to healthcare
People were mad
But now with you take it away from people who would die without it
That's they've Nothing Left to Lose
And they know the system where they could have had their lives saved
It's it's going to be f****** bedlam
If it if it goes through
Pennywise
Alex plays this trailer of the handmaid's tale
What's great
But he comes back afterwards and this is his sort of
Automation
Which is
Not great
So there you go total inversion of reality
The gentleman
So there's no Chris
Sounds like people do that I'd like to
To think about
Alex
I would like to also cuz they're a sign of pride
Get the f*** off at Alex
You're just scared of Muslims and you don't want to admit it
Yeah and he's
He's calling what they wear
But really a spot
That they're wearing
It's really I mean
The way they are dressed very Amish
I think that's more the point even of the it is war
Harkening back to even American puritanical schitt's very Christian
That's the whole thing is eight
Baby all the time
Prayers
Very
Schertzer but again
Alex is using that
Piece of fiction that is ominous
No future we could be looking at earlier Court Savannah to stop it
Yeah we could be close to that dystopia at some point
If we aren't careful
Using that as a reality
That's like
Come on man
Stop trying
Like I wish you would come out with it
I wish you would just come out with it and be I'm scared of other cultures
As opposed
Couching it behind all this s***
Resent his cowardice
Debater move
Real beta mu
So this next clip
Talks about a
A story
But he's misrepresenting about Russia
Then he lies about how he's getting
A little bit and then at the end
I really think what I was just yelling about
I think he gives up the game
I think he is no longer able to sort of
Mask is feeling
And it slips out
Washington Post total inversion of reality
Guns and religion
Now you see if you're pro-gun or Pro Christian
And the Second Amendment is the Russian
The 1776 and did all that
No rush and become more Christian and more pro-gun had lower taxes
Describe
Shutdown
Fellows are born New York
Port Charlotte
The first one
1791 not 1776
Secondarily
He's not being sued
Bye George soros's Law Firm that's just
Complete made up in his mind by a member of the Federal Reserve board
Chobani yogurt
Who was a member of the upstate Regional committee
Advisory Board
For the Federal Reserve
The upstate New York
Advisory committee
Where they had they have
Group
A business owners
Advise the board on what the economy is like in their estimation
He was part of that Alex's change that it was mine
Dewey's on the board of the Federal Reserve New York
Because he knows it'll spook people out and I'm not
Anyway
It's not a buffet
Donkey Kong
I think you're idiots they think
They're selling Islam everywhere
Nice here right waiting six years ago Islam taking over caliphate
New Mexico
Martial law
Are setting up in Islamic State
None of that's true
The state department
Incompatible oppressive people
There's a couple things there at the end
We are unfortunate
Accidental
Freudian slips possibly
First one escaping Islam
Vinology for people who have come to America
Woefully inaccurate
I think a lot of them bring their culture and their religion along
Escaping dictatorships
Repressive regimes
And stuff like that
That I think is
Just a clear idea of
Incompatible people
We're going to destroy the West
That's real bad
It's pretty shity
That's pretty bad also he's not setting up an Islamic State for a religious
Caliphate
He's just setting up a horrible dictator
It's not a religious dictator so
Soca
Doctors in
Lawyers
The
There was a good one
It's really fun it's really funny
I miss all these Muslim Warriors
By 1 probably
I'll be so great if the Chobani guy's lawyer was a wreck
Fuji
That would be extra sweet
Text Libby goes on to Al about things that aren't liberal that trendy think are liberal
And every single one of them is nonsense
No one really believes the things that he's claiming the trendy's believe
And they're all based on fake stories
He told in the past
On his show
It's passing a
This is why he's fake news
Legitimate
This right here
And the media acts like it's no big deal
He's talking about liberals and Muslim
I'm in Facebook comes out as targeting on people
But you're alone and giving them fake liberal culture it's not real liberal
That was based on a story out of Michigan there's a college
That's in their dorms they took boards off the dorm
Doors
That's because people kept writing the n-word on
And other racial slurs
They decided that most communication was done through social media anyway and they didn't
Spewing hate
Hey wasn't it was just at this is
More harm than good
So that story is
Evan band anyting
Halloween costume parties
Fiesta party system
Cultural appropriation
He specifically always complains about how people get in trouble for doing blackface at parties
And stuff like that
If you don't want to have fiesta parties no one cares
He wanted the Cinco de Mayo party no one really is all that mad about that but don't show up with like a brown
Don't use ethnicity as a costume
That's reasonable
Having a fiesta party totally cool
Anyway that's a weird take I mean I'll give him this
Different approach to being
Anti Halloween
You know conservative or Christian
It's not like it's demonic
Yeah exactly
Medieval
The next one
Oriental food is not
San Francisco
Orient
Has it been
Machinist
What words
It's about controlling this is
Music
The bat
French cuisine
This Means War
Doesn't mean you are sick
This means you'll upset
Online
So the rock and roll with the thumb tucked
Yeah that's the protection of Satan
For protection from Satan
With the thumb out that
Which is crazy
Also
Self
No one cares if you call something an oriental rug
Oriental is appropriate in terms of
People it's not
That is the line is very clear
Oriental was a pejorative term is used very degrading lead supposed to use it for them
Calling
Food Oriental
Is different non-specific
Like I could mean a whole lot of different cuisine
I think it's a bad way to use language
Oriental food
I can't answer that question
Cuz I do want tie
But I don't want Chinese
It's right so I don't know I don't know
It seems like that was probably not based on
Maybe somebody
Don't say that
And he just like
Who is this
Is it lodged
Oh yeah
That's not liberal
So culture and what have you but you know he's a religious man
You know that's right
Christianity
Would you believe
But he doesn't have a good grasp on scripture
Used to believe that
Hear it to police
I'm going to play for you him talking
About one of the most Elementary scriptures
In the entire biblical Canon
The story of The Prodigal Son
You know the parable of the Prodigal Son
He has a good son that runs the farm runs the
He runs off and all these fake friends screwing over
Prostitutes drugs
Alcohol
My Sunshine
SSI
I never
Thank God your brother.
I care about Prince
You're in a cult
I don't I don't know if that's
The point of
The Prodigal Son
Was just one just gambling and banging around you was doing some h
Is getting to the hard stuff a couple of the finer points of that story that isn't he's missing are that the younger son went away
Inheritance
And then he became a slave
If any like shitt I could just be a slave back at home
I'm going to go apologize to my dad
Apt2b
Slaves at my family's house
Eddie comes back and he offers that Miss other says we're having a party
You're back
A little bit you're so much better than him
We got to throw parties to make this little b**** feel better it's not that
Hey did the dad tells the older brother
We Rejoice because
Our son
Who was that is now alive again
It isn't like
You don't
Party
It has nothing to do with that
Jerome story the story isn't about reinforcing the older brother
It's not about that
It's actually about taking the piss out of the older brother
He is completely wrong
Of course
And I'm sure that this
I'm interested what you thought I was just thinking like I'm sure that this is like a lot of people
Is they like Miss
Interpret
They're contributing
To themselves
You know are there
Contributing to be
It's like my money's going to these
The right bottom corner
Probably thinks that way a little
4 time constraint
It's cuz you got to show this evening
But this next clip we're get it we're coming into
I'm here
Okay just some Asian starts here
Where else is going to talk about how it's getting real
Facebook
Right
This whole thing was supposed to be about this Facebook
A long detour
Clip is about how
A bad shift getting
Emily's going to lose the thread on that real
Energy
The world I know you got inside as well just like a candle I can light you on fire and you can ride
Statistically getting dumber and Secor way off the charts we all know this
I told you they had the 60 cyborg
Dog classified
Is that the dent
Understand
Power lines
Bulbs flickering
I was at a press conference Friday
Don't you understand the human animal clones
Genetic engineering
Everybody's getting sick from it is causing all these mutagenic virus
ABC
Lively
Equalizer on for
Aesthetic
Piece of crap
I pulled up the statistics from the CDC cancer rates are on the decline
, decline
Most of the cancers are
With early detection are very treatable
I'm saying fear-mongering
IGoogle
And searched as far as I could to cyborg cat
What you talking about is that there was
During the Cold War did they wanted to put listening devices inside cats and dogs
I'm use them as like sort of
Walkie talkies for recording device
That's not a cyborg cat would never work you can't control the behavior of a cat
Like that
Oh no it's because it causes
Chimeras
Okay
Did that is absurd and I love that
I don't like it either I got a cat shoes
Bionic
But then
In his post
Custody hearing
Press conference
He did get into
Chimeras
And human-animal hybrid
Now I'm familiar only with
Mythological
Which is like a being that has multiple species DNA
Lion
No that's a horse horse
Hippogriff that the horse bird
Horse
I apologize
Human-animal hybrid
Human DNA is being placed with animals and being implanted into the bellies of cows
He also won our last
Like two episodes back you was talking about how a genetic researcher in London told him that there are fish people
To crawl around in cages
Human Horror in their faces
Oh I love that sentence I've also research Vista bit there's literally no evidence or what he's talkin to
That sounds like
The only truth to it is that scientist
Experimenting with the idea of growing human organs within animals
Facilitate organ transfer
Because there are a lot of organs that we were
Jordan
You could save a lot of people's lives
Actually being done
Harvesting organs within animals
Yeah that's not chimera
Has a different
And everyone is laughing
Yeah I understand where the burden of proof lies
When he makes a crazy claim and I say nope
I don't have to prove no
Does he consider himself a journalist
Yes
In that certain
Journalist
He.
He thinks he's doing Journal
It's Dreadful press conference
There was maybe like
10 12 15 people there I would say
Reporters
And the number of them
Probably were Infowars employees
Working again
Bear
That's just paranoia
That's just his paranoid
I'm sure people
Yeah it's just weird demon fantasy
Next clip
He actually
Something that is kind of surprising
And there's one of the first times I've heard him say something vaguely negative about Donald Trump
He does let slip that he thinks Trump is going sideways
A little bit as he puts it which is
Real Jenner
He gets into what I would do
Described as
How erase it
Describes racism
Which is really a
I think I think he's wrestling with
Some stuff
And he doesn't understand that he's on the wrong side of it
He's projecting
Incredibly hard
So
Enjoy
All the trendy garbage can wake up
And understand why am I
You still doing some good get this job stabilizing tanks
He's going sideways because it's hard to go against this
When I get in
Most people are in that position where they lie to themselves
You're the one that doesn't
Accused in court
Is noclip no proof no nothing
Never be able to go
I was watching the coverage of the trial pretty closely that course that did not
That was nowhere in anyone's reporting I don't think that
Was hoping it was made in court I think he's
Internalizing some comment that was made I would assume
I meant all that other stuff that is
Clearly
What he thinks people are saying about him
Because we are
He is a racist
He is a cult leader
The clothes minded
When he's saying
But that's
You know that's the game
Hey brain control you to think that I'm the bad guy
That's the manipulative bad guy
It's a really really good trick you can play on dumb people but it doesn't work when anybody analyzes
Anyting
Conformist feel good and strong
Sexism homophobia
Even though you're not
Other people
They use it Master identity is a couple of terms you run around and used you have no family
Will television and the latest
Download
Over and over again
Year after year
So
He thinks
Basically
That accusations of racism sexism
Homophobia
Or not
People understanding recognizing real world
As much as it is the mainstream media tricking you into thinking these things are in Port
Which
Really sounds bad coming from like a straight white dude who's angry about Muslims
All the time
Well I mean there's nothing like
A racist
Self
My racism is a real it's you projecting that onto me
Write what a create event
I think this is the sort of thing you only hear from races
Yeah you do hear it from them quite frankly
I've never heard that kind of excuse like
Hey look B Dominica
Give me the buzz words of racism
I've never heard that come out of the mouth
Oh somebody who I don't have question
Right I do have some concern do you know
People who are racist
Where is this
Actually I'm going to get the Joker
Werewolf are alike
Anderson
But
He mentioned some sort of joke he's like
It's like we got to do this
This Record good
Because you
It's harder to wash away any
There's nothing harder to wash away than failure
Except for being called a racist
And Alex was completely on
Jokingly agree with that
It's just a word that they use and then what
Your races
I've been doing this show for we're in our 5th month now
No doing this I listen to him everyday
Words and I have the recording
We have it all
I use his words
Paint him
I don't bring anything
To him
Other than what he brings
Right I have my own political beliefs
And I have things that I think are also
But I don't think he's
Can't have those beliefs
Like I'm not I'm not in any way or I've no interest
In Quicken what he saying
My worldview
I can say that he's a racist
Based on his own words
Hundred percent
Material
Sometimes I will Dabble
I don't know what the
Poorly designed
Find a conservative
Websites
Because our mutual friend
Without my permission add me to close
Groups on Facebook Facebook
Look for like a bikers for Trump
I had a little bit time or he was forcing that into my life as well before I left Facebook
But I was miserable sod groups
Because I'm so fascinated by
I don't want to be totally
I'm not getting a beer.
I'm not getting write-ups
I'm getting
Another area
But I saw this link that was like
For the fire code
Holster
Said that
And so this this website was like
Seems like no real reason
Has petitioned we're trying to get
And
Someone had written
And there is this
Like this anime
Media always try to
Minorities
Days Inn
Muslims in it like in
Maybe Tuesday
Slater
And people who watch these shows have the gall to call us racist
If I added an affected axe
Yeah for sure
Absolutely
You're willing to own
Even in the moment
That affectation that you put on their eyes
Contradicted themselves within a sentence
On that website
I think that's really what
Separate
I don't want to say us from them
Because that's exactly
People who are engaged with their own feelings and their beliefs and people who just sort of
Have a rigid ideology
And this is the sort of parting shot
For the
The 35-minute video that you put out
Alright about to
I think at this point we've proved he's proved his point that Facebook is
Trying to turn people into Beethoven Cox
I didn't cut anything out
Substandard about that argument
At all
Piecing this together in a way that
I am not
If anything I'm being generous
Gets into like
You always have to end the middle and
Start things with please for people to
They'll promote his fight for him and give him money in
And stuff like that
He sort of doing that telling everybody is a crisis
But the reason is Crisis
It's cuz the enemies no
His enemies
Ifucking no
The enemy
Resetting us right now with everything they've got
Doing it because they know
We got the life force
We have the will
We understand global
Military police in a lot of intellectualism
Destroying
We're getting
Your support
That's not why
Absolutely that's his
Religious pandering that he does
Misinterpret
The most basic allegory in the Bible
There's no denying
It's not because the enemy knows that
He is the only person who can
Stop them
It's because he literally slandered yogurt
But I can
He's just going to
Yeah
He's going to take Alex to the Woodshed like it's going it's it's it's going to be a disaster
The globalist plan they're worried about me because that's the only way he's going to be able to save face when he
Does Luz
Or they give him a
Like
Conciliatory
Way out
Like
Couple million dollars and a formal apology and the suit can go away
He has to pre-plan
All this b*******
Foundation
Write 30 hour live broadcast
For that
Broadcast
It's about raising money
For your legal fees
What do you think
Prefer
What you'll say
She would prefer
To be able to
You still like Maine
Keep it going
Rather go.
I think the ladder for sure
I think that he's really obsessed with the idea of winning
And destroying the globalist
I'm not sure how aware he is but that's not a real group
He's fighting an imaginary enemy Globetrotters
He wants to join the general
He's obsessed with winning this unwinnable battle it's like me trying to fight
The Justice League
Or something like that
Superman's not real
I can't beat him
Do that that sort of thing
There's a part that if course he inevitably has to lose in a dramatic fashion
The time
He has air apparent
Like he could go down
And this movement
This
Very clearly subtly anti-semitic movement
Can be held up by people like Mike cernovich people like Gavin McGinnis
People
Across-the-board some of his old employer
21c goes down
I think probably he would prefer to end up being a martyr
As opposed to just grinding along
Does it mean if he gets out of this
There's just another lawsuit,
You slandered so many people
Yeah
It's only a matter of time
Hello
We will say
I don't time is moving forward we also don't think he's going to have a choice in the matter
UP2U
Sure television
Kind of person you can video cam
Yeah
Is there a
I appreciate you
Join me again in the studio will do this again sometime
Please you can find us at knowledge light.com also we're at knowledge underscore fight on Twitter
You can email us at
Knowledge fight
Gmail.com
Everything you can
I can find us on iTunes
Oh my God somebody blocks you want to donate to the show you can become a policy wonk
Just like Phil another time travel episode
We got a couple of
One of them
I'll tell you off air
You know we're just a couple
Holding
Alexandra first in color with huge fan I love your work