Air Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge but I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Stripe.com
Hey everybody
Jones Jordan
Have you ever been on the receiving end of a random act
Kindness
Strange
Oh yeah
Yeah I'm sure we've got some people who are
Random act of kindness song
Journal Patriot
Wow I can't remember the exact Pacific
Would someone went out of their way to get my wallet
Oh yeah and I remembered
Just the amazing relief of that like it was crazy
Does the
Thank God
We lose your wallet you
Various things
They're tough to replace licenses
Credit card
Security card my wallet for a while yeah yeah
Card number
I just thought everything was over
Went out of their way to
License back
Nothing was missing from it it was
Gerager moments like that
That I definitely of experience
But they're not
There's not it
Total Wireless stick out my head is much I can remember single heckler
B but there's some random acts of kindness and like man that was really nice
But that guy over there like
Removing alarm Max's one guy who mildly inconvenience to me I'm going to think about for the next decade
That's not good value
Nice moments more future
I'm so drunk today we're going to interesting episode 20
I must buy my memories random acts of kindness but I do know a lot about Alex Jones
So today Jordan of course
On Mondays we're generally back
In the past going over to
2013 has progressed after the Sandy Hook shooting and the boss
The bombing now since nothing important has gone on in the proud
Alex Jones has
Received
Very bad piece of news
Rodger stone is going to prison
Has been found guilty on all seven
Look at it
2 years in prison but of course he's not going to get.
I don't know any static slow but I would be surprised if it's more than like
Yeah that's kind of where I'm at
How much time to serve
I would be surprised if it's more than
Kobe silly for us to guess at this point
So whatever what will happen will happen will learn along the way but if he gets 50 years in prison
That'll be the most hilarious
I don't think so kind of against that way too strong
Even as much as I hate Rodger I think
I'm against
Long prison sentences I have to
Continue to be against long prison sentences despite
F****** awful Rodgers go to Shorter prison sentence for him I'm not positive
Productive Rehabilitation that
That's like saying Jim Bakker was rehabilitated you know
I don't know what you
To do cuz the issue is you got to take away or somehow mitigate his ability to be a you know as they say
I don't know I don't know what I've going to prison
Achieve that goal he's not going to learn a lesson
No there's no lessons to be
Knows I don't I don't like I don't pretend to know the right answer
But whatever the case is Alex
Thinks he's going to get 50 plus
Whatever I'm so we have to go over this because it's an unfolding Saga and Alex's life so today we're going over November
14th and 15th
Of 2019
Which is I guess what would that have been Thursday and Friday of last
Antisocial
Thursday the 14th
Is when Alex still doesn't know what's going to happen
Rodger isn't setting
It's still Friday
So his behavior before sentencing
And after
I think you'll see
Behaviorism
Great okay
Right so what we'll enjoy that is
As we go along before we get down to business day we can take a moment to say thank
Goku signed up and escorted
So first of all Samuel thank you so much
Next
Thank you so much. Pieczenik
But Steve thank you so much you and I'll policy want
That's bread man thank you so much you're now policy want
Amber from the vault
Thank you so much you are now policy walk
Thank you so much you're now about what you want
Next Lindsay thank you so much you are now a policy wonk
Appreciate that very much
And unfortunately they are both
People who have maybe correct pronunciation
This is a Redemption
Thank you so much you're now
And I do thank you so much
What's the business that heroin
Is freakishly large
Cooking the books
Indeed we would
So Jordan
Before gets out of business lets out here and I will contact drops
Today Show
I was in court once it asked me what Tik-Tok is
I'm curious too
I don't like that when he was on the stand was he under oath whenever he had to answer
Just been in the lake
The Halls
Tik-Tok
What do the Daleks say
That he has his answer to that very pressing
Question
So Jordan today like I said this is The Saga of Rodger
Anza Alex
On the 14th Song of Ice and Fire if you want
All the 13th Rogers cases still ongoing
And
Alex behaves in ways that
I think probably cause some problems
Rogers trial
He's on Aaron his big position
Is essentially that this is going to be a railroading
They won
Basically
Will Rogers town as we all know
And once I set the precedent
That they think they're going to Railroad everybody else
And it's real tearing
Miss Weldon lot of people up
And I learned a lot of really horrible things about the trial from the stone Camp last night
This morning
And this whole thing is a lot bigger than Rodger Stone this is about due process in this country being flushed
On the toilet
Because wants to process has gone if you think there's already tearing in this country
Well wait we'll get as bad as
North Korea probably a lot worse which ended everything real big in America
I'd like to point out that the yesterday on his show Steve pieczenik was on talking about how do process doesn't work at
United States at the joke
What's the prob get rid of it
I just need a guy in the Department of Justice
He will throw people in prison I don't know
Yeah it's already had a very trusted gas.
Process in America and it's not
For me it's for them why is it happen
Alex's is primarily focused
Stone Rodger Stone
But he's also
Touching in on the
Inquiry
Largely
His take on it is dismissive
You know it's
It's more less
Covering any of the substance
Bill Taylor
Ukraine
They just sort of just letting a lot of that stuff I think go on that run reruns
Pufnstuf
And all that stuff because they are
They are not really happy with what's going on
It seems like Alex is in the same camp he's not going to same route as a lot of these other media Outlet
But I've seen whether their coverage is it
This is boring shows
I'm so it in terms of the impeachment he has a weird.
Ashlyn expace
Did the Democrats are now calling for their not to be a trial in the Senate
Just give the house
Vote the impeachment proceedings initiated
Where are they have the trial they're claiming that do not work
Weather show trial
So the Senate doesn't need one
Where do they have a real trial Trump
Will be totally
And completely exonerated just like Rodger Stone would have been
In the center of town will be found guilty
I don't
Do if there's a lot of truth to it Alex a while ago I'm sure it was
A procedure needs to be taking people to be fine
And I don't think that I've heard many voices and
Democratic or less
Sides
Have any faith
That the Senate is going to vote to remove even if the impeachment makes it through the house
He thinks that that's going to proceed that way
Right will nobody does
The problem is
Everybody on the right agrees
We can handle this
And Trump is really trying
In hard to make it today
Like if Trump
Would just be
Quiet
I swear to God everything would be fine they they've you keep up they have 40 Senators vote to exonerate him
He be fine everything would go on he probably win the election but he keeps
What does it mean
Where's David
We're trying
Yeah
It's a it's a little weird he predicts Rodgers going to be found guilty
Feel guilty
So Alex it goes on his predict
Hiiraan
As you can see very conveniently sets up
The whatever the case even if he's guilty he's not guilty now
I am predicting other Rodger Stone will be found
Guilty
The
Rig jewelry
Believe me is it rape
I'm major Democrat
Official nearby ministrations husband work the Mueller probe
Was
So I can put the journey when we suppose that said you should have Obama
Real rear anybody else that work for my level on a jury
They said I should be arrested for jury Tampa
Totally legal
We know that they're bunch of other Obama officials Hillary officials and spook from the CIA or indeed
On that jury
Bonjour clearly with supporting
Stone
She fell down yesterday and hit her head
It was replaced by an
Alternate juror as they call them
No you can't make this up
Alex later says that she was like in a pool of blood like a real sensational
I don't know
I was I don't know I haven't been following this
I just like that it's really easy for Alex to come up with whatever disparaging think he wants to say about something
These jurors because it's in d.c.
The odds are in the jury pool there were going to be some people with
Full service perhaps
Given that the last
Years prior to 2016 was during
The Obama Administration makes sense that some people might have some of that in their resume
Yeah you can make up whatever you want about any of these people based on a resume thing like I read a story that's
Someone on the jury had had work to the IRS
Now we get to turn this into a text whatever you want to do you can do
The only Jerry they would accept is
Everybody was a long-haul truck driver but they were independent
And they all had Trump bumper stickers on there or not
So there's no indication that I can find if there's any foul play in the jury with Rodgers trial but it doesn't matter
Alex made such a huge production and production out of trying and failing twice to identify the potential juror to work for the
Obama Office of Management and budget
So now that narrative
Verbally in place
That woman didn't make the jury Alex is completely wrong about everything in that story but because he established it as a
Clear indication of railroading
All he needs to do to prove to his audience that Rodger was set up in
Yell about that person who didn't even end up as a jerk
Real flimsy work but it does work
Yeah that's
I can't find any evidence of an elderly woman juror who is pro Rodger fell down and hit her head which I'm sure Alex is
Bring up to suggest was an inside job
I'm guessing this is just based on the person who collapsed in the courtroom on the first day of preliminary jury selection
That story went around
When Rodger was also getting food poisoning or whatever
She's turned into a woman who is ahead by a camp
Lipstick and we've got
There's no reason to think that person was even a
Potential juror let alone an actual one
I would say probably impossible they made the jury considered
Collapsed and received medical attention on the day the jury would be collected so if that's what he's trying to bring in I'm not sure
Michael Jordan flu game that she came back
MC f****** mailed the jury questionnaire I'm not saying it's impossible that someone was replaced by
Alternate juror that is entirely possible but I can't find any real information about this
And later the only information Alex has
It's coming from Joe Biggs
Right there
Right he was there at the courtroom
And
Guisados
That the woman juror who gets replaced
Was anti Rodger the other way around
Right
I don't see
Any real
Cuz he knows out Rodgers going to be found guilty and
I need
Defense
So Alex
Brings up any talk to rod
Like a night the 13th
Credibly
Important point in human history right now
I can tell you that when Rodger is convicted
And I'm almost always right
Maybe a miracle going to happen
You know I talked to him last night he said only a miracle of God right now
It's going to
Stop this
Judging reason to
They'll even harder
But I talked to her in the courtroom and they said that the jury shakes
With hated him
And stares at him like they want to kill him
In their virtue signaling
To the media and the all of the intelligence agency operatives and Obama and Hillary officials
They're in there
Staring Rodger likes want to kill
Alright
So you know this is not a fair trial
Irene if everybody staring at him like he wants to Caleb's taking with hatred
Only on this show have I took with her
I don't know if that's
The common phenomenon
I don't believe any of this this is just coming
From bullshits
Rodger fans
At the trial
We're just trying to come up with whatever narrative is possible to computer the
The trial that's all that's going on here
I could
Guess at human behavior assuming that most of these people don't have a wide breadth of knowledge Rick
Rodger stone that weed
Rather than shake with Jesus
Chick with hatred they probably all just got to roll their eyes a bunch of every talk they're like
That's obviously bulshit but guess what the court
Rodger didn't
Talk
Nice
Smart he didn't try and defend himself
Text messages
What does literal evidence of you'd witnessed a area
Horse
You sent a note to one of the jury members that you'll give them $50,000 that's what kind of tampering you're doing holy thing
You have
Lake
The only possible outcome of you testifying is being asked a question that you don't want to answer
Whatever just like
From everything I could tell
Rodger and his team were just alike let's get through this
And hope for a light socket
We don't want to plead guilty but we don't want to cause too much trouble
So
Anyway
Whatever
Alex has talked to Rodger
But he has to be very careful
About what he says
All right I have talked
Rodger Stone
Last night in this morning
Talk to Allah
Reporters
Work in the trial
Today
Where
Are you closing
The defense
The prosecution
Ended
At 10 a.m.
Eastern
About two-and-a-half hour
Play It Again
Rodger hasn't violated
Getting into the case with
He just said
God's hands
Praying for a miracle
Porter's
Not reporters
If he talks about the
Obama officials
Not just the one that weeks
And as soon as the verdict comes out
You're going to get to learn about what
Is undoubtedly
The fakest trial I've ever heard of in US history
There is not a lot of information that he produces after the verdict approves this is the fakest
And I love the way this always works as like he yells about some
Something natural obvious
Real world
Conclusion of the thing happen but he takes credit for it
Like that person wasn't going to make the jury obviously not going to happen
He screams about it knowing that
We exposed
We did it guys elotes Unfortunately they had more than enough
To convict him on account of
You did it
Again
Saudia Airline
Tends to be that Rodger didn't do anything wrong
And the Trump obviously
Like Rodger got Trump elected
And like you
Come through for the guy
Alex
Trump
Rodger they're all still connected
Really weird
Hell I got invited
Allah going to go to the secret tunnel
Is that a family emergency
Rodger Winn
And I'm not telling a secret
We would not tell any secrets about the secret tunnel to describe that tunnel
Apparently I was got invited to go to the secret tunnel
Rules are not necessarily things that are very exciting except two children
Exploring around you find a tunnel very exciting
A way to what
It's good to know that our president
Really does lead into the super villain James Bond style aesthetic even his marahlago state has Steve
Ygritte f******
I would assume that makes some sense
Especially
Now that he's the president
Right
If you going to be there like you got to have some likes
Secure area
That's got to put something someplace where you could go into lockdown or anymore
I don't I don't think that it necessarily being something like there's a secret
Pizzagate basement
Or whatever
And I also do tomorrow
Mary's got a little pet way down there
Court sure
Like underneath the Willis Tower
Sears Tower
If you're tired
Yeah I don't know
I don't know how secret this is because I very little interest
And finding out about the architecture of Mara Lago and never have had much in
That might be like a like a
Poorly kept
Secret or whatever but
I've never heard about it
Alex
The first person to bring it up to me so
I feel like he's revealing secrets
I don't know
But the truth is that the globalist
Just hated Stone
Rodger
Because he gave
Great advice
Obsessed with him
He was
President great advice
Is it Go Back 40
4 years
Estonia to be prompt Swingman
Dating
Antrum
Beard
Not having a beard
Homosexual sex
Beards go the other way too
Your body does a
Girlfriend
When you're famous
People don't know
You're out with your girlfriend
That's what stone
The way back
Okay
I love
I love that this is the level that we've reached
Brought this up before in the past
Very focused on it in this
I got now that Rogers on
Trial
Like he's really bring it up and I don't know if like
This is an attempt
To like
Humanize Rodger
I don't know if it's an attempt to make us all think about Rodger and Trump both having slept with the same woman
Andy Gibb pretending that that's okay whatever it is is weird everything about this is a family show
Tell anyone
What's the type of
You don't tell people because that's very unrelatable you had a date the same women
I get bigger
She f*** my girlfriend
Checks
Spent all this stuff
Family show Family Show
I would say if they are adult
People getting in fights over girlfriends that they share they are children
Yahoo
I don't think this is a good defense against makes Trump and Rodger both look really childish and
Little bit little bit territory little bit possessive I haven't understanding where they can both date the same
Same women been fighting over that woman is
Very gross that is an inappropriate type of behavior
If you're in for a penny
A pound woman that you're dating into a thing
They are fighting over it
Man that sure seems to be something that
Trump has a long track
Seems like it might be
So I don't think this is good
Defense
I really wish that there was
I really wish the mainstream media would twist
Play story
So I could get a
Fantastic Chiron
I have just Stone and Trump Eiffel towered say woman just moving it on or didn't
How to get ahead of the story
I got a
So like I said Joe Biggs was on the
Rainbow JoJo bow
Rainbow Joe big band here is him contradicting Alex's narratives about the replaced
We're expecting it to be
It's not good in a we've seen it has been
From the get-go but we're all hoping for the best one of the jurors got sick
She was a lady that would actually kind of snarl
At the sight of Rodger so she's not been replaced with someone else
That could be good news he never know so I'll know Alex's position was that they replaced you're with someone who is pro Rodger
Apparently the person who's there on the
This woman snarled at Rodger so her getting replaced is actually
Probably a good thing yeah
What can't have it both ways
I guess you haven't you know what you
You can if you're Alex forgot
I forgot so Alex is kind of surprise
Like how much he's
Worried for Rodger
Which I think is strange
McKenzie
The two of them got very close over the last few years
I would be surprised if he wasn't really worried for Rodger
He's going to prison
Yeah I know
Think Alice likely
Alex is familiar with
Stealing such as like
Hair for another human being I still think it's
Primarily selfish in that like if Rodger goes down I'm an actor
Self-centeredness to it
But he surprised
I'm really
Surprise
How much are
I like the
He knows the bed
Dangerous Game
I just watch them
Systemically
Riggs media
Rig the indictment rig the jury
Learn the judge
Snorting
Witnesses
Rodger was not not allowed to have any Witnesses
The defense didn't call any
Right cuz then they would be asked question
Or the discussions would lead to
Yeah he did
Or the people that Rodger could call he would want to lie for him like who would be his
Randy credico
Testifying against him
Rodger doesn't want to call Jerome corsi to the stand so good
No but it's really good for the court of public opinion
Like it's really good for Alex that Rodger didn't take us and it didn't call any Witnesses
Because
Externally you could look at that as the judge didn't let him take the stand
If only Rodger could have got up there he would have been Jack Nicholson in A Few Good Men on trial
Admitted to the crime too so they're good about it not important to you
He would have gotten up there
And destroyed
But because he wasn't allowed to rise f****** Railroad
It's a perfect thing
It is really good
Yeah yeah
So Alex doesn't he talks to Rodger
And part of that is it now he's going to deliver a message
From Rodger
And I think that this is not good
Anybody donate money to me
It gets to that
Of course
But I think this is not good for anyone except
If you look at it from a game theory perspective okay Alex is the only person with a positive alcohol I like that
Stand up for down
Copperstone
And as soon as I was making some calls this morning
We don't want
She want she called
Home
WoW professions that nobody gets totally legal this to Danger
Question jurors
Corinth
The entire law profession
But I can tell people
This is what Rogers wishes are
And
But not just me up here coming up
Plan free ride
Rodger Stone
That's Rodger
Do you want to meet you'll say it's not
Partner
So Alex is introducing that he has a message from Rodger and it's really crucial that he's stressing that this is what raw
Rodger Watts
Because the trial is still going
Right
This is a murky territory
I'm not sure anything is necessary illegal
I am that but it's a bad strategy
I really don't like how often in regards to so much of the stuff we have to say I don't think
Necessarily illegal it's a gray area
Probably should be illegal
In certain
I'm not a bit of it strains Elder the technicalities
You can just released
Somebody else's name who's not a potential juror for
And that's fine cool
Alex says Joe Biggs on the scene rainbow joke
Rights and
Yep he apparently is a part of a
Plan that Alex is launching which is Rogers wishes
Aziz Express
And it's not a good plan
Hyperbolic
Joe obviously you've been let in on the plan
Even when he is
Convicted
Tomorrow
Good news along the Route
We need
Everyone to go
White House is surrounded for days we need more people to come there
Forging process
Attache
Enchant free
Rodger Stone
Again you just had Steve pieczenik on anti due process
But
I think there's nothing wrong with encouraging people to go to the White House and demonstrate but I don't trust
The Joe Biggs is going to be a responsible person to be involved in that
Seeing as he has posted videos with a spiky back or whatever running antifa
You got out with
Proud boys like I don't think
This
The indication that Joe is quote in on the plan leads me to suspect that this will be a very poorly care
Carried out demonstration
You know I just always think
It's a good idea to put
Notoriously
Violent
People in front of it and leading them up I think that's just a great way to deal with
I think it's irresponsible
Okay it's done it's done with like
Permitting and people behaving themselves and no proud boys
I would like that the idea that people would go and just like hold signs and protest for Rodger to get a part
I don't really necessarily think that's a bad thing
Bad idea would be a bad thing
Which I don't think is actually likely at all at least
Not until
The possibility of trump winning in 2020
If you wanted 2020 then I think there's a good chance he would pardon
But then again you pardon Joe Arpaio any just part of guys who got convicted of war crimes right so I don't
No anymore
Well it turns out that America doesn't really care that much about war crime
People
Essentially create
Internment
It really care politically about Rodger Stone
Do be a real shity feeling if you're Rodger and you see this news of trump pardoning
These guys
Rogers like
Killed three civilians why didn't I kill anyway. Me what I
All I did was get you elected
F****** president's illegally committing all these right way I should have said that
So Alex
Like you said already he has a message
Rodger but he hasn't said the message
Ladies and gentlemen
To you
From
Rodger Stone who's got
Who is facing certain
My view
The hands of a
Ford
And the railway
Judge Jackson
The federal courthouse
Present
For Donna
John Trump's longtime
Wingman
Why are you empathetic
Political advisory stat
But he is trampling me
What you get for being discreet
President wingman
He's trying to stress it because of I think he wants to really play up the idea that they're trying to attack
Trump support network as opposed to being Rodger did things that are illegal
Tubi
Punished for it
Selah
Why do you keep bringing that up
It ain't like I said he has said that in the past
But it's real
Pushed on this episode he's really pushing that really hard
And I think it is to personalize
It's it's because
If you think about him
This is just Trump's buddy they go f****** hang out on the weekends have a good time
Pureref
Helps reviews
Chaplin genocides occur in all of this
That Rodger Rodger likes to f*** with his buddy
Yeah
So he keeps teasing this message
Very weird to me I don't know what I think about
Dodgers Mets
To you
And
Careful
About what I say
Because they'll try to
Prison Locker
But
And
I'm not
Why would you tease me
Why would you say I'll get to it at the bottom of the hour
Why would you do that if you had a message
A desperate message from Rodger stone that he wants you to disseminate to your audience
Why would you do that
It seems like you would be like
Listen women leave the show with this this is really important
Rodger is you know what the jury is
Is deliberating as we speak
He is
Political prisoner that you would get to it
Got to be a big message
I suppose in
20 ft tall flaming letters on the planet
It's God's last message to his
Something longer
I would feel like
The sense that this is
Teasing for the sake of trying to
Build anticipation try and get people to tweet about it get more audience tomorrow
It's going to be it's going to be something about
IC
I get a sense
Of that because
An empty know what what's Difficult about it is like
The behavior of like
Getting to the news right ahead or teasing it is something that Alex could do with something with real or fake
Bright
Unpredictable player with this sort of stuff
They're like a normal rational human
I would see that behavior as
An indication that this isn't real
Right but with Alex
I really don't know I don't know
Anything's possible
Junkball
But he's going to get to that later
Coming down the road
But for now he's got to get too big
Important
Rolling Stone
Witnesses
Calling it
Bizarre
Sacre
Size parties at Redbox
Feds probe Adam Schiff dressed like a Gyptian
Bizarre sack
5 parties at Ed Buck Smith mansion
I didn't even know that
Rolling Stones
You're not understanding how news work
If you knew that and then you called him and even wears a pedophile
You can't just say it first into me like hey
Check that out it turns out I was right
First things first Alex is doing one of his old trick
Next year he's taking the story those publishing a shity right-wing blog never gets any stories right like troop on it and
Pretending it's a story in an outlet that has editor
Operates by some standard
It's like Rolling Stone
This is just a story on true pundit and like most of the s*** on that site
It could just be ignored
But this story is actually really interesting
If you read the article it says that shift was Grace dressed in
Egyptian Garb of the FBI's probing him as part of his routine present
Redbox
Math party
Since the story is being reported you might expect a law-enforcement source you might expect someone with the FBI
Given the comment
You might expect us supporting story out of literally any
Media maybe a local news Outlet something you don't get that
This entire story is based on one source
And it's a good friend of ours
Noted hard race enthusiasts Larry Nichols
This article. Larry Nichols
It was in October
Alright
This article includes a quote from Larry about the quote this guy is kinky
We're going to we're going to need to talk to Larry
You know he's old don't call him now closed will try and get ahold of him
We got Larry Nichols phone number but be you anymore
Beyond the sourcing problems here this article is just horribly written
Give him the chip was said to be dressed like an Egyptian the article literally says quote
We can make a leap year the partygoers were likely worshipping pyramid
Kids of math
This is terrible writing
So-so
Spiders that correctly if you are dressed in Egyptian garb
Going to a party
Chances are
As we all know from our history
Clearly the Pyramid of Maslow
This is a perfect demonstration of something Alex does a lot
One of his associates often Someone Like Larry or John Rappaport and don't lie to another media Outlet
Let that has zero journalistic standards
That I was at with publish Alex's friends claims with Sensational headlines and no scrutiny
Then Alex gets to turn around and report this as if it's solid objective reporting that is
Completely independent
It's an interconnected web of liars
But it's very interesting
You see Larry Nichols getting back
I haven't seen hide nor hair of him on Alex's shows in September 21st 2017
When he threatened to Blackmail Congress on air as a good day but it would make sense for him to start getting more active now
Clearly Alex and he's not alone in this
Was trying to create the narrative that Hillary is secretly running in 2020
If you need someone to smear people in Clinton's orbit
Larry is your guy he has got the fake receipts
For 30 years
Hold what you got all the fakir
Anyway the point here is that the true pundit story is s*** until confirmed by anyone who knows
What confirming
For now this is just Larry Nichols
Talkingshit
That's that would be that's a fun game
True pundit where you get to
So it seems like he was wearing an Egyptian outfit so we can assume it was pyramids of Beth
What kind of place give you the latitude to make that kind of
Got2b great jobs Punjab
If I was smart
I'll go work for that
That's it
Professional wrestling storytelling right there but at the same time nothing they do can make me feel as good as
Is when I'm listening to Alex telestory be like
Moment of Revelation
Decider
Nichols is back
Nickelback
Well I think that what's old is New Again
You know and I think
As Alex is trying to ramp up into this
This pretending Hillary's running
Again what he's got to do or what
Ruby has to do this but it makes sense to do it
You got to start going back to what worked last
Do you ran a campaign against Hillary four years ago
What did you do back then well bulshit that Larry said was really helpful
Yeah start recording on other outlets covering lies Larry says
I'm at one of the other things that Alex
Tries to pretend wasn't
What he did is pizzagate stuff
And so
What do you know we start to see
Zpizza gate ship popped
Weird-ass toughman Hillary and her foundation had got caught shipping all those little black kids out of Haiti a bunch of ended up
Dad
Disappeared
Van Jones man Jones knows full well that got a taste for black
Meet
Devil worshippers want that blood
I got to get the black baby
Nothing about her
Cuz he knows where he gets the money from
Thinking pointing meme say I'm the racist cuz I don't want to kill
Black babies
Every other day I maybe they'll
Get their hands on
Remember those Aleister Crowley sex rituals
They like the
Walnut sauce
What that is
And they going to get you
You're going to like them
There's a whole lot of very legitimate
Critiques that you can make about the clintons work in Haiti
And it would be nice if Alex were interested in any of those but he's not
Most of them are difficult to understand and he likes to keep those sorts of issues to a minimum
It's just easier to yell about dumb conspiracy theories about Elites kidnapping children to drink their blood
Wayless work goes into that
What else is talking about with that Clinton's in Haiti case it was a case involving an organization name New Life children's Refuge
And specifically the group's founder Laura Silsby
On January 12th 2010 there was a gigantic earthquake in Haiti
At least 100,000 people died as a result of the quake in the number is suggested actually be much higher than that
Silsbee was arrested attempted to cross the border between Haiti and the Dominican Republic with 33 children many of them who were
Not they were not worth it
Though they were heading for a makeshift orphan
She was arrested along with nine other missionaries she was working with
But charges against them all were dropped
Only she remained in prison
Though when she received the trial the charges were dropped from kidnapping to quote arranging a regular travel
He was found guilty and released having servers that
Sentence already well wait
Trial
This story is an offshoot p
Narrative
When that whole thing was getting going it was decided by internet sleuths
But this is how the clintons got kids
Is that they would then use to harvest adrenochrome in the blood-drinking rituals in the non-existent basement
Comet Ping Pong Pizza where we can assume there were
Alex is quite literally just bringing back up
And again that's the same thing with the Walnut sauce
That was another pizzagate
It was something the internet sleuths decided sounded
Weird and podesta's emails so they decided it must be code for pedophilia
This behavior is what you'd expect from Alex at this
This point he's trying to run a campaign against Hillary again
Like I said in the last time that involved a lot of pee
He doesn't even realize how much of the stuff he thinks has to do with her like it came from Reddit and 410
Bulshit from that whole pizza
He claims he never covered but here he is
We're going on about Walnut sauce in the
Kidnapping kids out of Haiti
We can't go into reruns
This is lame lame I don't want to watch
Virgin
Another
I want to watch Parks and Rec all over again Danny time for something new let's move on to the good place
We can't be doing this for but I think it's very interesting because he doesn't have good mines around
And not to save the buying to get around it before work good in the end it broad Center for creative
Yes
In the last election cycle He Had a Brain Trust of some real
Will
F***** up people you know he was working on all cylinders yet
Larry Nichols Rodger Stone
A lot of people real bulshit
And admit
Conspiracies that really stick with
You know there is there you got to
Give him some credit for having some cancer
Where's the theories that pen
Betrayed into the larger Consciousness and I don't think he has as good a peoples around him now or incompetent people around
Found him now and so what do you do well what work last time just a revert back as best you can
Roger's going to prison
Smuggled some notes out on some ideas
Go visit him and write it down and crayon
But the Raptors
Great now.
I hope it gets 50 years just a 10 years or now he can f*** with
Teri Garr
Alex
Teases that Rodger has an announcement
I've got a message from Rodger stones
World
Bite me
Yes I would say when you can
Lady Gaga
Rodger
I'll do that
The phone shop
So he teases it again and you kind of get a sense of like what could be
The delay says that Rodger said to make this announcement after
So that could be why you push back
But
Alex does not wait
Wait until after the verdict because when he comes back this is about three and a half hours into the show
You just do that makes the announce
World
Rodger stone that message is your basic liberties
Four basic freedoms
Due process
Under attack
Kenny Rodger Stone can be found guilty on any of the six-count
By this Kangaroo Court in this Obama
Appointed
Byron
Fake judge
No one in this nation is safe
So now what you have there is editorializing
That isn't Rogers message
But Alex has set it up as Rodger
Rogers messages
This is a kangaroo court it's an Obama statue
Jury so now those sorts of messages appear to be coming from Rodger
Whatever Rodger may or may not have told him
That's what Alex is presenting
Alex is narratives of
About the trial are now intermingled with the presentation of Alex's mess
H Rogers message throughout
Alex Watts
All of it to be Rogers message
Whereas in Siri
This is
Maybe what Rodger told
So Rodger Stones message is this
He expects to be
Convicted
He said only a miracle can save them now that's his exact words to me last night
And this morning
And he said to me Alex
Barring a miracle
Appeal
T'god
I appeal to your listeners for prayer
I appeal to the president
To Pardon Me
Because to do so would be a
Action
That would show these corrupt chords
But they're not going to get away
Persecuting people for their free speech over the crime
The president elected
We don't do that
It will embolden
Their Criminal
Activity
Alex is delivering this I don't believe it's an actual message I think
It may be some of the things are things Rodger told him if he was talking
Rodger I'm not entirely sure what
But
If Rodger didn't know Steve pieczenik Korea
Appetite
If Alex
Did talk to Rodger
I would assume he would say you don't have your audience pray for me
I would like it for Trump to Pardon Me
I could see
If he did communicate with Rodger that being what he said
But all the way that this is being presented
It lends itself
To broadening what Rogers message was
And that's really bad
Because
The stuff that I was talking about is about who
That last clip not the one we just play but the one about this being the Obama stacked jury kangaroo court that is
Discussing the case
That break
Rogers gag order
So if Rodger said to Alex
I want your audience to pray for me I appeal for Trump to Pardon Me
That might not be considered discussing the case
But the way Alex is talking about this and the editorializing it takes it into a place where he could f*** Rodger over
That's why
I kind of feel like Rodger wouldn't do that
Cuz he would know that Alex would do that absolutely
I don't know what's going on
Cuz Alex is going to
He's reading it off of his hand like
Rodger says hi everybody
Text Mom
Please pray for me but I mean
Can you imagine praying for Rodger Stone immediately following
The verdict I don't know I don't know why he wrote that one
Unreliable narrator giving us this message so I don't know what I believe
I'm I'm suspicious
Let's say
So here's the last clip from the 14th and it's Alex discussing how like there's a plan
If Rodgers can
There's a press release an article on newswars.com and infowars.com
That
Have the number to the White House on it
And even when he is convicted
By this jury
It is
Wild everyone share
The information graphic posted
Infowars.com
And newswars.com
With everyone you know on Twitter
Facebook
YouTube My Hand
You name it and that
Everyone
Who can
In the area of Virginia or Maryland or West Virginia
All of the country travel to d.c. anytime
For the week after this connection
And encircle the White House with bull horns
Demanding President Trump
Take action
Do you see like
That
It's it's
He's trying to control the narrative is Rogers Freedom or whatever
And he's using it to funnel it into like advertising for Infowars bright like a we have this press release
Nobody share it we have an infograph specific infographic that obviously is going to have
Infowars.com
It's going to be a great floors branded bullhorn
A promotional Blitz
I do I do see a little bit of that
But whatever
It's still not outside it's not totally in the realm of like
Over the top
Alex trying to profit off of Rogers but it is controlling
The space
What I hear is
His hearts
He just knows
He knows Rogers to guilty
And he's any the same time he's like
We got to try this
We got to try this whole like their railroading am narrative
It's a tough song People likes about Rodger stone is how I obviously criminal he was
Part of his
Yeah he even talks about that how I keep plays up his villainous aspect because they're fun
Please like
Well yeah really should probably go to jail we just don't want him to go now
It's a hard case to make those like wow
Should have been in prison long ago yeah alright alright you got them
Show me the regular
Praying for Rodger
Lord I just we thank you for this meal
I hope Rodger Stones okay
This sneaky
Top-hat wearing
Villain from a old movie
Yeah it seems weird
So we jump in on the 25th and
The 15th
And he is the sound quality in this is
Rochas
Friday November 15th 2019
I am your host Alex Jones as I predicted for weeks
And as I definitively said yesterday
Rodger Stone would be found guilty on all counts
He faces 50
Years
Ladies and gentlemen
Forethought
Crime maybe the sound isn't obviously different
Yet but
This verse like five
Minutes or so of his shell on the 15th is noticeably
You're getting it he's going to prison for 50 years got to make it as a
Beers possible
Great first. Cry
Sakura
Do you know those
Those thought that he had work rhyme
That's true even thought about committing crimes
Do Alex now pretends that Rodger is going to be on
Michelle later ladies and gentlemen
He was completely
And totally
Railroaded there's a good shop
Yeah they don't take me to custody the hearing is still ongoing right now that he will be on the broadcast today
They let him know that if he does speak out against it
The judge will throw the book at him even harder
The title of a clip Alex pretends Rodger is going to be on later yeah fukin right
Absurd to imagine
Best he's going to call in
After the sentencing until gets a number
He is not talking to Alex
At all cuz that never goes out by a day every minute he talks to house
It's conceivable that he's right about the juror
Situation
It's important because
You did that in order to have oatmeal
Away into attack
The trial whenever Rodger is
Inevitably found guilty
There's never been a rolling like this and remember
We suppose that there was a jerk officially got the name
And
Mueller probe
Exposed
The judge remove her off of
Somebody's trying to fix the hissing
Yeah that's that's great
That's the worst
It's real weird like we got the name right
Yo dude has terrible impressively wrong
So at the new
Point now
Is that if Rodger goes to prison he's going to be murdered in prison right like episode
That is the new angle
And Alex Express is that
This is a tyranny and it'll warm up for President Trump and President Trump hasn't gotten the sun's out of jail he could when he told
Massage release the Wikileaks that's a big black mark on the present
Pardon Rodger Stone
Well then I'm and I got to tell you
No matter how many good things Trump does
Doing the Tucson gem and letting Stone Hangout
He does this
I just don't know what I'm going to do
When you call the White House right now
20-24
5614 14
Until President Trump depart
Him
Don't let them get their hands on him they'll put him in solitary confinement God knows what to do with food
These people mean by last night
Killing
We hear their first indication of Alex being like if he doesn't pardon Stone
Not going to be put in solitary confinement
Who cares
Against that cares I mean who cares about that stuff because that's secondary to me
Then Alex's
Point vet if Trump doesn't pardon
I don't know what about
I don't care about all the good stuff he's doing
He's leaving
Assange
And Rodger Stone out to dry like
I don't I can't
Because I think it would Alex is starting to realize
Is that he will also be left out to dry along with literally everyone you stupid f******
Moron
Alex is starting
He started to realize that there is no honor among Thieves
There is no protection from her for him
Man he will be tossed aside as easily as these other people are
Guys have never read
A f****** book
All the Lord of the Rings series is about
Tilex side now you saying that Roger's not only facing 50 years in prison
He's facing maybe 100 making a prediction here
I'm actually
The seven charges
And the judge I believe could twist it she may give him more than 50
Because he's monsters want you to know they'll put you in prison if you stand up for America he is a modern thought Criminal
Who has done nothing
Come on and Trump told Julian Assange
Release the Wikileaks he did
Nicole
I like Trump
Way more than Hillary
Is a lot of good things but I got
I don't know what I'm going to do
If Trump doesn't
Pardon Stone
Is 40
Plus your wingman
He's got a date of the same women
Whole Nine Yards
They fix the hissing Trump policy is penchant
Brian people have to drive that got him elected
I don't know
What I'm going to do
I don't know.
I think he's facing a moment of like
I can
This is this is the good
Chance Yep this is how I can get out of
This is how everything can change
I can I can
Retain
All of my narratives about Trump
About how he was doing all these good things
I can retain
You can retain everything
He doesn't have to turn on Trump
He doesn't really even have to
You can just say it like yeah you know what everything that we saw that was good in him was good
We were right to do that
Trump is just he's not strong enough to stand up to the swamp
The Deep state is too powerful
He can
You can wreck on a whole bunch of stuff
8 something
The audience will probably see is acceptable
He won't stand up for Julian Assange and Rodger Stone I realize that there is a real problem with
The best I can
I could stop supporting
Or I can pivot
Whatever this is
Perfect opportunity for him I think he's
Yeah I see the light
Window well I mean just
Very obvious
Verbal pattern
I'm not trying to brag and then he brag
If you saying I'm not saying I'm in a cult
And then he changes in your life
Oh man
Your word get it I don't know if you get it in your head but your subconscious is like I'm Sentosa
Buckeye got the
It's a Nigerian email Tim over
Yep it is big a big picture
The Rodger did nothing wrong
The damn thing
And these monsters
We're going to use is a beta test with their jurisdictions
To go after everybody's got to put them in prison
I live in Travis County
It's so funny to remember that Alex has big documentary endgame
Literally ends with a shot of Alex bullhorn Rick Perry's House late at night accusing him of being a globalist
And all they did was trying to get him arrested for something they made up his Mane documentary that he says
Who's all his claims
Leave the viewer with a shot of him attacking Rick Perry
But now the Perry isn't with Trump used good upstanding American wants what's best for the country so spineless
As for the case of Alex is talking about this is what we talked about on a recent 2013 episode where Rick Perry
He was trying to force a Democrat ba out-of-office by defunding her office if she refused to resign
Which is not cool
He was indicted for that but the charges were dropped after he appealed when he was out of office
That's that that's
Okay.
Talking crazy
Fine just go away
Sure
So that's nonsense
Whatever
To try to use those as examples of
Like this
No
Anyway you shouldn't like Rick Perry why do you like
New process should be abandoned in this country.
About due process and I don't know why I'm mad but I'm mad about both
So Alex like I said I think he's starting to realize that Trump is a disloyal bad actor
Go stupid
And President Trump
Adopted up for the rocket
Independent president organized
Coming after you the members of Congress and walking
And I Know It Feels Right to sale Trump's wonderful and you know
Everything I do against him
What about us what about the president protecting the American people
Are they going to come indict me have another rigged jury
Plays golf and talks about how he's a
Stable genius
You remember what happened that night we all find a clip
2 a.m.
Collapse
You better get ready
Achilles
Guard yourself for true
Mayweather
Guard yourself for True another
I don't know what that music is but they play it
A bunch episode
And I all I can make out from the lyrics as you keep coming back for more
Which also seems almost
Steamatic
I don't know what store
Is it what
The people that work for him still don't know how to run his sound
Still
I don't know
Somebody choosing the music who is clearly f****** with him from time to time plenty of evidence of them
Very on-the-nose what makes they play that Depeche Mode song like you had something to hide
While he was introducing the up the Rodger announcement
Yeah there it seems like there's weird but how much of that is over analysis
I'll get plays over and over
In-N-Out of brakes
To the point where it's very noticeable like I've ever heard and episode where he's played something more than
Twice
I can sometimes happen every now and again
But that
Themes
So
On the nose and weird
Totally see one of those people like accidentally deleting the Spotify problems
Stupid industrial opportunities
Conclusion is notable infected
I'm so Alex is mad because Trump is
Sweden but he doesn't want tweets
Rodger Stone got Trump elected
Blisters of the show got Trump elected
Matt Drudge
Got Trump elected
The truth
You guys are doing great
Like I said on your stay
Show
I said
We don't need tweet from President Trump about this we need action
Tweet from President Trump saying this is a miscarriage of justice and then and then nothing
We need
Action
Now
Ebenezer the b******* the trumps feeding
He's realizing
I'm not safe
Noah
None of our allies in this propaganda game that we've been running
For the explicit purpose of Defending Trump
None of us matter
None of us like no one's going to be there like hey
Split Blast 3
4 years of my f****** life
Going out of my way to carry water
For this f****** a******
Abandoning
Everything that I knew except white supremacist was allowing
Mike cernovich on my show
You understand
Purpose
It's crazy and I like now there isn't anything
What you get for it
You will be
You will be sacrificed
If it is
Necessary I don't know what it's like to have a kid but that moment I imagine of you having told this child
Over and over and over again the same thing
And then never learning and then eventually them coming up to you and being like
You know
I realize that this guy really
Doesn't like me it isn't paying attention
Anime and thinking that that's something that they're coming to on their own when you're like I've been screaming that at you
For years you get it
So at this point Rodger actually
Hasn't been
Convicted yet but Alex is acting as if
Write this is still like at the jury deliberation but it's like we all kind of weld
Which is interesting because if I hadn't told you that you would have thought that he got convicted before the show
Yeah he did okay
So Alex sucks now about the last time that he talked
Did the pardoning you pardoned Arpaio we got the
Yeah, I got to talk to Trump
Naviga
I'm like listen you know they're putting the sheriff in prison
That woman's got a trial to know know the judge is doing it what judge can't do that
Yes mr. president
We need you to
Pardoned him they're coming after because he released documents showing you were being spied on they got from the DEA we released the original in it
How do you know about that
Telling you about a year ago
I don't need you to tell me how great I am
They take you out there going to get me next
I need you to go after him
Do things about that last clip 1
If that is true which I'm almost certain
It's not then if I were drop I wouldn't talk to Alex again either
That retelling is clearly an inch
Expensive Alex line to the president in order to get a racist authoritarian part for crimes he was absolutely guilty of
The documents Alex had were from Dennis Montgomery
We didn't entire episode about that b******* titled the dentist Montgomery invest
You can go and listen to that if you want to
Standard Foley
None of these documents were real none of them proved Trump was being spied on and none of them were from the D
DEA
Why would the drug enforcement agency be involved in any of
I'd be a good dead giveaway that Alex is just kind of make me
The reason that Arpaio was going to prison with contempt of court that is true
But that doesn't really get to the heart of the matter
Arpaio been the subjective
Very thorough investigation
And it was found in his police department in Maricopa County operated ways that violated City
The rights
Is Department of the flagrant pattern of racial profiling that quote reached the highest levels of the agent
And it was so severe that the department was stripped of its ability to legally identifier
Detain suspected undocumented
That's how bad their patterns
Again I'm against
Shorter prison sentences
Arpaio's the only person that I can
Think of right off the top of my head that I want to rot in jail go to The Hague
He should rot in jail for the rest
Do too many lawsuits involving his inhuman treatment of
Detainees the court told Arpaio that changes had to be
His Department
Arpaio refuse to do with the courts that he had to do
He was given many warning
Bennie January 2015
Years after he had every reason to understand that the way he did business violated civil rights
You held in contempt
Discord
The case went on until July 2017 at which point he was found guilty of
Criminal contempt
But that charge is not just some minor chart
That guilty charge is a front-facing mask that's covering of yours of racist and abusive police
Practices that Ohio refused to change
I know it goes without saying but the contempt of court charge means nothing
The reason Arpaio got a pardon
From drop the reason that Alex fought so hard to
Protective was the racist abusive
Police in the characterized as
Career
When they defend Arpaio that's what they're defending
Not some kind of bulshit a judge can send you to jail nonsense
You don't need a jury to hold someone in contempt
The court because of jury already decided the case
That contempt is based on
Alex knost
You just doesn't care cuz he needs to make his white identity believes look like a defensive rule of law in order to make it marketable to Allah
Larger audience
All that's going on here
F*** this
Pakistan said another bad exam
For him to tie
B Rodger
Now
Get to the point where I live
Rodger his
10 a.m.
Baseball cap
Four-door
Maybe 1776
How many 76ers on the front
Wow
Guide
The Revolutionary War
Thought
When they connect still today probably when I'm on are I'm going to wear
Hey I left it in my
They walked in and handed to me they got Rodger Stone can
That's not some psychic event
That's like watching somebody in a bullfight get run over by the bull and the Bull's horn go right
So that seems like a plug for his hat
Atwoods
More
Hat Pinterest
Then Rodger Stone news.
I was worried about the Hat
The long journey and took together
It took us a while to get there
Yeah followed by and see I'm not psychic
Obviously
I think we all knew that
Be found guilty
Something that I think is going on here is that Alex recognizes that
Almost everybody hears the news Rodger Stone has been found guilty is immediately going to go to Infowars
Immediately
I was going to freak out
Like I heard from people who was dark shadows like I've never listen to his show live I had to go immediately to
Watch this
Antique booster naughty I would be from
Answer why not use that as an opportunity like
Tell these great hats to wear this when Rodger was found guilty in order of the Revolutionary War
The great hats
Well made
1999 1776
You get a discount
Yep
So Alex now has a situation where all eyes are
His show
He's probably
He's probably at least somewhat aware of
Yeah it's hard to tell how much exact
He considered self-immolated
He knew that enough people were watching that I could have really done
I don't think that's the
He's already said that Rodger might be
But he knows that that's not true
But he does have
Some gas
Barnes
Very exciting things to just travel the big National sovereignty day
Is he will now
When I get to that
Next segment.
Responded
Starbucks
Michael's who is the concert McClendon
He's got big and tell on Adam
Chef and
Ed buck
And the Satanic rituals that went on there
Holyshit Larry Nichols is back
Larry Nichols is on the show Mary Nichols is back
He's had cancer for
45 years now
Husband
5 years
John
But I think you're free
Near me
I don't know what the cases with that I don't want to I don't want to sit here in Bach what may or may not
Not be legitimate
Illness
I don't know what the deal is with that and I don't like
I think there's so many other things you can talk about with Larry that's
So far past what I'm even in
Interested in
He's back
I mean just the day before on the show he started recording on bulshit
True pundit articles that are based on Larry's
Reportaj
Get Larry back in here
Reach out or did somebody did somebody from
True pundit
I got some b******* I need
I got to check with Larry
Or is Larry like sending out texts from time to time I know exactly how this works
It's much less confusing
Like I said
Get the sense
That Alex recognize
As if there's more people listening
Because instead of covering Rogers s*** in detail
Here's what he does
Going to 2020 or so much happening
We're here is your word-of-mouth getting around the sensors which is
And buying products
So I was going to before polymer came on
Talk about DNA Force Plus
Chicken stock
Co Q10 and the pqq Atmore
Barfly
The product whatever we talk about properly
Now this all happened so I'm not going to have time to get to it now
Oh no search
Just this morning
But I printed off
Mainline science
Nobel prizes
210 and
I think you're cute
Notice again he's using the Trope of the older guy got the full. I got a binder full of women that's
This is a long
But I wanted to play this just so you can hear the
Mundane
Banality of it
This is the same segment of his Show when he announced Rodger got found
Regrows mitochondria in the brain cells that nothing else
Alzheimer's everything they will not tell you about this
All here
50% off it's the one thing
Body should give themselves
Anybody about 40 should be on
The Pikachu the calcium channel minutes got all of the other things
That was the Fountain of Youth by the
Japanese reishi mushroom
Astragalus root
The Dragula
G a lot of stuff in there huh
The 40-50 $60 in Orange drawing or aren't from organic Source like these
Think about that
Okay
I'm thinking
Similar formula
Not a prescription by the doctors
So if you going to jail Danner
How long does it take delivery
Because it cost so much racket lawyer have a statement
Product
And something will you not sell it for 203
Marketing Barnes Road
Contract on this we're still going
Discounted right now
Nobody gives you this
Prophetess quality
7498 right
The product
Attitash
And if you're really the older.
Issues take a lot of
What happens what what happened
Hungry
Doesn't grow longer
Nope
This is insane
Like that was a long clip yeah as long as it is show he dedicated to talking about
Is DNA force in a in an infomercial way
In the time when
You would be most likely to have the most eyes on his show
If I were looking at this cynically
I would say that's an intentional decision now
He just got through Rogers going to prison you got found guilty
You say
Going to prison
Speaking a little bit
Presumptuously
All signs appear that you probably going to prison
And Alex's first responses to talk about this great hat he decided to wear whenever Rodger it's a really good head
DNA Forest it's f****** weird
Also
He's got a tie-in with Disney plus it's a whole cool thing but he does he's not going to announce that just
Strategically it seems like hey we have the audience that we are unable to capture in any other way
Let's see if we can move some of this stuff
Yeah it seems like that
Can I get Paul Joseph Watson
Who you mentioned went to that Independence March in Polish
About within the con
Text Stefan molyneux
Right
Interesting because the
The misconception
I suppose around that and granted I haven't looked into
All the Dynamics of this year's March
As it related to
Fun
He was going to whitewash
Watch that because the year prior
There had been a bunch of people with Nazi signs and
And that was outlawed do you want to be sanitized version in order to create the appearance
Your priors Bart
Was all bulshit in the last being out of control
I don't know what this year
Is Buzz I don't know if Paul's doing there
If he wants to just go to a Polish Independence Day Parade
Care but I do see it as signal
You know eyesight because of
Stephon going
And making a big deal of endorsing white nationalism after going
Poland
It has become a bit of a thing in this community
So
See that is kind of a
Tip of the Hat
There's no way that you could
And I'm not saying that
I'm not saying that nobody could want to just go
To the Polish
National Independence Day
I will probably be fun
Better yet know it's very cool is I've never even been to Poland I'd love to
To see all those things at anytime you're at a
That's very cool but Paul Joseph Watson does not just go to the pollinator in England
It's not just go to the f******
I agree with you but I also slightly disagree I don't I don't know I would say going not a big deal
Talking about it and being like a everybody says it's a racist parade
That's kind of like okay you're doing that a
That part's a hundred percent
I don't know I don't really care though I really can't I should stress I
Not kept up at unlike I don't know exactly what's going on now with the Dynamics are
So I'm probably not in the best place
Think about it but
Paula Zahn
And
He does not see
Very optimistic about Rogers Prospect
Will we see
This is
They're saying we shouldn't criticize Trump into man what he said he would do
Trump
We got Trump elected dammit
Friend
I want him part now
What song is back man
Paul does not seem like he has any faith that Trump is going to do anything and Alex
Nah
Man
Paulding
I did know that
The only one here is like
I know that I know what the score is I know what I'm doing
Bring the little bit the done videos that have come out where he talks about life
I'm not into conspiracy theories present himself as being Above This.
And to an extent
Like he's been far more willing to criticize Trump than Alex and
The past
He's had a sale on Facebook
Whatever whatever
Deanza
A little bit more of a like
A position to say like
Come on Alex than anybody else
But I still think
It's weird to say he didn't get do
Because you probably did somewhat but just not nearly as bad
Therapy
He kept Scott
I just mean like on a general
I would look at it as somebody who diversify their portfolio as opposed to someone who's all in on one stock
I think you put a little bit of like
Some of his
Steaks elsewhere
And because he's so singularly focused on culture War
Nonsense
It doesn't matter too much about Trump for him
Sanity of the
Left
And all that it's it's still plays
For even
Far
More
Artificial issues
Someone yelling on a campus so War on Christmas begins earlier
Yeah
So
Alex is seems
Stuff during the breaks
Apparently of people on
MSNBC making jokes about how
Rodger has a tattoo of Nixon Nixon's finally going to prison
That's on Rodger
That's his fault
Alex is
Yuri yes so you have to take those you have the pictures
Willie commands in physical 1776
From Summit. News here it is Gateway pundit. Commerce video
Set up his impeachment inquiry as we look live inside the news
Google
If it's not that one
He is mad mad
Hey your bet you one of your best friends is going to jail I get
Not wanting other people to laugh at
Yeah they're making fun of
In
That is this a great
Political
Anyway
So on are on the last episode
Ye did that real muddy
Reading of Rogers message if you wanted him to deliver
Now
That the verdict has happened
Alex gets a text allegedly Aram Rogers lawyer
And
This is one of the more ironic
Clips that I've ever heard
Let me hear show people the type of stuff I've got
The phone number of
My name on this
This is the type of stuff
That I get
Almost got Rodger taken into custody immediately upon the verdicts
Please be cautious about your comments
Lawyers
Think about this
Everybody
Nobama officials
So what's going on here is that
The way that Alex behaves on the November 14th show
Could be argued to indicate that Rodger had broken his gag order
So that is what the prosecution
Was saying
Terms of holding him
Right after the verdict
Which side
The judge didn't
Decide to go along with but did continue with gag order
Which makes sense
But
What I find amazing
Think about that
Is it this lawyer
Contacting Alex
Apparently
Google knows he's making this up
I don't know if he's making it up because
The framing the freezing of it is so like what someone would say
Telling him
Be careful about what you say about private communication
Repeating this private communication
Female I think I buy it
Just because
Of that line actually just because the liner is not
Hey
Shut the fuk up or
You got to be quiet about this there's too many powerful people looking it doesn't work well enough for what Alex's narrative is
Please please don't
Reveal too much information
Yeah
Man
What a f******
Yep
So the funny thing about that though is that this is him not being able to understand it
Like that's that's really interesting if that is genuine
Then he's even turning a genuine
Ostensible allies
His words into the conspiracy theory reality
As opposed to that Rodger Stones lawyer being like
Hey
Be nice to your friend you don't want to go to jail right away
You know yeah
Conspiracy theory
Yeah
So at this point Paul
Offended that Rodger is going to get 50 years in prison
For this
And then Alex
Normally people would get about six months prison time for this but Rodger Stone
Diaz which is basically a death sentence
Okay
All right so the most serious charge that Rodger was convicted of his witness tampering which is the result of him trying to threaten
Intimidate Randy credico into pleading the fifth
Generally speaking people don't tamper with Witnesses unless they know they're guilty
And looking for a way to subvert justice so I think it's appropriate for courts to take it pretty seriously
I tell a whenever I tamper with Witnesses
Cuz I'm like tell them I am guilty sometimes people only get 6
Months in prison for witness tampering that's fair a lot of it has to do with the context of the underlying
Crime
Princeton stead clout was a GOP member of the South Dakota House of Representative
In 2007 he was arrested for sexually abusing a
Is foster daughter
Among other charges
I ended up getting a pretty steep sentence but in addition he got 10 years added for attempting to
To tamper with witness testimony
That's a super serious offense
To tamper with Witnesses in that case is he deal
In contrast there was a case in 2015 or a husband and wife got sick at 6 months
Witness tampering
What do surrounding a drug arrest
Read the tampering was still serious and be the consequence
It was not merely a series
As a former state representative abusing Foster
For children
Deals with the witness
Tampering on a sliding scale
Hey don't say I had weed
6 MI
Hey don't say I
Rota f****** hell you there
I think he was trying to subvert a federal investigation
How to make all the arguments he wants about a Rodger did nothing wrong and all that but if that really were the case I don't
Vicki will be trying so hard to get credit code to stay silent
Rodger did that for a reason and the only plausible explanation
Come to buy
Is that he felt that Randy credico talking would be bad for him
So I don't know
The six-month thing yeah I mean it's technically fair but that is also just
Intentionally obtuse
About what the way these charges are added
Whatever
And that's the most series on that's the one that I carry the possibility of 20 years
As I understand
Not going to get all that time
Nonsense
It's a
You know it's it's
It's cliche
To point this out
But
You can f****** steal it election and you're only going to wind up getting a few years
Stealing an election is such a vague
There's a lot of you know whatever
They go to the Dakota
Alex Freeman
Freedom or death
Whatever
They come back from break
And Alex is on the phone
Paul Joseph Watson tries to cover
In common
Do some stuff
But then Alex
Jumps in
And tries to reset wow Paul
Is trying to
Reset himself it's very strange
He just jumps in his like shut the f****** all I got something to say not really trying to reset so he could throw it to Paul
Even though Paul is already talkin Kaiser while
Very strange
We live and we'll talk about what happened in Poland while Alex Jones makes a very important phone call going to get back
Breaking Rajasthan news
I am literally talking
And I'll be right back
Watertown injury 50 years
40 facing all 7 channels totally rigged
Has Paul just got back
Eastern and Central Europe
Alright you can hear almost even a little laugh Falls
Alright
Whatever this is that indicate like that behavior also runs in line with me thinking that he's become
Coming aware that he has a big audience
You said the drudges top link to as we appreciate it
He comes in because
He's like okay people are tuning in expect
Fantasy Alex
Paul is coming in from commercial
Establish my present be back in a few here tall do squats
Tell you all about these European problem
Yep
So Paul gets to talking about violence around Europe
Ladies migrants
And I don't really care it's all
Go to the same stuff you always
Prado's Auto by refugees show up.
He's citing the professor here
Who's talking about violence and sweet
Right listen to the weight
This professor because
Infowars
The Swedish state
Itself
Is in Japanese
He said the state's Monopoly on violence
So wait hold on
The Monopoly on violence is the token of a sovereign state
Because I thought that Alex hates the idea of the Monopoly of violence being in the hands of the
The state I thought that he thinks that that's a
Sign of tyranny
I'm going to need
Okay
The larger context of this is that
There are like a people
Committing crimes in Sweden to the to the
Extent that these Monopoly on the ability to
Violence and Power
Is taken away from the sky
Which is what Alex think what you think is good
I mean not necessarily migrant people committing crimes or whatever
The narrative
Is here but Alex
Is strongly opposed
Do a Power Monopoly being in the hands
Devastate
That is something he talks about all the time
Yeah
Talk about that being the enemy of sovereignty as opposed to Paul is saying that it is a Bedrock of Saw
Sovereign
It's counter to the stated editorial position of Infowars yet doesn't make any sense for him to say
What he does because he wants to make you more scared of Michael
No I guess
I mean I get that but
He wrote that down
Right because it's something that you folks an image of these migrants being overwhelmed
The police and taking a ride
Lichen
The framing of it is your right 100% counter
Crazy
Well I mean
Potential your contacts is
All of these hordes of non-sweet
Right
Are coming in and taking over Sweden
So he's really really catching it as like a nationalistic like all these not
White people are being taken over by black people and white people need to have control over all the fours
As relates to white population
There should be no power Monopoly of the state
I have two non-white population
The state must have a monopoly of power
Yes so long as the state is white
Yes yeah
Seems to be what that the confusion
Anyway Alex comes back
He seems like he's really mad
At the Trump isn't helping
And a lot of folks
Support
Or others
Everybody else
Add
Power is in the right to do it
My back's broken
Being eaten alive in a pit
Trump's up there
Not getting me out
He won't do anything
My back is broken I'm going to pit I'm dying Trump has all the power in the world did it solve this problem and he won't
Do it
Start to get real pissed off you can see
So Alex Rodger
Is found guilty
Put spent days on in the past
Now there's
And we bring up such huge news here all the time
It all just trying to get lost in its intention to get broken up
Coming down the pike
YouTube
20 years ago
The store
Confirmed object of what went on in court today
Should terrify
Everyone in America and the world
We don't get control of our government and our judiciary
Legislative very quickly
We are going the way that all other nations go when they
So
Isn't about Rodger this is the decline of civilization
I don't think I like your strategy
No I don't I think he's I think he's going around it I think he's going about it
I mean I think what he's trying to do is capitalize on all the
The larger number of stores
By increasing his ads and all that s***
When
That's not really going to do it what he should be doing
Is taking this time now that all these people are watching again
You're really f******
Hammered like crush this s***
You're like give the best
Free Rodger Stone performance that anyone has ever given
Andy should turn on Trump absolutely fire and brimstone We Begin the the
New conservative party that we're not going to call the white nationalist party but here
Today the one option that has the best
At the same time
Break your fall break
Like you have the most eyes on you people are interested in what you're doing you can now
Open
Good conscience
Retain what you need to retain
From your Trump years
Move on to something new
Because
Like it's something that even people on the left
People who don't like
Which will be like yeah
Dvi-d to Hubert turn on Trump because he realizes
He's not going
To save any of us
That is something we like
Yep you'll get some people being like we told you so you dumb a****** but at the same time you can't argue with that
Conclusion of course you should have seen this coming but yeah of course
Other things like when he dropped bomb to Syria now it's as I can
So close that is a position where if you turn on Trump for that people would be like
What what is that say politically what is there would be
Fusion
Him turning on Trump for not pardon Rodger Stone
There's no a political thing
Bucking llamas
In-studio to get publicity and the publicity he would get if he just
Came out on Infowars
We no longer support Trump
That would be MSNBC headlines that's that's
The type of s*** that
Inexplicably would get everybody talkin gone too far with this
What if
Wayne Rogers convicted
Alex
Going to keep people coming back and one of the llamas Rob do does a ventriloquist act with him at the lava turns on truck
Okay alright I'm in the other llama gets a tattoo of Rodger Stone on its back
Is just a pain
Very cute it's cute
So Alex
Freaks out
Here a little bit
And I think some of it might have to do with the pressure of their being way more eyes on
Building up suspense here
He said suspense Ali
What are
Confirm
From multiple people in the court
Specialist in this area
East Oakland
He's so evil
Did you guys find that piece of information I want you to print earlier
The criminal
Critical
Stream of consciousness
What
Give me paper trail
And then I'll come back and I'll get it all of it alright
This is a lot of that are
People are just
Unbelievable
Bring your skateboard as a file you have
That file
Only got that
Thanks
Information
If I could fire every f****** one of you I would if I could fire everyone but I can't
Ford better than you still mad girls so mad
So he goes it takes a break
Plays like a special report
And he comes back
And you can tell like
He definitely punched a wall or something
Way more professional
Gps-based in Austin
Wow
Infowars.com
You very clearly wouldn't behave like that radio host if you didn't have
Information that there are tons of people who have never listened to his show before you can
Phuc yea
Because of the
Terrible Rodger Stone
Political prisoner
Facing 50 years in
Jail
Hands up
The Obama
Hanging judge who let Hillary Clinton off the hook
Mozzy
The clear standout
Nice Railroad
What are yours
Nothing wrong
Drudgereport.com
Is top
Lynx
2R
Story
Live feed
We're breaking all of this down
So
Well it is true that Amy Berman Jackson the judge and Rodgers trial was also the judge in the case of palm
That is true but that doesn't necessarily mean anything.
This is up
They're only 15 judges in the US District Court for the District of Columbia and it's entirely possible that this was a coincidence
Timer
What you need to do better than just to say Obama appointed her to prove any kind of concrete conspiracy
That's a pretty serious accusation to make about a judge
If you look up a judge Jackson's History Alex's picture of a leftist judge Towing deliver a line just doesn't really seem to ski
Square with reality
Princeton she presided over the sentencing of Jesse Jackson jr. who was a Democrat member of the House
And the son of Jesse Jackson
What he stole about $750,000 of
Can pay money
You'd think she was a damn Hatchet person
Judith thrown out of sentence but instead she put him in jail
As a relates to Hillary Clinton she didn't do anything crazy in terms of Benghazi
All she did is dismissive wrongful-death suit against Hillary because it would have been illegal for it to continue based on the Westfall
The Westfall Act is a 1988 law that made it to the United States itself is to
Be substituted as a defendant
In cases where a government employee is sued for something that was the result of something that they did in their official capacity
In their job
This act explains a lot of questions
Why government officials
Vicars RV
Constantly suit
It's because they have a form of immunity
In terms of their official business
Alex can say that this judge was protecting Hillary but to do anything other than what
She did Judge Jackson would have violated this Freeport ruling and a law passed by Congress
It would have been very illegal for her to allow that lawsuit
Interesting life
In looking at the judge Jackson
I found a website that I had become fascinated with
And I
Too much time on
It's called Patriot or traitor
Don't
Don't don't Jordan
This is a Blog this is not tell me that you can just type in a name and it will tell you if there if it's been any name
But there's a big database has come up with a list
Traders and peppers
An editorial position for traitor or Patriot now
And I'm guessing who would create a website called trailer patriot.com
I'm guessing that
My guy
Who I appreciate are probably going to lean more towards the
The traitor side would I be correct
I think that you can guess based on who would make a website
Okay
First one Amy Berman Jackson
That was an easy LaVoy finicum
You got shot at the Bundy standoff
Patriot
Mad Dog James Mattis General Mattis
Pre 2018 or 2080
I can't give you that information
Going
Updated to Trader
It's not updated but he is a patriot on the website
Okay here you go
William Barr current attorney General William Barr
God I need timestamps.
People everybody is a traitor or a patriot
Because they're all f****** shady as s***
Okay
I should have assumed it was trainer otherwise why would you even bring it up
Representative John Lewis
Civil rights activist
John Lewis
Is there a super Trader
Bernie Sanders
Timestamp
There was a time when
These people especially would consider burning a
Patron but I'm going have to go with Trader you're correct trailer okay
Edward Snowden
Is it there's a couple here at the end that are a little bit too tough
Interpersonal
Even in the concern
Community there people who would say that
Snowden was absolutely a
Traitor and there are plenty
Patriots
I'm going to go with
Patriot
Son of a b****
And finally last one
Justice Antonin Scalia
Cub got a trailer
I'm fine with it I did find if you go through this almost everybody who's the Supreme Court Justice
Hell yeah cuz it is sooner or later you'll be able to find one Kaiser where you're like that's a traitor
Honestly that site is not nearly as fun as the idea of it is it's mostly the walls of text and I should tell you there are
Way more traitors that they preach
Hey Waypoint is Alex needs to do better than this few wants to Superior judge just because she's going to send his friend to prison
She had no legal reason to not dismiss the case against Hillary
It's entirely possible it's a coincidence that she got both Rodger and manafort's case
They're clear counter-examples in her judicial history like that of Jesse jacks
Junior the temperature theory that she's a biased
Set up kind of Judge
You can really tell though he knows that more people are listening
Detroit sound real smart and focus
And I think it's
He's doing it wrong you should be going full cravings
Yeah probably
Nobody wants to
Listen to a professional broadcast your Alex
F****** Jody
So earlier you said that he's not building suspense right before he started freaking out
It's because he has big news
I talked to some of the journalists are scared to come on
About
What was said
This morning and the trial
When I tried
Put Rodger in prison
Until the February 6th
Done and what happened there
And what was said about
Rodger
And myself and you the lister's of this show
You
Building up the suspense
I'm getting some documents
Especially
Erstatement
Get this precisely the way it is
About me
Yeah so he's he's teasing you know he's asleep trying to tease this out
Because he has a big things
Happening on the show
Isn't that what the real is really have anything
So he's trying to make up something frantically
Trying to find a way to spin whatever he's got going
Yeah which is just basically that the people the prosecution was
Arguing
That his actions
Were Abri to Rogers
That's really all this this this holties is all about
But here's the thing
Alex does have something huge
Going on
But most people listening to his show wouldn't think this is
Huge only I think it's
And that is that he's got Larry Nichols coming on
Join us again
Sunday on the Sunday Shelby lot for 6 p.m. or Monday
We get more time
For the clintons was Green Beret.
Cih.
He didn't help them
Get elected
Bill Clinton in a memoir gilded, very dangerous person
Well he is
Stanford
Crazy
To my knowledge Larry Nichols has not been on Alex's show in over to you
I can't say with absolute certainty but I know that I haven't heard him on the show since September 21st 2017
Why would I remember very well because I was at a Larry threat to Blackmail Congress and Mueller
If they didn't stop invest
Navigating trough old crime
Great day
That was a good one there's something going on here and I think it's something that I've been sensing for a while now
When Joel skousen started making
Increasing appearances on the show I thought it was possibly an indication of Alex shifting things a little bit in his show
Thousand made it very clear that he doesn't think much of trump and actually called him an idiot many times on Alex
The show
After the 2016 election when Alex was at the high point of his Trump infatuation
This led to them not seen eye-to-eye and he really was around too much as a trusted source
But he's coming back on the show now which is interesting
More regular
Then on November 14th
Sorry on the 13th Alex it's deep pieczenik back on the show after him being gone for over a year
And now here we have Larry Nichols brought back from the dead after a very long absence
I think these three reappearing a very interesting and I'll tell you why
Alex lost a lot more expert than just these three when he went full Trump
Webster Tarpley hates
And he would never talk to Alex again
Wayne Madsen
I hate Trump
And now if use Alex as some kind of a shield most likely for is
These were dudes that Alex built narrative
Webster Tarpley was like 1
Third of The Obama Deception documentary
You were Central figures
Annabi infowar
Thousand Steven Lee rear import into
But they're guys that
Alex
Has don't hate
For what he's become
Steven larrier into Trump
But obviously for their own reason
He wants to install a dictator and Larry just hates
Thousand doesn't like Trump but he still respect to Alex because they're shared in Saint
Communism
These are the three experts from days past to Alex Cooper
Credibly bring back into his roster while transitioning wafer
From chop successful
And that. Skousen to be presented as an expert who is regrettably right all along
The trumpet body to great
Promise for them but wasn't
Coptic enough
The follow-through
You can make up stories about how Trump could have saved everyone but the counter-coup is just too strong
Larry can connect any stories about any Democrat to the clintons
And Whisper ominously about witches he is got
You've got that
Let's kill in space
Witches
It's like he's the best at playing Six Degrees of Kevin Bacon butt
Instead it's always clean
I accept that I'm probably
Play overthinking
But from where I'm sitting
Seems very suspicious
Thousands been reintegrating and then on the day of the impeachment inquiry starting the hearings Steve is back
And now the day Rodger is found guilty Larry is back
It could all be a coincidence I'm totally
Find the Baddie look
Various
Find possibility
But these dudes were regulars on the show years
And just a few years back
They were the people who replaced by the Gavin McInnes is in the Mike starcevic crowd
For them to be making a resurgence
Feels like it means something
But I want to stress that I could
Just be drawing conclusions that aren't necessarily there
Another reason that I think this maybe might not mean anything
Too big
Is it Alex's in the middle of trying to pretend that Hillary is secretly running in 20
T20 so why wouldn't he call Larry
He's trying to run an imaginary Auntie Hillary campaign
But it doesn't have Rodger this time
So it makes sense that he would resort to whatever he remembers from
That's the pizzagate narratives coming back
And Larry Nichols dumbass showing back up to
It makes some sense
But it does also fit a pattern
Of what you would do if you were trying to save what
You could
Bright-eyed what I see is that
That
What is it
Common Sports narrative
We're the guys hanging out with his friends
We're from We're from wherever will always be from wherever
Doesn't matter he goes to the big time
Stops hanging out with his friends is like now I don't have time for you
I got the president elected I'm above this s*** and they didn't get you went back to his routine he's got a
Broken ankle and he's never going to be able to play again and all the sudden
Now he's back home
He's got a
F****** fix the relationship
View and it's difficult
To tell how much is it
Is
Some sort of a plan like that
But it feels like
I mean we're hearing these indications of Alex being like
Trump doesn't he's not going to
Back. So you're not going to Pardon Trump Rodger I don't know what I'm going to do
You have
Simultaneously the recurrence of these
These people who are
The people from his
Past
That have drifted for various reasons
Could reintegrate
And and work
I don't I just told man no here's with Eva ears with you and better and this is where I got it
Alright he's he just came to La's been working his ass off
Rodger Stone
Get signed as his agent immediately
Trump he's got that he's the head of the studio he's getting all kinds of pictures lined up everything is going
When is wife all the sudden
Stone
Gets arrested in truck stops answering his emails and now
That's where that's where I see it so that's where
He goes back to his f******
Missouri Hometown little improv theater
Bang it out yeah
Start a band whatever whatever the reality of it is I sent to drifting away
I sense a possibility of it being
More anti-hillary than Pro Trump
Certainly
These are the
Three people that I can think of
That aren't around or hasn't been around anymore
That Alex
Could still
Douche it where
Yeah a lot of those other people if you try to bring them into the show
It would be confrontation
It would be like if Webster Tarpley was on
He would probably talk about how libertarianism is
Is a gateway to Fascism and I don't know.
Like what the f*** is wrong with you
Then all those things would
Turn
Steve skousen
Larry r
Ways to connect
The past to the present
To have a coherent
Connection of Brentwood
They're like a constant
Stanley lost terminologies
It's a bridge between the past and the present
That he can use to work toward
Future that is different
Then what he has now
I don't know I don't know. Just doesn't have Stones Rolodex
Could be there's a there's a hundred possibilities
Could just be that he's I got no one else or talk to him
It could be nothing but
I just sent trends
P****
The problem with that
I don't see any way that it
Because if you're going to stop
If you're no longer
Carrying water
And if you're no longer defending all of the s*** he
Then you've only got
Anti
Hilary stuff
There's there's really nothing there
So you all you've really got left from
You do what you do have that to some extent I think that you have a tough time threading that needle
But
You could also really regroup
And be like okay
What we need is a trump but more competent
And loyal and trustworthy
Repeat shut up shut up about the whole f****** dictatorship
You get the f*** out alright
That will be another one
Sorry Steve was just screaming in my ear
You could you could see Alex trying again
With a more principled person or something
You can see him getting behind Jim Jordan as their new like Ulta
Or something like the new figurehead trying to reconnect with Rand Paul
Options
You could go to it right
Cool
You look too right
We talked about this a hundred times Alex's show works at
The counter to something as opposed to a supporting of death
So it doesn't matter
If he has somebody fully to support
You need to get that Albatross off his neck
And get back to
To just attack
Attacking Hillary
Is something and the Deep state
Can't be done without
Anybody can
And skousen Larry
And Steve
AR
Great tools
To have for him in terms of furthering that goal getting back to what works
As opposed to sycophantically
Praising
Your God
Yeah and they're all what is it done for him
You got Carpe donktum hanging out
Yogi's got there
He's got all these meme dicks
It's deathly alternative yeah that is
That is so
That must be so disheartened
Just like that whole like
The reason that I joined the truck
Cuz I was prey
Elevation
And all I've got left
Is
Carpe donktum
A guy with stuff with a hammer I don't know if he's going back on the Shelf
I doubt it
He's a little bit big
Do you know who isn't
Larry f****** things
So we get to hearing this raspy ass voice.
What is the Rodger Stone situation
About 25-30 years ago
Rodger
Attack
So Rodger Larry wants to bring
Soros
Into a conspiracy here but it's really funny because of this next clip
UCare come up with Soros
He's like I know there's a bad guy
Nobody's talkin about
What's his name
Tell me you're saying Mana
It's okay Larry stay there
I don't I don't think that that is like an aging
Memory loss kind of thing
I think that's just not at Larry heaven
Seriously but not really knowing what he's talkin
Yeah yeah
That's why I don't remember this guy's name
8U juggling too many bad guys in it
Yeah probably
So many Boogeyman
Who knows which one supposed to go where
Soros
The Rock
So
Alex comes back we heard that music again
I'm telling you it plays throughout most episodes
He hates his crew
So much I would too
Do they come back in Alex gets
Talking about how he's really mad about the fact that his name came up in the trial
I'll probably get destroying the process here the next few years
You know what
Because
Are you
Cannot do along with these people
Department of trump
Entitled
But they really believe I should be in a jail cell
Because that which war criminal Hillary didn't get in
Nichols Lake Hughes breaking things
Also
Well he's back soon
Do you really get into all this
Please remember what recipe
So what Alex is talking about there in that clip and it's basically just the big news that he had to deliver it it keeps teasing
I already thinks that the court wants him arrested
Yeah this is neither true nor is it big news
I was trying to find ecliptic out of him talking about this but honestly the deliver of it delivery of it when he gets around to it is so rude
Rambling and incoherent that I felt
We just talked about it
On his show on the 14th Alex reported to have that message
Rodger
That message was largely felt like he was going to be found guilty and he wanted Alex's audience
Pray for him and for Trump to pardon
This is unfortunately wrapped in messages
From Alex that if Rodger got found guilty of what needed goes around the White House and bullhorn them
And that it was the end of freedom
Caught up in it already
So because of that you know they did
Just felt like we've already
But that's the new talked about in court that Alex
Might have been responsible for breaking the gaggle
So ultimately you know
Holding Rodger after
The sentencing after the verdict
Is there any thinks it's the fact that they retained the gag order is something that is very responsible to do
So while under the gag order Rodger posted an image of Judge Jackson
Lacrosse hair
Alex has a habit of targeting people for harassment and that behavior has been particularly badly
It is to botched attempt
Suggesting Rogers potential juror names
Particularly notable
Plus the case Rodger was being tried for involved Witness
Tampering and intimidation
Putting them under a gag order is like spending someone's drivers license when they're awaiting trial for a DWI
You show me
Did the behavior response
More importantly you can hear
Italics this frustrations grow
His buddies are out here on the front lines and either doing everything they can
Trump refuses
Active support
Alex's TV turning on Trump so many times
I can't really trust anything
But I think that like
His Petty feelings about being abandoned
Are the most plausible thing
You are
If this is a situation that could easily
Create those feelings
That's the only reason why I take any of this like
As a possibility that's worth discussing
Like his behaviors so well
He could trample all over any political position that Alec
Alex has ever had
Obvious but he go but if he's
If he's like
Oh no sorry Alex I don't care about you what are you what have you done for me lately
I don't remember you being that important to me
Your actions were great but they don't deserve any
Reward
Is
The recipe for him
Yeah so in the next clip Alex is talking to Larry and makes an interesting caveat
Just get into the impeachment
And what you think her next moves are going to be
Front bolts
Anything I say Alex is not responsible for it's from me and that the prosecution won't come after me come out
Rodger Stone go to jail
He won't be there a week
Why is Larry saying that Alex is responsible for his work
Is that because the last time he was on he blackmailed Congress okay so there is that
And you don't want to have any of that masks the boilerplate
They're definitely does sound like there was a feels like
Talk a lot of s***
I don't want to get too I'm already getting soon already places
Everybody everyone yells at me
Me for things that my gas say can you please make a disclaimer
I wouldn't be surprised if every guest
Going for it doesn't have to put some sort of that Bart
Yeah so Larry has a theory and it's not well fleshed out
In his
Words
But I know from looking into this.
And he'll get
That way
LOL spelled out those words
Talking about the impeachment
Deep
Thanks
That it is very notable
That Adam Schiff
Is a screenwriter
Yasso
What's going on
Is
That Adam Schiff
Is screenwriting
A play
In real time
That is the impeached
That's basically the long and short of his beer
Impeachment
Play one
To the prosecutor
Which one
Is that it turns out
This whole script is going through now it's a subpoena crap
Figured out that the moment case
About halfway through the Mueller investigation
Adam Schiff
Thought about that hobby when we're back in 2 minutes with Larry nickel cuz I'm going to shut up for a while let him break it down
I mean to make this
You've literally saying it's a screenwriting getting it's not metaphorical
He's he's doing it as like a f****** Twilight Zone episode where the mystery novel writer
The Mysteries become real
She's at so Larry is on
Primarily probably because
He had this story about the Ed Buck being involved with Adam
Gets to that
And then
I don't know if you can make more sense of this than I can but Larry literally says in the middle of this clip
Adam Schiff went to these parties at bucks house dressed like an Egyptian
Because he's a screenwriter
Okay
Flummox
Dancers going after the ringleaders crimes exposing them and that's
Withered confirming
Knows that Adam Schiff
Good bodies
Asbach
Is there any 16 x bizarre sex parties
Ritualistic mock human sack
Sacrifice
Diaries
Black man
Someone crawling begging is he
Punch needle
Sacrifice
Purportedly
Nichols getting back
What you were saying longer saving coming up
Please continue with the hobby of
What your sources are saying
Back off your receiver a little bit
Verification 27 times
He was at a party
It's always up in evening
Battleships
Like you said Egyptian type
Demon
Freaky weird Egyptian type demon outfits because he's a screenwriter
Now
I mean
Diagram what I think
He's saying so you're taking some notes
So if I understand this correctly
Yeah
In order to further his screenwriting career
Head of the house Judiciary Committee Adam Schiff his dressing
Egyptian outfits
To go to ritualistic sacrifice
Yes and it's
Important to note that they must be
Because he only goes in the
Evening time
Alright
So I want to get this out of the way up top nothing I'm saying or any takes on this story that I have should imply that I have
Any interest in defending Ed buck
I hope his case is Thoroughly investigated and he's punished to the fullest
I think it's good for people to talk about that case as long as they stay grounded in reality
However I don't think that's what Larry is doing
Larry's been pushing this Adam Schiff narrative since at least October 11th
When he made a startling allegation on the YouTube show crowdsource
The truth
It's pretty complicated
Describe what that show is but I think it might be fair to say it's a bargain bin Infowars
Where Alex's guest go when Alex
Is too busy
Like when you get kicked off Twitter you go to gab it's kind of the same thing when a guest is no longer welcome on Infowars
It still has an itch to lie to people they end up going to crowdsource the truth
Jerome corsi and Larry Nichols are two of the show's regular guests
The host Jason Goodman is also welcome to his show some of the more unsavory character
Who popped up on Alex's show over the years
There's Robert David Steele the guy who told Alex a globalist
Can kidnap children to Mars base
I do think the two of them have had a falling-out though goodnight Robert David Steele
There's Laura Loomer
Larry klayman
Playsuit Alex along with their on Coursey
Is Jack Pacific
Project Camelot overlap in which Jason is head Kerry Cassidy on at least once
As well as her big
False flag expert
We haven't covered because it was episodes are not Project Camelot fun
Reviews on Project Camelot Circle false-flag along with
Jim Fetzer sometimes the guy who wrote the book no one died
So much
That if Adam Schiff and I don't even care if it's true or not
Adam Schiff likes to write screenplays and it's off time and that's evidence that you
Some sort of a
Evil whatever it is but Kerry Cassidy tried to write screenplays
But
She's the only one who's exposing the real truth now
Nothing matter
So hilariously the thumbnail image on one of the videos of this crowdsource the truth that was interviewing old lady
Is just
The Illuminati card game
Okay of course and has the title quote our globalist Elites Playing Our Lives as a game
Honestly I've considered covering that show as a Wacky Wednesday option but every time I've tried I just find the host so boring and
Content very unengaging
With Larry coming back into Alex's life I might have to reconsider but I probably won't will
Jason Goodman himself has been at least featured on David Knight show but I'm not sure he's ever made it to the rarefied air of being on
Alex
You also sometimes talks to people who Alex doesn't ignore
Like Mike Adams and Owen Shroyer
Also Jason Goodman was one of the journalists who attended Alex's weird press
Back in April of last year
It does show the traffics in all the real dumb
Cool conspiracy theory
Like pizzagate Seth rich
The Las Vegas shooting
He's even down with the dump Dennis Montgomery Village
My point here
Is it this is basically a junior varsity Infowars and it's not a good
That's where Larry Nichols started putting this information out after which point it gets repair
Repeated ad nauseam in The Fringe
Right-wing media
It's really easy to get this narrative cooker
Larry's a lunatic
The 20-something year record of making
Shut up for attention and money
But he can just go on a dumb YouTube conspiracy show say so
Stupid s***
Then sites like true pundit will report
Well breathlessly calling Larry a consummate Washington Insider
Clinton confidant
Jacked true pundit post articles and headlines like quote
Whistleblower
Investigating Adam schiff's Disturbing Behavior at Ed bucks method
Sex house with no confirmation or evidence other than Larry saying it
Sites with real smart
Sonic games like Global Intel hub
Get your report on the story linking to the true pundit story saying quote
Officially ship is under investigation
His story get to the added Flair
Of credibility because there are pictures of Schiff and buck at events together
Because Buck was a huge
Political donor
And because of that of course bucks crime deserves
Particular attention
I don't disagree
Or any other politician is they turned a blind eye to Bucks actions because of like financial support
And they should be held to account for that
But the simple fact of buck donating to shift or ship being seed with buck at a public event
It doesn't prove anything on its own
What Larry and Alex are doing is completely unacceptable
Because they don't care about bucks crimes except how they can be used to further their political ends
I find that shity
Is any of the stuff can ever be proven in any way I'm fine changing my position
For now I have a standing position of
Of not believing a damn thing Larry Nichols says
Nothing could be confirmed by someone who isn't a career liar
Yeah that picture that
But you seem kind of pic
Picture of trump with every Democratic lawmakers
Does that mean they're all 8
So do you understand though this pipeline
You have Larry in October going on crowdsource the truth which is a dumb
Conspiracy YouTube
Joe he says this b******* on there it gets picked up by a Blog
It has no goddamn
Editorial stance or standards at all
And then it gets repeated
I like a game of telephone from the are confirmed in the mainstream news
It's about blog post on true pundit
It's based on Larry
Just talkingshit
Yep this is how the pipeline work
CFI High School pictures
Throwing 95 miles an hour in a
8 month
What's there in the maze
Sure
Larry has an interesting position about these
These hearings that are going on
The impeachment inquiry
This is crazy
You'll notice what they're doing they're using this
Siri
Come out
And as we found out with them
If you don't have anything to report to get hold of us
And Chip will scream apart
Want to say
And of course
They're making it very clear
They'll never touch you will protect you
Open casting call Leeza in impeachment inquiry
Another way of saying that is he will include you in
I know
Even if it's literal that's why God that's
Bulshit Larry Clary
Hardrace from you not this soft bulshit know where is usually this week
Story right you will park at very dumb so what the other things Larry is bringing
This
Mentality
Now that Rodger is going
Prison
We've got to be the voice of r
No
Your info on Snap
We stand behind out tonight or anything like that
I'm just like so he's going around to the United States and their down-ballot funding
Skuter gin County Sheriff
Anybody stand up
America
Just like anybody else
So
Larry is saying that we
Voice of Rodger Stone right now
We have to be
Now that Rodger can't speak on Infowars then
We have to be Rodger Stones voice
Suspicious I think we do and now he's remembered soros's name is remember the narrative you supposed to push and that is
That they're trying to
Hippies
Prosecutor is in in rural areas in order to
Camp down rural descent
These f****** dudes in
County Sheriff
Where do the highest Authority why why would that even cross your mind is not a crazy
Nothing to say
Soros is funding new County Sheriff's in order to
Well it's because I think they recognized that the largest
Share of their base
And their audio
He's probably people in rural areas
Disconnected from
Barger
Communities
Who are County Sheriff
I am so like it does serve their interests to try and make them more scared position
That's just so slow
But Larry is insistent
This isn't about Rodger
This isn't even about Trump
Thank you
They know what they're doing
Change
Did you commit all those rides
Beers Ago
That would be a cool
Ian
Look
This is all like just
You know trying to personalize this to the audience
You know whatever it's exactly what you'd expect them to
And also what you would expect them to do
Is Larry
He's coming back
Pay the bill
And everywhere you turn
Big words and everyone in submission
It's a blessing to hear you Alex
Commission
Don't do it
Stop it
This is part of the arrangement upon his return
Wow
Or even if it's not it's just Larry knows the game
He knows what he has to do
And that Harkins all the way back to sir
Ted Anderson
Gold sales
Oh yeah
Apparently
Bulshit
Alright you might as well be reading off
Totally
So do you think Larry thinks that Hillary is running
You know what I mean
How to say that Larry thinks that there's no way Hillary's going
What she
Trying to do
What is orchestrate
Actual candidate and then when the
Candidate wins election
She will kill the candidate and assume the role of president that would be better you just
What I'm seeing what you see on it
Going down
She needs to be the head of it and she plans to be bad of it
In the past if you have me on again
I'll be glad to tell everybody exactly
What they're doing
Yeah you do let's flashback to when Larry was saying that Obama was going to run again in 2016 and then
Declare himself America into a Muslim country
So he would be the
Baby king of mobile Islam right well it was either that or
Trying to ruin his legacy as much as possible to remember when Larry was saying that they were going to launch a FEMA permit provision
Government state of emergency because
When the clintons do that if they're in charge
Write the president when now that goes into effect
And there are no sun
Congress members who are coming out telling you the truth because when that s*** goes down baby come to me
Yeah well it's either that or
Great
If you accept that there are only two possibilities each time he only was half wrong on boats
Sure
So did like when he says
And she sees that it's going down that's what he's talking about
Whatever government that where we get Kings and Dukes is about to start and she better be in
Charge of that
Liberty talking about this is like
Horseshit
Oh yeah
So anyway
You know
Alex
Try to talk about this
So he
Alex starts telling a story that Rodger told him
Free guy
It's okay for him to tell the story no I'm going to go with
Err on the side of caution man but it's about Rodger getting threat
If you didn't do what the globalist wanted him
Err on the side of caution Alex has also been threat
But there's a weird reason why
He doesn't talk
Specifically about these threats
I was told this before they
Goddamn
And so I can say it but he did have people reach out
Talk to him from the system to turn against Trump daily Malone
Add cigar SWAT team raid
I've had the same stuff as well
The closer than things like that and I and I and I
Occasionally
So I don't ever break those deals that's not criminal to meet with
The criminals
Meetings with the mafia people's Representatives
And there
Basically like I'm ever going to kill you I might well just go ahead
You're going to get it after that politically
The Alamo jackasses I will
You understand
You're going to get it
Blood running down both sides
Music again
And so if I understand
Sanders correctly tell me if you have a different interpretation haha
He has been threatened by these globalized talk about it specifically more but he agreed to
Confidentiality is confidentiality cuz he still likes to take meeting with these global
I don't break these NBA's with
Literal demon vampires who just having a meeting time to kill me
Cuz then what would I do maybe they have some
Something important to say sometime you never know
Keep your friends close dead
But keep your enemies closer by never violating their idea that's so stupid
I can't believe someone would hear that be like that make sense
Everybody
Sofa
Do you understand now they're like when I was telling you they keep playing the music
Pears like this seems weird
Do you agree with me because you look use I've never heard this I've never heard the same song this many
How to be a little bit hesitant
To accept my
Conclusion that it seemed weird
Okay
Well I get the point that I'm safe disappointment up
It doesn't seem weird to me because the level of incompetence is
Is established at such a high level
Man that they just don't know how to change the
I can't tell what the explanation is but there's something
Speed accidentally put their iTunes on repeat and they didn't know how to change it the problem with that is that it's not the old
Calming music
Play it played a lot
But there's other music like in this next clip Alex comes back from break listening to music from The Good the Bad and the
Arabic some say something
Really f****** weird question
Perfectly. The really great movie reality
So that's
Alex clearly articulating this this weirdness that he has about fiction and reality
There's this there's an unreality to the movie that makes it real
It makes it real
House
Yeah
Larry is gone but
Alex is still talking about the
This Buck thing
For a little bit
They can't stop
Muppet Chef
That's not just Nichols and that that's in the news he was in all those party for that boss
Drug addict
Look at chef
It's not just nickel saying that it's news articles that Larry is the only source saying it
News
Newsela true pundit the news is doing a dance
We can believe in the media which I've course have been screaming that you shouldn't believe
At all.
Never believe the media they're all lying
To you they are always lying
You cannot trust them
Embarrassing
This is this is a good to Media
Amin is only bad if they affect
That's good point
So Alex
Rambles a bit about evil
How do you not into it
That's the description on every one of our four April Fools
You should go back and edit every one of those pod cows Rambles about the devil
So he's moving away from the Devil
Anything corrupt
Evil
That was a joke
Accelerating away
Satan is behind
I just want
My children
Your children and all these wonderful spirits
They're good gentle creatures
Witnessing to the universe
And Justice and freedom and away from the Fallen Twisted in
Gone
Away from Adam Schiff
Aleister Crowley
You want to go away we want to leave you we want you
I want to give you guys a chance cuz
Get ready to sell my house so I can finally project which is I'm glad to do
It's just that with that energy
Want money because it's a weapon system
And it's because I can block his enemies attacks with it and then I
Open carry out operations against
Products you need everybody should get the force
Lawsuits are not going well I know I'm sorry he's funding new projects I apologize
Soap for a long time Alex is said that it
He has to be willing to sell his house to fumbi infowar
But this is literally the first time I've heard him talk about it as something
He's actually doing
I don't know if I believe
Because Alex is a liar and it's in the middle of him doing an ad.
Possibly pretty likely to create more incentive for people to give him by
But assuming that that's not a lie this is a very very bad sign for Allah
There's no way that selling his house could provide enough capital for him to run Infowars
For very long
This would just be a matter of him trying to buy a few months
Set best
The reason I say that is because Alex has made it clear that cost
Tens of millions of dollars to run Infowars
It's a complicated business with a gigantic Studio or rent it
It's not low
Tons of bandwidth costs
Entire supplement business with a warehouse and distribution
Connected
A bunch of lawyers working on a ton of cases
I don't know if tens of millions that figure is correct
But I feel like it could be closed given how many moving Parts in Vellore
The most expensive home sale ever in Austin with a gigantic mansion that went for 21.8 million dollars
And currently the most expensive house on the market
It has an asking price of 40
18.9 billion dollars
Alex obviously has a nice house and I bet it's worth a lot
But it's nowhere near the top end of Austin
Luxury property mark
If I had to guess I would be surprised if his house was valued at more than a few mil
Alex's said that his family owned some land
I have a hard time imagining that his parents were still alive would allow himself acreage
Been handed down generation Ali just so he can
Can keep up paying the legal fees
His Radio Show his rack.
Plus I think if that's what he was saying he might phrase it differently
Ultimately I don't know what to think here
If he's saying that he's selling his house when he's not
It's been it's just a crass and manipulative marketing ploy
I think that's possible
If he's actually selling his house then
His show is going
Not it's not going to make it another 6
It's not like Alex
Is Justin a tough
Matching needs to get through it and then everything will be fine
You fuc
In the long-run whether you makes it through this crunch or not
His reach is non-existent
His best friend
He changed his career for is going
Prison he's crawling back to Larry Nichols
Steve pieczenik
Is attempted to dodge the Sandy Hook lawsuit or all failing
The president has made the center of his career is getting impeached
Those aren't little obstacles in the road
Their major problems at six million dollars is
Probably not going to
Basalt
Again
I still think it's probably full of s***
But if he's not using
Serious trouble
And I would probably advise him a
You know this
You need the house recorded podcast in trouble
This is such a one of those moments
It's like when you're being
You got to admit sooner or later that
Whatever it is that they're they have on you is
Not as damaging
Continuing
Call game
Just get it out get it done
You'll be okay
Let's let's look at this
Let's say you've fallen for the Nigerian scam
Fair enough. Is it good way of putting it
Keep going
You're in the sunk cost fallacy
Genuinely
There's a way out of this world
It's it's probably not outside of like
Scaling back and seeing if you could regrow a little bit somehow I think that's probably the only real ploy
Dumping money into Infowars at this point
Short of finding an angel investor who will give you million
Into dollars millions and billions of dollars to keep doing what you're doing
Is a fool
Pools game
Yep
So Alex at this point starts
To speculate about
So when I was talking about this stuff in like
Alex bringing these guys back in
Seems indicative
Of a move away from trump it was a feeling that I was having
And when I got to this point new episode
I really feel like
Maybe it's baby it's more than
Then just
My feelings
Are you pissed
Trying to sabotage
I know that
WeChat these people
Hospice
Yes
Yes because
True
That's true also
God you're so close
Always you know
Let's not get distracted by the details stay on there
Stay on target your doing this
Come on
Because
Watertown did nothing wrong except
Well it is legally there
So you here this year
Introduction of thoughts about a you-know-what maybe Trump
Was put in
In order to
The pacify a neutralized elements of the right-wing
That are anti-gay
That's what you need to get there that's fine because if Hillary was in office
Not we would put up with this s*** you now that you absolutely nailed it come on put two and two together only doing it because we're holding out hope
You going to enact the white nationalist dictatorship that we will
Where is it
I mean it's still the end result still isn't good thinking it is what it is
So I'm he's just at the end of this episode he's just starting to recognize these things
You called me
Have a message for
Doing
Calculus
What's going on his brain about Rogerstown this is a lot bigger than Rodger Stone obviously
Not good
Rodger stone is not a fart in church
That we just try to put
Ninja Run
Chords this
Pardon Stone
Talk about Stone
Just like about Julian Assange
Call Julian Assange release the info
The lack of loyalty
Everything we told Trump
All the moles everything Indiana
Daddy
Play it safe while playing it safe goddess
Where We Are
Stop playing
I mean that's also illegal
It's got the
Political power
Twisting out the wind is not good
Right there you start to get the feeling that it's
What Alex is doing it soda waking up
From a being manipulated to recognize like
None of this s*** that I thought was going on is going on
Now
Some of that could be
The way you soft-launched a parody
Piano like you soft launch pivoting away
By pretending that you're waking up this deception that you
Or it could be real I don't know what it is but you can
You can clearly see
That Alex is starting to weigh more explicitly talk about like
Probably is not good
My theory
He is in a cult
This is as close as he's as he's going to get in the next
The next week is going to be him
Get right back, cuz it happened over and over again. But also you have to recall when he did that thing after the
We know
From going over it Alex turned on Trump
Drunkenly on air that night let's say he talked to Rodger who got him back in line
Rodgers not going to do that this time
Who does he have around him
He has people like Joel Sanders in
Don't get him back on Trump's team
I don't think
I don't think which is strange because everybody knows you listen
Right I don't think the reintegrative
Trump Network
Whatever is there
Like get Alex back
Into the fold if he starts drifting
He doesn't have the cult
It doesn't seem it doesn't
Seem like that influences
Is necessary here
And for that reason I think it's
Possible that some of these feelings will grow more than
With Rodger prison
Yeah if Rodger was there he would have been like Trump and I go way back we sucked
Same ladies together not weird it's not weird like that we've
Some fights in the past has made up but we didn't double team
I have no comment
That
It is entirely possible that this is going nowhere
Yeah and Alex will get back in life
That's entirely possible
Cuz I could see a situation where Trump does some sort of Overture
Yeah Alexandra
Back if possible
But I also see it is entirely possible that this will be enough and Alex will get where he needs
To go
One of the reasons
Speak that
Is
Very often
You'll see Alex's
Narratives
Pushing
Reflected in caller
So you get to call her
This guy has to say
Chris in Tennessee glencrest Round Here
How's it going Alex
Man I am a fired-up and just in war mode you don't sound like
I hear you
I'm a little sad in about what's going on thinking at a certain point when do we admit that Trump
Isn't a white hat
I mean Kingston sky
And what you said you hit the nail on the head earlier I think like
About to be smarter for the globalist to just
Valerian or would it be smarter for them to have Trump in
And just act like he's on our side
I don't take that idea
Because it
The swamp he listen to advisors
Rodger that
Stop during impeachment
The whole thing is a fraud everybody knows it called
Don't talk about yours all of that is just pure Mafia tactics
About Rodger
Assign
What's going on
He's done a lot of stuff like saying America's good and
Borders
By saying two things out loud
Is he
Trump is not a wimp
But
He's he's not as tough as he said
That's a really big wild on Alex's show
Do not say Alex's show his world is so
Bill toxically masculine
Like the
Action of masculine immature
Copies of bullies out there just
Or I can shop on people so strong
Was talking about that when he came back on the show that he's really not that talkative facade that he puts on that's why he needs
Either so Alex
You know being
No Trump isn't that
Tough is a
Huge slapping
Where is that might be
Something in another car
Contact someone else saying it your life
It's an interesting thought for Alex to say it's equivalent to him being like
He's not a man honestly
Saying he should shove
Isis up its dirty ass whole is like
Oh that's just gentle ribbing about his friends saying that you're not tough is
Yeah
So just call her and Alex keep talking
And Alex brings up at like
Hey you know if people stand up
For Trump
Trouble
And this caller brings up something
That I think is so f****** hilarious it catches Alex so off guard
Giuliani stood up
Just Cuttin Giuliani Lewis
Give me a break
Don't you think julliannis
Kind of shady he was probably involved in
Covering up 9/11 when he was mayor
Brother season right now
Giuliani is a smart guy
America
Whoops
Alex don't you remember how this is
The guy
No he was totally hear what he said there are two is like I'm more concerned with the season we're in
Yeah it's exactly what
Guy did 911 help cover it up yeah
Absolutely. Likes Trump now
That's the season were in
All that other stuff is not supposed to be important anymore
Idols I yell all the time about the mainstream media thinking you have no memory but you're supposed to remember it
Play build my career on 911 and all of this s*** yes absolutely 100%
Forget about Giuliani Elizabeth Novak.
I know you remember the original version but maclunkey
So we just got to do that's okay
And it's so awesome
Here's somebody like one of these callers who is like
Onboard with Alex and Alex feels like
Are we supposed to not like
Yes
Okay
B
Now I vases
Switch off one
Yeah hold on I'm going to need somebody to give me a cookie while I much the toll at the end of the f****** clip Alex saying
Don't think he's trying to screw Over America
How do you square that
Well I mean
Because he helped stage 911 it got us into the war in Iraq
And he's not trying to screw Over America
So this is the end of
The I guess what you would call the substantiv Rodger Stone
Pageant right
I don't know on the 14th you have Alex
Really acting irresponsibly whether or not Stone sent him a message or not
No position on that cuz I can't possibly have
But I can say
Whatever message Rodger sent
Alex deeply editorialize in a way that
The jeopardize Rogers freedom
After the verdict
Been on the 15th Alex response to the verdict being passed by
Marketing heavily and signaling
Very
We're interest in exploring the idea that Trump is not good it might be time
We got a
Jump shot
So that's pretty interesting
Now
He also talks to Rogers friend Tyler Dixon
It's just basically Rogers school
Is another narrative
And that is
I'll let I'll let out
Running Man
Written by
Stephen King
Yeah
Put somebody else's face on
Computers
Future
Wow like 2020 or something
That's how crazy all this is
This morning
A my workout partner goes look at this funny video
That your son wrecks tweeted
As soon as I saw the video I called Rex up in 2017 but finish High School
And I said you said that
Sent you this video
They said all I just heard that it's a joke and I said well
Okay somebody taking a blue screen of me
It's footage that I shot
The meme
We did a lot of the funny things I've done on Arab
Vegan
My head
Body
Thanks
And then
I guess somebody the process is his sent out this this green screen video
Now
Albion Court
Over this
Corrupting minors
So Alex's son
Tweeted out a green screen video of Alex doing some rapping
Little bit of wrapping okay and in the background it's like a booty dance
Okay it's just like women shaking their ass
Yeah so that's one state part of this
Right now the second part of it is Alex says it's someone put this over the green screen footage and he's trying to sort out
Who did it I got one culprit
What else presumably
Other people then check in without
He knows who he gave it to right now we got more suspect
Okay whatever investigation runs through one man and his name is carpe donktum
Yeah I don't blame anybody else for this
This is a little prank I'm going to have to go a deep state
God he sounds
Such an old
Yeah that is
That is weird old grandpa but
So now I find out
That my image can be put on the internet whenever they want and my son
Tweeted it out
Two people to talk to
Your son Carpe donktum
Bring this on your f****** radio show his Twitter account
Then take it away
So now Alex says seems to think that no one understand
What green screens are
Christ
If I was in the street with a bunch of women
Well it's just not good for kids to have you know
Yeah no we do
They're on the news illegal when it's
So everyone understands that I don't think I have a very tough time with that
That is
I do I do feel
People who are just
Absolutely unprepared for technology
Haha like
I imagine
You know you're my grandpa
He was born in
The Great Depression
He couldn't possibly have imagined that somebody
Take her face and make it say things like a course she begin
Loser s*** that's
Too big for her but I don't think Alex is overwhelmed by the actual technology everyone else exactly
Which proves
He himself is overwhelmed by all the technology to an extent
I mean this is a 02 me as it relates to the actual video I think it's just a dumb Alex me
I really give a s*** about it
But as it relates to Alex's like
Covering of it
It's weird I cuz he's seems to be legitimately concerned he really guy that there will be a consequence.
Screamed video
To the extent where I feel like he's trying to get ahead of the story
Because he ends up playing it on his show me feel like he hit in my mind hears what he thinks is going to
Happened in court
He's going to go to court he's going to play that video
And then he's going to play the video that was superimposed on it so you can see both of them playing side-by-side
Beyond a shadow of a doubt that of course this one time stamp from 30 years ago could not be the same video and the jury will be
Guilty
Cuz there's no problem.
Trying to get ahead of the story and here's the
Some of the funny things I've said over the air over the years I have some of this song before I think once
And
So they put me over it
It's my crime will probably go to federal prison for it everyday
Booty booty booty booty booty rockin everywhere rockin everywhere
Please Club
This is embarrassing
Lexi's embarrassing we already got their first Carpe f****** donktum
So embarrassed. Someone we got their first money
So
On this episode where Rodger has been convicted
Alex Spencer
Considerable amount of time
Doing damage control about it meme
That Hannah
Possibly hurt
He's doing damage control
About something that can provide
0 day only actually heard him in the court of public opinion
About like more purity
Tyrannical
Elementary
If you can search don't understand Greentree
And if he's concerned about that that's all so tragic
I'm going to lose out on my donut
What about green screen
Sonia said he talks to Tyler Nixon and and it's mostly just Rodger didn't do anything wrong he's being damned up I don't really care
It's not really all that
So I'm going to end
On a call
Metallica
2nd episodes
Sometimes on upset
Okay and this call is very much upset
I know we all want to do things
Like I said I am
Hublot officer
Tirehub everything and we've been legal and lawful and look what it's got us
Trump into
Give us a second chance
But he is how he is allowed drug people like Rodger Stone and
Wikileaks and everything else to go on
Caress to be
Have our hands tied behind our backs while we think we're in a fight
What we're losing
And it
Get hardcore this time to get extreme cuz we're losing our country
Trump will be impeached because look what they've done
Rodger Stone
Everything is falling apart
We cannot speak anymore we've lost our country as you said today we live in clown
Now is the time to make a stand
I'm afraid we're not going to have a country to come home to
Two references clown world of course a Neo-Nazi
Yeah you know what
That could not be more f***** up
We got a law enforcement
Music off
And what
Suggesting
We tried doing this the legal way we've tried doing all that and it's not working we need
Extreme
The only conclusion you can take away from that is let's do a legal ship
Yeah and if you listen to Alex's show what does that mean
Well I generally think it means it's a reference to
Killing people
Alright so if we pride
All of our legal in
Clearly what we need to do
It's figure out more legal in La Palapa
He's trying to say we need
That we say we need to be more
Creative with plausible law that's what he's describing dad
Active-duty law enforcement office
With very
Team Neo-Nazi ties be interested in violent
This is the part where it's really interesting
Because I think that there is
A dichotomy
Play and I don't know how Alex
Possibly work
And that is if there is this album
My tub is audien
But it's like he's faced easy Rodger being convicted inside while it's time to get argon there is no hope
Hope Trump isn't going to do it therefore it's time to shoot
And I don't know how you
Suppress that urgent your audience
He's built It Up Overtime
Like it hate it Trump is our last hope if it doesn't work out then
We have to go to the gun
That sort of thing
Mainstay of his rhetoric for a long time
What simultaneously
You start to
Like I don't think
That's what Alex is
Experience his transition
Because if he goes away from Trump
It's not necessarily at least where I hear in this episode
I don't hear him being like calling for
Since Trump do it we got a f******
Start civil war
I think that his
Attempt to
Focus on Hillary
His attempts to
Serta read maneuver what he's doing
It could lend itself to
More info War
So you have that
And then you have this element to the audience
I don't know what you can do with it
But it doesn't seem
Good this is
This is a
That Colour
Very scary
Because combine that with Alex
Moving away from
Anytime
Yo in in regards to Trump World
That we now exist in
We saw this
Bubble up
In real time
From
This Love
On the right way
We don't get Trump if it doesn't
Bubble Up from down where we are right
This this desire for
Autocratic
Right
This kind of thing bubbling up from below now the idea of well we got a
We can't be on Trump
We need to be anti whomever
We're no longer on Trump
We're no longer protected
Combined with the we've lost come
Sleep Athens
We need to start f****** guns out
All day
If that is kind of the new dichotomy that the
Conservative party wind up breaking into
Some weird s*** going to go down
Yeah but I think you're already seeing this
Like with the stuff with Nick Fuentes
Turning Point events
I think that's this is going to be real and that's one of the things I think is most
Troubling about the possibility of Alex
It will radicalize
Further
Yeah certain segments of his body
Yeah and the direction that they are going to go is
Kind of
Expressed by the
Absolutely
And so that it that's something
I never thought about this
Before
But
But I'm sure Alex hasn't either
But there is a part of his turning on Trump that like
Responsibility
There is there if he doesn't do it the right way a lot of people
Or at least your attic
There is like a real possibility of like
Real damage
Betrayed even by Alex
Batman
That means
We don't even have Alex in the infowar anymore
It's just you and me
Well there yet because if
Trumpkin
Be shown to be a traitor or whatever then
Alex can
And where you go from there what you choose to take as like
A good sorcerer
That stuff is
Struggling
It's troubling to think how you could go like what's worse
And that's what you would end up doing Daddy's
I mean it
It's very predictable this going.
By the way it has
When you figure
Power structures in the right-wing have always
Sing to co-opt
Lower
Distracting them with rice
Jason cultural issue
Shoes until 1 until 4 at the door.
To do all this s***
And by being able to channel that rage
They've been able to exist
State of minority rule
F****** forever
And now the rage is
Kind of getting out of there
Control
And they don't know how to react
Cuz half of them are that race
You know the power structure used to just be people controlling it
And now half of my are just
This crazy is everybody else
So I don't know why it's not
It is predictable
I have no idea what's going to happen
But it's inevitable
That we would get to this point yeah thanks just fractioning of
Stuffies
Inevitable group only gets smaller
Yeah and it's troubling
What
Could happen
As a
Alex if he doesn't do it right
And I honestly think
Bringing back
Bring back Larry
And having Joel skousen have a more prominent position in the show
Answer that is Alex trying to maneuver getting away for
I think it's incredibly responsive
I hate to say it
We will
Upon
That is a way to sort of neutralize some of that having to give Alex a kudos
Probably accident
And it's same way
Sort of
Doing it
I hate Trump
It's not like a violent
He's also more responsible
Then as a is a
Snapping of a twig
Where you just freak out and scream at Trump
The gradual disillusionment
Might be a much softer Landing
In some ways you would help
But whatever the case I mean I hate to make predict
Cuz I'm always wrong
We'll see what happens
I guess the biggest problem I have
The way that
Hillary with it
And so on and so
Beaufort so now
It's
It's very much that
We everybody gets disillusioned with the
Yeah everybody winds up thinking that politics
Going to be able to
Singing that it fails you in
Subway
The system
It's designed that way
But whenever
Did guy that you have
Touted as
The last guy
Turns out to disillusion you why bother with
Why bother with
That'll last guy is nothing
That's no disillusionment become
Despair
Despair in the hands
Of people who are
Let's say
Inclined towards militias
The worldview that that
Yeah expressed by these
Communist propaganda the Legacy
Includes the Turner Diaries
That kind of Despair is weaponized
Really easy
O'Reilly's
Weaponizer the right word it becomes a weapon really
And so I hope that that's not bad
Anyway I think that's the Big Dipper
Between
When we got
Faced with this kind of
Despair we started a
So I don't know we'll see what happens in the future
And it's really interesting to see this is how Alex respond
Narratively and also like he was sure he was going to get found guilty
So there's no like real
Surprised there's no need for a freak out necessarily
Non-normal Alex yelling
Freak out is when someone didn't have a
Story
Goodwill Special Report going problems
So I mean I think that's really interesting
We'll see what happens
But for now we have
Ouija
We're also on Twitter
We are on Twitter is at knowledge underscore fighting at go to bed Jordan
Facebook interview
Go to iTunes or other
Cast Yule app
Download it
Tell your friends
Job
No. Next time
Emilio Emilio
Dzx Clark
I am a weird freaky Egyptian type demon