I have great respect for knowledge B
MoneyGram
Stripe.com
Everybody we're couple dudes like sit around and talk a little bit about Alex
Indeed we are. Jordan
Pickler song ever gotten you through a
Time yeah I mean hundreds of them hundreds of
Go to like some people like in the olden times would listen to Blood on the tracks whenever they got a breakup
Something something like that you don't like thing that
You zeroed in on
Not as your song You Know
No I meant to say I got something that I've had to the longer
Yeah but somebody Mighty Bosstones stuff you know
I want to listen to half of Eli question the answers album
Probably be kind of sentimental about like talking
Songs in the garbage is that on that album I can't remember how to party that's on a different
Gets one more noise and other disturbances still disturbed by Boston song YouTube
The whole track listing of some of those albums
Terrifying
Love those album wake up in a cold sweat knowing this
Still got me through some tough times when I was a much younger man
Junior High and high school really loved a lot of that and maybe that has more of a strong sentimental connection
It's me a little bit ugly that's from devil Devil's Night Out
I can probably I haven't listened to any of that in a long time
But I bet if I turned it on
It would be really great
Next time I go to the gym
The other thing that comes to mind is now like I are a lot on the side of things like Kesha and Carly Rae Jepsen
And not in that stuff but that's not like as long-standing
Domino's pop
Is that like a counteracting allylic when you're feeling down you want to listen to bright shiny pop music
Like more than
Look up right now
I think it's because I listen to Tonto Alex Jones like I have a lot of toxic things coming in
Brightside
Siri
That's interested in a lot of cash isn't really bright and cheery
That's true
I know I don't have a song
Yeah that's right
So Jordan today
Situational irony
As I told you
Before we started recording he
I spent all day yesterday listening to Alec
What to drink to prepare an episode
Sunday
And Monday episodes from this week
And it's just it was one of the
I haven't had in a long time of just like
Feeling like it
All the with
Yeah I think it's just
Who cares
Sunday is it feels like him going back to his roots a little bit but it's just
Just kind of boring
Conspiracy stuff I just
It feels untethered and it Like Larry Nichols didn't come back on like he said he might have course
And listening to Monday and he's just talking about Trump going to Walter Reed hospital
Right okay and so it's all just drop is being poisoned
Poison on top of that I just felt like real
Inspired by it I felt like I
I did think it was a little bit interest
Only in so much as back the last time
Alex covered this
Poisoning narrative videos doing
The weather
The way he presented it was
They're trying to kill our president
You know it was very much alike Rodger calling for Global has blood
And the way I was I heard this
On Mondays show was much more like
Why what you going to do
What's the sense of Life president again
What do you expect from the globalist
There are people in their bags would be mad at them but it was almost like a prop
Yeah I just been was being done to him as opposed to like we've got to stop this from happening
Nothing but I also feel like I'm probably reading too much into
Smitty's just
I feel a little bit gun-shy about being too
Like over-the-top about anything but
I do think there's some friends easy as Alex was introducing
The narratives about is Trump there
The globalist
Stooges in here to make
Do to neutralize too much into that
Does going to like it
It's easy
Need to take Alex at his word and then be like
A couple months later
Shoot them they were talking about he was going to be going on to newer thing
Who burned by that a tiny bit in terms like oh I believe you
That's not fair no it's In fairness to us there's every reason to think like why this might be real but I don't want to
I don't want to jump
Too far into like
This time he's talking about poisoning he's doing
Anyway I listen to these episodes
Clips from that man like
Trying to find
Have to get into us
I feel like I was walking through mud and is like
I can't do this
So I've decided that we're going to do an episode today about a certain question
That I have been wrestling with and we brought up on the show before
It'll be sort of Wacky Wednesday issue as it's fairly wacky we are going to
Lord this question
I will get into that
In the moment
Do people have signed up and are supporting the show okay so first of all
Thank you so much you are now policy wonk
You got.
Next David thank you so much and I hope all is well
I'm a policy wonk
Next Justin thank you so much
Next
Propaganda thank you so much you're now about what you want
Asinine genius thank you so much
95.9
Are they finally likes it thank you to somebody who I donated on elevated level appreciate that very much so gravity head zero
Oh thank you so much
You're now a technocrat
Business heroin
So good
Freakishly large
Thank you so much gravity head zero
These gents to do that but be very helpful
So Jordan like I said
I have a question
Has been wrestling with
And the last time we dipped our little toes and
Project Camelot world
It was a question that was coming up
And insult
Important
And that is
Why is Kevin Moore doing what he's
He's doing right right alright he is the guy if you do not recall he's a guy who's producing and directing the doctor
Comentari about Kerry Cassidy of Project Camelot
And Mark Richards
And his actions seem
Very suspicious to me
So I want to give a little bit of an introduction for everybody needs a little bit of quick reference
On what has happened are you going to channel previously
You're going to need to do a voicemail
Word
World you've got to do the voice
So for those like a refresher
Early on in this doing this podcast this knowledge fight here we realize that talk about Alex Jones all the time
Good for anyone
To give ourselves in the audience a break we would take periodic little trips little Excursion
To talk about people who claim to have been to space
And claimed to talk to alien
You've been interviewed on a show called Project Camelot
Project Camelot is hosted by Kerry Cassidy the least credulous woman on the planet
Initially it was all a lot of fun with super soldiers and chocolate stealing Raptors
Until overtime at bake
Came clear that Kerry was holding some of the same underlying bigotry
We see and other right-wing Outlet
We're like this is fun
It's always her support for the protocols of the Elders of Zion was certainly troubling and I can't
I'm thrilled with some of her other comments about Jews generally speak
And suspicion
So over time it became less Whimsical and fun to listen to her show but her interviews with
Captain Mark Richards were still required viewing
Mark Richards is a man who paid a teenager to kill a guy who owed him money back in the 80s
Has been imprisoned ever since
Well in prison Houston talked it an elaborate story about how he's innocent because he was secretly off-planet at the time of the murder
Doing a space mission and its sentient spacecraft whose name is Minerva
And so far there are no holes in that Hill
He knows everything about human politics right Galactic Affairs and the only journalist he'll talk to is Terry Kath
Because he's in prison carry can't really interview him so she just goes to the jail talks to him then sits down in front of a webcam
When she gets home and reviews her notes
That's the name of her series about Mark Richards
Total Recall
Leave aside for a moment that the reference to a movie based on Philip K Dick's short story that plays with the idea whether or not Memories
These are real
That's not important
Over the years markets will carry some absolutely insane
Well she at which she then reports to her audience
Is Gospel coming to the very real and very reliable source who definitely isn't the murderer
He's a noble space Captain whose friends of raptors in the enemy of the evil Reptoid
He's got a you got a hell of a resume
You. I will give him a fake resume as long as the day
Enter Kevin Moore
A British documentarian
And Chandler
4 years Kevin hosted a program called
It still does to in some fashion
Call the Kevin Moore Show
Where he interviews some of dubious dubious people about paranormal and new-age kinds of topics
He's head Kerry Cassidy on as a guest and even interviewed Mark's wife Joanne Richard
You showed no signs
Thinking that what they were doing was absurd
Anthony's interview with Joanne
He completely white along with her stories about Mark being a secret space Captain who was framed for murder
But something changed at some point
And now Kevin is directing a documentary series about Mark Richards being a murderer
And how Carrie Joanne and another promark figure named Simon Park
Are all basically in a cult
Obviously Kevin is right about that
It's somebody's finally tackling this subject Richards being a liar
Because for the longest time when we've talked about it we both assumed he was telling the truth
He's really opened my eyes on the subject
Isabella's right
Mark is definitely murder and his Defenders are all delusional to send
But even if I agree with that conclusion something doesn't sit right with me about how Kevin reached the conclusion
You have no credentials as being a person who would have Scruples but now he's positioning himself as someone who's going to
Expose a major fraud
The Paranormal in UFO community
I didn't get it
I started looking into it
And this is all still reek
Well let's not forget
He still does not have any scruples
No
This is not a sea change
This is an isolated incident of him trying to do here
I suppose good thing still surrounded with scamming people for hundreds and
The dollars
It looking into Kevin Moore so far
No in the past I see nothing but a picture of a completely uncompelling charlatan
Like he has videos that we've talked about where he channels alien
Like this
We come to you
Many
The gift
Off Kevin
Is the gift to be able to channel
Triple
Entities
Multiple
Being
And that is
Kruger
In this special
Google timer
Canada's right now
He doesn't need to change his voice
Or accident different way
This is an agreement we have with him
Okay so he never is never going to get tired of that
Channeling aliens there's no rigorous standards of proof of what he's doing the psychic hotline
Use the show to give largely uncritical interviews to all manner of dubious folks like the employees of his psychic hotline
Or the guy from Apex TV who claims to talk to Time Travelers with really easy really just creating viral hoax content
Probably for ad Revenue
Kevin claims that he's making this documentary series because what. Marker doing is bad for the community of alternative Folk
Because they don't do their research they haven't done that there
Giving it a bad name absolutely
What they're doing is not real
Where is presumably what Kevin is doing is based on reality
It's an absurd just
Application for the documentary so I rejected
If we accept that can't possibly be why he's doing what he's doing
We're left to ask
What's really going on
I can't pretend to tell you that I solve this mystery
But I had a little bit of a theory
And I explored it
I'm going to present that theory to
Alright
What are the primary things that bothered me about this whole thing is worth some money coming
Who bigger Quest
Is Carrie his mom
No okay nevermind you already pitched at Marcus's dad
I know I've got one Theory
Where's the money coming from Jordan
Is Kevin more independently wealthy
Resale of a business ten years ago thats funding this whole thing
It's a relevant question because he's
Clearly traveling all over the place
Videos of him flying around he's going to California
Need to try and track down people involved in marks Casey's jetset
You're open for this documentary
He's gone all over the place and I will say that he has
Way higher production value than a lot of the folks I come across that this face weirdo Community was producing
Even assuming he look naturally talented video producer
There's still some money going in
Answer that question let me back to a video that Kevin posted
Introducing a new partnership
Withey Kevin Moore
Osho is in partnership with Ozark Mountain publishing
Taking weed
Beyond
Unexplained
Hello I'm Kevin Moore
And I host the mall show
Alternative late night talk
On radio
TV
And online
And I'm doing
Picture of Damaris
That's Amore
Now
The Marshall alternative
The edge of
Alternative
Radioactive
Programming
The show's mission
Is the ugly
Unawakened
Inhumans
Turnover researches
This goes on for a while about
All the books of Ozark Mountain publishing
And we're going to launch a platform where you can buy advertise
So it's
Comprehensive partnership
Do this is interesting
Ozark Mountain publishing is not a super huge publishing Outlet
So it seems strange that they would be partnering up with a not super huge paranormal show all the way across the Atlantic
Goshen
It's hard to say exactly what kind of Revenue Ozark Mountain publishing is pulling in put a review on Glassdoor from my former
Employee complaints that working there involves a quote crazy family managed environment
And says that it's a small company with less than 50 employees
It sounds right
I don't know why I think
For some reason I'm prejudiced against any company that is like
Ozark Mountain Air Ozark
About the Ozark water bottle
Singapore Mei you mean they make water bottles so they're bad
Lake of the Ozarks ever been there
Gorgeous like have you ever
Yes in the middle of Missouri
I think my buddy his parents had a lake house
We went tubing
Alright good time
Alright well then I retract my Ozarka prejudiced
Ozark is a big broad term don't be so bias okay
It was founded in 1992 by woman named Dolores Cannon
Doris passed in 2014 but prior to that she was a bit of a player in the world of the Paranormal
He's written a ton of books she put out the she put on the Ozark UFO conference which is allegedly currently
Right now in its 33rd Year I'm not sure that's true but it could be
I mean yeah the fire Fest is in its third year right something like
30 ER
I was being nevermind
Dolores was a doing hypnosis Back In The Sticks
What's Ryan help page
Listen to things like smoking
Hanover
Behavioral
Okay so she wasn't scamming
It's hard to say but I don't have a
I don't have a gigantic Lee negative
Sense about Dolores although I do think she's a little Scamp
But if you're trying to help people
Quit smoking with hypnosis that's way better than if you're charged $90 in a minute to get
Psychic reader 70 years
To cover
In the course of doing her work she stumbled upon a woman in 19 6
Regaled me with stories of a past life
When she was hypnotized
Dolores's workout interrupted when her husband got injured and she had to care for him and the family had to locate to the Ozarks
But by the late 70s he was back up and running hypnotize
I got a particular line and Dolores is bio pretty fun
Quote her early work was heavily focused on reincarnation
Which I got her acquainted and comfortable with
The concept of time travel
How could it not I mean
So many reasons
Sure I feel like those two things are not related
Not necessarily
So her work began is past life regression
But eventually grew into what she calls
Quantum healing hypnosis technique
Which is the name that you have trademark all right now
Little
And she continued to work in the field she found resistance on the part of the mainstream book houses to publisher writing and that she's
Started up Ozark Ozark Mountain publishing in 1992 of books of her own as well as those
Tons of other New Age sort of writer
Three of the books you put out where of her own
Victor they purport to be the authoritative interpretations of Nostradamus prophecy
Three of those
Well it's a three-part series
You can be certain that they are authoritative because Nostradamus himself tools are so
Alright
She was having her patient began speaking as Nostradamus and told her that everyone was getting his s*** wrong right
Because of changes to the french-language overtime
I need a Delores to write a book to correct the record
Of course you did I don't believe any of that
Course he didn't only writing
French but who cares
So Dolores Cannon runs this Publishing House
And they've entered into a partnership with the Maury Show in 2013
Which is kind of weird
What's up Thailand
I know how it can be when you're trying to get your name out there sometimes you make marketing decisions that seem strange to external Observers
Like a couple years ago I bought a Facebook ad
Princeton
But here's the thing
This wasn't just Ozark Mountain publishing buying an ad on Kevin's show
This was a partnership
Like in that ad that we was at that announcement it's a business integration sort of thing
You can tell I guess what this was not short-term
I were you two ton of Kevin's videos from the past few months
In 2019
And most of them start with an ad for Dolores Cannon
A great ad for deluxe
Define the power
To heal themselves
Physically
Emotionally
Spiritually
When I started teaching my classes it was in 2002
And I was just doing
The past life regression
And
Contacting Visa
Conscious Park
But then as the time went on and we found
Powerfulest
Do with it
A lot of the students begin progression doesn't really tell
What it's all about
This is so much more than that we think you
Change the name
So was a few years ago we decided to change the name
Quantum healing
Hypnosis
Technique
And this is the healing technique that reason album teaching it
Hortense 2002-12 year
What if you could time travel with them
Visit mythical places or Angelic Realms of a Wills
All the gallic
Help others
To speak to the highest selves
Yukon
Dolores has 2,000 people from
McChrystal
How to use
Qhht
I know you can learn her method
But going directly
To Dolores
Dot-com
And don't forget
Dimension the discount code
Mortal
So that's six years that the Maury show has been in partnership with the Dolores Cannon
/ Ozark Mountain publishing business
And that seems interesting to me yeah
Yeah
Having a coupon code for time travel seems very interesting to me it's not so much time travel for yourself it's the
Quantum technique
That allows you to help other people time travel
No I get that I think is even more irresponsible because you're teaching people how to do a weird therapy
Two other people
I'm not comfortable with any of this
Franchising your time-travel therapy
Borderline
I've got through tons of Kevin's videos and I can find no evidence
Do any other sponsors other than Dolores Cannon extending to the Ozark Mountain publishing
And his own website channeling.com which is little more than a front for Kevin psychic
So I don't see where any other income or flow of money is coming from
Accept this long-standing partnership with Dolores Cannon and Ozark Mountain publishing
These videos on his channel also have
Pretty low engagement
So be completely unbelievable for me to imagine
He's making any real money on YouTube monetizing
These documentaries but he's putting out like channel that what they call us channelers
This new documentary that he's put out that's not being sold anywhere maybe it's unlike real Boutique shop
Real
I doubt it I doubt even that
I can't see that that that being a strong Revenue stream
But he flew all over the place to interview these Channel
Like there is money
Flow something is happening
Right I just don't know exactly what it is
It makes me think
Live based on this he's either making a killing on that psychic hotline
Probably
I imagine there's no money coming in there but it can't
Possibly be enough
I just don't see you being enough
I think a lot of this money's got to be coming from Ozark Mountain publisher okay and from the Dolores Cannon
Branch
So that raises the question
Is there any reason to suspect
But there would be beef
Between Kerry Cassidy
And Dolores Cannon
I think that there is publish carries book
I don't know I don't know I know that you wouldn't
Bright-eyed I don't publish
I know that he would
She wouldn't do that either he was like no no Marco sharp cramping my house
No but he was writing that book Joe and his dad to be a soon-to-be wife
Was working in Publisher
Why was I was questioning this
Possibility there might be some sort of
Isuzu
Yeah between Cary and Dolores Cannon
And that led me
2A May 3rd 2010 video the Kerry Cassidy posted on Project Camelot
Of her interview and Dolores Cannon
Okay this is Rebecca in 2010 Dolores is Carrie's mom
Oh okay damn
If you watch this video
There's a very good reason to believe that these two Dolores and carry
Are not nearly
On the same page
Hear Carrie giving an introduction
Dolores
Services Kerry Cassidy
Project Camelot
Dolores Cannon
I'm very pleased
To introduce our audience
To Dolores Cannon
I have been
Studying your work
Quite some time
Read several of your books
And I'm very impressed
With your diligence
Carry you take
Each and every
Person that you read
And
And I know
Really want to
Thank you very
This is very friendly and jovial
It doesn't go off the rails or anything it doesn't turn into a fight right but if you know anything about Carrie
If you know anything about the world that she believes in
You will hear certain things along the way through this interview yeah that are gigantic
Things that she disagrees
This first one that comes up
Is a discussion of alien abduction
Dolores has an interesting take
On alien abduction
That is
100%
Counter to Gary
It was just
Taking them on board the craft
I've written about this
85 years
Call dacus
Custodian
Because all
Through my work I have not seen
It's always been
This is the way I see that
The first book Coronavirus
And I've never found that
Because I can
Why they were doing
Okay and when you say they
So up to this point the interview Dolores has just been explaining her backstory
To carry and describing how she's discovered through hypnotizing people that they've been abducted by aliens but that was always a positive
This is a major major
Departure from the worldview of Project Camelot
We're pretty much all alien abduction is nefarious and likely the work of the evil reptilians or their Associates in the human
Secret space
Even if they're good ostensibly in in her Pantheon
They're abducting people evil Masters don't kidnap people for good yeah
Chocolate Carrie believes that a lot of this stuff is done to like the abductions is done to harvest material from us
In order to produce clones are hybrids that can
I guess we used to better take over Society or something
Yeah they're made of chocolate
But Dolores doesn't believe that
And her experience all interactions with ET have been positive ones
And she professes to have an understanding of their purpose
Which is something that you know
Carrier can't argue with
If she has like I spoken to the aliens I know why they're doing what they're doing.
A dead-end is that there is a little bit of
It's like
Two people arguing over what houses look like in heaven where you're like
Shut up
So as Dolores lays out the interview these aliens are just the custodians of the planet
I want they have duck somebody they're doing it
The help them
There are these adjustments that need to be made humans in the ET or there to make those adjust
So the person can live up to the arrangements that they made before being
Inborn so they can carry out their mission in life this is
Great fantastic it's a large
Borden it's more new age
Inspired then a lot of work.
Yeah I know your soul and like before and after you die you and your soul group or together
Guys all make
What you're going to do in the neck
Life and then once you're boring your mind is wiped
You can't remember anything that's impossible have you ever tried to get for five people to go out for dinner making a rainbow
What you going to do in the next life is never going to happen. Your inability
Create those dinner plans it's something you agreed on before you were born
Remember you at your soul group agreed to make it impossible to make dinner plans
Coordinated on earth right you and your friends could grow through that frustration that created your own challenge
Freebirth in order
It's a new waves yeah yeah
Pretty common I got a lot of these circles after you
It's a predestination but also free well there's a lot like the other Minds wiped
It allows for both to sort of coexist
It it's where Dolores is at for sure and it is
Not work area
So when we see here is the first indication of a fundamental difference in the world
On small-scale
There's the different takes on alien abduction but if you zoom out this is a microcosm of a much larger disagreement
Primarily about what the character of the universe is
Mercury space is a Place full of war and different races of aliens doing battle for
Control of
I guess space resources
Dolores face is full of love and
Here it's just an extension of something that all about us but also much larger than us
There's a game going on involving Us and other alien races
But we're playing it together
And it's about Cooperative advancement
Keller
These are entirely incompatible views of the Galaxy
These two people have
I know what she would be called if Larry Nichols
Which
So we get to little bit later in the
In the interview and
They talk they start talking about like what aliens are you talkin
And we instantly find another branching
Between these
To that I don't know how they could possibly Bridget
You were talking to which group
Now they don't have
Okay they wouldn't tell you I'm going to do but as far as We Know
In other words we know about
For example
Santa General category
We know about Greg
Even reptilians
Have you gotten you've gotten a different charger do with all of them
Open
Where were you
You humans have
I needed we will give you a label
But they said if we told you we were from the planet out there to the north
Star you wouldn't know
Because it's not even
Calculator
But they don't come from
Picture of the Galaxy
Because they
Go to tell you where we are
And on board the craft store
Just like star
So here we have another fundamental disagreement between Cary and Dolores Cannon
What are the things that most characterizes carries view the folks from space is that they all belong to rigidly defined
Find groups
And they are defined by the group's characteristics
The reptilians are Draco there.
Spider leadership are bad and their meddling on Earth
The mantids were formally bad but they've made an alliance and they might be on our side now according to Simon Park source
The Raptors are good and they're our allies though they will lie babies on occasion and will kill you for chocolate which
It's like sometimes you got to make a
Look I mean
You know Saudi Arabia is technically our Ally you know what I'm saying naturally the Nordic
The alien the most like white people are unassailable good and the Palladium that is true
Delores he's a far more Multicultural universe
Compared to carry her view is downright Progressive
The labels of alien group names are meaningless in the larger picture they only exist because humans have a need to put labels
Nothing
In the real world of space nordics work alongside Raptors mantids in reptilians all the same space crap
It's a It's like Star Trek
Obviously since I don't believe any of this
I'm left to try and find meaning in subbed
I feel like the world that Dolores believes in is one where there's Unity
Where everyone can be valued in collaborate where group labels are meaning
Conversely Carrie seems trapped in a mode of thinking where what what group someone is apart of dictate
Intrinsic characteristics about
Applied to humans
This is what you might call Race
Yeah
The way Carrie engages in the stuff it's not necessarily fair to call it race
Because she could easily say that human is the group that that we would apply Universal characteristics to invest
Same way she does with raptor or reptilian
The problem is
And how accepting that kind of thinking allows a person to apply it to subgroups
Pretty easily
Carrie May believe its species is the smallest possible group where these kinds of generalizations can be made
But I don't trust that position to hold
Nor have I ever really heard her articulate that kind of hard and fast line
That kind of rule look like
This kind of thinking only applies this far
Reply to you need to be responsible if you're going to be like
This group is intrinsically this way this group is intrinsically this way
You got to be real clear about like
You better not apply this elsewhere dealing with here
Here is a clue
Classic
Did Bill & Ted win or did Bill & Ted lose Intergalactic governments
When it's
Why have you never seen it everybody are guitars it's fantastic it's amazing
But in Bogus Journey whenever they evil Bill and Ted around there
They're just cause
Destruction there just ruining everything
Carrie is the evil Bill and Ted this is unassailable lodgings as an interesting case
I'll say that what my perspective is
I appreciate you
But what I'm saying is this
I'm not trying to call Kerry's view racist and Dolores is view not racist
But I think what we see you're still indicates a profoundly Divergent view of the universe between their two were
Carrie sees a Galaxy sees the Galaxy as a war zone between distinct
Groups of alien races
Where is Delores easy to place it is a place of growth and evolution where different groups don't see themselves as different
And work towards shared goals
It's the difference between sees universe as primarily conflict
I am seeing it as primarily cooperation
It's difficult for me to stress how at odds their positions are
Which is very interest
Terry and Dolores don't seem to hate each other
And their interviews polite enough
But they have nothing in common
Yeah that isn't
Although
Dolores losses may actually and I don't even know if
This is brilliant within the context of her statement or if it's a
Exactly stupid as
It sounds
But the idea of an alien race being like
Yeah we're north of that star
North North North
In space your North in space North I think that you was saying that as a absurd way to look at it
In the contact sheet
She wasn't saying it like she was saying it like the alien race told her that I said you'll get better
I think she was using that as an example of what you would want
Figure from an alien and it being mean
Yeah that's what that's how I heard okay
Everything is open to interpretation or criticisms
All of these
People but I think that's nitpicky hard sci-fi
Alright
We're back to alien abduction
Your narrator
And Delores says something really interesting
That I could see Carrie take
Personally
The ideal situation
Should be the
The person never
Because they have been
Taking care of
And they don't want
Interfere with
We should cousin
Free will
You should be allowed to just
Levana
Scrooge's life
Cold
The chemistry
The pollutants
In the air
CID additives to the food
If the person is
On drugs
Define Recreation
Alcohol
It changes the chemistry of
Doss when the person
Remember
They don't remember at all usually
Port Arthur
Green
They'll remember you
Store
Correct
And their Fighters
The horrible things
What happened to the
And this is what the
Computer to UFO
Their speakers
Come and talk about all the harm
Well I can have the same
Person that somebody else
I do them
Story
Cuz we find out what
So close
And it's not
So Dolores is expressing that these people because they have
Ideally the aliens brain-wipe or whatever would hold
Because of environmental changes or drugs or whatever
Choose these people have a partial memory of something
And they're exploited by the UFO community that UFO community
At 1
Everything that she believes is actually true is a shity distortion of what's real right into
She's part of a group of people exploiting people paragraphs
Invalidating all of Carrie without being
Super or hyper confrontational she is saying
She just said everything you do is b*******
So I mean that's
Gotta be tough
Tahir
Firstleaf
He's pretty interested in this interview about the like we talked about a lot and I've already brought up this is
Obsession almost with
Categorizing the Azalea
And Delores seems to think that she's focusing on the wrong thing
Braces
IPad mini dirt
You wouldn't even break
But they're able to do
Communicate
And we have
Well okay
Will be happy to hear
Information I wouldn't
You think
I think I think there's a little bit of Carrie taking that as condescension absolutely
I could sense a bit of that through the interview although like I said it doesn't turn into a fight or anything
He might in the present or whatever they're still a bit of
Arrowroot respect between the two of them
And I think some of that might be a product of his being in 2010's things were quite
We're still free 2012 prediction was really excited about
This this world of s***
I'm getting a very maternal vibe from Dolores controlled relay in this interview vibing just in the way that she
She is interacting with Carrie as being lecture
You're you're young you've got a lot more to learn about this you're focusing on all of this
You're obviously take that is condescension
Mildly Maybe
I think it's more like I have a prospective about this that explains your purse
Perspective
And you could easily see that it.
But also
I mean Dolores has been doing this since the 7th
You know she's been
Even in this game a lot longer than carry
Sitting here talking about how great Dolores Cannon is
Later in the episode was talking to Carrie she's a pretty anti-vax
So
So I'm not I'm not I'm not here to say that she's a hero or anything
But the point is
These two people both believe in aliens
And all that s*** but have completely different perspectives on WhatsApp
Their disagreements about the nature of
The nature of alien life the value of dividing aliens into different groups
Whether or not the behavior of the UFO Community is actually making things worse for abductees
There's very little that they seem to have agreement on other than junk it back
Great
Good good way to come together on the right issue there
But I don't know if I can find any evidence of an actual public feud between the
I think the Dolores Cannon seems like a woman who wouldn't stoop to that
And I don't know if I've seen too many examples of carry directly attacking someone unless you perceive them to be
Attacking her
As in the case with Kevin Moore currently
If I were to make my
It would make my theory a lot simpler if I could point to a long-standing
Flame war between them
But I don't think that's ever happened
It seems like this is a case where there are two camps
The Canon side and the Camelot side
And they're just ideological Rivals vying for position in the Paranormal New Age community
Cannons work reflects a message of Hope
Of the new age ideals of human evolution and expansion of consciousness
Ozark Mountain publishing put out books with titles like
Dance of heavenly Bliss
Heaven here on Earth
And reconnecting to the Earth
Scrolling through the catalog it's more less devoid of fear
Selling the audience instead on messages of Hope
Conversely everything the Camelot puts out provide the Eldritch glimpse into a secret world of space combat
Secret technology being hidden from humans for evil reasons
And Grand nefarious conspiracy
Every natural disaster is just aliens eating people the government needs to cover up
Gore's their Temps
To stop Alien Invasion coming through Stargates
Secretly bombing the Stargate dealing with space Marianne Williamson versus Space Trump
That's what we're
Better that's our worldview ideological divide here
I didn't want to let that commercial for 2013 play all the way it was for Marion with no
But in Hidden Kevin list of people he's interviewed one of them was Marietta
Find that on his YouTube page
Also Two Carries World human tragedies that happened like mass shootings
Some things built those are false Flags
Being carried out by The Reptilian bloodline
Conquer the planet already through subterfuge
Everything is
Anyone who's spent any time trafficking in conspiracy in paranormal message
Boards are communities
Understands that these are kind of the two poles in that world
What kind of makes sense
Yoda perspective thing
How you could see the same glass as half-full or half-empty but just
Reply to secret alien
And all that now it's kind of
Fictional
The situation
But those that hypothetical glass we always talk about
So Dolores Cannon passed away in 2014
And her daughter Julia Cannon
And took over
I'm pretty sure that Julia was involved and maybe even running Ozark Mountain publishing previous to that point
But I can't say for sure cuz her LinkedIn page doesn't have any dates on it
No
I assume Dolores was
Very old
Like something like that videos
Confined pretty
Closter passing word white loose
Oh no I'm not saying that I'm just sold
You're 84 near me
Daughters
Going to run the
Operation
I would assume so you do that
Kevin is known both Dolores and her daughter Julia throughout his career in the Paranormal community
The first interview he had with Delores was posted on his channel on December 3rd 2011
And yes interviews with Julie are going back to 2013
I was wondering about this
That's because there seems to be a shift
In the present
Like a do Noah fairly
He's doing these interviews like with these time-traveler people
Got a call out the frauds in our community
If the
Possible
That there is anything to do with
Julia
Okay if
He's had this Patron
Over the years in the Ozark Mountain
Publishing
And he's doing and how he's doing what he's doing in partnership with them Dolores passes away right
Leah comes around and maybe she hates Carrie
Okay
Julia
Is
Officially
A loose cannon
I don't I like your pain but no that was just
That was just a thought that I'm tired and so what I wanted to do was
I wanted to check in with an interview that he did with Julia so I found this one here
From July 26th
This is
Mere months before he announces
Is Mark Richards documentary
I figured like is there going to be
Some Clues
Yeah you might think you'd find them in here
Enter this first clip
Kevin's talking to Julia
I feel like he's asking her about what her mother would think
About the state of the Paranormal community
Are that your mom did move
Solo
You know
Well
I started off for a late it was many years but I was going to let that such a touchy move it to
The era of
The myth
I think you know
It was
Pretty grounded in
Information that was out begging
You know the UFO field was
You know this field will most definitely
You know
A level that people
You know it was
It wasn't too far out there
In some ways right at
You know
My point is right now it's
Just feels that
A community
Such
Of such
Streams
And
Offset
Almost falling
The pot in summer
I wonder what Mom was think
I think
She would think it's
It's right on
You know this is how it's supposed to be
And
EOS
Gross
In a while
Like this
So she's doing gestures with her hands of like you think it's going to grow straight like
It's actually growing as two separate branches
Okay is almost like a Que Sera Sera
Kevin's being like what we got all this b******* going on any movement that sufficiently
Desplinter off
Series of different groups
Is her her basic
Got a threats there so it is inevitable why you're going to be
He worried about it
Yeah yeah that doesn't feel like what you'd expect if you were if my theory was to hold
Don't seem to be bothered in the slightest by the fact that like
Wow there's this but there's also this
And it went like you know that grows into differ
Print directions by the way f*** Kerry Cassidy but
Yeah
That's weird
So Kevin tries to regroup
A little bit here and reframe what he's asking of
It is almost like right
That you eat
The UFO
Text with your mom
I know work always
She was a very early
Promoting that
And that's exact
I think we're a little V
Either you are
Burnouts
Freeman that right he'll say
Absolutely
What about
That's right that's what it works gone
So so now we've got the country
Dismiss someone
Is the feel that I've loved
Episode long
The UFO
Wfo field on the other side
So long
And that there's you know there's a breach of the kid there's a gap in the connect that there's a connection
In between them
But as you said that they've gone this
We've got a secret
Space probe
Yeah
Coming out for
Language
Indeed
The
Stores that they
Telling
And the
Division in
Community
And
Desert
So cold
Is going on in the
Cotijas wellright
Recitative
I hate you
Never seen it
Divide it
Well
And I think that's another thing
That's
You know that's
Recently
Watching
A video they were just talking about how right now
Has always been the
And it's just the light is shining
Brighter and brighter
That's all it is
Oozing
Now we're just aware of it
So
Now
It's choices
You know you going to
Choices
Heathens all being exposed
It's wonderful
Not now people know about it
Yet. What were they were all hidden
She seems very Zen
About
Yeah I'm liking her vibe it won't I can't lie I came away from this liking Julie again in a bit
I look at this b******* always been there now they're people
Number one shining on this and they can't hide the certain things anymore
Fuller talking about it but she does not seem motivated in any way to be like today
There's no ruthlessness who's out
Addictive element there's no
Nothing it's just
You just kind of like
What do you get through life there's more information and then you have choices
I don't I don't know
It's insane she's very that could be the new version of the threat right there that we have
We have things that we can or do we have to choose
Crush those Dum Dums
Over there by 8
I think that's a giant leap but I don't think it's impossible.
In my mind that if you remember that Phil Hartman sketch on.snl where he's playing Reagan
And he was like
Who you're so little girl in
All that and then she leaves
Like that kind of thing yeah I understand that image can come up in your head but I would need immediately if not
Done like tons of
Research on Julia Cannon
A bit more information about her to be like alright secretly like a
Possible
So
Kevin gets to complaining some more in Julia's defusing
More when rubbish does
Microcytic
Or
Purposeful dissing
Information
That people feel as though it
It's real
Right and they going along with it
Where is p
Did I hate that word
It's almost like
Conspiracy
Infiltrated
Spiritual
That's how I
You know you got this
You know
I do just listen to everything
But that is that is what's going on though as a community
Right now there are people gaining
Seeing a lot of power in
Who are Mick
The spiritual
Conspiracy
Define do what you want to do
But then
As soon as you start state
Hang on a minute
Cuz it's going to be
270 we went weekend ungrounded head
Completely
Then they were there alternative
Did you do that
And it's like
Wow it's
Probably worth noting that this conversation with Julia was posted to Kevin's YouTube page about 2 months
After he had that interview with Kerry Cassidy where you tried to ask her about ink
Inconsistencies in Mark Richards
Story and she got pretty mad at him
When he's talking about people turning on you when you ask for better discernment he's absolutely talking about that conversation
He's very clearly talking about Carrie
Secret space program
Just complaining about Kerry Cassidy
Project Camelot Julia's response
Spell people got a thing
For themselves
There's almost Dolores item Eternal quality to carry
Julia has a bit of a maternal thing going on here with Kevin or it's like
Quit whining you
Crying teenager you're going to you're going to gyro older than this it's going to you're going to get past it you'll have some Wiz
Zumba.com from recognizing that people have choices
Sure there's more information that they can take that information to make a choice that they need to make with it
Open UFO Community we don't bitching about people because we're all lying
You're the worst
He's the worst I hate
He's the worst he's a shity interview earlier
Sucks that every time he tries to ask a question
Wind-up asking
For questions and
Not a bean
I know that
From the spirits that he channels
They've told me he's very good at it so
Yeah so it is next Clipper Kevin
Expresses shock
That some of his audiences interested in Project Camelot which I would say
Wow why I was shocked at where some of my audience was
I did not know
That we were
My admit myself my orders
Dividing so much
And how we felt about
Well then that might
Indicator
Yeah
I think
And I'm going to do that
That my next.
He's going to
Note Chocolat
Well yeah.
My next iPad 2
Coming
A journalist
If I'm unhappy with
With what's going on in
I think I've got two
Myself
Shine some light
And help people
What type of people but help
Chili's
Let's look at the
Stories of some
Black smoke cat
Where the f
I never thought
He going down that
So I mean there I think you you see that Kevin's deciding to be the change you wish to see in the world
Can't rely on anybody else to do this for me I got to do it I got a
Yeah but this
Still seems weirdly personal it is is it just
He is it just that she like
She didn't like his question
So now he's like I'm going to f****** take her down then that's what I'm happy because he's interviewed her in the past
Wayne Richards about Mark Richards
He has no standards video poles like
It was very recent to this
That he talked to those Time Travelers
Yay
Nothing about like people putting this information out seems to bother him generally
I don't know it has to just be personal
I think he just got annoyed with her and then he's
God he's the worst
Zagweb
The petty Grudge maybe or maybe not because I think in this neck
Text Cliff we get
Something that I think is
Crucial
In terms of understanding what's going on here
Unfortunately
These areas
Like you said they've just been
Prime
Find fields
You know
People that just come in
Do all car
I just put all this
Put so much power in
You know that
Text Darren dear to my heart
Note you know about Judith Judith let me just say something
You hit the nail on the head.
That is it
I'm going to use the woods
There is so much
Out there right now
Right in this
Field
So
I think the Julia again is is nailing it on some in some sense
Like she said you know you what you're seeing is
This world that we traffic in is
It's been primed
For people to be bad actors
So obviously there's going to be some negative things
And then they nailed down that like what it is is fear
The fear is the bad thing
They're creating fear in people in order to move whatever
But who believes that there are a lot of alien of the
What's going on in p
Can't remember them
I 14 remember them because
You'd assume that she believes
The same stuff is Dolores seeing as use her daughter and she's carried on her work
Is there a her daughter but that she still running the publisher
Shane Company suggests that yeah and the I believe that she also
Runs the Dolores Cannon hypnosis thing
Okay will do
You have to assume there's over
I got Kevin.
This really is trying to talk
Himself into this look like
Not that he's psyching himself up and wants her to give him the go-ahead he's begging for
Approval and
Started when they were talking about like
What would your mom think of this is almost like
Looking for the blessing of Dolores from Beyond the Grave
A t e k a
A truth that was a
Grounded in
Going to be getting
People that power back
But what's going on right
Now with this
I'm about to taking sides
Something
Go to
Pete makanji
Just sit there and do not
That's okay
But I'm
I'm saying right now I'm not
Going to do that because
The fear is golden
Destroying a lot of the
Goodwill
Good for you
See that's that's the lightbringer
That's your job that's why you're
When I preach
So I guess he's got some approval
But still he was
This is no definitely has no
Connotation towards that at all still doesn't feel like directions
Right like I can identify that obviously he's been in partnership with this company that's run by the Cannon family
Over 6 years
At least 6 years at this point
But it doesn't feel like when he's talking about what he feels drawn to do
Exposed Project Camelot
I I don't
Feel like it
This would be what the interview would be like if there was an interest in that
Just weird
Thermoflask Lapeer Kevin
Jesus is Project
Would you already know what it's going to turn into but she talked about it yet
Thanks Julia for being so
Supportive
We never know where we're going
Guided and
That's what's
Getting asked to do
Yes yes
Said that that.
End
Yep
And and
You know
I wish I could say more right now about what I'm working
But all I know is that when
Is finished
Going to be at least
My first bit of light work
The shine light
On this subject
Dot-dot-dot
So I don't say it
You've been doing
Lightworks
Was so abusive of you.
Go to sleep
This is our journey
Yes it is
Is it really is so
Surprise me
Sometimes
Yes it does
So
We're not even aware of it
That's what I like about you right I can get on here right
I can
Have a little bit of ammonia
Screen write about whatever I hate you
You just kind of 11 out of it you know what I mean
And then you get that from your mom as well I'm sure
Show you do
And
That that
That that is
Yeah
Thank you
That's weird
Wow that is weird I love her I love her
He comes off quite well
Is killing it
The listening to this interview with Julia Cannon I'm left with the impression that she and Ozark Mountain publishing are not
What's motivating Kevin to attack Harry and Mark
She doesn't seem overly interested in Kevin's new project
Liquor interested in a polite way and I don't know whatever but not overly so
And when he tries to complain about the scism in the UFO Community Julia tries to contextualize it by saying that
That's how it's supposed to be this is just what is this is a part of growth
Is Humanity learns and grows it encompasses many things
Some good
I'm not as good
He just doesn't feel like she's pulling any strings
This feels like it's entirely a cat she sounds super benign
Downright kind
Deescalate
I entered this episode kind of thinking that we would look at this clear source of funding of Kevin
New Age self-help book publisher with a polar opposite view on the Paranormal UFO world
Carrie's and I would come away with the scent if they were behind this documentary as of crass business move
But I don't feel that way now
I think this is actually a thing that ideological
But we've been missing the forest for the trees when we were trying to figure out what the ideology was up till this point
Before I heard Kevin talk about how this misinformation in the community was
You know it's you wanted
You wanted better discernment
I heard him talk about that stuff and I interpreted it to literally
I thought you was offended by people being full of s***
And that was what he wanted to push back again
That's why it was absurd that he could present himself that way and then do an interview with the fake time travel.
That's why it's comical that he would pretend to care about rigorous standards of proof while channeling aliens an offworld intelligence
But I had it wrong
It's about fear
Kevin doesn't have a problem with the fact that carry can't prove a damn thing she says
Because he can't prove anything he says either
It's not about research
The issue is that carry a Project Camelot are using
Fear is the primary element of their content
Where is what ring
True to him about the universe is messages of hope and love
He comes from the Cannon School
They've been his Patron for years now
And obviously he looks up to Dolores quite a bit
Even seemingly trying to ask for the daughters blessing what he's embarking on this new project
His ideological problem with Mark
I'm curious in this dichotomy of stressing
Fear or stressing hope
But you being dishonest about that
He's presenting things as being about how Carrie doesn't do our due diligence about the gas she has on
As he expresses in the video that he put out when he was explaining his purpose
This is the first docu-series
Of its kind
Looking into frogs in the UFO and alternative communities that are reps
Can't think of any other documentaries about fraud the UFO
Is not a credible research has
A sorcerer damage into people's awake
When people trying to
The idea that
There's a greater reality
And when it's met with misinformation and disinformation
You know that
Something that icons
Said so
I made it my coil right now
My calling
To show the opposite side
Of some of these so-called whistleblowers
So the way he's framing this is like exposing frauds in the community to do a disservice to legitimate research
He presented like that
So much
But underneath it
I don't believe that's the case
I think it's that he resents that they're not on the
Canon side of the things
Because he
Resonates more with the new AG stuff
The secret space program and that holographic Med beds and super soldiers of it all sides of this
Nothing much like Julia was expressing these two branches coming off the trunk
As things grow as the community grows
Obviously they're going to be these different offshoot rent Kevin
Handle that you can't stand it
Each sense to rejection from that side of the F4 asking questions
Yeah
I don't think he's I don't think he's ideologically against
No I think he is
I think in the general sense
Yes
I don't think he is above
Disregarding his ideology
Carrie likes a boy
Buttegieg his ideology ideology kicks in real hard whenever somebody doesn't like
But if you take a closer examination of the videos that he puts out on his channel you will see
A massive
Erring on the side of these messages of Hope
These non fear-based messages
So it's clear that his body of work does
Lean towards that side there is a clear ideological distinction
That is interesting you you
Reframed it obviously I took a
My numbing Lee literally the idea of it me to it's about research
You know like it well if you say you're trying to debunked
And you are
Then you have to up course look back
Get yourself and think what if
What what do you remove the Splinter from your eye etcetera
Spider-Man
But you can present it as I'm exposing fraud and not get into the
The fact that you have no proof of anything you're talkin about
It's because what
The exposure is really deep down on a visceral emotional level it's V they use fear
I use hope
More or less
Now the other thing to do is I mean you can't get away from it is there is clearly a personal thing like you
He has said in some of those things that we
Recover do you like
I'm going to make more documentaries in the future but these ones about like
Kerry Markin Simon parks are there more personal they're based in something
He's mad about
I feel like I have a better understanding of where Kevin's coming from now
But I still think he's an a******
He explicitly said nobody's talking to Julia that is concern is that there's fear p*** and negativity does
Biting the UFO community
And it's not about
Consciousness enough where you think that's the root of all this stuff
But then what he's trying to sell his documentary pushing it as an expose about fraud
What are you talkin to Julie are you said he's not attacking carry
Or the Richards is the mark and Joanne
But any promotional videos he f****** talk to Joanne by threatening to expose details about her previous marriages
Like this is bulshit you behave that way and pretend that you're like I'm not going to go about attacking people and then attacked
Yeah you can't pretend that this is about love and fear
Splitting of the UFO community and then sell it as like
They don't let their guests yeah
You can't
It's so Dishonored
Yeah it is but at the same time I don't think he could actually
I don't think you I don't think anybody
Like
If Julie is talking to me I'm going to be like I'm going to save the nicest possible things that I can
And then peep down inside I'm going to be filled with
Rage and hatred
But to her I'm going to be like
You know what you're absolutely right we should
Should forgive everybody
We should all do the stuff
What I set out to do this
Or this episode in particular it was looking into that element of this that I think is
Dangling thread
Trying to figure out why my bike hasn't did this
Any other question of you think it has anything to
To do with his sponsor
And at the end of this I feel pretty confident that this is not a follow the money
Situation
I think it's a Kevin Morris and assholes situation
Also I feel like if I'm ever mad I want to call Julia and I'm sure she'll be able to talk me down
Try an email or so you can consult
Jordan no matter what
No matter how many times Kevin wants to say that he wants good research in the UFO community
He's also a guy who runs a psychic hotline
And will straight-up face serious look on his face
He doesn't need to change his voice
Different way
Do better research on Mac
He's not a very good
Impressionist
He doesn't good
Jack Nicholson have you heard of
Maurice
Lamar's
Once Jack Nicholson dies we will handle him
You can handle zexion on
I also don't forget.
I like that I like that
I think that's a good Nicholson
So anyway I
I needed something to that would be interested me a little bit to really get the juices going after that disappointing
Chunk of listening to Alex
Got to get out of present-day do little Wacky Wednesday thing
I wanted things it was really sticking in my craw was that question
The money and looking into that a little bit more
I think it's fascinating that this
Is clearly
An organization the Ozark Mountain publishing
Aunt Laura's Kitchen
It's clearly
And opposing
Worldview of the space nonsense weirdos
And it's interesting
They have been funding Kevin
For as long as they have
But I don't know if that's related
I don't think it is I still I still have no
Concrete answer is to why he's doing this that doesn't go back to
Ideological opposition of like him being a part of that camp
It is opposite to Project Camelot scam
And
Him
Being mad
This is really good for me because I ate in all of our
Project Camelot excursions
It never really never even thought that there was
Thought about the new AG wing
Of that whole you apply
I've always been in this
In the space of like
My viewpoint on that UFO Community is
There's a guy with the Telus
You know like that kind of thing is so Broad
That's where it's always been in my in my mind so this is really into
There's the new AG side there's the the hard sci-fi siderite like mortgages more about like
The machines
What do you use a combustion engine better than a hundred percent
That's not actually true they fly with their minds they all know that
So anyway we'll be back here on Friday with a non
Space episode but until then Rick website Twitter
We are at Hooters that knows underscore fighting that go to bed Jordan and
We are
Yoda baby
And then if you would like to go to iTunes share tell other people leave review
All that stuff I'm told help
Yes I will be back but until then I'm Neo I'm Leo I'm bzx Clark
I do not have to change my voice
Holding
Alex