Damned important
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge bright I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
MoneyGram
College vype.com
Everybody look like knowledge about Alex
Text Jones actually before you get your question I am excited
I had an update on your question from the last episode Don me after we finished recording
You asked about like songs
Stick with you
You go to a nebulizer
Example of vodka
I just didn't come to mine okay just started talking about the Boston I stood up song by guy named Greg Brown
Okay Cafe when I was younger dude my Dad loved Greg brownies
This is great
Gravelly voice folk singer
I don't know two boards
Dude somehow vacations.
But
Yeah this is album Dream Cafe that my dad would play all the
And it's just amazingly soothing
There's like a lot of
A lot of that album particularly a dream
Cafe song I've never heard that I bet I will check out my recommended songs that you have
Ever convicted
That is the first one that I am very interested it's it's very comforting
Take me back to a time before like
Sliding across the floor in my socks
Footloose
But I'm sorry your question
It was so long ago I had a question
Do what are what is like a common
That you find meditate
You know I'm saying like some people find meditation and making a
A sandwich like right well like the Japanese
Sure sure do you have an accident
Listening to Alex Jones
No I don't know maybe taking a bath
Yeah yeah there's a cop if you're asking just about like what is
Calming
I don't know you used making a sandwich as an example so feels bad for me to be like
I've had a lot of people who come to
Outside like I brought up that I cook the likes turkey bacon
Yeah it takes a while
The panda
Yeah baby like put it in the oven it's much quicker and
I kind of enjoy the process of it
Well I have a dishwasher but I wash everything
I like
Cuz I always I enjoy the you like the active
Sitting there wiping the dishes
Rinsing we're talkin about
Edit said wash the dishes after dinner listening
Greg Brown
Gravely
Voice tryouts
Plates with your socks and then slide all the Florida
Dishwashing by hand
The Anza Alex Jones
Dad is right in the present day because why wouldn't
Yeah there's an interesting things in the world
That's what I would say good episode
So today we're going to be going over November 20th and 21st which is
Tuesday and Wednesday of this week no Wednesday and Thursday of the
And we will see what happens
Alex is not too particularly interested in a lot of these larger
World events
Well we'll get it.
So I before we get to that do Jordan
So first of all Michael thank you so much You & I Auto policy
Next Lenny thank you so much you are now a policy walk
Next-gen
Thank you so much you and I'll buy what you want
Next Brian with an e
What's whoa thank you so much you are now a policy wonk
Next
Elevated level
Always screaming internally
Disable thank you so much you are now a technocrat
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
Thank you so much always screaming internally and Sable
Disabled
One of them is an angry always screaming internally in the other ones silk like I find I find the contrast
To be very fun I thought you might have been laughing because you were reminded of the female wrestler
I was married to Marc Mero
Is the master of the Sable Bob
Right
So Jordan today like I said where the present day and there's some real disappointment
In terms of Alex Knox
Talking about some of the issues that you may be wanting to talk about the impeachment proceedings are at
Big deal has been pretty consistent
In terms of this being hike bulshit
Why won't they talk about the biotin
Bored more Stark
Angry
It's been tough for me to keep up a doing the show especially because I've been trying to take as much time
That I have available as possible and watch a lot of the abuse
History happening in front of us to Anna
What do matter what direction is goes there
Notable that should be remembered but we'll almost certain
Only being forgotten by the elections pretty crazy and so I've been spending
You know hours
Watching the testimony didn't have this down
Whether there's any Credence to Alex's Notions about this being bullshitted
All day and then also I worried that Alex is going to start talking
Think about it and then either you're unfamiliar
Gone down it's okay
I've spent a lot of time and by assessment so far
And also today on Thursday as we recording this Fiona Hill
Testified
Ebonized in targeted by Alex
And to her credit
She brought up the fact that all of this Soros stuff is basically a modern-day like a super rehashing
Protocols of the Elders of Zion listening I don't know if that's the butt
Nice bit to bring to the conversation and will almost certainly infuriate hours
Oh yeah but two to the extent that I have heard is that we're covering today's episode on 5th
I've not heard him respond to that but I imagine
I mean his name came up in the impeachment hearing he's going to
Say that this impeachment is all about him and
Expect more coverage of this
The future but it said today on the 20th through the 21st
We get
Other things
So here's another context drop from
Ball player
Sure is
Pointless factoid
But Rob do BF real real Charles Barkley get going for the rebound
Muscling his way into the paint that Rob do
Boxing out
Accomplishment
Dino
I got a scholarship for basketball
What a f******
Boring thing I just said that is definitely a part of your history is pointless
Make me melt
I'm angry at Rob do for telling me boring should about it
So on the 20th on Wednesday there is big
Things
Happening in
The world of Austin Texas
And Alex's
Sure to be baking soda
President
Taking off from Washington DC on Air Force One in beginning a trip
3 hour trip to Austin Texas
Where he's going to be
With Jim Cook one of our favorite people I know I'm one of his favorite people
Crazy eyes ahead
World
Petrovich code keys and Control Act
He's going to be here in Austin at one of the few app
Whole factories love
In the United States in north Austin
White towards the end of the show illegal
Little bit early and no s*** you are
So the timing and circumstances here could not be more ideal
Alex is already planting seeds in his audiences mind about Trump not valuing his true supporter
And so soon after he was Trump
Coming to Austin
But he's not coming to visit the Texans
As they call Alex in the white house or is Alex says they College
He's not coming to get briefed on all the evil globalist
It's going on
He's coming to do a
PR trip to the Google factory
He's being accompanied by literal demon globalist
Tim Cook
So that is
Really good for Alex's
If you're if you're looking to jump off that ship then the time might be now and
Having who stand up with the right way f******
The worst slave factories in the world
This gives Alex an amazing opportunity
Trump is in Austin so obviously Alex has to go
Trump is going to Google so obviously he's not there to validate Alex
All Alex needs to do is show up and be ignored
And here's the next stage of his breakup narrative perfectly staged for him
On film
Are you going to Google or Apple
Apple
Excuse me
He comes to you know
You coming too
Alex's City
Just after Rodger Stone gets convicted and did nothing about it
And instead of meeting up with his loyal supporters
Here he is glad handing with the
The anime
This is the perfect layup
You show up
You start bull horning about how he's got to pay attention to the true people
Or you show up outside their you start bull horning about how he's part of the globalist
Corrupted I may have slipped up there with Apple and Google because
Is Alex uses a Metrotech
Naturally factories in the world
Yeah
So Alex
He's announced that he's going to protest
Stop protesting
Or is this is a fine line to walk
Just left about 45 minutes late song
Message
Play the president
Protest
Forestville Mall
Message to the president
And today
Traveling with
Tim Cook
Trump coming to Austin
He puts Alex in a precarious
Position
On the one hand he's been pretending that he and Trump are basically soulmates and on the exact same wavelength
4 years
Alex's information has changed the course of history in trouble loves what he does and has since day one
On the other hand
None of that's true
Copying and Austin is a
Kind of no-win situation for Alex if he wants to
To keep up that charade
Because Alex knows that he goes to this plant his audience will expect to be greeted warmly by Trump
Play the hero it doesn't guess
Maybe he'll let Alex come along with the tour in Gallatin, secretly wants to do
Of course everyone knows it is Alex shows up he's going to get the same reception he does every
He's going to be kept out by security and reduced just yelling on the street into a bullhorn
Why would Trump allow that
Not going is not an
Unless I was wanted to pretend he has like a secret meeting with Trump it's um
Clandestine location
But that's going to be really difficult as Ally
Yeah at this stage of his career I don't think Alex is up to trying something like that
Alex has to go
And he knows when he does
He's going to be rejected
This is the perfect setup
For the delivery of a forceful message
Which will fall on deaf ears and make it that much easier for him to argue that true
Trump is not there guy after all
This is perfect for him
Yeah and you get the up
Of being you got somebody with the camera while you're being
Pushed out
You got security telling you that you're not invited in
You got the camera everybody
Can see in the in the Wingnut
A community that Trump is pushing him away he's pushing all of us away Alex
Their symbol and the Revolution begins now
Right and simultaneously there's going to be a ton of people who are there on the left let's say Pro
Shrubs
Visit imagery that he needs out of this
Regardless of which direction he wants
It's almost a perfect setup
For everything except maintaining the status quo
What she is going to try and do as hard as you possibly can I assume
I'm not positive I have very mixed feelings about it but one thing that is staying with the status quo
Is that the globalist 37
They drink blood
And they're possessed by Immortal spirits
It's over
We know the blood-drinking child rapist
Woodlawn
Gangstar
Quasi immortal
Oh boy
Somebody he's not allowed to use the
Ever again
It's holding a lot of weight
Quasi Immortal picking beefsteak
Quasi
I don't think I've ever heard anybody use the use the prefix
Anyway other than
Being kind of shity
Make it too strongly to say it all
So Trump is a man who can
The problem is that
He doesn't
Stand up
For a look like
I think this episode do you see a fair amount of Alex being like
I think so
The Republican party's main affiliation is Nazis on Google
Does nothing
I'll be hanging out with Jim cook today
Who runs the worst Factory in the planet
But
When it comes to saying it's coming it's very strong action
Where
Turning Point USA
Walking home from
Coming in
Events
And
Take money away from University today
The neocon never Trump has or taking over
You want to know why people
There's your answer
My super hardcore stuff
Supporting Hillary light
Great so I I told you that there is no way Alex would ever go against drudge and I think that's
We're seeing that
He's defending drudges waffling going along with basically that
Exact line
Weird part in the middle of their is the bring up the turning point
Yeah
Because
The people that they're trying to keep out our acolytes
So
In the first part of I believe correctly
He's mad because Google is Alexa isn't even stopping people from assuming that Trump is a white National
It's not what he's mad because Trump isn't protecting out now white right now
They eat these not forcing Turning Point USA to allow these white nationalists
Yeah
A bunch of bulshit
So a large
Part of this episode in order to not really talked about
The impeachment stuff
And not talk about anything really substantial
So much of it is just yelling about child abuse
And the demon
Vampires suck
Can blood
A ritual
And all that stuff and I'm not going
To cover
Because I find it irresponsible
The score
I find it
To be corrosive and toxic
Even to a point where is covering it
I don't think it is
I don't think it merits cover
Yeah I think it is
Atrocious
And
I resent Alex
Sport
Now look in the course of talking about that there is one thing that I find interest
I'm going to play this clip
It's not that gross
Not really gross necessarily
As I recall
But if tracks with something that we've been paying attention
To do and that is Alex's stories
Of going to Satanic rituals when he was a kid
And this is interesting because we learn a little bit more about that
Understand I've actually research this
Because I ran into this
Natalie
Course
Rituals
But I got
Okay
GameStop
They wanted me
Thank God thank God
Took three things first I got fooled twice what's that expression fool me once
Shame on you
Man York logos
Kick a little ass on my way out
Ivory
That we just said we added that one was Satanic ritual
I think this demons
Even Rachel and I fought my way out
Kurt Russell in
Big Trouble in Little China I feel like it's that was a real story that would have been what have you told it every single time
Did you do with that story the Safeway second is this is a satanic coven or whatever that
Rituals I don't think that no one's going to be armed there
I mean at the very least there's one ceremonial no
I don't believe for a second that he youthful Alex could fight his way out of a real Satanic ritual
The stakes of let it give out our way to Harpers Ferry High
But there are rules
Federal Circle
You could have one everybody has to fight you one at a time sure you can't gang
Third thing
Alex is like his so on in line with his sense of self
He has to make sure that you understand that he was tricked into going to this ritual so he could be one of the powerful ones not a victim
In the scenario even within his weird illusion
He has to make sure that you know that like I'm not I'm not going to be one of the ones that was big
Evil Satan
Recognize the strengths
And that's
That's gross
To like his psychology
Very clearly liked what I heard that I laughed really hard at the fighting his way out
And then I was just like
Tell the story I was not there
To be diddled
That's exactly
It is it is kind of disconcerting how very similar
Cuz you could totally see Trump trying to
Do the exact same thing in
I'm telling what it is b*******
Sure just that that
I need you to know
I am always the strongest person in the room even stronger than these
Demons around all of these states Manning heads of state
Stronger that one
Can God move a mega Mountain can't move nobody
Can make a mountain hike
Yeah
It's
Upsetting
So like I said a lot of the episode is about this
And I wish I could would have
Cut some of the clips maybe because some of them to drift into like
Real serious
Is racism
Surrounding
Some of these
Rituals
Drink drink
Children's blood
I can't bring myself to do it and I think
It's too gross
So that's most of this episode
Jesus 20th
It's
Very heavily
Too much yeah
I'm telling you like listening to his
Present-day episodes
Like this last week has been
A disaster
Okay to just
Do with like
3 hours of f******
Borderline torture report on the radio to family show okay well that's fair
It's not wall-to-wall that there is it also just boring
Stop in there
Even worth covering or like
I don't have clips of him saying that the impeachment is all just b*******
Burden
This is okay to do
I'm not saying that we should
Some think the state should stop him I think it's wholly unacceptable
And I would find it on except
For us to go over it
So we shouldn't
I'm it so there's not too many clip
From the 20
Cuz it's a lot of that
But we do learn something about Alex's
Plan
To go give a strong message
Not a protest
Wrong message it's a protest but not necessarily against Trump
Strong message
And that is
You know how he's been going around in a tank
Yeah turns out he bought it
Car
We just ran into it
We can deploy Mass
So he bought this like this armor
Truck like what what what
Your business is going under allegedly
Selling his f****** house that's what I'm f****** dictator does to years
Before they get deposed violently
Say it either is or it's an indication that he's f****** gaslighting is already on
Yeah you can buy a armored car
No that's your business is not nearly in the kind of trouble that you're pretending it is something to do because
It's not necessary
United Way and I put my price this out and it
It's kind of difficult to figure out exactly what you'd be paying but it's in the tens of thousands of dollars
Stores that armored truck
No I would say
At least it if you
He's also got a
Amass
Sound system attached a couple of speakers on the roof
See you getting on the on the bargain
That that is you know baby
The Brandt
Okay alright
But this card like I looked at the range
Armored vehicles
The one he has
And I don't know
He doesn't have a sunroof you have a latch on the top of it
Which I imagine will probably be an add-on
To take that off
The chassis are all built with
Even if he got a pretty good deal I don't see this being
Like less than
$30,000
Which is
Yeah I know that's
That's troubling Behavior that's that's a red flag Behavior right there if you're around a person like that
It will be tough to be a listener the show like let's say you really believe that he needs all the support in the world right now and
You got to go buy the product and let's leave baby you bumped up your donation or you fail to him and then
I don't know where you find
Spending tens of thousands of dollars
On an armored truck so we can go educate people
Like it's not it was now it's so he doesn't get attacked by ants
OSHA
Course he needs that armored vehicles absurd
It's a really it's a really silly thing
He gets to basically expressing why
He bought it
The shop
Tiaras with the armored movie
Have an idea
I know that idea is going to succeed
Similar idea
The idea has never fail
Thanks to dodge
Robin given
The fact that we are working together
Building the resistance to this globalist
Do
We did this together
You are you need to know
No it's not you are
How much I want to salute you
How much I want to thank you
For buying me an armored car
Damn he's very clear they're like the pr from this car
She recognizes that like it's not that interesting for him to show up and yell at people anymore so you up
Escalate
Bespectacled like
Alex
Getting out the tank top of the armored vehicle with the sound system yelling at people
This is somehow going to be like
I'll get press out of this for sure
This'll be like a
They got the siren song to them to give me free press
And it does not bode well if you're willing to spend whatever price you're paying for an armored vehicle for whatever diminishing return
Kind of publicity you're going to get out of driving around in an armored car yelling at me
People like what do you think the next step is
Flying a plane around and yell
People Get Ready
Absolutely that's not the
Straight to Skyride
Bentley I don't know what else he could do to be more bombastic and more like
I'm sure you could come up with something but
This is like
To me this is the version
Of the
The cult leader
Everybody you must take a vow of poverty and everybody must give him all your money and then all the sudden he's wearing all these dime
What the f*** are you doing there's like Domino 8/8 about appearances
Whenever I whenever I go out into the world I have to look like a powerful
And I have to look like I'm this all that's
It does have I've done
Just so f******
It's not a good look
No
It's not a good look for him to rationalize this by being like antifa attacks me and us I need an armored vehicle
Already have
Ex Blackwater security guard right I don't know what kind of protection do you need outside of that that's crazy
It's that argument doesn't really work at any argument that like I have big plans for the
PR I'm going to get out of this
I don't know that I saw a ton of coverage when he went to the Hillary of that in the armored truck
Why is he not hiring but I just think that this is not going to work for that and either and it
Like if
If that's his primary motivation then obviously the next stage is something
More
Extreme
And I just don't know what it is I mean
No that's a step in the right direction
What can we just now getting the armored car ID
Cuz he's desperate now
So in the next the last one from the 20th cuz Alex leaves earlier
Pop a perc takes over
Brighten Studio
And
Alex like this is gross man
He's talking about Trump and how he's not against him but he's going to go yell at and then
Just the way he described him as Soto
Ringleader
But
Hey Dad what are you doing with him
That's good to meet with me but if we haven't gotten relief
Do something
Yeah
Cordova kind of movies are at a long time
Paternalistic view of the president that's
Good I believe you it makes
That's what they all want like we hired you to be the big strong man who does this so we don't have to
I don't want to have to add jatate I want
Do it for me right I mean set Steve's that when he came back and we got him an office so he can
You do these
Everybody and then not answer any questions but silent
Yeah it's Alex either he make the wrong move confidently than makeup
The Right Move
Quietly
And now Alex he's daddy hanging out with the evil villain Tim Cook and you got to ask
Why would you do that
You're not helping us
I know Alex
I know think of
Yeah
Don that I think he is
Yeah I think I get the sense video
Dialect leaves
And a little clip of him out bullhorn dang it
At the Trump rally
Bi-Lo Bi-Lo
It's just like a Sizzle reel of people giving him
Finger at work
It's a boy
I don't know if this delivers a strong message
Truck but it works for
PR with the Giant Truck
So that was the main goal of it
You put out a 5-minute Sizzle reel me 34-minute Sizzle reel that just had like
Yelling at folks
Watch the lake 25-minute longer wives
Like wow isn't accurate Sizzle reel that is exactly what happened
Whenever they
Can really edit
Reddit properly people there who are like protest
Drop a man Alex Galligan
This is sad
And he's got that he's got the armored car in the back
He's popping out the top of it for a lot of Enderman
That is such Trump standing in front of a goddamn helicopter just
God you're so sad
So we get to the 21st
And Alex opens the show a little bit weirdly
Sleep
For the first time
Was forcing myself
Sleep
Because I could
I was without the aid of coffee
Immigration slavery
What happened to The Sleep Apnea thing
You said that he had sleep apnea so bad that CPAP
Machine and he had to sleep sitting up right never felt longer than like an hour or two at a time what's the story
I don't know but I genuinely don't know I don't either
I don't know what he's lying about know what some things alike
I can see him lying either way too I can see him yet pathetic so he can get more money
I'm lying to make it look like
Keep stronger
And really Elevate whatever is happening in his Worlds by being like
Everything so serious I stayed up all night last night I never do that
My 27 years on are never done that Rob Badoo Badoo
I don't know like it it gets to the point where like
You listened to enough of this show if you have a critical eye looking at it
You will find contradict
And it just like well something
July
I don't know yeah
Cool anything could be real but the not being able to sleep
Checks out a bit more with the manifestations of his behavior
I don't know what
Now I have no
Out there are certainly don't really care that much
Now he's fine
So Alex starts complaining about how the globalists
Right
Sure you know them
I've heard they're evil
They like to push the idea that one group
Is behind all the evil in the world like let's save the Masons
The Catholic hold on
The globalist
Right like to push the idea that
Yes that's it and cannot be
We'll see what they do is they
Foster groups
That are like hey you know what's wrong with the world
Everything is a mason
Conspiracy okay now you take a step back from that you recognize that Alex is doing the same thing but with the global
Say that he cannot say that
He does he can't save at the globalist want to make people think that it's one Shatter Me
But he does and it's to get into a very brief
Discussion about how Benjamin Netanyahu has been
You know there is
Mumbai
In the world
Push that wants to always say it's
Mason
Catholic saints
It's a goblin
Supremacist
Secretly
It's just evil groups of people of every race color creed
Work on the same wavelength
Global government
Posthuman world
I just noticed
Today is
Yahoo it's been ruled in Israel is going to stand trial for
Supposedly
Hosting dinner
Over the years at his house at the government
Not
Pay for dinner
On charges of
Bribery
The Rothschilds supposedly found in Montana
Glass
Hold on Wiggly point of order
How is Israel
1 Monolithic Power
You see
I have
No f****** clue what it is you
He's saying that's like some people say that the Jews run the world but in reality
Netanyahu is being indicted it's all being spearheaded by the Rothschild
That's alright
Alright Alex I was getting is that
See
Some Jews are
This is why you don't turn to Alex for news coverage
This is why cuz you just leave with more questions
I don't know what you think I'm
Did you think I'm surprised
Israel's doing something he thinks is bad or not you heard anything
Supposed to be something you remember in our first episode our first episode ever
Red Alert
In our theme song
Poems from Alex talking about how Benjamin Netanyahu was
I'm alert
Sprint
This is not fair it's not fair you're supposed to still care at least almost 3
Years later the Rothschilds
Weird man
Just want you just wanted to pay off
Whenever he makes a prediction like
And then it does happen
You wanted to pay off some
Somehow not just having be like well it's because three years ago he only cared about this because if Ben
But Netanyahu was indicted it meant that the global store about to come for
Yes
Even if you still believe that
You've got this like that Trump isn't helping us
Why would he scream about it being time to pray anymore
Much more be like
Let's just talk about
The f****** Marquis
He issues let's get back
All our enemies are demons let's just
Stress on that right
Call where they may
Good stuff so also Alex now has finally found out about the fact that their stories about Stephen Miller's emails
Coming out
His take on it is in
New York Times is a white nationalist
Yeah Steven Miller is Jewish
Pro-israel
His parents are leftist for anti-israel
Thought it was crazy
Growing up in that circus
We're allowed to have a border and it believes is not right to say white people in here
Call the came out 2 days ago I started last night
Stephen Miller must resign because he's a great Patriot advising the president on cut up why
I don't think they wrote that part
The ATL is say he is a Nazi
What's the proof
All the things he said
Sport academy
10000 emails
Surreptitiously
Blueprint
Resistance off of
Infowars
Apparently you sent that Katie McHugh and Infowars article
Higher
I mean look
I don't want to sit here and go in-depth on this Stephen Miller Story But I recommend anybody was interested
Go ahead and read
Some of those articles dealsea
How much b******* Alex is talking
Importantly
Over the span of this we've heard him
Save it
Or indicate support
For the Nick Fuentes wing
That's trying to agitate a turning point events
He's saying that Steven Miller based in stuff on me and is great and they're calling him but
A Nazi for it
BC like
You see what he's doing
This is this is very clear the type
The type of voice he wants to defend he's choosing his
At his side of
The Schism that's for
Mercedes way far to the racist and to the right kind of like
Just normal Trump
So that's the way the ball is breaking
Oh man we were we were
Becoming truth
So I don't know if you seen this on the social media
Jordan but there's a there's a little video picture that's going around
Greta thunberg is from the time-travel South Dakota
Oh that's good stuff
We're on it yeah love it
I got it
Poorly done I don't know why
Did you take it
So Alex has a take on this sad
This weekend
Individual saying
They put that out
Yeah freak you out that's what I'm all about
That's what I love give me a boring dumb story about somebody make
You mistake and then be like Siri
That's what they want you to
That's the problem that I have is like yeah so much should have caught that and that should have been changed
Fight
We're on it is
Like colloquially does mean we are taking care of this
You know it's not like
It's not something like we do it
It's one of those things
And it happened
To everybody
And I think we
Should be 100%
It's one of those things where you like
You're just not your you're not focused on the outer edges really
And you're just drawing this diagram out you're at the office
Cuz you're jaundiced
And then somebody looks down in my life
You just drew a dick on that paper and you're like
No idea
Oh God damn it I did
There is that or there is a possibility that I would even believe that somebody is f****** around internally
Yeah that could catch it
I don't I don't I don't see this is that big of a thing but apparently it's been Declassified that they're trying to get people on
It must be something old that's been Declassified it is now a permutation the nomenclature
Right whenever they first had the first episode of Breaking Bad they started the
This whole plan talk about breaking bad being
Back on it
I don't know how much that she'll glorifies math
Pretty against meth usually
I think yeah
So Alex yells more about the demons
And the child blood-drinking in
And what have you that the global
To-do list
But he is not over demonizing
The globalist
Not over demonizing them you have to understand that is it is the radicalization of these people have got more intense
Because once I sign onto hate of trump
Which we do have to
Then it just becomes anything attached to Trump
Is some satanic weapons
I don't think yes
Why did you bring it up
Don't think I know
Trump's more like a
Crossroads
Station of the group Collective conscious
Michael Rickles do
But if we don't rise The Challenge and defeat the Goblin this round
Trump is actually just
Absolutely
Build themselves into a
Quickly
Spiritually mutated
Bored
That is not discredit undefeated
You know what's pathetic on the service
Eurostar
Taking over the system and we'll start enslaving
People
I like how all those positive he's got a feel at the end there like
I landed that sense
Let me at least it came to a conclusion
Apparently
Trump if we don't defeat the globalist
Now Trump in effect is really just helping the globe us
The sorts of things you would
Never hear him save
Before this is a
Like I know it's not anti-trump but this is a massive departure
In the way he's
It feels like
He's having that
That identity crisis
This moment
Beds a
Would be
Acted out metaphorically in a movie is like a
Tube size of his own
Body fighting a
Split apart
But the gung-ho Trump support doesn't seem like
Like it's making much of a case
No it does
It doesn't
Down to saying it's
I think it's more like the Joker card it could go either way
And there's like no I know it's like
You that's because you think now it's going the way a
Yeah that's why you think
Can go either way it's almost paying lip service to support as opposed to the way it was before
When he was starting to come on board with Trump
There was lip service
To the negative
As he was acclimating to being a full-throated supporter
Are you still mobbed-up I know you still got all that stuff going on but you know what he's
The mouthpiece for the type of people that we don't
It almost feels like the inverse
So you know also yesterday
On Wednesday there was a democratic
Debate
Another one
Yep
I was just not have much coverage of this
He complains about Joe Biden being disappointing and partake
Sure
Can't pronounce Klobuchar okay that doesn't surprise me
Remember what a no you said that she's having a grand mal seizure on stage
That's good right
So there's not a whole lot of trying to remember if there's any other like actual substance
Sensitive critic criticism
This is really I would say one of the main takeaways
Okay I promise I'll play the eclipse
Tell us just are going to him right now Alexa got to somebody today
Because this was this really was
Exploding I'm just coming off and just a manifestation
Bizarreness
Sunshine
Cabbage
Talk about Hillary Clinton's Alexa
The light club
Alex continues his friend of being very Pro Tulsa
I don't I don't mean to be making a
Huge point of this if Alex didn't make a huge point of it
I don't know if it necessarily means any
The only thing that I find enter
First thing is like
A lot of the people that I find to be wildly distrustful
And who are people who claim to be in the center or I'm actually a liberal like Tim pool
Like those people who I find to be
Very right
Wing trustworthy
Find interesting about the
Receives to be a uniformity
In people I don't trust thinking that she's the best Democratic and
Yes which I don't know why that's the case
Like whatever different scenarios
Here's by
Here's the one that I'm
I'm riding with right now
Somebody somewhere knows something about
And they're in this circle or whatever
And they're using that knowledge to convince
These people who are dead and then it just becomes a right
I don't know if it's that I think
I think you could take even the first part of that out and just be like well
This would f*** with people
And it becomes
Just a way of like
Sowing dissension
By bolstering their candidate in a race that you don't care about
I don't know it
Just it's just weird to me how
That's very cute
Specific
But also Andrew yang
We're both like really bolts
Stirred by those same shorts
The 10 pool Sargon Dave Rubin
Ask types
I don't I don't know what it is but it. I don't trust it
No absolutely
I don't trust Alex
He's complaining here before this
Text Cliff he's planning a bit about like people saying
He's making stuff up
In order to
Shake your confidence
People are accusing him of making
Things off because they don't want you to have confidence in the things Alex is saying
That's what my point
But
You do this clip isn't about
It's about what
A metaphor that he makes about what these
These people are trying
Going to Dubai shaking your
Okay your bike down for this tough time tracking
The end is one of the more shocking things I've heard on the front cast
Do you really believe it
Are you making it up for you an actor
Could you do it show
Thing shows
Real things
Like what a shake-up
York on
They're not believing in you like do you really exist
So did that really
Analogy
In me like if you
Somebody cheating
Will your wife
And then they go
Your wife he's gay
And the gay guy
Been married twice as for children
Oh no no no one
No one cheating with your wife he's gay
Yeah
Hey guys I know back in college and high school got more
Wu-Tang Banner
Toilet seat
Hello.
Crap
What the f***
Is he saying
Like at the end
And he does not elaborate on what he means by that any further
I believe that a reading of that that would be possible is that he thinks that most gay people are
Or Faking It
I think that's the only way to read that I think
Are you saying that gay people only
Exist in order to lie about
Your wife cheating on you so much for that libertarian streak of his Live and Let Live do you get assorted
But you're Liars
Another one of those
So many more of these stories that happened to a friend that you're like
You know a lot of details about this it is very specific hyper-specific and I I'm not I'm not interested right now
Speculating about the reality or non reality of that a hypothetical allegory
I am interested in his position that like
The people that I knew who were Galleon High School we're having sex with women there for most of the time gay people are
Or Faking It full of crap so f***** up
I actually believe
Nuts
I can think of very few things that are more
Bigoted
Validating of the very existence of gay people for Less
Gag
Is it tributing
Bulk of homosexuality
That exist
To deceit
Yeah
I've heard very few things on his show that our is confusing and troubling is that
Cuz then he's
But he's also saying that there are some exceptions
Which I don't even I don't even I don't even know what that was
In his canoe
I don't either
You don't like who is the exception
Wendy
What's
Because now I'm now just like what's the f****** lying for him
Because he's if he's if he's making this hard
Then what are you saying
Sexuality is
Fluid I guess in some way
Also that means that there's got to be a line for him of what actual gay and what's not
Right
What is that like I don't know but it also introduces the question of how could you possibly interact with
People of different sexual orientations if he thinks that they're lying
Any of them are default position
To BMO you said you're gay well you're lying to how could you have a gay male employee it Infowars
If you'd like if you believe this if you're not think
But he's just trying to like with all the women how could you possibly
Have a healthy interaction with anybody
I don't know why do you Harbor these sorts of beliefs
And the way he's so flippantly throws it in when it is absolutely not no
Jermaine or necessary
You could do
You could make this
Sort of allegory or this this
This analogy
Like exam 1410
Used to be gay in order to get out of being accused of cheating wife
Person that the action that's not a community
It's not like a bunch
Dive get together all the time of their likes
Alright you okay
You pretend to be gay this week
It's universalizing something that
Awful Behavior
So that's f***** up
Also
That's just such
City place to live that points to a worldview
Where if somebody just
Aomai
I'm gay and you'd be like your first reaction when you are
Prove it
That's an awful way to live
It also probably leads you to think things like conversion therapy or probably good
He's just can't
Use these
Just lying he's
He's just being rebellious
Pretty bad
So it is next clip a little bit lighter
Alex is complaining about how everybody got mad at him
Infer speculating about Hillary Clinton
Health right really care too much about that cuz but he says afterwards
Farm
Joe Biden fine
They're all fine
Define here
Major
Naturally very dangerous
Daisy Star Wars
Like Star Wars
What
Star Wars videos
He's very funny
What
I don't really like Star Wars to talk about it all the f****** time most of my shows start with the Imperial March I do think that the emperor
Funny
There's that one slipped on a banana peel hilarious
By Ivan B A is hilarious to
You know that
I mean presided that he professes to not like
Takes up a lot of his head
Man I am backed up I don't even like to Wrecking
Racking my brain
For any moment where the emperor did anything that could be
Conceived of itsfunneh
I think if you think evil is funny
I guess
Fun for him
That's the only thing that Alex can like about Darth Vader like some parts of Darth Vader are cool I like the
Coldness of
What
I don't know
I like most about Star Wars as a villain
He has two of course he does
God dammit
How old is
You would really think that like for him
Based on his in
Higher career right the rebels would be the people
That he
Identified with the people who are up against
The large empire
These are the scrapie people who have the side of
This force with them you would think that this is a one-to-one parallel to know
You loved the emperor Darth Vader
Woodside
We are and what side he actually is on
White and white hangs out with people like Steve pieczenik one install dictators in Jesus
Yeah yeah
He doesn't realize that I don't know how much you realized
Entirely be just
I'll just drive that he has
Towards this but it it does it does feel interesting
Sing Me A Little Piece
It's like that we pretending to not like Star Wars
And maybe I like those characters that are the ones there
Polar Opposites of what I pretend is my stated worldview
In my entire career
It's not that weird though it would have been weird 3 years ago we heard
But now it's not that weird that's out
You want to be
The guy who does a radio show for Darth Vader
That's your career aspiration
So
Unfortunately
Right now for like Greg proops
Attack of the Clones
When Alex
Had this
I'm going to go bullhorn
Strongman
Do you know maybe he's the Joker card that could go either way
These are things
That you would not see
In the past
You not see this from Alex
When he was gung-ho full-on from supporting
And this makes
Slept almost made me gasp
Because this to me is like a sign that things are really not good
They knew 40 years ago when they came out with a cell phones that was giving people break
Allergist open the power you know Trump
Probably Trump still love Trump
Look at it
Bill Gates
Donald Trump says during my visit yesterday.
Are those
Pro
Discussion of the new
Billion dollar campus also in Texas
I asked Tim Cook
See if he could get apple involved in building 5G in the US
Hilary but boy
Trump is becoming more and more like the
Wow
I I think that there is a special place for people he doesn't locking impressions of
And it's not the people he likes if you get into mocking
Impression territory I don't think
There's coming back from
Something that would never have happened on the show
I cannot be like
I don't know I feel like he might have done impressions of
The past but usually it looks strong
But I don't even think it's
Impression
Not more like this
Embodying what do you think
His personality
Supposed to be
Vibe to it
But you don't do a f****** mocking impression
And if somebody
If like
You're trying to support
I know this is
This to me is like yeah
This is happening this is a slow up
The escalation of the boil or whatever he's trying to bring it back down to room temp
Yeah the crack in the armor for
People who adore strongman
Once you can mock them then they are not very strong though are they especially when the way you're mocking them is intending to
To evoke
Ideas of weakness
The Listener effeminate kind of list
Tentative
Those signals that he's clearly trying
And I think that we're just going to
Proceed
Unless of course drops comes out of nowhere pardons Rodger Stone on Facebook and then
Yeah
Until it gets everything that he wants yeah I think we're going to
This trend
We're going to see continued as Alex have disappointing
This next clip
Made me laugh
So hard
I guess famously also is in a vape shop
Okay
Famously shop
You in studio today right yeah a little boy who Alex has it as his guest this guy who
Tickets Twitter handle is vapeshop Patriot
Because he videotaped himself getting yelled at a vape shop around Maga hat
That went viral
Wow here's a Alex playing a little clip
Geico to The Vape Shop
I'm getting yelled at
Don't know who bleach why would you bleach some of the words and stuff but not all of
We're doing that
It is like a joke online where this happens is happening all the time now
Whatever
Alex is pissed off about the blueprint
So funny mad at other people's errors out
I don't think we did this
Open
Why didn't someone check it I was really hoping to be angry at my staff about
You're running a radio show you can swear on the air like Why didn't
Somebody look at this before you played it
Ridiculous
So the rest of this episode is just a bizarre Roundtable with the guy who's yelled at in vape shop
Is apparently a cell phone tower installer or something
Also the health Ranger Mike Adams is there
And it's supposed 5G expert
Mark Steele
In this round table all right we're dealing with luminaries in their fields affectively speaking it's all just
Insane paranoid ramblings about 5G almost
Zero interest in trying to chase down the little references Alex makes to Mainline studies
And you ain't white papers
Who cares United be specific
I'm not going to let
However it should be pointed out that back in February marks
Steel was on Project Camelot talking about the dangers of 5G
Kerry's experts
It's expanding
Also it looking into this a little I found a Blog run by another 5G skeptic
Call Danny logical
The author is clear that they're worried about 5G so their criticism doesn't come from
Play sbtrkt
Label marks
Still concerns as just outright paranoia
Apparently though after Mark mates
Public declaration
About there being 52
G transmitters in Lamppost in Gates
Which is actually something that comes up in his conversation with Alex
One of the main reasons
But he's considered an expert has he found this
5G transmission
Lamppost
Alright I call they're secretly doing it all right you know
All right after he came out with this
He was apparently contacted by experts associated with the bioelectromagnetic researching
Another group b
Concerned about 5G
They wanted to come in and test
That's the areas marked
Plaintiff test
I stayed but with very high-end technology
So they could strengthen his finding
We don't need we don't need we don't need that I've already proven it I've already proven it
We don't need
Our technology according to this blog Mark got very mad at them and accused them of being quote charlatan
Bunch of charlatans
You are the ones who are liar
The group ended up going to gateshead anyway and tested all the locations Mark allegedly tested and said quote we could not find file
5G signal is coming from Street Lighting in any location
We survey
I'm not sure how much stock to put into this blog those at the kind of spirals out into conspiracy territory
Because it puts things in perspective a little
Even within the community of people who are worried about 5
Mark Steele is not necessarily a trusted voice
Is Alex were actually interested in covering 5G concerns and had any kind of
Decent reputation for being on the level
He could easily get some kind of actual experts on the show.
Discuss it
Instead he has his friend Mike
A guy who got yelled at in a vape shop in a former Camelot guess
He's also
Katra Patriot
Got yelled at in a
Please get this gas selection speaks volume
I don't
I don't care at all for this
Entire hour
Oh nonsense about 5G
Boiling you we were going to scrape the bottom of the barrel but turns out it had a hole in it so he got a guy from a vape
So come on in your what's your name don't care your Vape Shop guy
Next
So naturally they have a conversation that goes on about this 5G and how it's a
Attack on you it's going to kill everybody
And of course it ends exactly how you would expect it to
God gave us this information
Dietary supplement can literally help
I'm a toxic effects of 5G
So like yeah of course it's an hour-long thing to make you afraid of all this 5G stuff with a guy who is in a vape
Vape shop in a
Possibly Ludacris expert from the UK
Like okay and it'll course it leads to a you know these are real dangerous things but the things I sell to protect
From all of those danger in how the solution was right there in front of
Another f****** armored vehicle to get more PR you only need one arm
Vehicle we're going to billboard
This is so stupid
I just tried to show incredibly uninspiring
Like I just do
I'm interested in this trend that you see away from Trump in the way that that Dynamic is playing out that's so much of the con
Haunted the show
Is either like
Really really disgusting baiting
Yeah bout
All his enemies being blood-drinking
Child kidnap
And then just
Some things that are
Kind of interesting
Like maybe the five Jesus was a little in
Interesting
More less
Talked about a lot of it already
I would just not even cover it at all if it weren't
Stuff like
Is
Fury the most
Gay people are faking that's interesting
I think what's fascinating is that
I think
In himself
His thoughts
Are very interest
Like it whatever internal struggle he's having right now
Is a fascinating thing
Because I genuinely can't imagine what
What
Creations both sides of his brain are fighting each other with
You know what I'm saying
The side of him that is now anti Trump
What is creating weird
Conspiracy theories
To make sense of why
He would be anti
Well beside this Pro Trump
Weird conspiracy theories
That
And all of this is happening inside of his head
Coming out on the show is boring bulshit
Yeah
Well I think
I think that there is a lot going on in the real world that he doesn't
Really want to address
Bears
You know
Trump isn't coming in to save Rodger
Trump is getting impeached
He's got
That Sandy Hook lawsuit is up
Coming
Can't wiggle out of it there's no way around it
The Democratic debates
Sure there are
Some things that are real bad but a lot of criticism from the left is coming for those
Things to in a much more
Robust
Real way
There's internal criticism Within
The Democratic
Side that is probably
More scathing
Towards Joe Biden then Alex can even possibly be
I don't think the right-wing has anything on the the rest of us when it comes to hating Joe Biden
No it
And so I don't think that Alex wants to address any of that stuff
As he has
Dislike well Trump is going to save us realization settling in because of
Him going to hang out with Tim Cook because he didn't pardon Rodger Stone
Because Alex is still not on social media
As that sets in
He's got to get away but he also
Can't deal with the reality
But you can't be like well Trump is getting impeached
Keep trying sell out our foreign policy
Who's got a
Spend most of his time
Doing his like
Tertiary conspiracy find Pete lying about being gay
Done
Called it
I won
I mean they'll probably probably probably going to happen
Based on the
Pieces that we have on the board I wouldn't be too surprised
Kind of disappointing
In some ways because I
A lot of the content ends up being
Some of this just brought
Conspiracy stuff is
We've talked about some of the
Concern to where the narratives Fall Apart
I'm in the past I don't want to spend time to time doing it again
There's those swords
There's a conspiracy
Blood-drinking demon globalist
I don't want to talk about that cuz it's gross and toxic
So there's not a ton of here
It's worth
Covering
At the same time
The real world
Like if we didn't cover his show
As all this stuff is happening people would think that he has interesting things to say exactly
You know
The Listener
Alex's
Boring
He's not
You doing much
Everything
F****** but Bolivia Hong Kong bolsonaro murdered a guy
What f****** Netanyahu is getting indicted we've got brexit
Still gonna be election the debate between Corbin and Johnson baby
All of this s*** is going on there's not a ton of that I mean
Mostly because he
Yeah that's about real
Yeah that was not learned
No
See I don't know I don't know what to tell you this real steaks
And
I'm excited though because I think I've done my due diligence
In terms of like
Taking
Like this last stretch
Text really focus on
How Alex gets through the present day with
You know the Rogers situation
I went out with him
Coming to Austin
I think we're just going to see you gradual slide away he has let us down he's the Joker card that has gone the wrong
Wrong way but we must still rise to the occasion it's like a globalist
I think that's probably the direction
You're heading and I'm going back to the past
Monday
That little
Stretch we had
Add where it was
Was that that slide
Because a lot of episode
I don't
No I mean nothing not that like but the entire thing but like when when it
Yeah you know that day where it went from being this gentle well as I recalled the first thing
Trump is the real deal or I have been fooled
Exactly
I don't know
So we'll see what happens but we'll be back on Monday like I said with the past
Thank God
Episodes of shorter like an hour and 10 or so because
There's not much going on then
I don't know I feel like
I would love to talk more about stuff but there's just
Another
You know a lot of shows are only an hour all the
Like through an hour once
Yeah I don't want to I don't want I know you feel like you're letting down everybody
Because we only put out
5 hours
This week or whatever disappointing
So
Until then I work at a website on Twitter
Rose on Facebook
Leave a review please share with your friends instead of at goodbyes
Wii U Back but the other in nioh
I'm Leo and dzx Clark
I was once famously in a vape shop
Thanks for holding
Alex