I have great respect for its knowledge B
Stripe.com
Beverages and talk a little bit about Allie
Alex Jones Jordan Jordan let me ask you a question
Have you ever been stood up
Yeah
Yeah I got stood up by a therapist
The end of a relationship
I had
I used to be really bad at
Keeping
I still
A little bit but when I really focus
Good at it
Been writing down making
Just double-checking everything
Can bacon Missouri I had a therapist
I was working with and I had written down
A date that we offer our neck
Text session
I knew
When we were supposed to be
Yeah
Now
At this point in my life
Things were real bad
I was very broke
I can barely afford gas
I was in
Silver
I was in a particularly tight situation
The month of
Totally sure
I am.
Last bit again
I just like
To get to The Choppa
Hot neutral at the very end
Real
Did it
I stuck to it yeah I show up
No one's there
No one's there at the office
It's just completely dead
Knowing
Furious like they went out of business
Yeah basically
Enzo
End up liking I get back
And
Double-check everything all of my calendars everything I had the right time had the right day everything
And so I can
Confront my therapist
About it
He is not giving an inch
This is I have the wrong time
What are those
I look back on
Did I have the wrong time and even now like
I don't know baby 150 years later
Certain
You will not be gaslin Missouri therapist
Yeah
So that ended that
Go to work
Together Rising
I always ever is a
Shut up I have therapists
Real bummer
Man that's
That's such a high level of responsibility to you can't be standing people up if you're a therapist
It's now it's your job to be there
Literally your job
Be there for people
I'm sure I have been stood up like on
I'm positive I have but I never really take those two personal life
You take other must be a reason to
You know that's why you needed to see that therapist in f****** dessert
Have another drink
You could go home
I don't know I don't have too many memories that
But I do have a lot of memories of listening
To Alex Jones
He's never stood me up
And tell you that right now
Drew Jordan today we as men
$2 Friday episode we are back in the
Yes thank God
Very exciting for me because investigation
Checking into the stuff that Alex did
Sandy Hook it now more
Specifically the Boston bombing
Buffets we've entered here
We are now at April 24th
2013 which is my birthday happy birthday Dan from the path
So now we get to see
If Alex Jones
Has any gift
Forgive me
6 years in the past on this day wearing a little birthday
If that's okay with you
Before we get down to my birthday episode of Alex Jones
Boston bomber
Montgomery
So first of all will thank you so much and I'll probably want
Next next thank you so much and I'll probably walk
Next pasta
You are now a policy walk
The clouds so much
Adam thank you so much you are now apology walk
Next Kathleen thank you so much you are now a policy wonk wonk
Text Joshua
Thank you so much and I'll probably walk finally Clayton
It's not this guy but I wish it was
The lead singer of Blood Sweat and Tears
Horn Rock vocalists
Sure which is a
Crowded
I don't even know where to begin making that
Top 5
Wow Dicky Barrett
The guy from
Chase
Ides of March That's Amore
Anyway Clayton
I'm a policy wonk
Yes thank you if you're listening out there you love Blood Sweat and Tears or this podcast support our show by going through our website
Acknowledge right.com
What's sure we would appreciate
So Jordan
Yeah
Last we left off
Alex's doing everything
And in his power to create various
A ethiri surrounding the bombing whatever piece of
Comes out
Molding
To match that
As well as manipulating
What about those stories
To match
What are you already determine
And I think we will see
Continuation of this
And actually I think there's some really interesting
Stuff that have
Evans on this episode
About it being my birthday acai
There is a really
Yes absolutely
We start off with Alex basic
Completely admitting
That he sent
Stanford MBA
Need to go to the
The Press
That he ended up disrupting
Ride with us
Is bombastic
Questioning
War.com East Coast
Privately
Release the Kraken
Run outside Boston
It is very interesting what does he say about that relationship now he does not like to make it so
So that he tells me what to do because
The times the damper dondi went down to Newtown
I'm in Connecticut and harassed the victims families
The lawyers
People involved in the Sandy Hook
Situation was after this point after April 23rd
So if Alex has established
President hear that
He deploys the Kraken
Yeah that does seem to indicate that possibly
The behaviors
The damn batondy Illustrated
Did
In in Newtown Square at the bass
Of the One releasing
The Kraken yeah and Alex can't be like underling who did it and they didn't ask me about it very clearly
Players like hey Alice
Should we allow this man to harass people in
Go for it and they're only skill is yelling at people and being a dick
So the idea that the common skill
So Alex like a couple hours after the bombing had already decided while we're disrupting
Like he had no reason by that point to think this is a false flag no other we know that he
Determined
He had no reason to think what we need is a bombastic guy who's going to yell the truth
Fat people
He just knew like a there's going to be a lot of media attention here let's
Infowars on
Let's get our Firebrand
Resistant to call him a gadfly
Butts
Let's get that guy
Deadpool
Yeah you should definitely stay
That so
Alex is really bragging
Think about Dan bitondo
I own this beginning of this episode and a big part of it is
Because
He got on National News international news yelling infowars.com which led to a ton of
Traffic he's the toast of the Town it Infowars right now
So Alex is talking about how big his head
And I think that this dips into a little bit of phrenology accidentally
There is a
Deep fascination with head size
Sounds like
YouTube
Accepting my head is bigger than
With razors I shave
Clippers
You want to give a $500
Yes
Obviously I'm kind of joking that this is a phrenology related but it's absurd like it keeps going
Alex keeps talking about relatives
Understand
Quite a throwaway headline there
So I'm sorry I didn't mean to cut you off
I think Jacari has the right response
I didn't come over here for this
Yo
What's a boss
Necessarily
Phrenology related right
Layer of Alex has a big old bigotry know generally speaking
Good to have a larger head which inside world
Leave YouTube for neurology
About Jakari white man has the biggest Hat books
Have bigger heads
Right
It's weird.
You know what he decides to have a
Happytime beginning of the show
I do like his version of like
I've decided
To be nice
Jhacari I'm going to belittle you to your
You have a small head
So
The birthday gift I think is that
Very least
News has come out that tamerlan Tsarnaev
The older brother in the bombing
Combo
Yeah I was offended
Infowars
Dakari's head grew two sizes
That is not the that is not again
Alchemy
I've been waiting for this bit of news
To break from the story from when
Real life
And I'm excited that we've got into it cuz I didn't remember exact
Actually you know some of the details and how Alex
Responded to it
I'm so you have
News reports coming out about
Tamerlan being
The fan
I've Infowars away that headline
So we'll get into it a little bit later when he acts
Ashley touches on
Story by
But yes my heard that in my
Like we are f******
Can moving along
So as we've talked about on a previous episode there's that whole ricin letters
Situation where the Elvis impersonator got arrested but he was being set up by a guy novan conspiracy blog
Can you summarize that for me and I will not find it absolutely
It's pretty crazy story
But Alex is still insist
But they're just shuffling around Patxi's in though
Different
Target
Of course
I don't I don't understand
The standard standard don't understand any of this stuff that is absolutely not what
They're not giving you the deluxe package
They're just giving you the standard one they're naughty
You don't need
No Frills
It's like the undercarriage and in a warm climate you just don't need
It's this is
This is a bad prediction
So I don't I don't know
I don't know what else to say
So Alex starts talking about how the man
The media
The globalist
They all want you to think that the idea that this was
Is a fake bombing
Yeah that good stuff yeah they want you to think that's a
The conspiracy
Theory that is what it is
Well
I mean literally
Well here's the thing
It's not
They want you to think
And the Alex
Got some reason
You shouldn't
And I think the
Okay just hope you don't
The New York Times And The Washington Post
New York Times
Federal court
Because their own intelligence officer
And they said well you're going to go to jail
1.4 million to go back to Egypt
So Alex is playing pretty fast and loose with the details of the 1993 World Trade Center bombing
I'm here but there's just enough truth in what he saying that he would likely be able to trick anyone
Who just like
I don't want to feel like believing in more interest
Conversion
About Salam was an FBI informant who penetrated the terrorist cell that it planned to detonate a bomb at the World Trade Center
And later he would go on to
Testifying the trials that would result in the
Convictions of ramzi Yousef
Abdul Hakim Murad
And Wally
Condamine shop
Salaams recording
Things that were supplied to the FBI as well as recordings of his own conversations with FBI agent
And according to
The FBI did have an idea that this group
Salaam head info
Will traded was
Planning to make a bomb and commit a bombing
What does pacific
Details of it and the target were not known
Agents were apparently not in agreement about the best way to
Proceed with one plan being to
Supply fake
Explosive powder for the Bob
So that they can arrest everyone when they attempted
You carry out the bombing I believe that's called the Wylie Coyote
That's ordering from Act
This was discussed
But the tapes
Explicitly show that this was not
The plan that was chosen
Instead they wanted Salam to wear a wire and gather more information
In about the plot
Some very important
Contacts for what happened to the lead up
To the bombing come
2014 LA Times story
Which is one of the first time Salam spoke publicly about after that
20 years in hiding
Quote
He says he's carried a good measure of guilt because shortly before the bombing of the World Trade Center he refused to wear a hidden
SPI microphone
I dropped out of the undercover work
You told agent wearing a wire was too risky and might bring harm to him or someone in his family
He later regretted the decision
I'm saying he could have saved the six lives lost in that attack
I could have stopped
He said but I failed
Salon was embedded with these terrorists I provided crucial information about them that led to their arrest
But he didn't entrap them
And his involvement in the case no way demonstrates that
This was a government plot or a false flag
There are countless complete lies that go around about salami
Conspiracy communities that distort real details
In order to suit their purpose
Princeton
A book called the puzzle of fascism
Claims that the FBI paid Salon $1000000 to quote build a bomb
But that billion dollar figure is the amount that he was given by the government for his testimony and part of his abduction
Tune in to the Whitney
This Protection Program
Other people claim that the FBI replace the fake explosive powder Salam was using to build a bomb with real powder
According to every single piece of verifiable in
Information I could buy this is just
Fabricated
This is mirrored in Infowars coverage where they said
2010 article quote
Even Wikipedia admits that harmless powder was swapped with real bomb material
FBI informant about Salon became alarmed at the introduction of real explosives and recorded his conversation
The FBI prove it they enabled and allowed the bombing to go forward that killed 4 people
Footnote Wikipedia admits this because 5 minutes
Before I wrote this
Wikipedia article doesn't
And even if it did like I like you said anyone could easily edit the enter
It's not a good
Also if in Fort Worth can't even get the death toll right I'm not sure it's wise
To trust them on the big-picture issues like a legend
Secretive plot
You know it's about focusing on the important
Sure
Interesting Lee on November 9th
2015 Alex actually had a mod salon on his show for an interview
Really
Weirdly given the opportunity to ask direct questions about how exactly the government orchestrated the World Trade Center bombing
You spent most of his time trying to create fear about Muslim immigrants
If I were to believe that this guy is a first-hand expert about false flags and he was involved in one
In the bombing at the World Trade Center wasn't actually carried up primarily by Islamic terrorists
Why would he interview him about how we shouldn't let Muslims into the US and Europe that's a really good question, strain
Other than that is on
I can't believe I wasted 40 minutes listening to Alex
Ask about Salam about have Obama's being secretly blackmailed by the Muslim Brotherhood instead of actually nailing down his
Conspiracy theory about the World Trade Center bomb
Because it's not true
It almost
Felt like Alex was worried that if he asked
To direct
Salon Mike
Contradicting
And that would be really f****** uncomfortable good worry to have if you're Alex that's a real dicey
Also Alex probably doesn't want his audience actually look into
The trials that
Salam was involved
Because in 1995 salons actions
Jeopardize the entire
Tire prosecution
End of a semi related terrorist cell
He'd infiltrated and irrevd irrevocably damaged
His credibility
From a New York Times article with the headline
Key Witness
In bomb plot trial admits lying about his ex
Flights
Quotes
The prosecution's most important Witnesses
The terrorism trial of Sheik Omar abdel-rahman
I am 10 others admitted yesterday that he had lied for years about his back
Posting to federal agent
Some friends that he was an intelligence officer
In Egyptian Army when in reality he been a technical officer who never saw combat
The article goes on quotes
Once he said
He even lied under oath in a criminal trial in men
Claiming he been wounded
Protect president Anwar Sadat of Egypt
When he was assassinated in 90
These were things that were brought up in the trial by the process
Fusion because they were so worried about how brutal cross-examination would be if they didn't diffuse lumps
Severe credibility
His pattern of lying had the
Potential to completely destroy the case
Confuse such a crucial Witness
Kind of
Yeah
The actual facts
Available did not support the story Alex is telling on this episode of BattleBots
Salaam and I can't really find evidence that salama's ever told
This version of the story
Himself
However even if he has I'm not sure if he wiped
To believe him unless he could prove it
Which is generally my policy with people who have had to admit that they've lied under oath that ones usually pretty pretty
Signatory
It's a bad sign for someone
Reliability
But it's also weirdly common thing on Infowars
The Habit
You have to lie under oath before you can
Go on Infowars
The prerequisite
Really important
Mostly that Alex
Had to do Don and
Get into that
Like that
Very strange
That's super
Yeah
I don't know
I I I don't like this story because I'm pretty sure I hate everybody involved with
I hate the terrorists
I hate the FBI
I hate this guy and I hate Alex that's
I think this guy medwell
Maybe probably
Alright I believe I will save it
Who's the interview with Alex
Exes
Rank
Xenophobia
Like
Coming from him
As well
He heals well then he's been redeemed in my eye I don't know what happened
To get him to the point where he is in 2015 going on Alex's Show 2
Agitate against Muslim
But he's there
That is we
Weird
So Alex gets in now
Into this
Last episode we saw that he sort of
Towards cast
Suspicion toward Saudi Arabian right right answer
Discusses
That Sunil tripathi
Who was the kid who had been missing for a month prior to the bombing
In a river
I haven't
Made it suicide
He discusses that a little bit
And then brings up
I really messed up
Which I Against
Google
Also which were
Muslim leaders saying the government was involved in Austin
I need bound his arms and legs
The Congress bridge
We didn't entire episode about Andrew breitbart's death and that was not a murder
It wasn't that wasn't even a suicide
That's just a super unhealthy man with a history of heart attacks
To love cocaine and booze
Escobar unremarkable
That's right I do remember that
Only thing I remember
I was thinking about us like
I remember he's a huge alcoholic
He's got a giant nose near the end
And then Anthony cumia said
He liked to party exactly you like to stay up that's all I'll say about that
Alright
The Saudi Arabian man that Alex is talking about like I said is Sunil tripathi
B Brown University
Student who'd been missing since March 6th
Are you dumb dumb internet sleuths
Decided to turn into a suspect in the bombing
Going for no reason
His body was found on April 23rd and had absolutely nothing to do with the bomb
His family was
Deeply traumatized by the experience of having their loved one be missing and then dealing with his death all while being harassed by dum-dum internet
Absolute were convinced that he was suspicious just because of his country of origin
This new story that Alex is talking about it is about this Muslim active
It involves a man named Riyad hammad
Whose body was found in Lady Bird Lake
In Austin
On April 6th
The details that Alex is giving like his stomach being cut open
I can't find in any official
But I do know what Alex's
Is lying about
Alex said dr. Ibrahim jamali on his show on April 22nd 2000
Discuss the case
And then Infowars published an article titled quote
Condition of Riyadh Hamad body contrary to suicide
The article discusses Grimaldi saying that Hamad had been cut down his torso and it is brain was Miss
Which has been reporting as being details that contradicted the police assess
Just being a suicide
And then he held up a man
Dr. Ibrahim jamali was the Imam
Islamic Center of Greater Austin
Who is the one who received tomorrow the body after it was released from the medical examiner's off
Jamali said the body was in quote barbaric
Condition
And described it as if quote and animal might have attached
You made a formal complaint to the medical examiner's office about the presentation
The body including the cuts
Do the brain cavity
Torso what you said we're in adequately suits
The stuff about his torso being caught in all of the related complaints
The dramatic made about the shoddy they were about the shoddy job of the medical exam
Not anything to do with this
From stances of homage to the brain hadn't been removed
Before he got right
Yeah it was then removed and involved in whatever it
Yes at least that's the
Conclusion you have to come to because I've read the autopsy report and it's pretty clear that none of that kind of trauma was present
Alex's willfully misrepresenting
I have no qualms
He has every reason to know exactly what your Molly was talking
About especially considering a kind of
Turned into a big
Deal locally in Austin
From an article about the circle
Dances in the Austin
The chronicle
Quote
Jabali demanded and received a meeting with the medical examiner Dalton
And Austin Police
Chief art Acevedo
Afterwards or Molly and Dominic
Each told
The chronicle that they believed the meeting was useful and should lead to better medical examiner practices
Jamali said he quote
Cannot accept the apology offered by Dominic
For any
Understanding honest
Could I believe they were sending us a message
Well damn. That what
I told
The people here at the mosque
That they believe they do not have to respect the body
It's very clear from the article in from the ensuing interaction with the medical examiner and
Aveda but this was an issue that arose from
Feelings of poorly carried out more
Yeah that was a disrespect
Muslim
Yeah and if you
Living in
The United States as you do I totally get
Immediate jump to like these f****** are f******
You know but at the same time it's
It's just
Probably more likely the guy was hung up
Hanging out like what I understand
The medical
Explanation for it was
Like there's a misunderstanding
Our office doesn't carry out cosmetic work that's needs
To be done
To prepare for burial Funeral Home
I'm not I'm not particularly interested in that
Except to say
That these are the complaints that Ibrahim jamali was making
And Alex is misrepresenting it as being evidence
That Riata mods body
Was I all tortured up and all of that
Yeah I doubt Alex
Is allowing Abraham on
Prevalent
Anti-muslim bias
Probably not
Alex's Behavior surrounding Astoria
Profoundly disc
Cycle no matter how am I
God.
As far as actual details go police reports indicate that Hamad had duct tape on his face
And that his hands and legs were bound
These would leave somebody to believe that this was not a suicide but in reality that is
It's probably too high
If someone were definitely wanting to follow through with their attempt to killing them
And they thought it through it makes
They might try to find ways to limit their ability to chain
Change their mind at the last
Last moment or limit their bodies
Will reaction
Toward survival
Also you have to consider that someone might want to commit suicide but not want people to think it was suicide because that's very
Over their loved one
Someone in that kind of headspace might try to make things look like a
It's not impossible that was
Guadalupe be presumptuous of me to say that I can definitely say
That this was a case of suicide
I kept
Any evidence that I've been able to find
That makes me think
It was murder
Yeah tall
It makes
All the evidence
Is available
Fit the
Add that the explanation
Riyad hammad was the founder of the Palestinian Children's Welfare fund
A charity that work to improve the lives of children working and living in refugee
Palestine
I can find no evidence of him by talking about the government provocateur in terror is Alex's
Is alleging that dozen
I have no idea where that's
Brought ya
A couple of months
Before his death
The FBI and IRS stop by his apartment into
Took a ton of files from
Him about his business
Changes charity
Claimed they had probable cause
Investigating
Charges of wire fraud bank fraud and money-laundering
Charges were never brought in the case
Because he ended
So I don't really know what the reality is
Whether or not
These were legitimate suspicion
Just kind of secondary to the fact that this sort of raid would definitely alter a person's mental state
This is only one of a number of pieces of circle
Central Avenue
You can find that make it
Really look like Hamad died by
In the days before his death he was dealing with that height and governments
Governmental scrutiny
As well as an apparent apparently
Kris and racist
Harassment
As reflected in an email you sent Friend
He told of getting late night phone calls
From someone who would ask him where he
Campbell was
An article from KXAN local Austin news said quote investigators on Thursday
Said families and other sources
Told them that Hamad was
This all sounds very tragic
In terms of what's relevant for our show though Alex
Supposed to be willfully misrepresenting
Details about this
In order to prop up
Which I find to be Google
Yeah
Maudlin
It's gross
It's very gross
That's a bummer
Why do why is it okay
I wish they could I wish that
I don't like that whenever people politicize somebody's death
In
A f****** complete out lie
Like with Pat Tillman
Like he is the former football player who who f******
Gave up his football career to go fight in the Iraq War hated every second of what the
The government was doing and all that s***
And was killed in Friendly Fire and then the governor
Walking covered it up
And treated him like a paragon of United
Colonialist
So Alex
Who is talking
He claims he has evidence
Nephew
White House did something
Distracted by
How good a Moody's
So we never find out what evidence he has about the lightning
Here I am
Yes
Most famous
Kelly radio by the way
The world iPhone
Alex Jones
And World gold medal
Alright
I'm excited to be in a good mood today
This show is so f****** stupid
So bad
Like here's a big how do you get away with that
Rachel Maddow
No boss there's no biceps
That is like Vine everybody likes to have fun on the job you know whatever I'm not I'm not like hey Alex has got
To be serious all the time things that I
The reason I play that clip
Is like his information is really bad
You lying about like the factual serious Duffy's talk about the show
And that's the B
Aren't good really the show fails
On every front
Yeah it's not good
The Flights of Fancy art good
The only times that are at their anything is actually kind of good is when Alex is
Just like Uncle
Play autopilot
I don't even know those are good that's it
It is nice to know that no matter what time
Alex
Cannot make a good job
And to ensure that this bad joke last
For forever
Pretty long
So Alex
Say is cursed by knowing
He is way too smart
Way too aware of everything
And then you talk about that a little bit in this clip
He gets down to this story about how tamerlan
And was a fan
And it's just bizarre I don't know what to say
Email
Okay I'll talk to him
They took it out of contact you are his boss
21st
Your comment about their one of the bombers being a fan of his
When he said
Iotw
I was curious like a
How did
How are you taking that account
There is a slight chance
I find that defense f****** hilarious
In the time doing this show one of the most consistent threads of Alex's broadcasting is him bragging about our gigantic his audiences
Over the years we've heard numbers in the Millions
To the hundreds of Millions
He brags all the time about heads of foreign states are daily listeners
In March 2018 Alex sincerely said on his show that his audience was
10% of the United States
And conservatively 10% of the
The entire world population
Yeah which is absurd I thought we had one where he claimed that it was 2 billion
No I want to say that we got there with the highest I've I've heard is 10% of the world
That's that's quite a bit baby too much
Something he said like interval
Like video View
That could be
Like that would be like all of his
Well he got
Views on one day
Everybody knows I went and checked out this BuzzFeed
Story and here's the quote that
It's just standard anyone you talked to his familiar with my show when I go out to public half the people I meet in the
This country in another country is to say they listen to my show
The show is bigger than the mainstream media admits
They weren't really taking about a contact
He's asked about reports that tamerlan Tsarnaev was a fan of enforce
His best event is of course he was ever wanted
That's a great defense.
So Alex doesn't have to deal with any real
Like why was he a thing or what is it about Infowars that appeal to him
The downside of using
Dodge is that you sound like a pompous
Dick so now Alex is getting defensive about that and claim he got taken out of
The weirdest thing is that this Buzz
Sweet article
Says literally nothing
Does suggest Alex's show isn't as big as he claims it is
There's enough about like
Diesel I already this show is that is hilarious it's a very Fair article
So Alex been rant about how the media is blaming him
For the bombing
Bombers
Alex Jones
Mysterious
There
Right-wingers
Infowars founder
So it's important to point out that Alex has failed to substantiate any of these things about
The media saying
Found any credence
To that and he keeps saying he's played the clips and I have not heard him play those clips
Journal but they did have front-page headlines
You right-wingers are going to get it and they put an arrow towards her own editorials
He's also even just embellishing the hell out of with David Axelrod said
So what's going on here is that Alex has completely failed with the whole they're going to blame right-wingers
Narrative
That was something keep stressed super hard
Based on board last nothing
And now the rest of the world has moved on
The real suspect has been captured and is more information came out notice really interested in using the bombing to demonize right
Right-wingers but Alex still needs that to
To be true for his victimhood narrative
The float and luckily reality threw him a little bit of a bone
On the afternoon of the 23rd it was reported the Timberlands rnfa quote taken
An interest in Infowars
I've read a bunch of articles about this
BuzzFeed Salon the Atlantic
An AP and I don't think it's a fair reading of these articles to say that they're blaming Alex for
For the bombing or even trying to ask
Associated with them
Unfairly
But I think it's a
Exactly the sort of impression
Alex would like to make
I also don't feel like these articles get to the
The Crux of the issue
In each of these articles they say that tamerlan took an interest in Infowars
And also mentioned he was trying to find a copy of the protocols of the Elders of Zion
But they treat these as unrelated piece
Information
As someone who spent as much time as I have listening
Infowars
I'm very confident
The Timberlands interested Infowars
Yeah
The grand conspiracy that Alex yells about
Hours a day is so derivative of the protocols of Zion
At that it shows
It becomes a natural funnel towards
Facilitator of those same ideas
The AP article about this isn't even about
Timberlands
Infowars that's really just a side note
Or less a trivial.
The article is about tamerlan shift from being a non-religious boxer and music studio
Intuit error
Quote
Began opposing the wars in Afghanistan and Iraq
He turned to websites and literature claiming that the CIA was behind the terrorist attacks of 9/11
And at the Jews control the world
An important element in the story is one that perhaps
Can't really be told by regular news Outlet
Let's and honestly it might be a minor point but I consider it to be very
And that is the Alex Jones Infowars Arkham
Hannibal with so many different kinds of extremism
And will never ever do anything to do radicalized
If you're someone who thinks that the Jews control the world you'll hear so many things that resonate with your beliefs and Alex's rhetoric
You can tell yourself that he's smart enough
To be subtle
So the powerful Jews don't kick him off the air and that's why he's not over it
Like you would like him yet
If you're someone who's inclined towards Islamic extremist
Alex will provide you with all the ant
Auntie American government rhetoric you look
Looking for and just for good measure really here
Constant denials of high-profile insta
Terrorism
Think they're actually the government
Acting itself
If you're a white supremacist you'll get your fill of white victimhood narratives all day long
Accompanied by an insistence
But these white identity narratives aren't racist
Their common sense
If you're up militia weirdo Alex as you covered with all the revisionist
American history you need to justify your beliefs
That one day you'll be forced to Noble
Kill your fellow citizens
In order to bring back
The glory of the Republic
When I hear report that a person driven by extremist ideology ended up committing a horrible a
And they are here that they were a fan of Alex
My media responses
Make sense
But doesn't mean that Alex is fully or even partially responsible for what they do
But it's foolish for us not to recognize Alex for what he is or at least
What he was
For many years
That is a radicalization
Pipeline
Because here's the thing
No matter what you enter into Infowars with
Regardless of the flavor of your extremism
There will never come a time that Alex
Tells you to calm down
There won't be a time when Alex says that your ideas are crazy
Because in order
To do that he would need to call his own idea
His business model relies on never moving backward toward less extreme
So when you have someone like tamerlan was getting into the ideas that the Jews Run the World
He's going to find Infowars
And what he hears their is going to make
So that's really what I feel
Think is important
About this
This story this
Wrinkle of time
Chamberlain being a fan of Ali
It's a recognition of like
Yep
That makes sense
Alex
Because of the way he does is brought
Because of the themes in it
Because
The
Tradition
He's building a pond
It's
It's something
The people of all day
Stripes
Of bad
Ideology
And resume
Yeah and I took
Yeah that is
That is really interesting
To look back at
One Cocker was still around
People didn't
Know quite what
Alex Jones was
Yeah a lot of people or maybe not many people do
Obviously some people of course did Buddy
People were like
I remember this one
And I was thinking is this more like
Hey this guy's a crazy conspiracy
Is conspiracy theorist angle is that what they're doing instead of being a
Anti-muslim
Extreme is terror attack
It's this guy is actually just like any other
Weirdo conspiracy
But now we know obviously hit Alex Jones is an inspiration
Yeah and I don't know
How much
You can really say
Conscious
Saint Alex's
Part but it certainly
Yeah and that's the part that I think is really particularly Dane
Keep happening
Any keeps refusing to exam
Yeah that leads
Suspect that he knows what he's doing he's in denial or he's fine with
Yeah that's
The situation
Neither is
So Alex is going to get back to this topic
Of course he is
Because it's about him
But he also has some other little narrative
Is the pepper in and one of them is
News about Eric Holder
Attorney General
Where is
USA USA USA is due process
Want the babies at the mortuary
Kermit
Not the frog that the abortionist
They brought most of charges with judges
Is dropping most accounts against
Associated Press
A year or so
Yeah okay
So first of all Eric Holder did not own
An abortion clinic
This was a right-wing talking point that was going around
Set this. In 2013
And Alex has been talkin it up a little bit
The story that's told varies depending on how angry the teller is
Is that holder
I heard variations of it where holder owns the clinic he runs the clinic and at the clinic he owns is one where atrocity
Visa been committed
This particular narrative is being trotted out at this point in time because Kermit Gosnell is on trial
And the anti-choice right-winger trying to craft the narrative where the doj is giving him a light scent
Which is naturally explained by holder owning an abortion
Sure that all makes
Perfect
None of it's true
The reality is at holders wife is
The co-owner
Kind of
Of a building where one of the tenants of reproductive
They have no connection to the clinic
Itself they're just sort of the owners of the building
I say sort of owners because holders wife is actually just a trustee
In a Family Trust
That holds
The property
Me and Eric are legally unable to profit from renting the property
To anyone and the money accrued from the building will be transferred to her nephew and niece
Along with the building itself
Because the other co-owner is
Bear co-trustees in
In this family tree
Okay cool I want everybody on the right-wing to have their lips
This is bulshit
The building was to be given to these children according to a will drawn up by their father prior to his death in 2004 but
But they can't take ownership
Legally until they're 8
Right so they have
If this Family Trust owns this building that houses a reproductive Health Clinic
They can't profit off of it
It's just because like a regent until the king comes of age
The story that
And the
Stuff is all getting mixed up because
The tenant
That one of the doctors
Who was working at
Did get
In trouble for
Medicare fraud
Okay but
It's being mixed up with all of the
These other horror stories surrounding
He kills babies at 2 years old and brought about about
Links to the Gosnell
What's trying to be all muddy.
Right so answer the question of Kermit Gosnell he's not someone I would catalog as an abortion
He's someone I would say is a murderer
It's a fair point to say that he was someone who worked
In the field of reproductive health
What he actually did was not appropriate care
This would be like if there was a dentist killing patients at his dental office
And I will use him to argue that the entire field
Industry is evil inverter
Yeah that'd be crazy that be like if somebody thought that psychologists wear
I'm trying to sabotage his entire career so he built a religion about demonizing
So gosnell's Clinic had a long track record of citation
A various
Complaints not as serious as what he would actually end up being charged with
But things that should have been real red flags
Hebron sued a number of times and ultimately in 2010 his Clinic was raided by the FBI working
In conjunction with Pennsylvania State play
The conditions they found were horrified
Patients were subjected
Completely unsanitary conditions
The clinic Gosnell was in
Employing unlicensed
Staff
And his surgical room was described as quote resembling a bad gas station
In bathroom
That's not good
In the course of Investigation detectives uncovered multiple cases
Gosnell killing babies after birth
Being delivered and at least one woman whose death you appear to be responsible 24 due to
Holy s*** that you're so f****** doctor from Hustler whatever you know about this dude
In January 2011 Gosnell was charged with
Is 8 counts of murder but by the time you went to trial in 2013 a ton of other charger
But added
When Alex is saying it's some of the charges have been dropped
It's because the court felt like
The evidence surrounding three of the counts of murder were not strong enough to
Pursue
The question came down to whether these babies were born alive
I need those three cases the
The state could not
Definitively prove
Where's they could in the other cases
He weren't trying to give him a reprieve
Nor did it really affect the legal position
Just a situation where they we
You can't really prove it but we can't prove those to indict you on five counts of murder
So obviously people are like
Why not hate your
Gosnell very clearly was still eligible for the Deaf
Even with those three
Charges dropped
Ultimately Cosmo made a deal where you agreed not to appeal the Court's
Decision in exchange for not receiving the death panel
He was sentenced to three life terms
And will die in
No one gave him an easy
The time
Just making s*** up in
Mirror
Eric Holder and he's not even really primary
Didn't attacking holder
So Alex has discovered
A person in government Becky
Feels like you probably has a bond with
Because she is out there saying that the Boston bombing was a false flag okay there's very inter
And a New Hampshire lawmakers Boston bombing was a government
Job
Lawmaker
Hampshire
Iran
Is responsible
Facebook
Top down bottom up
1 Prospect
Are now terrorist attacks
Byron government
I've been found out
Chamberlain win
This is weird this is weird
So in here we have been 2013 case in early
Of an elected official coming down with what I call the Infowars bug rights
Stella Tremblay was a member of the
New Hampshire house of
But I should tell you that she was not
Furlong
After this point
She resigned in June
2013 most likely due to a very considerable backlash to some of her comment
Earned her a rebuke vote
Former house collie
The public didn't seem to have too much of a problem with her being a pretty clear Sovereign citizen
And I guess everyone just got to put up with her being a very public
According to a story about her any hopping
Engine post six months prior to
Her comments about the boss
Boston bombing
Tumblr quotes
Email to the other 399 State House members with a doctored video she claimed depicted President Barack Obama
Thank you was not born in the United
Okay okay
Also quote
In February Tremblay told a legislative committee that President Woodrow Wilson
Agreed with Adolf Hitler
Even though Wilson died before Hitler Rose to power
Okay
He probably did though
I mean it all honesty Woodrow Wilson
Would have agreed with Hitler we're here at slightly different argument
My praise.
The story also points out the tremblay's history advisor has publicly claimed that quote the US government is under the
Control of Queen Elizabeth the second alright well that one's not true
I will admit that her history advisor told her that
This is all just now that you know it's just good fun
A little disagreement across party lines or something
However in the aftermath of the boss
Bombings Delaware
It's probably it probably wouldn't have been too big a deal if you just suggested that the event was
The false flag
Like that people kind of absorb those
She has a history of saying dumb s*** so probably just be another exam
The problem really seem to be that you was accusing victims of Faking in
Play went on the
Pete Santilli show and argued that
If she'd had the sort of injuries
She saw those pictures
Cheapies
Remix
These people who are there probably act
This is what led to the real backlash
And the calls for resume
He's a crisis actor
Conspiracy purse
So the possibility of Alex getting her on the show and being like Jesus talking about him
That doesn't bode well
Hose
Stupid he saw an example of what it was that he
Examples of consequences for calling People crisis actors very public while she hasn't been forced to resign yet
By the the larger picture here that Alex doesn't know how to deal with his in
On the one hand he seems proud that this New Hampshire House member is referencing him and hurting
Conspiracy ramblings on Facebook
Spell simultaneously
Complained about the media saint
Tamerlan was a fan of Infowars
The reality is that they're both into his work
The terrible influence on both
And I know
Pretty much everybody who falls for a
So I don't know it's very it's very weird to see this on the same episode he's really pissed off about people saying tamerlan
Does fan and then also being like
Play this lady who's my fan who sang the same stuff
Yeah
Yeah oh boy
I wondered about how much of this is like
She wrote this on Facebook to Glenn Beck
I wonder how much of it has to do with that
The kids I mean
Was she writing something to Glenn Beck that Glenn Beck this
So she don't look out for Alex or Alex
Just sticking up for her for
Glenn Beck
I don't know I'm not entirely sure but the fact that
What you wrote to Glenn Beck and Alex is covering it
Doesn't seem
It doesn't seem unrelated but
Anybody who's in an elected position
Mentions in Forza
Probably going to
To get
Some coverage
So when I looked into this episode and I know it started listening to it on like
Episode yeah Alex was talking about a limited fan of his we've got there
I thought that that was going to
To be like the real main thing
That
I found in this episode
Who's going to be interesting
Right and actually
About halfway through
Alex has another narrative
That actually I think is
Barbara
It has to do with a story that Alex's
Just found about
Chamberlain
Across Russia
Foundation
Jamestown
The board of directors of ngos previously entered one of the audiologist of US foreign policy
Russia
What is engaged in recruiting residence of North Congressman to work in the entrance of the United States and Georgia
Working for oil company
So this is a perfect case of Alex doing the worst
Job you possibly could as a news caster
Here he's trying to report on a story about why the Russian
Warn the United States about tamerlan Tsarnaev
You can't possibly be bothered
Specific about anything
I tried to search the article is talking about but it's almost impossible
Like what does it mean by Main Line Russian news
What is that
How do I look for that source
The way Alex delivers his stories is intentionally designed
To make it more difficult for his listeners to follow up on anything
So it's important that he has a particularly dubious piece of information
It's key for him to be as vague as possible so they end up hitting a ton of data
I heard Alex and Eclipse a document
Please
So I knew that if I found a video for this episode I did least get a
Brief shot of the article
So I hunted down the video and what a shock
Alex is completely misread this headline
The way he reads it is quote tamerlan recruited
View of the Georgetown Foundation Jamestown
Us non-profit
Very connected
Is a big Noob resent
The actual headline of the article is quote tamerlan Tsarnaev recruited via the Georgian found
The rest of the stuff he's reading his just disconnected bits and pieces from the article he's taking out of context because they're worth it didn't disappear
You can see the places where the article is like
These words do not read to the
The. Of the
Sentence read until the end of this highlighted
Gotcha obviously there's a big difference between Georgetown foundation and George and found a
What Georgian is a reference
Eastern European country where is Alec
Famous reading that is Georgetown because that's at University that plays a massive role in his
Beer SeaWorld
Carroll Quigley taught it George
And of course quickly was on the
It on the grand overarching
Conspiracy
In this instance I cannot see this as anything other than a
Unintentional misdirection
If it wasn't why would he
What do you just say that
The story of the Maine
Russian press
Instead of specifying a source
If you wasn't intentionally lying why wouldn't he
Correct himself a scene Georgetown instead of Georgia
There's a perception he wants his audience
What's to take in
And that is what the globalist
Dakota Chamberlain
And that person
What is basically impossible to create if you report to the story straight
In reality
This was a story published in izvestia
Which is not a source Alex
From 1917
Izvestia was the official paper of record of the Soviet Union
So he should probably have some
Concerns about their editorial positions in process
Just a few things Russian papers are notoriously objectivity government-controlled
The Soviet Union
In 2005 the paper was purchased by gazprom
The energy giant that's majority-owned by the Russia
Government
That was sold to the National Media Group into
Even so allegations
The paper being used
Disseminate Folsom formation put out by the Russian government have linked
I'm not certain how prevalent an issue that is but I would prefer to err on the side of not discounting the story just
Because it comes from what might be a dubious
I bring most of this up because Alex should absolutely not trust this
Paper based on who he
They were the mouthpiece
The Soviet Union for the better part of a
Century
And even after the breakup of the Soviet Union
They still employed Stalin personal political cartoonist Boris
Yakimov until his death
In 2008
For some powerful dude get up
Personal political cartoonist some good being a rich person
For some context that cartoonist
His first book
The forward was written
B raps
See nothing this is what I'm saying this is the dude right here I wasn't able to find this axe
Will article
But I did find an article in The Interpreter covering the underlying article
Apparently izvestia was alleging that they receive documents from the Georgian inn
Interior minister
Reclaiming the D Caucasian fun
Was in League with the Jamestown Foundation
And they were recruiting residents to advance us interest in
In the country of Georgia
Basically attack
Can Russia
The claim that these foundations were actually doing this has not been proven
And on top of that the additives
Situation that tamerlan attended one of the
The meeting they held to recruit
People is based on no information
I'm past the fact
Tamerlan was in the region
At that time
Even Artis eventual coverage of this story says quote
Georgia's Ministry of internal affairs said it had no knowledge of whether Tsarnaev had attended the seminar
Quote we don't have such information we haven't heard anything of the kind we don't know
Nino giorgianni
Head of the Georgian Ministry of internal affairs press service told Rai
Novosti
Both Russian State media is like Infowars but sometimes they issue
She Corrections like
Coverage underwire
An issue that needs to be pointed out here is the Russian state would have a very vested in
Justin trying to disrupt Western relations with Georgia
At this point in time
There was a process in motion for Georgia to join NATO which would have made it
The farthest
East Country due south
The time which Russia would naturally see as a threat
An incursion
Accusing the west of recruiting people to attack Georgia attack Russia from Georgia one of whom
Ends up becoming a domestic terrorist in the United
Seems like a good method to so some trouble in the NATO accession
Yeah that would
That's just kind of speculation on my part and I can't really stand behind that is being what's up here
All I can say is that evidence offered is
And I'm generally pretty skeptical of vague information that comes out of Russia about these sorts of regional issues
Involving
States that are leaning towards
I think that you need to really
Nail down specifics if you got a
Traffic in that
But even leaving all of that aside
The story that Alex is telling doesn't like
This report
From the Georgian Ministry
Into your interior Ministry allegedly
It's claiming that tamerlan was recruited in the summer of 2012
And that's why the Alex
This is why the Russian government
Warn the United States about him
Well that's when you would that was the summer of Rage
So
I wish I would recruit a lot of people
Unfortunately Russia War the United States about tamerlan in early 2011
Well before this alleged
Recruitment meeting discussed
Denny's Vestal
Therefore Alex's narrative
Cannot be true
It literate based on this
A piece of information that he's bringing
Table this is why the Russian government warrant yet
Can't be true timeline doesn't work
That sucks
Alex's just found it
Stan shaded report out of the Russian media that contains enough buzzwords
How to connect tamburlin with Georgetown and zbigniew Brzezinski
So he's running with
Is a sloppy work
And It ultimately mean
Have
Georgian
Georgetown and you just
Just don't do anything about it like either you can't read or you're just a flat-out liar
And that both of those are really bad later in the episode you read the headline Lee does read
It correctly but he's back in
Okay alternates a little bit
Kind of leads you to believe that it's
Just bad reading yeah
But the worry really brilliant blurring of the lines
While still giving yourself some space to be like
Don't know I said it correctly
It's hard just misspoke the other toy
It's hard to say exactly but at the
The same time
The Narrative that he's putting forth
More closely
I'm thinking it's Georgetown then Georgia
Yeah so I choose
Chooses top I mean
Inclined to believe
That its intention
But I'm not tired
So in the next clip Alex their claims
The he spoken
Tamerlan's family
And I don't believe this is
We confirm that I talk to her
I called her back and she's crying she does Abel trust me like a bug is there listening I can't talk
I love my family
America
I thought it was free terrible
Obviously
Catch
And by the way
I don't believe this for a couple reasons
Because it's Alex
Mostly
The other thing is like hey
Who's Drew
You probably just put her
It's serious Danger
That's one of the reasons I don't believe that it's
Because I think even Alex would recognize
I might get this woman killed
If I am talking like this on air
Yeah and I I just don't I don't believe any of
I don't
I just don't
Whatever
There's such a weird line that Alex has
Between like
What he'll repeat and what
Pretends he's like that's off the record I must keep that sacred
Like I can't imagine the reveal that Donald Trump jr.
Yeah
I don't know I don't listen to this
Just don't
The most
I will give him
Is
In in my head here's how this plays out
He gives her a call and she
She's like sure I'll give you a name
And he's like okay I'll call back that falls through with more information
And then she does a cursory Google search
Infowars
I am not going to be giving you an a
Or because you're f****** lying piece of s*** or even just a ball drop
Even know
Decision is made
You like that it never
Yeah too busy talking to other sources or whatever
Definitely not the government calling and threatening that there's also decent chance that Alex just saw some
Some comments the family had made
In other media sources
And realizes there's no downside to me just making stuff up
I think it's entirely possible that it's just
Hulk
That's possible
So is talking about how to do scientific
In the world is
Globus plan as we know he just saw Oblivion
Blown really really f***** him up on
So that is part of what he's talking about that's all the globalist
Name drops another movie in this
Is there a mic while that's in play
That's crazy he wrote Moonraker in the fifties
Ian Fleming
Moonrakers the play
Garden garden
Zardoz
I'm not going to be able to get the image of Alex Jones wearing that costume out of
The grossest thing are gross
So the this comes after like a really long stretch of him
I'm doing a call back
Depression and yelping about Cobra Commander
He's yelling about how like they're like the globalist
Are Cobra is the media's going to take this and say that I believe in g.i. Joe
No it's all the same
The media's going to take this
Play I Believe In g.i. Joe which is f****** crazy
I don't even start of idiots
It's at its very unhinged
He's just filling time and he knows that's one of the only.
Impressions
A lot
Guzzardo's Bobby does not
Abu
So he's got this story from izvestia
This
Story about
This alleged
Recruitment thing
The Chamberlain
Was in the region at the same time as so therefore Alex
Decided he did go to this
It's interesting because the next time he brings it up on the episode
He's completely changed the story
Even from
The beginning of how he was president
Story up on infowars.com is that the CIA
The older
1 Brothers
The older Timberland brother
So Alex has now changed
The story to the CIA recruited
So we have
The Jamestown Foundation
And the Georgian fund
In the article real legitly
Alex's change that to
But he's already pivoted because he knows
He's made it vague enough that nobody's going to be able to find his underlying story
And so they're just going to take his word on it cuz he's a f******
But you knows everything
So now I'm supposed to believe that the big new Brzezinski is working with the CIA
The thing is
You could believe that when he was a secretary of state
The thing is the big represents key isn't
Even really reference
In the article itself it's just
Did the Jamestown Foundation used to be on the board of
Right formula
Right so
Yeah whatever
Alex is just
Created this as a new wrinkle
That he's adding on to the story
He has no reason to report
What an ass
Write the stories
Enough on its own
But now you add this is just
Now you're just creating a fiction who isn't involved
Everyone involved
College Foundation
Zbigniew Brzezinski this all the way to the middle.
So it look dude
Obviously
You could have your
If you have
Your position
Different than Alex
Because you're dumb
And that is because Alex is backed up by season
Expert Auto Electric
Black Ops
Yes call me
They call me
Those are all qualities you associate with
I do love that like they call me spooky
Who's the second
Time the spookies come up I don't know it must have been some headline
About it must be some story I don't know what to say some local Austin paper and
Alex Jones
Is it ghost
Alex's
Steve pieczenik agree with them
I will say I am very willing to disagree without so
That is not changed my perspective you know they are seasoned to taste
They are not necessarily seasoned well
Took Alex doesn't have either of them on the show
On the 24th but he does have dampened
This is one of the satyr interviews I've ever heard in my life
Because we learned some things
About what's happening in Danville.
These life hasn't all Ono
Happened within
Infowars
My friend
So he has batondy on and it comes up a couple times
His life is falling
The part
Yes family members who don't want to deal with him because of this
Behavior right he said that his girlfriend doesn't like the fat his girlfriend's family doesn't allow him
Him at their house anymore that's good call
Look at these are natural,
It's going to reserve
Like bringing this kind of negative attend
It's your life
You see this and you hear Alex basically like they just they're just cowards
Write this is
Same isolation
They can see him doing with his collar
We start with the
14 year old boy
The last episode you see this like
Hey Alex all this negative stuff is happening because I believe
IQ and I'm taking the appropriate action
Based on what you say
I feel like these are negatives
No the positive all those people are weak
They just don't know the truth they can't
Can't handle it they should be giving you a parade f****** cowards the only truth is here
There's a f****** Colts
Yeah that's
That's really terrible because his example is
Is you believe all of this s*** and then you make millions of dollars lying
Like
Of course he's not going to say anything other than
This is the greatest works for me it works perfectly for me
0 consequences
Yeah only imagined one people saying that I'm
Tied to the bomber I'm able to turn into positive driver
It's a real bummer because like I f****** hate damp adande but it's same time even if you have this villain
Guy
Do you can still clearly see the manipulation that Alex is doing
To him
And when he comes on Outdoor Show and talks about
Personal
Consequences that he's
Having
Can't help
But feel a little bit for it
At the same time I think more of my empathy goes to like his
Or his family
Who has to make that difficult decision
Looks like hey
We have a boundary and you crossed it
Right
I just
The human aspect of this is always very difficult
When it's when
When it comes up
So I'm not going to play too much damn batondy his girlfriend
Family is super stoked
That they have to
Keep her
Boyfriend out of their house
Like that's any of the former pro wrestling a real bummer of just being like
Okay
It's Dynamic you never really want to
To have like you're dating
Somebody in your family doesn't get along with them
City yeah
Because he's an Infowars reporter who disrupt
Boston bombing press conference
It takes on an elevated level of like hay
That's that's not the look who's coming
To dinner but he does do some
That I
To pay attention
Oh no Thomas Jeff
Tell me about my day
George Washington all right that's a real famous quote that it's better to die on your feet than live on your knees
From George Washington it's a real rally and cry
I meant to give that you feel like you should give your life rather than submit appearance at George Washington 100%
George Washington
The best thing that Alex Arredondo could do to make this American in origin is to say that it's an fpr
Since he did say it on in a June 19th 1941 speech
Quote we to Born to
The freedom and believing in Freedom are willing to fight to me
Maintain freedom
We and all others who believe as deeply as we do would rather die on our feet than live on our knees
However
Fpr was actually making the reference
The source of the original quote
Which is probably why you said we and all others who believe is deeply as we do
The original source of this quote is Mexican revolutionary Emiliano Zapata
Alex does not like Zapata
Mostly because he was involved in peasant revolt
And carried out directax
Turn towards land reform
It's such a bizarre phenomenon among these right-wing idiot
They fetishizing lionize the founding fathers of our country and yet so much they think
They know about them is
Fruit
They imagine what their political
Positions really word attributed all sorts of
Wheelie Falls quotes
But the trend that I'm starting to see looks a little more Sinister than it is
These people are robbing non-white communities of their history
Alex has repeatedly tried to pass off a Frederick Douglass quote is being a
Thomas Jefferson quote
Adhered a downed he's taking his
Zapata quote and attributing it to Washington
They love the words but they want a white person
To be saying
And I'm not saying that Alex arbit on do you consciously even doing that
I think it's entirely possible that they just get all their information from places where the prevailing thought leaders
Or whitewash
Don't people like Alexandra.
They have no idea they're parroting back
Completely incoherent in Falls version of History
Did they claim to love some
It's most likely
Yeah I mean there's an ecosystem to probably Reaper
Purposes
Really great
Appreciate
That are part of
Non-white
Community's history puts them on people like Thomas Jefferson and so many of them are quotes
About defeating
The very tyranny that they themselves represent
You know like Zapata isn't
Isn't saying that
Because he wants a whatever-it-is government Alex Jones
No most always the polar up
So they take the people who are on the right side of History
Turn them white and use it for the wrong scientist like a Frederick Douglass specifically about the Confederacy and
Slavery
And Alex attributes that to Thomas Jefferson to do Alex's
Family members who were alive back then specifically fought against Frederick Douglass
It's just it's
It's nonsensical but it makes
Total sense all of the good parts
Of American history
Are actually done
Buy wipes
People who oppressed reason that does
So in his next Club Alex.
Is a gas that's
There's actually a little bit of drama
And it's an email.
He says
Friend
Show that is coming up
So I don't know if you actually Alex even gets to that thing
Sing from the Elijah
Cop I don't know if he does
If he does it's very
Subtly worked in
And I didn't notice it
Lindsey Williams
If you ever call Lindsey Williams
Who's the guy who claims
He was a chap
On an oil derrick
Or something like that
Through that ended up meeting
Elite globalist we ended up living with for a few years ago secret information
That ends up not being
So he's running that
Scam he's he's got that Forrest Gump thing going but he's he's adding a little Chaplin
Intuit so he's coming up later on the show which I was like that's not
Cuz Alex is audien
I don't know exactly the timeline of it but if I understand correctly by this
They've largely turned it
Because he is so clearly a shell not for like the government but he's just trying to he's running a hoe
Even Alex is audience
The see-through guy story makes no sense
These predictions are s***
You just trying to sell s***
Like I've seen it on Alex's message
Baseboards like a real
Anti Lindsey Williams
Yeah sounds like
So he's coming later
Alex Goes to call
One of these callers
Hissing Oblivion
Okay alright look f****** dumb laser focus now let's do that I'll excuse
Still deeply obsessed
So I want to rewrite this movie through what these idiots say about
Was an amazing film have to say
Pro-mail
I mean
It's something you don't see anymore
It's about clones
About water
Yeah they just like heaven session
Two dudes really love the movie
And then Alex of course he has to brag about how his magazine
Have the bad guy and I've only playing this
Here the giddiness
And Alex's voice listen to it
What
Czi attend
He's so excited
And again I have to stress the cover of his magazine
Lead was just a Photoshop of Hal from 2001 A Space Odyssey
Luciana.
This is
He doesn't get as much credit as he thinks he does
There has to be something that could have been like there's got to be somewhere along his life where you could have had
This
Very childlike
Glee it seems something
Exciting and fun and meaningful
The him and turn that into something other than
Turning into a f****** monster that harassed
The people in it
Only occasionally pulls out
Unfortunately the thing they gave him that Glee
It was
None dare call it conspiracy theories
Probably a weirdo JBS John Birch Society friends
Three-way last you think that Alex just saw a Bolivian once
Give me wrong I knew he thought I knew you thought more than once
Again of course the second time
Dudley man
I would have gone and seen Rush
I refuse to believe that he did this
This story has to be alive the story has to be alive because it's possible
A particularly big fan
I'm going to f****** rush rush
Is really great I like I like
And I do believe that
Possibly could have gotten backstage
Is what I understand Neil Peart is a bit of a libertarian
So
Incredible
And
The love
Great album liberate those drums from boredom
Sogo
So Alex has another little bit of a story that he covers and that is that
The AP was
Except it wasn't really okay anyway
This leads into more talk about
Everything RC
And it doesn't really hurt
Programming
Programming man
How does he feel about how the blank has fallen turned into a franchise
Do these dudes talk about this story super dishonest
There's kind of a perception
The Associated Press itself got hacked when in reality was just their Twitter account
Is much easier
To happen
And someone who is hacking around
Ended up posting that the White House there been
Explosions in present
It was injured
A group called the Syrian electronic Army took credit for the hack
And probably worth noting that they re pro-assad organ
Innovation 2013 Obama and Assad were not on
Particularly good
This was not a globalist false flag
But to know that Olympus Has Fallen was evil predictive programming
I can cross that off my list three more movies are we going to drop on the
So many
Business Club Jordan
I think it's
Fascinator
Cuz
Caller calls
And this guy wants to talk about the same sort of theories that New Hampshire
House of Representative
Stella Tremblay has sure about the victims
Of the Boston bombing being actors
Right
Now at this point Alex's heads
On the show to commit open
Right answer
Pieczenik
Very much
A crisis actor guy
Alex has made
Waffly overtures towards the idea that there were definitely actors
In the Aurora shooting
Sort of
Dipped his toe a little bit in
To Sandy Hook
Saying that some of these people who are survivors and family members are acting weird could be like actor
So I heard this caller.
I wonder what Alex's
Is going to do
His response
Really shocked
I'd like to address a popular photo
Circulating job
And possible use of actors involved at that field bomb
The one I'm talking about
Circular the immediate relief showing us a lot
Of the guy with the
Supposedly just lost his legs
Being helped by a guy in a cowboy hat
He's on a wheelchair
Is actually a series of photos
Close-up shots
All the bombs site itself
And it shows a hooded man
Sunglass
What looks like he's like
Dropping the guy
On the ground
And then
It's like all these sort of Fab
Other suspicious-looking photos where
I m like
There's no actual
Black
Squirting from the
Guys like
Two legs
Official
Over and over and over
They may.
Aurora
And the other guy
Signs of MS
I don't care
During this job
I want to get into it
Confirm
It's not a f****** lame man so this is super interesting
To me because if you really look at what he's doing he's trying to have it both ways absolutely
Because he's trying to shut down this talk of actors
But if it
Time
Saying
That these people who come out in
And talk to the media are Act
Yeah trying to
To give you the official story on it
So what key
He's doing particularly about the Aurora shooting
Is insisting that one of these people who claims to have been in the theater and survived the shooting
Isn't actor who the globalist
To put there to put out the official
Call story
That is invalidating
And taking away this guy's agency
And accusing him of being in on a false flag attack that killed a bunch of P
So it is the same
The only line he's drawing relay
Is where and when the actors
Get put into
Interaction
Somewhat but I think the more important
When is
You pushing back on the idea that people are presenting that no one
That's the only thing that he seems to really have a relevant difference with
With the people who are presenting the crisis
It's a matter of scale
Really is Alex is saying that some of these people who have survived these things are actors
Who are paid by the globalist
To put out the propaganda
Right
These other people are saying all of them
That's it that's the difference
Okay
So I kind of got what who what he was saying is that the
Actors who were there are
Hired right
What do it so if I understand his idea his conception of their pee
Alex
Yes
They are orchestrating this
Mass shooting
They have hired a couple of actors
Put them in there
I would say the or hired them after the show
Which way do you think it goes
My sense of it is
After
Or
Yeah I don't know he's not really clear see that's that's kind of where I'm
I'm confused as to
Because if they were there and it is a real shooting
Seems too risky
It seems like you wouldn't
Be able to make sure that the person
Isn't hit by a stray bullet
Yeah I would have
To say that it's someone who was paid
After or
They would have to have so much awareness of it to Nowhere to be building yeah
I don't I don't know it's very muddy
It's unclear
I don't know that is that's an interesting question
So the entire thing is orca
Castrated by the globalist
As a
I guess as a mass shooting
Yes
Then the globalist hire actors yes in order to tell the media
That
Do what they think happened
Didn't really happen and what the globalist say happened is what he
Yes
I think
Yeah it took give the official
Yeah narrative
But I do think that did
Have to be there
In order for there to be a credibility
Otherwise it doesn't make any sense
Yeah cuz if
Pressed on it to prove that you were there
I mean I guess Alex is saying that this guy produces a ticket stub and everyone supposed to believe that that could be
He's trying to imply the first
Wasn't that
Right
I don't know and if not official story then
You have
We don't need to hire actors you got cops
To say would have
It's really bizarre I don't know but I think that
I think the most important thing cuz I don't think we're ever going to get the bottom
I think the most important thing
Is Alex is already
In terms of saying
This is like people are actors
But he's just
Not committed
The larger
Picture of everyone
Rick B weide
Spread that there's a
He's already deaf
Currently saying that it's
Worthwhile to suspect some of the people
Yeah being actors so I almost feel like our investigation
I mean it's just
It's complete but it's it's
It is already happened
There's just a matter of him getting to the point where
Is full then narrative is
Right it's already started
Right right right
No what do you get started a long time
Hemoglobin
His material difference
His material difference from the people who say no one died at Sandy Hook
Is that he thinks some people died at Sandy Hook
Yeah and that's it
Otherwise there are crisis actors because they have
Be hired in order to give
Yeah give the statement
The whole thing is a false flag and it's just it's just he thinks that they like killing people in other people are like
They didn't
They wouldn't kill any
And if they like if Alex is saying that this guy who survived the Aurora shooting
Is lying
In order to
Put forth
The globalist narrative
It's not a far leap from that
To the Sandy Hook families
He's also are doing the same thing
So it is because the behavior is the same
They're in the media giving the globalist
Talking points about this
Tragedy
And so was the guy who survived the Aurora shooting right
It's it's the same
It's just a matter of
Putting it where it's
Inevitably going to
Yeah and furthermore it means that they
The
Globalist
Didn't just like engineer a mass shooting but they engineered eggs
Exactly how it would go down
And then hired
Something like that
So Alex gets back to the tamerlan
Russian story
This
Is really important
Breaking news
In Georgia training under a CIA program
That clip I think is so crucial
Is it perfectly illustrates the way Alex jump
Conclusions
The actual news is a
Possibly unreliable Russian media Outlet is claimed they have documents from the Georgian interior Ministry that shows that
Georgian foundation and the Jamestown Foundation
We're recruiting people to meddle with Russia
They don't say anything about the CIA and they don't prove or even
Specifically assert that tamerlan was definitely one of these m
The Russian media Outlet did not really
He's documented for all we know they may or may not eat
Exist
But you hear her Alex reports
He says that tamerlan quote on record documents released in Georgia training under CIA program
None of that even relates to the sources work
That's how it's making things up
And it's so important to understand the little things
Eggs and why he does what he does
He's talking like this
Got to make
Kids conclusions which are just his imagination
Sound definitive and authoritative
It's on record
So it's definitely true
The documents are released
Which creates the perception that Alex has seen these documents
Vespa certainty of his reporting
None of this has proven but Alex intense
Family doesn't show in such a way
Is to make his audience
But he's definitively proven all of these poi
It's something he does literally all the
It's how you take baseless
Is conjecture and presented as hard research
Artifact
It's how you act like a dumb
Conspiracy theorist
A pass yourself off as an extra
It's as easy as manufacturing evidence and misleading your audience
That's all he
Particularly distasteful
The documents have been released
Represent
Producers.
Okay well I put them in my safe because they're way too important so
I will just go get them
Jump up legs
So we
See that narrative transition
We see it start
Russian is vestia story
And Alex has now changed it
Dude that Timberland on record documents
Released using to CIA program in Georgia
In the same way
Alex takes the story of Timberland being a fan of Infowars
And change
Is that story as well
And we see that in
Next clip we're usually recording CNN Fox in a bunch of others when there's breaking news
Alex Jones listeners
Admission at Langley Virginia
So as soon as the suspect in the marathon bombings had been neutralized as an immediate threat
Actions of why did they do what they did
And interviews of the Johor it became clear that tamerlan had some religious
Just extremism to him
I'm so investigators wanted to discern where that it come from
Timberlands father Ruslan told CNN's of a man named Misha who is said to have been Timberlands
Brainwashed him into an extreme version of Isla
Christian Carol writer for the New York Review of Books
Extractme shutdown
And reported on their conversation
Mitch's real name was me kli lock
And he claimed that
You thought that though he knew tamerlan
If you've actually been his teacher as it was being alleged you would have stopped him
From carrying out the bombing
Absolutely did not support
Misha agreed to cooperate with the FBI and officials came out and announced that they could find no link to
I'm in the bombing
In the end mission was a bit of a red herring though the attention on him kind of makes sense
Thanksgiving-themed
Yeah media tone all the
The confusion surrounding
Timberlands father it indicated that Misha was responsible for radicalizing his
But he only knew him by this student
And that's
Redmi 4
Mysterious figure
Perfect for creating intrigue
So I don't know how they could have resisted
Reporting on this
The Talk
Alex is suggesting that Mischa is in Langley because that's shorthand
For the CIA
Pretend that Misha is a CIA operative which is why Misha would say that the Tsarnaev brothers were fans
Infowars
Where is Langley CIA or FBI
There's no evidence that Misha was CIA
A few days after this
Point where at you sound living in a
Apartment in West Warwick Rhode Island with his elderly pay
Alex's created The Narrative that tamerlan was working with the CIA thanks for the shoddy story from his vestia
So now anyone associated with him must also be
CIA
Is bad work
But the larger structural problem with this narrative is that music wasn't the one who said tamerlan was into Infowars
That information
Cut came from
Who was tamerlan sisters
Text husband
That bit of information about Timberlands media diet is
Completely separate from the thread about his possible
With Misha
But Alex wants to muddy the water
And the reason he wants to do that
Because at this
Point on the 24th the ex brother-in-law is a known quantity
He's someone that definitely exists
Tangible way but Misha does not
As of April 24th meet your only really existed someone who's been talked about
It hasn't been
Confound
So it's good makeup anything you want
This is a mini version of his larger content of
About the bombing
Alex thrives on manufacturing certainty
In places where reality reflects
Vagueness
Because Misha is an unknown quantity that being reported as a
Mysterious figure by the meat
It's analysis best interest to attach the idea that tamerlan was into Infowars to him
Because of the uncertainty
Surrounding Misha Alex decline with no evidence
But he's CIA
And that means what
Infowars it's probably coming from
The CIA
Because they were behind the bombings
Which is all meant to demonize the Patriots after all
So even so they have to do it
At a one step removed
Situation
Oz content Works backwards most of the time
There's a conclusion that he needs
Just arrived at anymore
Reality to support that
Conclusion
In the case of his entire coverage of the bombing
The conclusion
That must be reached
Is this was a false flag that was meant to be blamed on Patriots and gun owner
There's no evidence at this
The case no one seems to be blaming right-wingers at all but Alex need something to justify his narrative
And this'll do just fine
Instead of accepting the very likely reality that someone who is deeply interested in the protocols of
The Elders of Zion would also find his broadcast appealing
Play because they're almost identical in
Alex has to deflect
It cannot be possible that this guy was a fan
It must be the case
That the claim that he the fan is
From the global
Who see this as their best
Chance to blame the Patriots for
The bombing
In some way after all
I kind of understand why you do this
Considering that the alternative is publicly owning up
To the fact that you show appeals to terrorists
So
You got to do what you got to do usually admitting that
You are running a show that
The main demographic
People who wanted
Commit violence
Citizens
Usually that's not the way you go about
Yeah
Strange this is business good on his part like I mean
It's sloppy and terrible and the motivation
V b I can see why you would do this
Yeah and it's slippery
But I hesitate to call it smart
But it's wise
It's on what goal he's trying to reach
He's doing exactly what he needs to do in order to do that
Yeah
Smart is a
Got too much
Connotation
Value
So Alex is now decided that
She's probably behind
Was involved in
Drill
Sure
Baby missions behind everything
This is really getting hard to deal with this point
I can imagine you just made that up
Yeah you can't have a hard time dealing with something that you literally just made up to 2nd
I think what he's saying is hard to deal with is
He's got his narrative
And there's just
Too much information coming out that he has to incorporate
And it becomes exhausting well
Radicalizing
Figure that is father's achtung about
How does this fit into my conspiracy
Well okay you CIA
Maybe you did
Old is maybe he did
The bro it's almost like he's
Graphic designer and
Every time he sends it to the guys like you know what I really think that's close but maybe change this a little bit and over and over and
Turn over again Alex
Dealing with reality
Now they're asking me to put Misha in here how am I supposed to fit another character in I don't know
Babies
That's cool
That's kind of what I hear to almost a frustration
Supposed to f******
Work with
You did this to yourself
Could have just waited for information I really hate this novel that I'm being
Forced to write
Somebody
So Tremblay
Isn't the only government official that is saying things that Alex Jones
This is pretty into
Also we have some commentary by
The one and only
Beach ambulance
But Alex
Misrepresent
Boston bombing in advance Georgia Senator Saxby
Channel 2 Action News
Last night
Russian news
Boston bombers
But Alex is completely twisting the comments that sexbeat ramblas made about the alarm for 7 a.m.
We haven't advanced warning about the bombing
This is specifically about the warnings that the Russian government gave about tamerlan back in
11th and how that information
Didn't get cheer to all the places that it might have been helpful for it to get to
The way Alex reads this story throughout the show it's meant to imply that the law enforcement
Question
Add specific for knowledge
About the bombing it didn't do anything
Stop it just absolutely not with Champlin
What was Elijah
Nor is there any evidence
Conclusion that's been
Produced
Chambliss the senator from Georgia
NetSpend
Fun coincidence there that the senator from Georgia is talking about
Conspiracy theory of the guide
But I didn't put two-and-two together
That's fun
Coincidence and I'm no sex be shambliss Defender
Except for how fun is named has to say but in this case is point Isabel
There was a failure of information-sharing that it possibly could have contributed to Tamara Lynn
Falling off relevant radar
It's unclear how much of a contribution that had in terms of allowing the bombing
To happen but it's definitely a productive Avenue
For conversation
And after the bombing
It's just unfortunate that media Outlets decided to present this information with headlines like
Quote chambliss
Law enforcement agency might have had info about Boston bombing in advance
Why was a bad actor like Alex to create the
Kind of Optics
He needs which in no way reflects
So that's kind of what we're dealing with their
There is
I think it's just because there's so many
Yeah like you could be sex
He could be Saxby
Chambliss
Saxby chambliss
It's at
Saex
Bewhy
Zaxby
Chambliss
Or Zack
B.
During the
2008 election me and my buddy Swearingen where
We were hanging out
I don't know if we lived together at the time we did end up being room
I think it was
Before we love to go
Heather butts
We're watching the election results
Come in
And we had a bottle of Goldschlager
We're drinking every time estate went Democrat
Obama
And
Just because earlier in the night Saxby chambliss had won a race
We had no idea who he was but I was so great that every time we drank we cheers
Saxby chambliss
Oh my God what's his Vermont
It's always have a pretty positive
Weird
He's a pretty bad dude
Gap
So
Alex gets into this
Text Clippers
In this excellent. Gets into how they were going to blame the Patriot
And the right-wing gun owners
Auburn it didn't work out so now this
Make it Alex's fault
Is them trying to
Say Victory from the jaws of
They were CIA
Confirm now
But
Here's his first
So no one is saying that tamerlan liking Infowars made him do the bus
Embalming
Except for alley
Is the straw man that Alex is deploying to attack because he knows better than to engage at the actual reality
Where Alex to discuss this story as it's actually being reported he have to bring up
Tamerlan was into the protocols of the elders
Zion
And that would bring up some difficult question
Because the protocols are Sophie matically connected to his world
Discussing this issue in reality would force them to address the fact that
Globalist
Just yells about are real similar and characterization and in goals with the l
Elders of Zion
Which is a really tough line for Alex
Did he say that the protocols are real
That would take a show into a pretty overtly anti-semitic place and I'm not sure he thinks that's good
For business
Maybe he could save their real but it's not about the Jews
That seems like a little bit too hard for him to pull off in
It's embarrassing when other people have tried that in the past
I turned the thread that needle probably blow up in his
In space-plus he probably be accused of ripping off Bill Cooper
So what option would be like
Sing the protocols are fake
If that's the case then this
Historical forgery that the complete hoax meant to demonize the Jews
And it has
Staggering overlap with his rhetoric and worldview
What does that mean for the infowar
These are not questions that Alex's equipped
To deal with so instead of recognizing the tamerlan had an interest in the protocols and Infowars probably
He just pretends that everyone is saying that Infowars made tamerlan into a terror
Jump like that he's off the hook for the hard question
And he's created a completely false accusation that he can get indict
About people making
Plus it validates the narratives about the globalist finding a way to blame the Patriots with the bombing
Exactly what he needs to do but ultimately
And it's also
In a certain way
Flattering for
He's he's
Framing in such a way as
They think I have that power
To turn anyone into a
Of course I do
I could never do
You know that kind
That's pretty wild
So Alex
Sayonara
I wish this were
I wish I wish this was a real Attack
It wasn't the false flag
Affect your work
I don't want this to be an inside job
You so giddy
So giddy
It's
Tell me that's that that's the real
Face there
That's so excited to be linked
So Alex
Sarah has a story that one of his writers
This has put out
Trying to deflect
From the idea that
Tamerlan was a fan of
And this is just absurd
Boston bombers
Michael Jackson demo Thrones Finding Nemo
Facebook and social media
Spider-Man
So here Alex is one of his employees write an article desperately trying to create another straw man
Antop escape the connection between his working
This time ago this
How to say an interesting Infowars it the same thing as an interest in Spider-Man
Therefore if you're saying that it's a notable that tamerlan was in
Infowars
It's equally rella
He was into Spider-Man
Which I think is wrong because we all know that Finding Nemo is the movie that has the most anti-government
Sure
This is a joke
The issue was tamerlan taking an interest in Infowars that they did
It speaks to the worldview that tamerlan was called
According to that report in the associated
His family members said that he
You changed a bit
Years before the bombing
Becoming convinced of a broad range of
Conspiracy theory
He became a 9-11 truther it was dabbling in these ideas that Jews secretly Run the World
He began have a very
Anti us
Stamp
To the point where people around him
Took notice
Well it isn't necessarily fair to say that Infowars is responsible for radicalizing tamerlan it's
Equally unfair to pretend that it's not part of the equation
According to Tamlyn
Brother-in-law
Not Misha the way Alex.
The fascination with
Conspiracy theories particularly
Anti-government
Runs a very parallel track with getting into infowar
Believing the Jews run the world and becoming a
Didn't the protocols of Elders of Zion is absolutely
Hannibal
With the themes disseminated by Infowars
Even if Alex doesn't save the Jews are secretly behind every
The themes of the same
The anti-semitic tropes are used
Characterize the globalist
Extent that most people who are getting in
Semitism
Could be forgiven if they heard what Alex said as cold
This is why you never
Infowars is relevant and an interest in Spider-Man
Is not
And be clear I'm not saying that
Infowars or Alex
Radicalized tamerlan
I don't have anywhere near the amount of evidence I would need to make that kind of claim
I am saying that if Alex were sincere actor in the world he would respond to things like this different
He wouldn't get defensive and create multiple defense
It's narratives about Wyatt means nothing the tamerlan liked Infowars he probably didn't
Because that's just coming from Misha who's probably CIA
You would reflect on what he's doing and ask hard question
Particularly
What is it about what I do that makes it attractive
Do to people who subscribe to ideologies
Support
What unexamined parts in my worker
Compatible with toxic and important beliefs like those expressed by the
The protocols
And what can I
My dude better
To make sure my message that I'm sending isn't misunder
Understood as support those ideologies
Alex contra-flow
Because to reflect is to introduce
Possibility
He's wrong about
And he's wrong about something
That introduces
The possibilities wrong about ever
It's so important for him to
Because he's up there on the edges where he's most vulnerable
He has to protect his infallibility
Which drives them to do observe childish nonsense like this
Like making is writers
Put out articles behind interest in Spider-Man is equivalent
Do an interest in an extremist right-wing propaganda out
Bulshit
Very sad
Yeah
And it's not like the thing about that is that it is not the
It's not like
Infowars makes him
I hate the government
Or whatever it is
I'm extremely anti US government
The pathways that you take
Evidence of Infowars
Influence
Not
Not the initial starting point
It's Fitbit you know you go to Infowars because you're already
Inklings at Leeds
Do to find it
We'll put it is it doesn't lead anywhere
It's going to
To take whatever you have
Metastasize
It's not obviously
Percent
Effective
It doesn't it say it's not something
It happens to everyone
But if they're on that path Infowars will make
It'll convince them of things that aren't true
It'll create narratives in their head that are based on
Alex is paranoid delusional
A movie
Eduardo movies
And Fantasies delusions about those
Is being real
You know it is
Break it all it all makes total
And the way Alex is doing this makes total sense
That's too because
Dealing
Dealing with these things in a more realistic ways very very threatening
To the way he presents his show and his business
ISO
Obviously the most threatened
Nothing to him
Is people treating
Realistically
It's not a threat for them to attack him
In the ways that let's say
The virulently
Somatic people do when they say that he works for his real
That's not really tell me
Not at all people attacking him insane
Like hey you
Cause this bombing
That's not even really that
Threatening to really I caused the bombing I'm a radio show host
Spider-Man goes away
Don't understand
Of this American
Green him and the ideology
That do
Underlie people who
End up committing
This tax is very threat
Yeah
Pointing out that he operates under the same propaganda
Fix that
Isis for example uses
So we are one lion
I slept here
And you might remember that Alex said that Lindsey Williams
Interesting Lee
Oz interview with Lindsey Williams
Cut out of the episode as it appears on his rssb
Wait what
Yeah
I thought that was really bizarre
And I don't think I've ever run into that
In the past
Like I do
On the top of these episodes I've never heard an instance where Alex says aghast
Is coming up the guest never shows up
Eddie doesn't say like we had a scheduling issue or can't get ahold of him Lindsey just never shows up on the episode
So I went and found the full version
This episode and I listen to the Lindy Williams interview
It seems pretty par for the course for a Mac
It's also pretty embarrassing
Wendy Williams is just doing his normal stick of pretending to have this Elite inside or information
Somebody uses to issue dire warnings about the coming Financial collapse
All this prediction
Stupid and they're very clearly
His appearance is very clearly
Listen to me about trying to sell his DVD
I suspect however in this case Lindsey Williams
Alex's fine with Lindsey selling his DVDs as a byproduct of them coming on the show to give Alex quote-unquote inside information
Mason from this
Quote on quote
Imagine
But I'll
Can't accept
What's the inverse
You can't allow the appearance to be that Lindsay's
Primarily there to sell DVDs
He's doing that by
Pretending
The source
And I think Lindsay cross
Here's how that interview ends
I think it's I think it speaks
And why I got cut out of the episode they got released
Also I should say that what we listen
Do here is the third time
I'm in like 15 minutes
That Lindsay launched into a sales
Bottom line
They are
That's the state of plans of the globalist
To get our Pension funds in my account what you got on the waterfront
Premier associate you're saying number of months
How long
Lovingly
Taking over retirement accounts to safeguard them but also
Tax them all this is after tax money
I mean why not it's for the Earth Lindsey
Please go to Lindsey Williams.
Sey
Lindsey Williams
I have produced this week
Today
6111 American operators by the way 888
799 even about that
Out of time I appreciate it unless he's a great guy he really does have that Source I'm not paid about the stuff when he comes on
I'ma like Lindsey I like to stuff it starts you know
Making us have important information but
Adverb
You know Cancer Care and stuff like that I just not part of it
That's all I can say right there
Infomercial with
Youngevity stop cuz I really believe it and tested it until it is Clemson's done studies on it really as powerful
And my sponsors are great if you hear me and or something that's my sponsor but
Appreciate that Lindsey Williams Come on with us we're going to break now
That's f***** up
Cuz he says they're at the ends at like I infomercial for youngevity sometimes cuz I believe in that stuff which seems
To imply that he doesn't believe in Lindsay's.
No he does not
Of course that's what get
We've gone through so many of these old episodes where you're like
Why the f*** did you leave that in you could have just cut that out
But what gets
Cut out
A f****** sales pitch will the time with a guest of his made it way too overt
That he's there teasing
Fake inside information
In order to sell these DVDs
It makes it the grift way to up yeah man
So you don't want that to live on
In terms of
Really easily accessible
I lied or I misspoke there's one more clip and tell Alex
And the episode
He's teasing the knot Lindsey Williams
Kind of
I think he's mocking Lindsey Williams a little bit
As he teases the Nightly News
Boston prisonplanet.tv
Tennessee login
So when Alex says that you won't cure cancer
Printing back to just like a little bit earlier when you were saying about Lindsey I'm not into the cancer can
I don't think that's
Specifically about Lindsey Williams selling a cancer cure it just more metaphorical
That he's offering this miracle thing that isn't real
So I think
I don't know this to be sure
Wait bug Lindsey Williams cell
I don't think so about the globalist
Then how are you knows this Elite
Mystery source
Hotels in bad infer
Information
I don't know this.
Be sure but I
Tried to Google like Lindsey Williams appearances
Does on Alex's show and I think this is the last time he's
I'm not positive about that but all the other ones were from like 2009 2000
Domino's this might be the end of their relationship
Reply to close to the Sun in like Icarus
Your DVDs melt yeah you have to at least
Answer his
OceanFirst you can launch into the sales
If he asked you a direct question and
And instead you launched
Do the sales pitch
You get cut out of the oven
And Alex absolutely was not out of time out of time to Overdrive
Call mad all the time in the world
After Lynn
Interview
Who is realize that cuz I got to the end of the episode
That's not good out there plenty of
Wow
So we get to the end of this episode I think
This is really
Very fascinating
Because you have the
The first
Thing is you know you got the
Timberland
That's
Fascinating
Seahawks response
That is really in
But then I don't know where you got this is vestia store
Russian news story
That's how you see how Alex
Changes at
You see how he manipulates
The details
Is so vague about the sources people can't like his listeners can't verify anything that he saying
Turns it into
Proof
Document
Release everything is proven that
Timberland was recruited by the CIA in Georgia
Boom
Then
He brings back
The
Tamerlan was a fan of Infowars narrative
Connected to this music character
And integrate that
With
That is vest
Story
In order to make it so everything is the CIA
Everything
They're the ones were saying that tamerlan was a fan of Infowars
In order to
Satisfy Alex's
Prophecy
They were going to find a way to blame the page
It's really
It's really interesting
It all works
If you believe him
Yeah yeah yeah
It's it's kind of amazing cuz what we're watching is him rewrite
Reality in real time
You know like and that's probably why you so tired as normally he gets to have other people write articles for him
And then he can do it but this is almost all
It feels
Like him about the story when he started
Sara Lee it did Italy's doesn't seem like it until
Two-thirds of the way through the episode
Yeah but that's the same thing he's been doing with his whole body
For quite a while
I think
I think that element of it made this episode little bit more into
Interesting than some of the
Last couple days
Cuz those have been so
Like standard out
Alex yeah where's this is a little bit more
It feels a little more improvisational
You can see the instinct
A little more than just the like
Alright boring dumb propaganda
Dumb conspiracy
MN.
So I mean
It was it was
Really
Illuminating to see that Misha thing
Happened so quickly like it went from
I just found out about Misha to maybe Misha was this guy over here and then these this
Everything and he's CIA and then all of a sudden that all crystallized into truth
Yeah and it was concrete and he knew the whole beef of the soda I don't have a strong suspicion I don't know this.
Suspicion that that is not going
Tubi
Behind the drills
In Rhode Island
And Alexander
Sure it'll be it'll be
Something stupid but it won't be that
So I don't know I'm interested
See where this goes
There's still a
Even if there is
Feeling that I have that I kind of feel like Alex is already on the crisis actors
Yeah yeah that clip I think is real
Illuminating on that front
I still think that there's more that a greater fault
But he has to make
I'm still in
And then there's one
Big p
Of the Boston
Bombing
Narratives that
Is still not in play
And I do not know how he hasn't gotten
And so I'm going to
Continuing down this road in 2013
Did I do I don't know why
If it seemed to me that he hasn't brought up yet
I'm just going to keep that there is a
I will see when Alex finally does bring it up.
But I will get to that and then episode Down
Go to website
That is correct we also on Twitter
He's looking to Be Like That download the show please go to iTunes downloaded labor review etcetera
Other stuff patreon
Will be back
On Wednesday but until then I'm a Neo I'm Leo and easy acts Clark
I am Saxby chambliss