Important
I have great respect for knowledge but I'm sick of them posing as if through the good guy
I need money
Stripe.com
Hey buddy would have acknowledged vitamin A little bit about Alex
Dan Jordan in honor of
Turkey day
Advice guides
Don how would you handle your family
Have you ever had a huge
Argument at the Thanksgiving
Dinner table
Yeah probably I'm probably yeah I don't have
Nothing that sticks out as a
Individual 10 nothing notable
Mainly you agree right on Lotto Texas
I particularly might at least my parents and my brother and I are all pretty
Left-leaning
There's not too much
Concerned about that I guess my dad's parents like my daddy was a Mennonite preacher and
I got a real sense
Even though we never really talked
Fox politics
We got to get a sense that he's a bit to the right
I have no idea though really like a lot of that stuff never leak
Came up
I'm pretty open and
Progressive growing up but again I don't know I've never really had those Converse
That's fascinating
That's it I think I feel like that's a fairly unique
Experience right maybe there's a little bit of a disconnect between a lot of the extended family
Number of years growing up we lived in Hawaii
Almost the entire family lives
In California like seeing each other at all
Cross oceans we lived in Missouri
And they all still live in California
And no one's going to come to Missouri
California
Play dr. Under appreciated state
Rent-A-Car the extended family during the summer
And so there was a summer break and we would take a road trip
Across the country
Go visit family generally
These are these
Family
Thanksgiving
And Christmas is weren't necessarily
Super, there'll be more like phone calls on Christmas or Thanksgiving stuff
Specific
Terms of like
Family Guy
Visit in person
This conversation
Never
Coming up a lot of it like was more religious
Yeah my dad's side of the family
And I was my mom's side
I like that I like
I assume you have a lot of more experience
I am beset on all sides
You're surrounded
Yeah good luck with that
2 hours I will have a turkey sandwich on Thursday
I don't know too much about Thanksgiving fights over politics
But I do know a lot about Alex Jones hell of a lot about one and not much
Is beer in the present-day we're going to be taking a look at November 20th
To use
Tuesday
Monday
My day is next
Anti-Venom
Episode there's a lot that I found very disturbing
On this show there's nothing
About
Thanksgiving or news
There's a slight mention
Thanksgiving
There's nothing really about news
Alex is singularly obsessed with
One thing
And it gets very very out of control
Okay thank you
Does the folks who've signed up and are supporting show
So first of all Mike
Thank you so much you're now policy walk
JB thank you so much you're now if I was wrong
Jermaine Dupri I thought it was the Ghost of the
Brilliant produce
Oh okay
Yacht Rock
None of those people are probably
Thank you
Journal policy wonk
Lisa thank you so much right now
Apology want next Aaron thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
And then finally like to say thank you to people who signed up on an elevated level appreciate that very much
So first Travis that you so much you are now a technocrat
And Sarah thank you so much you are not
Technocrat
We got to go
Money off that heroin
Why you pimp so good
Is freakishly large
Thank you so much Travis and Sarah
Sure we would appreciate
I am done before we get down to
Do business business just a little programming no we are not going to have an episode on Friday
Take the end of this week off due to you having a holiday
It's tough when you know you got to go do you do these at the family Thanksgiving and that's on a Thursday weekend
Surly record on Thursday so
I'll be back on Monday so don't get too alarmed
There's not
Episode
On Friday if you're listening to this right now posit
Whenever your family starts talking on
Stop those earbuds in and you
Can hear us scream about not
Jerk so we start here on the 25th and Alex
It does have a tiny things
To say about Thanksgiving but this is the only
Well as we can predict there is a full-on assault on Thanksgiving and any other
He does not hold no I don't even want to imagine what his
Quote Real History of Thanksgiving
Yeah I'm sure be a little bit stilted I was I was like well here we go
Who is researching the pilgrim
None of that is relevant at all
It's a Alex
Is completely obsessed with something
Office episode
They didn't get to it immediately because there is a
She probably does believe that
There is a story out of the UK that Alex believes is evidence
That the demon called
Pedophile globalist
Starting to lose
Control
And because they're losing control they have to
Crackdown on language
All right answer this story out of the UK as evidence
That's why they're now
Salute
Complete warm
Rebels never-before-seen
On language
That's why National Television the censor board in the UK
Onward
Somebody
It was once used in connotation to black people
So that's the
The level of the control and I would
The ATL to call for anyone
Because it's about
Hysterical
Total
Complete
No control
Power graph
Alright
Okay so
Can I
Proposed
That we only talked about Thanksgiving
That he never speaks of this again
Right he doesn't speak of Thanksgiving again nobody speaks
The additional narrative
The Great Wave
Busov races
Pacifica
So this situation here that he's talking about is about a guy named
Eamonn Holmes
Who is appearing on the show at in the UK called this morning
Anti he described Meghan markle's attitude when she didn't want people take
Tons of pictures of her at Wimbledon as uppity
That naturally does have connotation
Since the term has been historically used to describe non-white people
Particularly black people in America who know their place in society
Ender to act like equals
The only way that that work and not necessarily there are other connotations of it but it is largely take
Make a nonfat connotation
It's very possible that Holmes himself was unaware of that historical use of the term particularly when it's being used
Describing on white person behaving in ways that you have a problem with
But the message is the same regardless
Whether or not he intended it to be
Airbnb reported that Holmes
Has been reprimanded
Which the network ID
Denied
And then you know it started be
Reported is the word uppity it been banned
And from ITV
Immediately the right-wing media went
Active mode
Because this was a fringe case or potential racism needed their help
They can't resist that brand of free speech issue
Seems like that's the only kind there really seems to matter all that much today
Wow I mean you good at you could almost use a certain word to describe the way that they are
You like that is the world of free speech
That they are
Only uniquely interested in
One thing that places like zerohedge made a very serious point in stress
Sing is that only one person complained
And it led to the Banning of a word
Best PC culture run amok Jordan
I noticed the same overemphasis V1 complaint
Issue in the coverage of the story nrt
But in other articles about this that wasn't
The focus
Like in the express the metro in the Sun
All the stories seemed to imply that there was only one complaint to the broadcast regulatory organization ofcom
But that detail isn't used to minimize
Is the complaint where it is
These other
Sphere it's used to drive it even further as as like it should have to be 1,000 people who
Complain before they
Get bothered by
Is that what they're doing
I guess I don't know they're just trying to say like all
This is one person was butthurt about this and that
Don't send
It's entirely possible that there were other complaints to
To the network but this one to ofcom is the one that prompted a reaction
Also it's possible that only one person followed through with the filing of a formal come
Even if that's the case that doesn't have anything to do with whether or not the single complaint is valid
In this instance if there's one person complaining that one person is absolutely correct
The term uppity does have racist connotations specifically in the way that Holmes was he using
As far as I can tell Holmes doesn't seem to have a history of racially inflammatory commentary so it's entirely possible that
You didn't mean there's an
In the way that it came off sounding
And that's probably why he didn't get in trouble for
The comment
The context was just explain to her
I am so that he could choose
Better words in the future
And the word wasn't banned for
A representative for the network was very clear
You're telling me
Quote it is incorrect to state that this is an it
TV ban on the word uppity
There's no such ban on the word up
Per se rather care will be taken regarding
Text of its use
Business situation where things played out
Pretty much exactly how they showed up
A guy on TV said something that he didn't realize was kind of racist someone pointed out that what he said was kind of races and their spawn
Good point let's try to be more careful about how we say
Things in the future
Right-wing in the United
Apparently can't stand that
To the point where they have to manufacture narratives about banned words
Adam schitt
Pouches versus even crazier he's saying that the word is being outlawed
Is it just say you're going to go to jail for saying absolutely
Apathetic
This desperation
To clean to and defend these remnants of a racist
Past well pretending it's all just about free speech
Crazy
Like the details of the
Story are real
To go like
The thing is it's just
Any
Anyting any small thing that they can find
They will attack on that just
Like my theory on that is
Is that if they
On those like
Edge
Edge race
Situation
Then you then we're all over here looking at these Edge bullshits going like
No you can't
It's something you can't say the word it said
Always been used in the
We're just very careful about the car
Context of this word
I end a turn that into f******
And then we still can
Can't get back to life
The mortality rate for black people is 10 million times more of like
That's the only battle vake
Like they can't really fight some of the other related cases
You know that's
He's in cages now hold on this is a First Amendment issue
So that's
This episode
Into a sort of like
Can I see where Alex
And it got where it gets so much worse.
We now get to what Alex takes most of this episode responding
And
It's
I don't know how to tell you this but
Is Borat
Eyewitness to space getting at the national
I sausage
Baron Cohen
I know that every bit of it was written by
Sure
The very Sinister forces by in the 80s
He called for the arrest
The big Tech
Specs
Starting with Mark Zuckerberg
Whoa
Can you do
Punished accordingly
Target
The silencing of Alex Jones
Has not been enough
He says that it was just the beginning
All Americans must be silenced
This isn't some old black-and-white film footage
Hitler saying things like that
Is me
This is
This is a unified front of authoritarian Danger
So I heard that clip and I was like this is I hope he's just talking about this for a minute
This goes very far off the rails
That's not good so Jordan
I don't know if you saw the video but last week Sacha Baron Cohen gave a speech at the adl's never is now
O'Mara's kind of a very big deal
Nexus 4 years
Cohen's been a performer that very seldom appears as himself
He prefers to exist in public almost entirely as one of his
Character
Dropping that facade in speaker
Bluntly Big Sur
A bit of a powerful statement on its own
But even beyond that it was pretty good speech
I found it
Pretty well.
A large part of Cohen's message about linking his own work to the growth of affect
That social media has had on society
Facebook and Twitter are profoundly
Powerful propaganda tools which are able to lead people to believe in
Completely insane thing
Which has led to a mainstreaming of previously Fringe conspiracy theories
He discusses how has his Israeli Commando character
Is part of the show who is America
He told the guy that
Attendees of the women's March were putting out chemicals to
Turn people Tran
And instructed him to plant explosives on
The man did it
And actually push the detonation button which would have killed
Tons of people if they weren't
Fake explosives
Cohen I believe rightly
Canex this person
Willingness to believe the dumb conspiracy that his character presented to him
With his prior interaction with online misinformation
It's a good speech
And honestly Cohen makes a lot of points that are completely compatible with the goals Alex pretends to hold
He's arguing for big Tech
Tech companies to be
Responsible for what goes on on there
Platform which Alex
Mr.wok they both don't want these
These companies to be allowed to hide behind the excuse that they're just a space where anyone can post whatever they want while their operation
The primary difference seems to be that Alex wants more unhinged racist
Conspiracy theories.
Be posted in Cullen twat
Less
The prevalence of complete bulshit being passed around
Is truth online as an effective normalizing disorder
Content Alex puts
Aspect of his business
Without the erosion of objective
Reality
You weigh less able to trick people into believing that his subjective delusional Fanta
Are real
I mean his subjective delusional fantasy is on display perfectly right there right there
Any sense or is true it doesn't reflect Cohen speech at all like he didn't call for
Zuckerberg
Execution
And Alex himself is barely even a footnote
Going didn't say that everyone needs to be silenced he was specifically talking about tech companies removing content like home
Because it's Sasha Baron Cohen puts it quote
That is not some random opinion
Those who deny the Holocaust aim to encourage another one
Again I can't help but notice that it
It seems like every free-speech issue Alex
Decides to get on a soapbox about his nothing or it has to do with someone who says hey there's a lot of races black wraps
I don't think that's a coincidence
I don't understand
I know it's nothing new but it feels particularly over
It seems like a lot of these
These free speech
Protestations that he has are too
Specifically director
Towards people who are pointing out a problem
Of
Racist harassment
Issues surrounding
Racist
Justin
You just representing
The
The idea
What what Sacha Baron Cohen
I don't know. Like
Prank guy I couldn't say I almost a performance artist
Tustin
In many ways
Immersive satire
He probably said that I don't know
I've heard him described
That way that's
The way it looks
To me like his character is often the satyr satirized version of something
And then people
Responses to it are the
Then inform the
Yeah they are
He talks about that a little bit
About
How
Derrick Eric like in Borat there
There are scenes that are
Defensive but he's doing something
Pensive
But what comes out of it is the illustration that people are willing to go along
Is a shocking
Thing to see
Of course not
The effect of the art
The guy doing the racist stuff which is the Borat character
Eastside Tire of that
Yeah
But it's far more powerful coming from him
Because of its
Infrequent
You know because he's spending so much time in this character
Alex has to
Personally just because he popped out
You know he's so used to say hello like Borat is
Why are people complaining about Borat he did
Then I'll like all of this stuff
And now Sacha Baron Cohen because of
Is lack of character
It taken attention I think that's some of it
But I also think that
Alex understands that
The themes that
Cohen was talking about
Are things that are dangerous to
To his ability to operate
He does mention Alex
In passing
In the speech I didn't know that
He does mention like Alex
Then I throw out all the stuff I said it purely because you mentioned Alex to Alex
He's going to talk about it
I think that's a big part of it but also theme attic
What he's talking about
Is relevant to Alex's ability
So that is also peace
But
Largely speaking
Most of what he was talking about was things
Like Holocaust denial right being
Acceptable on places like Facebook Twitter
Like why
Your
Yeah you make a choice
Right you cannot allow it
So anyway
I thought like maybe
Alex is just going to
Talk about that a little bit
He gets back to it
But there's another Ellen
This episode that I
I saw this at
And I'm like
And there's a storm brewing
I shot a very important sentiment report
Reposted the front page
Infowars.com
Few minutes I hope
You'll share the album tearing at the bottom of the hour
Voorhees
A major Google whistleblower
Megashare
So I'd like I said I just feel like a really over
Really problematic Storm is Coming
He begins talking about this completes bulshit story out of the UK about the word uppity be
Being band primarily to I guess argue that it's cool to call non-white people uppity
Weird
Then he gets a bit of a tizzy about Sacha Baron Cohen
Jdl speed
Most of which he should agree with
It seems to think a terrible because going to Maine
Point has to do with the need to remove things I call it cost to Niles from mainstream conversation
And now Alex says
This Google whistleblowers act Voorhees coming back on the show
That just fits too
Because if you were call
Zack's big cache of documents
It's that he released the project Veritas were all based
Meaningless
But in the Fallout of him going public it was revealed that Zach a track record of posting anti-Semitic
Conspiracy theories on social media
On multiple occasions you posted about how America had his dog
Zionist occupation government
Inside quote
Is very simple either you go along with the Zionist or you end up like Andrew Breitbart
Which is of course
To save there's also a
Zom or sinus occupied media
And I assume
He's saying the Breitbart was
Was murdered by
The Daily Beast reviewed his Twitter account and found
Zach believed that the prevailing concept of
Free Speech really meant quote
Free speech for Jews
Not free speech for Goya
He claimed the Jews were using vaccines to attacking on Jews of the world
When Alex wants to do the big free speech
Pageants in mysteriously only ends up bring up cases where racist
Stuff is the subject of possible curtailing
Any lies about the circumstances of
Sub-story and that has the guy on his show
To discuss the issue believe there's Azog
In the free speech is quote free speech for Jews not free speech for goyim you really have to ask yourself what's really going on here
This isn't the defense of free speech
It's protect
Racism and dabbling a little bit and daddy semitism
I think that's all this is
Yeah is Alex like
Is he going to tell for the for the
The real Holocaust denial Waters
No no
Show gets a little closer to that than I'd like
I am not saying
Hellboy
Thank you
Start stalking a little bit about
Baron Cohen
About soccer
Explain that on the other end
This club
This is this is so
Vintage Alex
Felicia met2
Batl University combine
I've left it there
Protection feel like myself and others Georgetown University is
Organized and funding
The fake Charlottesville case in many others
In the first two men
I'm going to take your speech
Everything until
We start refusing to bow
Refusing to be slaves to the system
Enrage the enemy staying on there this long
It's about the products wow
Wow
He's saying that Sacha Baron Cohen was saying you need to arrest all the Tek heads
Execute Zuckerberg
That's not what he said
He's actually Alex will play the clip a little bit later
Are you saying that like
Facebook ads
I've been involved in
Facilitating
Bi-Rite hanger genocide in Myanmar
We have seen these effect
If this happens again you have to go to jail
That's a knife
I believe I'll make this comment again later that is an overly generous position
I was 18 with Alexander I expected you to say
He didn't call Vdara
But you don't get to be a billionaire without committing some crime
I believe as I as I put it in my notes for later it's like
This is
Kind of
Too soft
Because the way that
Besides Baron Cohen
Is is a framing
He puts the deaths of these ranga people into a
You know fully once kind of situation
Take all of it seriously looks like
It's trouble but you see there at the end Alex gets
Into the
It's a very clear like
My cat just very normal
They're they're taking her your ability to say that the Holocaust didn't happen away from you and the only
Only way we can get your abilities they the Holocaust happened back
Cuz if you buy these products
Yeah so in this next clip
You're a little bit more in Alex's sales pitch
Play even more of it is because I think there's an indication
Some real trouble
Supergiant
Remodeling
First Watch
So the new special is basically the same as so many of these other we're selling off the store sales that we've seen in the past but now there's
An added bonus
For the first time ever you get Triple Patriot Point
Which I honestly can't imagine means anything
Anyone who's on the fence
About buying products cuz I don't think anyone's on the fence
Proud man is a triple. Once I let you know the devil didn't do it for me but you triple it now we're now
We're dealing with gold
By this point you're either in or you're not
And the temptation of building up even more points
The system that you're not even engaged with
Probably doesn't move the needle
Different kinds of sales are targeted at different demographic
For instance
A giveaway just a free giveaway that's intended to
Specifically increase your customer base
You have faith something that you're selling but you need Market awareness
So you give it away for a brief. Of time to get the word out
This is a strategy often employed by a lot of booze
Is there at the shop people go around like oh my God this is great
Everyone loves booze
Strategy
Get you to enjoy their thing
And then maybe you'll become accustomed
That's one
Tactic the people can use
Offering triple Patriot Point
Is the exact
Text opposite
That's a special that cannot appeal to new customers
Since the incentive to buy is accruing points in a loyalty
Campaign the patriarch part of
This is a strategy that you only employ if the people you're trying to
Increase sales for are the people who are already
Customers
Which absolutely tracks
The state that Alex's business
The focus of his advertising shoot
Geared towards
To maximize the amount
You can get from existing cost
Because he's probably not getting a ton of new customer
That's putting money
Towards expanding the customer base
It's probably fishing in a dry well
Not not going to have
At a certain point though that's strategy
Become very day
Eddie's Baseline two-way Patriot points work
Is if you spend a dollar at the Infowars store you get 5 paper
If you build a point
You can exchange 500 of them for $5 in
In-store discount
Basically you get a point for every $0.20
To spend at the store
And then you can redeem them for $0.01
Discounts
That's been our tracks
Under normal
Accepting losing 5% to incentivizing
But this can get really hairy when you start adding multipliers
Thanks
Because the triple Patriot points
If you if you do that with triple paper tube lights
Customers are now getting 15 papery points for every dollar they spend
Or one point for every $0.06
If the exchange rate still holds over 500 points
Equals $5 in store credit
You now have to spend six
Scents to make one cell
We're supposed to before was 20
To make one cent
What's that in crooner
You can see how these two
Prospects are pretty different
In terms of how much of a loss
You're willing to accept in order to increase repeat sales
This s*** will really cut into margin
At a certain level
It's just not a good idea
From a business perspective
Mostly because
If someone is going to be inclined to purchase
Product because of
Triple Patriot Point
They're probably going to be Justice Way by BB
This feels like a really desperate attempt to sell things off
To the base that he has left
Profit margin be
Be damned
Honestly he could offer 10 times Bakery points and it probably wouldn't matter
If he knows that
He's probably going out of business
Write rewards program
Specifically have no monetary value so if you go under and all your fans are left with thousands of unused Patriot Point
You don't have to pay them back for their imaginary value
This might be a good plan for him moving forward
Police the last people
Rabbit create
These absurd sales I just hope people know
Hope they don't
Cash in before you
Yeah this does seem like a
If they
Grab as much revenue as possible as soon as they can
And then they
Final that out into I guess
Legal defense
And then whenever they declare bankruptcy
They don't have to give up any
And they don't have to pay back all the pictures
This strategy
That one would be using
That looks like this
It does
Just feel like
Trying to patch up a hole in it
Yeah it it feels like uni
Squeeze the base
Immediately
I just don't I don't know
It's definitely tracks with a lot of the other indications
That we weave
It's not a long-term business
So
Alex Goes To Break
There
Try giving the triple Patriot Point
And he comes back
And he's playing that 7-minute
ATL Sacha Baron Cohen
Report that he had mentioned that he
Is he using the weird Chinese accent. He's not doing something all the track on Dragon
I'll just say this right
My title of this clip is
Not good stuff
Influential Jewish organization in
Yeah, that issued a public statement at their main
Conference calling for the arrest of the big six
Fully turn control of their
Carbone's moderation and content
This is literal terrorism
Find
I'm not enough
Maybe it's time to tell Mom Zuckerberg and the CEOs of these companies
You already allowed one foreign power to interfere in our elections
Facilitated genocide Indiana Mall
Go to jail the ATL then
Further and calls for a purge of everyone who does not
Agreed with them
Insist on fire
These lies and conspiracies from that platform not even hit
Conion
Holyshit
Eloise
No no no that's not bad
That's that was the point in the episode where I was like well
Where job where you are in deep
F****** trouble so he keeps
DL put out this announcement
There's a speech that Sacha Baron Cohen
The ATL
ATL didn't come out and make a statement
Keynote speaker at getting an award
Alex could argue all the walks at the ATL
Italy agrees with the Cullens comments but it's a gross mischaracterization to say it's a public statement put out by the ATL
He knows what he's doing and it's called lying
Also the like I talked about with the my Anmar right angle
Situation I think
I think that he's being a little bit too generous
But at the same time I understand why someone wouldn't make this feature
To be like you should be in prison right now
Just a little inflammatory I get why you would phrase it this way but I disagree
It'll be stronger
What the f*** is that what he's talking about this Hitler s***
He said quote not even Hitler gave speeches this evil in this draconian
He just took over and carried out the evil
Is that somehow better yeah absolutely
What the f*** is this point
Give a speech
That's rude it sounds like this is just an attempt to save the ATL is worse than
I'm pretty sure that's what he said yes
Also for someone who claims to be as much of a history buff is Alex does what with the 25,000 books on World War
Bread visit some of Hitler speeches
This evil as I was going back through my mind like
Whew man he sent them
I would hate for Alex accidentally say that those beaches weren't evil into Coney because he just forgotten
You know how evil and Draconian they
I could come up with plenty of examples of very evil and very Draconian things that Hitler said and speeches
Things that are far more evil than Sacha Baron Cohen suggesting the tech company should platform Holocaust
Denial carryout genocides
Right it's really hard
To say that the guy who is saying no more genocides is worse than the guy who said
Yes to Jenna's well the underlying thing here is that Alex wants to argue that
The abl is
Complicit and actively working towards a white genocide but he knows it'll be way too overt
Yatso
He wants to use all the rhetoric that's around that
Without actually saying that
Conservative
To really really want to see you all the time and
Those two things are not related
So this is kind of double prong situation
I'm 1/2 oz trying to demonize the ATL because he
He's a gigantic bigot in the ATL is kind of a threat to bigots
Cuz they take them
I'm seriously
But on the other hand in the process Alex's whitewashing Adolf Hitler
By implying that you wasn't as bad
Oz very very f*****-up
And the most generous reading that is that he has so little idea what he's talking about that he's willing to hand wave Hitler speech
Beaches in order to attack the abl
The least generous reading is it he actually does know what he's talking about
Any thinks Hitler speeches warranty
Well I would say that
If you're reading
25,000 books on WWII
Let's go
I'm going to go with
Between 40 and 60%
Of those are Holocaust
In in some form
Saudia the Special Report
Multinational corporations
Working with groups like the ATL have decided to Brand any
Resistance to their takeover
This is so incredibly dangerous and it's going to blow up in the face
Of those that are trying
The ATL spokesperson
Jew down the well so my country can be free
So I think that Alex is starting to realize that more people are taking
Seriously How Deeply rooted and anti-semitism
His worldview is
And then he needs to come up with a good defense
I didn't predict it would involve him saying that Hitler speeches worth
Medieval but Alex's
Consistently unpredictable pretty sure His Brilliant strategy for
Claims that his worldview is deep
Atlanta Semitic
Is I know you are but what am I
We were far from the only people who were previously pointing out that Alex
The conception of his villains
People have really from old-time antique
East Metro
But lately it seems to be more of a public
Text thing
Princeton
Last week we saw Fiona Hill testify in the impeachment inquiry during which points
I asked pointed out that the
Conspiracy surrounding George Soros
Are are little more than a modern-day update
To the protocols of the Elders of Zion which 100% means
Did she listen to Arch that was a forged document specifically designed to spread antipathy
Detour to
Alex has nothing to worry about from the sort of talk in terms of his body
They don't care or probably even support at least some of them support that element of Alex's
Broadcast work
But the more and more the rest of the world understands how much Alex's show does fitting
Into the box of this sort of propaganda the more likely it is that he'll be seen for what he is
Instead of some
Patriot truth
And so it makes sense that I don't realize it
He's probably going to be accused of being an anti-semite a bit in the future
So it's probably best to come up with the preemptive defense around that
They're just calling everyone loves America anti-semitic now
In Cohen's
Speech at the ATL event
He discusses that sketchy did Borat getting a group of people at a bar to sing along with the song Throw the Jew down the
The reason I've seen in Borat is so resonate is because it demonstrates how there are places in the country where anti-Semitism is so casually
Acceptable
But no one thinks this
Speak up when a complete stranger starts
Sing about how the Jews
Are the problem in their country
And how they take all your money
That scene is an actual example of satire
Sacha Baron Cohen did something very risky
Going onstage at a country
Free music night
Insignia explicitly anti-semitic song cuz he how people would react
And it turns out they reacted by clapping along and
This is like Roadhouse but better Alex can pretend all he wants at this clip he has is like a
The gotcha moment there proves that Cohen is the real anti-semite
That's our behaviors so intentionally obtuse you really have to question
To the motives behind
I'm I'm I just got to tell you nobody understand
And satire
White as
Well as
You know cuz that that
Satire requires bike
2nd level order of think
That Alex
Specialized
That's his game
And he is all about
So in this special report
Weaves
Seeing already
Alex saying that this
Speech that Sacha Baron Cohen is more evil and
Draconian
Then
Hitler's Ray-Ray
Which is nuts
I don't want
Even if you're
How is it that he
Play that clip of like
We saw what happened
With the rohingya in
Myanmar
If you precipitate another genocide you're going to jail
Even play
More
Of that clip
That's very straightforward
Don't know
This the Special Report is
It really blows my mind
Because it's deeply anti-Semitic
Oh yeah
Are We Done Yet
So the ATL going to protect us from all these Nazis and then we learn their Alex Jones Donald Trump
Stephen Miller George Soros it was an actual Nazi collaborator
This is dangerous
Then just about money
Dollars a year
Run their moderation and the training of their sensors
There's a lot of stuff going on there
So of course Alex Berry bullseye
More rank
Holocaust revisionism in the form of lying about George soros's actions during WWII
This is no surprise but I was pretty shocked when I was followed that up by saying that the ADL is out for power
But they're also out for money
Did I realize the characterization of Jews having no morality pass
Cast of lust for money is a deeply auntie
Pizza medic 40
From history
It's almost like he's going out of his way to appeal to
Tons of anti-Semitic shittin is weird attempt to defend himself or claims that he's anti-Semitic
Weird it's wild
Need leaning into being an anti-semite while claiming that
That's
This is doublespeak that I just can't hang with
It's about
He literally
What are the weirdest special reports that I've listened to on
Michelle it's
It's so Incubus
Lick everything
Together man are getting paid a lot of money they're doing this for all of them
Play and they control moderation
Sandwich in other ways
Basically says
The Jews control the media you can see there so maybe I am
Jesus isn't paid Millions by big Tech
Back to drain their scent
As far as I can
I was referring to a 2017 story he read and Breitbart about the ATL teaming up with Facebook Twitter Google and Microsoft
The creepy cyber hate problem-solving lab
A place where issues across platforms that have to do with hate oriented
Did Rasmus could be discussed
I can see how this would be construed by Alex's the ATL being paid Millions
The train sensors
But there's no evidence I can find that that's what
What's going on
Butea wasn't even the only advocacy
The group is involved in that project
Legitimately this special report is that Alex plays his mother was f***** up things he's done in awhile
It's completely misrepresenting Cohen
On every light
Is a misrepresentation of the contest
It's a misrepresentation that it's a public statement from the ADL
It even beyond that Alex's rebuttals to
To the strawman argument
Embarrassed
It's very f*****-up
Yeah it does seem like this is the beginning
Maybe he pivots one more time but boys
This is this
KKK level kind of s*** right here
It's it's weird and honestly
Anything where he says
They say that
We are Nazis
He's like me and Donald Trump and Stephen Miller and it's like yeah you all say the same Nazi
Play s*** like
This isn't worse than Hitler has said very publicly don't compare things
To the Holocaust I don't they've made many public statements about not comparing people to not to use
And
The concentration
Camps at the border to concentrate
Cap City
Like they may have been the people who aren't
Doing that
They are the people most
To call you at
Which is why this is so
So Alex comes back after the
Special Report
And
Easy seeing a trailer for
You show
Amazon show features white people wearing red Maga hats
Hunted as Nazis
Al Pacino
There's numerous similarities to the Hein
Flirting
The name of it
Is it called The Hunt
Nope
And that's just so sick
We're calling for violence
They're the quote anti-fascist funded by the most famous living fascist
To work directly for Hitler
Makeup the magnitude of that
So that mean
You can't you just
Yes you care
You making up with it throws work for Hitler not directly for Hitler like uses
This is straight-up defamation you can sue him he's making up the Soros fund
That's based on those fake contract yet
And he's the most famous fascist in the world
George Soros
The most famous passage in the world
Sorrel
George Soros
Nazi Jinping
No none of those
Definitely not
Hitler
It wasn't that evil or draconian
So I'm not sure how Alex get this is you talking about the
The show Hunters
Latest news
The hunters
So I'm not sure how you can see that trailer
I'm come to the conclusion that it's about Jews hunt
Coming down Christian
Or that it has anything to do with Trump or Maga
Answer that last part the show takes place in the 7th
Maga hats
Trump being president
F****** an anachronistic
Do the larger issue though
Which is that Alex sees this show.
Besides about Jews
Hunting down Christian
That's not the
Plot
It's about a ragtag group of Nazi Hunters who are not so much hunting down Christians
They are hunting down Nazi play I really feel like Alex
Connects those two
You know like that
Christian
And the Nazi party really identifies both of those
Play in a little bit
So
The show just released its first trailer and I have a few thoughts about
The first is that Al Pacino looks a whole lot like Marc Maron
The show
Honestly that's probably My Bae
Okay good
It's just another this this right here is just another in a long string of hits
Azar Alex
Seems to be running damaged
Control4 imaginary races
We saw him do this with that other TV show while back about the
Time traveler going back to
Stop a white
The bombing range Alex claimed was about a time traveler trying to stop Patriots from fighting Global exact
It's pretty much the same thing
He's talking about Michelle where a rabbi puts together a team of Nazi hunters and
He's claiming it's about Jews killing Christian
It's really f***** up
To see how consistent his identification with the bad guys
Like this is not real I don't know for what reason or another
For some reason he really didn't like the ending of Inglourious
These people are not real that he's pretending
It's it's bizarre
It's bizarre that the way he
Craft Bistro menu
Surrounding
He shows
But he talked a little bit more about the
The hunted coming out
People wearing a farm
Fox News I was going to cause mass shootings and so they
But now they've released
Hunters
Anyone wearing make America great again hat
Shirley secretly Nazis
What about the ones who aren't
800 down and killed
This show as best as anyone can tell at this point there's one trailer for it
Has nothing to do with trump it has everything to do with a real actual
Escaped into the United States and they're being hunted down by a group led by a rabbi
Who's pretty anti-nazi
I just
Just it
It cannot
Be said
These are the type of
Claimed that we are also
Haha yep
This is the type of person who sees the trailer for an owl Pacino
TV series
How long is the trailer
Minute 40
Offer him to
Decide to show that is when is it set
70s
Is actually about
Okay
One shot in the trailer where guys holding a red hat to his
Is chest as one might when they're in
Prayer
Well which is apparently enough for the whole joke actually secretly be about hunting down Trump supporters like laying with a Nazi
The redhead is not a trumpet it has yellow lettering
And it doesn't say make America great
It's just red
Other people in the same shot have no hats other another guy has a pork pie hat
Also there's no evidence
From the trailer this guy who has a red hat is one of the targets of the hunters
That's just an assumption that Alex
Is making there is a red hat in the trailer
Ipso facto
Okay so how about the end of Schindler's List
Did he not like the red balloon was that is that the part that really got it just programming for the hats
So this is just an assumption
Actually
Alex is just reporting
Honor Paul Joseph Watson
This is just outright white identity victimhood
Taken to a point of self
Parody
Paul Joseph Watson article on Infowars legitimately says quote
The plot of the show appears to Bear numerous similarities to Jason Bloom's the Hutt a horror movie that centered around a group of live
Liberals who hunt down red state
Conservatives
That's not really a good description of the plot of The Hunt
It has some relevant points in there but if I run Middle School teacher and that was the plot description little Paul Joseph Watson
Turned in for a book report let's say
I probably give him a seat
It demonstrates a lack of critical thinking
Contextual analysis
That's it there's nothing really similar about the plots of the hunt and Hunters
Their names are close and enforces turn the both
Open to attacks on Trump and white people but beyond that they're very
Stories
If you're a hammer everything is a nail
If you're a rabbit white identity propaganda
All you ever see
Or Temps
To make white people look
All that's going on here
This is pathetic
So we're dealing with
Second-degree bulshit here there they're not engaging with the hunters
But they are drawing a connection to the hunt
Which they already have narratives about
Because it's Hunters
And they know that nobody who watches
Is dealing with this s***
Is going to ask
Play give a s*** about
The Bachelor
I think they're huge Al Pacino fans
Infowars I think that's how you write article but I think the inspiration for it is there's a red hat
Great
I want to be
I want to work for
Because that is the easiest job in the world
You know what when I was doing
Stand up
One of the things that made it the most difficult was
Constantly being like someday people will find out I'm not funny
Imposter
I can't imagine how difficult that would be
If you work at Infowars
Like I don't know how you would
I see now I think it's one of those things where
It's like when you like how rich people become more sociopathic when it when you're living when you're riding the bus
You know
You're much more close to your fellow man and then as you get Richie
You start to become back
I think the same thing happens when you're in
Like you're in the pitch meeting and you're trying really hard the first couple weeks you're like
I'm going to really dig down on the story then after a couple weeks everybody's like
You don't have to
You're probably right
You're probably right and then you pick up a nice booze habit
Combat medic
3 whiskey lunches
So
This guy calls into the show
He has some information about the ADL that Alex should know
You can get a pretty good synopsis if you look at the executive intelligence review from 1993 called The Ugly Truth
Video
Bass
Larose group in a very good analysis
A lot of people say that the larousse group
Did a lot of
Greater Dallas
Okay
Got to call her calling and saying you got to educate yourself about to eat
Abl may I refer you to
Lyndon larouche
No cuz you please say what you really mean what
Which is that you just
Could you just stop right
So Alex is Intuit
Without heat
Talk a little bit about the route
Inaccurate
Go back to chases
From the roof patched analysis of the ID
Reading that report like a big
Magazine
Because he was a real progress in front of quantify things and
Yep peace with Russia and China
Capital One credit cards
So what are you can tell they're that Alex is trying to imply that there's
Some kind of a connection between LaRosa's publication about the ATL in his arrest
That's impossible since the pamphlet came out in 90
1892 whereas lorusso's convicted of
Receipts
Mail fraud involving more than
30 million dollars through 11 counts of
Actual mail fraud
Credit card
Conspiracy to defraud the IRS
In December 1988
These guys they deal pamphlet was released wow larousse was in prison for the things for horses
Then One credit card receipt not being right
This is a rule of thumb
I'm going to say this anyone you here saying positive things about Lyndon larouche
In the year of Our Lord 2019
You should walk away from
They're either members of his called or they're just too dumb to recognize what a conman Lyndon larouche was
And either way it's a gigantic red flag you do not need to engage.
Gogo
Larussa the name that you
Just pass on
No I'm going to look into what he's
You don't need to you don't need to he's larouche
So Alex talked in the
Baron Cohen
Has really
Prompted something in his collar
Does we get this called this when I was like hey you should educate yourself about the what the larouche
People had to say about the ATL
No will not
Omani get another caller
Hey Alex it's really great to hear that you know you're talkin about these kinds of issues
What it comes down to groups like the ATL
I've been using terms like anti
I sell my
As a weapon against their enemies that used to be an anti-semite with someone that
And now it really seems like it's turning into someone
Jews don't like
What
That caller accidentally revealed a little bit about himself in that brief sentence
He's an anti-semite used to being somebody didn't like Jews but now it's some of the Jews don't like
What does it mean by someone the Jews don't like
Who are these Jews or deciding who they like and who they don't like
Dear man
I've exist
Jasmine call
Anti-semite recently he might and I heard that I was like
Bet streaming of this he's so f***** up
Indicated
Give me something really bad
Sounds like you know what man
I might be
Guilty of the same a hammer nail
I dwell in a lot of Worlds of
Do you know pretty anti-Semitic
Conspiracy theories that are passed off as anti-communist in nature
I was like I was worried that I was maybe
Unfairly castigating this guy in my mind
No he's opened a space
I'm glad you started talking about these issues you know what these issues means to this dude
Could be just us
Hypersensitive.
We're not
Because he goes on and you makes a recommendation
For someone Alex should have on the
Hitler really really
Scary to see what what these people are doing and
There's a guy who's been writing about this for a very long time
Talk to him
I know this
Noe Michael
All I know is I promote Freedom Americana
So I'm always interested when a collar recommend someone that Alex
Should have on
And to Alex's credit at least you didn't say
Guy like him
Yeah I know
When they make recommendations that
What kind of thing speaks volumes about who Alex's audience thinks
He's in line with
This caller apparently thinks that Alex is on the same wavelength is
Michael Jones
Which is really f***** up
Because that dude is a huge
Bigot
Jones isn't
Extremist Catholic speaker who sets
Free outrageous things of the past few years
A lot of it having to do with how the Jews are behind all the evil in the world
Princeton's he said in an interview quote
If you turn away from the Catholic Church you will end up a Slave
A slave to the Jews
Either through their pornography or their user
That pretty well sums of his perspective it's not some kind of
Anti-zionist thing or something for their policies
This is a guy who literally believes that Jews are in
Intrinsically against
The good of the world
That is really bad I mean it's not as bad as like hey if
If you facilitate another Holocaust we're going to be real bad earlier
It's not that bad
It's not that bad but that is still
In the aftermath of the Tree of Life synagogue shooting Johnson
Quote you have undermined the moral order and now don't be
Be surprised if people start acting
Sing out there regression
Okay which is explicitly saying those 11 people who were murdered brought their deaths
Support themselves for being Jewish
Yeah yeah well I mean when your Jewish your immoral and
If you're immoral don't be surprised when people murdered
I feel like that makes
Since 1996 Jones has put out a magazine called culture wars
Which is pretty much
Just about had the Jews are bad
He's called Jews quote Outlaws and subversive who use religion as a cover for social Revolution
He said Judaism has a quote
Particularly malignant spirit
You legitimately argue that it's a requirement of being Christian
The anti-jewish
In 2003 he wrote an article for his magazine to blame the Jews for bring the Holocaust upon themselves as well as the pogrom
Incidentally e Michael Jones is a big influence
That's currently on one of the Alex
Former friends turned
Outright anti-semite
He's been interviewed by Benjamin a number of times and
Who played an important role
In him going down the path
But he's currently on
This caller knows exactly who e Michael Jones is and how much he hates doing
He's recommending him to Alex
Because to anti-semitic ears
Alex seems like he should be hanging out with this dude
They seem to be on the same page
AA Speakers volume
I do love a b soul
It's so transparent
And just write on
To be a Christian you have to
Is could not be
More obvious
Yeah if you think about that you also have to hate Christ
Dude are you getting this
Are you getting what you are
You are
What's the best
This virulent strain of Christianity
Hayden Christ
F****** awful
So when you look into
Michael Jones
These sorts of these things were like after the synagogues
Can you sing
Could use brought this
Upon themselves
Who sang they brought the Holocaust
The pogrom
Upon themselves
Great things
I need to hear a little bit of Alex
Threatening
Clip
Sort of similar
Crazy megalomania
ATL
When push comes to shove
17 Russia
So in many ways what he's expressing there is that the ATL is going to bring on whatever backlash
They have
Which is obviously
Some sort of a code for
An attack
So sorry
I'm so scared for the ADL
Because
If they keep
Eight you know asking my friends not to
Maybe y'all entice
Semitic my friends are going to start killing them
And that's not
My fault
Their fault
Beijing
Of course
It's a very similar mentality
Speaks again volume
As to why someone would think
You should be hanging out with you Michael Jones
So Alex says the
In the next clip that
Jdl
Stephen Miller
Because I
Everybody loves America
The New York Times that very day she heard Stephen Miller
These are white supremacist
Egypt conservative Jewish guy that loves America unify us around America
I guess your nationality
But some
I think they're going after him because he's white supremacist
Nothing unites
Quiet life
Building a giant wall between
United States
That's that's
Real
F****** absurd shock
Alex has Zach Voorhees on the show The Google whistleblower
You're having this kind of a
Show like you
It's just like you having this guy on it's really f***** up
It is
It is so weird to me that we are dealing with
100 year old Russian
Propaganda and
Present-day propaganda
Mixing together at the same
You know that
That Protocols of the Elders of Zion
And still being around
While the same time all of this
Is new s*** is being
Pushed out
It's bananas
They're good at problem
So there are Zack
I think it's absurd for anyone
To believe that there are any donut
I don't understand
I don't either
I know that he says
Explain why it's
Yeah let's
His argument is
Is bad but it's even worse
You know they're saying that there's a bunch of neo-nazis that there
About how ridiculous this distinct
We need to stop the neo-confederate movement in Russia
Like
Russia might be you know.
Taken over by me
This is what
They're trying to say in America is that we're going to be
Taken over by neo-nazis
German
Political party
What is on the verge of taking over America
So that's a huge slip up on Zach's bar
He's trying to say that it would be absurd to say the Confederacy would take a foothold in Russia the same way would be absurd for the Nazis.
Take a foothold in the United States
What problem is
The Confederacy was
Not really an international thing where it's Nazism involved in World War I
I supposed to be civil
Yeah which
Is a little different
But the bigger reason this is a fuk up is because he's on
Alex Jones
The show
Alex's entire Grande
Conspiracy involves the same globalist to Rand communism and overthrew the Czar in Russia and installed Hitler it did little
Really everything through history they were the Illuminati Adam weishaupt
They're now in power in the United States
Alex for Zack to mock the idea that a centuries-old group could possibly be relevant
The present day
Starbuck Alex is in
Tire world
This show
Is it's very pathetic
Endorphin self-contradictory
Mostly because they're all just making this s*** up based on their feelings of aggrieved
Also Zach
The u.s.a. Zionist
Occupied governor
Receives relevant to this conversation but weirdly
Never comes up
I don't understand why
Alex wouldn't ask about that
Awesome
Imagine if
When the Confederacy lost they were just kicked out and a lot of them went to Russia and became a political party
You've been yes
Anil Confederate movie
Absolutely take over Russia
Joined the Confederacy in order to fight back
Against
The difference between like 18
60 + 19
20 is pretty big in terms of international connect
Yeah
So like the possibility that in other circumstance
Chances that could have happened
That there could have been absolutely
Feasible on someone's slave owners took their slaves to Russia and
Being
Rich's s*** started
Doing the whole thing of course it's not as laughable as he's trying to make it snow
But I do think that the bigger issue is that what he
Describing is being absurd is literally with Alex
Good job Voorhees good job
Bears
Being
Equivalent to
Confederate sky
Kind of makes a lot of sense
Now doesn't it
Alex's parents bought for the grandparents
Great-grandparents
Answer whatever
It makes perfect
Wow that's not true
Alex's of the ATL or not
The Holocaust
Who
Even rhymes with I'm rubber you're glue
Rubber you're glue you're the best
Come on man
You can get a sense
Alex is really freaking
Like he got pretty mad once Zach
Comes into Studio
Like he has someone else to bounce off of
And I think I brought this up the last time exact is on the two of them don't have good
There is a real lack of
Not ready for primetime
He's not very smart is not very quick socially he is maybe having a conversation
Privately he could bring a little bit more the table puppy
Camera and on on bike
And so the two of them just had eight
It's tough answer when
Alex is already in the
State really
Mad about Sacha Baron Baron Cohen in the speech at the
ATL
He's had these callers call in and really validated his anti ATL
Is the direction to
He's launches
Isn't the yelling about how he's the Jew in this
Is equation in there Hitler
It's so far so far on the show we've had a
What a total of four white men bitching about being
Under attack by the
More or less
So earlier Alex said that he isn't
I'm scared of the ATL
You scared for them course
And that always troubles me a little bit
Play something bad could happen to your ATL I'm not saying something I'm just saying that if you keep talking like that
There's probably a word that we've used that's been associated with another race for a while you can't remember what word
It is maybe we talked about it earlier in the day
Azd IDL is getting
That word
It's a little bit worse
What's happening is the 80 open sitting back of the Southern Poverty Law Center in 11 single then get away with it I've gotten away with so much
And I'm just sorry that's not going to happen
Yeah I agree
Oh f***
Dallas officer game plan for him
I just can't believe it I just cannot believe this
So we know that largely a lot of the ways that Alex deploys false flag narrative
R2 mask
Apologize for terrorism that's related to people in his
Community the militia Community the white supremacist white nationalist
Yeah there are ever a
Acts of violence
That are carried out by Pink
Community makes them
False Flags
When Alex says something like you know the next step they're going to false flag themselves
What I hear is Alex believes that someone is about to attack
I never know cuz he
He's done that a few times
Times where it's at
Swear to God
I don't know if he's
Getting a
You don't think so either what there be crazy
There's a tutorial
It's like he in it you know
Oath Keepers are are hanging around and he's
Overhearing
I think Alex is plugged into those communities
Baby
Can you get a lot of it
Information from them
In terms
So just like blog post
I think that it Borgeous
Might be a situation where he hasn't insta
Sexual ability to read the tea leaves
From the rhetoric
It's being put out
And
I'm going to have to defend it
Yeah so I better get started now it doesn't really matter but
Track ahead of time
Let's say someone blows up the ATL headquarters
Of course
The Patriot
You do this sort of thing
Preemptively in
Incase
And I think that Alex
That's one possibility
I do think that Alec
Sphinx-like
To an extent
But there's also the possibility that you just talkin
And that day also
Possibility
That's what I'm saying I'm never sure like it you can get in your head
This guy is over hearing conversations
Indoor getting attack
Text from his buddies or
Whatever
And he's like
I know something's come
They didn't get share the
The details cuz I'm not
Supposed to
Not know that info
But somebody's planning something
I don't I I have to push back I know you're not
But I have to push back just in case anyone takes
Away like that's a
Legitimate possibility
That's a legitimate possible
I think the only two options are Alex talking
Is very possible
Or him having a son
The B climate is right
In terms of the wave
Peoples
Moody's coming up on a really highly.
Time with the
The election season coming
You have
Qanon is back
Now what
I don't know if it's even
I don't I don't know I do see posted I gave the most someone posting again
Yeah. Dude got to read ice just got
Kicked off Facebook
These things
Did r
Are things that will
Right
The worst that I would say
Is this Alex
Views it as a Justin
Incase
Yeah no no I'm not I'm absolutely not saying
That that that
The Conspiracy Theory
Is the case but it's hard
Think it
At least for at least for a little bit
So Alex
Next clip
Ideologies going to
Turn a lot of people into
Wow
I got an ABO working with Hitler on this one I would ask Alex to prove that claim
Because
That would be something I'd like to see you demonstrates that this claim if he's rushing out to break
Cuz he knows that he is
Could just reset when he comes back from commercial and never asked to demonstrate any of his f****** claims
All I can do is really sit back and think
Seems like a lot of the Jewish people that Alex disagrees with politically
Happened to secretly worked with Hitler in WWII
I do I do have a little bit of a tip of the cap
For anybody who out-and-out defames
The Anti-Defamation
If you're you're really
Talking Heads with locking horns swinging for the
So in this next clip we learned the exact thing
Thinks that
Still alive course
And the thing is is at Keating kill himself
He was transferred out of prison and I think
Probably living in some Island right now
Bryson's
Can't make this stuff up
That Song Is Back
Weird
3 Charing
It is
The guy who's lied to me for years says I know
Idabel
Revisit that I hate that are
If it if they keep calling us Nazis people who weren't Nazis are going to become
If that was if that were true Obama would be a f****** socialist
Troop that's
Bulshit
There's a lot of examples of people who don't turn into
The things you called them
Almost
Olive
People who are mostly
Likely to say that they'll be
Turned into
Really already there
Zach believes that the ATL is an extortion racket
Okay court again the Jews are extorting Chris
I've never heard anybody
In in his defensive that or is explanation for it is
Really absurd rewriting
Of a reason to
I mean it's an extortion racket like I'll come to you and let you make a donation
Send to our organization
YouTube largest video producer
PewDiePie
And he ended up
You know capitulating and then you know saying I'm going to
$50,000 to the ATL
Something amazing
Happened when that happened
The whole internet said what are you doing and it was such a commotion because
Landry operation is $50,000
Was all one about which one of these hate symbols
Go to phone call
The way he laughs at the end there is really troubling
But he's also not being honest about the PewDiePie situation
I don't believe this lady I was like Hey we're supposed to stop if you give us money
Which is
Bizarre
Notion
Then eat at the entire internet did not get up in arms about PewDiePie making a donation to the ATL
Neo-nazis
And white supremacy
It couldn't have been me or not
Sleep aid
Neocurly favorites
People is
Good God-fearing Folk
Who for some reason decided that a video game streamer
Saying anti-semitic things
Is a hill worth dying on there was a bigot backlash
And that's
That's what happened he's he's
Completely mischaracterizing very
Important elements of the story
That are really the capitulation was PewDiePie capitulating to the biggest audience
It's amazing how they can turn a guy deciding to make a public donation is by way of
As an as an app
Overture
I wouldn't give him I wouldn't give him too much credit for it
Making that decision
On his own
Is capitulate
Whereas him being screamed at by thousands of online neo-Nazi
Is him
Doing something amazing and retract
Real real sensible stuff
Who believes in Ozog
Really good it's
Engineer I don't know
I know right
Nothing because this guy
I have not seen his work
So we're done like with the
The content of this Epic
Episode
An insanely
Make it very difficult for me because on the one hand I recognize that the abl is not the same thing as Jewish be
So when Alex is really mad at the ADL
I don't want to say that that is directly empties
Somatic
Be very easily
Construed that that's the
The response that I'm happy
And I want to clarify that I don't believe that there are many criticisms
Can have a boat
Southern Poverty Law Center
Andy
The ATL UK
Tim have criticisms of all of them
And I would not say that it's
Intrinsically
Anti-Semitic
Disagree with ATL or bigoted
To disagree with the splc
There are fine
Ways to do that
My response
To this and the way that this
Carried out
Is that Alex is using
Very much
Anti-semitic ideas
To lash out
At the ATL
And the thing
He's responding to that they're doing
Has nothing
To do with
It has to do with
Tamping down on things that are
In his content
People's content
Avi hotel
Like outright Holocaust
So when you respond to
Things like
Hey
This isn't
Opinion
Propaganda that is met
Normalize mean
Stream up take the
He's out of the history of a genocide
We shouldn't be you should go out on your platform Facebook that's not the government censoring
That is not against the First Amendment
You have a choice in
In the matter
When you respond to something like that would like
This is worse than
In Hitler's
Speeches
That is not
Responding to the ATL
That is an expression of an to Summit
I was going to say we are not talking
He is using
ATL
Not talking
Think about the 80s
No you and I and
And he knows and packing
Annie's callers no
The ATL
It could be
Anybody
It doesn't mean it doesn't matter if
Batl
It doesn't matter if it's
The splc
We know what they're really bad at
The moment you say it's worse than Hitler
And the thing
Take the take the reason I want to make a clarification
Because I think it would be easy
To hear this episode and get it
The
Impression that weird
Treating it with the
The same like a memes
Oh yeah I'm not
Immensely
Secondarily you have to look at the way that Alex is audience response
It's to his discussion of the 80
You coming with
You know like larouche
Publications about the ATL lyrics
Well that's not good another caller who's like hey you should talk
Michael Jones
Would you have
The audience.
Clearly understanding
Is that like okay
You going in this direction
Lights
Let's
Let's blow his mind with
Real
Hardcore Asian
Somebody called it the laruffa
Alex
Obviously was sick
Second only to
Yeah and I
I am fun
When I when I hear all this stuff I'm left with like
A real
Troubling
Feeling
Because
This is
A
Almost entire episode long
Breakdown
About
Feelings of being accused of being anti-Semitic
Responding with
Some pretty antisymmetric
That's because they called me
The Medicaid turned him into an anti
And then beat that
Sort of repetition of something
He's going to happen to
That
Is not it just really
Doesn't make me feel good
So we end with one last clip
I think I think my biggest issue is this is
Maybe the most
A in terms of what I've heard
Recently
This is the most
It's just outside in the room either
Like cuz this
Really
There's still a bit of like
Linguistic distance
Little bit of like
Ghetto code
But sure but it's very
Mad when you're talking about Sacha Baron Cohen speech at ATL event
You say that
Hitler speeches want this
Steve-O
Your
I mean
I can't look at that as
Anything other than like are you trolling here
If you're saying that seriously then
You need to
You need to read some
I don't I don't want him to read those pages I don't want him to get any ideas
On what to say next
So
It will leave with one last
Alex gets another caller
Little bit later and
Michelle
And
He wants to give an a
For sure about 4
Sure
And I
Pink
But this guy is
Turbo Force
Sounds very similar to Robert Barnes wanted to sell it
Little bit about me I'm 245 lbs I work about 10 to 13 hours a day at UPS
Make a long story short
A problem with
I do have ADHD
I was taking adderal
Is energy-boosting properties
Everyday
Turbo Force
Really change my life
So he's a he's a testimonial for Turbo forces hey mad this is
So much better than abusing
Adderal as if it were
Speed
River barge is talking about the licky legal stimulants that he was using in Call of Duty it's very similar
Legal stimulants
Really starting to think somebody should test with x
Actually in turboforce right
I like it better that this is just a thing that keeps
Popping up with problems speed and expect
I used to do Coke everyday and now I just snort turboforce because it's completely different
Grateful when I go to the late-night party everyone wants to talk about ideas
I'll take an 8-ball of heroin and we'll just go all-in have a good day
Dammit
So weird
We're
Not a good
Selfie
So we come to the end of this and I feel
Gross I don't feel good
I worry about what the future holds for Alex
He's teasing around these sorts of ideas it doesn't get better
Doesn't get good from here
Nope so I hope everyone
As a nice rest of the week in the weekend will be back on Monday
Enjoy your turkey
International audience
Enjoy what
Celebrate indigenous people wherever you
Sure please
I'm so above the back until then we have a website
We do have a website
It's knowledge
You bet we also on Twitter
We are interested in Alexandria right now go to bed Jordan vonda's
We are on Facebook
If you want to download the show go to iTunes leave a review etcetera share it you know that
Name Rebecca butts
Emilio Emilio on dcx Clerk
I am quadruple
Alexandra Thurston color