Air Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge B
Sprite.com
Bourbonnais weather
Size around a little bit about Alex Jones
Do you have a
A regional saying that you appreciate the most
Like I know we talked about the proof of the pudding is in the
That's not reasonable
Is the correct
I'm just saying is there one that you recall that was like
Maybe you brought it out into the larger World in Chicago and somebody's like I have never heard that crazy
You said before
I don't know boy howdy is
Goodwin
Did the greeting
Knee high to a boll weevil
I've always heard knee-high to a duck
Reminder like weird things
Like
Bitten
Like a cigarette
To do that it was pretty big in Missouri I don't know if
I don't know
I don't know I'm not very malleable by way of
If you will it's not how I would put it I just don't
The slang
Right it's not I feel silly wait did you say you don't cotton to slang too much yeah okay well that seems
I don't know
Oxymoron I feel silly using these things like
I make a joke out of
My personality doesn't fit well with slime
I don't know babe I feel like region
Colloquialism
Anyway but I don't know
Understand probably is
Sticks out too much
Edgar from this area
I'm from Southern Illinois
Which is not too far away from
But yeah I remember all of them were about fishing
Because my grandpa was my grandpa was huge and
Inefficient
To the point where he took my grandma fishing on their honeymoon
Cuz she was six
And
Leave that alone.
The 1930s right there right
That's a great depression man
But it was always like a
All the crappy you're really biting today in your life I don't know what you're talk
About we're not fishing right now
Now so
What's that sounds
Like
No I wasn't awake yeah but that was just an example
Something far more
Inscrutable
To the point where I can't remember any of
I don't know
I apologize
Little bit
I apologize as well for the same situation this is the show where I don't know a whole lot about the times that I've adopted Regional fly
But I do know a lot about Alex Jones
So Jordan today we're doing episode I don't want to do
And we'll get to that in a moment.
I will take a little thank you
The books are signed up and are supporting the show
So first bred with
What thank you so much you are now policy walk
Thank you Fred
Jeff with two F's
Thank you so much
Your novelty welcome
No it's Jeff
Call
Standard holy normal
Text Rachel thank you so much you're now a policy wonk
Next Salman
Semenex
Exit the end of the word salmon thank you so much you're not allowed to walk
I've no idea to what I feel so out of touch
I got that one
Onyx Sean because much you know about that
William Baker so much during our technocrat
Amy thank you so much you are now at
Business
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
Angel with these gents to I'd like to
Jordan today we are going over November 29th
Teen and actually we're not going over the whole episode because
A lot of it is not nearly as important
As
And interview that Alex has
On that
Yeah yeah yeah
We are last episode we saw Alex go pretty hard against
Jdl the Anti-Defamation League in the process of doing that some of his callers
Call Dan expressing kind of more overt
Anti-semitic ideas
When's the door up with this sort of language
Caller calls there's an investigation by the larouche people
Another caller calls in and says hey you really need
Need to talk to this guy
Play Michael Jones
Okay
And Alex
Super aware of who this guy
The caller is like
What is right on ya
You hoped that wouldn't go anywhere
But
Alex
Within a matter of days
4 days
In four days
3 days
25th is one day or whatever
Three business days
Alex has
Michael Jones
As a guest
Really problem
I don't know
Play problematic
Because that seems
Trade there's some real problems with him having to have on the show
The word atrocious pops into my mind
Right there's some issues with ever having him on your show.
Which will discuss
But there's some secondary issues that are unique to Alex Jones Infowars having him on as a guest
That I think make this
Way worse
Okay and I hope that we'll be able to get through this
We'll do our best
Because it's going to be very
Do you know folks
Kristen and singularly pointed on
This interview I thought we'd get warmed up
By Sasha Banks theme song
We could use it
Warmed up here with the Clippers
Text talking about a headlight
That he is putting out
Okay no just to get our toes where at
There has been a bill introduced to ban
Krav Maga
Brazilian jiu-jitsu
In Virginia
And again that shows you where all
Is going
They want an outlaw
Citizens being able to defend themselves
Antifa
From the top
All the rest of it where I live in Austin
There are
Giant packs of Communists in black and red mask
Beating people up
Attaching building for white people live
White people by the way almost all of them
But if you have a cat sanctuary in East Austin
Did you build a new building there then
Gentrification
They're going to city council members home
Putting people's heads open in Austin
The police indicted one of them
And the city dropped charges under orders
The prosecutor is on board with them
Once they get the police in place
Prosecutors employee
Your only recourse will be defending yourself a deadly force when they try to kill you
Wait you're so pissed
And so
Remove by Banning
Krav Maga training
All of that okay
Defend all Brazilian jiu-jitsu
Alright
It's like dodging
But Mom mainly through mad still out
No surprise that Alex
Who's lying about
Virginia Bell
This is a recording that is based on a story was originally put out by Mike Adams natural news that argued that a proposed bill would
Would outlaw firearms training
And all martial arts
You could get that sense from the bill if you don't read it
Sent it does say that it would be unlawful if you quote
Assemble with one or more person
Thanks for the purpose of
Who traded with
We're being instructor
The use of any firearm explosive or incendiary device or technique
Capable of causing death
Pasta person
That could definitely include a lot of martial arts
Some definitely cover pretty much all shooting range
Glasses
Butterbean I really feel like that
The hammer is going to come with like
To create a paramilitary force hell-bent on destroying the entire Union
Bill sharpen blades
Because
Ends with a qualification to Wood Circle
Open stance is under which those active
Would be illegal quote
Intending to employ such training in use in or in furtherance of a civil disorder right right
Also this has been on the books since
Since 1987 all the time
Now that there's slight changes being made to the language of the Bell
For instance to include marching with weapons with the
Intent of intimidating a person or group of persons right as prohibited paramilitary activity
Well I mean
I would argue that would also count against the Black Panthers
In the lights
I think
That
This bill comes down to the interpretation of what intent to intimidate a person or group
Right right right I don't
No
What would fall under that but I would assume that The Oath Keepers would still be able to march with weapons
Valley Fair
I assume.
I assume that the Black Panthers would not be
And The Oath Keepers would
I'm not sure very possible
At this at this point when I was looking into it still a proposed bill I have no idea
The thing about this is you can find tons of right-wing blogs picking up historian reporting on it as tyranny,
Coming out into the open
Very similar tone
There's a write-up about this on tacticalshit.com
Includes a picture of an Instagram post about the bill saying quote
You want to start the book
This is how and why you start the bug
Comments on political bullpen
And says quote
This might this just might be what
Kicks off the second Civil War
These two people are saying the same thing
Since Boogaloo has Reese
Become short
And the right-wing extremist use to flip it
Only discuss the coming
Second Civil War
God they're so stupid
Children
It's just another in a long string of ways that these dangerous bucks
So tried to normalize the fantasies of Justified Violence
Discussion of the
The great idea of
Killing Eve are we murdering hundreds of thousands of people if not Millions
No we're just starting the book.
That's all we're doing
Alex knows what he's doing by selling this fake narrative about this bill
He's trying to raise the temperature
And help
Disseminate something
That will provide that reaction from
These communities
So
That's great
We get to the center Dakshin
Here we go
Joining us this
Where is Michael Jones
And on a few times
I forgot my head
One of his books years ago
Monsters from the ID
Oh no, he was a professor
And he was removed
Because he was paralyzed
He's been massively persecute
Arrested they don't submit
Purging
Come on
About this big move for total censorship total control but really he's an expert on
Societal collapse
The plan to take our morals away so we can be easily enslaved and control
Code and one clip my worst fears about the direction of Alex Jones's show the way it's trending or completely
Confirmed
The very idea that you would have Michael Jones on as a guest and give him that sort of any reduction is so revealing about the way things are going
1 thingy Michael Jones is a well-documented entice
When Alex says that this guy is an expert on societal collapse it would probably be worthwhile.
Point out to his audience that he thinks Society is collapsing because of the Jews
It is publication the Jews and moral subversion
Michael Jones says there is quote
A group that is responsible for virtually every social in our day
From the wars in the Middle East
Pornography and gay marriage at home
Namely the Jews around whose evil machinations
History turn
Okay so it's not the Buddy comedy that I was
Moral subversion
Gotcha not that one
When Alex went off on his Jag the other day about the ATL and Sacha Baron Cohen speech you can very clearly see that his audience took that is green
We'd like to bring some hardcore anti-jewish talking points into
The conversation
Better than of itself isn't really surprising
Nor was it really that surprising that one of the callers would
Would suggest that
Interview e Michael Jones
What is surprising is that Alex not only said nuts
Like a good idea
Any followed through with the booking
In a matter of days
This tells me a number of the
Any which could be possible
It may be the case that Alex knows who the
This guy isn't still wanted
To have him on what to be f*****
It may be the case that he didn't
No we was but decided to book it without doing any research
Also
Pretty f*****-up
But even if that is the case that means that there's literally no one working at Infowars who decided
To step in and say Alex
This is not a good booking
I know you're mad at Sacha Baron Cohen right now
But this is not the way to go about doing
Yeah I assume if you just Google is name at least one of the whole being a All-Star
This dude is a f****** nut
It's very
Find
I'm inclined to believe that if you're considering having e Michael Jones on your show there's no way you can possibly claimed ignorance of who he is and what he's
It's Records Long and very over
In 2070 give a speech to the
The Press Club at a memorial for Samuel t
Francis
Himself a profound racist alleged journalist
This event was supposed to be aired on
C-SPAN it never aired
According to people who are in a tent
It's because e Michael Jones gave a shockingly offensive speech
I should point out the people who called the
Shockingly events
Where people who work for organization
Like the white nationalist publication video
Even though you thought Jones was way out of line
Yeah Himmler was like Jesus man, down they were at a memorial for a man who once wrote quote
Breaking down
The sexual barriers between the races is a major weapon of cultural destruction
Michael Jones made them say well that's a bit
Okay alright
So they've so segregation now segregation forever is even that dudes like
Eggnog
Okay
Gotcha
I couldn't find video of the speech
But it did find a version of an imprint the Joneses
Self-publish
And I would say I can see how someone would find this very offensive
Here's some Choice passages from his speech
Quote as the gospel of
Play John makes clear the Jews became the
The Jews the minute they rejected Christ
As such there only identity is negative
Boy that doesn't sound right
Quote if what's left of the WASP establishment or the Paleo conservatives are other men of good will want to do something effective
In the culture wars
They will have to understand just who the enemy is in this battle
In case you're curious you later clarifies quote The Real Enemy that turns out was the Revolutionary Jew
That's that's not the the twist ending that I was expect
From this Agatha Christie mystery
Quotes many if not most of us are here today because our careers have already been to
Destroyed by the Revolutionary Jew and is goyish frontmen
The Jews spy on us through our computers they suborn fellow Catholics to betray us get us fire prevent us from speaking
Our backs are to the wall
And when was this was a 2007-2017
Jesus
This was a big deal in conservative circles 12 years ago and John says not toned it down at
At all since that
There's literally zero excuse to have them on your showing
Anti-semite
Or possibly in the rare circumstance
But you think you're capable of having a concert
Rotational interview with them
Even though I really don't think that's
Stephen a great idea
Do that
Yeah I could I could see that
But
I would say they'll advise
I'm really disappointed in our
Ever since he was kicked off social media today
His feelings about Trump and started to Waffle a little bit
Cardi B like watching a coin flip
Had to go back to being a coded speech
Conspiracy guy was mad
The three people voted in the Federal Reserve and you
I get to hang out with Ron Paul's brother
Tails he becomes the worst version of
Himself possum
When I was doing some research for a 2013 episode I came across an article in The Daily Beast
About the tendency of people to
Describe two conspiracy
The main thesis is a familiar one
Basically
Describing guilt for a largely random event to a defined
Anime you can subconsciously feel more in control of your
However the article includes a quote from Stephen Lewandowski
A professor of Psychology from the University
The Western Australia
Who is he's dedicated a good bit of
It's time to study
Conspiracy community
And I think his comments are particularly relevant right
Lewandowski is discussing the dynamic it play with
Conspiracy paddlers like Alex
Glenn Beck
And healthy
Music
Economy is comprised of both these
Peddlers and of consumers
Of the information
And these groups their motivation
Spring gauges
Conspiracies might be completely
We different
He suggested
It's possible that these be
People like Alex
Glenn Beck
Maybe motivated by money or attention
Going on today
Say quote I can't look inside their head
It's but there's a lot of snow
Suggestive evidence that people say crazy things sometimes just to be notice
I know this from my work on climate
Because if no one is listening to these guys
Or fewer people are listening
To them the more over-the-top they go and the crazier their pronounce
Come
I think they're watching themselves being ignored
And that's the one thing they hate
So they crank up the volume and spread their falsehoods and Anza
I think that might be some of what's going on here as well
Yeah talking about Glenn Beck's Behavior
After the Boston bombing
This is well he's suggesting that that was
Play there I would also argue that that dynamic
Is true for bachelor in
I've not watched it but I'll take your word for it
I fear that the situation we found ourselves in the 29th
Is one where Alex's experience
Himself be
You can get local protesters to Gallatin when he shows up to rallies and it
But you can't really translate that into marketable attention
He's no longer than me machine
Triggering
Bricks don't really
Work anymore
No one's really interested in
Dumb s*** to buy his book to make it out of the
Play the number one seller
Really
Many books
Begin with
Riding harder
In many ways we've already seen this playing out on a
Show in the past year is rhetoric has escalated in
A lot of horrifying ways
The disgusting over-the-top
Obsession with delivering elaborate Fanta
Disease about kids being murdered and
His demon voice is just one of
Money manifestation
That
I don't know how else to describe so much of what Alex is doing these days other than
I'm cranking up the volume
Zied seems to be being ignored and
Tolerate that
Yeah embracing the void
And I think that this interview
Accepting it
Doing it
Can't see it is
Much elves
Other than that also
Things you can't really claim ignorance
I mean you can
But I'm not sure I believe you
Before we get into this I need to make clear that Alex Jones and E Michael Jones are not capable of having a cold
Conversation
Because they're both playing game
But they're kind of
Different games
Alex Jones a super into white identity and Christian identity
Extols the virtues of the West
Which we've heard him explain repeatedly is more or less just code for white culture
There's a heavy racial element what drives out
Well it's true that his worldview is structurally supported by historical
Semitism
It's not so clear that he necessarily hates Jewish be
Yeah
Conversely e Michael Jones is Not primarily concerned with Ray
In fact he believes that if you identify by your race you're falling for a Jewish trick
As he put it quote
You lost the battle when you became White
Because they get to Define your identity
And you didn't
He adheres to a fundamentalist version of Catholicism
Infuse most of the world's history of the battle between Judaism in the Catholic Church
We're all the criticisms you might have about the Catholic Church
I really just things that the Jews were at fault for
Sure there was that whole thing about priests molesting kids but they only did that cuz the Jews sexualize Society
We're not so we're talking about torquemada
That's what that's what we're doing right now
We're going there
You'll find a lot of arguments like that
One of the Hallmarks of Jones's rhetoric is the idea of logos
If you listen to another anti-semitic leaving right way
When content like Owen Benjamin
You'll hear the word come up a bunch
Generally is someone saying that logos is rising
And when you do that's a reference
Stewie Michael J
The foundation of his worldview is that the Jews killed Christ
She was a pure manifestation of logos
Essentially reason in the unit
And that kind of thing
All right because they did that they're all
Alright literally Express this on a podcast called red pill religion
Insane quote
The Jewish people as a group called for the death of Jesus
Is Christ the Jewish people as a group killed Christ
And they are enemies of the entire human race
Essentially every Jew was at bat
F******
Speech
Jesus man what an
It's
Jewishness
It's it's
It's a mess
So what we're dealing with here if I understand correctly is
Alex Jones
Is it possible that he's anti-Semitic
Incidentally
As a as a result of his white identitarian
Where is e Michael Jones
Is f****** in it
Yes and it's f******
But his version of anti-Semitism was a little more complicated then
What you might find on
Just some run-of-the-mill Neo-Nazi kind of
He has
He has this
Religious aspect
Vitz Metals Intuit
YouTube
It is
It's more complicated
I hope I think
And as we go along but
It's
And as far as Alex Goes
You know
I don't want I don't want to say
Incidentally
That
Whether or not he's aware of it
His world is based on
Incidentally is not the word I think I was more going with consequence
In that regard
He's at every opportunity
Opportunity in the course of
His career to understand where his beliefs
Come from and he has
Is either refuse to or
Never
So
Whatever the case is about
The beginning of their conversation through between the two Joneses
Centris primarily around the edge
Which adds an extra layer of difficulty
I'm trying to parse out
People are saying
For Alex bohica
Complains about the ebl he's really complaining about the globalist
Free Michael when he complains about the edl he's talkin about Jews
In general
View others even further blurring the complicates
Wednesday
And that is the E Michael Jones plays kind of fast and loose when he's
Is talk about what we means when he says the Jews
He doesn't believe that Jewish is an ethnic identity
This position seems to be that he's only against religious Jew
But that doesn't make any sense given that so many of the Jewish organizations that he's in
Conflict with aren't religious organization
It's all very complicated I promise I'm going to try my best to maneuver some of this
Pretty dicey territory
But I want to apologize upfront
And if I make any missteps
A lot of mess so could you get away from him if you're like not a non-practicing Jew
Or even if you're like no I'm more of a Christmas
What's an Easter type do you know I don't go to church all day
To it along the road I know that
He doesn't have a problem
With Jews
Jews have converted to Christianity I know that much
Ultimately for Alex Annie Michael both of their positions are rooted in historical and
Semitism
So they're able to have a conversation there on the service
Surface appears to
Scents to both of them
But they're talking around different
And I don't know how much I believe Alex isn't aware of
My advice for Alex
If I wasn't employed Infowars let's say maybe his dad who works
I don't know if his dad still works in HR but I like to imagine
He still does
Work at an invoice and I was Alex's dad I would have told him
If you're going to go on the
Since the edl the last guest you should have on
To help you get someone with decades-long history of overt
Agro antisemita
This is a
Horrible decision
Itself
Speaks volumes
Dad died I respect your opinion but I need to find out if he's my real
Same last name according to Alex that's proof enough for
Bandsaw a whole bunch of other people so introduction
Michaels.com
Joining the infowar today
Thanks for coming on with us you got the floor here to start
Wherever you'd like first
You could make the argument
You know like he doesn't look at this from an external perspective you could make the argument
Alex just wants to have this guy on the same way he wanted have David Duke on back in 2015
Either way of trying to debate someone who also they both believe in
Immigrant
Different
Ideas about the nature of the
If you listen to that intro
That is not the sort of thing Alex's doing
Is a friendly very respectful introduction
Is not confrontational
Adam Eve is a massive disappointment
Is couple years ago Alex at David Duke
And all he wanted to do
Let's try and be like hey
We both believe in this stuff
But you're bogged down in the race
And now you're someone who
I don't know favorably or unfavorably could be compared to take put to Kenny's like anybody
That's no good
That just
So this is not a situation where he's bringing them on to try and
Flush out the finer differences
Between our worlds
So like I said they start off by talking about the Ada
And it does
It doesn't take the entire it goes off
But it does start
With some complaints
Mostly about Sacha Baron Cohen seed or
Again I regret to inform you these guys are mad at Borat
Great major move on the part of the
ATL just this past week they gave an award to Sacha Baron Cohen
And he in response gave a speech that I thought was kind of chilling
He starts in demanding that the censorship be imposed on the internet
And the 380 lb in charge of the censorship
And then he goes on to say
If you big check people don't do it we're going to throw you in jail
This was kind of a shocking turn of events
Organization that suddenly is supposed to be put in charge of what we are
Thinking about what we're allowed to say on the ATL
So the first lie here is I'm saying that Sacha Baron Cohen speech included him saying that there needs to be
Censorship online and demands
That the 80 lb
Be in charge of that
You probably make an argument that he was calling for a form of online censorship and is much as a platform like Facebook and very easily
Strike things like
Holocaust denial from their platform easy
Without infringing on anyone
Is right to free speech
It's a matter of disentangling the idea of censorship from the idea of Oppression
What time censorship is appropriate
All that aside in his speech Cohen was not demanding that the ATL be in charge of online sensor
That's probably have someone like you Michael Jones my
Beetle
Watching the speech
But it wasn't
While he was speaking to a
A Jewish lad organization so naturally the only thing that he could assume
Is that he wants batl to control all cents
Adult speech anywhere Dan
Second Life Jones is very clearly trying to play fast and loose with who is doing what to whom
Sing the Cowan was saying that
If he's tech companies didn't go along with the edl censorship
And then we're going to
Throw you in jail
It specifically Mattis
Subconsciously in plant the idea in the listeners had the authority to
Send you to jail
In reality it's very clear to listen
The speech Nicole was advocating for the passage of laws or regulations that would play some responsibility on these social media platform
For atrocities that are facilitated by them
I know again
Someone Like You
Michael Jones that
Feels like the ATL sending you to jail if they don't like your free speech
But it's complete
Misrepresentation of what's being said this is the difference
Between
Feeling
Versus reality narrative
Versus
What would a narrative versus critique
Here's what I
I hear a sentence like
Hey
If you facilitate another genocide you should go to jail
And you here
Well they're just going to throw us all in jail
That suggests something very specific
Sure you're for
The whole you know that stopped
So he has some other things
To say about the 8th
CDL
I don't like
The way this is
Who is the idea what is this organization
It's an organization that was founded to protect a pedophile
The name of the pedophile soundtrack Frank
1913 he was arrested
Sexually molesting and then murdering a thirteen-year-old girl who worked in his Pencil Factory
At this point the he went on trial he was found guilty and then a series of
Attempts to overturn appeals took place
The appeals went all the way to stream Court every single appeal
Reaffirmed the original decision and at that point the governor of Georgia community
One day before he was leaving office
At this point the people Georgia rose up an army of about two thousand armed men approached the
Governor's Mansion
Is that point that Governor fled to New York City where the call Jewish media basically created
Him as a hero
This is this is an organization that began by protecting a pedophile
And then continued in an operon operation where
The main point of this operation was to make sure that Jewish criminals did not go to jail
I think you can tell by this man's motive speech that he might have some more
Extreme positions that he's leading on on air
Sing that the governor flight to New York whereupon the Jewish media turns him into a hero is a bit of a red flag on its own
Didn't realize it already only a minute into this interview he has every reason
To think he's in
Deep trouble
This guy is clearly a
Boulder brand of anti-semite than he's used to dealing with and he's also very slow
The real important piece of the case of Leo Frank that e Michael Jones is kind of glossing over here
And that's after these men.
He's talking about and as far as I can tell they were less than
I'll bet the way he's putting that they could approach the governor's mansion
After that they broke into the prison Frank was being held in sees him and Lynch
They were proud of themselves
Stephen Posen
Four pictures along the way and it disgusting display of Malbec
Activity
Why what is true that Leo Frank was convicted of the murder of this thirteen-year-old Mary phagan
And it is true that his appeals were rejected
It's almost Universal consensus among his story and said he was probably in a
And it very least
Did not get a fair trial
The case of Leo Frank is endlessly complicated and it'd be pretty impossible for me to lay out everyday
Detail about it here
So the best I could do is
Point out some places where you Michael Jones version are less than
Honest
He says that the ATL was quote founded
To protect a pedophile
In this case Frank is the alleged pedophile
There's no evidence other than rumor that Frank was sexually involved with
Girl
Though he was convicted of murder sexual assault charges were never brought again
Dance them and that's it
Improving
Jones's further saying that the ATL was founded
To defend Leo Frank
That's somewhat disingenuous
It is true that the ADI was founded after Frank was convicted and that his conviction was one of the issues cited when they formed
It wasn't like they created this organization
Specifically to protect
But now it's grown into what it is today
If you look at the history of the case and the trial that led to
To the conviction
You can easily see how this is the sort of thing they could be a signpost about some dangerous societal attitudes
Regardless of the outcome or even Frank's person
No guilt or innocence
For instance as the trial was proceeding groups of people would rally around the courthouse
Chanting hang the Jew
The environment and Georgia was so openly hostile to Jews that according to the Times of Israel after Frank
Lynching
Half the states Jewish population
This is more with a DL was formed in response to and it's absurd to imagine that he Michael Jones doesn't realize
He's creating a scapegoat out of Leo Frank in the same way that Lynch Mob did back at 9
Interesting Lee Jones seems to ignore the other group that grew out of
Which is the second Ku Klux
Which has relaunched in Stone Mountain Georgia at a meeting
Flash cross-burning
It was attended by some of the very men
Lynched Leo Frank
These are elements of the story that
Michael Jones
Intentionally leaving out because he
You trying to recruit
This is the stuff that's fine to know once you're in the door but you don't want people to know it when they're just first taking in the message
You want to ignore the fact that Leo Frank was probably innocent
And was lynched by a number of people who go on to be a part of the formation
The second plan
Because those details with tent
Turn uninitiated
People off
From the message
Did your trying to push
And Alex is letting
I am glad for that
Extra contacts
But if you just said 1913
Trial and non-white out of been like he was probably
There's no
There's a lot of Dynamics in play
Interview the case
It's far too,
Of course of course
So he goes on
Jones Goes On
It's very complicated because his last name is Jones
Pretty much throughout this if I say Jones I'm referring to eat Michael Jones
But so do another
Criminal
The ATL
It's supposed to protect
The main point of this operation was to make sure that Jewish criminals did not go to jail
Meyer Lansky is an example of one person I'm talking about gave the ATL a lot of money it didn't work at
Time
So weird free Michael Jones to use Meyer Lansky is his neck
Example of a Jewish criminal the ATL tried to defend
Berlinsky was a big-time mob figure is associated people like Lucky Luciano
When was IMDb
With organized crime
To be sure
He was mostly operating gambling rackets and made a ton of money in that Hustle
In 1970 facing prosecution a flight to Israel which is exactly what neo-nazis say all Jewish people get to do
Because of the right of return they can just
Commit whatever crimes they want and when it gets too hot to go to Israel
I can hide out there
That's not what happened
Israel deported Lansky back to the United States
Stand trial where he was acquitted
And most sources I can find say was because he was too ill to stand trial
I guess the fact that he got extradited is what Jones means when he says
It didn't work that time but honestly I think his point is just a
Incoherent
It might be worth noting that the neo-Nazi
T crowd really
Really doesn't like mayor Lance
I have a suspicion please folks might be a little biased
Because outside of being a famous mobster
He's been a good amount of his time busting heads in American not
Here's Lansky describing how you disrupted a brownshirt rally in Manhattan
The stage was decorated with a swastika and a picture of Hitler
The speaker started ranting
There were only fifteen of us but we went into Act
We threw some of them out of Windows most of the Nazis panicked and ran out
We chase them and beat them up
We wanted to show them the Jews and not always sit back in
Acceptance Auto
Interesting will you can see how Publications like the national Vanguard Spinda
Lansky's gang took time off from clipping
Suckers and burger and Rivals to breakup purple
Legal meetings of the pro White
Pro National Socialist German American Bund
Being presented as a case of these these white rally-goers being a
Deprived of their free speech
Which
That rhetorical strategy of course has Deep Roots
And continues to this day
And these
F****** awful circles it's really cool how you used to be able to say very
Currently the pro-white pro nationalist socialist boond
Why would anybody object to that
That's not
Something that used to be
National Vanguard
Concurrently
Yeah it's f****** p
Yeah
So you know you can even see overlap with that like these the this National Vanguard ideas like
He'll Hades
Nazis just wanted to have a rally
And I need you
You can even hear a sort of Echoes of that in the
Hades
The abl wants to say hey you guys shouldn't
Hate speech of like
Holocaust denial
Are depriving me my free
Kind of see how it isn't never really change
You guys know what you're defending is
And you know damn well would it be
Go fuc yourself
So far the two criminals e Michael Jones
280 H setup
Protector I probably wrongly convicted man who subsequently Lynch by Future klansman
And by far the most prominent person who fought back against the American Nazi
Tea party during World War II
So far so good Coca-Cola
Near the third example a guy named Moe dalitz who was a bootlegger and eventual Casino guy
I don't really understand the point John's trying to
How to make about him
I think it's just at the ATL awarded him there torch of Liberty award
And Jones
This convinced that it's just because you gave him a bunch of
Show me the Bears mentioning is that where Michael Jones is putting out unchallenged on Alex's show right now is identical to its putter
Stop by the national Vanguard
Their article about the eight
CDL uses all of these same examples and has almost an identical
The national Vanguard isn't explicitly Neo-Nazi Oregon
Translation
Alex legitimately might as well have the Nash
Vanguard
Madagascar
He's got nothing
Simple but I know what you're
So Alec
Has a response
Do this
I think it's telling
Santa is real I'm not anti-jewish anything this is a group's got an ally it Mafia
Knowing that Americans don't want a give people for religion or race or anything
A money-laundering operation for international Mafia International crime
To go after anyone that exposes any of these Criminal
Just like the mafia says I'll burn down your grocery store if you don't pay me protection money
Mark Zuckerberg is a Jewish man
If he doesn't give this group of pirates
Full control over his company so it's a very dangerous Mafia
That rebuttal is really dumb but the only reason Alex's saying this I believe
I think is that he can tell he's talking to and
Anti-semite about the ATL
That's why you stressing me that he's not anti-jewish or anti-israel and has ucker Burgers Jewish
I suspect that's a subtle way for Alex.
Stewie Michael to speak in the queen's English if you will
Kind of way of saying don't say the things you want to say without having to
Discomfort of that actual conversation on air
Anybody want to get that sense
I
Fuel that
Away
Cuz it'll be really hard to hear the things
Is that junk something up to this point
And not be like
Kind of ghetto
What your
Laying down
Yeah you did
That's like the ATL specific
TV channel
Okay
He's talking about exactly what he's talkin
And if you know anything about the case of Leo Frank like
The fact that he's describing the events
That way and leaving out the part where he was
I think that speaks volumes on its own to
So
I remember
Like when I was
In my really early 20s
Like 20 22 something like that watching Sealab 2021
Which is
One of it like love that show and there's an episode that centered around all these
And the joke was
Set the people controlling everything
Where the 5G
Right
And I thought that was funny
Because that's
Seems so over-the-top and stupid
Really
That's what you think that's
Hilariously stupid
Now I know what that that was
That was f******
Wow
So we go off
Yeah I know
It's not great there's a lot of bad stuff
So Alex Goes On
To complain
I don't even know how
Clive ladies and gentlemen Michael Jones gizzard I want to just remind
Without you will not be on here we are
The pogrom against
Injustice 2 things of Martin Luther King jr.
F*** you
They call me white supremacist they call
Stephen Miller a white nationalist call for his firing
It really is defamation
I would everybody can be saved by
Budget
Forget we have the biggest sales the Year this is our biggest
That was weird just can't I just can't do that
Do that
That's a lot but also lazy
That's all I hear that's a lot
On your on your
Here's what we got a an explicit anti-semite
Who's saying that the Jewish media is control and s***
And they're trying to run a pogrom against us
Also we got the biggest sales on right now
F*** off
SMS
Pretty bad
So also Tim Cook was given the
Hey Tour by the ATL and 28
But it's complete bulshit for Alex the climate of Gattaca
Silence Dalek
The reason cited for his receiving the award where that
He matches his employees donations
Charitable organization
The fact that you responded to the United right rally in Charlottesville head-on with the employees at Apple
In condemnation
Amanda vet
He's been a voice of support consistently for lgbtq
BBQ in Emigrant right
All the reasons that Tim Cook received this award are things that Alex stands against
That is fair enough
But I was trying to turn this into some
Transactional thing with ATL wanted Alex silenced
The Tim Cook did it for them so he gets
A childish bulshit
52 5th Ave
So
You might go goes on
To complain
I bet about how it's on
Unfair
What's happened to
I don't agree
That the problem is you can't object so it was Jose they attack me on Monday last week
And then I go on another YouTube show and I said look the ATL just attacked me
This is not fair I don't think they should have this power over who gets on the Internet or not so guess what hap
YouTube video gets gets
Wait a minute
Can I objected
To what these people just did to me
I have no idea what he Michael Jones said recently to draw this rebuke
Goodbye based on the sort of things you said in the past I really do
Don't think it was not deserve for Buick
So he can claim all you wants that it's just as Jewish organization that the
It's everyone
Anti-semite
In 2004 the Catholic League put out a statement saying quote
The Catholic League condemns Jones's antisemitism repudiates his efforts to
To justified in the name of Catholic theology
One thing is clear there are many Choice terms one can use to
Describe Joneses view of Salvation history
Catholic is not one of the
See I just don't see any Catholic voices out here denouncing this kind of behavior
I don't see why is it that every time
We have some kind of radical Islamic terrorists all of Islam comes out and announces to everybody that we don't suppose
For this kind of behavior but that a Catholic does it and I don't hear any voices
I'm not complaining about Catholic
Salt Lake up that I think
The game is pretty simple with this sort of
Assertive provocateur s*** like you say something that's in defense
Cebollin bigoted
And then some organization
Is like hey indefensible and bigoted and then in order to defend yourself you have to say something worse
Beach and that's because
Would you date me
That's the sort of game that's being played at
Whatever
If you need to really cut through the b******* I should probably tell you that a 2000
3D Michael Jones with Addison
CD called watching it
MTV
Neo ethnic songs and dances
Which included a track called
Fear the Jews
This man is not interested in any sort of corruption in the edl or not being able to respond or anything like that he's a pure
Or to his core anti-semite
And what else is doing here is selling him to his audience
The disgusting
Display
And I honestly generally
Do you know what say I can't say I'm super surprised
But I am kind
Is that a
Is that a like
Parody version of Don't Fear the Reaper
I didn't listen to it the greatest Weird Al Yankovic
Then I got to be specific
He's not white Nashville
I understand
He's adopted by a lot of ointment
True but he himself
He has a singular Focus
Yes
Scaccia
So
Michael Jones start speculating here about what's going on
Between the ADL and
Like Facebook
Of them
And I don't
His theory
So I think I think what we're saying it is push back
Because they should have been insiders here in the tech World there was a big Grant they got in 2017
Team up with all the big players
And why are they saying that they're going to send them to jail
If you're on the inside why you doing this to the people you're working with I think what we're saying here is push back
But he said the people at the tech people are saying wait a minute we're the ones who were taking the full-year
For these guys they get all the credit they determine what hate speech is
They get to fight their enemies and we get to pay the bill
We're the ones who look bad because we're censoring people dancing to their tune
So I think that notice you'll notice it notice that Sacha Baron Cohen said nothing is enough it doesn't matter what you do you have to let us
So if you listen to that clip one thing it's very important to point out as the only evidence for E Michael Jones as fiery as his imaginary
He's decided that it's a case that
This is pushed back because he thinks
The tech companies are getting mad at
The ATL for being so controlling
Look like that look like the bad guys are censored people
Jones is just assuming
That because of his own feelings
Clear instance of Jones pushing a sort of Jewish
Puppet Master narrative
Traditional antiques
From the protocols on down to everything Alex Jones says about
George Soros the notion that the shadowy group of elite Jewish people control things from behind the scenes
If I do it bankers
Is one of those lingering characterization
It's used to incite people again
He preys on resentment and unfulfilled desires transforming what isn't going right
Your life from being a product of circumstance into the result of Jewish Medellin
That's a worldly that's being perpetuated by John's on this show not being supported seconded
And sold by
This is something I want to make crystal
Clear
Michael Jones isn't outright anti-semite
Alex Jones may or may not have actual feelings
Songs about Jewish people
Structurally built on
That is why these two can have this sort of a conversation where they see eye-to-eye
So long as things don't get to blonde
So long as he Michael doesn't bring out his rhetoric about synagogue shooting victims deserving it
Alex can hear everything you saying is being about the globalist
Because you can do that he can allow his audience
Things to do the same
Weather in
Intentional or not
Alex's feeding izadi
This man and no matter what the reality of the situation is Alex's responsibility
Not to do that
Situations like this are 14 Alex's the greatest
Responsibility
Because these are the situations with the most damage
Is possible to
Who is audience
And Alex is failing
Listen to me this is like a situation where you know it like
Somebody who's older who can't hear as well wants to watch Downton Abbey but they can understand them so that I we got to watch subtitles whenever
Watch this.
Like on the broadcast of this
These guys need subtitles
To explain what their actual
Well I'll look into
I mean you have to assume someone dead
Right I mean
You can't you can't assume
Just did this interview blind no one at Infowars Google
No one
Anyting
But you can't
I don't understand
This facade
Is so difficult for me
Hold up
What does the right way to put it
That the sort of excuse of like I stupid
Yeah yeah really really tough
For me to look at an interview like this
And think
Anything other than
He knows exactly
I just don't
I'm starting
Catalina Direct
Can pretty heavily
Well it's like that
It's likely the fuc
Climate dude that I talk to
About where it's like
You know who he is if you book them on your show you know what your
That's what you're doing
Well
Badoo and anti-semitism
How long but
If you
Google him
And and I don't care
If you
I don't care if you've never heard of the guy and you Google him before he
He steps onto the f******
Stage
Google help me put the difference between that example and Alex is that like you're talking about Mark
Moreno being booked
On like Fox News where there's
Competent staff
The guy who makes me videos hitting stuff with hammer
I could you know he's right away he runs the show is so unprofessional and shity that you could be led to believe
He doesn't give a s*** right but it like I don't believe that anymore
It will probably only to see what kind of social media Rishi have
Exactly
And if you were just doing that about you Michael Jones you my black guy is a lot of fun
Alright
I don't know but that illusion is falling away
So in its neck
Flip going to use talking about the ATL send
Sending people to jail
I think this is his rationalization for it I'll say
You can't have this type of
Basically tyrannical rule over the internet and then say well we're a private
Organization even though you basically have the force of law you can overturn laws
That's we we've entered a new era of History
We're basically the oligarchs can if they want to overturn your law
They bring in that the shock troops might mainly groups like The homosexual activists
The overturn the law in the state of Indiana they're doing the same thing in Ireland that they're doing the same thing as Silicon Valley
No news to you but I mean we're in a war and these are one of the people who have for them
Directors of the of that Warfare against the people of the United States of America
And now the internet's gone for being millions of diverse side
6 having 96% control we're now in a panopticon prison
The leftist Wardens
In all our personal messages all our data we've invested all our promotion into their platform
If you platforms they don't control
This is a very dangerous combination of evil
Yeah and that's why we have to stand up to it right now
So that clip is really important because I think it really illustrates first of all how on the same page
In this interview there in agreement
But if you understand
What they're saying
They're not they're not supposed to
Are not supposed to be in agreement because
Michael Jones believes
It's the Jews
Alex
Says that's not what he believed
Right who are definitely not the Jews cuz I'm not against the Jews
One of the things
Incredibly clear about this
How they're the same
The ideologies something we've talked about
Light on in the
The past
And I think it's on Stark
Display
In this interview
That's something that really troubles me
Yeah I'm really trouble to find out that we're entering a new era where oligarch
Sharks can overturn laws that they don't like that
Terrible thing
That's the other thing
A lot of times when you're dealing with people like this
One of the strategies
That uses making valid criticisms and then perverting what the point
He was with his oligarchs
Controlling things in overturning the laws
But he doesn't
But he's not fine with
People
So in that last clip Jones talked about Ireland
And
That if you talk a little bit more about
About this and maybe one of the closest
Things too funny
What episode is Alex keeps trying to butt in
EduCare
And
Also this
With Alex new
Hey i e Michael Jones believe
This would have been a time
This is not going to go well
I'm interested in article on Ireland
Ireland
What's Concord
It was conquered by a combination of of multinational firms tax-exempt foundations and big
Paycheck like Google and Facebook
Didn't need an army they just come in there they got a beachhead because of low taxes they invited all these firms in
And then suddenly tired that firms are telling him you have to overturn the constitution of Ireland
The first thing they did with the family then they gave him homosexual marriage and then the last referendum was
That one abortion
All those rights were just taken out of the Irish Constitution
Now it's late grown man
Coronavirus Ireland
Play freedom of speech that's in the Irish Constitution this is the way war is waged in our day
Exactly
This is how Wars wage and the new Sacrament is full grown man with our children it's really needed to get that in
Really had to get that one in 802
I really need you to reconnect your lies that into
Michael if you heard my Rifts about to drag queen story time
Cuz I really like to do one right now
Find the article that Michael is talking about here but I did find an interview did recently about Ireland with a noted
Far-right provocateur name to Rowan cross
It's fresh and
To be circling around the idea that Jews are sending immigrants to Western countries to attack logos
He's got a
He's got a focus
Yeah the things that he Michael is talking
Think about happening in Ireland or very specifically things that he has blamed the Jews for in the past
For instance as it relates to homosexuality he said that the Jews are responsible for promoting marriage equality in
The United States
Many times
Event says that Ireland has passed laws providing access to abortion
In a video posted to YouTube John said of the United States
Quote if it weren't for Jews we would not have abortion
Examples using what he thinks are evils that are befallen Ireland were curiously exactly the same things
He blames the Jews
We're having promoted in the United States
It's painfully obvious what he saying here is that the Jews of taking over Ireland
Alex's letting him
Because Alex
To pass that off as he Michael just saying that the globalists are taking over Ireland
You can agree with that
You Michael Jones is Not
Saying that
You saying that
Because I went to the lamb this and agreed with it it has the risk of mainstreaming eat Michael s*** to a large portion
One of his audience
Also the Irish Constitution doesn't guarantee
Until last year it was illegal to publish
Blasphemous
It's still an offense to publish content that's deemed to be
Seditious rndc
They have a group called The censorship of publication
Board that reviews content refer to them as objection
They were film centers office
Ireland is a really bad history Bad Country
Free to choose if you want to talk about Free Speech being eroded
They've a very long history of being a country that's pretty into censoring things
If you want to learn more about that look into the
The troubles
No no they were fine
That's not a great example
It's really
Stark
The way that he's using
Exact same examples
But he talks about in the
United States
Is being things
The Jews have done
And you can see the way they like he bakes
Palatable by saying multinational corporations
Special interest
Groups
Where you do that is that the language of Infowars
I just I
It should be against the law for them to be like
See they're taking rights away
When there
Giving a
Access to abortion
Like when they're giving access to equal rights for marriage equality
Breakthrough
Take on that is
Is that they're taking a right to murder those people
Catholic
Yeah
Extremist Catholics to live in a country where there is no
Acceptance yeah there is no abortion
And I would say that so miniscule
But
Alex
Is
Adeline Adeline
But when the ATL says they're going to destroy you if you don't submit we bend over
Well I'm done bending overlays gentleman
Stay out of this
Unify American
Around freedom and Justice Autocare old Ian black white Jewish whatever
You like the pre-market
You're great
Hopefully you don't wanna kill babies
But
Our Guest
Was it University academic
Tell me a faster
And he got removed at a Catholic University
Because he was pro-life that was decades ago
That's where this reign of tyranny is
That's where it is
We need to get upset at motivated but Americans are so used to
Anyways
Bennett so don't say homosexual
What's a scientific name for your feelings I won't do that
Play mother father don't stay there two genders don't say America should exist don't say illegal alien do what we say to what we say
Point out the shop cribs
The Last Frontier give us control your children
Public schools in Texas day
Men dressed as women come
Silver labs
We're going to have
Time alone with your kids without you knowing
Same group
Chain groups taking over the Boy Scouts
It's a pedophile ring
Very important point
Michael Jones didn't
Say the shocks
For the pedo Lobby
Specifically said the shock troops were homosexual
Yep Alex is rewriting comments Jones made earlier the show to make Jones's comments more closely
Wii Fit his worldview
He's not trying to find areas of disagreement
The distance himself
John's are clarify things
He's seeking to make him more compatible
With the rhetoric that Alex
Put that on the Shelf
Which is terrifying
Also when he says it's the same group that took over the Catholic Church
Be aware of what you Michael Jones
Think about that
Fun bingo
Man
It lives a very simple life I suppose that's pretty predictable when you want to guess
Convenient to me in any way guess who did it
Yep
Alex also largely in the eclipse Peak inflating the ATL with literally every problem he has with modern
Culture
I don't think that the ebl has anything to do with people telling him that is language surrounding gender is
No one is saying that he can't use the words mother and father
Like he's talking about a nightclub but the imaginary people chastise
Infer that have nothing
Things to do with the ATL
Successfully change the name of Thanksgiving
Whatever it is
If Alex wants to make some good faith
Complaints about the ATL he's absolutely Within
Is right to do so but that's not what he's doing
He specifically talking about the ADL as being part of a and maybe one of the most important
Parts of the large
Scale worldwide globalist
He's not speaking in his any specifics but he's using just enough concrete terms that if
Point does get across
He's tired of bending over today
They're trying to get control of language
I'm not there going to
Corrupt your kids
Is in the schools
This is very much protocols s***
U4 protocol number one
Quotes that are used as ground stupid on classicism
Formerly immorality
Into which it has been inducted by our special
By tutors Lackey
Governesses
The houses of the wealthy
Bikeworks another's
Or we could go to protocol number 9
We're fools been used in corrupted the Youth of the goyim by rearing them with principles and theories which are known
Westerby false
Although it is by us
That they have been inculcated
Quote Maria educating youth the new traditional religion
Then afterwards
Consider how often Alex talks about the
Like the state being a new religion
Talk to your kids
By the globalist
This is the conversation to absolutely
We cannot have
What he's trying to
To have about
We're tired of bending over to the ATL you cannot have that conversation
In good faith when your guest is e Michael Jones
I've absolutely zero patience for this low-rent normalizing
Vicious anti-semite
And I have even less patience
Alex Jones right now
If he doesn't know what he's doing
Use the most oblivious person in the world
And some of that oblivious
Having an audience
Is a risky thing
Also e Michael Jones claims that he was fired
St Mary's College
Bookscool first positions on abortion
You said that I don't believe him
This is a Catholic School in the late seventies early eighties
That's going to be a pretty
Conservative place
Politically
Or could be his stance on abortion is I
Should Outlaw abortion
They were like great that's wonderful
And if somebody gets an abortion I think we should
Did you tell him they were like back off
YogaSource away could pass
Possibly
I'm so Alex's discusses how the Warriors here
And
Nothing good
Michael Jones you were explaining were in a war
Dewar's here
And now it's the hate speech laws
By the ATL on American soil
We're going to arrest anybody
That doesn't do what we say and if you point out
These groups are staging hate crimes against themselves we're going to arrest you for that too
So what Alex is talking about is more of his preemptive false flagging themselves
Rhetoric
I just think it's real bad
This is real terrible
I'm super easy trying to ask you Michael about like there's a war here
And in this clip
This next clip is where everything
Up to this point it's been
Complaints about other things
Being presented as
Complaints about the Ada
Yeah yeah
Very inaccurate
And
Coded complaints
It's about their they don't like your speech they're going to arrest you kinds of things
Make it clear that your problem isn't with the abl It's a larger
Thing that you're focusing on because you've made a boogeyman
And out of
So far we've been listening to too old assholes complain racist
I mean it's between continues to be that
But this is this next clip is
Where things
Go off into
A very crazy
Directions
And it mostly has to do with
Yeah I mean you're right it is a war and end in order to understand that you have to take it back to
The end of the second World War
Germany is a conquered country
We have complete United States has complete control over whatever goes on there
And the first plan is basically the morgenthau plan they're going to starve the Germans to death
Is that point the the the adults in the room realize what we need Germany against
The Communist okay
So they introduced the Marshall Plan
And this is the beginning of
Social engineering
Or this is Warfare this is psychological warfare we call it social engineering
We are going to take complete control over the flow of information in Germany
This means that any book any newspaper any play any TV show any movie
He has to get a license
It gets a license from a man by the name of David Marta Kylie V
Who was a Jewish psychiatrist from New York City
He hands out the licenses and therefore they determine the flow of information
At the same time this is happening
Germany is now flooded
With pornography
Flooded with material as soon as the valence reform took place as soon as I got the currency reform
The pornography claims in tons would come in from Austria and the place is flooded with pornography
I might have just been a natural thing after Hitler
You're never going to win against pornography
You're just never going to win
Kind of don't really know what he's talking
Think about but I suspected what
Like the basis of this I think he's referring to the practice
During war
Other people are engaged in of dropping pornographic materials in
An attempt to demoralize the end
I think that's what he's talking about the only thing that makes
The Axis powers dropped nudie pics conveying the message that f****** was way cooler than fighting against the Axis powers
U.s. tried to pretend that they didn't also engage in these sorts of psychological tactic
Text but they almost
I think largely with my e Michael Jones
Complaining about here with the deer license
Sentence for
Stuff going around I think he's talking about D Natsu
Application
Propaganda about Jews
Introducing pornography and
The world as an attack on
Some type of church
Because that is a position that he had stopped with
The problem happened around the end of WWII and then finished
Because Germany
Urban League
The theory that Jews are behind the propagation of pornography is super popular among
Close to Neo-Nazi areas of online
Right wing
They believe the pornography itself is a Jewish
Conspiracy meant to made white matter make white men lesson
Interested in
Basically is a long game towards white genocide
3 strangely commonly held belief in those corners
Is the internet but basically it's just repackaged Nazi
Hitler believed the Jews responsible for prostate
The tution which is preventing Aryan race sorry perverting the Aryan race
And spreading
You talked about it a little bit in mine,
World Devastation which this depravity brings with it are sufficient
Destroy people
Slowly but surely
The Judy ization of our spiritual life and monetization of our meeting and Paul sooner or later be fouls are
Tired
So I mean it's all just
Country package
Fine
So in the seventies e Michael Jones was in Germany
Teaching Ono and he has some ideas about
The evils of sex
To liberate
I'm guessing he got kicked out because of his quote
Super views on pro-life yeah
And over this. Of time you have a battle
For the mind of the German people
Being seduced
Bisexual liberation
It gets more and more intense over this. Of time
Until you reach the 70s when it states the movie
This is when I was in Germany I was a perfect I was a teacher at a give nauseam in Germany and the girls
They're coming into class here are holding the magazine called Bravo which is for
There's an advice column
Buy the man a man by the name of doctor Somer whose real name is Martin Weinstein
And he's teaching the girls how to masturbate
I don't really
Scared to hunt down the Steve magazine
From the 70s in Germany the Joneses talking about here
I don't really trust
The only only kept that clip into illustrate how compatible
Alex Annie Michaels world
I would spend a lot of time yelling about how Jocelyn Elders was trying to
Teach kids how to masturbate with
Depart of the globalist plot
And here you have a guy who Alex's refusing to realizes a gigantic anti-semite talkin about
I call him this teaching German uceta masturbated
The corrupting I want specifically pointing out as a Jewish surname
Michael Jones is a funhouse mirror of Alex Jones
Except none of this is fun
So
At this point Alex invites
Michael Jones back on the show
And
And I'll have you back again soon because you're right on.
Or liberals like joke about this
We're not scared of women and we're not scared of sex
The point is this is a real psychological warfare plant George Orwell wrote about it 1984
Because he saw the plan as a top propagandist in
OSS
And an MI6 and then I was later Declassified
Declassified
Breakdown Society
In the family
And that's what he wrote about a 1984 so
It's early sexualisation
And all this is about people not developing the higher centers of their brain
Been having dreams it's about
Destroying them while they're young destroying their innocence
So I don't have time to flower to fully develop
That's why they're now targeting in the US
We're going to teach your children to masturbate
Nh5 sexualisation of children pedophilia
And you're not going to stop at so it's again a psychological warfare plan
Developed
Alex Trails off weirdly there at the end
Why didn't you say you develop the plan
Is it possible that he knows who e Michael Jones thinks develop the plan he doesn't want to get into an argument about globalist versus Jew
Because I think that's a possibility it's definitely there
Don't think about 1984
First of all
It's not real it's a book
Don't
Inasmuch as it could be
He said that it's
Ballistic Orwell himself
Explain that the book is based on his imagination
Cannabis stalling like government based in totalitarianism
Speaking place in a western country instead of Russia
It wasn't that He Came Upon a secret
Globalist plan and he decided to get the warning out
To the masses through the book
I know that Alex likes to play that
Make references to
The fact that Orwell died just a
The book was released
But that's because you've been dying from tuberculosis
For years that that
Subculture
TV wasn't
Oh you'll be over it sure
You'll just be over it soon
1947 Orville road
Piece called why I write which describes some of his formative experiences
Dabbling in writing
Stent in the Indian Imperial
Becoming impoverish
And coming to a greater understanding
King of the working classes
Use understand decided on a lot of issues
At least until 1930s
Quote
The Spanish war and other events in 19 3637 turn the scale and thereafter I knew where I stood
Every line of serious work that I have written to
Since 1936 has been written directly or indirectly against totalitarianism
And for Democratic socialism
As I understand it
It seems to be nonsense in a. Like around 2
I think that one can avoid writing
Search subject
Alex believe George Orwell was reviewing some secret plan of the globalist because because
The text of 1984 the dystopian imagining of a totalitarian
In Britain
It is Imagine government is very similar to the
The paranoid ravings
Alex's intellectual predecessor
The anti-communist Cold War weirdos like anybody in the John Birch Society or W Cleon skousen
Alex is unable to engage with a 1980
Before because he thinks
It's real
He's unable to detach it from the anti-communist propaganda that he was raised
So to him it reads like just another book from the John Birch Society talking about what the globalist have
Also
As I recall pornography didn't play that big of a rolling
In 84 and the proles were
We're totally allowed to have it and f*** all they wanted
Only control stuff was just
For the party
Yeah I was going to say like I'm trying to go through all the possible dystopic
I'm like Huxley they were they were all about sex but then you have like the
Liver and it's like
You're not allowed to have sex and all that stuff is rigidly controlled
You're going to get a dystopia
It doesn't matter what flavor f****** you're dealing with
Apron you or when the state has
Control over
That we wind up getting f***** over
Then yeah.
Yeah it's not like owed its moral to have pornography or not have pornography
State to control
The larger point
To about what Alex was saying there
They're better take your right on about this civilization
Is
Betty Michael Jones
A hundred percent
I believes it's the
Doing that
That are responsible for the sexualization of culture in order to corrupt the minds of
Everyone
So when Alex says you're right on about this
He's tacitly or not even test
He's explicitly supporting
Something that
Be maybe shouldn't
I find it incredibly difficult to imagine that
He just doesn't
This is to
Ridiculous I mean it's it's
It's either him signaling hey
This was always compatible
From the very beginning
Or him signal
I don't care anymore
And so I am willing to go as far as not
Yeah it's hard to say if it's
If it's any of these guys it doesn't matter how hard
Core they are I am willing to
To Chase
Survival over
Anything else
And it's going to wind up killing
I don't know
Make predictions
Alex asks Michael Jones with the end
Oh yeah
Probably similar but different answers
And it'll take anything over to understand it
How do we counter
What does pedophile called is doing because the ATL is also come out and said drag queen story time is a month if you don't
Big fat men dressed like clowns have accessed your children unannounced
Bags under the eyes crow's feet
The cut off by the brake there
Unfinished thought
But you also see this tendency that he has any
Keeps trying to bring back
The is drag queen Story Time narrative
Cuz I think it feels safe
I think that he recognizes on some level that like
I need this ball to be in my court
And if I don't
Somehow
Control where this is going and could get out of
I am really quickly
You and I can both it
Twistedly agree pedophilia is bad
To explicitly talk
About pedophilia
But if you start going on today to Howell homosexual Czar destroying everybody
I'm not there yet
At Banner if you go on to say how the Jews are controlling everything
I'm not allowed to do that will get there very quick no matter what topic
You talk about this guy
Unless
Yeah I'm waiting for him to just answer everything with yeah you know all Jews are pedophiles and you like talking
Great
So in this next clip is its
The closest that
Really fine
Of Michael
Episode of proving that pornography
She is a weapon
Is a lot there's a lot of fun are
If you talk
What's at the bottom of the
That whole where is all this going
Dr. Jones
Yeah you're right it's a weapon pornography is a weapon and this became clear when the Israelis invaded remodel
They coming to town
Are they take over the TV stations and they start broadcasting pornography
Don't wait a minute I thought pornography was freedom
I thought it meant Freedom so does this mean the Israelis want to bring freedom to the Palestinians
No this proves that it's a weapon
Okay
Is subjugation people is supposed to keep rail them and supposed to be range them and it's also supposed to be
Block any type of rational response to what's going on
A couple things
Things here first it's amazing
Me how Alex is just letting you Michael Jones
Just keep on barreling through with every single example he says about anything negative surrounding all of issues they're discussing
Coming back to the Jews
Every example of individuals he's brought up our arduous
And now the proof he's giving of the claim that pornography is a weapon is Israel airing foreign when they took over Ramallah
Alex legitimately
Has to be the most oblivious person in the world
Or else he knows he's talked to a jacket
Anti-semite
Yeah it's really pouring broadcast
Sing 2002
I'm obviously opposed
But I think my reasoning is a little different from John
Are the relevant reasons the broadcasting
Born is bad but p*** itself is not
Israeli specifically did this because it was offensive to the residence of the Westbank I believe that motivation is important
Factor in this equation
Here's what I mean
I don't think pornography is intrinsically bad
But I do think it would be an immoral act to hijack Jim Baker's compounds cable network
And Airport ography
Before all the Sunnyside residue
One part of it is because you have a reasonable cultural assumption that what you're doing with
Appreciate
But the other part is that it's never appropriate
Force pornography on somebody
What does break the pornography itself bad it make
Hijacking stations that would otherwise be
Be playing familysafe programming
The airport ography Raw
I'm not an expert on this matter and tarred to trace down concrete facts on the subject so I'm going to leave some of the questions here alone
About that specific yeah
Mostly because they're not really relevant to the matter at hand
This incident is now
Not proof that pornography is a weapon it's proof that could be used in ways that are meant to
To cause discomfort in
Disturbance
This is not the same thing
For instance
Heavy metal music has been used as a tool of torture I was about to just
Bring that up that does not make heavy metal music torture intrinsically
The way that it's being used
That is the problem and I don't believe that this guy isn't smart enough to understand
Did willfully obtuse
That's all
Yeah
This is wild
Right
I just
Because it's so
Insane
It's so unhinged and and disconnected from
Any and all reality
Like when you're this singularly focused on
All Jews are evil
Then you bye-bye
Very nature just
Exist in your own world
You exist
Completely separate from the rest of humanity
8 Ball
It's a bunker
Pretty bad
It's told you
I don't want to do this
I hate him
I really don't like him
So they talk some more about this for no issue
Why not
And
Michael Johnston
It's talking about no nut November
Of course he does
Webcourses
Of course
Because because
So he's
Framing this as a boycott of pornography
Amman
He says that people got mad about that boycott there's an article in Rolling Stone
Solo Double J
Pornography ruined excited to work against it
Ruin sexuality ruins the real thing
Absolutely
Absolutely so they said what we're going to take back
We're going to take back our own minds we're going to take back our own bodies
Going to take control of Our Lives rational Morrow Control of Our Lives
Bendy organizes boycott
Well guess what
The pornographers are upset
The people who instituted this regime or upset and there was an actually an article in rolling
Stone
In which the author says that these people
Are anti-semites
If you don't masturbate if you boycott pornography you're an anti-semite
I didn't make this up
Okay
So what you're saying here
In general is
Oregon Ducks losing control of the narrative
What are the most powerful subjugating narratives of our time was pornography
It made an entire generation docile to the commands of their rulers
And now people are waking up to understand that sexual Liberation is a form of control and they don't like
End up breaking up their own change and escaping from the jail
That's the culture has created for them
It's beautiful because people realize that they're getting outside together getting away from their phones and they're realizing all of this
It's meant to give you fake
Satisfactions you don't go out informal relationships
A real relationship
Just imagine Alex f****** gardening
Wow so that article in Rolling Stone is not about calling anyone who decides to not for taking foreign or specifically.
Does no nut November
Anti-semite make it up
That is exactly the sort of straw man version of the story
Spectre raging anti-semite who believe the pornography the secret dude
That's the strawman they would create out of the story.
To attack
To be clear the article literally says quote of course it goes without saying
But not everyone who participates in no nut November or no fap is a white supremacist or religious Fundamentalist
Thanks man
This article is basically about how there's a weird overlap
Between imports not masturbating and right-wing groups
Princeton
The proud boys make you not masturbate if you want to join
Most of the article is about a meme that have been going around
It's sort of dances around whether or not there's a bigger meaning to them
And honestly the article itself seems undecided
On the issues
I don't really feel like it
But have any concrete conclusions about it
The article doesn't say the people do today
Port Aransas
So it doesn't accurately point out that people like David Duke believe the pornography is a secret Jewish
Attack plot
And talks about how there's some people in the morning
The street who received a no nut November related harassed
That was also.
Deeply anti-Semitic
It doesn't mean that they
Hi riddy
The beach
Mission
Is rooted
There's an overlap
The content of this article are not things that Jones wants
Particularly to be looked at realistic
You prefer that the uninitiated not know that he does think that the Jews created pornography as a weapon
Because that makes them look like what he is
Instead of dealing with the article as it exists
He creates a fake version
Discuss
They said if you don't want to look at p*** you're anti-Semitic
And just like that he refuses the rightful accusations of his own 87
And Dodgers the question
And brought up by the article
It's literally the exact strategy you see Alex
Employee constant
When news breaks
10-20-30
That one of the Boston bombers was a fan of his sight
Instead of seeing that
Question what that means
He pretends the people are saying that he inspired the bombing
Thereby creating
Thank you strong
They said I called the bombing
It's so much easier to defend yourself against then
It seems weird that this guy was obsessed with the protocols of Zion was really into your show
What does that mean
It's important to understand this text
But it's also
Important to under
Understand the fundamental reason it's employee
Whenever there are straw man
Wherever you find him
There's also something underneath
The people don't want to talk about and Dan will be there
No other man over his head and tossing it to side
I will not suck you you Michael Jones
Also when you Michael Jones says it pornography quote made a Generation Doll sold to the command of the rulers
It should be pointed out that he literally means the Jew
He's been very explicit about this in the past saying quote
If you turn away from the Catholic Church you will end up a slave a slave to the Jews either through their pornography or their usury
Alex is just
Agreeing with an
Licit anti-semite who is Tony
Just enough to not sound off any alarm Bells
But he still being
Very over
Hopefully for a second Alex dozen
This is exactly what it is
And
Next clip
I think we passed
The line of any
Real
Acceptable
In this next I feel like plausible deniability
Could be
Dubiously maintain
I don't see a little biased
But I think here we really cross the Rubicon
Hitler Hitler wanted sexual Liberation in a use pouring stuff as well and
Relationships why is that why the fascist while one is well
One of the one of the books did Hitler Burns where the books of Magnus hirschfeld
Mom is here spelled was the head of it was a Jew who is the head of the institute for sexual distance
I wonder why
Type of abuse
Germany a conquered country after WWII suddenly these people are
Or let loose people like Mom this year's felt or let loose and suddenly the people are resentful they don't want the corruption
And they turned to somebody like Hitler because he said he would straighten them out
This this this could have happened to could have been shot earlier
Holyshit
If you listen to that clip you have two men contradicting each other
Alex is saying that Hitler wanted sexual Liberation because he's operating from a place
He's supposed to be attacking sexual Liberation as a means of bringing social degeneracy
But also still thinks Hitler is bad
Yellow Hitler must have been for sexual liberation
Which is 100
Is that not true
Conversely
I'm not convinced e Michael Jones thinks Hitler was bad
I'm pretty sure he
Does not
If Alex thinks that the lebensborn program
Did the Nazis Institute account sexual liberation
That says something about him
Encourage out-of-wedlock births
It was specifically about creating more racially pure children
It wasn't like
Sexual Liberation you should be free to control your own body it was more like
Sexual Liberation you should be making more white
So that's not quite
The same thing
The things you generally might associate with the types of sexual liberation
And Alex is talking about where things were brutally repressed by Hitler's government
Tens of thousands of gay men and lesbians were imprisoned many of them sent
The camp something
Subjective experimentation
Change your sexuality
The Nazis shutdown Club Band gay Publications and overall had an attitude that the Jews were to blame for these cultural perversion
Like gay people existing
And as we all know they were on the right side of his
History there which is why America
Kept up the practice until
I don't know
Conversely prior to Hitler's rise to power the Weimar Republic had a very sexually liberated Refuge
There's a budding sexual reform movement where access to birth control and recognition of different sexualities
Gender identities
We're taking over
Even passed a law in 1927 that made it so doctors and have to treat sex workers who came in with venereal disease
Without judgment
And then temperature
The actual issue of Health as opposed to the fake one
Which is marginalize insects were
Naturally they were all murdered
A large part of the scene in Berlin was thanks for the work of Magnus hirschfeld
The very person eat Michael Jones Justin
Listen to the language
Is it that dude is you
Is Magnus hirschfeld didn't exist Hitler
The creation
It's meant to say that this guy is actually
Magnus hirschfeld
Justify Hitler's
So so well
That if he wasn't
You'd expect Hitler to come up with it a fake version of him just adjust
Defy his actions including Holocaust
In case you forgot okay now I remember that one
You know I've read
So many books on WWII I often forget the Holocaust part in whether or not
I was going to rap
Magnus hirschfeld was a pioneering research
Researcher it's the recognition of gay bisexual and trans men and women
Topics that were not being well handled that point is
He was putting that work exploring the idea that sexualities exist within a wide range of intermediary
Really hard to stress how far ahead of his time he was
There's a lot of work being done regarding the
Acceptance of people who
Just outside Bridget views of identity or sexuality or gender to the point where they were movie
It's about gay character
Being played in
At that time there weren't
Yeah yeah
Months after Hitler became Bryce Chancellor he ordered hirschfelden
Berated and the library was burned in a Publix
Swiftly
And Hitler use sexual degeneracy like what hirschfeld was doing
Asthma attack
The Jews
Not to put too fine a point on
But it's very similar to the function
Genevieve Michael Jones
He says cool people these people like Magnus hirschfeld are let loose
Suddenly the people resent
They don't want the
The corruption of their morals
What John says that
That's the same
Bigger plan behind the scene
The hirschfeld was just
Carrying out
Hearts not here that is it basically saying that the
The Jews were corrupting German
Society through promoting sexual deviant
Exactly what Hitler said
Right
Not overlap there
Yeah people weren't resentful of the sexual liberation
Until the until it was used as a scapegoat for the country's other problem
Like what John saying that there was a backlash against someone like hirschfeld that you're trying to say that was the people's will
And Hitler was just curious about the people's will
Is very troubling
That's that's
It's one of those things where
I I it almost like this b******* almost convinces
Is me towards the incremental
Argument
Because anytime you see people ahead of
History
You see them get
F****** murder
Almost
Well hertzfeldt you know
He went he was out of the country
Regardless of whether
Yeah it's it's just like
These these f****** lunatics
Cannot hang
Cannot hang with there with a
Complete
Control over other
It's real
Antecedent
I can't even handle
This is f***** up
The end of that last clip
If you said this could have been taken
In care of much sooner
That alone is a really f***** up idea
He goes on to talk a little bit more about that
Next clip and this is the point where if I were Alex
Outside be behaving
And so many
Right right
This is the point where it's like
Talking to him in the first place
No not at all but if I were
Somehow
Accidentally in the situation
And I've been obliviously Mister Magoo in my way through conversation up to this point
Naturally
Vice versa
Come
This is the point where I would be like get the f*** off my
That this is a point where I just
I can't believe
I fell for it
This this this could have happened to could have been stopped earlier
The uncle of Pope Benedict the great-uncle of Pope Benedict
Wrote a book called a what
And he said
If the church doesn't step in and defend the People by enforcing the laws that protect tomorrow
Order of people going to look for a leader but guess what the German word for leader is
It's truer
And they found it
They found their leader this is the type of reaction we want to prevent here in America
And the way we prevent this is why open dialogue
And able to wear were able to to
Criticize the people who have subjected is
To this reign of pornographic Terror
Doctor Johns
It's going to get worse with the left and their final hunger across-the-board
Is children
I don't give a f*** about Jones
Is bulshit op-ed from Pope Benedict's uncle or whatever the f*** he's talking about
I don't give a s*** because this argument boils down to something along the lines of
Gay people walking around in public so what do you expect to happen of course it
It's going to happen that's why you got to let the church come in and force you out of the public for your own good every time you guys try
Ryan beat yourselves we murder you why are you trying to be yourself
Right
When you Michael Jones says that a Hitler come to power is the sort of result he wants to avoid in America that is still a threat
He's not making it clear on the show but when he talks about the quote people who have subjected us to this rain of pornographic Terror
He's talking about the Jews
So I guess what he saying is that he doesn't want another Holocaust but it will happen if what he's proposing doesn't happen
Which raises the question
What does he want to happen
Well if I understand so far his
General Vibe demeanor and actual meaning of his words
I would say his basic
In order to stop another Hitler for rice
We're going to need another Hitler
Maybe maybe not
I'm not drivable answer to the question of what he wants to happen but Clues
Maybe a decent clue comes from that speech he gave in 2017 even V bear
I thought was a fence
Quote
The Revolutionary Jews are enemy because he has rejected logos
That means that Jews to the extent that they accept honor and Revere logos
Are not our enemies
They are Jews who accept logos fully by sincerely accepting baptism
And there were Jews who accepted and some lesser
Capacity by there. Cilty to the truth
That statement seems to indicate that all Jews convert to Christianity specifically the extreme is Catholicism the Joneses
Except the Christians are right and stay in a docile state
Symptoms of
Be cool
It seems like it would be Jones version of what needs to happen in order to avoid another Hitler situation
Which is
So f***** up
Alex just going along with a guy who has more or less saying that
Jews all need to convert or some
Submit
What happens if they don't converters
Well I mean
I think we know the answer
Well we certainly do from his comments about to like synagogue to the Tree of Life synagogue shooting
You guys you didn't
Converter submit
So
Just unacceptable on every level and I've listen to Infowars everyday for the past
3 years of my
I can't even put into words how disappointing
It is to hear this guy saying things that essentially boiled down to Hitler did what he had to
To do and Alex's responses is the pushback or in the interview it's to escalate things to be in about how they want your key
In the world Alex is pushing
The global student want to want your kids
But Jones
You Michael Jones
Wasn't talking about
The globalist
He's talking about the Jews
It's kind of easy to see how it would make that mistake though
When your whole worldview is based on
Homedics
It's hard knock
Accidentally agree with it get along with an ant
Anti-semite
Honestly Alex pivoting to talking about them wanting your kids and then going off into a little bit of a rant about to drag queens
Feels more like Panic on his part then
Anything else
It's almost like muscle memory
He has nowhere to go with this conversation
This dude is
Pretty much
Applauding Hitler yep
It is too much of a coward
To ask this guy
You believe the juice of humanity
Cetus Retreats into something he knows to go
Like lying about drag queen story
About history
II
You find it
No this the doubt
It has been removed
And when you have
That like
Moment
Particularly
When
You have
This guy
That there was this sexual Liberation that the Jews Like Magnus hirschfeld
We're responsible for her
Carrying out they were let loose in Germany
What are you going to do
Hitler's going to come along and take care of business
Do you have someone
Saying things like
After all the other stuff you said on the show
Yep you have no excuse not know that
The person you're talking to
And would like
How
This you know your response
And the only reason
You fail in carrying out those responsibilities
The pushback or end the conversation
Is B used for
And
II
My feeling on it is Alex retreating back to
The drag queen story time
I'm stuff is kind of a like
I don't know what to
But it would be delusional
To think that his discomfort is in somewhere like I want to end this interview
Because it goes on to
Five more minutes
Dr. Michael Jones culturewars.com
Very interesting only five more minutes with him about the election about Trump where he sees all this going on invite him back up interview
Upcoming book as well
Please remember without you were being shut down
Alex better be real careful with which books of Joneses
The plugs on the air
You can plug something with an innocuous title or you might accidentally plug is most recent book
The Jewish revolutionary spirit
I was about to make a joke that it his most recent book would be too obviously anti-jewish and then you'd
So cool I've seen some comparisons
Do
Unfavorable review comparing it to the protocol
Houses as addiction
No idea
Or you might accidentally plug shylock's using Rams
Are you might accidentally plugs the Jews and moral soup
Diversion
What I'm saying is this guy's bibliography is a Minefield if you're trying to
I carry the illusion
But he doesn't believe
Exactly what he believed
So this is weird Alex Goes To Break
And he comes back
Enemies
I don't know what he's
The globalist great error with the believe that has a collapsed Humanity
Battery is coming down fast but we're miles above them
You're listening Alex Jones Show
That's
Really weird
Are we rebranding this is a show that's about the journey to hell
I didn't know that was what we were doing I did not know that
Female actually
What part of retroactively makes
Brookside stimme if he's just embracing the we're on the journey to hell
Or did he just quickly it maybe he
It was that on the very beginning of the shelters that the first time you heard that
What do you mean
That that little we're way above them on the journey to hell part that's
Did you ask
I mean have you heard that
Not not not the same way I have heard him
Like rif over the helter-skelter music about how like we're coming down
Right we're miles above you
To imply that when we land were on top of the globe
Yeah I bet they never heard it articulated as we're on a journey to hell maybe he just baby
He just was like
Oh I got it now
I got it
I'm just going where we're all doing
My own personal Journey there quick positive
F****** Maria I think
He knows he's on his way to hell
So in the next
Click we see them come back and
And talk
And
I think that this is a good illustration that Alex is still trying to
Pretend that
They're talkin about this
Is not Invincible they're carrying out
Experience their satanic compulsions
That into a political plan
But as you said all they ever do is summon their own destruction
Though that's some instruction
Run lyrics civilization as well
So I can see what you're saying at the wrath of God
A giant thunderheads rolling in a typhoon towards the shore
Isn't long I from colliding into civilization
Alex is really keeping up this facade that he thinks e Michael Jones isn't talking about the Jews
I was just pretending the Jones said that the left summons its own destruction
Unless he said that off are in the commercial break
That's not something he said about the left
What he did say is that the sexual Liberation in Weimar Germany summoned Hitler
Which was
The Jews fault
Promoting sexual liberation
This is absolutely not
Is the second instance of Alex taken
Decided repackaging it
Infowars
Sort of language
When the shock troops are the gays that is a homosexual as they put out on the street
Alex turning that into its the pedo Lobby
Benny's does this here with the you know the Jews Simon their own destruct
Turn in the form of Hitler because of their sexual
Deviancy or whatever and Alex Ortega
The left
Samantha rone
Weird
He does a drone
Does this a lot
You Michael
That thing
Summoner
Struction
He blamed the Jews for the Holocaust and the pogrom
Before I would assume that
He is a talks about this a lot particularly after Jewish people are targeted for
Protects
I mentioned on our last episode that after the Tree of Life synagogue shooting he said quote
You have undermined the moral order
And now don't be surprised
Did people start acting out their aggression
Towards you
Which I guess is kind of his answer to what happens if people don't
Submit orca
Convert
You're the long history of blaming the Jews for things that people do to them
Any justifies it by saying that
Anderson Just converted to Christianity and accept this old logos idea
Go to saved everything
This is
This is I think
Cuz we've talked about the him
On the day of the
Is a dirty a******
Maurice
Fat like
There is an ark
For him to
To take
Back away
From
We're here
And I don't think
Is a
I'd like
Even if he tries
This
F****** episode should be a stone around his neck
He has no Arc
This is this is an anchor
Yes is done
Yeah
End
Anytime if he tries to pay that back towards anything that's even remotely
Positive
I don't give a fuk
And he has every reason
To know like
Just be very public
Betty Michael Jones
Yeah
But even beyond that Alex has every reason to know about him
Because
Alex
Used to employ Owen Benjamin
He got into these e Michael Jones ideas
And went down this road
Alex knows because he
Doesn't have an employee
Used to
And they've had a public Feud about the the idea that Alex
Doesn't
Get into the Jewish stuff
So Alex is every reason to understand that this man who he's now talkin
Is an inspirational figure for a lost
Quote unquote friend of his
He has
Really no excuse
And I'm finishing up this interview I couldn't
Help would be struck by a few
Is it pretty much done
First thing I'm stuck with this very clearly Michael Jones was throughout this interview what he
A lot of it was just not specific enough to fly under the radar but he was pretty over particularly when he started ranting about how Hitler
Who was the leader of Germany needed
People
From reverting the country
It'll be very difficult to hear and say the things that he said and not ask a clarifying
You're almost have to make yourself not do it
Because you already know the
And you'd rather keep that
From the audience
The 2nd
Something I'm struck by is how Alex seems to be going out of his way to
Package of things Jones's saying
And put it into the language of
Infowars
Jones has consistently talking about the Jews and how they're up to no good but Alex pretend that's not what he say
John says
Perversion
Jews engaged in a prewar Germany some of their destruction and as we said Alex Jose
Like you said the left always someone's its own
Destruction
I was really wrestling with these thoughts
And to get a better handle on things I wanted to see what
Some of the internet
Response to this in
Interview was
And communities that maybe don't believe the same things that I do
I came across a site called Occidental dissent
Which had some
Some comments about the inner
I don't have much interest in Reading much
Beside itself
What's the recommended blog links
Conclude David Dukes website stormfront.org in Venice
So I kind of gives you an idea what the editorial line was
The author of this piece says quote
I'm watching this and E Michael Jones
Is dropping tons of red pills
Alex Jones is sugar coating and delivering
Come to his audience
It's hilarious
That's exactly how I
Bad guy at least somebody's got some pretty good analysis what's going on
That's exactly how I would just
Any ability for me to convince myself that it's
Not in some way intentionally
Was quickly leaving my
My body
I have a habit of generally blaming so much of Alex
His behavior on him being dumb and not having anything but
What toxic information streams are
Curates headlines from
I don't think I can accept that as an explanation for what I've seen
Prior to the booking Alex or anyone at Infowars
At every opportunity to know exactly who Michael E Michael Jones was
And during the show there tons of red alert sirens
It should have been going off
But none of it face Alex
He is charmed
And I'm just so disappointed
I cannot wait for him to go
Get sued into Oblivion
For the majority of the time that we've been doing this podcast
Because it took a little while to figure out the lay of the land
Another firm position that when you get past the bulshit headlines Alex found on drugs or Fortune
When you push aside the science fiction books that are movies that Alex
Surreal
The Bedrock of in Fort Worth
Not that it's historical and
December 10th
Repurposed in the end in renaming the villains
The globalist
While retaining a lot of the major theme
We talked a lot about this with a heavy over life
But the protocols and how Alex
Albertsons
Conceptions
Mirror the histories of the blood libel and well poison
Narratives
I've long believed that one of the more dangerous aspect of Alex's
And the world deepest emanates
Is it a paris's audien
Games for hardcore thing
Because Alex has built a worldview that Sophie matically reliant on historical antisemitism
But he's insistent that
Not
He allows his audience to internalized these themes without realizing where they come
When he does so they're likely to
The same things being echoed in the rhetoric of people like Michael
Who unlike Alex does
Not tonight but he thinks
Images of the problem
And there are far greater risk of being hooked by
Oh man I was a huge fan of Alex for the longest time but
Then I saw he's I saw couple videos and I realize he's not
It's something
Globalist man
The globalist the globalist are what they are
The Jews who are doing it the Jews are behind the globalist
The Jews are the globalist
To the globalist
To us
Or you'll hear Alex have an interview with e Michael Jones where they agree
Pretty much across
The board maybe you'll start looking at
Some more of Jonesy Michael Jones's content you'll start
MC like oh my God this guy believes
Behind every
Maybe look at
It's a message boards
Comments
Two people
Saying that
Is just too afraid to say this and you like
What he did at this guy who believe the Jews are
Everything
Agreed
Everything Alex
Who's really
Will do
Is something
That
Because
The world
Are so identical
You have greater responsibility
Protect your audio
From people like this
You have like
I mean instead of actively courting his audience while funneling yours to him
Because Alex is never going to come out ahead in that
Alex isn't going to sway you Michael Jones's audience over to Infowars
No I don't go back from anti-Semitism to just regular global
The only way you do that is if you become more like e Michael Jones
The radicalization pipeline in the states does not
Slow the other Direct
The only possibility
Is introducing
Normalizing
Mainstreaming
His
Ideas
To your audience
Local colloquialism s*** flows Downstream.
Sure
I know the other the other piece about it is
If it's really dead
Disappointing is
Like
You can just see
Very
Clearly how
The
The delusion of
Alex's
Sort of ideas that he
Is worldview isn't based on 87th
Collapse
Yeah
It's now it's explicit
Well I mean
I still think Alex will I have the same rebuttal
You can even fall back
Behind the same defense
Spite
I just
I I think booking you Michael Jones
Is an editorial decision
And I think that's
Enough to signal that it's
Explicit
I think booking e Michael Jones and then agreeing with him all the time while
The same time trying to
To cover for him is the most
Yeah so I'm out
Yeah I'm out on his I'm out on any kind of cover now
Isis
Explicitly
Fight
Nationalist
Anti-semite
Monster
Data to Alex Jones
Time up until now I don't think
He's used his platform in as
Explicitly
Dangerous way
Because like
Critique would be while you're David Duke
And I understand that and he looked
Real bad when he had a 4-2
But
The intent behind it was very different
The at least the pretense of we're going to
Talk about our disagreement
Yeah I'm going to point out that he shouldn't blame black people in the Jews
For all of this
That is a completely structurally different thing
Been having this guy on
And covering
To just shoot. Water
Making his
Believe
More closed
To yours
If he says
Something that is a hot word that you don't want
You would rather he said
Globalist
Switch it's a pedophile
Do something like that
Added into one of your other Neri
Don't allow him to be
Explicitly anti-semitic beak
Because you know that's what he is
Is it you know that's what you
I mean
I can't even begin to assume what the motivation
But at this point
The list of possibilities
Are very bad
So here's how Alex ends the
I hate the Jews
That was a very informative interview Paul Joseph Watson is coming up recommend morose
You like us to have on it showtimes infowars.com
That's not good this was not an informative interview
Wow
I don't know is grbl still available for an interview
So
They come to the end of this
And like I said
I didn't want to do this episode I hate that this is the direction
Things have gone
Although I will say that I was not
Unprepared for this to be the case
Still
I know that it's become that meme
Hate to see ya
I do hate to
I really
I guess I just
Haven't
I had every bit of Hope burnt out of me by cynicism but I was really hoping
That with the Drudge
Turn an Alex's turn away from Trump I was thinking
Maybe
Maybe he'll just
Pointed back a little bit away from from this
Andy
A Linden
He leaned it
Like I think we always kind of had in the back of her head that was
Probably most likely outcome could be a blip like it could just be a single
But maybe they won't be this is an anchor
Well yeah I agree with you and
Unless he
Apologize
Then this
I would allow that made a public apology I would say
Alright
I'll go ahead and
I have to be a pretty in-depth Bubba
F******
It would have to be
Book I would need a f***
Creative non-fiction book about his apology out
You would have to be between the world in me that's what we're talkin about
I don't know it could be a blip in the radar whatever like
Inviting him back maybe that next interview will never happen
And baby
This isn't necessarily indicative of a trend down this road but
Considered with the larger picture of
A lot of the people he's been having on
You get the sense
I I think he knows it I think he knows that he's on a journey to hell and he's trying to take the rest of his with
That is your theory
Anyway I will be back
But until then we have
Andrea
We do have Twitter at that knowledge underscore fight when I go to bed
Jordan was on
Where on Facebook you can download the show on iTunes or other
Podcast app
Believer
Deal
Until then
I'm busy at Clark
I am the juiciest
Ice Cube