Jordan.com
College B
MoneyGram
Who Alex
College.com
Everybody would like a little bit about
Alex Jones Jordan
Jordan
As we enter our fourth year
Perhaps we could even
Sure my question to you is what's your favorite season of lost I'll be
Wow that's a tough question
I mean the first one it's so shrouded in mystery everything is
You're discovering the island what is it about right who is this locked character
Is that a tires point in
Excitement
There's a lot of absurdity
YouTube butts
I don't know it's really hard
To say you love lost so much
Toughness review
I didn't care to
Too much about how they resolved some of the Mist
Of the island I thought a lot of that with Kyle
Kind of soft
In the last season but I do like the finale whichever want you notes very
Polarize
Divisive
But I didn't drive
I would say everything but
The the season where they're traveling
Time a lot
I've not that I thought it was bad
Sound travels to pull off
You could I think I think probably the best
Ava Dazzle
Probably I think it's
The second Seas
Okay
The end of the first season
The Mystery of the
The Dharma Initiative and all that stuff
Starts to form right right
Excellent
Alright this is a lot of feelings but lost
I also know a lot about Alex Jones
That's correct today we got
Last week
Sort of
It was my intention to cover
Last week's
Goings-on on the Alex Jones Show
And get us through enough
The speed and what I did is we start on the 3rd December 3rd
Are we
Until I had enough
That is about what
What form does the San Mateo
Turns out I can make it until 4 I get sick
Of Alex is not
That'll happen so today I will be going over that
Before we do got to take a little moment to say thank you some folks are signed up and are supporting the show
So first of all William
Chanel policy
William
Text Keith
Thank you so much
Next Abigail thank you so much and I'll probably walk
You Abigail Abigail
I'm a policy wonk
Spectrum app
Thank you so much you are now a policy wonk
People who donated on elevator love that very much so pasta
Thank you so much
And Maddie with an i or an alibi was
Technocrat
What's the business
Money off that heroin
So good
Freakishly large
Thank you so much pasta claw and Maddie
Export these grants
Yeah that would be very helpful
So Jordan like I said we're going over the
December 3rd 4th and 5th
Today from last week on Alex's show
I think that they're each really interesting in their own right and one of the reasons is they
Osterley disconnect
Did from each other that sounds right
Is almost a bottle at
Episode
Okay
Internally in
Consistent
Some things are like there's a
Progression going in One Direction anything
Completely
Like a broccoli dropped naturally it's it's very bizarre
Scratching narratives here
In infavorof recap
Need money
Pretty consistent
You're looking for a through-line
It's what Alex needs
I got you on the 3rd it's
Largely about how Alex
Wants to talk to David
David Icke is a guest
2 hours
Best
We'll talk about that here in a second before we do here is how Alex
That gets going on the show
Complaining about Elon Musk
I would encourage listeners and viewers a lot of you do actually
Look into what I say and what I claim because
Ninety-nine percent of the time you can easily just go find it
What is from the globalist perspective
Telling you how great is it all
NextGear
Tesla's going to roll out
Not just bring chips but dozens of wires put in your brain
But it's essential that it not be done at the hospital cuz that sounds to medical and scary brain surgery
It little
Kiosk at the mall
Sign up and you didn't they don't worry I'll robot
Cut the hole in the back of your head and Sheridan wires in there and he sign the waiver forms and then you walk out and all your friends go all your
So cool you're a cyborg now
You're so cool you're a cyborg now I love them
I love that idea and I would also like to meet the if I could feel anything about mall kiosk
Be very put-upon employee there staring into nothing I'd like that brain trip that allows me to enjoy
Orange Julius more only exist in malls
So the story Alex is talking about here is Elon Musk coming out and saying that he's company neuralink
I was working on an implantable brain-chip which she hopes
I could greater merge human and AI intelligence
As well as completely eliminated number of conditions like schizophrenia and Alzheimer
Right
Leaving aside the fact that his miracle cure language is abs
3rd and almost certainly something
DeKalb back up the larger reality is that this is
The project that is not going anywhere most likely
According to the Observer when asked if these chips would quote allow us to ultimately ride the wave of improving aai
I systems Elon musk's response was quote
I think the chance is above 0%
Good
Think right chances above 0% would you mean
It's very possible that he's wrong and the Chance is in fact 0%
The important element of the story is how Alex engages with news
We've talked about this before but it's important and important things
Point out particularly in the wake of that New York Times story from the
From his past employee Joshua
Alex says that 99% of
The time you can easily
We find things he's talkin
About Butch from a global
Perspective
That's how Alex
And how he makes it acceptable for his audience
To be completely
Unable to confirm any of the things he says and then Keep On Believing
So the globalist perspective you can find on this story is the media Outlets covered Elon Musk make
Braggadocio
Explain about his company having a Buick miracle cure implant they'll also give people access to quote
A tertiary layer of digital super-intelligent that's what I've always wanted
I look tertiary shitt sir
Most of those articles are critical about Musk
In general and more specifically about how Medical Science and the understanding of how the brain works isn't even close to a place where something
Sing like what muskets proposal
Could be done
Experts I've heard talk about it seemed to think the
The most likely outcome of all this is just developing better versions of already existing technology to do things like him
Improve prosthetic limb robotic
Wonderful biologist who spoke to businessinsider call the plan to merge AI with human brains
Quote aspirational Fantasyland
While giving the caveat that it's
Hard to predict what would be able to do in like 30 years
A I hope that's not aspirational
That's terrifying that's that's Fantasyland that's nightmare
Well of artificial intelligence controlling our very own brains
Feel like aspirational Fantasyland is
Asia value neutral
In some ways
You could have a terrible fantasy
That's the global Express
Activate
According to Alex this is what you will see
Right if you're one of Alex's listeners you'll try and track down the story that he's telling you know
This is what you'll find and it doesn't it all match Alex's tacos
Brain surgery being done at the
The kiosk between the Auntie game
Pretzels in the Hot Topic
But that's okay
Because all the stories will find are just
The globalist
Perspective
Their spin on the news where is Alex knows everything
He's researched everything
We can read between the lines
His version of it is the truth which is only further established by the
Back that no one but him is saying it
This is just line
But it's structural I
It's a self-aware deception
Because it includes a built-in explanation for why anything you made
Try to confirm
Will prove that he's wrong
It's because he's just making s*** up
He knows that
You can get your ear pierced at the mall and he's a terrific
Wires and somebody's brain
I like I like that idea of his is functionality of the kiosk is if I understand correctly
There's going to be a weird saw
After you walk into the into the chaos
Yeah I saw that opens up the back of your head and then they're just going to jam a bunch of wires in there
Done and done
Problem-solve
What I was reading area Zacks
Actually like a machine
That must
Proposing in
That would implant the
The champ
The chips right
Oh there are wires and actually has one of the biggest
Innovations
Talkin about
It would go from the
To the
One of the problems with the brain
And Sophia is the rigidity of wire
And how can cause damage
The structures in the brain that's what I was thinking that you just
Answer one of the hopes
Is that along the way we'll be able to
The develop more jelly
Psy
Or something like that
Some of them could be used in those medical app
The kind of like a realistic hope
The people
Neurobiologist
At least the ones that I read
The news articles
Deserts of incidental
Certain technological medical advances that come along the way
When someone has aspirational fancy as their target
I prefer those things to the
Kiosk I'm going to go that way
That's my that's my opinion
So Alex gets around 2 after
Rambles about there's a little bit
Does a full segment of
Like it's 10 straight minutes
Of just
Commercial
Suspicious
Exhausting
We does that Migos
And he comes back
One thing I didn't add last segments of the very exciting
That we've been working on
Third dimensionally exercise
When you do it gives other people face and other people
Really excited I can't tell you how many times I walk in the door
Children or my wife or my parents or my friends
Rock face
Infowars carbs or I was in East Austin 20 spray-painted it big up on the side of number password
Bumper stickers all over it and it just excites people
Spread the word and enforce Bensel demonized
Really is now a symbol of resistance
Global stand for
Until I went to my great graphics design folks
I said I want 15 new stickers.
I said I want 15 new sticker
So you did 10 minutes like a full break to break
Infomercial
Goes to commercial comes back
Now he's selling commercial new stickers are amazing
5:45. I thought he was like we only made two
See more stickers that's all we can
Can afford right now
That's next week
It's just
Excessive yeah it's pretty pretty f****** X
I think one of the reasons for that is
But he denounced
The David Icke was going to be on the show
I think he was hoping for a little bit of like
Increase
Exposure attention in the first hour
Then David I comes in for the second
Cannon 3rd hour
And I know
Cuz the people who were in it for David ikard
Can you turn it off
Most likely
So like I said this was largely like this infomercial s*** and
I'm like really trying
Sell stuff and then to David Icke
Rite Aid so here's Alex's introduction to David Icke
Heineken
Hilarious
Remember
British Broadcasting host Sports programs
The UK
Around the world
Many a day
I guess all on the road to the man
Moment
Complete mental breakdown yes
Suddenly so different
Paradigm
View
The universe
This is really funny to me on a couple levels
The first is that Alex
David I got to Saul on the road to Damascus
Gizmo my perspective
2 Chainz
You be fair to say that I definitely had a shift in his Paradigm after he was struck by lightning or whatever happened to him when he was in
Bru B
Compare his experience
Answer that assault
Saul was a Pharisee who is intent on destroying Christian
Then he had an experience on the road to Damascus and changed his ways becoming the Apostle Paul
Eventually being one of the primary forces
Does it spread Christianity in
As well as the conspiracy theory that all Pharisees were lizard people dance
Approximately half of the New Testament is attributed to have been written by
I thought
Conversely David Icke having this life-changing event proceeded to go on Terry wogan
Show and declare himself the son of God
Which is a little bit different of a trajectory
Slightly you can go find that interview and if you do it's sincerely uncomfortable to watch
Ike is just saying these things and the audiences
Who's Laughing witch
I tries to play off as people being joyful then wogan jumps in and clarifies that the crowd is laughing at him
And not with him okay thanks
So goddamn
Uncomfortable
Aspirational Fantasyland
The duty of the broadcast
The second reason this is particularly funny as an introduction for David Icke is the Alex Jones didn't always have such a
Highview of David Icke
Before there was Alex Jones there was David IQ says
Not before there was Alex Jones there was Bill Cooper no
David Icke
Is the Alex Jones prototype
That's really bizarre
Because here's what Alex had to say about David Icke in the year two thousand when he was being interviewed by Jon Ronson
Producers
You just get tired of the real issues
True
Ministers and premiers and presidents
Real meat and potatoes
But it's being picked up
He's got
Punchbowl
That's his job
How many texts
Punchbowl
But Indian league with them to do that
World
He's completely insane or he's working for them
Attack on man
Understand how things work
Alex says the David Icke is a misinformation guy because he says a lot of true things but then throws in the blood drink
Making stuff as a turd in the punch bowl so no one
Ever get
The real stuff
Bill associate the real stuff with this nonsense about vampires they'll just think it's all bulshit
It's so hilarious
Nice to hear
Something like that and imagine how Alex Jones
The year 2000
Would review his own show in 2019
I would go with
If you could just use the same word imagine you call himself a comment
That didn't take long at all embraced all of the things that he used to say where the reasons David I could
The conman
Yes and that's mainly because he's a con
The reptile shapeshifters but he's
Kind of in on that too I don't think he's that far away from it
No he just calls them interdimensional
Other demons
Yeah yeah that would be silly to think that lizard where people
So Alex that continues his introduction this is just one of them or embarrass
Introduction
I mean based on that
Heart Alone
Like the fact that
Alex is more
Into
All of the negative parts
Prior characteristics
But then
Man this is just
I want to cover the Waterfront today
He's been on Hiatus books making film
Here's why should I just had my head down
So Alex says the David Icke is both been on hiatus
And also been making films and books which is not what a Hiatus is now he's on Hiatus from what
Not making bugs in them
I guess if I had to be do assume what do you mean
I think it when Alex says I8 if he means he's not been answering my messages
Which makes a better side could be
On September 8th 2016
See what I gave a little interview on the
To New York City
When he was in town to give a lecture
Everything about this interview is super notable
Because well Alex and Infowars are never name
The entire thing is
The complete f*** you to Alex
41b interviews being conducted by Luke rudowski
From we are change
That's a dude who was down with Alex from day one
We are changing the loose neck Collective of people with cameras are going to yell at people and do confrontational stuff on the street
They're mostly relevant because of 9/11 conspiracies and promoting Ron Paul's campaign
President rights
In terms of overlap with Alex there are few group so you could say we're more in line with him in those early years
The fact that it's lucrative ski conducting this interview
Really brings into sharp Focus
Alex
The changed
More importantly
The actual content of this interview is absolutely scathing
And very clearly directed Alex
Calling him an embarrassment
For supporting Trump has David Icke laying out
Play alternative media's
Basic foundation in relation to politics
Husband
Any fact it doesn't matter who you vote for because
The same Hidden Hand gets ID
Republican or Democrat
Basically the same
Political class
Is in control and us nothing changes is actually deeper than that there is nothing changes but
That that's fair enough
As well
Since the emergence of Donald Trump
Subtly
Much of that has changed
Suddenly Donald Trump
This
Vacuous
Demogorgon
Who
Just comes out with stop
Phrases about everything without
Any substance
Without any
Explanation of how these things are going to be brought about
Plays on people's fears
On people's prejudices
Somehow
This man is going to take on what they call the globalists
As a result of that
The Narrative has changed any
Responsible tentative media from
You can trust any of them
They sold a rigged system to actually it is rigged against Trump
In fiber Clinton
What I see is
Some areas of the alternative media becoming little more than an alternative Fox News
Yeah I think there's a broader indictment of a lot of
Quote-unquote alternative
Media and chat Breitbart in the like it very clearly
Well that's a big part of it from other context clues
This is mostly about
Hey look David Icke sucks
But I mean you can at least say that you
He wasn't to Trump
And he's guilty of the same things that he accuses Trump of but maybe moving
He was one of the many
Along with people like Wayne Madsen and Webster Tarpley what a change of heart about Alex Jones
And this is the most likely explanation for why he's been on hiatus
Hasn't been on the show for a while
Because he thinks supporting Trump is embarrassing
I don't take my word for it
Here is
Here is David Icke saying that supporting Trump is embarrassing
Is foreign policy
Isis
Easter Easter baby
What was his words basically bomb the s*** out of them
Mysticism and alternative media
Stop pushing for president
On the basis.
This is going to be
Transformative
Expansion of this
Worlds
New World Order Global state
It's ridiculous
And why it's happening that's probably many reasons for it
But it's some
Embarrassing for the for the alternative media
That 2016 interview is a shot
Alex
His old buddy lukert asking someone to Alex basically put on the map is interviewing one of the biggest figures in the world of weirdos
The entire thing is more or less an indictment of what Alex has
Comped
Not to put too fine a point on this but David Icke showing back up on Alex's show seems like an ID
Navigation that either icon
Is desperate for attention
Seems pretty unlikely
He has his own Big World Cottage into
History of his own
Point of allowing Gaston who are harshly critical of trump or have been in the past
If you think that there's some publicity and it for him
I feel like they slow pivot away
Alex
Everything you need to know about him
He said in that club
From 19
How about David Icke
Alex has now come to the point where he's a purveyor of all the stuff used to say was a turd in the
Yep he's completed that transition
And now it's so interesting
To see him with David Icke
Being like
Now I also believe blood-drinking vampiric Elite
Yeah narrative Alex spent the last 19 years drinking all the punch and then shiting in the bowl
So I don't want to play a ton of clips of David Icke
This interview is just standard David
Like garbage
Music zactly what sort of person I hate
To talk about cuz
Too boring
To be like Mark Richard
Any simultaneously to disconnected from reality.
Deserve to be take
Seriously
Like I just
It might as well be white noise
So Bland
Anyway
It's with one of those thing I have a lot of curiosity
My curiosity only extends so far
I've always been fascinated as to how David I got so popular cuz he doesn't have any
Estimate Charisma that I am
Some
People discussing
And I think that one of the theories that I find the most
Compelling
Is he went on was already really famous soccer player
Early rheumatoid arthritis
And then he became a sports broadcaster
Guy in in
And started telling me about lizard people I'd be like okay cool
So what ended up happening is he went to Peru
And got kind of involved with
Got out there stuff
He claims to have had a transformative experience that I am saying he got hit by lightning or whatever
Talk about it before and it's like this
Felt
Like electrified and couldn't move and had a vision
Experience in Peru he comes back he goes on the bay
BBC gets mocked in front of the entire nation
Talking about how he's the son of the godhead or whatever
And then he goes on
Speaking tours
And this is how I I've heard it described before like how it transitioned
Into
Celebrity
On its own right
People would come to laugh at him
He would go give speeches and
He would he was just in
Incredibly persistent
And people would like
People weren't going
Because they thought he had a good point
Right go Justice
Spectacle of somebody deliberate
Is ridiculous
That was
Absurd
People would just laugh at this
The spectacle
And then a couple people in the audience will be like this and then over the year now
Keeps growing into an organized group of P
Given enough time you'll find people who the message
Message resonates
With even if 80% of the
80 + 7
Gotcha
Started that
What was it he was 91
It was when he went on
The BBC
And 99 is when he put out the book where I believe that was the first time
It started with the
The Reptilian lizard
Shape-shifting alien stuff
It runs a fairly similar course fits
Yeah that is
Most people are laughing and enjoying the entertainment
Then there's the other people who are in the anti-semitic murder called it speaks to the danger of allowing
Stuff like that
To go on exam
Yeah it is an
Be around for too long
It's not to say that like you should shut down anybody Hussein crazyshit
My life that's that's not the
Ideal out
B
I think
I just think you know what is one of the cost of doing business
In a free Society
Unattended
Yeah
Celebrities with
I did to me David Icke
I don't know if it pains me because I think a lot of people are in
But I'm just now
Yeah I do not like
Interesting at all
I just don't care
I wish you hadn't gone to Peru I don't have it I listen to him talk and I to do not
Have any
You just boring
I don't even I don't even want to laugh at it because I'm already like at maybe if I'd have met David Icke before too much
Maybe back in 91 before I've already got Mark Richards
What what is David Icke have against that
F*****'-a he doesn't have a better butt
Nerva flying him around
So anyway that's not too much to care about with David Icke
And that's most of the Third
So we jump into the 4th
And this show takes on a couple
Different care
We have David Icke interview where Alex's
I'm trying to
Gas
Chase
Those kids say David Icona going to try and get
The lottery
Kids in really try and make the most out of this
Answer the 4th
Is very different
Alex is in a real like they're going to put
I sent to
Machines
Mood
But more important
There's a real world
Wednesday December 4th 2019
And this is the transmission that the globalist
Most human extermination because
We're putting out the reality of what's happening on the planet
We're getting people all over the world to talk about in to look at who is actually in control and what their plan is
As we are living
In a science fiction
Dystopic
Future
The future is here
The future is now
The simulation is real
Waffles are trying to create artificial stimulation
What does Saca stand to it
I thought long and hard
This morning
Before I went live here
About how I wanted to say this
Because it's very nuanced
Don't say it just right
It won't convey the thought I'm really trying to get out there
I think is important for all of us have a discussion
The debate about
And that's President Trump
Okay it's time to debate now we're having a debate about
That's right baby should have done that for years
Come on
Everybody in hindsight is 20/20
Rodger
Activate John
So Alex
Says we need to debate Trump
Like this is us this is big
Yeah he's already
Days past
Donut mocking Trump impression
Like that's a big huge f****** thing and now he's pretending that he prepared for the show
Gathered his thoughts about
About debating
Where is this going to go
And it turns out
It is disappointment
The spirit of God Trump
And office
He's one that's upset with tyranny upset with corruption
One Stop in the status quo
And wants to transfer
Our back to We the People and back to our elected constitutional government
They're a large swaths of folks out there that
Say oh just trust prompt everything's fine
Well we know if you
The information has come out but that is not the case in the Trump he is putting on a nice confidence back that's good
But that he's fighting for his life
It's always America and so is a Liberty Movement
Is it a full effort by us
Politically active economically active word-of-mouth activit spiritually active
We're going to lose this golden opportunity to really
Shortcut around the New World Order and not have to really go through
The worst deaths
So I would sum that up if you know if you want to put that in human language
We weren't wrong but Trump is not doing a good job we were right to do this but it didn't work
Trump is bad but that's not his fault
You putting on a confidence that is great
I wonder if he's just saying that he's
Pretending to be confident
Or if it's a
Con man
I think he's trying to think that he saying but the former but
I think he both he knows that
It could be yeah
Suggestion suggestion
Is that you need to put pressure on
Which is
Whatever
But
More important
Play
Another theme develops
I'm at is that Alex seems
All of a sudden
To be much more
Explicitly mad at qanon
Okay
He thinks it's b*******
So there's a psychological tendencies
Does your circle the wagons and fully get behind the president will you don't do that
By not putting pressure on the present
We know
That the board office desk
Information is Rodger Stone
You'll make the right decision every time but if he isn't given the right information
Shelf
We need to be very very Act
We all go just that kind of attitude
That's the stuff that defeat is made
Victory is what
Awesome
Kick-Ass audience of activists
Disappear
Broadcast
Lined up today I'm going to tell you Trump's biggest failure and get into it with evidence wake up
They look at the biggest positive things about what we can do
So much more today
So that got me really excited
Because
There is a presentation that Alex said he
Paired which always means
He's like well
You'll have your thoughts
Extemporaneous off-the-cuff riffing about nothing
So if he's going to talk about the good and bad of
Will actually be able to hear is prepared thoughts
This is the best you can do
Do you present this
As I sat down I thought long and hard so I can make my point
We're about to launch into
What is good about Trump
I was I was going to say that his biggest failure was probably on flush number 9
That was the one that
Shockingly doesn't come out
So in this verse it with this is just a segmented
From his list of the good things about
Gotcha didn't cut anything out
This is
Political correctness
So the first thing is just the taillights the trumps an a****** doesn't apologize
Yeah that makes sense
That's not a meaningful
No
But that's how
Dysart's list
Where's the next one
Even great saying America's a good Nation we should proud of ourselves
We can believe in ourselves again tomorrow I
That is equally meaningless
If your list of great things president has done starts with he's unnecessarily rude and then he followed that up with you says posit
Things about the country
Vacations dude hasn't done too much that you're in
Yeah that's pretty much I mean
What would that his ideas that Reagan City on the hill speech is all you needed to do is present
It's a soft
Soft list again
Point partnership
Hillary Clinton
Transferred
Secret Tribunal
Beyond even the tyranny of the World Trade Organization
Exiting the TPP is one of the only things
Alex
Can hang his hat on the Trump
Has.
I don't necessarily agree with Alex about what the TPP is but at least this is finally one thing the
Did you
Did Alex 2.2 is proof that he's doing
It's just a little lackluster how for the past three years this is the
Something Alex
Can think of to justify his zealous support
About Trump he's not good he didn't even include the fact that Trump pardoned war criminals that one wasn't
Happy best left unsaid
But we get to more substance
Reactivated
Are carbon
The world leader
An energy so that we can
Self-sufficient in under level of control
I was kind of weird I don't know why you would say carbonate
Nicole
I would assume he means coal industry yeah
I ordered it.
You reactivated our climate change exacerbate
Also I don't think that Trump has done quite as much as Alex thinks
The coal industry
A recent article on CNBC looked at the state of Wyoming
Where 40% of the country's coldisak
Extracted
The article cited a recent report from the US Bureau of Labor Statistics
Showing a 13% decline in coal mining employment in Wyoming in 2019
And a Wyoming state Geological Survey reflected a 30%
Drop in production
In the first six months of this year
Compared to production numbers from 2000
M14
According to the financial times
Coal is responsible for approximately
24% of electricity generation is
The United States
Compared to 48% back in 2000
I think call Alex is saying is the Trump has signaled an opposition to environmental regulations
He's related to carbonate
I'm not sure why he's praising that is be carbon into
History but whatever
It's not really an accomplished
Not as much as it is something I dropped over promise
Anyway
Is the next one
Border
I don't think any president or history is
Opposed to borders
This is just meaningless signaling disease
Xenophobia
Do you think that that's again really soft
Three of these on me
So you get this
Here's the last one
Gotten two supreme court justices appointed that are
Light years
Hillary Clinton
Hanging On by our fingernails
The list goes on and on
So Alex should not be in favor of the Supreme Court picks
The trumps made
Neither of them are really people who are in line with Alex's bizarre interpretations of the law so he has two couches prays for them
I miss being like yours better than who Hillary would have predicted
This is kind of week
Seeing as the nomination of these Justice
May well be the most impactful thing that Trump has done at office
Since their lifetime
Appointments
And Alex can't really even celebrate either of them being on the court in and of themselves
He can only celebrate that they're better than the hypothetical people Hillary would have put in
Just kind of sad
I mean there's nothing really
That's the end of the list
I didn't cut anything out Alex have you prepared his thoughts we can make his point even with
Forget the preparation
This is the best I can do to argue that Trump is good
Is not a deep list
There aren't real accomplishments on here certainly not the sort of list you use rationalize why you change your
Tire life
Does a porta politician
It's sad there's a reason that the Justice thing was the headliner on
His his accomplishments
Betts and maybe it's the only thing that the
Imdp higher-ups really want
Is a bulwark
Maintain minority control until they die what's so f***** up
I would understand that from them
Yeah but from Alex it does not make
No absolutely did not like
They're not in line with his ID
Right they must have put some wires in his head
That would be my absolute
So that was the good stuff
And now things turned
But when it comes
Standing up for his supporters
You shouldn't the Punchbowl
And standing up for Piero's like Julian Assange
President Trump is missing in action
So that's pretty big as an actual criticism
Because
Ed from all appearances
It doesn't appear to be real
Yeah that one strange
And Alex is smart to couch this as like putting a focus on Julian Assange as opposed to him
South or Rodger
Let's do the pure too self-serving and bitter
15 this way you can take her to the high road like Trump isn't loyalty
To these people who support him
I think that's probably really Wise Way
The picture that I don't particularly care about Julian Assange but I would like him to Parton
My buddy
So you got you got like these good thing
Things that Alex is sad and most of them were like he's rude you like some Erica
He thinks we should have a border they're all just
Superfluous nonsense
Yeah I'm going to get like a kritikos like
He doesn't care about us
But that's not it
It comes to getting the justice department
Criminals
There are reportedly at least 20
Virginia Maryland
New York outdoor areas
Individuals in the FBI and other areas that engage the whole fake russiagate
So Alex wants Trump to lock up his political enemies and he's not doing
Which is a real
Stumbling block
You know the rhetoric
Half of the people who voted for Trump probably just wanted him to put Hillary in jail
Okay you can retire now or whatever I don't care I actually don't like you but you did say you were going to lock her up lock her up
Up and then you can serve out the rest of your term make all the money you want
Will vote you out in 4 years we all had a great time
It was cathartic
Are you dressed
You know it's it's weird for me because I
I still think a lot of this
Trivial
But
These critiques that he has of trump come from a real Earp
Place
Then the
Praise but he has
In terms of the substance of getting out of the TPP is really about the only thing that
Alex
Can wheelie
Like I said hang his hat on
Where is here we
To criticisms
1 is
He's left me out to dry along with Julian and Rodger Stone right
Play the next one is
Hey our worldview really depends on the idea that
Attacking these globalist that you're going to help
Those are two fundamental
Talib
Problematic thing
For the
Narratives in the world view of Infowars
These are robust criticisms
It's a little bit like
It's a little bit like a delusional guy
Goat giving a pros-and-cons list for the woman that he wishes
Is that he was dating a
Wellpro we are going to get married someday live happily ever after
Conshy absolutely hates my guts and doesn't like me
So there is you know I think I think I should stick with her for another couple
Years but
We'll see
It's yeah it's hard
It's hard to make that equation
Yeah
Be able to much longer
Particularly after he starts talking
About how Trump is also in bed with Silicon Valley
When he came to Austin he was hang
Hanging out with Tim Cook
That's no good
Cook's in bed with China
By the transitive property
Trump is in bed with the chai, exactly
America's America's Best
Blocking everything we do up front
Antonio election meddling in Republican ads
And everywhere
Members of Congress the president
And he just sits there
Where is Ivanka
And Jared Kushner going to dinner with all the big stores on Valley people
He's letting them do all of this and is presiding over
Applebee's
Vai Global takeover that will destroy America and every free Society
He just did what now so Trump is apparently guilty of treason
That one is I okay
So he did get rid of political correctness
Sure he is also guilty of treason
It's hard
To say that that is putting pressure on some
Somebody
It's hard to say that that's like an accusation that you're making
In order to like
Get him to let you back on face
Facebook or something I really like the Supreme Court Justices he appointed that's really great
It's but at the same time I do think he's guilty of treason and us should be hung
I do think he's presiding over the destruction of all free societies
But I like that he's rude
And I got to be honest
Love me some Porters yeah
I mean when you look at this the balance of this is maybe a little
Heavily skewing toward the negative
You know what's fun though is honestly I do think that that is such a streak
In these these white nationalists
We need our borders kind of stuff is
I would rather the guy who I literally think will destroy the world
Then the woman who would let in three Brown
Like it's it's
I do think there's something to that for a lot of
Maybe
Then maybe you might be right
Do you think though
When he was rushed out to break
Do you think he
Came back from break
Inside ala
I said Djokovic.
I didn't mean
It was just a heartburn
Do you think you said that
Kind of yeah
Doesn't
What I didn't say that President Trump was guilty of treason
RockShox is true
Bum bum bum
I'm guilty
Guilty of treason
F*** you
We sit here and we accept he will only accept corruption
We don't fight against it
We give into it and we compromise with it
We become guilty of
We're taught by the system that sin is
Thinking of female form is beautiful or eating too much food and others
Extensions of that gluttony your luster
Whatever the case may be but
Alcoholism
It's just being a coward that's the real
Thou shalt not be a coward for a long time
Pretty sure that one wasn't it as apparently she wasn't at the top of the list
Some permutation of like being brave
You know is
Is spoken of positively throughout having moral character
It's definitely didn't get rid of the rest of the list
But
That's all saying is
Therefore
You were all guilty of treason
Because
Man Deuteronomy had so many Sims in there and I really don't think any of them we're just straight-up cower
So what I think about that that's a remarkable because Alex is doubling down on his Trump is guilty of treason
Rowlett the same time undercutting what it means to have committed treason
You taking it out of the political realm and he's putting it now into
The spiritual Realm
Yeah it kind of It kind of sounds like
Rather than
Is it doing the the classic like
Like I'm sorry
His way of apology is
Is Jaclyn Keys over here and don't look at what I just said
Yeah yeah yeah I think so
I didn't get to way of like I mean if I'm being perfectly on
It's a way of walking back what he just said what
Without walking the back
Kind of
I mean
Using his own terms
Stop being a coward not owning your position
But whatever he committed treason and now let me explain to you why treason has no meaning whatsoever
And I'm by my definition of it
Alex
We're about to jump
It turns out
Do you remember the third Alex is talking about Elon Musk wants to put those branches
Chips in your wires
I don't start scrambling a little bit about how there's a space
What's going on
Google and Facebook
And I know I don't remember if
Have the fold breakdown in the
But basically what his ideas is
Is there companies that are creating their own like artificial realities
That are competing
And they did end point of it will be like you got to choose which one you want to go with
Okay jumping
I'm leaving their artificial simulation and that's apparently now the end
Game witch
I don't remember being in his documentary endgame
But anyway
He was a real revolutionary
You would understand
But there is a race like a space race
For the gold in the 40
9 +
California
Or one of the Wacky Races
Rat race start growing at
Absolute place first
You can get everybody the most addictive
Tips into the brain
We want to dominate your life
Decision made by the computer
Interface with your brain
Giving you unlimited pleasure
Delivering you the unlimited pleasure
The best
So you will choose our company and upload your Consciousness to us
That is Satan
Angels I want you with me I'll give you anything you want
Just put these wires in your brain
Sounds like a good deal then it's going to be hell on Earth
Call shims you give up your physical body
Machine
Uneasy
Okay
Are sending all the humans
He talks about this a lot of
I love
I love that I love the way you put it
It felt like oh my God the aliens are real or anything is there an is there an inconvenience you like these damn
Stop it with the traffic
It's like how you think about like
Rodents
Apostles eating your garbage or something
Yeah
It is a nuisance
Please alien
So if you don't understand entirely here's what Alex believes
There's going to be
Enticements of uploading yourself
Put into these simulations that are in
Artificial reality now what's going to happen is there's going to
Tubi
A situation where your your body will have to die in the process of the uploading right
Two people will go ahead and do this
Now
People who are running the simulation
So already
Created
Wheatley realist
Assemblies of you based on
Voiceprint
And I all the spying the to the globalist to do natural he'll be able to create perfect versions of you inside the artificial
Reality they will kill your human body your soul will be uploaded into the Demonic realm whatever
Clear
But is artificial version of you
Not you
It is not your soul okay it is in the computer and it will be used
Other people to go along with hey it's
Really cool in here
It's real great y'all should do it so then everyone will die
Right to have themselves put into the artificial reality
And apparently there's also stuff about
Like cyborgs
Shirts
Okay so the global is Ultimate plan
Is to make us all NPC's in a role play
Yeah
Yeah I guess so cuz NPCs don't really have any venomous or yeah or any any agency
I talked to him we're all going to be a shopkeeper's in Skyrim
Yeah
Alright
But you won't
Experience
That
Your soul will be in the demon realm or Saturday
He's not he doesn't spell that one out all too clear
How this stall is uploaded somewhere else
Like beef
I don't know
I just don't
All right we got to squarely in that David Icke category of like well can't look into this
Elon Musk hasn't made any we're going to upload your soul into the demon Realm
Comments at all
Okay he is
Alex.
Drop
Deeply
Classified information
Really excited to do it but also kind of mad
Aaron's
Brains
Literally Garden classified stuff
Elon Musk his meeting with
They already been delivered out of the Moon
Mile run over on the dark side number 3
3D printer
If you even believe any of that
A Jones
Really go further here
So we got
So I guess Elon Musk working in concert the printers on the moon to create
Based on unspecified crater on the dark side of the right
Will not stop getting in the way of this Dark Side of the Moon crater nonsense
This is deeply classified information
Is it the is it
Okay
So Alex
Shrew
Is basically
Advanced AI
Really old rebel system
System
Your riffin
You are ripping. Shut up
And so just interchange aliens for demons and you got it
These damn demon
I don't know I don't have to replace your good to go
With blizzard people we're all on the same page
Speedway
Nothing is real
I would prefer to be in a simulation is an NPC that live in the world that he made
Stop thanks
It's tougher this
Ksubi
Position
Very
Research
Really like a news organization just making that s*** up is because Alyssa's
I have heard a guy rip out
S*** before poorly
Many a time and that long like
Chocolate
Same bringing a bunch of system exactly struggling
I would just say that it probably is just him pulling from like
Memories of Bee Movie
Syfy
Like just coming up with whatever
Makes a compelling narrative ancient Satan might be Event Horizon
That iron
Something Iron Sky
Now that I know they're Nazis on the moon
She's on the dark side
Side of the Moon Nickelback
Pulling from
In order to build up the
This narrative
A butt
He's not going to back down
Alkaline this pretending the
This Moonbase
Like this
Classified information
Is real and then he starts shooting on
Really really super loud
Care
Wheel bearing right here
Sad
Man
I don't know I don't know man
I just don't know
I just I'm starting to see all of these people as
As like one giant convention
And they all just have boobs right next to each other and they're all all all kind of hate each other
Listen to the guy next to me
Formation accept each other for
Validation
Promotion
There's a Taco Bell in a Baskin-Robbins
2 in
Text at like
In the same way that Mike cernovich had a little season they didn't reward
People that drift into each other
Spheres of influence
It's like a Premier League
Somebody's somebody gets relegated at the end of every year
Dialects and Barks on what I would describe as a
Derivative
Standard boring rant about the devil
Okay on for quite a while
And it's not notable stand on the deck
Anti
Okay
Just want to be clear
Strongly handsome Harry
So I just wondered
I appreciate you asked for clarification on that last anyone
So yes is long boring rant about the devil
It's not notable in any way except for how we
We are overrun with the slug
Fellow human that sold out to the gremlin the chief loser
So he doesn't fight the AI take over unless it goes
Through
He is an agent of Satan
So now we're opening up even the suggestion the Trump is an agent today
As opposed to just
Committed treason
Psychic
I think we're getting pretty strong scents
That's
Alex's
Really flirting with
I think he thinks
Rent though like I think yeah yeah yeah
Fueled
Look at it feels in some ways I can specially cuz he framed this is like we have to put pressure on Trump
Pressure on him feel like I'm willing to say stuff like
Yeah you understand I'm going to be gone
And I don't think solutely now that's where things get really interesting because we're recording this on Monday
Stay the night
And just this morning
Owen Shroyer showed up at the
The impeachment
Hearing in the house
And started yelling about a bunch of stuff and had a score today
No I don't have it because it hasn't happened
I don't know what Alex's
Is going to be probably giddy
But if you really look at it with variant
Is what they have done by doing this.
It's not endear themselves
Delta Trump at all
They have made it that much more likely the Trump will not do the things
Is that they want to do
Like they want him to enact all this social media stuff in order to get them
Access to Facebook and Twitter and
910 YouTube again
They want him to do all these things that would directly benefit them
And by disrupting the impeachment inquiry
I think the Optics are impossible
For Trump to do anything
Did signals support for Infowars
Zenna becomes a transaction
To an extent
Where we're going we're going
Tending to be a news organization
A doing completely activist nonsense yeah trying to scream down Jerry Nadler literally the f******
Boston bombing
Prescott
Yeah absolutely
You know I mean that was still like under Deval Patrick in like
Official people do a press conference
This is the f****** house a little bit different I will admit
He wasn't already there yet
Sweetie
Like it's an intense
Disruption
I honestly don't think it's
Meaningful in any way other than to demonstrate like
Infowars
Desperate desire for attention
You know coverage
That is like the only thing that he wanted
Witcher
Yeah that's good I mean that's good for them I guess they
Pull up a publicity stunt like this and feeds them
Whatever attention they need for a little bit
Yeah
Can't possibly
Get them to where they need to be with Trump
So while you have Alex going on this rant about you no like Trump may be an agent of Satan
Really appears be like I'm leaving I'm leaving you can stop me I'm leaving yet
They going public
The stopwatch
That much less likely that Trump is going to do the thing that they're asking him to do for them not to
Believe
Almost like a self-fulfilling prophecy
I mean either that or it's just an admission that they realize he was never go
Going to do it in the f****** purse
Possibly if anything's going to happen we have to make it happen.
Ourselves
And we can't rely on Trump
Obviously
Which we should have known from the jump yeah it's really hard to tell the motives that
Outside of just sheer publicity hunting
Like it's kind of tough to tell where they like
What are you trying to do the number one is always going to be I want to get Infowars trending right that's number
One on the list
Regardless of any
Better that's definitely
Play trivia question
Becomes like is there
Some other thing you've
Right
And I just don't I don't I don't know
I think I think it actually
It hurts them probably
With Trump yeah yeah I see that especially
I don't pretend to
Trump
But I would assume
I would assume that even he would be like
Good
No let's see are there any positive
I mean other than
Once again turning the hearings into a
Circus which I guess is
The only thing that
Would enjoy it
You know
Yeah that's that's it but it's a short-lived
Circus Yankees removed
They can move along with
Their business right like it has an impact on the action
I don't know it's it's interesting
I look at
More from that prism of like this is shooting yourself in
And
I don't know if Alexandra
Really
I might be wrong
I might be wrong I mean
Trump
F****** pardoning war criminals
It seems like that would be
A short leap
To being like
You wait you disrupted the impeachment hearing
Rodger Stone goes free
Right
Hey depending on what you just about to get a different Prisoner Part
Iaintasaint world that doesn't happen
I don't know where we are
So Alex gets into yelling about how
There's no man
Anymore because men would fight the globalist
Sure if there were
But there are
Especially not Trump
Wow maybe
Okay for the average man
What was happening and nnn ever felt the animated contest of engaging
Turner discernment on would never
Want to just screw off and play games all day
But
Men are arrested on average at about age 12
Women are arrested about
What
Get the f*** out
You just made that up
Through
Persecution I not been through adversity
I got his f****** puberty
They're trying to get rid of exercise itself
You know Rudolph the Red-Nosed Reindeer
Rankin and bass Nation
Reindeer mean Demi has a red nose
It's a story of overcoming
He has a gift and and the and the other ones are inherently jealous of
I will say on the one hand I'm glad that Alex can interpret the meaning of Rudolph the Red-nosed
At this point with like children stories
I think his batting average
Is pretty bad this one is
Jealous
I'm trying to figure out who the bad guy is that he would
Probably like
The only guy I respect is Darth Vader in this whole situation like in Rudolph
Rob Rudolph
I know one of the other reindeer
Dad
Home and he probably identify so much with Rudolph though his dad was probably like
So also Jordan this guy has no one's Banning Rudolph the Red-nosed
Disagree I have done it now
Alex's
Talking about a video that The Huffington Post put out last year around Chris
Which they even clarified was meant in jest
It was more or less just a compilation of people joking on Twitter about how the story of Rudolph is
Is problematic
Of course this became the focus of a right-wing out Reagan actually in the 2018 War on Christmas
Is there a bad and now I guess we're doing it at
Yeah no one band Rudolph is just a dumb Huffington Post article the people like Donald Trump jr. over react
Yankton Sioux and that isn't
Example Alex can come up with when you talk about kids
These days they don't have any advice
Varsity jacket
Finger development
Ridiculous
I was
1520 years ago when you first got arrested when they outlawed dodgeball
Who's got time
It's a tough time for us
All we could do with ribbon dance
Call Emma Delarosa at 10
Is that
Alligators
So each of these episodes
The third fourth and fifth all have
Terrible gas
Check we had
David Icke
Aeroball in on the 4th
We've got
Gavin McInnes
Leader of
The proud boys even though he's not anymore
You still always will be no kidding
So Gavin
A lot of this is about China
A lot of the interviews about China I was wondering what the proud boys thoughts on
He's not with the proud boys anymore
Easy
I want to be clear about this cuz what he's going to say is going to say
Tremendously races
And it's I don't know if it is as bad as it sounds it's only Monumental erasers does clarify
By the way
Chinese Americans
People who have moved
To America
They
Are very compatible with the United
Okay
Cher
China
Itself
The way China operates incompatible
With the United
Okay
Do you think about me relative like the government is not the people
Kind of he's trying to make that Arc
Yes okay in In fairness
Okay
But here it is
Just dumping
But the way they see life over there
Is totally different
Then the way we see like they don't value the same way we do
I'm glad you make that point you know
Asian-American
Virtue signaling a squishy
They are the biggest supporters in Florida
Population
So Alex you're saying that Asian Americans are the largest Bloc that supports Trump outside of the white population
Hispanic
I should tell you that in the 2016 election Trump won a proxy
27%
Deviation America
The most generous poles
Someone suggested the number could be much lower than
The Asian American legal defense and education fund
The more in-depth survey and they sounded 18% support
For Trump lower than previous Republican Presidential
Candidates Mitt Romney and John McCain
They're pulling codes
Pretty troubling indication
Eroding
Support for the GOP in Asian-American
Communities
In 26
Like they're finding
20% of self-identified Republicans
Voted for the Democratic
Okay
That's probably not good no Republic
Or Trump
No and that trend has not stopped
Vox published an article in May 2019 that the headline quote
Trump could be turning asian-americans into reliable Democratic voters
Part of this was based on a 49% democratic voting rate in the Asian America
Community community in the 2014 midterm
Compare 27
27% of Asian-American votes going to Democrat
Exit 28
I'm not sure what Alex's what he saying is true that the Asian-American Community is Trump's large
Just block of support outside of people
But he's presenting it as if it's
If you believe that's true
Is a sad brag
Considering the overwhelming evidence
Is that the community is moving
Pretty solidly to the left
And a lot of that is directly in response to Trump's rhetoric and actions particularly surrounding it
Which is even more
Likely to create a severe back
Clash in order to try and maintain a
Minority white rule
God I hate this
So annoying
A lot of this
Gavin interview it's not very long
And it's just
Kind of boring
They don't throw any access or some s*** don't they always get together in like hit each other a little bit
Really what it is is largely
Gavin just saying like
Flippantly offensive things
I'm like What's the value in listening
Who gives a s***
Kotori funny
Exciting things that Milo posted on Telegram and like
Make a call reference
Tommy Robinson
Okay
Cool cool
Yeah it's just a meaningless interview
But there is this funny point
That he's complaining about people at like
He gets into argument
It's about abortion
Right and
You know what they say is there
Pro that's now
Hell yeah I did not even say that they are
I think there's something else going on that
We say we're pro-life of Rancho abortion
You're in New York City it there so radical that I've met many people who go yeah
Abortion is murder
Murder to go well I don't know where to go with this argument here that's exactly the fork
Of course they want to end the conversation
Bye
Shut up I'll eat.
You suck yeah I love
Ooo do you guys you guys are not even protein
Sure
I'm pro-death
Leave me alone go away
It's that it's the same thing with Alex talking about people at abortion rally
You're f****** with you
Engagement
You're an a******
So Gavin has little interviewing
He's gone and Alex gets back into plug-in
And
Man
Lot of the time he's just talking about a greatest products
How you need to shop with Infowars
Just plugins on a little bit of a different note where he's saying if you spend money anywhere else
Sporting something pretty bad
Sales running right now in Fort Worth, or AAA
Dubai 3313
Bayview Auto shop at Walmart or Dick's Sporting Goods or Target their funding anti-gun transgenderism
Five-year-olds to Dad the right taken away and then
Squeeze chute
This is all mainstream news lights and gentleman
To the family show
Dick's Sporting Goods you're right
Okay let's see
I do like that method of inspiring
I don't really understand where else he has to go from a marketing perspective like we've we've turned it we've
This from like
Extreme
Panic
To let you know you need to support me by buying products we're going to be gone in a year if you don't buy our product
If you buy from anyone else I'll cut your kids genitals off
I don't know what else I don't know what the installation can possibly be if this doesn't work
One step in like and it is freedom fries
If you if you buy anywhere else you're supporting the French or something like that and then later on you can go to
Your kids
Their genitals chopped off man that didn't play back the last time
Fair enough roundly mocked
So
Take a break after this ad
Pop quiz
What is Alex believe in
Free or post-trib rapture
Hell yeah you know what it turns out
He's pre-trip globalist
Pre-trib rapture
Surround your world government Christians getting persecuted
Coming
Bible
Armageddon
Is it
Could
The pre-tribulation
After is only 180 years old
And was developed
There's no need to do anything it's all handled by somebody else and he is really Swinging On Cue
Like he's been pretty
Subdued on that note he's made overtures towards being against it
But of course also
Sort of a cool with it back when
He was trying to do his own version with jealous jealous of it
Yeah yeah
But now these this stretch you really see
Taking some shots
Seems to hate them
Yeah I think he's I think this
Like a a hole
He's having a rough time now that he's got two
Turn on Trump
I hate that I'm finally going to tell the truth if you hate if you're starting to turn on truck then it would
Lend yourself to be anti cubes
Remarkable things
Videos
Staunchly program
EXO
Another layer
And also a real dick thing for him to say that their whole idea is
Nonono everybody else is handled it while his whole idea is pay me money and I will handle it for
For you
A lot continues
Do y'all about the rapture
How much she believes
Revelation
Literally
We are going to be living on literal hell on Earth billions are going to die it's going to be
Falling away from me
Drooling and nobody's being pressured and that's good cuz they're going to go to the real Church
Fit inside of them in the ratio of God is to be a Revival
Active wish we never seen
You are
God is going to send
We are uploaded the god of the people
Going to get killed and then rise again right up in front of everybody in Jerusalem
Kill these people
Imagine that point
Think about that
You're going to see all of it.
Evelyn change
Oh okay
So I kind of kind of honestly believe that if he
If he was if he was pre-trib rapture
He'd be pissed
Probably want to take a swing at God
Yeah well I mean the hardship is
Half of the fun for you
Like the concept of living through the
Being so strong I survived the whole thing even though billions died I'd
Did that's like his Amazing Race whatever like
His version of Survivor
Yeah man alright
So Alex is
A lot of this
The lot of us
A lot of devil ramp right out of Revelation talk
But then you get blindsided by
The news the truth
Those two
Just step down that could either mean they're putting work level up then
Operation to remove
War Machine
Realize that started
Putting it up on the screen
That's a to Google execs
Steps down
So I'm third news broke that Larry Page and Sergey Brin
We're stepping down from their executive roles
Google's parent
Alphabet
I'd remind you
But Alex's reporting Mississippi
Breaking news in the third hour of his show on the 4th
He can't possibly be doing any preparation for his shows or else you would have
Sing this news on the morning of the fourth before you start it
It's just inconceivable that is processed as anything other than
People showing headlines and then he rips on them
As for the actual story
Paige and Brandon both retain their seats on the board of directors
And maintain their voting control of the direct
Alphabet
Need to step down from their roles as CEO and president of alphabet
Respectively
The reason for this was that they decided that having two presidents of two CEOs for alphabet and Google with
Kind of redundant
And that the management structure would work better if those redundancies were phased out
As such in the announcement of their stepping down was also announced the Google C
CEO Sundar pichai was going to be taking over as this
Alphabet
As well as staying on his butt
Your Google it's corporate RaceTrac
Here's an article that Alex didn't read and he's just guessing
He thinks they're going to either bring in worst worst globalist
So Trump is making
Has moved but in reality
Streamline
And you would know that
If you read the article
I think the way I was reporting the stories partially an attempt
Fully turn on
Just yet
His entire grape
Foot drop is how we won't take action against these tech companies and you can see how eager Alex's
To take this headline that he knows nothing about
It turned it into a paw
Possibility this is the long-awaited answer
Search with prayer
He's looking for excuses not to turn
But I think he's just going to keep up coming up after you
I don't think it's
Yeah I mean
Because everything that he thought Trump was going to do is imaginary and he wasn't going to do it from the first place
Right that's just you just can't live on imaginary food for that
Miss Isabella
Now
Can't do that
Swapno
Brightly colored flop
So Alex
Schism to a little bit of bad head
Space as this show wines
He starts
Screaming about how he's going to start a bunch of new shows
Yes
Now old man house phone coming back
What's great about that
In the past Alex is always talked about how he's going to go
24-hours he's going to give all of these people show Absolutely
There's a slight difference in how he's talking about it now see if you can pick out the different that it might be
Obvious
You know what
Haircut at 3:30
Double H
By the way I'm going to start I'm committed it today
Seven days a week starting a new show
Today
That's not good
I I can't I can barely feel the three hours that I'm on today and now I'm going to go to a
At least
9 total hours add a couple more hours of me talking about the devil
So the main difference here is he doesn't pay anybody else
I was going to hire people who just called in and I assumed that they were good enough for show but
Man it's just got to be me
Just got to be me
I think what you see
Here is
I think it's pretty well reflected in like
What the times that I've gone to banned. Video is YouTube
Clone or whatever
You go when you look at the light
Anyting
Are the other house
David Knight or Owen Shroyer
Dear such diminished
Audience
Right Paul Joseph Watson also isn't as much as I
But that's because you know you at he's also elsewhere
Yeah it is no need to bottle that
And if I had to guess
I would say that his ability to drive sales
Is
Soundly better
Then these other hoes
So when he does this even if he's not paying people like the callers
Call Lynn hoziana or whatever he's not paying them he's still losing money
Cuz he has to have the crew they're like
So handsome
The bandwidth
Or whatever I write overhead is so high
A call-in hosted show is not going to move the
The product in the same way that Alex is absolutely is like if you buy from Hobby Lobby
General cutoff yeah
That will do it
Old man house phone definitely is
I'm just going to scream out that Walmart's going to chop your kids dick off at trails
Pink spit in the next year in order to make things
Write make things
The ledger balance
I'm going to have to do three shows a day
That's not good
3 hours is too much
For him to be doing of this a day
Absolutely
Not good
Adding more oh my God
I honest
But that'll destroy me
Yeah it's Ryan listen to his three shows you're not allowed the same time. I will take your
Computer away from
The same time the content that will be an hour 8
Will be unbelievably on ridiculous
Yeah that's true also he's not going to do that he'll be on he'll have to be on
Speed at that
Hellboy
Rainforest
Sew-ins
Suit of a continuation
Alex Costa
Calls
This this color here suggests that Alex should
Turn Infowars
Something positive
Well
Yeah I understand that works I just said I think we're this is going to go but it's not to say that in four words isn't positive
In the Scholar's mind
Inspiration that it could beat you haven't opportunity to
Turn it into
Alex
Freddie Mac turn Infowars into a crowdsourcing apparatus
Crowdsourcing the best engineer
Enfield a world that people these millennials
Want to live if we don't give them a direction that they're all searching
Tried to build something and I'm not the best at it
Platforms as well what
We're good at putting content out covering things and I've got a great crew I just I can't do more
Trying to get out here with you
Is that
Yes we need to talk about the good world
Earlier
We can barely produce the shows where people for some reason
Some reason
I'm just saying that that that there's a lot of great stuff
We could do theoretically
Information on Ted call
Pretty more shows here on the weekends.
Go work another place tonight
Hobby Lobby
Yeah we love you dude but it's all about you no tip of spear tip of the spear now we got to move to the shaft is
What comes after
Fraser
So Alex's
Yeah if they doesn't
He can't get Crew 2
Come another weekend
Can't
I can't afford to hire people who can't afford webmasters you can't
Sure I mean I understand that
That is that is that is a tough situation
Doobie and where
You have an audience
Expecting you to do
All this stuff
To fight the globalist
And you just
Yeah the only solution to that problem is the audience giving you more money
Which day works unless you're the one doing
Going to
Active
Yeah
Ebenezer stuck between a rock and a hard place
And I have a theory
About what his plan is
I'll get to that in a moment
But that's pretty much
Before he gets just
The impotent
State of Infowars
It's so annoying
Every time the answer to a question
So utterly and blindingly obvious but the
The person saying is like
For some reason
You know like
Ike I can't hire people for some reason Psychonauts for some reason one you broke into everyone thing
Exit this is a toxic nightmare fact
Well those are possibility
For some reason it's still a mystery to us
Probably a combination of those two
If it's not one it's the other and usually it's both
Yeah
So Alex comes in on the 5th
And
He's
Meow basically just made up
Made peace
With the fact that the house
She's probably going to
The vote to impeach
And makes a prediction
Based on
Is
I guess prediction
Pelosi says we will impeach of course you
Add the votes as soon as they won the house
In the midterms that was a shirt
Is going to
Not go to remove the president
Add on the current course that's
Accurate
But you see they got a bunch of
They got a bunch of
New allegations in fraud that they're going to be bringing out. It's on the president
But on all of his Bedrock supporters
Info stories everywhere total lies
About the president about myself about others
Try to really defeat the American
Resurgence that's been taking place
So Alex is making this prediction that there would be negative stories about him coming out
Weather prediction of this episode this episode is from December 5th
This is not a prediction really
Since that morning the New York Times story written by Alex's former employee Josh Owens
Todd Alex
Kind of pretending he's not aware of that story you just reading the tea leaves they're going to spend it
They're going to spend this house is planning to beat unless you know there's going to be negative stories about Alex
Cuz he's drops guy
In reality I don't believe that he's not aware of the story
It seems like an intentional set up so we can make an after-the-fact prediction would you think Little Kim
Play whatever he brings up the story he can be like I told you they were going to put out a negative stories
About me
I know everything I know the global is playing
Yeah that's how it feels to me but honestly
I'm not positive how much he
Because later this episode of freaks
Alright, but I think he's aware that there is a story
But he hasn't read it
And I think that is
Staff hasn't told him what
I think that was smart of them
I think that's the state he's in at the beginning of his mental state does
Pretty dramatic
And I think that's when he finds out what's in the story
So
Alex is talking a little bit more about impeachment year and you know how the globalist are like 10 years behind they are usually a decade behind
Yeah well
Turns out
Impeachment also
Behind
Okay 15 days
They're going to hit with everything
This December the January
Already articles out impeach by Thanksgiving to rub it into the American holiday that they ate so much
Sure to have going on right around Christmas
Make everybody turn away from their families turn away from Christ
So yeah it's a war on Christmas
Wow
I mean you know any construction project off
Time falls in today
The delays and I think 15 days in that terrible I mean Lord knows it's you know my roof repairs
15 days I think they're I think that's something that it's not what you're shooting for but it is
Still somewhat commendable
You got War on Christmas happening through these impeachment
Isolated
These sorts of things happen a lot
The attack on Christmas legislatively
The globalist
Just like we got the income tax on Christmas
Fell reserve on Christmas
Law passed in takes Thunder from the stage for legislators
Will let
Senators they were creature of the state
Victoria lectin
That all happened the Night Before Christmas
When all through the house not a creature was stirring
I knew that was coming
In 1913
What's the weather like to do it
We know that Alex thinks the Federal Reserve Act was passed by the votes of the three members of Congress
He also thinks it was passed on Christmas Eve which is just a monster Ubly not true
Be one way to prove that it's not true
Stall the bill itself was signed into law by Woodrow Wilson on December 23rd 90
Which is not Chris
It passed the house on September 8th
It's 1913 in the Senate on December 8th
The mythology of the bill is that it was snuck through without anyone having time to read it or discuss it with
With the evil globalist pushing it throughout
Everyone was too busy with Christmas to pay attention
But none of that
True
It's just flimsy rationalization for why this thing pass
Yeah like it's not like
In order for it to be like this
Nefarious
Plan
There has to be a reason for why no one ticket. It does have
That does isn't reflected by history
Yeah the way you get around that is with this like three people voted for it
I push through on Christmas
It's just not true I mean
September 8th
18th to December 18th
Lakers months
Between it's passing the house and the Senate
Plenty of time to discuss the
The bill come to
Consensus
This is just a mansion
Bulshit
Actually argue rationally it with
Function and form of the Federal Reserve
Which there are there are rational arguments against but you can't make
So rather than do that just
Call the entire
Creation of the thing suspect
And that you don't even really need to worry about the
Right you know go it's it's not the argument
The cover-up
Is the bigger issue
Yeah
Yeah yeah yeah
Yeah it's a shark
So why in the next play Alex hoo-boy
I'll tell you what a lot of this is Ben
Sounding
Sweetie
Negative
Towards Trump
On the third and fourth you have indications of a drift away
Next clip here from the 5th I guess Alex is back on board or something
He's very wishy-washy
Extra surveillance grid
But
Factory stood up for pro-life in the fact that he's gone a lot of rallies
Things like that
What affected
Either get us out of the TPP and he's been trying to pull the troops out
Definitely a real president and I believe he has the best interest of country bar
I should hard to see him
Committed ring for us
Dangerous
Why didn't you think of the going to pro-life rallies trying to pull out the troops when he had time to prepare
List of these good things about
Why did they go
This is so
It's like when you gets like when you get made fun of and then it'll like a couple of days later you think of the
The perfect guy
Comebacker
The same thing you know he's trying to think of good things about Trump
There's such a dearth of them
I made it to plates
Do you like going away from Trump option
Available today
AMV retaining
That they're too it's just
It it's kind of
It would be tough
To understand
Where he stands
If you're in the audience
If you're listening to this show like with any regularity
I just I don't know how you'd be able to like if I were to ask you
What does Alex think about Trump
I don't know if you'd be able to say
And I would guarantee I would I would almost guarantee that whatever I did say he would deny
Yeah so
Alex I think at this point
Now
Has heard
More about the New York Times article
But I don't know if he knows everything about it
Because he's
Easy saying that there's a story but he won't respond
Listen to something
Listen to it still happening
I'll respond to hear on air
That defending ourselves and I'm not going to do that
Stanford I have discernment
So
And I hate that
Clearly more directed at a specific thing
I know a lot of people probably are curiously
Like what my position on that is on that article
And
I would say that I can sum it up pretty succinctly and
That like
If Josh Owens has good
Intentions behind this
Great
A lot of the things
Betty brings up in that New York Times
Defected Alex drinks a lot
The fact that they make stuff up
Yeah
Even though
Phone call vidhi talks about we're at when he decided to leave Alex said that I want to leave to
Those things are things that you could deduce from watching Alex's show
They're not like
They're not growl
Groundbreaking
In in
In the real way
Their observable fact
So it's kind of surf
Evan secondarily
The things
It better like the most resonant images
From the story are things like Alex
Killing that goldfish
An employee had a goldfish and Alex
Yeah things like that
Or not
Really
Stuff we can work with
I Don't Need You and I
Give me the world can't really work yeah yeah
Oh he's a bad guy
The guy who denied that anybody died at Sandy Hook is also a bad guy on a personal level right there's that ass
Speak to it but then there's also the he said
He said yeah I do
Elementary
Everything that's in that article
Is largely stuff that Alex can
Wiggle away
I don't I read it
I could be wrong about this but
Primarily there was stuff in there that
Was
It's easily deflect
I would say
What would make
Me feel
Way
More
Confit
About this
Is if in that article
He also said
I'm testifying in there we go
Yeah
Some kind of an indication
Like where
He could be singularly used
This is a person who clearly has
Paid
Clear indication that he doesn't care about whatever ndaa he might have signed half with Alex he's writing an article for the New York
4 *
About his time there
Clearly has inside working knowledge
Of how Infowars operate
That extends to
We make stories up
So
He isn't
Singular position where
He could be
Very helpful
In terms of
Bringing to light
In a courtroom
The way Alex is propaganda is
Used and it hurts
And I think that would be much more meaningful
Then
New York Times Are
And to be clear
I don't know that he's not doing
Itemized
No he could be he could have been supposed to could have all that stuff that's entirely possible I don't have it actual
I just
Do not care what he has to
To say and he should go be a bricklayer for
20 years and then maybe I'll give it
What he has to say
I don't care I think I care about what he says in his much as its interest
This is the world
Absolutely
Any kind of
Beyond a surface-level interest
I have no interest like
Fuckyour Mia culpa
This isn't Redemption this article is stupid
Don't care
That kind of that kind of feel you can have that position I think I would be a little less
Let's lift Hurst
About it I wouldn't say
Play fuk your me a call
Appreciate the
The perspective he's putting out I understand where he's
Coming from
I just I just don't I don't know if there's anything
In that order
I don't know if there's anything that moves
The needle
Past
A lot of stuff that like yeah you could
You could definitely assume that
Like he told a story about them going shooting
Alex almost shooting
Yeah I do have it if you produced tape of that
Then we'd be like holy
Ya know where the phone call that he has a dollar
If you had a recording of that
That would move
Sings
But as it is it
Kind of
Interesting
Yeah but I don't understand why Alex
See that be like OSHA
Sunnyway Alex isn't super mad yet
You just decided
I'm not going to
Big Giver I'm not going to
Because I think you can defy this with a
Because I still think he doesn't know what
And
So he just goes onto complaining about iPhone alert
UPS has been getting a lot of alerts
Eddie thinks that everyone is okay
I don't think
Cookies right every iPhone user in America
How many years are probably 70 80 million
Look up the latest numbers on an estimated number of iPhone users in the United States
Text my wife the same thing
Same three hearts
5 a.m.
Am I am
One-sided Pelosi sang
What planet is
Mars
So that's how they're going to steal the election and they're doing it in every way
There to steal the election with
IPhone
10 million
IPhone users
110 million iPhone users
108 million right now
100 + million people
Hammered all day long with only what Pelosi say
Sure
Okay you go to settings
Yeah you got a notification
Alright you can show what shows up on your lock screen
I have an iPhone in my hand
Yes you do I have had an iPhone 4
We did have a conversation on Saturday that where you did have issues with shutting off
But that's just for like my email
Yeah I know right now I have a GrubHub
Is GrubHub in for
But I think it's
Better for me that I
I have an alert for an email then
But not
But here's the thing
I've never gotten an update for Nancy Pelosi
She waits she hasn't texted you
I get texts from her all the time
I suspect
That Alex
And his wife
And this employee
May have signed up for something
Or they have an app like a news app update
Like that he's complaining about something that is a choice
Yeah him to receive or not receive
I don't understand what's going on here
I don't know you have an iPhone I have an iPhone
Updates from Palouse yeah but that's cuz we're soros-funded she doesn't need to jam those updates
Down my throat I guess
Be what's going
This is such like a Peggy Noonan
David Brooks
Column of like I noticed one annoying thing so this is why all Millennials are going to
Frankie
Yeah it's very much I'm an old man and I don't know how my phone work
You should get a house phone in
Be like his old friend
So Alex
Now
I think has figured out
What's in the story
And that's kind of
I think his reaction to this
Is what makes me
Suspect that some of it is actually true okay
And maybe there's some evidence
Has been produced
Because he is
Pissed
Broadcasting worldwide on this Thursday
Program I'm your host Alex Jones
And a big story about Latimer cooking the segment that I had some breaking news I don't have to deal with MS
So he has to get off there okay
How is this for an interview or is this so he can scream and punch a wall and maybe kill somebody's goldfish
Probably
There is no breaking news that he ends up getting too or anything
Really think that the only thing that's relevant and his world is this New York Times article
And do you see the progression of
I think he's aware of it from the beginning when he predicts that there's going to be negative stories about
I think he
Is kind of aware more music I will not dignify this
The combat
And he's like
God dammit
I am going to go end
The concept
Exercise how angry I am right
Gotcha Real Pit
And the playing
Special Report then comes back
Can complain
About how the Chinese are trying to kill all of us
My cousin my wife my husband died of Fentanyl
You don't hear anything about that killing Millions
Oh I've heard this tone of voice before
The idea that
Is killing millions of people per year is absurd
According to the CDC there are approximately 69000
Total drug overdose deaths in the United States in 2018
He's actually a 2.9% decrease
The World Health Organization put the number of global drug-related deaths
In 2015 at approximately 450
It's some estimates are even a bit lower than that
Makes sense what I was saying if he's talking about globally
You're not including all of the people that the fentanyl mascot has
Strangled to do that all these right and we're back in absolutely they were back up in the Billy offensive character
Brother cdc's numbers 2017 was the worst year in terms of drug morbidity
In the recent
There were 40 7600 opiate-related
Of which 59.8% were connected
Static opiates
Of which Fentanyl is one
About 28,500 deaths that were related to
Static opiates
In 27
A lot of that is
No but that category also includes things like methadone and
Tramadol
So wouldn't be a safe assumption say that that number is a precise gauge
Of how many fentanyl deaths there were in the United States
I don't get me wrong
This is a serious problem
Has gotten worse in The Last 5 Years
Or so and it requires attention and action
It just seems like
Talking about the issue in this kind of language trivializes the actual damage
It's being done by synthetic opiate
Which presumably is what Alex should be
Concerned about
But that's where things get Mark
Alex isn't concerned about the overdose deaths
Stephen Curry so dramatic
Or at least that's not his primary can
This narrative exist for him as a way to attack China
The story is that China's bringing in this fentanyl is a way to attack
Hack the West
Of course the people being hurt by this matter and it's a tragic
But it's also in Alex's best interest to exaggerate the problem
The larger the death toll the more reason there is 28 China
So we can be inflated however he wants to suit his
And so that's what you say
I need this next clip
He makes it impossible to confirm
Whatever statistic
Presumably is relying
Complications Egyptian the million
Eduardo
Complications from what
Purpose
They wanted
It's all being done on purpose and you nailed it
Complications of it altogether all these different things
It just becomes almost impossible to track down what he's even
Presumably talk in the
And it's just
Alright whatever
What is heart disease heart disease but the bodies Fentanyl
Basically include that
Right
So now Alex has his bad guest of the day
We've had
David Icke
Heavy Hitters luminaries in their field and now someone new
Levant
Tom and still on Twitter
Zeitgeist as well
All of them were various ways in which he doesn't like Muslim
Jerome guy
Alright you come as no surprise that
The founder Rebel media is on the show today after one of his big Marquis employees Gavin McInnes was on the despres
Prior
Taking in concert with Alex's rant
About needing to go work somewhere else
Surprised
Define Alex
Having a show on Rebel media
Within the foreseeable future
What's going on here with him being on his really enter
Cuz I don't know if I've actually heard Levante come on Alex's show as a guest ever
But his influence has been a very strong one
Wonton Alex whether or not Alex realizes
If you look at the list of the people that have worked for Rebel media
The past years you have a who's who of people Alex has promoted
Faith Goldy Lauren Southern Katie Hopkins
Laura Loomer and Tommy Robinson have all work
Jack the Staubach was there d.c.
Bureau chief
Filling in their Jerome corsi shoes
Gavin was a major player in trouble
You work there for awhile left
Austin is back now
If you look at that list you see whole lot of people who Alex's treated like experts
To the past few years too embarrassing result
From Jack for sobiks terrifying reported
Pizza Comet Ping Pong
To Gavin slap fights with Alex in studio
This is just a crew folks have done nothing but make Alex look like a total idiot
But they've also been a radicalizing influence
What's the new shift towards being so strongly anti-muslim
Most of these contributors at Rebel have an almost singular focus on Islam being the big problem in the world
People like Katie Hopkins or Lawrence Southern or Tommy Robinson
Are people whose names you would not know
If it weren't for their over-the-top islamophobic stunts
Interesting Lee ever Levant of gaunt on some roads
But Alex can only dream of
Going down
It is career as a guy who writes down Bulletin
And by that I mean that with Ezra Levant was working for Sun media in Canada
Back in 2010
He wrote an article about George Soros working with the Nazis in WWII
And Soros threatened to sue him
Yep
Naturally levantan Sun media immediately issued an apology
Who said quote
The management of sun media which is the state that there is no basis
Is for the statements
The column and that they should not have been made
This is exactly how things would play out if George Soros really cared what Alex said about him
Alex would get a letter from a lawyer and it was probably copy and
That sun media apology
And that would be that
The Alex has got to be really jealous
He's not he doesn't even rated letter
That's disappointing
Yeah that's really disappoint
Leaving aside other times levantis had to make
Corrections or apologies in the face of defamation claim
He's also had to apologize for
Pretty blatant
Bigotry
2012 Levant basin
Comments on a show he was hosting called The Source
Victor Willets a word
Not very kind towards the Roma
He said quote
These are gypsy
A culture synonymous with swindlers
The freeze Gypsy and cheater have been so interchangeably interchangeable historically that the word is entered the English language
Is a verb Egypt
Gypsies Archer race they aren't a religion they aren't a linguistic group during medieval prototype of the Occupy Wall Street
A shiftless group of hobos that doesn't believe in property rights for themselves
They're Nomads or four others they rob people blind
That is a swing
Wow
Damn
I feel bad even reading
The roast of Donald Trump Christ what was that
Naturally people
Like this too much
So he was condemned around
Six months later he issued an apology with seems a little flat
But at least he did get around
Man it's
How is you know the only reasonable explanation for why a term like that would become part of our parlor
Because it's
Trudeau
There's no possible way that some sort of bigotry could descend
Throughout our f****** history escorted a twisted view of linguistic yeah
Jesus couple years after this incident
He started Rebel media and I think if you look at is hiring decision
Viewed in concert with his past Behavior
You could pretty much get the sense of what this guy's about
He hired Faith Goldy
A woman was made over overtures to Neo.
You heard Gavin McInnes the guy who created a western chauvinist streak
He hired Lauren Southern
A woman who teamed up with a white identitarian group to intercept
Migrant boats in the
The Mediterranean
Good went on tour with Stefan molyneux
Fire Katy Haupt
Suggested we need a final solution
Muslims
Of course he hired Tommy Robinson
Speaks for itself
If you hire one of these people I'm going to be super suspicious about your
When you hire all of them
It's not an axe
These are the people you want to promote in the message
That sounds is very clear
Are you saying to me
That
This kind of like
Apology
Before his
Anti
And very bigoted rhetoric
Was was maybe not
Not something that he actually meant
Instagram
Are you saying that maybe some of his apologies have perhaps been performative
M b i mean
Maybe
How to start running
How does get going
And this is
Just stopped
He asked how the rebel new started
We used to have a real TV station that was on real TV they called us Fosters
Closest Kohl's
Tell me when we have to go to break
We had 200 people we were on cable TV we were across the country
But then our regulator
Our version of the FCC
Injected as basically aborted us
Bye
Having a regulatory ruling that made us
Enviable
Overnight this TV network of 200 people that was pumping out
A freedom narrative a counter-narrative to the media party
Not the audience
So that so then we started Rebel news out of the ashes of that
So before starting Rebel media Levante works for Sun News
On by sunmi.
Shockingly is comments about the Roma somehow didn't
Tell result in his termination nor did his defamatory comments about Soros
Sun News Network went dark
In February 2015
And it was not the result of overzealous Regulators it was a failing business
In 2013 the Canadian radio-television and Telecommunications
Commissioned
Their request to be included in the category of channels that are required to be
Be included on basic cable package
I guess I could pretend that this is why they failed
That's absurd
The commission's reasoning for their denial was that
The channel was nowhere near meeting
The criteria for being on the list of
Require Channel
Perspective
The Canadian Broadcasting Company did they reported that data reveal
At The Sun News was available prior to them being
Denied this
Request
They were available to viewers
In Fife
Week 1 million households
And they were only pulling in an average of 8
8000 View
Not popular
And they were basically throwing out a Hail Mary
Where they wanted the government to
To require their station to be on every cable package
And then when he didn't get what they wanted
It became a case of government repression
The government to regulate them into the TV and then when the government did not
They complained about government regulation
I don't think these people have any good faith argument these days
Not really don't think they do
In 2013 Canadian Broadcasting Company was reporting
Station at lost
13 million dollars
The previous year
There shouldn't be any surprise
Collapsed
Sun media sold off most of its assets to a company called post
Media but they weren't interested in buying the Sun News Now
There was no buyer and Son media wasn't there to run the station
So it went under
Almost immediately the van started the rebel and honestly that's what he should have been doing
Begin with
Rickety puts out
That's it how many YouTube channels
Yeah to make it financially viable is a television station
Isn't going to work
The whole the government-regulated us out of existence story is great
Please well on Infowars
But the reality is the government right we assessed at the station didn't meet the standards they ever required station
In basic
Cable packages
I am dealing with reality
Not in the best
The egos involved
Telling these stories
Yeah I don't
I think that he would be
At all willing to just be like
Well we all had eight thousand people watching so it turns out in the marketplace of ideas
F****** suck and you can make the argument that
That they're like well more people would have watched us
If they didn't
To pay for the
Cable package that we were on sure and I mean I guess that is only making the argument that no one thought your product was
What we want for our product
Free in order to compete with other people
So here's how Alex rewrites
What happened to your network
You watch it tell people the name is she looked into it years ago
Do the government shut you down
This is Canada folks
Florida horseshit
They talked about that
What about China soccer
And I really
I don't particularly care
I do think though it's interesting
Because
What you have here is Alex freaked out before the
He is so mad he was like I have to go out there and play this special report
He could have canceled this interview
Any dip
There's some through some reason that he still did it
Because immediately after the interview
He plays another Special Report
That is
Bizarrely spiritual
And then also indicates again
Alibaba
Radiation chemicals
Perception
Make a larger connection with the universe
Itself energize
Is a 90 TV Guru thing this bad even complete with abuse
Like what are we doing
Open it
The world
Okay
So
Oh no
Michelle
That's a weird way to frame
Paralyzed by all the news I'm in the cereal aisle and I don't know whether to choose cat
Krunchers
Crunch they're all crunchy I don't know I definitely relate to that in the cereal aisle
Although I would say
It doesn't makes
I have too much content
To produce
Absolutely
That's your issue right that's why we only I mean
Keep moving
I guess
This mood
Just gets way worse
And baby I would be more interested in like talking about the guy from Rebel being on the show if it weren't
For like it really seems like it's a blip yeah seems relevant only to me
Only because
I don't think he's ever been on the show before
And Alex said the day before he's going to have to go start working other places yeah
X seems to me like that's the only
And Ezra's the founder
Yeah okay well that's editor
I think that it's only important because as his mood is so terrible
Like
Still had to do the interview I think that's interest
But far more interesting
Is how bad thing
Wait what hour we are we in
Okay
In the fourth hour okay so he still has to Ride This Out
To the to The Bitter End of his third hour
Well I mean he does say a couple times that he should be off air
Because
Biscuits
So f*****
Thought a lot about this
I just really can't lie to people
I need to just tell you the truth
I just lay out the best of my knowledge what's going on I think all you have
Really good idea what's going on
Probably better than I do
Because I did a lot of preparation last night today I probably work 4 hours last night on this show and I have a comforting I intended to
We know and I operation early this morning
Then why you doing things but
We don't
A subject
In its fullness and its totality
Poor people understand the interconnectivity and then out of defeated
People know there's a better option and end
What they're missing out on
We're going to lose this thing and I just don't want to be
Commentator
Ball game
I don't want to be a spec
This is a strange headspace because
He has Alex saying
That I can't lie to people I need to tell you the truth
Which implies that there's something he's been less than honest
Just about to begin with
And I don't know what that
I don't I don't honestly even knowing how the rest of this episode plays out I'm not
Positive
Are you know exactly what he's
Struggling
So
That would be a big one for him to
I think I'd be in a slightly different mood is that was
There was even some
Some sort of amass
Reveal
I think there's
Escalation towards like
I think there's there's violence here man
I think that Alex is almost giving a sign
Is audien
And
I think he starts by justifying it
By talking about the evil violent things
That the globalist are already doing to us your
Advance
I will say this is pretty heavy
But at the same time
Pretty funny how this clip app
Intellectual and political album
You come to the realization
That
They're doing violent things.
Institutional
Ambien
Systems the way you would slowly poison
A while
Bird
Large group of horses called
Crows is called
No it's not
Getting a bigger it's called a murder
Came up with
What is happen
Well saying about is
Would you call
Herd of horses
Are horses
Bags under the eyes crow's feet
Fine lines and wrinkles
He is so distracted but I think that's because he's recognizing on some level
He's going down a path
Where he saying that the globalist by
Doing all of the things that
He says they're doing to us and has for years
Are committing violent Acts
Against us
That is a justification for violence against them
They're putting stuff in the water
They're trying to kill all of us
For decades
His show has been
Adjust ification
For murdering the globalist
Andy realizes
I'm so angry right
I'm not sure exactly what about could be the New York Times article I'm not pop
Whatever reason
He's Furious
You recognizing that the path he's going down is going to lead towards
A Murder of Crows
And so he gets distracted by talking about groups of horses
Because
I don't think he wants
If you pardon the expression pull the trigger
What is an abrasive horses
It's actually her
There's a ton of words Collective group
The course is depending on if they're Wild
I believe I've already come down on collective nouns
Sounds pretty negative
They're they're fun
Anyway Alex comes back from break and again this is not great stuff
Towards the end of this episode what they're still moments of levity
Ladies and gentlemen we are back
Broadcasting worldwide eyebrows Dallas
Maybe some days I should just go off here
I don't want to start yelling and screaming and threatening people
Yes
Good
No you were screaming and yelling
So
That is a really glad that that was resolved I'm really glad
Moment of levity mixed in with like this real
Terrible stop but
What he said let me get back to where I was I go
I need to resolve a group of horses
Clear this up
Look at you know I've seen a lot of TV shows try to end and they leave that one narrative strand
Resolved and I'm not going to do that on this show
You are going to know what a f****** group horses is
Or I'm going to end it now
So the club was doing all this violence stuff against
People
You know Alex has been
Waging his on-air campaign against them for a very long time but it turns out it also has led him
To be socially weird
I get pissed
Because
My Children Go.
Please don't do it
Vaccine inserts
Cousin telling me that are my friend
What's going on am I supposed to talk to each other
What
I approached pregnant women at stores and tell them about Mexicans I'm not trying to be here but if I see a random
Pregnant woman I immediately go up to her and tell her how to raise her child
Scaccia
Strain not weird I do want to be weird here it's all in services
Do you know the story that he's telling her
Here is about
That was the reason he was struggling to come up with the word for gang horses is because
He is
Trying to make the metaphor that
If there's an unwanted horse population they'll poison get rid of them
The vax
Seems low ride in the water
Is the same
The globalist
They're doing to us
Answer that leads to some
Start a troubling
Things
Violent towards them and defend ourselves
Use that against
Do the vaccines arrested
Sure
They're going to Stage stuff in Ark
But we should have a debate about the larger panoptigon
Universal
Paradox
Radiological
And just going to go on forever
A lot of people
So
Was that what's that movie with no that was
You know
Panopticon debate
Is here other than is it time
Yeah it does seem like he is
Inspiring people to go commit acts of violence
And also at the same time saying that
If somebody commits an act of violence it's the globalist who are false flag
But if they if it wasn't the global is false
I would still support you
Because the globalist
That's what the water like that all the time so we should be doing this
And it's disappointing to me that the global
BlueStar doing it for us
I have no idea
Trouble
Buy this hat
It's also with the thing that I find the most troubling is like he's clearly mad about some
Something and that's what's precipitating
This this
Line of thought in this sort of like
Look I'm not trying to threaten you I'm just telling you a lot of people like me who kill list
Yeah
A lot of cult leaders one of their defining characteristic
When they get into a bad mood
Others get
Stroop app
So
The time is fast approaching
When
The people will put this into action
So you're involved putting floor on the water
Turnball try to push all this crap and your Bayer pharmaceutical heads that knowingly put HIV and hepatitis and millions of pee
People
Screw those hemophiliac what what are you going to do when somebody walks up to you
Screw you
Carotid artery
Aorta
How are you doing
You're a human your life values we're all animals all the rest of us UFO over
You're not just telling you
That
You guys
That sounds like a threat what you're doing now
If you don't back off
Real quick
Cats
Definitively a threat
That's that that's that's doesn't get more a threat than if you don't stop
We will hurt you
Yeah you could you could make a pretty interesting
Argument that the threat I don't know I just
I mean like there is no
Backing off
Like the terms that he it what is he want like
Like no vaccine
Given to anybody
Like what is like what is backing off
It's such a ridiculous concept depends on his
Descendants
Badly
This industry
I can't help
But think it's in Subway triggered by the New York Times
It absolutely feels like he's just a child
Yeah it's this three-day stretch has been so childish
Of like depending on how he feels about anything
Is how he's going to lie about it and there are all of these people who are just
Apparently captive listeners to the whims of a f******
Rapidly deteriorating Luna
Yep it's
It's not
That's not good
Yeah it's not a it's not a good show no
And like I said the beginning like I listen to until I was like I've had enough
Because like even at the same time even isn't listen
It's all this stuff where it's like
You don't back off
There are all these people out there web list of people there ready to kill
And you know something's going to happen
But if you don't if you don't f****** stop
You even it as he's expressing those things
He of course naturally ends up getting into a grocery
About drag queen story
Quick right
As you listen
Do this
Like you can tell like this is still him trying to get money from people
Major newspapers in Wichita Kansas or defending not knowing their identities we could we just need to groom your kid
Orchids
What's coming out this look like psychotic
Demons zombie movie
Brooke
Unreleased
It's all in the background it's been waiting
It's been preparing it's been tearing up
He's going to do it through Christmas shopping here change your life here
Infowarsstore.com
DNA Force Plus
Whatever bad Moody's and it's not so bad that he can't launch right into that voice
Nope now
So what I do think there is some like real
I would like
Prices
Betty's feeling
What
End in
The terms of
From you know
Maybe
End of the first hour he's in this mood where I've got to get off Airplane Special Report
Doing this interview that he has to do
My theory because he wants to work at Rebel media
As opposed
But I can't prove that I don't know it's just a theory
At least keeping his options
Something longer
Have to do this a good sign
Interviews over he's freaking out even more and it deteriorates
It's to the point where he's
Sort of
Fantasizing about these
Patriots with kill last
Being out there is something real to how he
Keys
Struggling
With it right
But it's not so bad
That the primary function
Can't still be sir
His
Got to get that money
Yeah I mean he's a f****** Pro
Like I don't think that I don't think that voice has been real for
20 years if ever
You know that's that like sales voice
He's not a pro when it comes to
Collective noun that's true
But what
Just this is
This is bad
It's bad stuff
The last week wasn't great
On his show
But it is what it is
You know I just don't understand how you can like have a show where
You have
Discreetly differ
Days you know like David Icke
Extravaganza one day
Turning on Trump
You know like these in a cowardly way which is he is described it is treason again
God yes
We are you have these like
Picture of formulaic
Meaningless good things about Trump and then
Declarations that he's committed treason and maybe working for Satan
Wright and rambling about
How you know about a moon base
Yeah that one was trouble
Sort of
You know esoteric nonsense about the devil
On that day
Hey, do the fifth that just have a breakdown
Probably about this New York Times article
All that leads to
Celebration
Possible coming
Right-wing terror attack
Yeah I suppose that's that McPhee his best strategy to get new
Listeners in
Viewers moving forward
Be so unpredictable that
You'll tune in just to see what lunacy happen
Yeah maybe
I mean
What once you've already said
Shopping anywhere else
Children's can I guess the only other players
Just like
Complete
Unpredictable disconnected even from yesterday
He's just like The Tonight Show and have a
Have a week
Where the animal Wranglers come in not just
Llamas let's find out what else we can put in that
At Studio
I'll maybe you can't afford it
Probably not
But like I said the through-line is
We need money
Money is
Too tight
Bedtime
And so at least there's that
Arknet
None of the substance
The Narrative Arc is I will do or say
Anything on
Any day to try and get more
It does feel that way please I'll turn against Trump today
Do you want is that what will give me money I'll do it give me money
I will I will send Owen
Destroyer to interrupt
Yeah I will I will do
Anything
I said
The Trump committed
Treason
I might be working
For the devil
And 4 days later
My employee disrupt the impeachment
Screaming about how Trump is in
Great yeah
Memes
That there is real
I'm thrilled about it what I love about the alternative media
Is ideological
Sure always been my favorite part of David Icke is a turd in the punch bowl I say all the things
Videos on his show any all publicity is good
Even if it's with a guy who shouldn't the Punchbowl
Well if they both
Yeah well that's true they got dueling shitz and dueling Punchbowl
We will be back I don't know what to make of this episode like this
Time other than that
Convoluted nonsense
Live with
Financial desperation tonight in money and he needs to know what the collective nouns
All kinds of animals
I looked up a bunch
But I don't remember what they are
Things that I hate most about
Will be back but until then we website
It's not right. We do and we are on Twitter
It's a knowledge underscore fighting that go to bed Jordan
Leave a review other stuff Spotify
Until then
Emilio Emilio I'm dzx Clark
I'm the juiciest eiscue
Holding
Alex