I have great respect for knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
MoneyGram
Stripe.com
Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Jordan
If you recall everything I have perfect recall
Absolutely you had a bet with a friend and your hair was incredibly
Yeah my question
Yeah would you ever grow your hair out again
BMI of course I would but I don't
Voluntarily
My hair grows really fast
It's a real hassle
For me like it it's a situation where I have to either like
Except very heavy
Expenses going to a barber shop or just buzzing my head in in intervals and that's the method
I'm going with
You stick with Matt Yanik buzzing yeah I just
Yeah yeah
Good with the hairdos or
Moose put mousse
What have you put mousse in your doing I was much younger Paul made
You are a
I don't know if your
The part in the middle or to the side I don't understand I don't get a hip it
My head looks
Pretty decent
Just buzzed
I'm kind of like I'm cool with that
I'm just hoping like
Eventually I either go bald or gray figure out what to do with it
I don't have to worry about it for too much
I know that when I had hair down to like me
My shoulder
I don't want to do that ever
Yeah yeah that's too much
You had to condition the s*** out of
I imagine right one by
Pareidolia
I really really hate
When my hair gets long enough
Yeah really find that to be
Especially that middle ground grits
Short
To put behind like an ear
And too long to not keep out of the eye
Anyway I probably just
Keep buzzing my head for a bit
I don't know a lot about the moose
But I do know a bit about the Alex Jones
So do I figured you do today is like
Continue a little bit in the present day
I felt like there was stuff that was going on that felt a little unresolved
Like that I didn't
Hill at the end of our last episode Alex was really freaking out about something
And it definitely appeared to be that New York Times story that it come out that same day
Ballet cats probably what's going on but I wanted to know a little bit more wanted to test my assumption
You know if that was actually the case
And see if he actually responded to that story at all so I continued here
Discovering
December 6th
To the 10th
But it's really just
The SEC
It'll become clear why the temp is involved
There is a coda
Butts
Say thank you to Spokes
To sign up and Reporting
So first Sean thank you so much you are now a policy wonk
Next sign
Thank you Steinway
Next
Al Muse thank you so much
Journal policy walk
Next Bradley thank you and I'll probably walk
Knock because I'll have to run our policy wonk
IQ policy Nook
Where's Malik
Where is
If you were out there listening like they showed like support
This courtroom
So quick a little note here
I'm
Getting into this
New schedule here
Ruby Tuesday Thursday
Episodes 2-week
I'm not enjoying
I know it's not the two episode aspect of it I just doesn't feel right
That's all I think
I hate to make these fine-tune adjustments after we've already made and adjustment natural they kind of have to
So I think what I'm going to do is I'm going to say
Starting next week
We're going to go Monday Wednesday
Yeah I think that feels a little bit more
Better
Feedback from listeners if they miss
Starting to the week with the show
Yeah that works
I meant to make sense cuz a lot of people listen at offices
I've heard enough of that kind of feedback
And I'm also have experienced a little bit of
Myself that I think that's a much better
Schedule and I only chose tuesday-thursday because it seems like it was spread out
Throughout the week
Right I have no marriage to those dates or anything
Sing like that so
Will have episodes on Monday and Wednesday and then the other thing
This is not a backdooring of train
How to get back to three episodes really feel like you're about to
I'm not specifically doing that but
Having Monday Wednesday be the episodes allows us to in case there's an emergency
Having episode on Friday
That possibility
Is much better than having the tuesday-thursday where it's like well
If something happens at the end of the week that's like
Critical talk about scramble
It allows us a lot more Flex
Disability and
Better serves
The people who have
Responded
Moving for everything to do Monday Wednesday
Well businesses
I think that's a good idea
Learning by doing
And so you could start doing some
Adjust
A little bit
So
Get ready for that
Let's do next Monday
Text the 5th was the day of the last
Should we cover to Alex and the show and just
F***** up headspace he needs to get off there he's talking about how like
It's coming time
Kill people
And it's just it was very until
Yeah
Zoe starts on the sick
And Alex is a little bit more
December 6th
I tend to get in here
Broadcast
Have this whole transmission planned out
Really mad
Myself Simon try as best I can
In the first 30 minutes to just
All this New Zealand I just mention it
That's not helpful
We can open the phones up
This is so standard now
Like this is become
Just like his boilerplate enter intro to episode like it's not every episode but it's Gary regularly
Shows with
I realized that I never get to anything
I'm going to do it and I'm going to take your calls it's going to be great I'm going to do what I
Set out to do
Right it makes me it makes me worry that he's never going to quit
Well I don't know I don't know if he's drinking
We've discussed in the past that like Alex has
Said that he stopped drinking
Singing that he's like I don't know it was like 90 days
Off booze rack
Rogan said that Alex had told him that behind
Great entirely possible I'm not
I'm not one to be like
Make accusations on
On that cuz the kids behaviors that we could pinpoint as
Is drunk behavior is like yelling at that woman cupcake on the street talking about pissing on a tree stumbling stag
Slurring words are those and drinking on are like those I have not seen during this time
Sorry I believe that
However is it saying that I'm going to get down to business and really take care of s***
That is never willpower I'm not saying that his willpower is not the strong enough to quit drinking
But to do his job well
The different muscle
I think I think that
You know
What what what is going on is
Is that he recognizes
Is that there is an issue
But he also doesn't have a solution to that issue
No it's definitely not mentioning fix buckling down
Actually getting to be
These new stories would require like actual meat
Substance
He knows that there's nothing past headline
You knows if he talks about any of these stories
Without
Ranting about the devil if he takes more than a minute or two on any of these stories it immediately falls apart
Reno's he can't buckle down but he also recognizes
That is what I should be
Please start every episode like this is the time I'm going to actually get down to it
That's great
Adidas actually talk talk about some news headlines
He doesn't mention something
Carrying over from the 5th
Is it the end of the episode on the 5th
Alex said that there was a story a big story about Putin that he needed to go
Get to I didn't even do it to the story
Answer here on the 6th
Makes right
Some of this news is news I didn't get to yesterday that's so important
Today
And that of course is Putin
In some countries the world
Some countries in the world
The word mother
Is being replaced
How big is statement is that actually true
And just let that sink in
Play Thinking Jordan
Okay I've let it sink in
So Alex is covering the story about Vladimir Putin expressing
Comments in a meeting
That was taking place with you Russian
Council for inter-ethnic relations
Putin said quote
You see the word mother cannot be replaced
Turns out maybe a can they replaced it in some countries with parent number one and parent number 2
I hope that never happens
Not even the people who encourage the use of
Did your terms like parent number one or two or stop saying mother and father
More of an effort to society recognize that not all families but the same quote on quote traditional definition
They've been considered the norm for so long
For instance on school forms that makes
To have parent number one and two
Since the child's parents may not be one mother and one father in terms of that formed the language does nothing to diminish one's
Fatherhood her mother
No it's so perfect
No but a man it sure seems like some really stupid people get up in arms if somebody with power
It's one of those things that is
It's
It's a way you can really incite somebody overnight
Easy stuff real
I think that Putin thinking about this is a little bit lame at least the way it's being a
Expressed but I think it's even Lamer how is this article that I read about it on rtn
The article was written by Neville nabo sommelier
Who's credited as a senior writer
But this last paragraph reads more like a f****** Facebook post
Quote
Well Western quote-unquote human rights
Groups maybe girding their loins to condemn Putin
These remarks as yet another example of Oppression in Russia
They should hold their horses before cashing those lobbying checks
In the meeting he also talked about welcoming the except welcoming and accepting immigrants
Condemnation of ignorance and
Extremism and support for Russia's indigenous peoples
Who live in better conditions in in Far larger numbers than Native America
It should be sad
That would complicate The Virtue signaling morality plays the pay their bills though so we shouldn't hold our breath
Damn what was that was that reported
I'd like news article or was that a op-ed for the Wall Street
It's hard to tell because the article is presented kind of is
AZ news
Yeah about the
These comments that Putin said in the
But it also could have been more of an editorial
Yeah it could have been but whatever the case is
Yeah whatever the case is that tone at the end there's
Like what are you doing sounds like a Paul Joseph Watson
Scrap Salute You virtue-signaling morally
Stigler players unquote human-rights groups
With your lobby answer your sort of your virtue signaling
Putin bring back mother and father
Roof
So I complained about this seems to come from a place of admiring Putin
Standing up to the PC
Police were completely out of control and they wish to minimize language in order to control the population
That's an absurd notion
Sincerely believe that that's what the poop what Putin's doing considering that the Kremlin band swearing and quote book
Books films Music Theater and popular blogs
Which was to quote a quote from an article
The guardian
AAA quote attempt to cleanse the Russian language in order to insure it
Purity
Just imagine for a second how Alex would feel about the US federal government Banning swearing-in the Arts
Are you bb-8 absurd like his is that
Unhinged reaction to that
Also there's a law on the books called article 281
In Russia which makes it
Prime to make statements
Denying the territorial Integrity of Russia
Which is a
Pretty serious impediment to opposition Oregon
I don't understand how that could be
In 2015 to 26
16in that year 15 people were charged under this act
Eight of whom opposed the annexation of Crimea
You can see how the sort of law should be a pretty huge red flag
For someone like Alex says it's kind of
Nationalist states rights mentality
But Alex does
And yet
I've never heard this come up as an example of Russia's Crackdown on speech
None of this is ever it's just hate
You said the same sort of s*** I say about other trying to ban the word mother
Yep
You can also see this weird sort of chauvinist
To there's a there's a
Women
Yeah
So
If this is a big piece
Shoes for Alex although he does
That didn't match his
Normal Style just touch on it and then move along
I imagine he agrees with the whole swearing thing but that's mainly because he agrees with any statement that begins with
Cleanse and ends with Purity I don't think he worries about the middle
Grounder the middle parts of that I do think those get his ears
Yeah you could say like hey the federal government does
Enact
Swearing laws
In terms of the FCC but of course that does
Cover a whole host of
Media that is covered
So that argument doesn't
The Afghanistan
That argument doesn't really attract
Aequitas
Not even
So Alex doesn't talk about this story that much
Assertive a hoorah how great it is to have
Putin
Making these statements
Bed support myself
Stupid yeah world leader is saying something that I would
So I'm going to Crow about
He's writing an article that sounds like my second-in-command
Editorial copy
Butter Alex
Is much more interested in talking about this New York time
So he finally whereas
On the 5th
New response was I'm not going to dignify that with a response and then freaking out on air
5:55
He's got a
Pretty robust in dignify it with a
Now he could talk about
New York Times article yesterday
But I secretly hunt
And cover-up videos of animals I've shot
Aliens that live in New York some areas most high-rises
Like hunting be legal
Covering
Videos of
We played some of those
Sexual
Strata creative strawman should bypass article
Yeah because you are unaware that they're listening
One of Alex
Ex-employees Road nautical
For the New York Times called I worked for Alex Jones I regret it
He discussed his time there and Alex
News
Presented as a really abusive
Employer
And one of the main takeaways that everybody had about it was
His discussion of a time that he was sent to cover
Community of Muslim Community
Recalled islamberg
And I
In the other Northeast
And he didn't get the story that's at Alex would have wanted and so they manufacture
True story out of it
And so that that's kind of the thing that I think people take as the most
Important piece
Of that
Did anybody think that they weren't making stories up or something
Well I think that you know people give a lot more credence
Do you like I worked there this is
Is my
Personal experience
Then
The very
Clear evidence you can get by just watching his show
Because now have someone who's like what about this
Sure
I thought that it ate
What expresses it didn't come to me until later
And that is it no matter what I might feel about that article and how like a lot of it isn't really stuff that you can act
You know cuz there's a lot of Pikachu
Is this is like well that's not true he's lying
Whatever I might feel about it there's an overarching positive to it that I don't think that we
Pointed out
There's a possibility that there are many former Infowars employees that would like to come out and talk about their experience at
The company but they've been too afraid to based on the nda's that Alex allegedly has
Sign
If Josh Owens has the guts to come forward and the result is that nothing bad happens to him
That can have the effect of emboldening others to speak out
And then the stories of what work is
Cuz like it Infowars could be more than
Subjective
Telugu Tales
There could be people like yes I can back up at that did happen
I was there when that happened now you've got corroborating
Stories
And if that's the result
The destruction of the illusion that Alex can
Keep people silent then I think that this could do a lot of good
Sure I think that's a positive that maybe we didn't pay too
Do on the last episode
And possibly one of the reasons why Alex would be
Pretty upset about
If there's a puncturing of his ability to
Have control over thing
Sure that would be very threat
As for the stuff about Alex hunting with the handgun that's in the article that's cruel and it's a betrayal of Alex's supposed
Responsible gun use
Narratives
But it's also something that you just have to take
Crossword for
Plus if Alex is already answered that he hunted bison with
Inappropriate weapons
I don't think they'd care at all
Which is why this is
Is the safe subject
Alex greatest Ramen of the article
It's just like oh yeah they just they can't handle hunting
So
I was going to get back to this is going to be sort of a running fee
Him
Responding to this New York Times article while saying I'm not going to respond
But
Discusses
Text clip how at the end of the day on the 5th
You wasn't
Because of this New York Times story
Like it was that
He comes out
He literally just said in my first love
I'm not going to article that I'm not going to dignify with a response
Here's my response to the hunting party
I miss you
No it's
Although all appearances
And assertive
Friends you can pick up from Alex's psychology would tell you that is absolutely wood
Alex has a big story
And then let me just tell lister's about sound distracted towards the end the broadcast yesterday
We're working on big
Stories
Confirm
Man's going around
Picking people up
All over the United States
Sneaking around
The bushes
Hoopa
What bush
We got is so big
I'm going to be up here Saturday and Sunday
Shepherd with a regular Sunday show out of normal here from about 2 to 6
Working on
Empty
Documents and the witnesses
When people see
Both being put in the van
Black SUVs by men in suits
People just do instinctively that's scary
Sure
Not going to disagree people being thrown in vehicles is scary
There was one purple Buick though and that was it that was less scary somehow little bit less
I'm so this is a little complicated so I'm going to try my level best to lay this out for you
Alex has been pushing a narrative for a couple days now but how their people in white Vans were driving around the streets Snapchat
Can people up
Now it apparently has evolved into involving black SUVs as well and it will be telling people to fear
All cars
There's two basic elements.
The first is a story that Alex reported from zerohedge back on December 4th with a headline quote
Baltimore mayor warns of body snatching white Vans targeting young girls to sell their org
In an interview with wbaltv11
Mayor Young said quote
We're getting reports of somebody in a white van trying to snatch up young girls for human traffic
A selling body
His only reference
And citation for this was post on Facebook
Though he said it was quote
Something that are police officers are aware of because it's been reported
This was immediately refuted by the Baltimore Police Department
Are these random Facebook post
Door explicit that they have not received
Any reports of actual incident
BFDI DoubleDown
And said there was nothing to this but they would be willing and happy to investigate any such
Report that would be made if they're ever met
This is an urban legend
That's been repeated by a major cities mayor and that's given the level of credibility that it does not Merit
However this order thing as a self-fulfilling nature
An internet hoax an urban legend to start circulating on social media
Which that enters people's conscious
People exposed to this hoax or now living with a heightened suspicion of white vans
That's such
The Experience encounters with them differently than they would have previously
If they see a van parked in the residential
No previously it wouldn't have even registered in their mind
But now with the colonel this paranoia in there it becomes a deeply suspicious site
Cuz maybe there's kids walking around this residential neighborhood
That means that's why that van is there obviously
So they can have this
This heightened
Suspicion
Which might prompt them to post their own story to Facebook
To add to the urban legend or even call the police
Thereby leaving the paper trail that seemingly justifies the urban legend
With official documentation
Phenomenon happens
More than
You'd like
Cuz people are sick
What was the scene that movie
Urban legend
Where everybody gets everybody gets murdered by a separate urban legend
And there's like a guy and they're all doing it to make urban legend
True terrible book
I feel like I probably saw that but
It came out
I was pretty much
The only one I remember is that apparently if you are passing a car
Lights off right flashlights at it
Kill yeah I remember that from like just being younger
Are all white vans
True
But this is more or less the process that took place on Facebook regarding white Vans particularly in Baltimore through November twenty
That's started to ask
Escalade quite a bit
And now here we are
Oxygen reported that on the possibility that this has already led to one murder
In Memphis Tennessee
Where man named Anna's REO Garcia
Who drives a white work van was killed by the two sons
The woman who had hours earlier posted on Facebook about a guy in a white van trying to abduct her
It's unclear if there was a
An attempted abduction underlying this but police have been clear that there's no evidence
That Garcia had interacted with this woman
Do that
The earlier in the day or anything
It's unclear if this was all related but it seems like a distinct possibility
And if this white van paranoia is at the root of this killing
It really highlights the danger that
These sorts of mass paranoias carry with them
If you create enough of a fever pitch of people thinking the folks driving around and white Vans or sex traffic
Kidnappers
It's
Not unlikely that a certain number of innocent people who drive white vans
Could get hurt
France 24 reported back in
Can March of an outbreak of white van abduction related to
Asteria which resulted in what they described as quoted
Kawneer lynching
Urban legends recirculating on Snapchat WhatsApp and Facebook
All surrounding the idea that white Vans were going around
There is no truth to these rumors but that didn't stop gangs of Vigilantes from attacking
Camps of Roma people in Northeast Paris
Setting their vans on fire and terrorizing
These sorts of mass hysteria is a profoundly dangerous
And when they express themselves people seem to have a troubling tendency to director aggression
Towards vulnerable and alienated classes
Does a people
In France it was the Roma
In our satanic Panic of the 80s was largely the lgbtq
Community
It remains to be seen how far this
Current American white van paranoia Alex is trying to stoke is going to go
And who will be hurt
But it is clear that if it does
Progressed
Someone will get hurt
It's not going to go well
It's a it's really
Disconcerting
How easily a
Meme fear
Just
Grip everyone and get people
Sure it should be harder right
Oops if you just get a Facebook postings like white Vans are stealing people you should be able to go like
Turn on the f****** news as well when there is a tantrum
Now that's kind of
That's upsetting that's not good
It's pretty disappointing to have
What would be the equivalent of like Grandma for your emails
Being repeated by the
Mayor of Baltimore
So the other thing Alex is working in here to build this narrative
Is that recent release
The FBI documents
About the finder
The suspicious group from the 80s or as I call it
These satanic
We thought had ended
This situation is a big kettle of fish and it might be something I'll get into it a later date but for now
Suffice it say Alex
Does not read those FBI documents
He just knows that the story involves two suspicious men who drove of
I don't believe Alex was creeping around in the bushes Last Night Train
Navigate to Van snatchers and honestly if I had to guess
He's just seeing all the hoax Facebook post
News reporting of his hard news
Abby far from the first time he's ever
So he's got this big narrative
It's all like this white van
The hysteria is is coming in its
It's rising in the Infowars Arena
Okay are you saying to me that
He his big news
Is that he stayed out
At 10
When you know
The world is
So quiet not
Nothing
That's when the white van hiding in the bushes
Videotaping to see if there's any White Band anywhere near
See if complicated because that is the way that he's
Presenting
But I know from
Knowing where this goes that it also involves a secondary narrative that has
Has nothing to do with it
Video combiner
He loses interest in the white van part of it
More into another side of it as things go along
But we'll get to that it's really hard to sneak around the bush
Whenever you parked
Louder little bit obvious Where You Are
So he's
Still on
Vivere narrative
Here but this is
Kind of where
Aleve
The river is there taking organs
Which organ
And we know some people have been kidnapped and organs have been taken I've got all the documents all the article to call the crime statistics that's in our room
Everything's okay
But this is even more diabolical than that
This one story of his somebody broke this one story
In their lifetime
Because it's so incredible
So this is the sort of
Self-fulfilling prophecy
No one cares about whatever bulshit I'm coming up with
So big not because it's misrepresenting
Mission of everything
It's the stuff of Legend
Mainly because
It's not true
This is a career case
This is where you put this where you make a name for yourself in the movie
Totally
They say this is me finding carcosa
Whatever Alex Finding Nemo
It's
You hear them say they're that this is
Is bigger than
Yeah we're here
The bigger part
Will take up a bit more later in the episode
But he gets distracted
Because
This guy named Donald tusk
Who used to be the head of the European
Teen Council
Tweeted a picture of himself putting like a finger gun
Up to Trump's back and this is really angered Alex
And guess what even though
Dave prior
Alex said that Trump has committed treason yeah maybe working for Satan
Which are both things that you would assume the punishment for
Wow
I mean you know
Whatever
Turns out that this guy tweeted out a picture
And now Alex's
Pulley back on board with Trump
100%
This is the Big E U
Party head
Is Merkel
Simulating shooting trap in the back
He had his assistant put the photo out he had minutes
Removed
He's openly calling for people to kill
Caesar
Caesar's dad
Any says Trump is just to season he's going to be gone very soon
And when I see stuff like that
Really shows you how real Trump is he's a real president he's really trying to the best job
My heart
And that's my gut
And I'm just back in truck
Really bust their rash and that means well and
Or smart
With all this
Plus job
You know what what
Station
We should thank God
And
What to try
I mean this is just such a clear-cut thing I'll get it it's so in line with Alex's
Psychology like
He defines himself so much as like
Like almost just a reactive Force
Blankets
He needs
The appearance of fighting against
Something or something fighting against
Him to validate
Justify anything
So you've got this guy whose former head of European Council
And he puts
This picture out and it's like
Aha proof
The Trump is the enemy of the globalist therefore
I have to support him 100%
You'll meet yeah it is
It's absurd
It's fascinating to me how lame it
Okay so let's say Bernie Sanders become president and there's an overwhelming Democrat
Majority in the
Congress and we packed the courts and we do everything that the liberal dream would always want to be in the global trade and the globalist
But if you left me out
To dry
I will give him a Beat
Like I'm taking it down at least a little bit sure he's accomplished every liberal goal that I've always wanted but he's left me personally out to
Right right right right but you're not taking
Into account is Alex's version of leaving me out to dry
Part and part and parcel of it is
Did Trump is selling us out to China which is the end of all civilization
It's not just like he has
Uno
Not been cool with
Or whatever it's not like he's not returning my calls its
Leaving us high and dry is the end of civilization as we know it
So that I would give him a seat
It's not a minor thing it's kind of the whole thing
You know you say that
But just because there's the Optics
Send the appearance of
The opposition with Alex's imagined enemies
And prompt like there's tension between them
He has everything he needs to his back f*** it
Whole Hog
100% I'm on board
Should take longer
You should take more very simple
Nope.
God dammit
Alex
Donald Tusk guy
But that finger gone right up his ass
Some of that gun to my face
Cuz I'm going to take it out of your hands and shove it up your damn
Excuse me delay that for family to yours
This is a Bentley
How about you stick that breaks your jaw you little rat
I bet he doesn't
Tamal
Bring it home
He's the man in the arena
Is all the only justification for supporting Trump that lingers
Outside of like a really like
Signaling
Xenophobia
The all that s*** outside of that
Want to make that two over
All it is is Defiance
Like it's just
8-bit just adjusted
Location through defiance
Advair
Very low
Level
Kind of reason to surprise somebody
It's kind of sad
I mean it is one of the it is a major part of it
Though is that
A large number of his supporters are happy with a crumbling country just so long
Long is somebody finally
Tell everybody to shut
Shut the fuk up
Don't like
That goes a long way for a lot of people
There's a cathartic versus to it
But it's also again
Very low-level level rationalization
But that's where we are
But just like their products
70cc we love
It's getting lower
So if you need to
Be spelled out for you Alex's supporting Trump 100%
And he will piss on you
If you think he's wrong for
Clearly clearly
Because he's really the president
A hundred percent
Today
Criticize
Atone for yourself they're all into this
Fake moral justification out there the moral Authority
Absolution
To be lectured to by the left
About about
Trump support
Proud
I'm glad I got something off I'm proud of being persecuted
No.
Mythology is like I'm being targeted
Because I'm right is like
It's such a dangerous
It could be because you're very wrong
Sure
Absolutely you could you could save it
Evil bad guys are targeting you cuz you're too close to the truth
But it's equally likely that just people are saying hey you're being a piece of s***
Totally possible
It's that same thing as that like
That Gandhi quote people Trot out
Like the first people make fun of you that your
The revolution is like
They mock you and then eventually you're right
Is the progressive this always goes down
Really terrifying if everybody
People we ever mock
Eventually took over
Yeah that would probably not work
I mean eventually sided with adjust towards like
My instinct is to block this person but I know that everything will go right especially
So I don't know
Anyway now we get to wear this white van narrative
Involves the offshoot of it the other p
Piece of it comes at the
Play it involves people experiencing homelessness
In Austin
We've already heard back in October Alex
The beginning
The narratives about microchipping
And
Yeah he he goes pretty deep into this
On this episode and it leads to one of the like
Most exciting thing
I think I've ever heard
On Alex's show
But also just
A lot of bulshit
Use the UN invasion
Can you find out
They set it up in Austin
Cover for it is the giant homeless problem
When the mayor said here in San Francisco here in LA
If you're in Portland
If you're in Kansas City of here in New York if you're anywhere
Free stuff
Old
Hotels big one
Refurbishing for you and you get free money free everything
And we're building warehouses with your own Apartments come here
How much
Triple
They're every
We look like La just like that
So I don't care about Alex's dumb xenophobic b******* about refugees and immigrants
Is discredited himself 100 times over on that front so I get can't even find the energy to respond to his attempts
Humanitarian
Doesn't look like devilry
The story he's telling
Is the evolution of a larger narrative that we talked about a while back where he's been yelling about how they're putting microchips in people
Experiencing home
We already discussed the reasoning for this and the reality of that proposal so be a waste to go over all that all over again
I mostly pulled up his clothes because Alex is just making things up
CBS Austin ran a story and March which covered the stats put out by a number of homelessness advocate
Cgroups and in the past year there was a 5-4
Reason homelessness triple not a tripling
It's entirely possible that the number has risen since
That point but we don't know that we won't until the beginning of January twenty
20 with the advocacy groups do their annual information
Put simply Alex's just making up the idea that the number of people experiencing homelessness has tripled in off
There's literally no way for him to backup
It called on it he would probably just appeal to ideas of seeing more people on the street
And meaningless subjective things like that
He's not making this number up to better serve these people who are in need
He's doing it
It's 2
Make them
Threat
If if the homeless population
That would be Fox news's
Is only Story 2
Track from the impeached
Be all day every
Right and it would be something that people would be talk
Think about you vanilla sauce made
Yeah it would be a big big
So the issue here is what Alex
Is putting forth
Is the
Un is set up these
PG centers and stuff along through Central and South America
And they're trying to build them in Austin as well under the cover of a homeless
Shelter
Is anything else microchipping them for some reason
So this is Ghana
Double devil going to evolve over the course of this
And like I said there is just a real big
Like amazing
Moment
Hey this is a crescendo of this
Lego builds and it builds
Okay I'm turning the homeless into cyborg cyborg Warriors
You're thinking way too small
This is the crescendo is not a narrative crescendo
To a declaration
That I couldn't predict possibly and I found to be
Startling okay and completely non-believer
Okay we'll get to that as as it as a belt but
And the sex club Alex lays out what the plan is moving
Going forward
And it has to do with like 10
Taking out Trump
And then the ball gets rolling
Bill Ayers and all them it comes out in court that a plan to put 15 and re-education camps
Kill 25 million
Excitement
Court
Connors Steakhouse
Kill Trump
False Flags blame right-wingers they say we're terrorists
About to the leadership
Thousands first
You don't respond then they start arresting hundreds of South
Take your property
Your Republican donor your NRA member young a car dealership
Nubian the second
Where
Complaining won't turn your bank account
Roundup need to buy a new car
Deserve to be arrested
He fought back for the other day
And they're testing and they're doing it and Searles are spending billions on this right now
We've confirmed they got Parabellum
Rouses ready they got the food ready
The first wave of a collapse
Stabilize the economy cuz they were
This feels so familiar
Like this is the same
The Galaxy's now weaving back to a lot of the old
Same narratives from like 2009 forward like Oprah FEMA camps
But it has a new mascot
Like it hasn't new layer
In the sense that like
Back then there was the summer of Rage coming and they were going to crash the economy and that was going to lead to people going into
FEMA camps in
But now Alex is far more obsessed with false flag
Certainly
Like you
He was
To an extent back in 2009 feel like after the boss
Embalming and
After Sandy Hook pretty wild I surely haven't
Everything
Becomes a big piece
The Narrative and now Trump is also like
Secondary aspect
Of the nerd
Like what existed before was
Like
I don't
There's some reason
And why they haven't done this yet there's some reason the plans aren't in place
Already whatever and now Trump is filling that role
Trump is like cheerleading and riding the economy afloat because he knows that the
The first Domino that falls in their plan
He's just repurposed
Their plans aren't ready Trump is stopping them he's the bulwark against their plans being implemented
What is our only like form of the the
The same
Conspiracy That Never Was
The eventual
Forced collapse
Leading to
Alex and his buddies
He's being taken to a fever
FEMA camp
Cares
I made it who cares if it was real I would be against
But like
Maybe they're even coming after
Car dealerships that is weird they're coming after our car dealership
Hamburg Republican don't realize that
Car dealer was such a like
Synonym of right-winger I realize that offer 0% financing for
For five years
Doesn't even matter if it's at a car dealership
I mean I guess that's
Maybe that's true baby that's a stereotype but I was I was unaware
They car dealers are all Republicans
Third on the list third on the list yeah Republican donor
Scott Wayne LaPierre
And we got Danny's Discount Auto
So Alex gets into talking about being in the bush
I think
It's unclear
Alex has been speaking very own
Precisely
Play here but I think he's talking about when they went out to go
Get footage
I've stopped
And he sees immigrants being bussed
Somewhere
It's unclear I don't think any of this happen
Then some people Alex's decided or gay start insulting
I'm in various m
That way
Hi I don't I'm not okay with that sentence
I don't think any of this is real but here is Alex.
Across the street
Hundreds of people have to put on buses
America
Play psychotic
Microchips
Hotels in Austin
We've been there
Government you screwed up he didn't stop at we got in all facilities
Hahaha
Hey Brother
Is the beginning of what really excites me
It's all coming out next week
I like there is going to be
No this is not happening I'll be pumped and I swear to God if this is the Obama Phone Lady in a hotel
I'm leaving I legitimately have no idea what Alex is talking about but if I know anything for my years of listening to him what he says he is
Is a big scoop coming next week it means that scoop is not real and it's never come
The only other possibility is that something doesn't upcoming would it
Huge letdown in nowhere near what Alex
What is claim it is
And honestly I don't know what the big can
Beersy is he
KVUE the local Austin news channel reported back on November 4th
About the city council granted unanimous approval for the city to repurpose an old hotel to be converted into a homeless shelter
Yes
It's not a secret it's been publicly debated as a
Plans vary out in the open
If I had to guess
Someone who works at Infowars read the story about
And realize that the name of the hotel they're planning to you
It was public
Okay bue article clearly says that if the Rodeway Inn
It even gives the location of it
It's the easiest thing in the world for Alex to send someone down there at night to get footage of the building in disrepair
Because it's an unused Hotel
Airport with the city council is voting on was appropriation of funds to renovate the hotel
I predict Alex my down there and got some shots
The place looking like a disaster area
I don't really see what the other play is here because the story is a zero based on everything I do
Until the one area for manipulating objects
Is gaining footage of the pre-renovation building and pretending that it's
The condition it'll be in Watts
It's up and running
But we'll see
It's also entirely possible that nothing ever materializes
Cheaper than sending somebody to islamberg
That's true
It's possible nothing materializes in this is yet another instance of Alex bring up something he has in his possession that worked
Definitely sink
Enemies
That them seriously has forgotten about within a few days
Time to play it
Then there's just too much noise too much news than this
Has shades of that time
Jerome corsi had a dead man switch for some bombshell Seth Rich info it was going to get him killed the definitely never
No that was real that was 100% real it's just waiting there for somebody to kill Jerome corsi
If I recall correctly the day drunk or is he was supposed to reveal that information Alex didn't even show up for his show
First half-hour with special report and then Rodger Stone interviewed
A Musician's Friend
That is sad that is that is called a real good.
So Alex says this narrative
I guess there's
Immigrants refugees that are being bussed places
Disguised as homeless people or something
Microchipping
Putting in hotels
Very
I don't know I don't know
Breakfast Point what the f***
He's talking about
No I don't know what the conspiracy is I don't know how this fits in with his
Collapse
Plan that Trump is stopping by keeping the economy afloat
I don't understand
They're going to
Teach all of the homeless people how to drive
Specifically white Vans or black ass
Those are the only things that they can do
I could be part of like a job training program
You know like a lot of white Vans or work van
Yeah I have the Cure people carry their tool
Dodge
Until
You know if part of
You know
Getting back into life
Can you get my baby you're getting trained in carpentry you might drive away
Somebody make sure that Austin doesn't allow people to drive white vans
You know what I've got I've got the solution
Everybody puts a Yes album cover decal on their white van not a bad idea
Never but everybody knew that unicorns on the side of vans
One day one day that runs into money
That's fair to talkin about how evil the government is
Is as is his
But he realizes that like
Ash
I'm talking too loud
Bad stuff about like
People who might
Be inclined to like me I'm supposed to be a guy who the military likes supposed to be a guy who liked the people
On the ground like the suits snow
And so he has to correct himself really
PeopleSoft
That's a that's why I called plugging on a dime that was a that was that him
Yeah yeah yeah
That was that was like a white van coming to a stop
Joe Alex
He's laughing about like haha we got it and we got all the footage yeah hog you're all done
He said next week
House like s***
I don't maybe it's
I want to cover this if
He's teasing and I wanted to know when it's going to be out and luckily
He gives a specific
Open borders the Caravans
Simon in the news but we've confirmed it that all the documents I mean it's just crazy
Call next Tuesday
Next Tuesday
All the stuff is just amazing
So this is why we are going to December 10th because that's Tuesday
Sweet dreams it Tuesday when we are recording this is yesterday so we know for sure what this is
Is going to be very excited
I had this situation on my hands where I was like all right I want to check in so you could I figured eventually
We'd have to talk about the New York Times article in specific
It's was like okay I feel like that's at least something that we should cover I think it's response to it might be kind of interesting
Until I got into that he reveals
I'm going to drop this on next
Tuesday
I'd like I got a I got to get on my horse
And ride I've got to I can't allow him to
Tootie's that
Absolutely not
I can tell you
That I do know what happens
News on Tuesday
And I do know what Alex says is going to happen on Tuesday cuz he gets even more explicit later
Hibbets
East 141
If there is an Alex that I enjoy
This is
This is pretty close to
Hubris
Certainly tried coming before the fall
Silence announces big news is coming on Tuesday there's a lot to die
So he's not going to
I get to it now
CAP Talk
About the Vegas shooting
No
He doesn't
This is really interesting because Alex
Has had a lot of ideas
About the Vegas shooting
Mandalay Bay shooting
SOS tpp's
Well Steve said it didn't happen at all right
Weather
Bulshit
Alex has a lot of other ideas he said that it was a Saudi Arabian Civil War or something
Do Saudi Arabian
Attacking
So we know that he has that in his Arsenal
Narrative
You can't even more explicit
In this clip and like
I find this to be upsetting
Tell you what happened and I just said don't ask questions
People getting shot inside Hotel 2 miles away and they showed shot out windows
People sitting on the ground here and there were
Attacks all over the town
Saudi Arabia
Bath Royal housing
The Saudi Arabian Arabic
The top
Yeah that all came out right
No
You know what that uses torture centers
Fancy hotel Aruba Tuesday
Put the homeless and former hotels in Austin really
Did they collapsed GOG
Civil unrest that comes out
Bring Anna permanent
Martial law
Everyday
I probably do
Don't cover
10 articles I would say that a much higher
I guarantee he doesn't cover waiver
Definitely
DC that like a week hinge thereof like a hotel hotel everything's related
Harvey Oswald driving a car who else drove a car
JFK we always knew it was going to happen they're the same person
The Las Vegas shooting was not a series of terrorist
Although a lot of really sloppy conspiracy theorist has made a bunch of very flimsy and ultimately debunked claims about the shooting
Attempting to make that very argument
Alex is that a lot of these people on to disseminate their bulshit people like Shepherd ampless who contends that there were helicopters
Shooting on the crowd that music festival
And it's
Review that
And I'll find it lacking
Can't believe
Beds
Josh Owens was
Was telling the truth when he said they made up story
I just ate some amazing I've looked into a lot of the stuff and a fair amount of it is just completely unfounded
Another chunk of it is
Based on pretty easily explained quirks of science like how acoustic
It's working can make it appear there multiple sources of gunfire when in reality you just hear different sounding shots it's the results
Some echoes
Another segment is people misunderstanding or misrepresenting erroneous immediately
Reports are police scanners
And the rest of it is just the lingering Remnant from people creating outright hoaxes
Intentionally in the aftermath of a tragedy
But Alex never really looked into and it sent incorporated into his view of what was
Is real
I know I've heard Alex say that there was a Saudi Arabian
Element to the attack
Before but the part about Trump involved invading Saudi Arabia as a response is
Kind of new
It said any principles this imaginary action should absolutely make it in
Possible for a
Support Trump
If what Alex is saying was true
Then Trump would have
Clandestinely
And without the approval of Congress carried out a violent action against a sovereign foreign power
With a goal of regime change
I don't understand what your problem is
This is something Trump would have to have been doing secretly with Alex
I should be against seeing as this would be Akin
Receive that has enormous geopolitical ramifications
And we can see the results that have come from
From the gigantic weapons sales to the turning a blind eye to the murder of Jamal khashoggi
YouTube Trump veto on the resolution that would have ended our support
A Saudi Arabia's actions in Yemen
Alex always says you could judge a tree by its fruit and if that's the fruit
Trump's imaginary coup in Saudi Arabia that tree is not good
What he did
Was he invaded Saudi Arabia
Performed a coup of their government and then gave the previous government everything that it ever wanted
That makes perfect sense merrily executed people on behalf of us
Soap for real that's all nonsense I don't really care.
Take all that stuff
However this one important feature that I think the
Escape highlights
Really well and that Alex Jones seems
To be way less interested in sniffing out conspiracies and yelling about them
If he feels like he's a part of the
He gets to act like he's in the know about this secret Trump invasion of Saudi Arabia he's not concerned really about how
How that action recounted a literally everything
He stands for
He's on the team
So it's okay
That's bad
That's probably not good
Indicates
To me it sent
Is it like
He doesn't really care
No I don't think
So Alex
Soon as I get back to the New York Times article
And
He feels like he's probably address
The fact that
You know
There's accusations that he made up news
About the Muslim Community
Now he's addressing this immediately after making up news about Muslim
I don't know if it's immediately after but yeah it's after that
Within that space
Great
New York Times that affect new story understanding almost all it was complete
Afros
Michelle Dockery
Dignified
You're talking about it now
Demanded stories be made up about Muslims
You understand
Articles
Allah Akbar I don't need
It doesn't
Great
Totally believable denial there
Manufacture
That's not good
But it gets worse
Because Alex
Now has a conspiracy theory about this article in the New York Times
That's what I was looking
And here it goes okay
Don't secretly slaughtered animals that wanted it kept see
What
Crazy lady
Hold on
To write for the New York Times
People go out on a hunt
Trailer
Alex's got more specific about this conspiracy theory but he apparently believes that some older woman named Elizabeth
Wrote the piece in the New York Times and then put his former employee Josh Owens name on it
Which is why
How does he know
A very small but incredibly specific
Set of details about Elizabeth way
About
It's not a number real
Part of this is probably his way of getting out of having to publicly show that he has no control over his past employees
If you tribute this article to this other person then it's not Joshua and seeing these things and therefore he hasn't broken his
Is NDA
So there's nothing Alex can really do about the globalist attacking him
Another element is it Alex probably feels hurt by his former employer betraying him
The dude worked at Infowars for 4 years he got it thank you
Do you know the guy
Alex wouldn't want to show that kind of weakness
When it comes to be
The Optics of it being too mad about it
Call Vicky
Really wants
Show that
So Alex thinks that Elizabeth Williamson wrote the story
She's a writer for the New York Times
And she's written many stories about Alex in the past is probably pretty
Fixated on her
Williams didn't write that story Joshua instead
But that reality is
Pretty hard to accept so this is the way Alex
Deciding to play it with
Got a bump
Meowth
One of the ways Alex is using this
Completely made up narrative
Williamson wrote the article is to say that you some kind of knew
New York high-rise living Elite who's never been to the real America where people hunt
Leaving aside that you was born in Chicago went to Marquette which is in Milwaukee and doesn't live in New York
This is just stupid pandering to some kind of folksy notion of Americana
You can't take with this Elite New Yorker who may as well be
The Real Americans like I seriously
That's basically the mess
Socialpoint
Like honestly how many Alex Jones listeners do you think actually read the
Like what
What kind of an actual threat is this
Whatever holding
I mean
Probably at least read the
So if they're scrolling through whatever Newsfeed that it is they've got they'll get one
Headline of Alex Jones Alex Jones fan and you see that's
Posting the New York Times
Like you're not going to take yeah you're already done
It's not theirs
It's ridiculous that he needs to come up with this this deflection of
Someone else wrote the story
Also there a high-rise live in New York and Lee do doesn't know what it's like to be out in the field
It's a
Kind of absurd
You know
I would say yeah it's probably more just the person
It has nothing to do with what his listeners are going to like or dislike about
New York Times you everything to do with him just being like
I need to create a story for me
Make me feel better feels like whatever is going on
What is about addressing
Those cancer
In the same way that you knows
He doesn't care about conspiracies
You feels like he's in
Not them and he needs to guard his ego by
Pretending someone else wrote this story
All about him
So in service of that like
Like these
Rich Elite New York
They're so different from us that alien
Alex descends into like
A really weird
Start a diatribe about these are these
High-rise living Elite sure
And I remind you before we listen to
Is a family
I've been around the generational rich people talk
Don't know
Anything
They just grown up
Horse
Seen any other
You know it started a woman that's never gone out again
A Big Field
Truck Farm
I don't know whether
Is going
And put them in there
What's a metaphor
In the house with a woman pulled their clothes off
Because it's so instinctive
With the sound of the bugs picking vegetables
With a man
Serial killer
Because I shoot animals at 6
Squash cooking
What if Japan
What's the grossest thing ever
Is grosser than anything else
I did seem like it was a grouse nest
Aldi's
Diesel leaks fuel York high-rise living people that want to f*** you when they coming to you
That's
So like crazy
That's insane
Lovett that's where his brain work
These people don't know they
Pick vegetables and then they f******
I'm so horny gardening as foreplay
Guy that's so
And not just that but most of the people who write for the New York Times can't afford anything let alone at the people who are
Are New York Elite through right for the New York Times
Probably agree with Alex more than not
It's possible
I don't know it's just it's just
See the way his
His brain
Deals with information
But I love that at the end very sorry
Potatoes
And it gets into like this I do this stuff for myself
Myself kind of thing
And I think
Thinks he's going to end this list on like oh really
Punch okay accidentally said something I think is if I
Use the word Freudian slip
But it is
Feels like
Okay
On groceries
That's such a weird
I think what he's trying to say is
I don't have other people kick ass 100%
There's a truth there's a truth to it as much as he creates his own problem
Bio-data
You globalis at the New York Times trying to destroy me I'll do it for
Probably needs to be dealt with I will deal with him myself
Yeah I heard that I was like that goddamn
I buy my own groceries and
I kick my own ass and I'm all out of grocery
First thing he's ever said
So Alex Goes to break and he comes back and what do you know he continues to not talk about this New York time story
I'm not going to even take us out.
No reports mention of indicted signify
Must have been trying to impress his reporter that he was moral
What
The hell
Really talk about
That doesn't sound good
They would never write a big check to somebody.
To be clear in the article Josh Owens says quote
Once when I went to interview a frequent guest of Jones's I was sent with a check to cover a potentially life-saving cancer free
Larry Nichols
During the time frame to do one's work there it's pretty safe to say that there is only one frequent gas to sounds a lot like that and that is
So that would raise the question of whether or not there was a time during Josh's employment when someone from Infowars would have been in Arkansas
Talk to interview Larry in person
The answer that question
Is yes
In 2015 Alex released
The new Clinton Chronicles which is basically just Larry rambling a bunch
Bulshit about Hillary being a witch
It is
Professionally shot
It was done through info
He was never released an actual DVD or anything so really it only exists
Listed on YouTube
That makes it damn near impossible to track down any credits for it
As such I can't prove definitively that this was the time when towing
Deliver to checked one of Alex's frequent guest
But I'd be very comfortable and assuming
That's the most likely
Play situation
So probably that and Alex's Alex like yeah it was just someone who we were interviewing who
Wanted to help him out you evil people would never do something like that
Kind of feels more like
Alex is paying for Larry's
Interview exactly
It's
Josh
It's lovely that you
Yeah yeah
Continues to not talk but this New York Times story that he won't dignify with
It's just when you get into the mindset
It's so weird it's so bizarre
Now do always my ride a fake piece
The only take something from Hollywood
In their face
Peace
I guess the other
Wall Street or somebody grabs
Somebody fish
Like fish
Employee fishing killed
50 something so over-the-top
Turtles
Cool
So is defensive shot Turtles didn't kill that goldfish
His defense is also
Baby I
Good morning
Klepto is am accusing the globalist of using things from movies yeah
Hey guy a guy who thinks that childhood's end is literally real
Haggai
That makes me believe it even more that he knows that it's from Wolf of Wall Street because that suggests to me that he
He probably watch
Wolf of Wall Street
Close to that event
And then decided to do it
Oh that's interesting that makes the most sense
Yeah I didn't even consider that that's a possibility
I don't know I just think it's funny when someone whose worldview is almost entirely based on science fix
Jason movies and books
Accuses the globalist of using
Always using movies
And now it's possible that
He actually
Just watches a lot of movies and then applies whatever is in a movie to what
Happening yeah you know me always put it in there for him to find you know those people that you'll run into wherever
Free joke is like some reference to a movie
It's probably socially would be fairly close to that and maybe acts out things
I think he feels I think he still does my wife
Navigate to I think he still does
No he probably doesn't hate that's true
Probably starts with a
Punches a wall
Alex is done for now talking about the New York Times story but he hasn't turned out
Story the day that he
Right
It's 21 but he didn't
Cover
And it's about like
Some sort of a polyamorous relationship
Okay that was covered in a V I didn't even look
Can't really even care
It has to do with like a woman who's with four men or something and okay Alex's real judgy about
This I'd like
To point out there
He's a libertarian
I got this video I didn't get to
Polyamorous couple of four men and a woman are you there
This woman is their mom
She treats them all like they're her twelve-year-old son
AOL
Sun
Like if she's really going to protect them from the Army
This is what are friendly nice
Society not giving people guidelines
Follow has created
Hey guy you want
Guidelines
What word would you use
The government
You want start of like enforced
Relationships trucks I'm pretty sure that he does yes
I don't mean like it's hard to say that that's exactly what he's advocating but it isn't outside
The possible
Absolute
But I think we use more interested in then government doing it
Is society enforcing it
Themselves
Right people in these sorts of relationships
Being like
Marginalized to the extent where they're not welcome
Scarlet Letter type shed
Libertarian at all
That's not
I would say
Mind your own business
Who gives a s*** if this first of all
Who gives a s*** if this woman is dating for dudes
Work together with four Dudes
Who cares everybody who gives a s*** if there are
She's pregnant by one of them everybody who cares
Let them be
Hey Alex
Excommunicate you do you know it's
Not going to workout
Why do you care this is
Literally every time
He even mentioned
Gay people he always follows up with
And I don't care what you do in bed you can be you can be with anybody that you want
You cannot be with more than one person
Yvette is where I draw the line very clearly does
Oh absolutely
It's very bizarre 100 million percent
Not about multiple people
Being with one person
No it's not no it's about multiple men being with one woman f*** you
That might be
Or not
Primitive levels
It's not manly it's not cool it's not
Confident
Thought my thought was to that that's that's a completely once a year on a certain
People watch
Scott Manley
Domesticated
So-called Mothership
Absolutely is the family show Jordan
Family to do this but it is mainly to go fuc
If you've ever read the book sex at dawn that is actually what the beginning of civilization looks like
Pointed
It's not manly
To be in a situation where there's one woman in for dudes
He is so threatened
Yeah that is very such a weak-willed
It's very revealing
Cuz
The it's still
The way he's talking
Think about it is like it's manly to go to an orgy
But it's not manly
To share
EvanTubeHD
Framed
In the terms of Manliness and manliness is what needs
To be retained
Very
Messed up I'm always amazed at how
Manliness
Is
Maybe the most
Fragile thing in the world
These guys
Whatever it is is there is very threatened by this
Potential polyamorous couple that he's heard about it has nothing to do with his life at all
Is manlier than being terrified at every moment that people will find out you're not a
People are happy in that sort of arranged
Why the f*** do you
You care because
Even if even if they have an arrangement that
Involves likes
Some sort of a maternal dynamic between them
One woman and four children
That's against the rules
So crazy
Any consensual relationship that I don't approve of should be ended
Family
Show
Got to go f*** each other
Alex's brain is
So
Fascinating
In Florence
Like the question
Where do you draw the line
For so many people is relative
Simple they can draw the line invented
Places very quickly
For Alex the line is zigzagging upside down
And then at certain points
Parallel but also never to know Claritin Bunnell consisting
Falcon
Knee-jerk
Whatever the f*** makes me feel weird
Cuz it'll change tomorrow
So we get back to this
Story about people
Put Spirits in Houma
And like I said when Alex from flights mopping to get back to homelessness
Okay
Because what happens is Alex's an interview with former MLB player Aubrey Huff
Because Aubrey Huff post a picture where you was out at a shooting range with his kids he said
I got to teach him how to use a gun in case Bernie wins San Francisco
What what
She's a gun guy
Anyways
Oh no by the way most baseball
They're all f******
What about Brian Wilson
Yes
So look
He's on
Interviews whatever it is
Who cares
In the middle of that Alex gets a call from a woman in Florida who claims to work
In the homeless
Population
And she has also heard of somebody getting a
So this turns Alex into like going deep in that direction
Alex is already revealed that on Tuesday
He's going to break his big news
Bombshell little destroy the globalist
Alex reveals what
Plan is
Made me
Like over-the-moon like Jess
I was so excited okay
All this stuff
Areas to get more contacts
Tampa forms everything else right now okay
We're going for is the
On TV will the doctor here next week okay
The whole world's a stage
Wow so real quick PT Barnum
PT Barnum what I believe his quote was all press is good press that kind of
Alex what he does is so much closer to Barnum
So it makes sense that's where's mine will go
Like getting someone in studio to cut a chip out of them is absolutely carnesha.
And I love listening to that my first reaction was amazement that Alex announced that he was planning to do that
Which very quickly became a certainty that this was never gone to
I feel like this is Thomas Edison
Electrocuting an elephant level ship but he backs out van like
This is
I mean
Sure
Publicity stunt maybe this is a way to call Bud
So what's going on here like I said is this woman called in from Florida
She claims to have 30 years
Experience
Working with people experiencing homelessness
Specific about what any of his experience is
You mentioned that you work for a nonprofit but I don't
It's weird and a white van only nonprofit and I don't know what she's doing at their very vague
Anyway she meets a couple who then disappear for 6
2/8 weeks
What you meet back up with the dude from this couple it turns out that he was arrested for trespassing
In the process of being booked
Is offered at to be part of a program where people who would speak
Helplessness would be given
Implantable chips
Dan all of the relevant medical records
Navigation
Anyway we talked about this on pass that by
That makes a lot of sense for people who are living with housing vulnerability
To explore that kind of a notch
They don't have no secure place to keep important documents
And that could be the difference between
Progressive towards stability and being trapped in a never-ending
Cycle of consistently having to get new copies of necessary
Willie gums up the word financial burden physical burden
Anyway this woman calls and it's
Completely freaking Alex out because he hasn't even broken his big news that he was planning to break on Tuesday
Because I've already heard him talk about this back
October
And even at that point that wasn't news
Other mainstream media Outlets have been discussing this
Proposal for months even a year
Before Alex
Even caught wind of it
The bottom line is what they're talking about has this Colonel of
It is much as there is a plan that's being discussed and being worked on
It's all bulshit when it's being
Combined with this
FEMA camp fantasy
Seeing all the globalist
Which Alex is doing
I should also say that I don't find this caller to be someone who strikes me as being a good source
Here's a clip of her talking to Alex
But I think it's full of
Red flag
And being a liberal for 30 years
Being a liberal for 30 years
Hello
Somebody's trying to microchip me and then I'm listening to Alex Jones because I want to be
I want to be enlightened
Habanero's only for weights
Space and yeah there it is Kelly
What are you going to do now
So In that clip this person claims have 30 years experience in the field refers to these people as my
I homeless
She's using a possessive descriptor which I think seems really weird and kind of gross
Doesn't make a lot of sense
Amy at very least
It's an indication that she has a pretty weird View
Of the work
She's doing 30 years of liberal
Liberal and then
One of
My homeless
They they got microchip
And I was listening to Alex Jones
Switch
All three of those make perfect sense in the sentence
I mean like beat that's so glaring claiming to be a liberal or decided to listen to Alex Jones
The year of Our Lord 2019
Search for enlight
Where you have to really go find Alice
You can't just you too babe looking for enlightenment
Like either the liberal past that she
He's describing is being manufactured to give her story more credibility yeah like as if to say you know like you can take
For me I was part of a group that hates you even I think you're
Or she's just delusional
You just can't have it there's no kind of liberal principles you can hold
32in in the Infowars and fake Hades people are really swinging yeah yeah
It's totally possible that she's a real caller but this is the closest I've come to think
Caller wasn't
Yeah that sounds like a plan
It's just really hard to swallow Dan elements of her story
That's
You know
I just don't
I mean it's possible it's entirely possible these are things
They could exist
Perceived yourself to be liberal
It just being a completely
Inaccurate
Alright
Frederick possible
But I just I have a tub
It works too well
Towards
Justifying
Alex is narrative
Spitting his narrative
Exactly
It's it's almost 2
But again
It's not impossible that some listener
Would be
Exactly what Alex need you could take that call
I thought before you can play this
That we were leaning more towards this
It's like the letters that the veterans get
And the guys like
Well I haven't gotten one but I haven't checked the mail recently or the other guys like I heard someone
Got one I thought that she was going to be like
I work with the homeless and
What I heard that
Kind of
She heard from the sky
He's got he's like showed it to
He didn't get it
Oh you didn't know he got an offer to get this
As opposed to like doing
60 days in jail for the trespassing
Like almost like drug court
Like it's an option that you can take
Being involved in a program
And I don't know if that's true that's just what she's saying
And so like that
Commands to her
So a lot of this is being driven by a video that made the rounds at the end of November
Beginning of December area
Supposed to do on YouTube by a channel called beardbrand
In the video of Barber is giving a nice haircut and beard trim to a man living with all listeners who apparently it help the shop out with some
Cleaning like the windows and stuff
The video itself is meant to be a heartwarming thing where you see the difference that little things like a haircut or the human interaction with the
Barbara can
It is really
Kind of moving to see like the end
Like how much
How much different this guy Peter is it
The beginning and kind of like
Disheveled
Really great haircut
You see his face lighting up more yeah it's nice
At the beginning of the video
Getting haircut says that there's a plan he heard about
I'm trying to put a device on
People at the house they're important
You've even expressing it is like this is not a bad idea
So naturally Alex sees this as an ex
Slip-up admission of the grant
Conspiracy
Perfect plain
Insight
There's nothing secret Anna farias about the my Pass Program.
That's being disgusting off
It's been really public and I can find articles going back to at least April of last year covering the launch of the plan
And how they're working with people
And with blockchain technology
In order to try and navigate
Some of the larger data privacy
The issues that
Nothing like this would bring up right
We talked about this last episode so I don't want to belabor it but it's worth recognizing that this is a real thing
It's being lied about
And the real-world function of what Alex is
Who's fighting against
Is the development of a program that
Could you people experiencing homelessness
Greater access
Do the tools they need
Need to manage their lives
Victim
Of his narrative
Well he doesn't want any problems to be solved
Because then he wouldn't be able to yell about
That problem
Sure
Alex covered the story weeks
As if it was breaking news even though it been public and covered for over a year by other Publications
But then he let it drop
That was good enough for him just to touch on the story to come back to it if you need it
But I think you knew there was no legs to the story and it is what it was
But then this beardbrand video came out and it went really viral
It raked in millions of views with a currently being at about 6.5 million
On YouTube
Is it clear demonstration that the public was interested in the story so Alex
Reprioritize
I can't see any other reason for his increased Focus
What's narrative
There's no other news other than what he's already lied about back in October
And nothing that the man in the beardbrand video said
Adds anything more to the story
Yeah all that happened was there was a video that got millions of views and Alex realize that maybe
Disturbia story he could take ownership of
And get some of that at
I'm self
From his perspective that makes total sense
Give us the keys and he no longer has access to the means of guiding the conspiracy world's attention
Since much of it lives outside of places where you can exert his influence
He's less relevant to the larger world than Facebook hoax
So what do you have to do is bases
Content that on chasing
Topics that resonate
With the consumers a thing
Like Facebook hoaxes
You can see it with the white man narrative you can see it further with this microchipping
Bulshit
Again
Just chasing down
Whatever scraps
And trying to
Build it in
So
That's all here there's a viral video of a guy getting haircut
Dimensions
This
Program
Been publicly discussed and
The secret to anybody
And I was just turning it into
I'm going to cut a chip out
Somebody on Tuesday
Yeah
That is absolutely no
But it's overwhelming
Alex
You just can't handle
Process
This much stuff
Exaggerate
Giant stories
It's always 10-7 of a completely confirmed
Shaking
Problem
Are the same story
What does that mean
I got 10 stories 7 or confirm for the same story
I've no idea
Is this a real is this like what has
Two legs and what has one leg in the morning two legs at night and four legs at dinner
Doctor is the mother
I am the greatest
So Alex
I guess he's 10 stories he doesn't say what they are
He has four of them
Or
Are we actually dealing
With eleven stories better actually
8 stories
Who knows
Doesn't matter
None of it's real
But then Alex has a little bit of
I'll break.
Is a deep state was going to try to have an economically implosion in martial law which they admit they want a civil war
America will never come back
The planning and the money and the infrastructure that will go into that
And then imagine
Coverstore
For the different pieces of
I have reverse-engineered
Troy
Hold it in my brain
Write out the basic skeleton
Has a paper
Double space
Handwritten
100%
Confirm
At this point it's not like I'm looking at something
Connected
This thing is crystal HD
This is such a classic con man shyt
Like Alex is sitting up here and going on about how he's figured out the entire globalist plan
He can hold it in his head and maybe write it out in 20 pages but
Can't seem to just explain it in
Clear concise language
It doesn't end up turning into a pointless rant of
Time-filler about the devil
Is Alex Andy does have this entire globo's plan figured out that he has a responsibility to put it out for the
If you can write it out the skeleton and 20 Pages he needs to sit his ass down and write it out
Getting through that 20 Pages shouldn't take more than half of one of his daily shows
He writes it all out
Teacher class dick
There's literally no excuse for him not to do that just take one day who cares
The world keeps on moving you'll miss your ability to rant about to
Putin say mothers are being outlawed
Take that day
Do your business
Get down to business to get really specific
Site things clearly
Don't go away
Open the pointless rant about nothing in the devil is lay out the picture that you claim to see
So Crystal clearly
And everything's proven
Not going to do that
Lil Boosie
Talkingshit
This is
This is this is abusive
Yes
This is such a crock of s***
It's like that really kind of like make me
I'm amused by a kind of way
Just that like I am the Oracle cannot tell you his ways
Do not look behind the curtain my friend I'm telling you that because that used
Hotels in one place
Then the fact that use hotels other places
Means that the thing people it's this sense of like okay so what
What what I'm telling you is I feel
It's all perfectly prove everything is Krista
What would so what's going on
I can't I can't I can't
Commit to slow it down
Just take your time to think through it I've got the money empty pages for you to write on typewriter
Handwritten I'd love person would even work I would love to do that but it's
Too much
Even really tell you
So what I can 41 pages
Now what I can do
It's because I can hold it all in my head
I can do is I can have you tell me a headline
And then I can tell you what it means
Okay I like that
It's not a parlor
That is nice okay grand mother
OK Google what's a different hat on
Mother
I am balux girl
Soothsayer
Yeah I mean that's all that's going on though really is just like the making a rationalization for why he's not there
Doing the thing that his show is
Supposed to be
Is it like I can hold it all in my head that's why I just end up ripping about all this stuff
Whatever I could give you all the information
But how about you give me the information
And I'll move some blocks around and I'll go
Give you different for guys
Instead of teaching a class I would rather do an improv show
That's all it is yeah pretty much
So Alex now lays out the
Plan about like
How this all fits
Gather you know cuz he's already said that like they're going to take out Trump
And then that's going to leave
To the
Collapse or whatever
They're microchipping people experience because
There's something that it's disconnected I don't really understand how it all works
I understand how it all works together within this clip
Tries to bring it all under the umbrella
And I would say this need to rewrite okay
They are intending to remove Trump one way or another
Step one
Winger's blue stuff up wind up to
They're going to truck mom and mash
And say we did it
When they removed from
There's going to be homeless running around crazy everywhere what
5% of the opiates
Cut those off for about a month
Set for
And it's going to look like a zombie apocalypse
Un vehicles
Hundreds of ngos running around getting emergency centers ready
For the homeless
Explosion
Microchipping ready they call Andrea education camps
Obama army manual
Sorry that we talked about that already put
So Alex is basically laid out of this microchipping the homeless population
Complacent the globalist
Again
I have to stress that none of this is in his film endgame
Which is another version of a totally proven Crystal Clear Vision of what the globalist playing for their endgame
They're all this stuff about the Chinese cutting off the Fentanyl and behind so we need
Endgame he didn't realize that they were going to have to update their stuff as whatever
PlayStation
Update whatever
You got to just download it
It takes a 45 hours but you just lived through
So Trump gets removed
Then we end up in a situation where right-wing extremist pull-off more attacks
But naturally these are false Flags
Like all the other ones
Right-wingers never commit Viber
Is this
Civil War will break out the economy will
At that point the Chinese can cut off the opiate Supply which will make the homeless population turn into a walking
Zombies
And then all the old school Alex Jones FEMA camp fantasies finally come into
Honestly
I think that the element of this narrative involving homelessness is
Kind of Superfluous to the larger plot
I don't understand once a civil war breaks out I really don't think the government would need any other excuse to an active form of martial law
I don't know how people going through opening doll Everman is my quest
I don't know how people go to open withdrawals is going to like Ray's the steaks from a civil war
Is this where screenplay and I was giving notes I would say take
Take that part out
It just over complicates things
It would make me think that I was talking to a writer who maybe it was try
Trying too hard to jam
Time to plot
Baby baby kind of just doesn't
Russian novelist
Also Alex is making up that statistic
90% of opiates come from
Vagina
You may be spiritually right that a majority of fentanyl comes
China but that's not the totality of the opiate crisis
Anti
He's not taking into account the people who have used fentanyl also probably use other oppa
No it's not like fentanyl disappears and then adequan to say like
I can't use heroin
It's just not as good
It's just not a good enough hi I understand the fentanyl is way stronger you know whatever but it doesn't
Once you go
Once you go with fentanyl man you can't go back
This is August
Completely disconnected from reality I even more so than normal
For Alex
It's a lazy and sloppy although I will say it does feel a lot more like Alex's old work than
His current work
There are these elements of it that are much
More
About this
Like it cuz the FEMA camp stuff
Was so Central to like the older days
And having a lot of that like really really emerged as a
Is this overcomplicated scenario that is going to take place
If Alex isn't successful and then it all leads to the predetermined destination
Alex being dragged off to
It is
Much more reminiscent of that
But the problem is that he's been goofing off and do dump truck bulshit for the last 4 years
So those muscles are not
Is good as it used to be good at doing that anymore
Simplot that has nothing to do with anything
I mean it
You still got a monster of the week
You know you still going to have a monster of the week
He can't just cuz he has a overarching
Storyline doesn't mean that
You still don't have to
To fight the gray man every now and again
Gray man
Trying to make
Connected to the overarching
Plot is not
Right right
Anyway the FEMA camps
For longtime B
Trump was literally
Doing all of that stuff
Yeah that silly wanted to avoid the
That did probably put a wrench in
Focusing
Too much on that
It's weird cuz it
Sore bubbling back up at
Same time that he said
Trump committing treason then that a couple days later side.
That's weird
Anyway
I mean well I mean he's committed treason on the show too so it's like Hoosick treason is off
Again I mean it's
Value neutral
World
So much like Steve
We have another return
Guest here
Although we have seen him
Not to dis
Austin passed but another person who
Is from Alex's Salad Days who is
Now we're coming back into the fold
And he might have gotten a check
Larry Nichols and the clintons
Rockefeller Foundation others healthy
Handle them
Killing even neighborhood
So he found Jesus
Vagina cancer has adjustable
And that we found Christ and repented difference of info
Larry Nichols and Courtney famously suppose
Famous Tate
Larry
As best as I can tell none of that was true 0% of that was true
I do eat the boss
Expensive part was
Larry's been a good source of information the most flagrant lie
Introducing a man who famously got
Everything wrong
Where is Kate
Which is an
Meaning of itself
So Larry's on it's kind of boring
Especially compared to the last time he was saying that Adam
A shift isn't where is Egyptian garbage goes to ritual sacrifice
No it's but at least his last appearance when he returned
And from his long absence
At least there was some juice
This time it's board just like
Where we're up against
The Wild Things
Jack things are bad Alex
Okay it's very standard boring Infowars gas
But because they're talking about this
Like how bad thing
Things are for
There Patriot
Community or whatever
Alex gets back into that headspace of like
Think it's time start killing
And John
Dammit
Larry's response is really interesting
So what are you do when you're facing an unlawful row government
He's got to go to the people and prepare to go with the people in the US Military
Winnie-the-Pooh
Be honest Alex the one thing we got left
Play Spirits say this country we got one
November 20th November 2020 the election
Alex is being what the f*** just happened there damn nickels as big a voice of reason how dare you
Alex Alex is being like we need Trump
To get the f****** military to
To clean out our enemies in the government killed millions of people
Trump to use the military to unseat people that we deem
To be part of this globalist cool right
Which is
Bad
Obviously
Mary's like nah man
We got an Alexa
I'm coming
Hold on 1
We need to focus on the
Peaceful transition of power
But hold up until the election happens before we say
Murder millions of people
Yeah but man if millions of people die it's just
Globalist
So Alex doesn't care about that
I don't want this to happen
Trash
That's why when I got cockroaches refrigerator I just
Clouds
Are really asking for it
Becoming like the sunshine
So I mean
If Alex is saying a million globalists are going to
To die then
This isn't
The same conspiracy
He's always been talkin about
Because
I believe you said there's 60,000 globalist in the past I don't think that you could take
The people who are in these bureaucratic positions and add them up to a million
Like whatever he's talking about is Slaughter
It is a massive he's already said like
All these Democrats are all globalist
Call Satan worshipers and
The minions
I mean like this is a
Horrifying
Thing that you suggesting happen
Cool
So much like
F******
It's just like
Whoa whoa we can all have an orgy
But if
Three or four Dudes with the same woman that.
That defies manliness and almost died
It's the same ship just like other government is doing something that I
Don't like I got so let's kill Millions
People
Great so I should also say that Alex one of his main things
He talks about all the time is that the globalist
They're trying to destroy the family
I like a family is
Is the most of the day
Right so the mother for fathers to kids
Perfect family
This next clips on Ebay
Estranged mean
For someone who
Love's family
People's family disowned the converse of people's wives need to leave them out to submit to them
Republicans
Absolutely
Lose
Are losing their job
So Alex is saying that if you don't support Trump your family should be destroyed which is like
Okay
School so in the last clip he says I don't want to do anything offensive
And in the next clip
He says we're at War and we should all take off
Well under assault
I mean it is incoherent but its intention
In the same way that you like I understand crystal clear all the things globos they're doing but I walk sit down and just
F****** teach a class on it
It's the same thing he wants you to be like we're in a war we're being attacked
I won't do anything offensive Lee but giving every just
Application for why whatever you might do is actually defensive and you probably didn't do it anyway with a global sports wagon
Same thing try and keep people in this weird state where they
You don't know what he's saying
But Larry is
Is
The same thing he's always been saying
Which is it
PeopleLink
Congress
Are too cowardly to do anything
Because they need to keep their jobs because when the trouble starts
They become dukes and duchesses right
That is true
He can't possibly still thing
He does
The president becomes king
Okay or queen alright everyone in Congress is Doutzen.
Okay so then in that case
The Congress people
Would it be super for
This happening
Because then there is a table
It's just the king and them
Dukes and Duchess
And when you get there if you got a lot of dukes and Duchess
Somebody's going to over
Okay
I just going to happen
You think yeah but the King has the praetorian guard I forgot about that
Procedure to he's back for season 2
Yeah
But I wouldn't be learn Echols appearance on the show if something
Completely absurd wasn't said by him
I had to get back here
You have got to engage over
Galaxy angel
Uintah
It can be here in 6 hours
Why are there
Why are there Alex
I have literally no idea where after Larry's getting this 250000 un troops
Being S3 from
Every more than that I think the population of Cuba is like
11 million
Yasso 250000 80% profit yeah
Bored
It would be like
Half of the population of the second largest city in in Cuba it's absurd to imagine
But what are they doing
According to the UN there are 11 un police officers are experts on missions in Cuba
Jason is part of peacekeeping Missions
Actually I misspoke there were 11 back in 27
Okay well
If Larry wanted to like have a higher number on our border than you should have gone with me
Mexico
But even they are
Do you want to not have troops in the way that Larry is making me audience
Think
They have peacekeeping forces their station
Countries around the world with more being in countries that have greater unrest unless in relatively stable
A lot of what they're there for is monitoring
Not actually
Engaging
I made it through there also to
Assist to be country's existing power
Currently there aren't even 250000 un peacekeeping
Troops in the entire world
Not even half of that there
The current latest tally is just over 100,000
They're spread out everywhere
In about 40
2000 of them are not even uniformed individuals yes just civilian
Yeah
I tried to look up where this information was coming from
The only other place I can find a reported was a YouTube show called The Common Sense Show
Which is hosted by guy sitting at a desk and has American flag there and a cactus
His name is Harry lickle
Don't know why he's got Cactus but
Isaac actor alright
So he's interviewing guy name
Paul Martin
Who tells him without citing any source
But there's 250000 un troops
Cuba
The host decides that the most likely reason there there is
Planning a jailbreak
The free the terrorists being held in Guam
I don't think you need 250,000 to Weekender Guantanamo
I'm sure he imagines that it's like a full prison with an entire Army in it but he must be forgetting that Obama kept trying to close
Who is the Detention Center
And that led to their only being 40 people.
They're currently
And honestly if he's imaginary un troops
Planning anything I would say
Finishing the job of shutting down Guantanamo which Trump is refused to do
That's not the worst thing they could do
Also I feel like you could probably
Do a successful jailbreak there with like
10 guys and a montage
I have no idea who Paul Martin is
I have no idea who the host of the show is or why you're the cactus on his desk
But I heard this show and I thought well this must be where Larry is getting his info from
It's complete bulshit but his version matches up exactly what was being done
Just got done the show
Listen to little bit longer and they make clear that their source for this information is Larry Nichols
It's a circle time is it
Time is a flat
They treat him as a credible Source but the host does ass
Quote did he say where he got this information from to which Paul Barton replies no he did not
He knows a lot of people
Exactly 250,000 people
Business libel individuals is a classic Larry Nichols trick
Cross-pollinated right-wing media
He's so stories in various places coming through various mouthpieces to create the illusion of a reality behind his story
There's not 250000 un troops in
Cuba but you'll see the story being reported in Baltic
Full dum dum right-wing media Outlets because he
You made it up
And told all of them
He comes from the days of like the old-school what do you plant
Stories that like tabloids and that helps to reinforce
What you put in this one is back
Buy this one
Even though you are the same
Anyway
Kind of how I know all these people are f****** liars and they know it
Larry Nichols has been wrong about pretty much everything he's ever said
He's been a terrible repeatedly discredit source for information
Concentra the 9th
Babies to the present day
He said Obama was going to suspend the 2016 election
We could remain president
Then declare America a Muslim Nation to make himself
The king of Islam
And he was being abetted by Congress cuz it all gets become dukes and duchesses when he made his move right
That was some completely unsourced
Clearly made up bulshit these hosts
Eat it up and treat him like he's got a Hall of Fame batting a
They know what they're doing they know he's full of s*** but they just
Like the kind of shity
There's something
Is all natural
I just another hoax
Hilarious come up with
Cuz he's a board
Psychopath
Yeah that sounds about right
God can you can you imagine if the UN even
And had to endure
Well it's people would lose their s***
Opposed
And actually 250,000 was a number that was suggested
In the past when they have tried to make
These moves
It's never half
No because people would lose their right but the fact that
It's been suggested is what Larry can fall back on when he's trying to spare his client
You think they did
Actually make it
Sure that that
We didn't find what
So I meet that that would be where he falls back to if pushed on it
And I think that's the reason that uses the number 200
We talked to him I believe what he would fall back on his
You can believe what you want to believe and I'll believe what I want to believe him
Mine happens to
That is probably also
So here's how it sends the show and I think it's
A bit grim
And I can tell you the people in Kauai
The people in
Areas of
Pacific other people and places like Tasmania
These are the people like that globally
To apply to their readout
What they were supposed to already have the robot fortresses automate
Security
You know the guy that comes to do maintenance on their underground bunkers. Down pouring bleach down it
Hot down the ones that are left that rattles I'm not
5%
That sucks I mean it's just becoming kind of
Standard for him to make these like you're all dead if you don't back off
Kind of it's much more consist
It's pretty it's pretty regular and it doesn't
It doesn't feel good
Hey
Don't make me kill
I don't want to do
I don't feel good about murdering
Bring you a be terrible but I have to murder you
Because you're doing something that I imagine is real even though
Well now you're going to talk me but people I talk to whoever killed it
They would never use them because all right wing
Alright Wing murders are false
Right there is at 2
Some globalist redoubt is flooded with chlorine
Absolutely
Absolutely where does this fit in with his
Pre-post riprap
Unclear of all human life
Including the globalist who caused the human
Is that part of the trip probably okay
So Alex very heavily promoted on this December 6th episode that he was going to break this big news about the microchip
Keeping up the homeless population
He's planning to have a surgery where they remove one from a person on air
Obviously I had to check out the show
From hell yeah hell yeah
You cannot knock
No they read be irresponsible
It might surprise you to learn that Alex never
Forgot to that big
I don't
He totally could have
He spent almost the entire show on the 10th
Calls
What are you saying you was going to do was a very high preparation presentation
And what he delivered with something that requires literally
No preparation
What a surprise
I generally just listen to these episodes since watching Alex really annoys me
Menow his facial gestures alternate between the smug
Dissension in
Sweetly tragic deflation
And I find it really uncomfortable to watch
Adding to that the way he just can't sit still
They just visually
Pleasant thing to to watch that I usually just listen
However I'm glad I tuned into this show on video
Because it's Christmas season
So he's updated the big video backdrop screens behind them
The one who is left is a big fireplace
Very quaint
I think the one that's directly behind him misses the mark a little bit
That though it's just a Santa hanging from it
That would be Autumn brand
It's a nighttime shot of a snoke
Mountain top
With a constant trickle
Snow slowly falling
Space to Serene
When is juxtaposed with Alex wiggling around desperately trying to lie
Well his face is just screaming to feet
It looks like it's freezing
You've got the fireplace right they're just trying to survive
Suppose with Amad desperation
Just varies
Bizarre
There's a scratch on the eye when he shows where Alex is trying to
The claim that the media was reporting the Owen Shroyer had yelled about lynching Obama when he disrupted the impeachment hearing
It's very clear that they were reporting that he disrupted the
Impeachment hearing
And had previously on air said that
He belongs in Guantanamo Bay
I mean look I'm not saying this should happen but Barack Obama you know find the tallest tree in a row
It would be pointless to put them in Guantanamo Bay we already know there's 200
50 un troops
That's what the
Waiting for God
Alex is trying to
Pretended it media is saying that
He said a few things about Obama when he disrupted
Clear
Yeah Alex's face as he's trying
Find a thread this needle is really sad
You can see the recognition in his face that there's
Heap of Owen Shroyer saying those
You can see him
Fully aware that if any of his listeners actually read the articles
Exciting in life
Vanity Fair salon
The see that Alex is lying about what they're claiming about Owens disruption of the
The preceding
You can see him flailing you can see in his eyes that the gears are moving
But they're fully aware that it doesn't matter if the gears move
He's spinning plates for no reason
And it's all falling snow behind him makes the Tableau more
Profoundly Dupree
And there's no that's not even saying anything about how bad the Optics are when he's rambling about how you should buy his dumb pills
Because shopping anywhere else is giving money to Satan
Are the snow slowly fall
Very weird
So he doesn't get to his big story cuz there is no big
Big story
I went back and checked his Saturday Sunday and Monday shows to be sure and
Nope knowing show in studio surgeries
No big bombshells
I'll just hype for nothing
On the 6th
Alex who sang they had everything confirm
Add all the footage
The interviews they have the doc
He set a date for the breaking of this big story
F****** way
You had 5 days to smooth out the edges
Seems like it was just a matter it's using a filling out Hippa form
That doesn't take long
It couldn't be more obvious what happened
Alex thought this kind of publicity
Restart was going to be a good option for him to get a tent
Owen Shroyer disrupted the impeachment inquiry which was a way more potent option for free press
I just ran with that completely forgot that he promised a big reveal this bombshell
It would bring down the f****** blah blah
I don't know maybe he had to push it back cuz he couldn't get that Hippa form so it was sorted out
Recording this on Wednesday so I have no idea if he finally took down the globalist on Wednesday show
One day late
I guess we'll have to see
I want to leave things on here
It's been a long time since I've watched Alex's show
And he absolutely doesn't look
Same as I remember
It's not about his beard or the weight fluctuations that happened in fact I would say you look slimmer than I remember
But he looks
Crushed
Even when he was ranting about winning his eyes are Hollow and
Is facial gestures come often
Contrived
He's constantly looking at the
So he knows how long he has until he needs
The Dismount from
Current nonsense
So I have time to get an ad in before the commercial break
His anger reads more like frustration
His rants about the evil globalist take
Trying to take him down now see more sincere
We're only when he's yelling about how you have to take the
You know like around the office
Rio Vista
Adding visual component is
Yeah
There's one thing that's too
Stuck out to me the most
In these other days of shows
Was from his Sunday show
Where is responding to
The part in Josh Owens article where he says that Alex called him
And said that you wants to
I wanted to quit doing a show
I may have to quit
Just because I can't handle
Caring this much
And I see everything
Just reaching a point where I
Can't do it
Every little point
Every article
Another article
Everybody put out I can pull up a whole system otherwise
How they cooked up the decision
7 years later the reason some white paper got a report about a committee meeting and they say exactly what I am
Vision word-for-word in the meetings I knew was going on
I've studied them so much
And how evil they are that I'm inside their head
They're inside mine I can't stand
That's just f****** absurd wow Alex hasn't studied Global is so closely that he's in their heads and can predict their every move
Move even read any of the Articles you can claim they can connect with 1,000 other articles
Expect anyone to give him credit for psychic level scholarship about a secret group
Runs the world
Best childish it
The f*** out of here with that
You just a propagandist who realizes it
The time is up and the desperate way for him to go out looking good is
In the case that happen
He's no Bill Cooper so he's not going out like that
Do you knows everyone's laughing at David Icke sweet like going down that path either
The way he's making it sound here he's preparing for people people
For him to be the one world government conspiracy version
That 45 year old is at the bar talking about his Glory Days playing High School football now we could have made the end
NFL
You can hear resignation
But an insistence that everyone know
But even if he gives up
He knows everything
He could have stopped the globalist
If only people I bought more of his pills
If you would have been allowed on Facebook
Yep
That's amazing to Dupree a justification for like
It is this is all going to go
You know what I just can't handle the burden
Of being the person who
Can win
I heard that music This is
Bummer no this is slowly falling snow behind
He's a
Fragile little
Really it's really paper thin
It's
It's just like
It went when the
When the kid was having a
Tantrum
Was so loud and boys
Build this adult man
Dancebody you're like
Fun and scary and now you see just
The very small 12 year old boy
Who can't see
Sit still
Who is afraid of anything that's
Who can't handle
The idea of masculinity being
Different than his own
And who is dealing with the disillusionment of this cycle
Sort of Father Figure in Trump who would protect him and thought he would bring about all of the
Things that he right now he's going to get me a pony or whatever
Pony in the form of kicking out all the immigrants
Disillusion that that isn't coming
And not only is it not coming
I'm not even going to protect
Do you know what you having this
Crisis
Everything you saying is not 7:50
Proofing it all in
Yeah there is no in-studio surgery that he's promised right
Wouldn't be surprised if this was so reminiscent of when he
He was 12 and his dad's like
Take over and they're going to kill all of us that happened and then
Yeah I mean you know it's it certainly
Narratively seems pasa
I wouldn't want to speculate on that just because it feels like
You know
Personal we have no idea where it is going to be Rosebud
That's all I'm saying
Creative nonfiction story
Follow that path
But it may or may not be true
Anyway I just I mean this present day is
Is getting weird this show is crazy
Love
The stop where he's talking about how orgies are man
Like
I would probably listen to
I show it if it was all that
Alex getting into like being Tom Leykis I would like to know exactly where he stay
Hands-On all kinds of s*** like that like a polyamorous relationship
Don't know no more than one dude or a bunch of dudes and a bunch of ladies can't do the other way around you imagine
Jerome is fine but not the reverse
Is this all falls
Alex starts doing what
I love linetype shell that would be amazing
Jerry Kids
Terrible advice
You don't even need to ask where I stand on pegging I'll tell you that right
Not manly
Also I love it but
I like that silver stuff is so insane until out-of-state
That was what he
Thinks his show is
Find a kind of
I find that kind of delightful
On some level even though it is
Gross
Batman when you got a show in a situation where he's building this
Stuff about the like
Got this out of a guy's arm
It's just such a bust
I can handle that too
Like in the present-day I can
That's that's fun
That's good fun shouldn't be allowed to do
If you are
Violating chekhov's
One big rule
Oh yeah yeah
Especially the way that that Tuesday show was just
Taking calls
Disrespect
If you if you have a gun on the mantelpiece
Then leave that girl alone it's scary
Jones's
Yeah so we'll see what happens we'll be back on Monday
Next week sounds like
Not just going to be covering the present-day stuff just wanted
To get back up to
Speed probably have a present-day episode on Monday going over the rest of
This week just in case he does that serve
We'll see
We will see but until then we will
Hindi video
College fight.
I wrote on Twitter at go to bed Jordan we are on
Facebook and we are also on iTunes
Download you can leave a review etcetera Spotify I don't know you guys
Will be back but until then
I am Neo I'm Leo I'm dzx Clark
I got my own groceries and I kick my own ass
Alex