I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Need need money
College vype.com
About Alex Joe Jordan
Louis ask you a quick question what's up end-of-the-year doing all kinds of recast of list
All I Want To Know Dan is there anything in 2019 that has surprise
Know exactly right
Everything is so incredibly surprising nothing is surprising yeah you know
You're like I can't believe they would just do that
My brain's been burned out to novelty yeah yeah
No try a nice dish
Crazy alright cool
I guess okay I'm a little surprised
Not drink
It is much as I thought I was
Maybe they have some of the same charm as for fun maybe I was 18 when I played the first one and I'm 35
Imma try to play it slowly so it lasts you know I come back to it I don't even know what I'm doing
I guess that's a little surprise is there a wrong direction
Your friends were stuck in painting
King Boo Butt
Run around
Each level of this hotel is
Spider ghost boss
I don't know man
I don't know
By Kester I do a lot of surprises this year but I do know a lot about Alex Jones
And I don't know I know
Today we're going to be going over some depositions that drops
At the end of last week at the end of November
All three of the Musketeers Rob do Paul Joseph Watson Alex Jones
Boat against gave depositions in the ongoing Sandy Hook lawsuit
And
There's some interesting stuff in there
It low-key I think Rob dues might be the most interesting of the tree
I couldn't that's the surprising figure we go all right
That's the surprise of 2019
Rob dude his deposition was more interesting to me than Alex's
Get that out of business and talk a little bit about that
Boku signed up and recording the show
So first of all Caleb thank you so much
Text Christopher thank you so much
Thank you very much do I need to Hook conspiracy next Josiah thank you so much
Elliot
My favorite character
The show is it all close-up magic no it's all real
Terrible show but I love I like magic I love it whenever I'd be out at the bars doing shows and stuff until
Summer walk up on the street while I'm smoking a cigarette want to do magic tricks
My favorite second only to the next person who is assigned
Thank you so much Rachel you are now a technocrat
Heroin
So good
Is freakishly large
Thank you so much Rachel
Yes thank you very much Rachel if you're thinking
Gore website
So I was kind of struggling with trying to figure out exactly how we should
Do this episode cuz it's 3:00 deposition
You know and it seems a structure be weird I should we take intermissions redo it as separate episode
Could do with a classic three-act structure much longer
Alright
Broadway play
We will have third-act problems problems
Bonita each of these depositions is really interesting to me and very different ways
To each of them you can predict with Alex's is
Doesn't remember anything ever understand anything or nothing had anything to do with him not me
But the other two have a very
Bizarre
Kind of
Most through-line through them got something interesting going on Rob do visiting Fargo
More interesting
Don't let's start with the Paul Joseph Watson
Okay he sits down and
I will say that I do not foresee a very clear on this
I don't like Paul Joseph Watson
Me neither
I find his voice Inseparable and his positions are nonsensical bordering on evil
I think he comes off like much more of a human has this deposition because I think that he has
Some sort of a brand to protect a little bit and he doesn't want to
Comes off because there's one and that he does have
The history of telling Alex to stop doing the Sandy Hook she does have that in his
That arrow is in his quiver that you can pull out be like
I try
Look dude whatever
So he has that
MN 2nd
He knows then he doesn't want to look like he's a f****** idiot
You don't want to come off as like
Alex
Obfuscates everything is like I have no idea what my name is
Look like that
And so it creates an interesting Dynamic wear and I think a lot of people took these headlines
He's turned on Alex
Trying to defend out in in as much as you can while still being like my hands are clean I don't know you guys do what you're going to do
Do without he's got a tough tightrope
Yeah I would say she's like a mid-level mafioso I don't express
But it is a tough position where we learn
DePaul
His never actually even been employed by Infowars for me every job
Position U of L
Without Jones Infowars or Free Speech Systems LLC
An unknown employee and have never been an employee so I haven't had to
Official job position
How would you describe your employment relationship in your working relationship with mr. John
Contracted
This is interesting
Who's been there for 20 years
Are you doing what what is I was going to pay insurance benefits of 401k
I would certainly hope so for one of his longest you find that very difficult to believe
Yeah I think it boots and weenies Underoath
That's why I was stupid
If there were very easily attainable records that he
Use employee that has been that stupid thing to say
But hey
Yes I guess it like it is prowrestlingsheet
Alex is Vince McMahon with all these independent contractors masquerading as employees
I think it must be partially his
Kind of decision as well
You can't you can't be an independent contractor with somebody
For twenty years and not at least have a conversation of like
You know maybe we should deal with actual labor laws today in the UK
I make things a little difficult
Level of responsibility
Had over the years I didn't forewarn editor-at-large rights
The bulk of the materials
Like yeah he would have every negotiating chip available to him
Give me an employee should he want to be
I got maybe maybe there is like a mutually
Advantageous
Reason for that I'm not entirely sure what it is but I thought that was pretty strange
We can't take each other
You know that kind of thing like if you go down I am not going down with
Grandad that goes I both directions like something so f****** crazy that Alex would be able to
The distance
You never actually worked
I was just
Which is stupid but
So as we know from listening back to the episodes of Infowars from that stretch of time after the shoot
Shooting at Sandy Hook we know that Paul Joseph Watson did interview Professor James Tracey
Of the crisis actors
And put back a little it was muddy it was a little bit mixed in my
There was much
Lenience giving remember at the same time Paul did say I don't agree with these idea right
Again like I said the Sinister phrase I did say I do
Don't believe that right
So they played a little clip of that and this is really important because
What this does in terms of the questioning
Is
Explicitly layout
Surly is like February 2013
Be polite Infowars world where that the parents and family members were being harassed
The imams after Sandy book
You were aware at this time
30 parents were being harassed by Believers in the Sandy Hook conspiracy
So that is that's demonstrated
Yeah that's not good no good for the Outlook of Alex in this scenario in the clip that is played
Interviewing Tracy
Even back then there's audio of Paul bringing up to James crazy that people are being harassed to there's a
Large awareness of
Oh yeah
So also a back in the early days
Leonard Pozner sent an email
Infowars selling them hate
These people are harassing us and they need to be reeled in I used to be a fan of your show but I think
Now I realize that a lot of these behaviors are being encouraged
The response to that email
From Infowars
Was apparently written by Paul Joseph Watson
Later
Alex's deposition there'll be some
Maybe insinuations that Alex wrote it with him
But it's unclear
There
In this deposition it's clear that Paul wrote it himself
Another stroller a response
You remember writing this response
You bring back that memory
No this is presented to yes I didn't recall it
When you initially broil but yes
Sure
Now do you know did you do this on your own or was this a collaborative effort among other people Infowars.
You remember that
Dollars would it be me personally
Okay
So are you almost done
No nobody else knows how to read there yeah
Defeated Seth hot pack with the rest of the guys by myself
So now this is interesting here for one reason and that is that this would give Alex a little bit of plausible
Deniability
Because the interview with James Tracey was done by Paul maybe I'll write a he never heard it he didn't know about
How to talk about the grass and the parents got that email I wrote
Go back to the guy maybe Alex can pretend he never saw that
Steve Alex Cruz that up later
So what are the things that the lawyers Sea-Doo watercraft on is like
Guys
You really think that what you did was okay
Do you think that would Infowars engage did was alright
To ask people if they actually have morality at all do you have no decency soap all is ask that
Any tries to wiggle out of giving a yes or no answer
But in terms of
What you think is decent and right in terms of covering the story
You think Infowars always adhere to what is decent and right coming the store
Subjective
From us
From my personal perspective
Decent and ride
I would not have covered it in that way now
So that is pretty that I think is where you could say like he's throwing Alex under the bus
That would be the only one
To be fair that Paul like what position is he in
We have no reason to go to bed we like everything was just fine I told them to cut it out
No I with the gift of hindsight realizing how I say was decent
That's a beautiful opportunity
Because I think I would want that question to them be broadened
I've just like
Do you think
Anything you've done they're teasing and rights
I think I think
If you're talkin
Paul Joseph Watson and he's being
This sort of
Bear yeah yeah you don't want to jeopardize
I don't know I want to shoot the s*** with it see what's going on today that the lawyers would be wise to not turn this
Adversarial
Candid enough with his answers
That like why why fight with this British guy when
We might be able to get some
Piece of information
Appreciate Paul more when he's not able to edit his annoying voice together another
Tubac nightmarish
Hellscape yeah it does make him seem more human
So the big
I think one of the big revelation
Is in Discovery Alex sent over all these
From Infowars
And the lawyers have gone through them
I want to do emails they found
Wasn't email DePaul Center
Do Buckley
And Anthony gucciardi
We were apparently in managerial roles can I get you to drop some tunes at my next
Oh that is not there that might be another email
Miss email
Paul is telling them what he has told Alec
He is texted Alex a message and sending it to them in order to
Have it on the record
Call whatever
This out here to show you another document now
And I would like to show you an email
That Euston
In 2015 on December 17th
So we got a 2015
December 17th email that was sent to these dudes
Here is what email
I think that this is where we get into like a real interesting
Seesaw kind of situation of like
Is this a good email
We'll see
I want to read what you said to Alice
This Sandy Hook stuff is killing us
Is promoted by the most batshit crazy people like Rim inspector who all hate
Citizen Way
Plus it makes us look really bad to align with people who last the parents of dead kids
It's going to hurt us with Drudge
And bringing bigger names into the show
Plus the event happened 3 years ago
Why even risk her reputation for it
My first question is
Let's first talk about who Jeff the rents is
Nwbo
Jeff rims is a
Notoriously unreliable
Conspiracy theorists and rabid anti-semite correct
I'm not in school in the Rabid anti-semite but I would say
That's that's kind of a consistent thread throughout this is like the Heap. They keep asking about Visa
Jim Fetzer you know this guy is a
Deeply abuse Medicare
The reason I think that email is a seesaw is because on the one hand you have Paul saying we got to cut the s*** out
Which is good
Because the end result of that would be stopping the behavior
Yeah on the other side of the seesaw
It doesn't seem to come from a place of concern or this is wrong right it seems like well Drudge
Like us so much Ryan we won't be able to get big S2 because we're engaging in this kind of bulshit rice
Know how I feel about that
I knew you'd be like
Fox News canceling Tucker Carlson Carlson show because all of the advertisers dropped
You know it's like
You guys let this white to clear white nationalist white supremacist run on your network unabated
However long in the only reason you're stopping if it's because of appearances and money I miss you there is that
Sort of sentences like doing the right thing for the wrong reason and I
I still applaud like his ability to speak this yeah yeah
Do you know there is some voice there that's like we shouldn't be doing this I just wish it came from a place of
Reason to not want to do this cuz it doesn't fly that like if these things were so concerned I wouldn't have
The problem with
Yeah that may be the case this is probably the best we're going to get from
Probably you know although it does also introduce another strange Dynamic and that is it that is a voice
It's there you don't really think about that the possibility that I didn't forward there is some $0.02 and they
They still do what they do
Scarier
That is a good question because we talked a bunch about how it's like shouldn't there be somebody they're going Alex
Don't f****** do this
And it's clear there are people there saying Alex maybe not all the time no probably not
Control himself I don't think that
Like just going based off this
Genuinely think Alex
Would listen to edit the same time
Not be able to control himself
On the air
Yeah and wind up just
Saying that dumped one of the problems of his sort of improvisational Style
It will lead you to some places where you like
It's not doing not doing it
In the email Paul Joseph Watson says the Jeff rense and Jim Fetzer Arbor
Batshit crazy
Now that's about Ukraine
This opens up the possibility for this lawyer to put Paul in a little bit of a trap
They say he doesn't see you he's real to be a checkmate
Show me how you came to the conclusion
Got these two gentlemen the Infowars was relying on
You're batshit crazy
Because they were pushing
The notion that nobody died at Sandy Hook which I felt was
Not writable immersible albino evidence so that fall was a crazy conclusion to make
Alex Jones
Equally batshit crazy
I wouldn't describe it as batshit crazy
What kind of crazy
I would describe it as him
Commenting on the controversy of the conspiracy theories that were swirling about Sandy Hook of the time
That that's going to be also a sort of refrain is like we were covering what was happening
Kind of
I think when you consider their actual behavior is that
The side isn't very strong now it doesn't seem like a really great legal arguments
But I do I love that I love that okay
Why are they crazy
Ex Behavior Alex does X also
I do like this is in an echoey room because I don't know if anything has ever run more Hollow than his
I think he's just
Covering the controversy like you can thank for that
You're calling in from Jolly Old London
So they put her on this question of like why is this behavior in damn crazy and not Alex
And I don't know if the PJ dubs is is convinced me that there's a difference
Okay so just rinse or Jim Fetzer start pushing allegation
But the children aren't real
At the parents are fake
Let the crying dog shaking and throwing up
You're batshit crazy
But if Joan says literally the exact same words on this telephone web broadcast
He's just doing a good job as a girl
Well
Taconic combine this with your previous question I would say
Description of them as batshit-crazy would also involve
Things that I've said in the past unrelated to Sandy Hook maybe about
You assholes all alien abduction or
Holograms on 9/11
Big thing for awhile so
They have they had a previous has engaging in very obscure can spare
Description of that she crazy
Can you think that their history of doing that as any different than Alex Jones
Buck
What do I say what do I say
No but again
Speech under the First Amendment
I'm not this point I'm not asking you if you had the right to do what we're we'll all figure that out
What I'm asking you is
Alex Jones and it's crazy conspiracy about Shadow interdimensional government
And alien fish hybrid
Things like this
Especially with no difference in how they cover conspiracy theory
That's your view I wouldn't necessarily agree with it
People like rinse and fats are bad
Mr. Jones not in the same way
I would say no in the same way because
Alex was covering the controversy
Sure buddy you get the get the same
Alright so I think that
What you have there is
Absolutely evidence of
I don't have a good answer for this
He thought he was he thought he was so smart when he gave that first answer of like well because they said that Sandy Hook was
Was crazy that you got this follow-up questions like s*** I should have said that everything else they said with f***
Crazy if you like if I'm working for Alex Jones
Tractor whatever the case is and I'm getting deposed
I might come up with a reason why Alex isn't the same as the other people who lie about Sandy Hook
I feel like that's just something
Probably could expect Mike come up
Doesn't seem like there's any preparation here
You know
This reminds me because I was just thinking the exact same thing I was just thinking that their brand of crazy cannot survive
Underoath situation with somebody who is prepared to
More less such that psychopath of like
No matter what I'm the smartest guy in the room
You know I don't need to prepare I don't need to do anything yet I'm going to outsmart this no big deal
Yeah like it that I'm not sure if Paul is 100% on that tip
Because I think he is still being agreeable and
I do see some indications that he might have checked his emails that he had written in their ass
Yeah that kind of thing to know what might come up but the fact that there's no
Good answer for salt like why is this person different than other conspiracy theory like you've worked for him for
20 years yeah
That indicates to me a lack of
Care or concern about it like defending yourself or like
It just feels like
It's a tacit admission that you're not any different
Well I re-up I think
I'm surprised that he doesn't have a stock answer because it was like that would come up in a normal
Any interview yeah
You know the conversation hundred times of your life
Skip this one cuz it's just the lawyer pointing out that Paul was right about Sandy
Alex didn't listen to him
It's true that FairPoint
That's coming up
The lawyers asking Paul about an email exchange that he had with Buckley
Again is a manager person every house DJ and Alex's cousin
So Paul is received an email from quantcast the website ranking
This email was to inform the Infowars it seen a large surgeon traffic recently
And as a matter of policy that make quadcast who could have put a temporary hold on ranking Infowars in their charts
They build that they are they building these protocols so people can't easily mess with their website rankings automated traffic
Just a standard procedure thing yeah it's more effective than our f****** voting machines
So Paul sent this email to Buckley you forwards it on who replies to him
And that's where this clips.
When you sent this email
Buckley m Joe
And I want to read it to you okay
Ted
But no
Surely it's a conspiracy theory
But they are trying to suppress our popularity
Do that
Lizard people
In return to the Ascension pad at Sandy Hook
On sacrifice crisis actors
Here is making a joke
About the craziness of the series is it
You have to have to ask Buckley
Smooth
When you eat an email
In your day-to-day business
Let's talking about lizard people
Going to the Ascension at Sandy Hook and feasting on sacrifice prices doctors
Why don't you say I would presume that is dark humor
Dark humor
This is a very important line of attack that I think the lawyers are going on here I think it signals a really good strategy
See what this email tends to demonstrate is it people behind the scenes at Infowars had an awareness that the things that they were saying
Publicly about Sandy Hook were not true
This email joke it offers a glimpse into the way that the tragedy was being discussed internally by people
Mike Buckley
Who's someone who like I said was in a managerial role and is related directly to Alex
He's obviously joking about this thing with podcast being conspiracy against them and the use of Crisis actors at Sandy Hook as
Is the outrageous example in the joke
Imply that he considers it an instance of something that is mockable
What are the reasons that this is such an excellent line of approaches because the lawyers are able to combine
Private information they founded Discovery with public statements
And sometimes when you do that
You find something damning
Like his disgust
In this next clip
Were you aware that mr. Jones just a few hours earlier
I've been on Infowars accusing the parents of being actors
But I don't think I joked about crisis actors in the email Wilson that Buckley the
Use the same crisis actors
Okay let's rephrase the question
Were you aware that in that email that you said you were having a Buckley
Where he joked to you about crisis actors
The outlandish nature crisis.
But that same time 2 hours earlier Mr Jones was on his show at using Advanced Pediatrics
Are you wearing
How do you feel about that
Popular use
Completely inaccurate in my cannot claim
Not something you're proud of
It's not something I said so
This is also the problem with the sincerity that Paul is kind of throw it out a little bit he allows himself to be put into
Situations where there is no other answer than that sucks
The same day a manager Infowars who's related to Alex with privately mocking Sandy Hook conspiracy
Simultaneously Alex was promoting them on his show
It goes a really long way towards building the case these people knew that what they were saying wasn't true
Earlier in the deposition it was established that at least Paul was completely aware as early as the beginning of 2013 that the fan
Families of the victims are being harassed by people who believed these theories
Which implies that the argument that they didn't know the consequences of their coverage probably not true
And here you have a little glimpse of the behind-the-scenes vibe that really seems to suggest that people in forwards were aware
The information they were Aaron was worth mocking
Which is to say not true
The pieces to come together out of this look really really bad
Considering this is not even close to all the information plaintiffs are working with it really seems like Alex's
Probably in some serious trouble when this is all said and done I honestly think is probably played playing this
Almost exactly like you should
I don't think he has any liability in this Infowars goes away he's still a star
He can he can he can maneuver his way around this a little bit even any contracts to rip up
Now
Here's what's interesting
I know that it came out we discuss this and we'll play a clip of it Alex saying this later but
Robert Barnes is not in these deposition you can tell because no one's yelling objection every
So he is no longer Alex's lawyer
Which confirms in this testimony that he doesn't work at Infowars in any capacity
He is no longer involved with them at all
What about Paul
Mr. Watson
Can you tell me what you did to prepare for your deposition specs
I spoke to Robert Bones on by Jeffries
Okay you review any documents
When did you speak with your counsel
Gherkin
Sunday evening my time and
This afternoon today
The way Jeffries is Alex's lawyer
Is that now the person who you'll hear it saying objection to Alex's
Yeah not nearly as much as Barn
Right but he's probably a better lawyer
These depositions are happening at about the same time these were over the course of two days at the end of November
26th and 27th
And so Barnes is still somehow in the mix for Paul
But not for Infowars
Which I find interesting I don't know what it means it made me nothing but it could mean something
Very interesting
Here's my pitch
Alright this is a
Personal thing
What happened between Jones and Bar
A hundred percent believe nothing that happened between we have
Here's what I'm going to go I don't go it
Telguard might realize that Barnes was trying to take over
That's my theory that is my theory I think we sow Discord amongst
I don't think I don't I don't think there's any likelihood that's true but I do
I will go as far with USA
I would believe it something personal 100% more than any kind of business
Issue that
Either that or he couldn't afford parts that could be even though he was working at
Almost profile.
For exposure
Paul you kind of
Making a stock defense of
All these behaviors all this stuff like we have
You know just the first amendment in all this
Intubate ask him
Education in the fetal Ono when it comes to what is or is not allowed
You really don't have to call
No laws what I do is related to free speech so although I don't know
Academic qualifications I would
Do you like to consider
Reasonably good grasp
That to me is not the answer like I've studied it extensively not in a formal setting
You know I'm aware of these various Supreme Court rulings of limitations
Not Nuance to that there's just like
I work in sort of this Fringe area where we yelled at Free Speech Bunch so I'm kind of
Intimately involved in it
I like to say things that anger people
It seems like he's really taking the idea of
Free speeches whatever I kind of personally Define it as too hard
Yeah so far is he doesn't have to know what it
Is legally
I don't have much of a different perception
After listening but I don't know I don't know I would be interested I would be surprised
Done
Reading on the subject
But I do here I don't hear it from the the answer
Almost it's almost more it almost makes more sense to not look into it
It's so that your ability arguments about what free speech is can never be clouded
Incidental knowledge that it actually
Yeah yeah
Another thing that's a big defense is that Alex isn't a journalist
Right that is going to be something that you hear a bit like this is just okay
Alex is doing is a pedia
If you have somebody of a track record
Being batshit-crazy unreliable
Violate the Simpsons journalistic integrity
What they are saying as fact
Direct
If you were a journalistic
Middle-of-the-road non-porous is unknown commentary
Machado
So Alex Jones is allowed to do
Other other people who claim to be journalist aunt but Alex Jones
Underground journalistic ethic ethics
Alex Jones
Would because he's an opinion
Commentator
And he has no journalistic
Well you don't judge me so now he's not he doesn't abide by those ethics because he's not a journalist
Text restore
This opens up a pretty interesting
Vista
Because once you're doing that once you're like yeah he's just this is all just a pinion
Now it becomes
Pretty important to nail down what's the what's the difference between opinion and
Back and this is something that is going to be a little bit of a muddy
Problem
For both Paul and Alex when they're deposition
Neither of them seems to really understand
The different crystalline fashion the difference
Here is Paul trying to walk that line
Indians versus assertion
An opinion is your viewpoint
Max's already subjected unfortunately in warm side has a set of facts which
Patreon
Neither side has it said facts which they agree on
So it's a very vague Concepts in 2019
You cannot have an opinion on facts that skews one way or the other so it's very difficult Iris
Will you degree there are there certain thing
Like if I was to say
This person is Butte
That's subjective it can't be proven ascertainable e true or false
It's something like
The Sandy Hook school was not an operating school
That can be proven
Sure
BarkBox toys I bought
They can be proven but it's in based on whether you believe the proof that's presented mean
Jesus that should be on humanities gravestone
Well I mean it's I guess if you have to say some
Something
In those sort of under pressure valve
That's really sad about your opinion on that
What is it infects don't exist but that is basically the underlying class Fair
Do you say one side has their fax the other side has their facts and they're at odds
Yes that is a denial of reality and that is
Grab that is stuff that makes it tough
To imagine
Because that everything is the domain of opinion there's no responsibility for anything there's no
There's no reason to get anything right just f****** do whatever you want to do that that's
Makes me really bomb I mean that is really f******
I thought he would say it's like it's like Lindsey Graham
Oh this is The Darkest Timeline
That you're just saying that
Look because they're just opinion so right over it Infowars and also all reality
They should be held to a lower standard than people who
Are foolish enough to believe that exist
Paul expresses that they should be held to a lower standard
Infowars does something like that
Text evidence and makes a jumping
Is it a responsibility to be accurate
In the context of opinion
Common tree
I mean you could save as a
Yeah you should strive to be accurate but insensitive
Banana journalistic ethics bowl game
Based on whether they are opinion Coventry oil down the line journalism
You should be able to a lower standard than perhaps other media organization
Butchered
Wolf
That's not good
Shoot for the stars strived to tell
Screw things up but you know if you lie all the time
That's fine too
That's brutal one of the
Confounding things that just seems to be completely lost on
All of these three people being deposed
Is
How is the audience supposed to determine what is opinion and what is being presented as fact if opinion is presented as fact
Wright's what is the what is the differentiation between
This is just something that
Well they
Use their discernment whenever you
Opinions
And then you say it's in the white paper or it's all been proven right it came out in court document right
Whenever you use those things to reinforce your opinion in fact
Drive to say that things are in the white papers of favor
Play papers you shouldn't be held to that
It's just it's just interesting
Play white paper bananas
Yeah so
That doesn't get resolved
At all really like I don't really think the Paul's testimony is really all that
Except for the part where you get into that Buckley email
Yeah and also there's a bit of a conversation that Buckley attached a meme
Do the email joke back it's like a 4chan meme that has maybe some
Offensive connotations to it
With Richard which leads
Like Paul being like I didn't
Don't know about this
I'm not sure I believe he alright alright buddy
I think that like difference between public and private especially with I get that email being on
On the same day as Alex engaged
Some of this
I think that that is a Grimm
Picture
Yeah it is a peddler of jokes the
You have to have awareness yet in order to find the Crux
Find The Leverage in order to
Elicit the actual joke
Yeah so if you don't have awareness you don't have a joke
If you have a joke
Chances are
And that the second thing is that email that you sent
To Berkeley and Anthony gucciardi that was based on a text
Message that he at least some sort of internal conversation about this not being
A good thing to do
So this interview ends deposition ends with
Name something that Alex didn't think was a false flag
Hilo hell yeah he lists off a bunch of things that Alex did
Aurora
I thought he was right
That's all
So you list off of you
Columbine Oklahoma City all these are false Flags what is something that Alex thought was not
Let's find out
Can you give me an example
Open us mass casualty event
Mass shooting bombing or the light
Stat mr. Jones
Didn't say
I would say that the most recent ones post Last Vegas Massacre
Night of the Dayton Ohio shooting
Shooting
I think after the Last Vegas one he was
More
Radisson tacoland false Flags
After I sue the right
I don't know when you sued in
Yeah you do buddy cuz you are quite astutely pointed out both of those
Paul is asking
What did he pick Israel what did happen what isn't just a government Falls like long cause comes up
Two things that Alex
Categorically
Or false flags up by antifa or whatever it is either a
False flag radical Islam or whatever right wasn't that wasn't that it
There two types of terrorists or something
Yeah it's I don't think
I struggle with like how much Paul just doesn't care what Alex does not spare the possibility that he doesn't know what
Alex thinks about Dayton or the El Paso shooting
F****** show there's a very high likely
Yeah I don't know it's tough for me to believe that he doesn't know what Alex's positions on these things are unless there's just
Not caring at all
About just like
Trash in trash out f****** filter it through
Whatever I'll fix the grammar
Yeah I imagine that's the only
The boss to be honest
Yeah I don't know so I don't I don't
I'm interested to see where some of that goes
I see some indications from that deposition that there's some really
What would you call it
Just some good lines of questioning I think there's some
Positive
Indications that they're onto some
Potentially like really
Troubling thing like I said that joke
I would say
Probably most
Not that I know but like that's something that would be easy to
To miss or to discount but the fact that he was like
This is a joke is
This is the Crux point
But I think that you could
If you're Alex you could say like yeah Buckley's a weird dude I didn't either
Whatever I say
You could maybe I'm just inflating the importance of it because it's the only thing I really
And that's why I'm saying
You know like a joke
Especially on the same day as Alex's presentation
That tends to imply
There's a difference between the public and the private
I'm not sure if it proves it
But I do think that it's enough to get put into your mind like
That seems
Seems a response but we'll see
God I want it if I had
This power I would just be
Like if we reach the end of the deposition
As far as the Sandy Hook stuff goes
Now I'm going to lightning round you like climate change real or no
Go
I think that's an abusive being under oath
But my fax on it
So move on
To Robert to do let's do it by Robert but
RAB do
Jordan
But I never expected is that robbed is deposition would be the one that I find the most compelling
Both Alex and Paul Joseph Watson said positions
Are interviews between the lawyers
Alex and Paul Joseph Watson as people respectively
They're there to answer questions themselves about their own knowledge and experience
Conversely Rob do is deposed officially as a designated corporate representative for Infowars umbrella cup
Albany Free Speech system
Now that was a bad idea
Rob does not seem to understand what this means
It's clear based on the lawyers questioning that they provided Free Speech systems of the list videos for which they need
Provide information about sourcing and how they were produced
Each of these videos which are being said to be defamatory
Contained information that was relevant to the case to you know you want to know where it came from
In order to sort out how these videos were made the lawyers requested Free Speech system
The designated representative to speak
Or the company
But more importantly to prepare
Compile the information they were requested
Ross Muffet robbed robbed
Okay
That's a swing for the fences right there it was robbed his responsibility to speak to the people who produced these videos and
Wrote the article where they got the information from
This is important to sort out because you know if there aren't any sources it could be believable that these
People reading for just making stuff up
Rob do his not prepared at all
His deposition is a profound disrespected this entire process
The reason I think it's interesting
Is it has not read it all like blustery disrespect
This is not Rob dude standing defiant making a mockery of the entire lawsuit
It's a man who seems to really not realize why he's there at the deposition he seems to not know what a.
Corporate representative means he doesn't realize that he's there to speak
Who is the company you can I call you mr. Magoo from the rest of this deposition
His body language and facial responses to questioning read like discomfort in confusion
He's not there to Stonewall on behalf of free speech systems he thought he was there to appear as Rob 2 and I could pass
Where answers like
I don't recall can be used to dodge any question or representative
That question the answer is not acceptable
A company cannot not recall something
It can either know something or it cannot
So in his capacity as a corporate representative Rob do has a responsibility to prepare and know what Free Speech systems
No
Woody's asked what the source for video number one is
You can't not recall
You have to either provide the source or say the company doesn't know what the source was
What he's asked for particular employee worked on Sandy Hook material he can't say I don't recall
You have to say that they did they didn't
Or the Free Speech system doesn't know if they did
Because of his lack of preparation and semen lack of understanding of this role
Rob dudes being forced into a position where he really can't do anything
Other than physically embody the
Competence of Infowars
That might be their only defense
Like hey guys
It's not a good defense a shity run that's what we've got like
You're going to lose that if you just shity and incompetent you're still responsible
This this supports my theory that Alex is just trying to spend all of the money he has
Before the judge Brewster's Million I really think it because Rob do
Azure corporate rapper nobody else
You've been there forever interned he's been there forever he has a you know he hasn't
Has be quote-unquote news director for the the station
Call Cowboys had like executive managerial roles
You've been there as long as just about anybody pulls too smart to do this
Who else would you get like who's still there
Jerome corsi but you have a Magic Carpet representative
He's going to get you in more trouble
Yoga Source is free
Rodger going to prison
Who do you have
I don't know also you can't send it in today with her anymore otherwise who
So like I don't think Alex has anybody else other than Rob that you probably Trust
To not like Owen Shroyer
Slayer
Legitimately do think he may not have any other option
No I think you might be David Knight
Maybe I bet
I feel like
I'd love to see that position with him
Did he didn't get the post I hope you did not not into using the release that then we got it
It's very very very funny even the lawyers for that we're like
God he's too boring he's just too boring to depose
Shell on his information sit there listening
A 2-hour nap be helpful
Look it wasn't a surprise what topics were going to be discussed in Rob's deposition or what capacity Rob was a
Hearing it and yet this is how he shows up
It's disrespectful but it's not Macho disrespect
It's disrespect born out of a person not being equipped
To have the conversation that they were legally required to have
Yeah I find robbed this deposition
Far more fascinating than Alex and Paul Joseph Watson because of that dynamic
It feels like he might as well as like
Sent Brendan dassey in there anybody
I don't know send
The tank
The other reason I find excuse me could you please establish your ownership
Answer your opinion of some people that I'm owned by some things I do
Yeah the other reason that I find Rob's interview and deposition more interesting is because
In addition to being there in a formal capacity as a representative of free speech system
This is supposed to be about the sorcerer
This is supposed to be about where did you get this information from
And that's always something that I would love
For these people to be forced answer is always going to be either made it up or
Weird right-wing websites Larry.
Some completely
Uncredible person like a pet sitter Wolfgang halbig absolutely it's always going to be
Exactly what you know it is but they pretend it's not
Always going to be some flimsy b*******
Disrupt you give
Any source
Okay alright the situations where
Like you know how whenever I talk about like when Alex sits down he's like I'm going to prove Chemtrails yay
Excited cuz then I'm like okay you will actually give me things to go and find right always get pumped
About that is anyway I always get really excited when
There is the prospect of
They're going to
Have to answer that
Yeah it's because
By all accounts this should be there big day
Yeah
They are the truth-tellers Eyeworld they're the ones who were right about everything in the globalist media can't stay
And it for sure setting where Rob do is tasked with laying out
The sources that they have for this
Course for the hit that the coverage that they had
And it's just such a dud they also have tons of exonerating I don't know if you do that they've got them
Any other things Rob is like not going to
Give you any of the sources
You should pretend that their privileged sources or something like that. We we refused to give up our sources
And there's none of them to have some sort of trintellix
There is none of that
Posturing and bravado.
So anyway here restart Rob's deposition
And he says something that is ultimately the least true thing possible
Which of the
The Four Tops
It's listed
The bottom page one
Top of page
A cheetah
Sourcing and research
Forward the video to
Scruggs
Tissue
Internal editorial discussion
Kindergarten
Coverage
Sandy Hook
He is not
So a lot of this interview deposition is hit the lawyer ass
Asking about various people in whether or not they still work at Infowars because Rob has this sort of
I guess maybe it is a thing where if they don't still work there he would
Be able to really ask them what they did or corporate representative
Potato press on people who don't work there anymore Jackson doesn't work there anymore
So there's no line of questioning about them
Why people like Darren mcbreen or Daria
Do they ask
Did they have anything to do
I don't recall and then they have to remind him
Does Free Speech systems no play like I don't know
Constant over and over and over again
Someone is brought up
I don't know why I'm here guys so a lot of these clips are just titled Rob is not prepared
So I don't know how to set this up but Rob is not
Cher
Deposition testimony
Regarding sourcing and research
Videos described
Not much
What
Wicked indeed
This document
Germs
Yikes
That document that he's referring to is the list of videos that are supposed to be discussed so that's the only thing
Let me let me throw this out there for all right now
When you say a woman is beautiful
When you say I'm prepared to speak about A and B
Didn't you say that you're not essentially
Benetton objective fact that you are not prepared
So they have to keep reminding him that he's there is a corporate representative
For that as well
Did you ask him if
He's done research
So you don't know whether
I can't remember any videos
That was
Because I'm not asking
Terriers
To discuss topic
As it applies
Sort my question
Are you prepared
Discuss
The research
The dermacrine was involved
What's regarding Sandy
That happens
So in this next clip they try and explain to Rob like what he is therefore and then they teach him
Alphabet like what's going on
Doesn't seem to really grasp
I think he does eventually but it takes a while
This priest
Paralysis.
The answer is no
I didn't ask what
Weather
Videos
You understand that when you were tab
Representative
Topic that you had a duty
Prepare yourself to discuss that topic
Nobody
Right now
You are under the impression that you
Testify
As to what you
You know Percy
What did you say
Interview right then like
You can get the sense that like we're here to have a conversation about this forcing stuff you have not prepared in any way
You don't understand your role
Is a corporate representative
Why are we proceeded why I would just be like
Get out of here and then we will reschedule this instead they keep going
To embarrass him but it's
I think that
Like they keep trying to dig okay is there something
You do note sourcing of
Trinkets yet information and so they talk about us
Report at the front of the class the teachers like did you do the book report here like
No and they're like okay then sit down
That's it
You should probably
But instead
You know we just trying Soldier I'll just try and find something that you do know the source of that we can work with
Are you
Believe sitting here right now that you're
Care to discuss the store scene
Research that
2y peep
Yes I do
Adam DeVine
What's the source
I don't know this person
That's not a good answer
You say that you're prepared to talk about the sourcing of the video that you edited
And it's probably some random person yeah probably is a problem
Another problem so that's not good
This is where we getting
Trouble with
The law and people who feel like stuff they want to be true is
Yield
Real so prepared for this alright ask me a question
What's an opinion
I have no f****** clue I am so prepared for this next question
What's a fact
I have no clue that's question so prepare
What's up big piece of information in the summer and a person probably brought up
Leads to talking about the Anderson Cooper nose disappearing ship
Green screen breaks believe
And the lawyer gets a little bit sappy you about the ideas that
The FBI as forensic experts that have testified that this is not a green screen
Write this is a compression error in the video that is happening
Hey Rob you doesn't trust that and
I think that you could understand a person getting a little bit frustrated at that you'll believe random people you don't believe me
FBI
He gets a little Agro
Mistake or not mistake
Anderson Cooper was buying Toulouse wasn't in front of a blue screen
The only reason I would say it's not a hundred percent into somebody asked him if he was there and he denied being at the
Videos
Video of a guy asking him
During a taping of a show and said hey were you at the
If you don't know I wasn't
Right he wasn't
A tan inside the
You understand that
You
Corporate representative for free speech systems another lawsuit
In Texas correct
Tremont you understand that
Expert
Who has Decades of service in the FBI
Video forensics
Determined
But that was not a boy
I've heard people say stuff
You know the FBI also said they
Photos of two guys who supposedly bombed the Boston
Marathon
So the FBI weisel
So you don't trust the FBI
I don't really trust much
Okay
Do you trust Anonymous sources on 4chan
I don't know if I've ever used
Do you know that's where the picture of Marcel Fontaine was
What's
Found
Didn't use
Are you
You don't understand you don't know who Marcel fontanez
Is the Easter poor individual that lives in Massachusetts that Infowars
Randomly put up his picture saying he wasn't he was responsible for the Florida Parkland mass shooting
Interpretation
Why didn't put that up but it what from my understanding I'm not asking you whether you put it up I'm asking
Free Speech systems is okay trusting an anonymous source
Completely
Unverifiable
Using that information but not trusting the f
Fiat
Is that what you're telling testifying to
I still don't understand the core concept of a corporate representative
It's been
To cover up cover their own
You tell your uncle that
It's already established that the reviews on colizzi former FBI
What's the worst
To cast aspersions about Sandy Hook
That long cuz they're I think is really like
Indicative
When I said that it's not a brazo like nacho kind of
Disrespect there is a look on his face look like
Like I know you're joking like s*** what do I say but there is a feeling of like
What
Why do know that does makes total sense why would we trust not me personally
I'm here for the company that deed use anonymous attacks report
And yet I am
Saying the FBI's experts are full of s***
That is a tough line to walk in the same way that Paul is trapped with
Hey why are these people insane Alex is totally fine
It is like yeah you know what I really
Don't have a good answer for this
He said he talked to his at
So his attorney must not know that he was the corporate representative right
Otherwise the attorney cuz it seems like the only advice that his attorney could have possibly given him is
Say you don't know over and over
Dobrik
Vitiv like been the thing where you talk to Barnes Barnes & Noble longer their lawyer and he was not doing
A good job baby like
Tell him that the FBI's a bunch of liars
I'll probably more billable hours
I don't know what yeah I have no idea
It does seem like they've had a change in lawyer possibly there's a mystery
Caitian possibly
Nobody didn't get the right info where it's supposed to be
But yeah it seems absurd to me that no one was like
When I when you appear right
Mnl48 you could have been talking to his lawyer and the lawyer like you know your appearing as a corporate beside you bet I do
Or we pay the lawyer assumes he knows what that entails and he doesn't it
If possible
Rob do you think you're prepared for this be back okay then you get on in there buddy
So Rob claims that respectful
The victims and family members
So he was unprepared for this this is one of these like you know
Just a slow motion volleyball hit that Rob is doing
It just like immediately cuts to normal speed and someone on the other side spices in there for me
And I believe kids are trying to kill in the beginning
And if you look at our articles
We always talk about the victims we were never
Disparaging towards the parents
Video of mr. Jones mocking Robert Parker
Bothered by mocking it
Crying is grieving father truly
Robbie Parker's father I don't know if ever seen the video
Caesar
You seen the video of mr. Jones mocking Robin Park
About crying over his dead son
Right
Video
Your corporate representative
So you're not prepared to talk about that video that's listed in Plano
Petition that
But you have duty
Need to prepare for
Video
Robbie Parker crying over son
Ono of mr. Jones mocking
Robbie Parker
Crying over
I wouldn't be either omad
That stuff back when you're trying to present like we were always very respectful what about this time Alex is mocking
Who's on first
Illegal
Do this
I don't know the law well.
A lawyer supposed to like his contempt
Contemptible legal definition but I find this to be
Describe it is a rank disrespect not
Middle finger but we just like I don't even care enough to do what I have to do
Locked up
So
What are the other big things that Infowars did
In their Sandy Hook coverage that is particularly disrespectful
Is that they
Put on screen
And posted the address that Lenny Posner used to pick up his mail
Yeah the PO box that he was using that was
I believe the address of the honor Network which was the foundation that he put
Together
To try
To get like pictures of the children eloquent conspiracy theorists would use their pictures
Videos dmca structures
Heroic
So Alex
Was pissed off about this because some videos of
Fringe weirdos that he Associates with we're being taken down at the attack on Free Speech
So
They got into the honor Network and posted Lenny posner's PO Box address
Right on
Which
Some people could say is
Robert
Probably not a safe thing to do
So they discussed that a little bit and Rob
Makes pretty
F*****-up claim
The videos.
Had taken down
Are those true
Sitting here
Might have to see the video
Uno
Sitting here today weather
Buddy I think a lot of it he pulled down just cuz
They were given carte blanche
And you're just making that up you have no evidence
I have no idea
And I just want to make sure again we're sitting here as you make up information
Makeup information
Okay
Okay it sucks to be in that situation where you are just making stuff up and
Just to be clear you're making that up
I mean
I don't have evidence to answer like
Yeah
Yeah it's very childish it and I think that's what happens when people do stuff like info
Ford Hazard cornered like you can't really have any other
A response then like sort of indignant disappointment
It's that it's
It's sad now it's it's still wall like it what are you okay you Corner him and he just says fine
You think I make stuff up all this
I'm never going to actually believe that you're never going to be satisfied no
And that that's what I was getting out of the beginning of what why this is a more compelling
Deposition is because
Presumably this would be where Infowars it supposed to shine
Yeah if they were what they pretend to be
The sourcing
Deposition would be long
On every on the record everything
Yeah Lynn Posner was just launched to take everything down and
Like what
I mean I feel like it
So
Rob it is also unprepared because he doesn't have access to all the videos
To go over right
Just this one more time
You are the
Corporate representative
YouTube took down their YouTube channel
So all those videos are gone right
I don't know. Dog internet 8 homework
Rob claims that one of the videos that you supposed to prepare all the sourcing for inside like
Can't find it
And then his lawyer
My God he is just not putting up with Rob spoken
You don't have
By you you mean
I didn't have it in any of the searches
Okay where'd you search
I've seen some of these actually one on the internet see if people and reposted them
I didn't find anything
Refined
Stop it
People repostar stuff
How long did you spend
Sources
Video
For Sandy Hook false narratives versus the reality
Electrical video Maybe
15 minutes
Are you aware that in this
The problem is
I think I discuss this in the lab
Deposition
We don't have videos that's the titles that you're using or you're referring to YouTube titles
Those aren't always
What's a video file as name
When he gets up
Urdu
You gave me this video
Free Speech systems produced this to me not you too
Understand
So
You have it in your possession
Correct
What is possession
I don't know if I
How on Earth could Free Speech systems
Reduce a video to me and it not be in your possession
You had it in you spoliated it
Which is the destruction of evidence
Or two
You never had it yet somehow magically produced it
Which one of those is
It's probably more Act
Or 3
You're just not prepared
Discuss
Those three I think that's probably
Video you gave it to me excuse me sir I would like to amend that back to Magic
Asthmatic admissible in the court of law
I mean that is so disrespectful that is that is just like
Manifestly
I don't care
Yeah I was told I was supposed to do all this stuff I'm not taking this seriously at all absolutely
Horrifying maybe not the right word but it's it's
It really is
Is this is the first time I've been surprised in 2019 right now though
So the subject
And every know the Kraken right is released from time-to-time sure and one of the things I find
Particularly interesting about their angle on but button is
There's a unified front
Pushing the idea that damn Dandy went around it was yelling at people at Sandy Hook
Galaxy like I don't want anything to do with you
You're fired get out of here in the first place microphone screen that says Infowars
Cut it out how do we how do we do
Chain that illusion
You are
The lawyer brings up an email that they sounded discovered
Shortly after that video
He was fired because of
What he was doing
He wasn't he was doing contract work for smooth either accept
Or not accept
And after that you stop
Accepting
Stop responding
Last time
So it's weird that
Produced in this case
For the first time
Email
You're involved with
It has damaged dondi
Being fired
For how he was acting at a Donald Trump rally
In 2016
Fun fact
That is a fun fact
They really should have went faster Discovery stop
Really screwed by this like we just sent everything over we didn't review anything
These but the plaintiff lawyers are going to look through all that stuff that's gone to find these things
Hey you know you said you fired because of this abusive behavior and all that stuff that's a great story but it turns out
It was because he was acting like an idiot at a trump rally in 2016 you didn't want to be associated
Right
So fun fact
Thank you for bringing that to my attention you personally are on that email today
I don't I don't I don't recall and I reject of did the FBI send that
Gmail
So they get to talkin about this video that Alex put out which is called Sandy Hook vampires exposed
Bob says he can discuss the sources of that because he worked on it
Then the Lord brings up something
Unfortunate that you think vampires are real
Yes
2:19
Final statement
Is Sandy Hook vampires
Do you remember that video
Who researched the information
Myself
What were your symptoms
Kelly interview
Any others
And then I believe previous
Videos of lucrative
Are you aware that
On April
22nd 2000
Megyn Kelly
You haven't even had
Disgusting
Fun fact
Yeah the source for that video is Megyn Kelly interview
Afterwards
Can I go back and revise my answer to Time Travelers real
Would that one help
So I think this is understated but not do his job as a corporate
Representative that is I can only assume the reason that the interview kept going was just
Because the lawyer really wanted to expose
How
F******
Shameless it doesn't feel vindictive it don't like they're questioning doesn't
Xavier too far into like
I'm going to humiliate you I think the reason that I'm saying that is simply because
I think if it were me
In there I probably would try and set more traps
Do all sorts of crazy if that's your ankles you would go on it but I
I don't think that they resort to too much
No but like I said
Yeah and I would say from the last deposition to this one I see
Not a market Improvement because I think I'd be condescending for me to say but I see far more what
They're trying to get in this
And I think that it
Problematic for Alex like I think it's much more troubling probably a large part of that is based on the Discovery
Process moving
Being able to match up these private Communications along with
Public statements and I think that they're doing
Good job
Unlike Rob do come on
Where is uranium
You think
Without this
I wouldn't either
What
Really really
Really
I'm not going to answer that what do you think that was about
It's a fair question
Actually I did I didn't really think that's a great question because that is indicative of the entire ethos
You also wonder to like it's not a question that's meant just a fraud like there's no
Did exactly what he was supposed to do
So like I said in the Paul Joseph Watson one there is a
Attempts to sort out the difference between opinion back
Presentation of it on the show and it comes back up here with Rob
Where
The discussion is broached
How are people supposed to tell what's reporting in WhatsApp India
As a journalist
Don't you have the duty to be right
And not burst
We're not always wearing journalistic at sometimes were commenting on
So when you're commenting on something you just make it up
It doesn't matter say your opinion
And anyway is that differentiated on air
Does mr. Jones say
Here
I'm just going to make stuff up
Here you should trust me because we're truth
Journalist
Does he do that
I think it doesn't play Devil's Advocate as much anymore because of
Because I got sued
Do you guys
Not want to answer my question or do you not understand what question
I think that question is being asked
Credibly clearly
How are you supposed to tell the difference between opinion presented as fact
And
Whatever
Okay they just gave me a very clear question and I'm going to respond with eight
Time-based question
Which has nothing to do with it's completely impossible to answer
A dangerous
Then for them to
Infowars to even
Give a bath
Because it is every single thing is presented
100% truth
You can't you can't unsee
You can't listen to Alex Jones for any extended period of time without
Coming away with the impression that he first of all is wrong and second he is absolutely making statements of fact
Whatever ways
He can couch it I don't know
Based on the law
Where the line is or what's IDs on
As a consumer of it
And a listener 2-0
I have no problem
Saying that they blur that line
Perhaps intentionally and it's super unclear
Because you can you imagine
If Alex is just like
Yeah all the stuff is just my
Yeah that's just my
Like what I think about this
I'm not saying that it's based on
When I say that it's all in the white papers and everything I say is proven right my opinion I believe
Leave that everything is been proven
I'm not saying to you that it has been proof
What is your show then
Well I mean my opinion is me
Dang that everything has been proven to you
Is a statement of opinion
We will never solve this because
Circle
This deposition with Rob do and
With the lawyer asking if Rob is proud
Avoiding forward.
Wait now is that a personal question or is that a question for him as the representative of free speech this might be personal
So he asked that and Rob's answer
I think might Loki mean that
B b b
Way more of a f*****-up bad dude
That we pick
Is this answer is
Borderline sociopathic
My last question is
Sitting here today
Africa
Are you proud of
You don't say
Will shooting a have
I think our reporting
Stop what was going to be
Anti-gun legislation
You didn't answer my
My question
Question was
Are you proud
Of the information that you spread about Sandy
As a company
Is that what you wanted
I don't think we're going to
What do you think
That's what you want
I think
That when you're being asked are you proud of this
You should not have like if you don't want to show ass
There's enough there's some sort of an answer you could give that's not yes or no
Your mistakes were made you going to are you
Proud of every mistake that you've ever made
Presented by other people as a complete
Credible Source times you believe people who aren't you shouldn't believe
You can do whatever you want
He's answer being I believe that there was a lot of gun legislation that we stop yeah
By lying about Sandy ad
So expect an end justify the meme arguments to do are you saying that you spread
False information in order to achieve a political result
Do you know we have a word for the that
I mean it does seem to imply that he doesn't have
Qualms with
Like putting out false information if it's
Expedient to his goal
Yeah and that to me
Underoath
Yep speaking for the company sure he's not good now
Yeah I guess
Haven't you said hey we stopped a gun legislation honestly
I don't know if kerbals would have said he was proud of the misinformation
Consider like
These gun paranoia fears that they've had over the
Decades
Like
They didn't need to fake something like this they didn't have to engage in this to stop that legislation
Play kirtans of money from the anti-gravity
B effective
Gun
Advocacy groups do enough
To make sure that a lot of that legislation doesn't pass
You don't need
People like Alex doing this sort of delusion
Dollars on lobbying directly to congressmen and essentially have purchased their votes
Did the NRA ever
He lie about a mass shooting
B of A
Deposition is
Like this
Real spectacle of incompetence and
Disrespect that I find really interesting I find it to be
Like
Like a real low point
These depositions in particular
Types of potential the sources
Find out information about Rob do with a backwards beanie on just being like
Do anything
You're speaking as a company
The company doesn't know anything
That's so funny
Yeah I didn't at least it was just because if anybody
Had ever given me
We are going to depose you
You're the stuff here's the stuff you need to know
I would have done the s*** out of my homework so nervous yeah
They're going to depose me I'm under oath I better get my facts right
And these people are just like
We had Paul Joseph Watson is the opener
Rob do is the feature right
Which is the best spot as as clearly as tradition we got our headliner
That is a course Alex Jones being under deposed again
So we had like these
Paul probably was about an hour-long deposition robbed is about an hour 40
Alex is almost 3 hours
Him under oath
A large part of the beginning of it is discussing like
What means did people communicate with each other internally it Infowars
Which is to try and be like do we have all these internal communication
Email
August did y'all use Slack
That kind of thing and Alex is very
Wishy-washy about all of this
What's Slack
So he can eat in this
Cooper sklepy claims that he's never texted with anybody about
So you're saying you never receive text messages relating to Sandy Hook as your testimony the same that you've never sent a text message
Or something
Talk about Sandy Hook
I very rarely talk about Sandy Hook.
So your testimony as you've never sent a towel
Text message relating to send you a
To a fellow employee resource
You're somebody else
Okay
That seems to be in direct contradiction to Paul Joseph Watson sent to Buckley in
Which was a like a on the record version of a text
Listen to Alex
Yeah I'm glad I was literally waiting for him to be like
And here's the text you provided us but I don't think he needs to
I don't think that the lawyers need to bring that out you just need like here's Alex being deposed as it's not
So one of the angles that I thought was really interesting at the beginning of this conversation with Alex he's getting into
You ever disciplined anybody hit Infowars we just talked to him
Could use a little question is all about weather
Someone has put out. Where's the question is
More just like have you disciplined anyone for anything
Sienna
Let's talk about
Request for production number three on page 4
This request
Thought all documents reflecting disciplinary Acts
Taken against any employer free speech
Systems LLC
For publication of false information
For breach of journalistic ethics
December 4th 14th 2012
And April 18th
Irresponsible
Correct
Yes
None
N6
Years
Apparently
None
No one has been disciplined
The stuff I mean it does really feel like their defense
Yeah I'm at I still think that's all I can say that doesn't get you off the hook for those course not
No that's what I'm saying I
I think they I think they know they're going to lose because
Of course they are
F****** let's
Let's push this back as long as possible with Rises out of Erie frame this
It's not necessarily that they think they're going to lose
But they
I get the sense that
They think it's more likely outcome than they might have previously
Not surrender is not giving up or anything like that but
He's weird
This hinge of
Call opinion
Yeah kind of thing is
Not what you'd want to do if your Infowars you don't want to testify and then put on oath
I'm not talking back to you
I mean yeah but by their own definition of facts nobody is going to Care listen to them because they're just going to say
What using
Like facts are not going to convince anyone
Maybe
So it before we get to some more talk about disciplining
Employees we get to this idea of what is an opinion
And what is fact
See if Alex knows the diff
Okay what would you think Sandy Hook is not an operating school you think that's an opinion
I'm just saying right now if I told you I said you wasn't an operating school
Not what I meant
I see that
I'm asking you if I said to you
Right now I'm going to say it to you right now
Mr. Jones
Sandy Hook
Wasn't an operating school
Did I just make a statement
Or did I just make an opinion
So those sorts of statements can be set on Infowars
Without socks
Contacts
So the reason that he's trying to nail this down is because
Trying to get the sense of like if you're an employee for Infowars if you want to just say something on air is there
There any kind of
I believe prior constraint is there anytime
How would you go about making a claim like Sandy Hook wasn't open
On air
And it turns out well they said it
Except that in that is not enough
That is something that is eat that has a truth value attached to it
And
That I think is
One of the clear thing that comes out to me in the course of all of these depositions
Is a staunch refusal to understand or accept
But there is a difference between a fact and
Yeah I don't think that these I think that there's a strategic reason for it
But I also think that there's a possibility that they
Like sincerely don't quite grasp
I genuinely
I really I really don't think they do and if we're going by if I'm going by that like
They're the weakest link in this propaganda name
I think they're low enough on the totem pole where they're convinced that there is no
You know like higher up
In the in the upper echelons of journalists at Fox News who are opinion people have
Fox News they have to be aware that they're not telling the truth
But these guys generally don't believe there is an AA truth
Yeah and I don't believe there's a place it's really hard for me to tell because it is it seem
Possible
That there is
An inability or unwillingness to understand the different on their part and it's possible
But I can't really necessarily believe that because I also think that it's exactly the last Refuge you would
It is where you would go if you like well everything is indefensible and my behavior is
Clearly
Shown to be bucked up yeah there's opinion
Right exactly where you would try and hide out
That's true I mean obviously they can't combat it with any kind of facts
Cuz there is a functional used to find it hard to believe that it's just like
Inability to recognize reality
Yeah if it didn't serve a purpose that maybe like that's fine
But that's something that I hear so often from a lot of people is that
Baseline beliefs
I don't know I think it's a combination of
You know
Purposeful ignorance along with a
Willingness
What is it
Constant bombardment of this as true you know like they
Somebody repeated it often enough
And I don't want to really engage with effect of repetition isn't reality so
I meant to say that it's
Yeah like that's kind of their operating see
We get back to these employees who have not been
Discipline at all
And we get some example
What's an editor
Publishes an accusation
That someone is acrimony
And in doing so they relied on a source
Whose identity
They cannot verify
I have no idea who it is
A totally anonymous
And then it turns out
That that recording was full
Is that okay
You would take disciplinary action if that
No what kind of display
General a district-wide
Know when kit Daniels
Randonautica
Accusing an innocent young man
Based on a
Whiskey could not verify
You didn't fire him.
That that individuals name was not put out
Bad
It was from another
In the record
On purpose
He intentionally on purpose recorded an accusation of a crime
Based on an anonymous source
Whose identity he could not verify
Correct
No it was a
The match
What sites are you talking about
Before Kate Daniels public
That's your belief
Insulting a tweet
Define anonymous
Twitter account
But I do remember that
If if that was true though
If he just
Relied on
Two Anonymous sources
Identity could not verify
That's a fireable offense
That's not good
I cannot believe
That he is not clever enough to sense that a hypothetical question is going to lead to a literal question
That is insane to me that he's answering that question honestly as a guy
Answer that
Answer a hypothetical
It's not like he's going to ask you a hypothetical question that's going to exonerate probably not
So yes that one and then there's another example
You didn't take disciplinary action against any employee involved in the false
Recording on the Chobani yogurt
You publicly apologized
That was a publicity stunt by Chobani yogurt Norristown money it was altogether there were migrant workers being brought in there were right
Self
The Reserve Board member
What
Didn't David tell you supposedly that there were no right
That was false
I don't know what you're talkin about
He just commit another cross I'm not entirely sure it does seem like Underoath
He just said that Leah was
Involved
I wonder is that a violation of
Seems like it would there's no way that it's like oh you can't say it publicly however
In a deposition in another lawsuit it would be totally fine and when it's released on the internet we won't consider that
Haha yeah that's insane
Until you got that
Really f***** up answer and then also a demonstration didn't know when the whole Chobani thing haven't no one was
That's bananas
I'm starting to think that that public
Genuine
So
Any disciplinary actions about
When your recorder Owen Shroyer
Tried to falsely connect
The Austin pizza restaurant
Eastside pies to a pedophile ring
You didn't take any disciplinary action
Correct
You never taken any disciplinary action against any employee for any of the false things
Said about Sandy Hook on
Infowars
Pretty clear what I'm getting at
That you create environment where everybody is not in all punished for putting out
Impact player actively encouraged to do so seems like that's the pattern how do you know
Not know what I'm getting
I am very clearly leaving you
That's that's why is Aurelia so like come on man
So then he comes up
And of course Alex wants to downplay his relationship with the Kraken
Okay that's mr. batondy
Yes I think
That's the man that
Enforce it to Newtown
Report on Sandy Hook in 2040
Correct
Listen to Boston
Do Infowars
Sent him to Sandy
In 2014
Right
Cavity did reporting
4 + 4
In 2014
Incendia
He was working for
He wasn't your reporter
You're very handsome
He certainly has that was certainly heard him described
Same place right
That is an opinion
Zoe's
Alex tries to play the same game
That like a Rob do does and that is that our sense of decency was offended by what their padabi was up to
So we told him to suck off
What did you think of mr. madani's work in Newtown in 2014
I did not follow
Okay when you
Did find out about it what was your reaction would you do
I don't remember the specific
When you testified back in March didn't you say that you would seen what he did had a reaction to it
Are you talkin about this report
Talking about support
What you think about is work in Newtown in 2014
Do not get your you're not reporting for us to stop using the bi flag
E-year okay yeah
I like your demeanor Kraken
The guy who I specifically praise
Or his demeanor I might as well have created statue because he disrupted Boston
Related press conferences
I didn't like the way you was carrying themselves this is unreal
So ridiculous I don't understand
Why there
Why is Alex doing both
Trying to do both the I don't recall and answer the
Because I think it's hubris I think I think that sometimes he feels like
I can handle this
Feels that way a little bit
No because Rob he's not prepared he hasn't
Just really sorted out
There is a part of like I don't understand what you're getting at is kind of
Stand some of the lines of questioning and what their purpose right you didn't discipline any
Give your employees for instances of
Being lazy be happy being irresponsible
There's a point to that line of questioning
In the same way with Dan baton do you like bringing
Him up there's a reason
They were going down this road were there depositions in the Home Depot
I don't think it proceeded to that point you can be settled before
Any became public
Yeah
Cuz it kind of feels to me like
The advice that they must be operating
This is going to settle
So don't worry too much about react yeah
We're going to settle this the same way that we did with the other law I forgot what BART it's going to cost you money
Yeah anything else just said that I would die before I give into the sea
I will not be taking down by yogurt never
So Alex
Get another line of
Very consistent is
That I don't believe that the lawyers think that Alex has any sources
Really
Outside of Wolfgang halbig Jim Fetzer
They seem to be pretty clear
That like any any question
Kind of traces back to them a little
And so on
Really wants you to know that Jim Fetzer wasn't thesaurus
In addition to Wolfgang halbig one of your other sources
Recording with Jim Fetzer
Fitness professor
He was one of the people questioning
One of your sources for Sanyo coverage correct
Remember
Call my show
Can you testify that mr. Watson was telling you that Mr Fetzer was bad
You shouldn't be relying on them
I remember Paul saying that like that's alright.
Mr. Fetzer is a retired professor in a rabid anti-semite
Right
You didn't know mr. Fetzer was a rabid anti-semite
You didn't know that Mr Saatchi thinks the Jews did Sandy
Just like the Jews did 9/11
Alexandra Lee know more about the the world's that he dwells in
It seems like it would be helpful to him
This is banana
So in the deposition know the name of the guy that they fingered as the
Parkland shooter which is crazy because in all of this
Negative attention these lawsuits
You would think that this would be something that like okay we got to cover our bases on
Yeah recognize the guys name
Now Alex doesn't know somebody
You remember at the end of the 2016 election
Media coverage
About how you would sit on your show that trumpet calls you and thank you for your help in the election
Some of those mainstream media sources were
You remember.
Yes
2 days
After that happened a woman named Erica Lafferty
Yoo-hoo
The daughter of dawn offspring
She currently suing you you don't know who she is
Okay
You didn't know that
Can you didn't notice she currently
Is the named plaintiff in a suit against you in Connecticut
Call Lafferty versus Jones
Oh I've seen that name
Crazy
I don't even understand how you can be that level of
Cuz it doesn't feel like that's not a genuine answer a genuinely believe he has no idea
It seems like
When he's lying or trying to find a way to lie but now
Deposits for about 45 280
There is a there is a strange
Enable just goes to the larger picture of like what I see is
Like just
Late disrespect
Gohan
By these people
They would
Actually be
They have they have to balloon explain the lack of preparation advice
It's possible or they just thought like these does go put these out
Will just be able to
You know keep this under wraps wow
So this is
The lawyer plays a video of Alex's
In italics is discussing some of the evidence and some of the reasons why you know
Your suspicions around San Diego
And this is one of them
But the biggest
Piece of The Smoking Gun if you would
Avocado
Is the Wayback machine internet archive
We see Sandy Hook Newtown website
K through 12
Zero traffic
Two thousand eight nine 10 11 12
All the sudden
It's impossible to have zero traffic
2 AK
Tire
School system
And the word is
That's cool system
Was shut down for those years
Put the record show
Jealous
It was open
So you might have some questions about how that evidence works
Very confused one question
So you said in the video
We see Sandy Hook
What's the website
70 traffic
So
Internet Wayback machine
Do you believe that that shows internet traffic
That what you believe
What shows is what's the archive
There's also
Go back to Jersey
And that way back machine does not show internet traffic
Material in traffic
You were going to stick by you thinking
You chose traffic
Internet traffic
That's what it's measuring
Traffic in posting
You ever read the Wayback machine FAQ frequently asked questions or figured out what it is
That is not with the Wayback machine.
So you have this like it's
The Smoking Gun is Alex called it on this 2016 videos that is a coup
Beat
Misunderstood misrepresented piece of information
And what makes it
More troubling
Is
You say there's things showing that there's no traffic coming to the
What are you talkin about
I think you could pull it up pretty easily because it comes from Jim Fetzer
Bookwright you can just open up Jim Fetters book Noah
What's your phone's going to caution you again
Answer your question
You can see it's very frustrating
Affiliated with any party
Is a private person pay to provide service
Come here to try to write all this down
Let's try to behave in a deposition
Let me finish my quest
You didn't check any other Connecticut school district website
Because they all look like this
I don't remember
Well let's say hypothetically if you were gone and you would seem that every other
School District website looks just like this
He pretty irresponsible to go on the internet
Call The Smoking Gun
I was predominantly talking about the other information that I may go back
I am
I'm glad he finally understood what a hypothetical
Yes you're right that would be wrong
Did you do that
Ride hypotheticals are leading to
Yeah I mean the problem with that is like
Yes or no you're wrong oh yeah Connecticut school districts have the same pattern on web
Back machine
If you did look that up then you're willfully lying if you're not then
You clearly just took this piece of information
Presumably from Jim Fetzer
As Italy's of his book
And Alex does not want that to be the perception because Jim Fetzer just lost that big lawsuit
WeatherBug
Jimmy
If you put out that book back then
You know still now he's losing a lawsuit
It tends to look like Alex could be heading for a similar path I believe Alex is never ready
I believe I believe that he has been given
Several quotes from
Or the same information like let's say he read a Blog that was based on
That maybe one of his employees
Give you a cliff notes
Which is why it's important for the Rob interview to have actually had some substance to it
Price down what's the process
Nope
So in that same clip from 2016
Video record show that the school was closed
And you get to ask about that
Right after that
Wayback machine
You said the word is that school shut down for those
That's what the records
That was your
Correct
That's what I'm asking
Those records
What are you talkin
You haven't done that
You've been under lawsuit now for over a year
Sandy Hook related
Multiple cases
And you haven't done anything
To go try to find what your sources for these claims
Is that is that an opinion or a fact uncompelling response
I did all that
So Alex like I said you just really doesn't want the
Perception to be getting his information just from Fetzer at Epic because that looks really bad yeah
So he keeps claiming that he can produce other evidence
But then
Somehow hasn't
So if I wanted to know when you say the records showed
I can show what I was talking about that
There you can produce whatever you were relying on it
Specified
Lottery
Sure
When you
You're asked a question
Produce to me
Your source
Or record
Information
You relied on
They say the school was closed
That's something you could do
Yes
I don't know.
What you looking for
If you had record
Information
Infrasource
Showing the school in America's most horrifying school shooting with actually closed
Price save that
What specifically mention I can bum and I remember what what what they were poking out what was going on
I'm asking you if you would have saved
Ernst
I'm asking you where you at information
Let the school shooting at is the most famous in American history
Actually occurred any school that was closed down
Wasn't operating school
Did you say
I don't remember
7 years ago
Okay
Originally run businesses
And it was a long time ago man I had this game-changing information as ads long time ago
So
This narrative is bunk and I think that in this
Course of this conversation they pretty well laid out like you were full of s*** on this and his only responses
I guess I could find her information but haven't yet
So the other one another one is the Anderson Cooper nose thing
Kind of talked about that on the last deposition so it doesn't come back up
Another one
Is Alex has this job narrative about a CNN
Interview
That took place and it was two people that were out in a remote location
And you can see the same car past behind both of us
Alex is saying that this is
Meant to be
Faking the news and it's meant to
You know it's supposed to be like oh they're pretending they're in different places but you could tell they're in the same place cuz the media is
Sure
That has nothing to do with Sandy Hook
But it had to do with this media liar
Yeah it was actually people waiting for the Epley that was the jury verdict in the Jodi Arias
Murder trial
So Alex is like they're pretending they're in different places but it's clear they're in the same place
Ergo CNN lies
Biscuits dismantled so f******
You remember that bus and going behind them
The story was there at the same location
Explain what you think's going on here
I'm saying just they were staging
They were
Different locations
Where they stating that they were in different locations
That's what I believe the report was
DC out the top of the picture here you have
Little boxes that say where they are
Are they in different places
Are they both say Phoenix
Remote
Sure but they're only 40 yards away from you
You don't remember what they're covering here
He has no awareness of the details of these
Pieces of his narrative
It's so
Tragic
But it's so obvious
Panthers he could ever offer
If if pushed on it like why do you think that they are presenting themselves as being
In separate places
They're waiting outside the courthouse one person stationed over here the others over here
Enter having conversation while they wait for the
Sure you.
But that's not suspicious they didn't presented as anything other than that
You are presenting it as something other than that
List biscuits today that like
When people ask is if you would you actually sit down and talk with Alex
Like this is what you get if you if he thinks he's telling you the truth
And if he's under oath
Yeah
So
After this point I think you get to the only point
The interview wear
I got the lawyer gets a little bit
Pointing the finger at I
Are because he starts comparing Alex to Nancy Grace
Tri-Cities the same thing as her
You know I don't mind getting a little personal and being like you should visit what you doing
But that's a statement of fact
You're basically the same thing
I don't follow Nancy Grace
Really really Reckless track
And you do the same thing with the conspiracy to us don't you
No I questioned a system known for
RWBY Raconteurs.
Obese men in the Benghazi stand Oz we've been lied to so much
It's like most Americans I'm question
What question did you ask
I was talking about some of the question
I'm not I don't what was the quest
Question
I heard a lot of State
Can you tell me what the question was
I was putting out some of the
Reasons people
You were putting out
Assertion
That were false
I like this approach because it's not getting bogged down in the like what about
Babies in incubators it's just letting that roll off his back what was the question
What are you questioning that was perfect because the entire the whole babies
He's doing his classic laundry list of things hoping that you'll get
Caught on one and then he can be like
Yeah and I believe was in the Rob do one that he brings up also the the babies in incubators thing
And he's like the lawyers
You know
In that case
If
One of the people in like let's say saddam's Army
There's a people who are being lied about in that case
If one of them wanted to sue the media they should be able to write
These little unexamined of flip itself.
See how easily they can be and Alex accidentally does that to himself
Because throughout this entire interview and deposition
Alex keeps bringing up questioning Epstein's death
And it leads to at the end of this Alex stepping in a big old Puddle of Mudd
The dad is going to be his big like
What you do you say I can't question things but what about
Much like I robbed you in the
Do you have babies in incubators it's turns on him very quick yeah this is very clear that
Alex and Rob do exist in a world where they think they're smarter than every
And they don't have to prepare
That none of this is going to be a big deal I can take care of this
You're absolutely right
PJ dubs comes out of this looking like looks great I am out of my class here so I'm going to be as honest as I need
Need to be while still controlling what I can I'm going to get this in get this out
It's an hour-long deposition the reason I do that is because there are pieces of evidence that he was not in
With this b******* you can take a little bit of an external like
Well look man I tried to say don't do this I can't control what goes on it and yes I still
Still work for them afterwards
How many independent I did what I could
Time to work
He's a shitbag for so many other reasons but this one will take off of his list
Low priority
Alex
Being asked
About that video that they just played
About all this stuff
Or ask any of that true
Literally every single
Assertion you made in that video
Not one thing you said in in
No
Nice
Namely
One of Alex's other big narrative
About Sandy Hook is
Bloomberg sent out
Email the night before
To get ready
Sheriff's up big chair this apparently probably it's not true
Female that comes up there was an email sent the day before
Dang
Get ready next 24 hours are going to be a big
That email you've been asked for that
And you say you don't
Right
We were we were covering reports of the email that was sent out of activist groups has been on the news
Where were you covering it
Women who you cover
We were covering the report
Activating Rivera
Orientation
Okay well Sears
I thought there must be some email
Coincidentally sent
On the day before Sandy
Dublin burgers
People sent
That you must be wilfully misinterpreting
Promise
Nobody would look at this has been able to find any evidence
And I want to know if you can
Taking your first investigates
Well I must that's why I've asked you questions in Discovery
And you haven't been able to produce
We have an email in Gmail
Other news reports
Could you find those reports if you needed to
Could you identify your source
See what you doing
What do you mean you can hold back a source of fuel
What does that mean
Force
April 4th premiere
Text about that's how I remember
News reported on
Why haven't you
I just can't
The great thing there is that that's
Greeley water I think that's the only time it really comes up with the idea of holding back information holding back to source
And Alex is doing it specifically to say that's not the case
It's the only time with that trigger it looks like it's going to be pulled
Iiii
I'm Amazed
The clear message that you get is just like
Okay can you
Why haven't you produce this
Well
I can't prove all my claims but I can't I have to watch that video again
Everything I've asked you to produce in Discovery
You just sent me a treasure Trove of emails that you didn't even read
And then you didn't even bother to look into other s*** that I asked you for $94 bill
Bounty
Got censored and then
Man so Alex's asked if he is ashamed of his Robbie Parker impression here we go
Does bit about Robbie Parker
The whole
Fake crying B
Or are you
Totally fine with seeing video yourself
You did
That is an interesting response I
Instinct is to protect his abilities as an impressionist
Pensively
Well well well you're doing a shity me come on now that's weird
Quality
Wow so
Spice dancers
Play a video of Alex and Rob do talking about all of these anomalies in
Sandy Hook case they're saying these things always if they're like
Definitely like well the school wasn't open your all up yet
Do you think not as asserting that mess facts
Or statement
And so when they come back from
Again the question comes up of
Do you know the difference between an opinion and a fact
I want to ask you about the things that you and mr. do
He said in that video
We can agree
There was a list of factual claim
Correct
No I was giving my opinion
When you say porta potties were delivered an hour after it happened
They were delivered center after
That's not what I'm asking
Resting is that a factual
It's not
It's not an opinion
That is an assertion
So you call it
Alex keeps trying to use this excuse the reason why I had a little bit of a sort of fumbly around
Answer to your like you saying these a statement
The fact is because Alex's defense is
I was just explaining why people were suspicious about Sandy
Write to that's his way of getting around like these are things that I'm saying is a
I'm just explaining why people were suspicious
But if you really break that down
The way you would do that responsibly is say
Here's something that's not true
This is why people were suspicious about their is Ally going around that much a porta potties Wordle
Liberty instead he's listing off all of these assertions effectual things and being like
That's why people had suspicions
The way that's presented
Retains the truth
Of these statements that he's making
Or the presentation of Truth
Beats Pill
Even though he's saying like this is why people were suspicious XYZ
That's still
At least in some fashion
Presenting x y and z
Here's why it's wet outside of my apartment
Somebody let go of somebody open the fire hydrant that is a statement of fact
That's not why people think it's wet or that's not why people are concerned that it's wet it's just
What is right if you're doing this as a like this is why people believe this step and your
You're doing it responsibly
And not in a way that is to lend Credence and credibility to the thing
You doing at the Pumpkin Show
And Alex is not doing that he's decidedly
So he tries to explain that is just so thin
Started the video talking about the wrong name being given
Tillandsia had his older brother's ID on him
Why does that support
Conspiracy
Why is that weird
I think the problem 21 people are questions with a lot of
Why why does that make you cry
That Adam Lanza had his brother's ID on
That was robbed
Okay why is why is that
Listener green with it right why are y'all question
We were pointing out why people question
Okay when they said
Rob said they're pulling guns out of cars Lanza had a shotgun
In his trunk
Why is that support
Question about whether sand
Memory services
That was at inside of it was inside the Bushmaster
And you understand your AR-15
Actually this wasn't 7 years ago
This is April 27th
I know I'm just saying going back
That's so weak
Such a weak defense for this
So
The thing is it Alex like I said I keep coming back to this cuz I think the sense that I get
Is that Alex is really trying to protect
From the perception being Vicky's just repeating stuff from Fetzer
Individual sources that we research yeah I am repeating whatever anybody
I think that that is really important
And I think that's what he's doing
Send you a kids going around in circles with their hands up around the school
That is false
The truth
I have to review it again
All these things you were saying as fact
You were saying them just a couple months before you were
All these things
I don't know about that sir but it came from people question
It's important to him somehow to disassociate himself particularly from Fetzer and I think it's good
Cuz he lost a lawsuit
Not because he's a rabid anti-semite I don't know about gravity
So
Disclaim
That's a Dubai porta potty
Alex's wishy-washy
The next one that says
Why were porta potties sandwiches fruit
Drinks
And chips Broughton
Set up for people at the crime scene
Inside the
School
We'll take a wild guess right now weather.
You think people ate
Food inside the school at the crime
That's what you think
So that's another thing that
Put on your show without you
You're saying is from holiday
I thought you just agreed it was
Okay okay
You just said earlier probably got there
Great is if they win
This can't if they don't get taken down by this case
It's going to have to be on some b******* technicality thing where the judges like
Clearly you did all of the wrong things that is it but according to the law of this is
It's on a Tuesday and you said two bouquet
Like that's the only way
Sovereign citizen miracle
So we can sit in his chair and be like I'm proposing you what are you doing
So Alex also
Wants to fall back into this place where there's a lot of questions cuz there was a ton of secrecy
The around the case
I didn't even put out a report
Tell her whatever you know like
How I supposed to know there's no official information out although I would just not believe the official information
Alex
Can you take a wild guess as to whether or not that's true
The part about why didn't they let paramedics and EMTs into the building after
27 children were declared dead
I remember being reported
Can you force true or not
You didn't March right you read
Two different EMTs who went into the building
Perform services in the building
You read those reports correct
What country was the level sacred seed
Domino's Pacific for years and years
Official crime report
Very long not years and years
About to go back online
Crush wine
Carlos unpack all of that
Because first of all
When you read those reports
In your deposition
You acknowledge that
Paramedics
Building correct
You showed me documents
Recently come out when do you think
I just know there was a big
Controversy about
Cover in your testimony
Those documents were out in 2013
And here you are in 2017
Talking about there being no paramedics in the building
Pretty bad errorism
Absolutely
People need to get fired
Instantly deflated
That like
You see that super long pause and what about Yaya
No I thought you were a globalist and you're trying to defend all the globalist stuff
That is something that does come up to is the like
You and the estate
You think of it I wouldn't sue the mainstream media if I had the opportunity to do think I wouldn't take that case jacks
I think I am the establishment I am not
It said it said it said it is queer
That Alex is still even in this case under oath
And the here in this deposition
It's clear that he's still kind of at least
Somewhat thinks that this is part of a
Conspiracy yeah absolutely it's very it's very tragic
I'm just trying to figure out exactly how many other offenses
Since he's committed in this
Deposition like the hum
Like there's no way that you can
I don't know
I can't
I don't know enough internal details
But it doesn't look good
So
Earlier we talked about Paul's deposition
And in it Paul said that he wrote that email back
To Lenny Posner himself
Now because Paul said that
There's plausible deniability for Alex to pretend that he didn't know the family members were being harassed
As early as 2013
Alex completely blows the Alex
We got a clear path to the end zone for you just run that ball right on in there ever call 11
Different remember it's a clear path to the end zone but it helps him and he destroys that
And then you and mr. Watson together composer
Correct
You don't remember saying that you and Mister
Watson where did this together
So
Is the older there's differing
Slightly different takes on who wrote the email
Dr. Oz clear that he had a conversation with Paul about it and
Wanted to invite Posner on the show
Indicates
That he was clearly aware of all of that
Yeah
So in that email question
Do you think he knows the difference between
A criminal trial is
Not the finer points really does feel like he's trying to
Call display
I don't know
I don't recall
I don't know see you guys can't get me on it you can't force me to testify against my selfie I don't know if
Appearance of playing dumb
And I think that's some of that is
Is
Is just
Maybe you believe that
Call Marin they can't prove
Exactly how we arrived at the conclusions we arrived
So
Let's just keep that vague even if we lose we'll lose a ton of money but will be able to keep on with the
Or or something
More just
Defensiveness
Anything else
Almost instinctive reflex
If you're someone like Alex you never want to give up your sources because it will only reveal
But you have no idea what you're talkin about
I think that's
When does the Dominus in real life
I could find that I've been busy I don't know any of that I think it's because on some level Alex
Knows you dig too deep
Into whatever his sourcing was for any of this
You're going to find Fetzer you're going to find how big
And it's just not going to look good
It's going to demonstrate that he never did any kind of works
Corroborate anything
It's just going to it's going to look real bad like his disciplinary
Anything Goes
Outback Steakhouse over there
So in the email DePaul Center
He was saying we do not
Encourage and condone the actor
We are just leave distanced ourselves from that
So they ask Alex about that this is a yes or no answer
This pathway is blocked
Mr. Watson rights boxer
We have not promoted.
Quote unquote
Actors
In fact we have actively
Who's ourselves
Over the next six years.
You didn't you didn't
Yourself from the actors thing you actively embraced
Brought it up
You produced a video to me
Entitled
Crisis actors used at Sandy Hook
And has an!
Not a?
What's up video you admit to me you endorse
Videos
We gave you work work work work videos that that we were in
Infowars produced the video and uploaded it to YouTube
And it was titled crisis actors used at Sandy Hook
Contradict
Yes I mean I need to see that
Do you have why did you say yes there is no idea because
If they're asking the question with the specific of an! Set-up?
You got it know that they have that
You got to know if they have evidence it's on the list they already told you that they have
You just admitted.
How's it going with
That was a typo
Fake a heart attack do something to get out of there
What is an interesting question could he have just been like
Can we stop real quick he doesn't deserve a break just because like I don't think it's because
Of a question
Is bad yeah but I think
He could have called for a break
Yeah Oregon can they reschedule
Maybe I mean
Baby they have been
We don't know how many times
I've been put off or not
I don't know I feel like there's a reason why you would proceed with the Rob do deposition in spite of him being completely under
That's fair
The normal thing to do would be like
Do the work you need to do and come back in a week
But I don't know I have no idea how these
That's the only thing that I mean if I was in there and I got two of those hypothetical questions and I got a ride
Hey we're going to break for the next two to three weeks while I actually read up on all the s*** you're asking me because I'm
I'm going to lose this time
Not looking good
It gets worse
Because as we talked about earlier
Posted
Address of the mailbox
You're right
And
Bad
My opinion is
And
What makes it worse is providing surrounding context to it
Which state do
It does appear that Alex
Was mad
Epistra Posner
YouTube strikes on unarmed people who were using pictures
About their dead children
You didn't like
The foundation
Poster with running
Voice didn't remember that
I remember those guys with some of my thing I said nobody.
Parkland Florida
Just say no one died again
YouTube
Cuz I didn't say nobody.
Said to send her parents
Stirring up a hornet's nest
Right by coming after you
Cars for sale
You told the Sandy Hook parents you're not a goddamn mess with
On your show you showed mapson addresses used by a parent
You can play
Cousin your mind
He was running an anti-freeze
Translation
I did not show
What do you mean you didn't show it
Aren't you running forward
U-Haul in parking lot
Music.
A public figure
You said that I remembered once trying to find it and
This is a shame
Parking lot
Post office box
Certainly never said that but I thought they were saying
All their houses ever done that ever said
Harassing myself
You showed mapson address
Refuse my parents
That's what you did
You showed mapson addresses used by scanning
Apparently
That happened
We we show
Where is foundation
Shepherd
We're saying it was fake
That argument is so thin
The idea that he had people who were saying
This is a fake Foundation
And he put up the address of it and show the Google Map
To the location of it
As a way of De bunking
This was a fake Foundation is Ludacris
This is a this is a
Conversation
With an eight-year-old who stole a cookie
Every single like
Ultra I'll throw out anything to avoid saying yes
What's so crazy about it
Weird
In my mind is that
Alex is presenting this thing that is not
A bad thing it was actually trying to help mr. Posner but also he did do it
Unless you convince him he did do it
Sure play me the video
I didn't do that before that I was saying or stirring up a hornet's nest no not someone to mess with
Who's cry
Find to help
That's why I'm not somebody to mess with I'm so helpful
Don't mess with me I'm trying to help you find this hard to swallow
So now the topic comes up of when was the
Fire
Alex plays.
Or the truth of the matter is
One thing about it I do need to spend time in Berlin this Morris
Sisseton Sisseton
Cuz it's like I remember a lot of it
I think if I go dig even deeper I can
You know that your second deposition
In the Sandy Hook
You got more going up in Connecticut
You got Discovery in Connecticut
Even Discovery 3 times
In Texas
And you're telling me you think you need to go borrow in and figure out what happened
Who is very much asking about Mr madhaniyan when he was terminated
Actually mr. Jones
Your document production in this
Shows you did that in May 28th
Right after you
The truth of the matter mister
You knew immediately after being sued
Barnes
That's real
I believe he is under oath that you hear stuff like that
So
Do the lawyer wants to really nail down
Tease
How all of Alex's sources are really just Fetzer
And so
This is really into
Anna video Alex is saying that
You awake
Retired policeman in school investigators and they've all been threatened he's like creating the perception that they
Tom the people
Being frightened about Sandy Hook
This is this is just great
Mister Jones before we break
I asked you about
Your statement about what
State police officer
Threatened
He told me mister how big
Make somebody
Can you said that
School investigation experts were threatened
Who is that
There was some other groups and people matching questions
Other professors
Other than job
Even you said that in addition to those two groups
That
Some school safety expert
Righttime Enola
You're not
You're not years old
Shut the fuk up
You just answered yes by the way you said no is
Yeah that's bad
You just said yes
Maybe one of the other professors was James Tracey
Professors in the Bay Area
But all these other descriptions like
Retired state policeman and school investigator are being presented as two different people they are guests.
All of these
Trying to create
Chorus of folks who just got to do
I would like the stenographer
Make sure that the record shows while he did say no please put a parentheses
Yes right next to a beautiful lady
Wow asked about his narrative surrounding
Ambulances
At the school I don't think
Comes off looking
You setting up video ambulances came an hour and a half later that's not true right
Are you going to claim in this lawsuit
Backyard discovery
Wonka memory
What were the results of Utah
Whatever
Discovery
Correct
I don't have that problem
That's just nothing
That is
That is tragic
In Wisconsin
Judge just ruled
You know the 200,000 people could be purged from the voter
Because
They have to respond within 30 days
Do a change of address
And the judging is ruling literally is like
30 days I don't understand you can get it done in 30 days that's plenty of time
And that is how people are going to lose the right to vote
Alex can get away with this s***
That's unacceptable
That's unreal baby it's the end of the road I hope so
Because this is
I mean just this deposition alone should be enough to be like guilty I would be so fascinated to find out
Someone who likes Alex and believes him
How would they interpret these answers
How do you interpret
Like he's clear
Inability to
Answer any direct question when
Anything he
Should be saying would be completely sculptor anything
The key presents the way he presents himself on the show I have all this is all bruised and got all the documents yet if he had
Have any of these documents
This is the context we're in bringing that out that would be like oh okay well you Arkham
Completely
All right to do this and in fact all my God what's this
Yeah you weren't your correct here's here's the thing if
Anderson Cooper did a three-hour deposition
He answered every question confidently and clearly he had evidence backing up but there is one question
Action words like
Oh man I just don't have that one in front of me
One of Alex Jones listeners or Alex himself would have
Grab that clip of Ben like
See he's a lying. You can see it it's all a lie
But if somebody can watch this deposition and not Come Away with being like
Oh that guy did everything you say
It's
Weird I just don't
I don't know how
It would be interpreted like
What is the what is the logical explanation for why
He is behaving like that
Other than
Flippant disregard
Because that's not really a good
If you consider like
Worst case scenario
You going to lose tons and tons of money and possibly become financially unviable as business
Best case scenario
Gets away with everything and everything is good why wouldn't you tend towards behaviors that would be
Towards the better outcome
Acting like this is only going to make it more likely that the bad outcome happen
You not acting in his own best interest
And that implies to me
Can't acting is best if there is no best case scenario
Best-case scenario for him as he loses and gets to stay he still wanting some
Sure you know
So now the lawyer plays the video of Alex
Talk to a collar and saying I didn't believe it at first but Sandy Hook was totally fake there no kids
Kildare and all of that
I don't recall that I'll have a well when pressed on it his explanation of what his show is
Is very bizarre luminaid
Legitimately
Looking at
Going back and forth
Yeah you said both things and then you said things that were true
Let's just go and use your word opinion even though we all but we all know that not an opinion
Your opinion is full
Kids
Died
Right and I didn't kill
You see me anywhere in this deposition saying you killed shoulder
You think you're here cuz you killed children that's the echo but it is like I'm Adam Lanza
Responsible for the things you
If I put a journalistic report and said this is fact then that would be what I want to show talking about how I
My feelings and say that
I would say I'm gone all over the map
This is internal
Absolutely not
Talk about my feelings
So apparently Infowars is Alex talking about his feelings unless directly
Presented as fact
Which again b b opinion
Feet now in earlier in his child custody case when his lawyer said that he's playing a character
Mated your character and that's me it's a compelling cuz it's
Lawyer and also it's in the car
Context like a family case
All very messy
This is Alex directly under old saying of my show is mostly be talking about my feet like this
Yep
Buy show is
The closest that I can get to therapy as a
Toxic male
That's what I've got this is
The area I would like
Things to go in wearing now we look at the show as
What is the say about his feet
Not the interpretive Direction I want the show to ya
But it's going to be hard for me not to
About that
A lot of this could just be a manifestation
What you
Feel
Right but it's presented as being backed by the white paper
That's not good baby just joint nonsensical thing
I don't know the thing about the deposition
Especially here
Is I don't know
Whether or not he believes anything he's
That's true I just I can't
Because there's so much of him here that is
Wriggling that is desperation
Noemi even tried in one of the clips that you played earlier I noticed that he was trying that like
Apologize to Authority kind of way of getting out of
Something like yeah you know what you're right we made some mistakes I'm sorry about that will work to fix that in the future
As though he was talking to his boss you know instead of being like
It really does feel like he thinks he's talking to somebody who can make it all go away if they just
Decide to leave him alone
That's weird that's wild
So Alex wants to talk about Epstein
That's interesting because
It's a deposition
About
This I believe whatever he says now I believe he's
Which strange is Alex should have known
That something was up because the lawyer does want to talk about it
Still doesn't God bringing up apps
You will get that I know and I know Alex I'll be like Legend never ever speak
You know what actually a good point that this lawyer is going to make
He just doesn't get that he doesn't get that he thinks they're having a conversation not the lawyer spend
Hours and weeks preparing for this exact interview
I think maybe number taken gasket
But I think one of the things that you and I agree
Large segments
Indeed the world
Psychopath
And in fact because of that
Wendy's really really strange happenings of Pepsi
When Epstein killed himself
Incel
When you're supposed to be underwater
My federal officials
Suspicious to save them
I think a lot of people in this country
Think it's most likely true
A lot of people think
And now it seems a massive public figure he's been in the news
Partially because of something called the Lolita Express
Yes
And we in this country gets talked about public
When you agree
Two things
One Alex be terrified
Right now my hackles are ready I sent something bad coming around this quarter
Do you like
Standing
The second thing is you can tell how much differently Alex respond
These are direct yes or no quick answers you're on my team yes yeah yeah yeah
I'm here
He doesn't realize that the entire abusive bring up Epstein is to use it as a case study
About why it's okay to say whatever you want about Jeffrey Epstein but it's not
For someone else let's say
That there is a security guard
At that federal penitentiary
Missing Bob
You want to get on TV and say
Bob Smith killed
And you were wrong
You be held responsible
Private citizen
Gorman
Trying to get on the news
Issues
Question
Weather was whether whether Bob was involved or not
Didn't know
Is that okay if you're wrong
Where does Bob Smith dies responsibilities Bob Smith
Make that right
Not if I did it
Out of out of your believing it was true
That is a weird line
But he Alex's pretty far off the beaten path is there in terms of
His understanding of what is appropriate with private
Public figures
Things they try to lay out is that
Bye
Implying in and saying directly that no one died there
What you're doing is accusing all of these people of gigantic crime
Not only because they're involved in some elaborate hoax
But because let's say
If you're a parent and your child it didn't die
You have filed false police report like there's all sorts of implied crimes there a host
Yeah so bye
Behaving in this way you are making
Criminal accusations
The gas people whether or not you directly say it
Play the games like I didn't say these peoples name
Like what you said
My clients son did.
Because you said no one died you are talkin about that
I would like to
Ask you to explain that
Because I
Because it's clear that this
Down the road
It's going to snow
A private vs public figures
Alex just starts rambling
Probably one of my bigger laughs of the of the whole procedure
Some stuff really
It's hard to believe that
That's all
You know questionnaire answers
A large question about
A couple things about
It comes down to with your Converse
Sullivan
Intentionally on l
Tried to hurt people
My questioning big public event
We need to question
We don't worry North Korea I asked you sir
Would you be responsible to Bob
And I told you that it would be
Pacific
Yeah
Access
Dr. Bob
I was doing
No
Then I'm cool
Out
That's probably not the case with private citizens
Ashley if you're relying on people like Jim's Restaurant
For no reason
Okay so
That's
That's insane
God
You know what question
I love that that's my favorite
That's my favorite line of the entire day
Yeah cuz I've always
I've always wanted to ask you exactly what's up
Through a lot of s***
So
One of Alex's big defenses is basically that he believes
That the family members are Publix
He believes that just by virtue of them being victims and family members of a tragedy
Have entered the arena
Whatever no fault of their own
Massive amount
Immediate
On them
Has that's raised them into public figures
Opening them up to now it's interesting because
Literally
Courts of rule
Well there's that respond well to that being brought up
Okay but what I'm trying to get to you
Did you agree that there's a difference
To an internationally recognized
Famous person
And a person spitting
Millions if not billions
At a private citizen
There is a difference in journalistic ethics
And at the end of the day with a private person
You would agree with me the info work needs to take
Appropriate
Make sure reporting phone
Most of all we do
Upon entry and opinion
When
Parents and others become
I would figure that go out with a political
Mission 2
Chuchu restrict gun ownership
Into the arena
Unicorn
Protection
Will you were involved in a lawsuit
Veronique Delarosa
Reno Texas court of appeals came back and told you they're not Papa
Democrats Court
Sure they'll be delighted
What's a Democrat
Yeah
Alright so
Essentially he believes that no law can be made
Unless it's made by people who agree with him
And he doesn't have to follow any law
Eddie Eddie Lovette a Democrat
Judge
Says it's real. Seems that way gacha
Cuz they're all demon Club
Right
I mean that is the logical
That is a logical extension is he actually believes that there
All out together in a conspiracy
Take a break
Come back there's just a couple minutes left here where we get
You got to update on Barnes
Should I get the disc mounts right and then we also get first
Alex
Needing to clarify something about his sources
They don't exist
I find this to be weird
Clarify something
Open clarify my route
You kept asking about
Sources and at Willy's horses are
We have articles
Thanks.
And so
I've given you
Everything we've got
Thanks to other sources
Are online
Anything that
We have to give you is outside of my office in my office when you say a source
That was a few newspapers in archives and TV reports
That are outside of my office on the internet
Your forces are things that I'm
Thinking about to go out and find
So
You degrees it's not
General practice
This is not part of your operating protocols
To save
Corroborating information
Underline
We we save some other than overtime it
Information
Call wife
Most of what we have is
Is Article 4 Linx
The links
Go to outside websites
Outside TV station to network
That's what I go by
Remember where I got something
I need to go back
Articles that you've been given
Call the Links
Through their mother
Olink
Always links II
He's so unusual the concept of a follow-up question Jordan that explains everything
Thought that he came up with a brilliant
You really did think he really thought that okay
Look you're a newbie to my whole version of Journalism all right so when I have a source now this
A lot of other journalistic out
Outlets don't do this
All I'll do is,
Hyperlink
You know what I'm just going to call it a wake
Hyperlink might be a little hard
I'll make one of the words like a little blue right and you click on it and that's my source right now.
Internet never heard of
And who knows what's going to get burnt so when you click on the link sometimes
Not there anymore I'm sorry this all makes sense
Please do not follow up with any other question
That's
I'm flabbergasted
By this level of
Needing to clarify that I really think
He seems to be thinking
You know what the great defense
Sometimes some of these links are dead later gone you've already talked about the Wayback machine
I understand that but that's only for traffic on school websites day I forgot didn't you know that
Forgot that's all it was
So here we get to this update on lawyer
Certainly not Alex
Understand
Liquor Barn
Robert Barr
No longer representing
Is he still employed by the company
General Counseling in now
While he was there to do you have any managerial responsibilities
Do you have any director
Did he at one point service
What was that mean you trying to
I was just trying to get the case of
Dyspraxia
I wonder if that line of questioning has anything to do with like a suspicion that he was doing more
I don't know
Could this be
Start of standard question
Stop
Frequently Barnes was appearing on Infowars Alex said he was going to give him a show
It does seem to like
The fact that that line of questioning was he a director it Infowars roll
Makes me think that they might have a different suspicion but I might be over reading
I don't know the first thing that I thought
Weis
What they're asking
4A
You didn't disclose some
Like there's some communication between you and Barnes or
Between
Somebody
That you guys didn't disclose or wonder
That's that's the only thing I can think of in there and your argument that you didn't disclose it is because he wasn't an employee or a man
I wonder if that's the case
But it could be just now
Yeah I know it could just be
Is Byrne still around
So here's the last clip
Alex being asked if he's sorry
He's not
And is Big dismal
I want to ask you now looking back on this
Are you sorry
Good place in my heart
So much
That's so much that.
Wow
Everything I've done has been from a place of really Prime
Truth
So I'mma roll proud
Skeptical
Selves
Let me get this
These videos we just watch today
You're proud
Video
I'm proud of the compendium of my work not
Small quick steak
And I'm a good person
Little Bill
We were wrong about you.
What you say
That there's They're laughing
.
So when Epstein didn't kill himself he's going to go out on a meat that's his plan
Alex is deposition
That's horrible and stuff
Wow it's strong stuff from everybody has really
This
I wanted to
Present-day episode 4
Today because
I want find out if you did that surgery
Studio
People ripping computer chips out of there
Sometimes things happen
It's on a curveball
You got to watch seven hours of testimony
From these abuse
Obfuscating weirdo
I I can't
I can't hang with him
Being like
You know it's really sad that the mainstream media isn't
Trusted enough anymore that my brand of
F****** with people
Is it
Like it's almost like him being like well it's
Your fault
Did I even have a Jew baby do you guys made this face because sometimes you get things wrong
I can lie and this is your fault
Manifesting
Yeah it's a very
And Alex you're not
Tyson
What is so interesting to me is how all of these three
Are so different
10 inseam
Wow
The feeling is so very different like Paul covering his ass kind of 100
Agreeable agreeable
Light weekend
Yeah you being cooked
Completely underwater not knowing what he's doing no
I can't believe that that
I genuinely can't believe it's legal I really can't believe that what he did is illegal and then Alex
Being Alex
But also just
The feeling that I get
Watching this deposition as opposed to the last one
Is it feels like Alex's
Closer to the wall like it feels like a room is closing a little bit he's out his ability to dodge things
Is
Greatly diminished
Without Barnes there just yelling objection all the time
It kind of Hit the flow of the the questioning is much different
The lawyer not having to deal with Barnes Antics makes him
Way more effective
And the way that like
Repeatedly Alex would do those things like the babies
Incubators and the way it's just like
Say whatever you need to say I'm going to proceed not allowing him to do those pivots and Dodges like
You can see what happens then
Yeah I know it's okay
Patient with
He's like okay we have your little tantrum
Then we're going to come right back here I'm not going to engage with you
I'm not going to do man
That really bums me out
That that's true because that suggests
Then
That Barn's
Did Alex a good job
He was serviceable being like a complete
Accessories
Rebecca on Wednesday but this is Ben
Deposition
But until then we have a website
Fight night go to bed
You got to wherever
Listen to podcast you leave a review
Sure
I will be back but until then I'm Leo
Dzx Clark
I am the juiciest Ice Cube
Alex