Damn important
I have great respect for its knowledge by now I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight.com
Sit around with novelty Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Damn
He's the reason for the Xmas season what then pray tell is your favorite Christmas tree
Their Christmas tree I like peppermint bark
I think we talked about this before I've been roundly attacked for this
I don't take care too
I do I do I don't want to hear the b*******
I like peppermint bark
Everyone go fly a kite interesting leader
He candy canes with peppermint bark
Partially based don't like
The licking on the account
Candy is generally available
I think it's
The combination
Into the chocolate
It's like texture and also the flavor like
Like it's much better
Good with the richness of dark chocolate
A peppermint comes together in a very nice
It's dark chocolate peppermint flavor combo
Just because I assumed that peppermint makes everything white generally have like the dark
And white peppermint is the KKK of
The Christmas tree
I don't like all these attacking my beloved peppermint bark
I'm not attacking my mom always used to make also like egg white cookies that little meringue
Oh yeah I've never had one of those
I like those quite a bit too but I don't really know how to do
Describe them
Is an audio media
But to those would be nice I don't know what those are
Traditionally Christmas but I associate
Yeah of course any kind of homemade
Cookie is
Christmas
Who's on Christmas bread
In all its variety
Abscess bike astronaut about peppermint bark
A little bit better about it apparently
I know a lot about Alex Jones
What about soy
Going to be going over December 13th
2/16
Okay but I'm excited
To get to that but before we do get there
Books
According to show
So first of all West thank you so much you are now if I was you want
Next Michael thank you so much and I'll probably walk
Thank you Michael Bianca thank you so much
Talk to you on our policy walk
How about a walk
Are you very much let's all next Christine thank you so much and I hope I was wrong
Next I Am The Whistleblower thank you so much you are now about what you want
And finally like to thank you
Somebody who I donated on elevator bubble we appreciate that very much so often with an
You at
Thank you so much
She went out.
Business
Heroin
So good
Freakishly large
Thank you so much Austin
Website
And while we're on the subject of thanking folks like that I gave Robert Evans and behind the bastards we are the
This week.
Enjoy
Give me a shout over there
Defensive
Okay myself I need to stop trying to make
Jokes at the beginning of those episodes
The last two times we've been on there I've tried to open with a joke and it has fallen
And I look like a f****** a******
It takes you a little bit to get revved up into the floor thing I think you
We came all this immediately following that Taraval the Mike Adams episode I made a
The joke about us being the first repeat cast
Supposed to be a joke
Pterodactyl There is five minutes of stunned silence
Chicago is a big city can have anybody as a gas but you chose us I look like a goddamn narcissist
I was trying to lead into saying like
You go to head Rahm Emanuel somebody with particularly weird
Yeah could have been anybody about ketchup on hotdogs
No joke no joke
Anyway despite that I really appreciate it thank you to Robert and apology
Cut that.
Hey that's my main issue
So Jordan like I said we're doing just
Number 13
Today and I realized it's been a little while
Drop here is a nice out of
Merry merry Christmas
Love it
That's like a
Card you get in the mail right there that's that makes me feel great it's one of the cards you open
Put it up and it starts playing that song for that's audio peppermint bark for me
Man I think that's a curse to get a Merry Christmas from Infowars
Certainly
So the last
We checked in on the present-day stuff we had a situation where Alex was really going hard on this their microchipping homeless
Yep and I'm going to
A chip out of somebody on here
F****** body with sorting out the Hippa forms otherwise we got this setup
Everyone's going to love it
That's that's dropped
Shroyer interrupted the
Impeachment inquiry made a big deal out of it and that got the fact
Did Alex and now
He does not care
About that people experiencing homelessness in Austin
So Thursday waiting for him to say he can't afford a scalp
We would we'd love to but we just don't I can't use a razor blade literally just can't afford
So he Thursday was the day that those depositions
Yes
Alex Paul Joseph Watson
And Rob to
And so we went over that on on Mondays episode and I figured like
See if there's any kind of a weird
Response to that
Cuz Alex is pretty responsive
The news about himself
So I decided to jump in on Friday
On Friday you recorded a little introduction for the show that sounds like he's
Speaking from inside a Nalgene bottle
It is Friday 2019 I am your host Alex Jones this is going
A very important transmission is going
Steering the ship
Those two things
You cannot exist still the same state
Informative show hosted
By Tom pappert is it
So I did not listen to that episode
ICare what's on peppers
Springs
So we jump at 2 Sunday
Sunday the 5th
Kirby vacuum
We talkin about stuff and just taking a day whatever right
Alright so we got to go to this
And
Alex's and he's really easy to cover everything up today if we're covering the 13th through the 16th we really got gotten through
Through the 13th through the 15th quit 10 minutes of the episode where the last day of our coverage
Will be a 45-minute episode
Alex's in studio
And he starts off on a really weird now
I want to give you this
Upfront Maybe by way of an apology Maybe by way of the
Explanation
Some of the way I'm going to cover this episode is heavily informed
By Alex
Is deposition
And a lot of the
Other stuff in those Depp
The recovered on Mondays show
I figured
We Now understand
Away the Alex defense
Is
It's all about his feelings about his feelings blurring the line of what's fact and what's opinion
I don't think there is another
As as an exercise
To an extent
I am going to
To frame
A lot of my response
In terms of asking these
These questions
And looking at this
As
Is this is feeling
But might get a little bit tired
I might have like a broken record at times
Only listen to the first half of whatever open
So Alex is a bit f***** up
At the beginning of
Trump demanding action
I've got feeling things have changed
The globalist had a deal to back off they haven't backed off and because of this impeachment that
Behind the scenes.
Update
Is
About the fact that impeachment is
Proceeding is right-wing on going forward
And that's a really interesting clip to listen to in the aftermath of the deposition in that Sandy Hook lawsuit
There's a bunch of little things that Alex says that make what he's saying mean
Literally nothing
But the intended impact of his words based on the context of his show in the reason
Is anything but meaning
The first point is Alex's
But he has quote a gut feeling that things have changed
Granted we know that
He said approximately 10000 times it is gutted
It literally never wrong and he has
Literal psycho
Powers
The end of the day all he's doing here
Feel that's true nothing actually is
She has no proof that anything has changed
Just a feeling he has a things of Jane
Premier Alex jump
I'm still talking about and imaginary behind-the-scenes deals the globalist
Had to back off which
They're not honoring
This is not a field
This is something Alex's directly asserting as a fact
The globalist tented
Deal I had a deal in place
To back down they are not backing down
So date aunt is over
This behind-the-scenes deal isn't real
But the claim Alex is making involves a real imaginary thing
Now to further complicate the
Alex is using his feelings
Namely that something is
To assert that this imaginary deal is not being held up by the globalist side
The way Alex is reporting on this real imaginary thing is being effect
Acted by his feelings
The headline is that they talked is over and the globalists are breaking
But that's strictly Bass
On Alex's feelings
About a real imaginary
Yeah
Yeah not the reason why this is so particularly upsetting in this
Case is because
The last week or so we've heard Alex very
Very consistently work himself into a frenzy
Particularly at the end of
The point where he declares it is the globalist
Don't back off
It might be
Me time to start killing people
He's not directly saying that
The time is come here at the beginning
Episode
But if you're a regular listener of Alex's program I think you'd be able to put two and two together
He's established that the global
Don't back down there's going to be just
Certified violin
It's down against
And now here
He's opening his Monday show by explicitly announcing
That there's an imaginary behind the scene
Scenes deal for the globalist
To backup
Off
Which they have broken
And they taunt is over
The proof that his imaginary deal has been broken is just his gut
Feeling
I don't think that Alex's listeners will hear that is called
Time for killing
Just come and then they'll start shooting
Nor do I really
That's how Alex cemento
I just think that because he's so reliable and made up s*** and Reporting things
Based on his feelings
Sometimes he is literally
No idea how the things you think
Play into the larger
Stuff is work
And that is dangerous
Yeah that makes
Yeah no he's not even tying together the fact that if the deal is broken
Which he's already
Right we have to
We have to start killing
And then he's later saying that the deal has been broken he thinks that they start regular
Yeah he
And we're going to move on and go to the next thing he doesn't realize that a week ago is like
And now we burn everybody to the ground he doesn't he doesn't realize the trailer
He's laid like
Picture I don't think it's leading
The worst case scenario
But if it did
Think it's an open-and-shut case
That he is inspiring people towards
Certain
It does feel like he doesn't think reality is cereal
You know what I'm saying like every he thinks every episode is a completely independent thing
Not realizing that it's talking about an ongoing reality I also think it's so indicative of the fact that he doesn't believe anything
He's saying he doesn't think none of it's real time
It's all nonsense neeb stupid
Leave it there
Feel like that is
The case but
How you feel
So Alex is not really talk at all
About the
He doesn't even address
As being public he doesn't care at all
He does
Care though
About
UK
Of course
Do dachshund little bit about that
And he
Wants to leave this in with narratives he has about the United
States 20
16 election
Primarily about how the media was saying that it was likely that Hillary was going to
And apparently Alex believe
That the media was saying that Labour was inevitably going to win
In the UK Alexa
Oh no they were not say
Well that's not what I
This election
All the media trying to deny
We're going to win
Just like they did three years ago for Hillary
Didn't convince people to say all will suddenly the Liberals are ahead I'll vote for them to feel like I'm a winner
The real poll showed
The conservatives 15-20 points ahead
The conservatives won by a whopping
20 + point lead
Meaning they have a
The majority wide in the parliament
I don't know of
Anybody who votes based on who they think is going to win
What Alex is expressing here seems to be a fundamental disconnect from how cumin
Think
It seems like he believes that the media reporting it for example Hillary Clinton was going to win that would drive more people
Go to vote for Hillary who were previously uninsured
Inclined to do so
That's absurd
And I would argue with anything
Media coverage of Hillary being in
Would only serve to Galvanize the opposition to work harder thereby increasing their likelihood of turning out more voters
I don't believe that a person who prefers
Republican policies
Going to hear that
The Democratic candidate is leading in the polls
And it annoys the likely winner
Then they're going to go out and vote for the Democratic cuz they want to feel like they're on the winning
What sense is there to be another winning
Team when that team is opposed to the things you want in society
Yeah that I think
I mean this isn't like
Durant signing with golden state you know it's not like
He gets a ring because he wants a rigged
You know.
Yeah
This is wild
If Alex has any studies decide to backup this trend in voter Behavior I'd be happy to take a look
The but it seems like this is more him talking about his feelings
He desperately wants to be on the winning team in assumes that everyone else would sell out his heart as he has
The trump in order to make that happen
I think this is just about himself
Like people don't operate that way
At least none that I have ever met or no
No there there is
There is something far more Illuminating now that
He's admitted that the show is basic
Really him talking about his
Right
So much of the stuff you can now like
Like really just go in and be like
This is you talking about you
What did you not used to match up with anything I can find
Jeff
Indications that a lot of people are motivated
To vote
Not motivated to vote for a particular but motivated
Because they want to not
Feel the shame of having to lie about Knoxville
Societal
To fit in and be a part of
The response
Stability of voting
B drive people to actually vote
That has nothing to do with two who they go for
I don't
Know what he I can't find
And indications of anything
So when he's
Pitching something
It doesn't seem to be
Supported by any evidence
Damental human psychology
Is this about
You
And I think it is
So you know
Pause daily
Because
Cher
But Alex also lies about
Polls Trump has gained 5 to 10 to 15 points
Real Paul's Trump's 15 20 points ahead
Democrats right now they're in full panic mode
We're trying to get him out of office with this impeachment
But it has spectacularly
Fired on them
According to 538 aggregate of bowls
They have Trump looking at a 43.1 approval rating and a 52-point
5 disapproval or approximately -9
Net approval rating
RealClearPolitics list some of the more recent polls which are mostly
Not good
Quinnipiac has trumpeted -9 net approval USA Today has naked
To Rasmussen is -4
NPR in PBS there pull has them sitting in a -10 Reuters at
-15 and even Fox
News most recent poll conducted
Between December 8th and 11th is at negative
Simply put there are no really
Credible polls
They put Trump anywhere near a neutral approval rating
The polls regarding various
Possible 2020 democratic
Candidates are a little bit less
Consistent
But most of the reputable polling Outlets are generally showing Trump losing
To most of them
If the election were being held today
A lot can happen between now and November and we don't really know who the candidate will be this hard to put too much stake into any of those
Specific polls
But it just isn't anything I can find the reflects the reality that Alex's
Presenting
Alex
Feels like Trump should be winning in the polls and so he says he
He is
You can't find any polls that show the Trump is up 10 or 20 points
But that's because
All you have is access to the cooked fraudulent
Where is Alex has the real
Your numbers which was
Mysteriously are out of step with everyone else
But completely in line with his feelings
So what is this
Is this opinion or reporting
I mean Alex is definitely behaving as if he has proof that there are polls where Trump is beating the Democrats by
20 points whatever that mean
Vague notion of beating the Democrats B
These 548 from 3 to not be based on anything but Elaine's
I don't even know I told you was going to get a little tired already two clips in this is trouble
I don't know why
Cook polls
Wood
Even try why would cook polls be like well Trump is only + 10
Instead of the plus 20 that theoretical reel Pole
What's the point of cooking
If it's still going to look
Because Alex seems to think that like
These statisticians
Are like
You know
Pushing up a
Wrongly pushing back against them
That there will
Cannot manage Trump is up by 10
Cursor keeps writing 7 and then
Yeah basically it's a Herculean effort to make it look like Trump is only up
10 points
Squeezed
I feel like that could exist
So if you ever needed
Just a snapshot
Of why Infowars
Is the stupidest buck
TV show in the world
I think I can provide that for you in a very short
Companies in cos that's great scourges
Break that down at the bottom of the next hour with
Voorhees.
If you listen to Infowars and you take this s*** seriously
You need to wake the fuk up
And that clip is a good
Example of why
Alex is going out a little late
Riff and then he announces that Zach Voorhees is going to
Maybe coming on to talk about it cuz he's done research on the issue
Zach for his only notable in anyway because he was
The Google employee who was the centerpiece of a project Veritas publicity stunt
He gave them a ton of documents that were ultimately meaningless and didn't show what they pretended they did and then after that report came
It was revealed that Zac was an anti-Semitic
Conspiracy theorist
Posted online repeatedly about how the US has a z
Occupied government well I wouldn't call him a rabid anti-semite the web
That term
Zionist occupied government
Azog
Pretty unique
F***** up corners of anti-government
Conspiracy communities
The temp
Towards the
Neo-Nazi
Yazoo dog and like Boogaloo now our
And are you can you mail those back to work has been for a while
That knows nothing about vaccines
Zack has no expertise he worked at Google he has no expertise on the subject
He's just a guy who camping
Much older than 30
Foodworks
Computer scientist at Google for eight years when he went public this year
He's not someone who you'd want to go to
Cooper conversation about Becky
If you were taking the subject seriously
He's someone you talk to about vaccines if you were trying to
Cultivate a new star in the world of right-wing propaganda media
That is I suspect with Alex's doing here
Exactly
Clearly willing to keep coming on his show
You got a little bit of
Juice cuz it is Project Veritas video let's see if we can make
Just already
Because Zach is a snooze
Really dumb
Yes but he's not
Busy dad and that's the most important part of trying to make a new star for Infowars that is true
Zach Voorhees coming on the show today to talk vaccines because he's studied the subject is a perfect example of how little
Alex cares about doing the good job
There was a time when he did least have the decency to have fake doctors on
To talk about anti-vax
But now f*** it let's just get that project Veritas guy who believes there's Azog
I can't even get Mike Adams anymore
They probably could bike might be busy too
Not busy
I had
Where and when
Did he study back
He did was it was it a Google
But at eight years was the only working on the vaccine beat at Google but they have a backup
No
Ironically
When he finally does show up at the end of the episode a bunch of the stuff that he says his
Probably just stuffy red on natural news
Probably just reading Mike Adams articles
That's great we need a Mike Adams surrogate
At 2 anyway
Preferably
Towards
This episode because I have distain for anti-vax stuff which I do
I mean void of that
Really stupid
Like things that are disqualified
Basically anyway
They grow vaccines in
Honey bees hive
Might as well
So Alex says that you know
Impasse
He's avoided being too optimistic
Stick about thing
Listen
I feel like he is not
Easter games in the world
Okay something really revealing
At the end of this
To be too optimistic
And I want to say the president in danger and I wanted to say that we're not completely wanting
Twilight what are you
Because they are really screwed the pooch now
False Flags right now
I would Marley do that myself but if I was there right now
That would be
Opposition
If Alex were the globalists
He'd be doing some false flags and blaming his opposition
I feel like this is a very good example of how twisted Alex's thinking is
And how he forced it onto his audience to accept as fact
When it's just
Is feeling
What strikes me most about this is that we've already heard Alexei repeatedly that the globalist are about to pull false Flags in order to blame the p
Patriots in the surrounding context of
Impeached
You said this as a prediction
Based on his gut
Which is never wrong
He said it was a certainty many times in the past week but now he's presenting this as a if I were there
And that tells me some
Namely
That is
Alex's enemies are in his head
There's no concrete reason
For Alex to predict these globalist going to run false-flag
Everything he calls a false flag
Isn't one
And it's not like he's making
Prediction based on whistleblowers are leaked globulus documents
Discussing false
Like plan
Space solely on his subjective
Perception
When Alex says if I were to go bust
I'd be running false flag
That is a pure distillation
Of his prediction the globalist
Are going to pull false flag
That is what he's really saying when he predicted they're going to do this
It's merely his own projection of his warped and violent mind being put onto his imagined enemies
Alex has created an overpowered but also ultimately
The powerless enemy
To fight in the process is
Convinced a not-insignificant number of people to buy into his Fanta
There are no globalist planning false flag
There's only Alex Jones imagining
But that is what his pretend enemies would do
Because that's what he would do if
Beware them
Then when a tragedy does inevitably happen Alex get
Gets to call it a false flag for no reason in order to fraudulent
Playing the role of a prophet
And then the cycle repeats
More brainforest gets old and Alex tells you that were so close to see
The Anthony's globalist
This time
They've been on the brink of defeat so many times before but never like this
This so close to
And they're definitely going to do some false flag
And when they do is crucial that I see
It'll be on the air so by warbrain force and that's how you can take
Like your ancestors did in the Revolutionary War
Not everyone gets
2B George
The Jordan some people are patriots only inasmuch as they can keep buying my b*******
Got a little worked up it
That is a cycle video
He's doing that's what he's doing.
I always think of that b*******
Like that projection
Because that especially to way too obvious
I'm just like
If I were them I would be false flag
Are we Burton say similar things in
Look up 20 rare for him
Frame it in that
Yeah right away
I think of that in the same way that those like
Alright guys who don't want to go who like
Toca talk just
Right before they get to all the way alright who are like
You know I do
Think when
If all the
Oppress
People's right now get all their power they're going to do all that s*** to us man like nah nah
That's not how it works
That's what you would do in their sin
Make you the f*****-up person
Yeah yeah yeah
Not good
So Alex reports
That this Dyke you know this
Impeachment thing is going forward
Of course it's all bulshit
But there's still reason to be concerned because people are getting
Breton
Got Tricks
Their sleeves
And they are threatening all their menus right now
If you don't do this we're going to release this dirt on you if you don't do that we're going to kill your daughter or your son
Right now the threats are flowing like Niagara Falls
Okay is that news or is that Alex
His feelings
Is it opinion where's Alex actually asserting two people are being blackmailed and
Written that the kids will be killed
If they don't go along with this impeachment
What is what is it
Because if he's reporting
That is fact that's a very serious crime that he's presenting himself as having proof up
Of course you just making this s*** up
But it's presented
News
Started as a fact I don't know I think he might have some screenshots of Larry Nichols email that we're going to get to that
I'm sorry I keep framington things this way but after spending so much
What time with those depositions
Felt like it would be a good idea to take this
As an opportunity to demonstrate these real examples
Where these issues manifest themselves
Outside of oi don't know legally actionable places
What Alex says it's
Sandy Hook was closed at
I'm shooting for insta
Then pretend to stating an opinion that's a matter for the lawyers
Symbicort
But he does the same thing everyday surrounding
All these other issues
He's talking about quote-unquote minion
G b b anybody from government office
Does Clerks 2 Congress be
Being blackmailed
Threatened to railroad track
But I guarantee that he has nothing to baste
Hey babes will be no doubt that if you had to answer why you said this Underoath you would say it was his
It's true
It is opinion
It's my opinion the people are being
Threatened
In order to
Make sure Trump gets out of office
It's my opinion that this is the case it's a vibe
It's the the zeitgeist
Do you feel like that's responsible for you to say that to a bunch of people who rapidly believe in this insane things that you say
H-E-B Mansion the back when the Mueller investigation was ongoing
Larry Nichols literally came on Alex's show and threatened to release damage
Information about Robert Mueller in ever
Remember of Congress if they didn't stop investigating Trump
There is no proof of the conspiracy that Alex is talking about right now
But his show has been host to the exact same behavior
Just directed at the people that Alex wants
Do Target well if I were them that's what I would be doing
So when I'm not them
That is what I will be doing
I'm against Larry Nichols impotently blackmailing people in Congress on Alex
To show in the same way I am against
People being blackmailed hypothetically
2 / Trump
Yeah I am against it because I'm against that action
Yeah
Have you considered that maybe blackmail is a
Great thing so long as it doesn't have
Into you
I am now officially a sovereign citizen
Alex Russo
The worst
Is this is this is so
We're
I guess maybe you could
Possibly get the impression that he didn't like Larry Nichols blackmailing Congress based on the fact that he didn't have them on the show for like
The year
But that's only implied I never heard him denounce that I never pushed back on Larry when
Larry's on
Any Titan back
So you can't it can't have been too big
It's
But I
The fact that there is no
Assistance
Practice of idea of a
Ethics
Through
Ideology is
Right
Is f****** right like Mitch McConnell like we'll never see it as Supreme Court Justice
If if you could you would
Or the day that's just how it was
Because he thinks probably
Bet if I were the other side
I would be doing the exact same thing
Even though that's demonstrable
Yeah it's
Hip Hop
Chrissy is no
Pointed attack
Or whatever accusations
Hold any weight
Not anymore but it's still it's worth pointing these things out particularly when Alex has been party to
Literal blackmail of members of Congress and now he's making up
This
Reportaj about Trump
Biddy the threats are
Flowing like Niagara Falls
If a buck out of here
Do you think he thinks that there is some like
Equivalent Force to Infowars that he just
You know like
Does he think that there is some
Bizzaro Infowars that has
Bizarro Larry Nichols on threatening to Blackmail
Bizarro members of Sphynx that's what MSNBC
I kind of like you just do what a lunatic
So you got that the spirit in them
I figured out about this
Like fighting back
And he
Expresses this
How do you think this is
Damn fake
Osceola spirit
Oh my God
So fake
Alex we're going to have to ask you to take that one again. Just let's start that over
This was a warm-up take I understand.
Yeah
Yellow leather yellow leather
What a dork
Anyway
Alex is thrilled about the UK allow
Primarily because Boris Johnson is a nationalist
Most candidates are we've got
Theoretically
Which is ironic considering he's doing everything possible to turn the
UK into a colony of these
State
Leaving that aside for a moment because we might have
Time for some more
Politic
In the UK just Josh
Inasmuch as
We can a little bit later
I was just thrilled that there's his nationalist getting elected over the world
That is the answer to his globalist prob
Yeah right a global
Well
Turns out
That even though these nationalist candidates are getting elected Place haha
There's still trouble
Everything they're throwing inhumanity journalist and populist are getting elected and of course
Those nationalist movements are infiltrated with global but it doesn't matter at least they're having
They're Patriots
To get elected and then it's only a process of removing
The globalist who are able to get in
Lying to the people
The case of the leader in Brazil and other areas
Patriots
So it's just their minion that we have been discovered and removed
You can see here why Alex's Griff will never naturally reach
It's an
Point on its own
It's entirely up to Alex
The site is wind condition
We can just change those whenever he wants
More importantly I think what you see here is that Alex
Given the authority and ability to do so would be an absolute scourge of a political forum
You'd be the sword
Runs all manner of purity test
Purges in order to make sure the party doesn't have any
Infiltrators at at
It has always worked out well as we can see from Russia's perfect example of solid
Worked out great
Yeah it definitely a natural end result of your worldview being in
Hayirli based on defiance
Only defined by being against something
Once you have
Ostensibly conquered that thing you have to be against something else
Alex
Is defined
As a media entity
Higher personality isn't
Tire reason to
This is based on I'm against the globalist
If he has a situation where like now we have vanquished the global is
He has to create his own enemy he's already
Itau
I would be fun to see if he could hire somebody to photoshop
All of his picture
And how many people would he get rid of it all the sudden
He's just a load in every pic get Zack and fungal
To do that for us
Back to the Future
Everybody's disappearing
So these people they're against the globalist
But what's this A bunch of people that Alex is labeled as auntie globalist
Winning election
Which it signify that you've achieved your goal
Now you can go back
Creating the suit on Utopia
It would have been possible all along heading out for been for those
Meddling globalist
They can't do that
Even interested in that sort of thing
Even if they could
Do the game
Changes
Some of these nationalist groups are infiltrated
So now it's not enough.
Get nationalist into
The office to make sure there aren't any globalist infiltrator
SB root it out at every turn
The thread
Internal and external
You can't trust your own man
Nationalist party
Probably got
Some Global spies in there
Again
This is just based on Alex's
Has no bearing on reality
On the one hand it's a way of escalating paranoia and the deeply on healthy way
But in another it's more likely than not this is just Alex's way of creating an excuse for why
After his pretend 1776 2.0 is happening
None of the things he says are going to happen happen
Because these Nationals to be elected or Secret globalist
Do something
Because Alex gets to set these
These wind conditions in his imaginary infowar
There will never be an achievable when can
You be pretty naive to think that he's not
Keenly aware that he's
Pretty much useless once the globalist
Defeated yeah
Also Alex knows
Nothing
About bolsonaro
Other than he's heard him refer to his Brazil
Trump I would bet
Anything that I own
Fit as Alex was saying that sentence
You didn't even remember
Davis
The awful
The worst
I think he takes that Syfy
Fantasy
That
Neither evil nor good can ever fully defeat
The other
And never-ending struggle and no matter what
If good
Defeat the evil in the seed of its
Destruction is
Inside of it
Evil look
It's just everything is that
Titanic
Eternal battle the
Between good and
So no matter what
There is always going
Be somebody
It just boggles my mind
That nobody
Has ever opened
History book and been like
Well when people start talking like
That means their organization or their group
It's going to cannibalize
Yeah matter what
Yeah it always does
Yeah we're always soon as soon as you're like
Alright
There's enemies Within
You're introducing
Call it out
You're you're introducing at least
The justification
Bad actors will not
In order to create
Those division
End up completely
Destroying whatever you
Every f***
Cooking time
It's it's
It's the US versus them mentality brought into in the house
When
Even outside of the house
Let's say metaphorically
It's not a healthy Outlook
Cruising versus inclusion
Yeah I mean just that the
Praise
Destroyed by infighting should be like on at the
The doorway of everybody's house in there in those
Itsfunneh
Because we actually get a a literal exam
In this next
Split rates because Alex brings in Paul Joseph Watson to talk about the UK election okay
And Alex has some dumb things
That sounds right
You don't brag about it but
Yeah you're in the inner workings of
The brexit party and then W Koeppen
Quarterback for Raj
Behind
Boris Johnson this is really going to scare the globalist
The guy that kept way out in
For so long as now
Power behind the throne with the Nationalist parties
Taking over Europe at every election
How does an amazing time pull awesome
Well exactly
So before I get into this I'd like to make a caveat that I'm not an expert in UK followed
I know what I read on the issue and the sense that I get from that landscape is that Alex
Said isn't saying
The matches up with the analysis
It seems like Nigel farage in the brexit party or effectively completely neutralize now that the election is over in the
The conservative party won
He had tons of chips
In his hand
Prior to the election
Because he was threatening to field candidates and conservative held
Constituency
Which effectively create
Complete split
In the Pro brexit voting block
Garage is only relevant because of that threat
And as soon as he announced
The party would back down he became a non-player
The brexit party has zero seats
In Parliament
So there's no real ability for him to be a part of the coalition government he's only relevant is
In the fact that he's a rabble-rouser and for the sea
City currently holds or the party holds in the EU Parliament
Which will see if they even hold on to
Their end goal is to not
Even have those seats in the EU parlor
It doesn't make any
For those to be any
The bargaining chip
If your entire goal is Right lemonade
It doesn't say
Seem like there's much
Since 2
Garage being the power behind the throne
For Alex to feel that way
Because he's talked to faraj before
Another important
Important point is at the brexit party and you kept are not associate
Nigel farage created the brexit party specifically because he was disgusted with the direction of you kid
And their anti-muslim obsession
He wrote an article in the Daily Telegraph announcing his departure
From the party saying quote
The very idea of Tommy Robinson being at the center of the brexit
The debate is too awful.
And so with a heavy heart and after all of my years of Devotion to the party
I'm leaving you kept
Today
Garages full of s*** about caring about anti-islam sentiment is about to go there
Party that field people like
Count dankula in
Tommy Robbins
Candidate is one that can't be
Successful on the ballot let alone
McGovern
The party he let it become unrecognizable.
And the way it was unrecognizable
Was it the fact that they were taking Alex Jones as guest seriously
Paul is friends with you Kip esoc
I'm pretty sure that he has nothing
Thing to do like
Formerly with the brexit
Party particular
Movie considering that he made of
Big public spectacle of joining
You kept
Along with Tommy Robinson
Thank you Lord
Just a few months before faraj quit
I'm sure the
Paul has some contacts
And they may mean something
They made me not they may not I don't know
I find it very unlikely who's involved
Did anything relevant
Where is Johnson would never be associated with Alex
The Nigel farage probably wouldn't anymore either
The wing of UK politics that Alex has access to
You kept
Might as well be a dead part
Yeah so
They made the classic mistake
Starting to buy their own bowls
Like a good politician
Sargon of akkad in office
All-you-can-eat can control that they're too but once they start Fielding those candidates are like
Yep it's
Yo it's exactly that thing though it's the division
No they the UK and brexit party
Conceivably be
Well they agree on every
Except for the believing this b*******
Using allowing
This
Wing
To have any products
Somebody
To the actual Party Guys
We're willing to accept
Exploit
Anti-islam fervor we don't want to be
Part of it
You are so stupid
Yeah and that for that reason I like I've seen some pictures of like Paul hanging out with some people who were involved
Is it party I'm sure he does know people and it is so so
But any kind of proximity to
Actual s*** yeah
I think they know better because
Paul Ferreira
All of his
Increased popularity over people like
Count dankula
I don't even like him exist and his
Decreased
Toxicity that compared to someone like Tommy Robinson yeah
He's still in that world
Still that
And associating with him
To any
Large
Degree
I think that's
That's why
Garage left the brexit party
Not going to now allow that in
That maybe you would I don't fuc
I mean well
I wouldn't be surprised if some UK people infiltrated the brexit party
I mean a lot of people did
Where they left yet
I mean who
Just the fracturing
Anyway
Paul has some weird political analysis
Episode in the first one that seems to have to do with a Twitter poll
Maybe sure
Yesterday
Tweets from Jeremy corbyn the Labour leader Boris Johnson the conservative leader
On the morning of the election
Pointing out
Corbyn the Labour party tweet
156,000
Beacon 70 pops we got 12500 likes
And that
Message on the street was consumed on explained
Support for labor
Yeah we have a huge Tory majority when it comes to the election
Voice because
You created this massive Echo chamber on Switzer on social media
By Banning people
By forcing self-censorship of alternative opinions
So don't be surprised when reality
Does it reflect your social media
This is great and Alla
Alternate alternate Theory damn
Victorious filled with f****** old people
The end
On the 2019 election
To show the quote for every 10 years older of auteurism
The changes in voting
Conservative
In the UK election increases by nearly 8%
Conservatives got 16% of the 80
18 to 24 volt 18% of the 25:2
229 vote
And 23% of the 32:39
How else did they how did they do with the older the
That's compared to 58% of the 70
B+
And 45% of the six
T9 vote
28 cohorts you're not likely to see shooting office
Comment section to repeat it
This variable alone could help explain the differences
Between tweet
Votes
And then you have to take into account the fact that
Twitter users
Exist who cannot vote
UK I don't understand Dan Howell
Bacon Rita
Three things I would like things
No it's British Twitter
There's a far greater solidarity on the left internationally in space is like Twitter and you can see that in u.s.
Jefferson Express
Support for Corbin in labor
Where is internationally
How many Grassroots folks on the writer necessarily that
Excited about Boris
Just off the top of my head these are
Two possible alternative explanation
The phenomenon Paul is
Describing but his opinion his
Feeling
Is that the differences in tweets
Cuz I ain't no compared to vote is the result of
Conservatives being banned
Twitter and not being able to repeat their support for Boris or something
Yeah how many
Conservatives have been banned for
Twitter 100,000 is that what he's so cute all of them for what it's worth Paul's Twitter is
He's verified news over a million followers
Stuff is all a load of s***
Play Miss that Twitter victim game with your literally living proof that
The Narrative is
I I would I would ask him real quick
Did you retweet the Boris Johnson
He might have might have I
Feel like he might not okay
I'll let you report that is fact
So you know
Something we're talkin about here a little bit he's date
Polling does show that the youth are far more into labor
Far
Higher support of the Tories
Conservatives
In the elderly
Right which is why the old
The same is true
Phenomenology
People in the United
Midstates younger people
Do towards the last
An older people that like we want your door.
Now that is
A true thing
That it's based on Pole
Now
Paul
Wants to explain
This
Talkin about that
Is
Game
As
The great replacement
Conspiracy theories
This is a swing
I think Paul is way out of line connect
Snow people on the last descent
Oh just be patient will win it with the demographics will win it with the mass immigration
Is a white supremacist
But if you talk about it in a positive way and you're on the left
Then it's perfectly acceptable
What does a sea of red
The 18 to 24 year olds in this is the problem
Because Tony Black
Basically sent into policy
This goal of having 50% of
The people
Go to university
Now
He's doing that because universities even more so in the UK than the US in many places
So first of all what a shock Paul feels like colleges are marks
Is brainwashing
I should tell you that in his deposition Paul did testify that
He didn't go to college so I guess he's not speaking from any personal
You're so weird these people who run misinformation Griffith
Really want people to shutter at the thought of people getting higher education
Almost as if their business model depends on the population devoid of critical
Either that
Write Tony Blair the noted mark
This could be just wanted kids to go to college so we can bring
Absolutely I think that makes perfect
The larger problem with that clip is hippolyta
Disgusting Democrat
What are you doing is advanced
An argument that is very dumb on its face
What the function of its
To be in some ways meant to legitimize
Is this great replacement theory that no matter how snarkily
He says it
He's Advanced by explicit white supremacist
What national
His argument fails for a number of reasons that aren't even worth breaking down but I think there's an important
Distinction between the way Heat
Discusses demographics
And how someone noting that the youth support left
Candidates much
More
And it's about the next
Stout
For someone who sees that the younger age cohorts are more liberal
Tell Kelsey that
Maybe they'll hope that they retain.
These political ideas as
They get older
That's it
For someone like Paul or been either
Associates with
Daisies
Statistics that immigrants have a higher likelihood of voting democratic
And that's not it
They haven't Next Step
And that's advocating
Positions like closing the borders
Mass deportation
Building a wall
Oh I don't see no I assume that what they wanted to do was
Create policies that were more inclusive and get those voters onto their side
That would be an interesting
Possible way to go but it's not how they
The next step in the logic is really the problem
Because it's never analysis
Like you're pointing out there's never a moment of reflection
Good where you think okay please population segment over
Particular
Is there possible policy reasons
Their response is a
Pure need jerk react
Betsy's a population
Votes in a way that they don't like
No responses to try and remove or limit that population from the country
Equivalent for this in the age example would be a
People in the life
For holding rallies were they
Change to the battle Logan
Run style euthanasia program to remove the elderly from the boat in blocks
Someplace kyuzo fart
The bright
Or maybe that's too extreme to let the magic they're just saying that no one over 49 can
Convoke
You spoke
Do note that the younger people skewed left aren't
Advancing position
Specifically designed to marginalize
Pause the old
People like Paul
They note that immigrants cute
To the left go to pattern
And then advance
Physicians designed to marginalize
This is the primary difference
And why his analogy make
Makes no sense
Yeah the rest of the stuff he's talking about I'm not even going to dignify with her
All he's doing is trying to create a what about type argument in order to justify
Is demographic justify
Vacations for white Nash
Because I don't
Here
People on the left saying
All these immigrants coming in to vote for the left so hooray
I've not heard anybody
Use that as a Justice
Application for
Increased immigration
Or maintain
In current levels
Nope
Only heard that is a conspiracy theory by people advancing the great replacement
From the right they go
Cuz it's it's
I know you are but what am I you're doing it so I have to do it in order to stop
Of course we're trying to limit the Democratic voting population
Because that's what you guys would do if you could
It's so f***** up that these people think they're doing good
But they're playing the game the right way
It's it's
Brutal
The political party
Similar to that
So College
Is Marxist brainwashing
We know that
Girls last
Sklepy up bands are you speaks a little bit more about
Some people would say
Those 18-24 year-olds
Begging to become Property Owners they going to have more wealth another than actually going to become more conservative
That's not the case
We don't have problem in the boxes brainwashing
Because that social engineering last forever
I would f****** love for Paul to even pretend he's not just making s*** up out of thin air here
Colleges are boxes brainwashing km to the powers-that-be want more people to go to college so they will be brainwashed in order to make it
So they don't naturally get more conservative as they grow older
What a f******
Idiot
Saying you know how many assholes I went to college with who study business
Graduated in their old
Conservatives now
Get the f*** out of here the week
No
Actual data doesn't backup anything
Isaiah
It's all just Paul's feelings the college is liberal indoctrination
Well when I talk to somebody with
The college degree they
Say I'm wrong damn
The conversation publishes study called ideal
Back in February 28th
The conclusion of a years-long
Surveys
Given to a representative sample of over 7,000 students
More than
20 colleges starting
They were particularly interested in seeing how these students changed if at all and their perception of varying political
They surveyed them when they were just entering college and then again during their sophomore year and the results are pretty interesting
48% of respondents quote viewed liberals more favorably in their second year of college
They arrived
The poem must be right
Almost half of these students got sway by Marxist brainwashed
Problem is they also found that 50% of respondents also viewed conservatives more
Early after going
The college
The proportion of those who view whose views worsened
We're almost also identical with 30% towards liberals and 31 Floyds
3 towards
Conservatives their views of them
I found this paragraph particularly in Port
Quote the data show us
That's the most growth and appreciation
Can happen among people who were initially least
If I'm either liberals or conservatives
In simple terms
First-year college students who began College
Really
Disliking liberals or conservatives
Have their attitudes
Softer
In college
Exposure to people with different beliefs
The news
In an integrating environment that helps people understand each other
It seems that the effect of making radicalization
It's not good
For people whose business model is radicalization
People like Alex don't want you to humanize people you disagree with he wants you to think that their demons who can literally only be defeated
By his yelling
Would you make possible by buying is dumb
Pills
According to the Pew Research Center something bad
What is happening with the people who are on the right
Right now
In terms of higher education
If you look at the proportion of people on the left
To believe colleges
The positive for the country
That number is been in the range of 67% to 72% from 2012 to the present
Fluctuates a little bit but it's pretty much
Barely
Conversely on the right there is a distinct
James
It is very
In 2012 53% of Republican
Can psychologists positive
And 54%
In 2015
In 2017 that number dropped
And now in 2019
It's 33
If you look at the graph the approval and disapproval
For college
Collect
There's something happening
And it happened in 2016 that is leading to a noticeable shift
And right-wing opinion store Tire in
Ooida
You know it's anyone's guess why that's happening
But I would imagine that the GOP becoming a party
Completely infiltrated by scam artists
Probably isn't
Games
Let me be clear
I would welcome Paul to show me some evidence of going to college
Resist
Greater conservatism
You're getting older
But I suspect that's not coming anytime
It's so obvious
It just for my experience
Just would like personal
Experience on this regard is
I grew up in a small town
Isolated
Everybody's the same everybody believes the same bulshit
You get
What would you call it I don't know brainwashed
Because it's such a small
Closed off Community it's not even brainwashed
Culture
And then you go to college or a city and you're exposed
To so many different things and you realize holyshit
I've been told that this was scary for forever
Now I'm doing it
And it is not just
Not scary it
Great
A f****** great
Yeah that's
That's the way you explained
All of this like why are City so blue and
Rural areas so red
Why is it that so many colleges especially on the right
Are trying to create their own
Isolated Edge
Educational Systems
Where they have complete control over what even can be said
You know you look at that grass
The
Like the inverse
From 2015 to 2017
Yeah and if that should be
Cause for
Alarm
Among the people on the right one of them
But know what are your things of of like
Something that you've said repeatedly
How do we stop this
Horrible right-wing propaganda
Our only hope is
And you're like well now that the people we need to educate the most
Actively
They hating education
That makes that really really difficult
Yeah I bet it's not impossible
Yeah but I think that's probably
It sound for that it's what they think we would do if given the opportunity
Sure
Sao Paulo
Got some dumb things
Andy wants to complain a little bit about you
YouTube
Then let's get into poodiepie that's pretty big nose
Is it
Well it's the Great Awakening the residents the great backlash with PewDiePie and social media censorship
Widely
YouTube Institute of this new policy
About insulting people based on all these different vague new categories but the thing about it was they
Retroactive
So it's like
Cuz I passed a new federal law
Making marijuana completely illegal across the entire country
I could then retroactively do you smoke
2 years ago Wagon Wheel arrest you for it that's how dumb YouTube new policies
The analogy Paul is trying to draw here is absolutely flawed and it doesn't work
At all that's how dumb polish
Recently YouTube roll.san new changes about moderation
Content that is deemed to be
Maliciously insulting people based on things that are
Considered protect
The classes
Like race gender etcetera
But that's what he said these vague
Sing them I'm proactive
Consulting
Cool
It's all part of YouTube's March towards pretending they're TV
Network in anyone who's surprised by these or two moves
Either a fool or somebody probably makes money by maliciously and smoke
PewDiePie has far more to worry about regarding these new rule
Set to kick in at the beginning
Regarding health
Lake Brantley YouTube is violated the children's online privacy protection
Mostly because he has a gigantic audience of people under 30
And their rule
Regarding advertising to children that have been ignored by
YouTube up till now
And if they're enforced very likely cut into his bottom line.
Mysterious
That has nothing to do with RuPaul's complaining
Yeah yeah
Is a big deal
Concern for something like PewDiePie
PewDiePie's
Long-standing
Agreement with Camel cigarettes really
Isn't going to help her out of trouble
So the reason Paul's argument doesn't make sense
Cuz that one YouTube deciding what content is or is not okay is not a law
And therefore there aren't ex post facto rules
Regarding of moderation
But more importantly
Content The Toasted online
Constantly new where is if you smoke weed a year ago that's one disc
That makes no sense to take Act
Turn against a person for 12
You actually made prior to allow changing
Because that action has no effect on the change you're hoping
To make through the law
The same is not true videos that are maliciously harassed
If you made a video a year ago the effective harm the rules are seat
Minimize is present
Each new view of that video
You could maybe make the argument that YouTube shouldn't harshly punish people for things that were okay before but are now again
Proposed angles completely absurd
But the other problem is that these aren't new Paula
They're just saying they're going to expand on already
Existing rules
And suggesting that maybe they should
Actually info
Yes.fit already
Expendable
Yeah it's it's
It's hosted
Every
Every click
Is a new
Running over and over and over again
It's not it's not like I yeah
That's that's stupid very soon
If Mister Rogers had a YouTube channel and he was sounding the alarm on this rule changing
And not doing with this super flimsy weed legality analogy
I might take it a little more seriously because obviously he's not going to
Be affected by that rule
As it is Paul
But you know damn well that a policy change word maliciously insulting
People based on protected attribute that effectively Works Direct
Play against his business model
Kind of sounds like a bully trying to fight anti-bullying Rules by crying free speech
If you don't Halo
And more than anything
Like
It feel like
Paul talking about his feelings
Face mask
Good as a political tool
I really think that Paul should
I should be best
I really think you should strive to be best
Also something we don't talk about much because you don't talk about Paul
Much breathing is important
I need to point this out
Paul cannot form sensible analogies work
Comparison
He thinks YouTube content rules of the same as arresting someone for something that was previously legal
Which is when there's a bunch
Two reasons why that doesn't make
Events with discussing voting pattern
Songs based on ages
The same as the great reply
He thinks like Twitter likes and retweets should match up with voting
Results
He's not very smart
Is what I'm getting at
He delivers this s*** with a smug present
Knowing what he's talking about but it's all ultimately meaning
It's just a dumb guy saying dumb things that feel good to his audience because they give the veneer
Of intellect to their bigoted
You really could have used with some mark
Marxist brainwash
Little Community marks is brainwashing you know he doesn't need to go to a full four-year marks
Brainwashed
I didn't want to descend to that level Estee sound elitist
I mean any basic
Philosophy class would teach you why these analogies that he's drawing
Legitimately make no sense
It's not like I graduated I dropped
I'm still not a displacement Theory
So PewDiePie
Right
He's
The biggest thing in the world
According to Alex chair
Annie's YouTube rules
Going to screw them over
PewDiePie
According to Alex
To make his own you
Anybody could launch an alternative
McDonald's
He's like a hundred billion views on YouTube
You talk about just
Old anybody 225 knows who he is
And the guys really funny
Is he bigger than all of the other media combined
We need we need him to join with us
Join with Sauron
Why do you always present yourself as the bad guy
Secret protagonist
Lord of the Rings oh my God
PewDiePie was on our side that would solve all of my attention problems
What's be the one trying to destroy nuclear weapons probably
I think
So it is next clip Alex says something that I
Really think
Kind of undermines his reason
People are going to reject
The NWO whether we're their opposing it or not
And that's what she's so insane about
Crazy left
And the globalist in their Baubles and their big Tower of Babel
Master plan
So according to him
Everyone just going to reject the New World Order because
Why do you need to exist
What is the point of his show if he's not doing anything that's not just going to happen naturally
Somebody needs to point out that Kevin Nash is just too tall
Sure that's why he's here
Well I mean
If this show is just Alex talking about his feelings and it's clearly not
Going to bleed to the political goal that he's seeking
Nope probably
Get some therapy into cool
He could do that
Make way less money selling to you have to pay for therapy
Where is people pay you
For free lies
True
So Paul is Anisa
Stupid s***
He's done
And now Alex has Owen
Schroeder
Okay and man
If Paul is dumb
Owen Shroyer
Iraq
Let's find out the clock back out if you remember
In 2016 obviously most the audience will remember the Carl the cuck AIDS Skrillex video
Bat video in 2016 created a new genre of content
Or people not go out and confront Trump protesters
Posing how they don't know what they're talkin about exposing how they're falling for false narrative
Exposing how they're all parrots clearly being
Train
In practice
Aziz AstroTurf protest that goes viral
Now Alex we've seen in a very short time span
It in the in the Cyclone of time here as it gets tighter
Now we already have after what I did Monday
Dozens of videos
A politician being confronted
This is some of the most
Flagrantly self-congratulatory s*** I've ever seen I feel like I just heard him come a little bit
He's jerking himself off
So hard dick
Unreal is getting up here on the bike and
Pretending that he pioneered a new genre of entertainment when he yelled at some truck protesters
And that was his publicity stunt at the impeachment hearing he's done it again
Eroica
We transformed
Iron Man
Media landscape
Single-handedly Howard Stern
Truly the most Innovative entertainer of our time
Delete James in the game and elevating the art of yelling
Based publicity
I would like a Pulitzer thank you very much anybody anybody out here publishers
On the one hand this is sad
But on the other hand it's
Like I said he hosted the Sunday show this week
And he started the show by reading basically the same
About how we invented a new form of entertainment
What are yelled at some Trump protesters and now after yelling at Congress
Another new genre is emerge
Leaving aside how Owen was definitely not the first person to record themselves arguing with protesters
And how everybody
Preferred the guy who threw a shoe at George Bush
I'd like to remind him of something
You may recall that video of Owen made the rounds in 27
We're young girl calls him a f****** idiot
And give them the finger
9:30 is the new genres
Actor Owen
Start interview with her saying quote
How are you young man
It was real fun to see this
Great kid out there
But what you might forget is that Owen
We got on air on Infowars and try to play the victim insisting that he'd open the conversation saying ma'am or not
Man which makes no sense given that he literally says how are you young man
Young amam
Insisted that the media was lying about him and trying to malign him he said ma'am
Leroy sane
Manager
Fair
You might also forget that he started reading Bible verses on air that he took Comfort Inn in his dark time
Which interesting Lee is my favorite genre of entertainment
Self-serving victimhood wallowing with a
Televangelism spin
Yeesh
Next to Alex reading Bible reading Bible verses
Because a young girl that called him a f****** idiot and everyone loved it
God just go to Marxist brainwashing School
This dude is the worst
But he also is
So not interest
Is just a desperate attempt to belittle Alex but he just doesn't have the
The chops
Like Alex Daniela but I recreated investigative journalism by breaking into Bohemian Grove and it's clearly bulshit
But you kind of wonder if Alex actually believes what he's saying
With all and you know it doesn't believe
Something the Intrigue out of it
Could who cried believe that they created
It's so flimsy it's not even in
Yeah that's that's been
That is bananas
You can create a new genre of clip-on Tik-Tok
But you cannot do that
On YouTube
This whole thing with Owen is
Largely just about how alike we getting
Attention
You know it's there talkin about creating these new genres
As a way of being like we
Really are like we get so many views on others
That means we're good
If they talk about another part of this
President Trump tweeted out our great reporter will Johnson
Out there at the cap
He's got a mic
Flag for his other words as we encourage him to use
And so they repeat those videos you noticed they don't retreat the Infowars videos unless they don't have the Infowars Mike
We've done that so it makes it easier
Alex is talking about here is how one of his employees will Johnson
Send a host of Firepower
Which may not exist
Anymore I'm not
Play sure he was interviewed by
CBS News back on December 10th masquerading as
Normal everyday Trump
Supporter hanging out at the rally in Hershey Pennsylvania
Will was not identified as a person who works in the median or is an employee of Infowars but just
I'm a guy who believed that if Trump is removed there will be a second Civil War
If someone who works on are like The Young Turks
Was interviewed at a Bernie event Alex would never stop talking about media manipulation
Pictures of plants you just they were there pushing a narrative Delta evoke lovers himself
Just being shrewd smartest f*** out here buddy
Not think about Larry Nichols blackmailing Congress
On air
Brian
Define if we do it obviously it's sloppy as hell for CBS tonight vet this interview and presented how they
They did
And it's profoundly unethical for will Johnson
Do not identify him
So his interview could be taken and it's
Contacts
As it stands his behavior about to misrepresenting
Himself by omission
In order to
To inject Infowars talking
Listen to another network discovery
Which normal journalist
Would not
Do
But this is the thing
Alex and everyone at Infowars knows full well by this point that taken in their property
Contact they will always be ignored laughed at or yelled at
That's why Alex tell people to misrepresent themselves when they're out doing interviews by using a dawn Infowars bikes
Pretending you don't work at Infowars
Because he knows that no one presenting themselves as an Infowars employee will ever be taken seriously by normal people
They'll never be able to conduct an interview because everyone knows their brand
Is s***
Alex is keenly aware of this
But seem to think there's a there's
Virtue
In baking
Into all of his Fieldpiece
Which is a really bad sign
If you're a reporter in the field and you misrepresent who you work for because you know that your interview subject would respond
Differently to you if they knew who you work for
Anything that take
Play some that interview esteem
It's taking place under false pretense
And that's fine without
He can't do anything else
Even jayleno man-on-the-street interviews the guy was like I'm from
Jay Leno
Like they know that if you're on Jay Leno as a man on the
The street interview
You're going to look like an idiot
That's just how he even then they're like yeah sure okay
You guys are what everybody
Yeah
So when Owen went to disrupt
The
Impeachment hearing
He got arrested
Jack Nichols
What happened
But
Complain
About people who interrupts
The Kavanaugh hearing
And how they didn't get
Didn't make it arrested
We'll talk about it yeah the only shorter Twitter
Valiant was women
Yeah and
Well I don't necessarily want to get into some of the logistics of the legal battle that I made
Encroaching on right now but you know
I was arrested I was sent to jail
They weren't
Why am I such a criminal you know I was perfectly Cooperative I didn't even try to
Point good point then firstthingsfirst good to see the
The crushing bias
Conservatives on Twitter somehow hasn't affected Owens f******
Shroyer still having a
Account which is verified by the way retweet Boris
Election
If you do literally any research at all you'll find out
A lot of people were arrest
Surfer protest
Kavanaugh hearing
Emma Goldberg wrote about her experience getting rest
Disrupting the hearing it up
USA Today
On September 4th 2018 as reported by Politico that the police announced they had arrested approximately two dozen
Protesters
And ultimately that number would reach 70 arrest
That day among them Linda sarsour and actress Piper Perabo
Or you can find articles in the washer
The post about protest against the confirmation process leading to 128 arrest
The Capitol building
On September
Oh and then there's an article you can easily find in the guardian
About how on October 4th over three hundred protesters engaged in a sit-in to oppose the impending
Vote
For confirmation
We're all rest
I just don't get it beat no muslim leaders are out here condemning these radical Islamic attacks
None of them whole lot of people were arrested in cavanal related protein
Including p
People mostly women
Who disrupted
The hearing so that raises the question
Why are Alex and Owen just sitting here lying and saying
These people
Arrested
You like
That's exactly right
It feels like these women weren't arrested
Alex
His opinion is that that didn't
Happened because it's
Fit with his worldview
So it's
Fact that these women had no consequences for what they did
Where's his Noble UPS
Son Owen
So unfairly treated
For being paid
This is legitimately how the sausage is made
Lion
Jane Fonda's out here getting arrested
What are we what are you talkin about nobody
F*** you
Troyer engaging in Civil Disobedience
Requires a certain amount of
Acceptance of risk
If you're going to disrupt it
Congressional hearing you need to prepare yourself that you might get arrest
That's just the possible cost of engaging
In the contact you feel is morally necessary
If you believe that
You'll accept
The punishment
Carry on the fight
If you're doing it for a publicity stunt you'll probably do it Owen and Alex are doing here
You pretend it's an outrage you got arrested
You lie that no one else gets arrested for this
You'll try to get as much at
Can for yourself out of it
As opposed to keeping the attention
Squarely on the matter they are civil disobedience
It was supposed to highlight
For instance
Like
You don't remember that Piper Perabo was arrested
In the Kavanaugh hearing about herself
Linda sarsour
He doesn't even remember that she got arrested
He doesn't remember because
They were rarely on the protest
Being self-aggrandizing bullsh
Put simply Alex and Owen or children
Who create completely fictional reality
Which they presented factual
Because the lies better conform to their feelings
Then reality.
Yeah yep if I if my reality is this
I feel good
If it's not I feel bad
So just because reality is different
That doesn't mean
Get in the way of me
Feeling good
Feels good feels good
I would rather feel good than bad
Yeah
So this entire Owen interview seems to be mostly an excuse to end up playing a video of a guy yelling at Joe Biden about his son
Actions in Ukraine
Chat about how Trump is innocent
Danielle's infowars.com
Owen and Alex revelant
Celebratory laughs
This is a big victory in a total
Slam dunk
They seem to be acting like this is completely organic and natural like people out there just out of their own accord or showing up and yelling
Looking forward to politicians
Does Infowars
Is so successful
So real
But unfortunate
I listen to Alex's
MSI recall how on September 29th 2019
Alex Donaire made a big deal out of telling his listeners to go to Democratic candidate events
And do exactly this
You talked about how in the past with the Bill Clinton is a rapist contest
He paid out hundreds of thousands of dollars to people that got on the news plugging Infowars
He couldn't afford to do that now but the implication was still there that he would reward people who got him the Optics he wanted
A very least you have to expect
You get to be a guest on
Show if you did what I was wanted I mean he's had that thirty-year-old guy who sued his parents
Stickman house on more than once
This under
Liza
Another Super unethical thing that Alex does
As it relates
Presenting the truth
He interferes with the stories he's
Pretending to report
You cannot possibly report on a story like
Guy yells Infowars at Joe Biden
When you mix
Listen to told your viewers to go yell Infowars it
People like Joe Biden
Unless you make clear that this person is doing the yelling
They were directly
He told to do this by your show
Alex's actions at the root of this story
I'm presenting it as a Grassroots citizen
Infowars
Completely just
Ingenuous
This person yelling at Joe is taint
Because Alex has made it super clear many times
The past that getting infowars.com in the
The plug is part of
The condition of
As it was the case
Case of the Bill Clinton
It's part of the in forwards unit
All of his listeners know
Is you're going to do something
Like this Alex will promote it if you promote him
It's a reciprocal thing
And not acknowledging that is unethical
On Alex's Park
Can you imagine
If
Presenter at
Cnngo
Just started going
Yes or next week we'd really like to cover a war so if somebody could start a war for us that way we will have
Have the coverage that we want we've already got
Groundwork laid
It doesn't matter who starts the war
That example might be too extreme. Same behavior
I would ask you to tell him that down and stayed a little bit
I recognize that it's dumb of me to expect good work
Please dude
Things like
Employees misrepresenting
And themselves and failing to acknowledge how they are the cause of the stories they're reporting
These are fundamental
No organization that's willing to engage in those two
Kinds of basic malpractice
Can be trusted
With anything they
You like these are bedrock
You should have to go to journalism
Washing School
It could help
Man that's that's 101
Marxist journalism Breakwater
Yeah I saw a few things like CNN's should have done more wedding and I
I got that but
No
Self-respecting journalist would not
I would not be like hey I work for the guard
Yeah and then we can
Can still do the inter
Yeah that's it it's insane to me that he just lied to them and people
It made me uncomfortable
When we learned that add-on Salazar one of Alex's producers
Who's following us on Twitter because I was worried about the effect
That our existence could have on the product
We recovery
And we're not journalist
We play currently dismissive of it
Because it works better boy
So Alex
Gets into this is just sort of shity setup
Nguyen give their systems are challenged that's why they drain the pool
It always has
A bunch of fancy high-tech systems and
Communist China that is going to work here
Communist China is on the verge of collapse
This is not
Going to go well if good men and women stand up and say no
Operation yellow
Beat this is so explicit
Like your ancestors did in the Revolutionary War you stand up
Also by the way 12 Days of Christmas sale currently
All right.
Second day of Christmas my true love gave to me
LOL give you the burpees
Whichever one is cocaine
So interesting Lee I mean we have a lot of conversation on this episode mostly because of Owen Shroyer being on
One of these stunts
That they've been doing
Lately
And his next clip Alex makes it clear that they've paid off
Sort of
We probably had
6 mods
That is not
Translate into any extra sales and imports for.com
Watch they listen okay
Interesting products
But literally do all of this
What's the most important part less than a bulldozer running over the
The Treads the wheels the engine
The scoop on the front it's all very important but the fuel
Is Paramount
Allegory
So
Alex is traffic
Tripling now is so much smaller than it would have been in the past
Like when we were going over the boss
Embalming. Is traffic
The doubling
Multiplying by 10 million
In this case
It's probably just some people who are like a owen Shroyer interrupted the
F****** dude is up to we went from 25,000 hits
Something like that maybe not that small but something like that
It's not
That
It's not Millions
Not good
It's not
People who are interested in what he's doing
Now it's like
You can't translate that
Any
Money now
Really encourage
That's actually very in Korean
Don't ever make just as much then
Sense for him to lie
Like put a bolo
Yeah let me this is a this tells me
At least on some level that
The thing
That Alex
Can work
Which is getting
More people to watch
You know through publicity stunts doing all these are two things
It doesn't work
Translate into
Thereby into his business
And again
That's only taking his word for it
Rhinos with real
Based on what he saying
It feels it feels like there
Probably aren't a lot of options
For what what he can do
Right the ship
But we'll see
His entire career attention
Equals money
And now no matter how much attention
The money stays this
Daddy just doesn't understand the map
No that just means that I need more attend
That's not how it works
No attention no longer equals money
So
Speaking of attention
Alex says
Zacks The Whistleblower on
And
Jose
Did this clip is a really good
Assertive boil down
Why this dude is
Realtor
Google what's a blower
Tell me about the
So dumb
Google whistleblower Zach Voorhees is on to talk about vax
Seen research he's done now you're telling me about nautical and Breitbart
Every piece of that sentence is stupid
Yeah I could
Anyway you here
Talk about an article on Breitbart you read and I didn't let's hear some brilliant analysis about somebody else
This
Is
One of the more convoluted
That I've ever seen somebody walk
Okay alright
So it starts
Voting
Issues
Right
It Ben gets into abortion
Okay and then it comes back to voting issues
Alright
Are David Bowie and Jennifer Connelly going to show up because this is a labyrinth I had to take a walk around
Around the apartment
Oh
Alright alright I'll do my best
Someone's
Really dumb and then you keep listening your like I overestimated
So you're the first
And now there's a lawsuit that says Hey look
Detroit you're using dead people to vote
And their responses
Not that no we're not they're saying no
Racist video
That's happening it's a direct attack on people of color
It's like
Come on why is
Accusing them of
Floating dead people to vote
A direct attack on
People of color I don't get it
So when I'm done look into it so what I saved that Zack is really
Not that smart
I'm
Mostly talking about his inability to properly assess information and express it
Because the level at which he's seen
To be able to do that is startling
Because he's an adult
Although it does kind of go a long way toward explaining why he thought those documents again project Veritas mention
Yeah
You still don't understand
The suit that he's talking about him.
Detroit has nothing to do with any proof of
Someone ever voting in a dead person
Name
It has to do with there being a lot of dead people
Still on the voter roll
It's less a problem of any kind of actual voter fraud and mourn issue of Shawty record
This is true and probably
Every city
In the country
These databases are really hard to maintain
And if the political Capital that Alex and Zach want to expend on this
Is solely
Yo and initiative in order to make sure dead people aren't on voter rolls
Then by all means they should make that their primary issue
Yeah I know that anyone's going to ever contest
Yeah except for people who don't want to put the money into that because they
Just don't want it
Alex him probably wouldn't want that anyway cuz that's funny compliment bureaucracy anyway
But usually issue
That's not
Their issue
The actual real-world concern is if they're poorly updated votary
Which in no way proves the people are voting and dead p
People's names
In order to remedy this
These people like Alex
Zach they don't advocate for more resources being directed to the Departments to maintain the
He's rolls
Instead they want voter ID laws
To be enacted
Which is solving the wrong problem
Consistently Studies have shown that measures like voter ID laws disproportionately affect voters and predominantly non-white District
The one that's
The sort of solution you have to wake
Sweetly unrelated problem
It makes sense
Be less interested in the real problem in mortgage than
Justifying your
Actual go
Voter disenfranchised
I think you might have
Just answered.
Tax question
She didn't understand that it didn't make sense to him now
Now I assume after you explaining it using reality Adonis will change his mind
The probably not but honestly I don't really know if it is actual confusion
False confusion for performance
Zach I don't know
Yeah he really could just be
Incapable of comprehending
That's one and that's borne out by the
Because he gets onto another story
I said it pivots to abortion
Check wasn't sure why
It seemed out-of-left-field
Also there's an interesting story
Botanica thumb
My friends are gone
We discovered
Stats
If
Children California
Don't have to be issued a death certificate
There is truth this is true
So I don't believe for a second that the small-government anti Barack
Chrissy world of Infowars is really concerned with a
A f****** government requiring more paperwork
It's pretty hard to imagine that they're taking issue with some abortions not requiring death certificates cuz they're super into death certificate
And the requirement
Purple
In reality I believe that this is just an attempt
To frame the opposite side of a
Conservative an issue
The Republicans currently trying to pass a bunch of bills that would make accessing
Did Healthcare board Borden
C'Mon people particularly there's one in pants
Sylvania that's
Disgust right now
Many people interpret this just being purely based on trying to create subtle punished
Meant for things like
Like a portion
The bill in Pennsylvania would require burial or cremation for all fetal remains and would require death certificates in all cases
Even including miscarriage
These sorts of measures don't do anything
They don't provide better Healthcare
They don't serve anyone's
But they do create expenses for people
Seeking reproductive Health Care
And make things
Like an abortion way more costly
Because if you don't do the things that you're required to do based on this bill
You could be hit up with a fine up to like $300
It does feel like
So many of these people are
Are like
Well
All of our ideas are unpopular
Stupid
How about instead we punish the poor into the behavior that we want them
Yeah how about we how about we financially destroy people who are
Accident way we don't want
These sorts of measures really only exists upon
So the best way to frame the discussion is
Not talk about those bills like
It's to say hey did you know that some places don't require death certificate
Pittsburgh Orscheln's and then feign outrage about it
These dudes don't give a f*** about deaths
Certificate is looking for whatever Trojan Horse they can use to attack
Right or at least
That's how people generally use the sort of rhetoric
I should have known better
Executive theory about this that without stupid
I've ever heard
And of course he does
Certain aborted children
California
Don't have to beat you to death
If it gets
And
Their yes true this is true
And there is Dysteria why would they do that is it because they are registering to vote as
As Democrats 18 years later
Wow
God is the Lord God
That is the game right there
Oli
Pretty.
Holy s*** that I think that all of the dead people who were on the voter rolls don't have death certificates for them
What is going
Does he think every aborted fetuses as a name
This is
That's the dumbest thing I've ever heard it's staggeringly
Shredabull
Expressively
It really is because that makes
No sense
If you if you are capable of putting yourself into anybody else's brain
That
That thought would never accursed
Here's why they're not issuing deaths
So in 20 years they'll be able to fake votes
Right that makes
Perfect sense
Start doing that are they only starting to program now you get to a certain level where you just like
I can't believe Alexander in the interview after that ridiculous Theory
That's a new one he doesn't push back on it either
No no no not at all
Of course that makes sense
II
But that means there has to be like a really cool
Placated log of Xander with staggered
Dates when people would be available to the infrastructure on that plan cost more than the
The death certificate plan
I just don't know I just want to hear stuff like that I'm like
I can't imagine listening to this showing
These things not being like Jake
Kantik red flag
Organic wake up calls you hear Alex not treat someone like that as if they are dangerous
Totally insane
I don't know I know how you can just think I do yeah Alex's got a good head on his shoulders
Ethics
He thinks this guy's worth talking to
I don't think
Fit physical violence is the answer but my
My first like if I was going to go through the steps of how I would deal with this if he said this to me in person just
Adebayor
He says that and I'm going to start laughing like a lunatic
And then he's going to stare at me weirdly Because he believes it's true right recognize he believes
Strip
And then I'm going to go no
And my first instinct will be like the only way to solve this problem is with the flat
But then I'll just walk
Is it what do you say
I know there's nothing
To say if you know what the problem is too he was a software engineer or software person at
A Google for 8 years
Kind of got to assume he went to Marxist brainwashing
So like I don't even know what sort of marks
I don't know what kind of educational going to help this one
Teach yourself to
Dakota lot of people teaching
That's that's
This guy is
That stagger
Staggering
So he thinks that the others he's real problem
With voting
Andy
He owes me an interesting
Example of voting done right
We should look to Iraq to really a hot event
Down cold
Your finger you dip it ink after you've
And then
You can only you know put your finger and pink one
Does your finger
Y'know notoriously
Not full of
Voting
Problems Iraq
Yeah
I didn't think you could top it definitely thought you would have to do some work to Top-Up maybe they're both
Voting in 18 years under aborted
We should follow Iraq's example and you can only dip your finger in ink once
Is a boy
I mean this guy is like
A pinata that's
Just never a a little bit here in there
Another thought
Hear about
I don't about voting scared Oregon
You don't have to come in to do you can
Send an email
Father's going to come in
Absentee voting in and of itself is
Proof of intention to commit voter fraud
According
Into this guy
Who believes
Who's that aborted
Fetuses are voting
Betta rack system
Zach in 2 seconds this is how long it took me to think of this so you think voters you think military people
And US citizens overseas should not be allowed to vote okay well then we're done
Goodbye
What about people who are like
Should be able to
Okay only only able-bodied people we should also Institute a poll tax
Text and I boy however many other ways to be racist
What about people just have schedules
Such that they
Take the time to go to vote with a w
Well the offer that option to people
There are ways
Twitter
Super controllable
This is
I don't even know I remember respond
This is so poorly thought-through
No this is
This
Vaccine waiting for Zach to be like a lot of people
The left want to make voting day an official holiday and I think we should Institute a 23 and a half hour work day
A on their mandatory to make sure that everybody votes on time
Yeah it's approved you wanted we get a lunch break
Also all crime is legal for 24 hours why not
Look dude
This dude is
IRA
As bananas
If we'd encountered him two years ago he might be up there with my favorite crazy
Like you might be someone who I like
He's not a white supremacist at the other day I didn't know that he believed in his dog
Maybe I could see this through different eyes
But for now I'm tired
It could have been our original
Guy with the telescope right here yeah I'm world-weary charmian
Before
I'm sorry I could have really enjoyed you over text
But now I think you suck
I just never
I've never heard of anything this stupid
I hurt his feelings
His opinions are done
He does he has a Feeling
How is Alex
Even responding to this with the straight face this is amazing
Was it a project Veritas video and has a little bit of celebrity to him and Alex wants to
To see if we can work with it
So he's going to talk
Vaccine
Here we go.
I was going to pull the computer chip out of it on Tuesday right they talked about like potential side effects of vaccines
I don't think anyone's denying any of those things exist
All
Medicine
But Alex
Dixie
He's found a slam dunk
And if you listen to him read this
He accidentally contradict
Is entire narrative
And then tries to just laugh
As if he has
Okay dad from various
Following vaccination with measles mumps rubella vaccine however
A causal relationship is not been established in healthy individuals
See contradictions
Contraindications
No death or permanent
Does that say
Permanent
Madekwe Lee Tukwila
Reported in the published post-marketing surveillance study
In Finland involving 1.5 million children
Adults
Whoops
Great save
He just saw the word death infection
Is that what's going on with that
Did somebody forget to take their vaccines
It is at its
Ready
It's spreading
I mean this is what happens when you have a flimsy ass argument and you think you have the proof and you have no
Miliary with the proof that you're trying to present you end up reading something stray
In there and if you're unlucky like Alex just was yep you will end up reading
How this literally is saying the opposite of what you're thinking
So that's good
Now Zack
Though
He is not an expert in any
Did anything
He did get
A vaccine
Feelings about okay I decided that I want to get
Vaccinated
Against fpd who won it
Take a shot and all of a sudden there's one less thing to worry about
And then after getting the shot I started getting
Kind of sex
Like headachy
Striking like the flu a lot
And now in retrospect what I suspect
Is that I suspect that the vaccine was extruding Factor
And I suspect this because of all the
Poisons that are in the
He's vaccine
That's your feeling
Onnit
What's your definition of getting the flu
I suspect
How many hours
This means nothing this is
That's enough
A whole lot of what they present is just like Alex is like my uncle got a tetanus shot in Hackensack exactly
Yeah I mean at least this is Baseline stupid this isn't it
Way out in the following voting
Yeah it's mostly anecdotal stuff that is like okay I don't know your uncle Ali I don't know
If you're telling the truth about this and even if you aren't doesn't mean
Okay Ali
You just read a thing saying there was a study
Done with 1.5 million healthy children
That showed no
Causal connection
In between that
And then you presented as evidence
Against it
Your uncle didn't like a
And that got a Gardasil vaccine and suspect
So so I'm going to go out on a limb here and say I'm going to trust the the big one this is how this stuff
Spilling aspect is so dangerous
Is because what he
He's doing is he's appealing to people's parts of the brain that work on narrative
Story story
That may or may not be true of an exactly Nicole getting a shot
Anime guy
Got hurt by a
That is more compelling than this
Study of 1.5 million right people
You can wrap your head around so I know somebody who's got in the shop
Before and maybe I think they did act
That's the part of the brain
Being hijacked
Now like I said
Zach is dumb
And
Here he shows himself to also be dumb
In the field of vaccine
Ever know anyone with
A peanut allergy
Do you know why
Stop
Stop right there
They were using peanut oil as an adjuvant for vaccines and now they stopped
And now the peanut allergies are
At Conway.
Alex knew the answer to that question but he didn't want to steal next on me
Zach is very dumb
There's a narrative an anti-vaxxer colls that is very calm
The peanut oil was used in vaccines as an adjuvant
And this explains peanut allergy
That sounds pretty
Be out there but it's very common
And that world
Really yeah
Every single instance of this narrative popping up traces back to one
There may be a bunch of books
The make the claim and there may be a ton of websites repeating it but if they had to produce their concrete Source on it
It would all point to one
Single thing
There's an article in the New York Times from 9
Before that they were misrepresenting
The article does mention that there were clinical trials being done by Merck
Involved vaccines with
The peanut oil based
Adjuvant in it
The article in no way demonstrates
These trials resulted in the product being approved for human
When or even non-human you
This article
As well as another for 1960
See sex about a public discussion
Anne of the clinical trial
Are presented in the book
Peanut allergy epidemic
Heather Frazier
Which is the source
Zach probably thinks
Exciting here
Very popular book
Circle
Snopes looked into the claims
About the peanut oil adjuvant being used
Vaccine given
The public in frayser
The author of this book reply to them quote
Adjuvant 65-4
The peanut oil
Was never licensed for use in the United
I did not mean to suggest that this Edgmont was used outside of her
Clinical trials in the United
This person who wrote the book
Even says the peanut oil adjuvant
Wasn't used
Clinical trials
And yet the narrative
Persist
Because it makes sense
Feels
Right I hate
These people sell by date
Feels like it makes sense I hate them so much
Peanut oil
Feels right
Meredith
Send
I'm not saying that
That's
Text against the law
There should be a law
Zach is repeating complete bulshit
Probably read on natural news
Announces allowing this
Because this
Accurately depict other field vaccines work
None of this is real
Public Health
Risk
Shouldn't there be some sort of like FCC like will send him a couple letters of like clearly this is Falls content please take
We got plenty of time
We're not being ain't we're not angry with you maybe you didn't know maybe this wasn't malicious
I don't I don't I don't know I don't know how you do that
Like eagles like you got to be something because that's just
Evil
Killing people with
Dumb bulshit life
Damn
There's not much really in terms of the meat
About the vaccine stuff
That's not a surprise if there is a lot of peanuts there is
Not a lot of me
Really dumb
So
Big talk about
Dislike
Think about how vaccines are evil
Conspiracy fact uyurken
Conspiracy fact
And then Alex talks about how he's not allowed back on Rogan
Anymore cuz Hill
I'm not allowed back on right now cuz it's because of the number of podcast.
Was your
Because will tell you read them
Small Point Alex's second appearance on Rogan show does have
16 million views
Second most popular episode
Rogan's interview with Elon Musk has 28 million views
His way boards
Alex's first appearance has less views than what a Rogan's interviews of Ben Shapiro
Is less than
The time you sat down with Bernie Sanders Edward Snowden
And less than
Two episodes
Featuring Neil deGrasse Tyson
I suspect Alex just isn't someone Joe wants to have on much right
As a special event
Insanity
Sure
No need for that ship more than once
Two-year yeah you do that reggae
At the log diminishing returns with
That kind of a show is
Instant
Yeah
They're talking about these backs
Brave
And they go to
Perfect
They took
They took out a Nutty
Vaccine and I'm not talking about peanut oil adjuvant
I'm talking about cuckoo
Cuckoo bananas guy okay
They come back from commercial break
I don't even start talking about cannibalism
I don't know what I don't feel like this relay
2D surrounding Conte
List of anything
But Alex just starts talking about cannibalism
Inform you Jordan
Alex Jones
Kind of pro cannibalism I actually thought that was going to be the
Voorhees myself about different pentagons studies they've done in situations
Food most people become cannibals
I wouldn't go out and grab other groups of people in them
But I'm just being honest with the lizard brain kicking in the lower brain
What's a trading party comes your house
That you haven't eaten in about a week and a half there trying to eat you
Alex is a cannibalism apologist
REI
I think I used all of my laps on Zack's first clip
When does the
I didn't know what to do with myself
Okay did you look into the exact numbers of people
I don't care
Somebody to
That's my plans.
Start people for 10 days it turned its like the Stanford Prison Experiment but if
Cannibalism is 1.5 million people in 1982 they founded
80% of them
Wind up eating the 20% that killed themselves and everybody was fine it was the only people who really got bones
Existed it would never be back talk about a lot
One of the biggest
In human history
How much does it take
To turn people into cannibals
What was the great thing is your torture
Yeah for the study
Another one result of it is
Either they commit suicide or they each other
And if there's one thing I know it's that
The ethics in scientific
Dutch that that's okay
That's just okay it's all for the pursuit of science
And if there's one thing that I know
HobbyKids
Party
Only eat self-defense humans
Waukegan
There is such a joy to listening to Infowars
When this happened
I hate the show so much and listen
Listen to Paul be a f****** idiot not be able to make an analogy to Owen Shroyer pretend
Years like
The liquid the Innovative showing the century
Creating new genre
Listen exact be
Completely
Doll and dumb
Like that's all
Hartford
Then 3 hours into the show
Hey man you know what I'll eat a raiding party I'll just be honest
I will eat people
No he's not re-elected today
You can handle
Let's all grow up
Come on guy
Come on
Where where it's all it's just us here now we can all just admit to Arizona wild weed eat people
And some of us have eaten
Pooped in the sink
If you don't think that we can all relate to as something we did or would do
It also really calls into question what other fundamental human taboos Alex would break
In
Do you have
Tactical apps
If you're if you're willing to
Let's say
Humans as opposed to
Borage
Yeah
Of course
I'm going to tell you I'm going to tell you right now
If there's one bad guy that I know Alex identifies with it would be a more tanjo
Mad Max Fury Road
Okay no doubt in my mind that he's like no drinking breast milk I'm loving it
Eating people
The poor are going to starve to death I'm all about it
So this isn't the only thing Alex has to say about cannabis
Apparently
It is there more there is
Disgusting
You know
True story
They'll send the logs
What
Okay
Ambiance about it
Lesbian
I'll be honest I didn't look into that because I don't care but
What's really seems to be like
No qualms
About eating peanut he's fine with it
He's he's ready for the epochal
He has been preparing and now it's.
I don't remember Humphrey Bogart
Eating anybody a movie but I guess that must have been the case if you are so blase about eating p
People why do you sell survival food
I will tell you the answer to why you sell survival food
Made up
I think
That like
Okay yes
If put in
Into that situation
Where it was I'm going
To die if I don't eat
A person like
Let's say
It's a are we doing this I want to draw an important comparison
Put in the
Situation
I don't know what I would do but has a really decent chance
I b
But if I did it would f****** up forever
One of the most horrifying thing that I would have to do
I probably never be able to
To deal with it could never leave you alone
Alex is printer Beyond 24-hour suicide watch
Hannibal apologist
I've no way
No way I'm in the 20% all the way I'm I have a hard time making it through the day and I eat well
Yeah I think there's a decent chance
I would go that way
Expressing is that like
Sitting here with you right now
I don't know what I would do
In that circumstance
There's a possibility but I recognized it would be traumatic it's not traumatic and Alex's
It's not weird
It's inevitable
You know what you might as well get past it now
It's going to happen
So it's like you might as well deal with it preemptive
I think you're I think you're just not preparing yourself to eat somebody's Alex
Is embodying the
The end result of doing that preparation
I don't want it I'm looking up recipes right now on my phone I'm going to find a way to sautee it
A person pretty well
I wish you the best
Sitting here right now with you
One accident and I'm eating
Yeah that's
So they have this cannibalism
Conversation
Gets back to vaccines right the end of the episode
And
Overseas like
Hungry right I don't know why I just turned into a roast
Lego Looney Tunes
They talk about vaccines
Access
Come on man
This so dumb
Japan
15 years ago band children under 2
You actually got
It right
Zack should be made aware
You might be surprised to learn this that your pain is currently battling their largest measles outbreak in over a decade
Directly traced to people not being vaccinated out
I think if he says they've got it right
Then he asked you
Explain
There and they should have.
Iraq's voting policy
Well I think that would be
Everybody needs
Dip the finger pretty soon Japan will be right all across the
This episode is
Terrifying
Glimpse into
The show into the way these guys
Actually think
It's insane like
They need the amount of this that when
Viewed through the prism of like
He feels no obligation
To say things
That he can
Defend
When pressed on it does result like Underoath saying I did a lot of it's me talking about my feelings
One click
Through that prism
It does make a lot of sense
Never presented that way
It's always
I'm telling you things that are based on reality
It's it's
It's terrifying
Also everyone around Alex
Is
A different
Kind of loser
That is just
Profoundly
Paul Joseph Watson Owen Shroyer this exact fella
Just
Bombers mix you what like
Because of the way that this feels
To me like
The the show is very much like
We're ripping around
It's very personal
And it's
It's very much like
I'm bouncing stuff back and forth off of you
Like that's what it it feels like
To me like nobody
Nobody's really paying attention
Lifeforce yeah yeah
It seems to me like it
How many how many of these guys if you scratch them
You know if you wanted these famous pub
Commentators are Congressman or whomever if you just like
Scratch them too far on one subject how many of them would have
Dumbbell fly
Oh I'll tell you right now
They're not doing death certificates because they're voting 18 years
I like how many of them
Cuz that's pretty far out
Yeah I don't know
Yeah it's
It's pretty
F***** up
To think that someone
Willing
To espouse that
Believe
Yeah would have access
To a radio show
Theoretically has
A million listeners Harvard I would like
That's
I mean he did like
Iran has in a certain level I think part of it is just the unfamiliarity with that
Insane
Bang
Which which is why it feels so crazy
Cuz I've never heard anybody say that
What does aborted fetuses are voting
The other thing too is that
Like Alex
Clearly
Is is not heard the aborted fetuses are voting Theory either
You kind of want to surprise and he feels
No need
To discuss it further
He has no he feels no responsibility to do anything
Tube frame
The presentation to his audience so they can take the information in
In a better way
This allows it to be presented as a
Hey this is Zach is real credible guy and here's a thought
He has
I mean you have to very unhealthy the only reaction
He can have it has to be like because it's a human reaction
It is like
Get out
Get out go ahead and go
Explain how about
Go for it
You can't you have to be
Give me a step-by-step plan on how that would do the interview just start but I got to leave
I got to go
I got to go your husband
Zach you did a great job
I have I have quit and we are turning the lights off and I am burning down this facility with you
Tell you I'm Bill Hicks I'm going back to Comedy
To protect the world from Muzak I'm
I'm sorry this has to happen
But we're going to eat
You now
Haven't even 10 days
In preparation for this evening
Anyway we'll be back
But until then
Your website
I feel like we have a Twitter
Pretty sure we do although it's not verifiable but if it was
Did Woody at knowledge underscore fighting at go to bed Jordan on Facebook
Download the show go to iTunes or whatever
Cast app
Leave a review
If you do
But until then
Amito
I'm Leo
I'm dzx Clark
Biggest motor
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work