Alexandra Thurston color
Welcome back to me cuz I wasn't here for the last time we missed your friend you doing
Terrified
Why the world is encroaching upon my psychic
?
This is a show where we sit down and drink red wine
Stop rabbit you do that
I've had a lot of weed
There is I know
So much about Alex Jones
Everyday let me tell you something about me I know nothing about Alex
I live in except for when I come into heater and I discover all of the things
News about Alex Jones
I despise
May you make yourself the brexit
Yes you're going to get into our episode for today
But first I'd like to give a little shout-out
Congratulations you are now a policy wonk
We will be
We will
Immediately broken your contract
Immediately not today but I will do that I just I'm saying some
Subject matter is stuff I don't want to talk about people who are donating
Playing the game correctly
In that they want to torture you
Morley's awful time
And Alex is Pat so we will be doing that
But today
I got a real fun
Exploration for us
I don't know if you're aware of this Jordan
But last week ended on Wednesday and Thursday
Were they
34 hour live broadcast
11 Central
And they went through I believe 8
8 or 9 on Thursday 8 p.m.
On Thursday
Whoa but here's the thing it's
Kind of b*******
What
Yeah because Alex Jones wasn't Manning a lot of it so you have like him doing his own show
And then periodically they drop him Special Report
Does pre-taped losing his mind at 3 in the morning
See him gradually get
More and more one
Very drunk
Yeah even when
Beyond what humans can do
He's at
27 hours and they're still seven more to go
Hot
In the background of the video just like map
The nature of David Knight like
David Knight should have read him a story
You want people to stick around
Paul Joseph Watson who's in London
Until like he could just man some off-hours really that weird for him
He may be a robot sleep at the other way it doesn't matter
You have these things in like
Rob do staring at the
The camera with his eyes
The nature of a Telethon
Is
This
Tension of candy maker
Yeah that's why Jerry's telephones back in the day were fun because celebrities
Frazee hours
Any black guys on his last few
And Alex didn't engage with that
As a genre of the telephone
But you did
Adhere to the ohfuck
Let's try and products as hard as we can
Good every hour they played a 10-minute thing
Of him just it was just Alex
Free tape
We like to joke around
Is the globalist
It was a disaster
It was so embarrassing but
The Telethon did include appearances from our friend Mike cernovich
Greg who's now an official Infowars employee
Wonderful
I'm so glad that
Sevierville is really enjoying together into a gelatinous
Choose of monstrous
A lot of my theories are starting to come together about these consolidation
We have
Infowars
And pizzagate proponent
Jackson getting hired at Rebel media
Along with Gavin / Nigel McGuinness
And Lauren Southern
And based Stickman
Deniz weirdos of the alt right
You have that team over there at some point in the future she is a
Crazy
She's just another one of these provocateurs
Anfo
Journalist yellow journalism
I don't know what it is
Citizen Kane Rosebud
Just completely
Just a liar
So you have that at the rebel media
Joining up with Alex Jones
Over on the Infowars
Ebony Vibes yoga Rodger Stone
Jerome corsi
You have
Game over here
Rebel media up in Canada
Did the Canadian companies
They're influencing our politics as a foreign company
I don't know it's very murky.
Be people the rebel media
The southern
Baked Alaska
They are getting paid
By some organization Weatherby Rebel Media or
Some other
Organization
Counter protest
In Berkeley
Like they're getting paid for their coverage and organization of these
Anti antifa riot
That are going on in Berkeley
Actually paper
Exactly
And if put and it's swell
It's so obvious and overt that it's almost
Blase to call out
Your company is paying you to incite violence
You're not a paid protester you're a journalist
It's kind of that we're development office
F******
It's terrible
But he also had appearances on the telephone from our friends
2015 Lionel
Lionel
Yep explicable how to destroy the world
I had no idea that that was the Playbook
His team he was on
Find appearance by comparison
Why is Ron Paul doing I don't know
I think he is
Ignite
Is what I would say
He's like
He's like an aw-shucks
I'll do it for you Alex
You just seem like a good ol fella I think that's a piece of it gets a lot of mileage out of his sort of cartoon
Okay old man voice
Cuz I think the people were like a little bit
He's not he's not up to something he's just
Quirky old man
I think there's some of that but here's the most
Originally supposed to be a 30 hour marathon
That would end
At the end of The Alex Jones
Show
On Thursday
Yes he has a 4-Hour show
Start at the beginning Go 24 hours
I guess it was maybe supposed to be 28
Or maybe it was supposed to include the 325 live after Alex who cares
The Anchorman
On Thursday
He did the whole thing
He did the last hour
Is it there at all
He still hasn't put it up I know
I was
And I realize that my mouth was making the words I was trying to say no picture
Which is not good 30th power this Marathon episode
It was all a crock of s***
Jon rappoport
Report was boring we don't need to go over it
It's
Toothless in many ways
To play it was really all about
Insanely about selling products out of context drop
Alex Jones
Marketing pitch
A person was wearing my shirt
I think the Paul Joseph Watson
T-shirt is great
For women
Dudes don't wear dudes on their shirts
It's gay
Obviously
That's what are you playing
Basically
You don't want
Alright whatever Alex
Are you all right
I just
As if you were going to take a note
I don't even understand that
That
Toxic masculinity
Cauliflower
Don't worry dude space on your shirt like what about all the
Face on there
Now admittedly Paul Joseph
Blick
I've never seen
I'm guessing that's why
Episode where Alex Jones
Very
Clothes like very was
Toeing the line
Call Joseph
He's really good-looking male I think I think that that was Gavin McGinnis you think
Washed overtimes material
I guess that would apply to pjw
16 years
I'm not saying that for other reasons not that one
Our episodes
Recovering the Wednesday and Thursday episode of The Alex Jones program contained within the
Gotcha
So
Mostly Wednesday
Cuz Thursday is a little weird
But I want to start with Thursday
Cuz this is our 26 of the marathon and then we're going to go back
To Wednesday and we'll touch back on Thursday a little
I want to start with this
Because podcast
Just because
I want to start with this topic
Because it makes
Me so happy
On Thursday
An article came out in BuzzFeed
A guy named Charlie warzel
He have been doing amazing coverage on Twitter of Alex Jones custody
City battle
And it turns out he has been researching Alex Jones has passed
In the way that you and I
Head really wanted
Contact people who worked at the radio station
LinkedIn
So we were about to go down this path
Cuz this guy did it for us an amazing piece of Journalism
Honorary policy
I would love to get him on a really cool
If we can get in touch with
But that would be really cool on Thursday this article came out
And of course
There's a lot of news in the world
Alex Jones
That's take up
A bunch of his program to talk about it
He's going to talk more about
Jones related
Turn on Alex Jones
It's interesting it's interesting that you would say that
Okay I'm going to ask her if
I'm going to read some selections from this article
But I want you to see what he's focusing on
In this clip
I think it's I think it's pretty important
Kristoff BuzzFeed
Is reportedly a hundred million dollars in debt
If not I don't know
Publicly traded company yet they're about to have their IPO next
Beer probably
Which is awesome. Bailey
Matt is right guys
How much he was getting called
By BuzzFeed
I read this article.
And it's literally
95%
I guess make it look like it's real
Little stories in there
Totally made-up
Yorkie
They didn't talk about my dog
Office lunch
Best Buy Medford
From Shipping loves you so much
I have a fake voice
I've openly said I criticize it
I don't want to be
Voice I have a raspy voice I've been to
He wants to be a
Wasn't wasn't high voice
And screaming
Had to go to specialist
A bird
Suggest
Big dicks
Why are you picking on little old Alex Jones look at all of my problems
Choosing one paragraph from BuzzFeed
To discuss
Disgusting during the Obama years
Others close to Jones during the time said that
Rolling audio
Against the broadcaster was insecure
Two former colleagues that Jones Reserve his greatest resentment for Rush Limbaugh
The jealousy was so intense that Jones began to
The creep his now-famous Crush
Gravel-voiced
From the talk show Legend
We spent weeks getting everything just right in the studio
Former employee recall
Then he'd go for a drive and hear rushing
I need my voice to sound something like that
And so we completely re-engineer the sound to make him gruffudd
So
Listen
Who cares
It's the most
Irrelevant thing in this entire article
These
Infowars employees that they got to speak to them
Or all anonymous
FaceTime lifetime non-disclosure
I'm so he can deny Flatley everything that these people say
Panino's but they won't come out no ice
He knows it'll never get proof cuz then those people
It's not what I feel like
It's a thing you can willingly enter
The part of
Anyway
Is there a moral Authority
Good points has nothing to do with some more stuff from this article
I want to close out this clip because
I am so funny
Lost control
Sexier
Shed
Re-engineer the sound
To make me rough
I don't like my voice
Voice
The only people who like my voice
Get ladies wet they said on speakers while I scream about the globalist
He's going I just did like a 45-minute
Bit about my voice
Israel
Polyps
Probably isn't going to engage with like the
The meat
Criticisms even like the article
Itself is called Alex Jones will never stop being Alex Jones
That's it
About not about how he's fake
It's about how he can't stop himself from being himself
Right
His Own Worst Enemy
Essentially
The real problem is that he's too real
This voice stuff Ergo I'm going
How to reduce
Excerpt
The from this amazing
Article
Amazing
This is about his early
Jones was a modest Public Access success
But he owes his first real media job to his dentist father
Who solicited
Station manager at the Austin talk radio station
Kgfk during a routine teeth clean
He said
You got s*** in the guy TV like
By the way
Summer job don't you
Poke
Poke you want to get my son a job don't you
I want to keep that
He said my son's got some out there ideas but I think you'd be perfect
Darrell O'Neill the kvsk manager to broker the deal explained
The next week he brought Alex in for a meeting
Just secure Jones a spot on the station
Jones's father became a
The first it sounds first on a response
So
All of his complaints about people like taking shortcuts that and all this
Isn't it
Hire these made a lot of good moves
ISM into a whole lot more than most absolutely all of it comes from his dad
That's super f***** up
The more we learn about his growth is
Daddy issue
Mommy is
Here's a little thing about a personality
That is back in the
Kjfk days
Remember Jones
Is volatile easily bruised
What associate recall Jones Terrytown bulletin board
From fellow station producers who criticized one of his more controversial
Segment
And an Austin Chronicle article from July 2006 multiple Public Access producers
You claim quote
That Jones has used both ACAC policy
A legal Maneuvers to intimidate them
Or get them thrown off the air
He claims the globalist
And AC DC
Is always back
You got big balls
Turn on TV or radio has a way of changing you Austin Chronicle founder Lewis Black
An early Jones critic and frequent Target of Joneses early Ranch set not the big one
And for Alex it was
Was always
Always about you go
When he got that validation there was no going back
That's on someone who was
Involved with him early on
Quote
This
Is a nice confirmation of something we've discussed and a theory we've had
Yes
Sometimes he'll say he has sources
He's been told a piece of news has been confirmed but we wouldn't have that information
A former Infowars
Employees at
Quote
Later we find out that it was because a week earlier we had to call her on-air who theorized about something and Alex repeat
It's true
It's true we figured it out
Literally seeing that
Christina happened in the the Y2K episode
We haven't really talked about it but after the inauguration
During the during the post inauguration celebration explained
That Islam
Believe that every country that believes in Islam is the house of Islam
And everything outside of it is
The house of War
And there needs to be war on all of these
These places
Alex is repeated that verbatim
Repeatedly
Nothing
He never said it before that guy on the street
It's crazy you don't
Things that key like that
That he likes the people
Tell him and then just turn them into truth in his
Keep starboard
Professor and researcher at the University of Washington accidentally stumbled upon Infowars digital footprint
How rumors spread on Twitter during the 2013 Boston bombing
Starboard found that
The Navy SEAL so I could not love starbird
Yeah that's great that's perfect
She found that a specific rumor that Navy Seals have carried out the attack was largely attributed
Unlink
Second only to YouTube
At the time we thought this was pretty insignificant
Countryside but things look very different
In hindsight
Korean there I apologize
That was in our world they look very
Yeah I was realizing
Call myself out
When the Fukushima nuclear disaster happen
Alex
Tons of
Potassium iodide and oh my god did we sell that
A former employee recall
He can sell 500 supplements
Set an hour another counter
4 conspiracy
Yep we now that
According to one former employee Jones brag that the Infowars store grossed 18 million dollars between 2012 and
Wow
Another source puts that number closer to 10 million dollars
And this was before the popularity Jones and Infowars enjoyed today
The store camp
Tom Jones's ruthless Dilma
Quote
I watched him on the phone with some poor author who written the book jones wanted to buy
And Jones go she ate him down until he's making no money
Jack blood
The former radio colleagues
Wow
Two former employees
Alleged that Jones would instruct
Staff to find products that were failing
And convince them to whittle their margins to almost nothing
In exchange for the Infowars endorsement
Quote Alex's business model was
Are these companies that a low rate in lock-in exclusivity
The former staffer said
Noting that attaching the Infowars brand to a Prada
Often destroyed a seller's future prospects to go Maine
Stream
For some employees
The shift from what they saw is acris
A crusader journalism
The content marketing for colloidal silver with jarring
Quote it became a moral issue issue for me one said
If why I don't work there
Okay well f*** that guy
No he quit
Quit because it went from equipped because he was like
Is all about the conservative ideals in the fight against global
But I think you could make a much better
For being involved in
At that point
Then once again
Colloidal silver
Like that's unacceptable
Having a conservative beliefs and believing that this guy is on the Vanguard of that
It's understandable know he's conservative beliefs
You know like it's
No I'm not going to be on the east side
I'm going to give him a walk guy
Order I don't know
The point
More former staffers
Suggested that this influx of money inspired the greatest change in Jones demeanor
Quotes
It's become less about affecting change
And more about being Sensational and making money one ex-employee explain
It didn't start out that way
He was a lovely person to hang around for a long time but that soon if accurate evaporated
In interviews for separate employees
Describe Jones quote
Do ocellated maniacally between excitement and anger
Quote working for Alex
It was like a combination of Blackbeard meet
Hitler one former employee says one minute just on a high and swashbuckling and calling us to action
The next
Punching out walls
He was a bad dude
Which one is the guy who punched out
Please say Hitler is more
Hitler
Hitler was known for punching out Jewish
Drywall
Two former employees recall that after an employee left the company Jones would call a staff
Pull up YouTube videos of their work
And take turns making fun of
Quote
The unsaid implication a former employer said was that if you leave this will happen to you
Quote Jones rewards the people who buy in all the way one former employee said
But there's an expectation
Not to contradict
Him or the message
That is that is abuse
Still
Like what
Just what you are getting the criticisms about
Literal corporate
Now he's making my he's a bran
So he's just a corporation now
Ocean isn't going to reward
People that buy
I used to work at Groupon and if we had a meeting after someone last
And they were like making fun of how bad their work was
I would be
So uncomfortable
That kind of environment is hostile
That's abuse
And the idea that the implication is that when you leave we will do this to you
Keep people in line that's cult Behavior
Though
Union implications of that
That's different than just like
Will restock the shelves because it is
Sort of creative work in terms of Infowars
Even if you are creative
Right it's different than stock
Anyway
Here is a quote
That really gets into the last paragraph summary
Amazing
But this one is about
It sorta validates a lot of the theories we have about the political landscape right now
According to one person
Some president for Studio on election
The 2016
Jones boasted of having 18 billion km in
Quotes
Now Jones is probably exaggerating
The Source said
Serious influence if you can get them voting
Alex doesn't have list
Get followers
The audience Jones
Spent decades building
It finally made its presence known
Hit Rally's on social media and finally at the poles
Quotes that rule vote for Trump nobody saw coming
The Source continued
It wasn't only Alex
But I think you can describe a significant portion many first-time voters
Of those votes to him
Quote
He's like the girdles of 2016
Another longtime Jones Associates
He really want the election
Trump
Why we are here
Like
Weeds that noise out pretty quick the article also goes on to say that he probably didn't want to drop to win
Because then
Liberals in charge we got a defense
Conservatism
Because Trump won
You have to shift his his shift has been
Jarring
Almost certainly due to that
Extra
Influence
And extra visibility
That's where all of these lost his lawsuit since
President we had the the Liberals to rail against
None of this s*** will be coming on if we be getting sued by Hillary
I mean Google
If
That I mean
It's much more
Like I don't think there's any surprise
To the timing of
Giovanni's
Once once
People started watching
No actually it did that's not I don't think
Certification
I think that the timing of the lawsuit coincides with
The closure of the
Court case
They had to do with
The children
In Twin Falls
Idaho
That case that case and recently
They wanted a retraction
Alex did his b******* because he's influential
What's happening at the
Same time
Very public custom
Yes
Gotcha and I think it's very unfortunate time
Let's marry
Stevens
What's in this article
Go back to Alex returning from breaking
Send to any of it
Suddenly sounds different
Coronavirus
Either they're there their leader of there
He's referring to like private message
Messages between
BuzzFeed writers they were joking about the ID
It's probably inappropriate but at the same time it's not like
Inappropriate
Just goofing off in private message
Yeah it does you mean like normal people are doing every
Single goddamn Day on
Sure
For several months
College my first job
To make something up
Is that I'm not an actor
I didn't want Obama to be defeated in 2012
That
My voice is Trey
The producers
Voice is annoying time
Where would you think about record
Rush Limbaugh
Went deaf
No that's at work
High pitch low voice
Weaver mobile
Graph filter
Who cares why are you fighting this battle
Look
Nobody
Valise
An interesting or important thing in that article
If it was if it was anybody else I would
This is a diss track
From dealing with the reality of the article
I think this is 100% the thing he is most angry about
You guys are saying that I wanted to change my voice
Just sounds like that guy
F*** you
Part of it that's that and then I think the other part is just that it naturally fits into his narrative he's already
Spinning about like people think
You've actor with the kids
His lawyer said
It's because I go this
Matches good finding pieces of things that fit what he's already doing and then just sort of incorporate
Bring them in
He's kind of like a bulshit
Black hole
But just put a black hole
Yeah absolutely
So
He goes on another like
A couple minutes talking about his voicemail least like 10 minutes covering that nothing about this
Substantial
A lot of his Thursday show
Now let's go
Somebody said my voice doesn't sound right yeah among many other way worse than
Gas discussing whether or not my voice clips from The Joe Rogan
Podcast you guys know what I sound like what I'm not on Infowars
We've got this BS Mike cernovich, then talk about voices great
Every guest
Discussing what their voice sounds like cernovich coming in to talk about how my list is real
It's insane
Israel is everybody else's that cuz they're made
Bromley real American made
Headed teeth removed
Melt it down and then rebuilt into teeth and put them back in his company these are Americana.
Exactly that's what's important about Rappaport
George Washing
Wow
These Anza
The b******* but let's go National Treasure 3
Let's get those
I am still seriously waiting for National Treasure
I'm very excited for to eventually come out
Is there only two there is National Treasure in the National Treasure Book of Secrets
I've actually sort of written aspects
4-quart Lisa outline do with Nicolas Cage
Also known as Benjamin Franklin gay
In the movie
Is that a character's name
It's real tight there I guess that must have like just broke in my brain to the point where I just skipped
That's Nicolas Cage
His name
In every movie Nicolas Cage is in
Nicolas Cage
You find that the Napoleon never died and was actually taken
Are you from space
He's been planning ahead like he's going to take over America
But the secret
In order to like a plan
How to stop him
Are underground in Arlington
So in order to get to these plan I love you got to become president and then faked his own death
To get underground at Arlington Cemetery get the plans and stop space Napoleon
To become president
Regardless of the rest of that
Treasure three should have absolutely has to become president but as a con
Becoming president is incidental to his plan somehow
Anyway
President 60 Seconds
Yep I want
First of all I would love it if that was the point
Even if it's not I need a third when I love those movies so much
But let's go back now
2 Wednesday
The Telethon
Wednesday
A clock set for 11
Central Central
Alex Jones
Take them things off
He starts off Wednesday show
Very weird
This is the opening of the the Telethon
Yeah
Something really strange
And Alex
Add the trend that I think
Is going to Blossom
In the coming weeks and months
And that is
That wasn't ever
I got this to say Trump is really going office trajectory more more
Here's the deal
Trump is draining the swamp
Polly Pocket
He's like fighting the big Crime Boss
Power level down
He's looking in the eyes of the devil
He is slowly becoming them
100% first 30 days
Was it 95%
Havoline quick lube
These are real things
Getting big bag of small businesses they arguing that
So you can't
Bring up that
What is Obamacare
What I want to plan a visit before the house-passed know about that guy
He's not yet jerking off about how do you feel
Break cuz I'm broke on the Thursday show
Or was it
Whatever
Get into it
Send it
So in that saying
First of all it's amazing
Restarting to give Levi
Track frame to get off the Trump
Bandwagon
The things that he's still holding water for things that aren't real
Nothing.
That's
One true thing
In that list of stuff you saying
He's done
Like I guess I didn't see that we withdrew from the
Little Rock
But it's it doesn't Kate and there were a lot of people who want that it probably will
Happen if it hasn't already
We're not working at better deals with China
Unless you consider all the trademarks they've given Trump personally
Beyond
Panthers
It's just it can't
Cuz it's impossible and stupid came out and said they would consider it a hostile Act
It would be
It doesn't get more hostile than building a f****** wall across a border
India and Pakistan are really good friends because of that giant wall on their f****** border
So the other thing that sort of a chav
Build a new wall
Shut up
Commercial credit score
Play Dragon versus
Space Napoleon is a great
Is a great movie
The true comedy of it though is that like
I've talked to a number of people who support Trump
Support about the building wall is they think it will block drugs
Coming into the country
Not realizing the drug dealers have lots of boats
An airplane
And most of the drugs.
Get smuggled into the country don't come through the Border like that
And build a taller wall and there's tunnels underneath the Border it's insane
I like lasers
Electric fence
If you want a 6
Cesspool
That is
Impossible
On the Mexico United
Dig
What
20 miles Underground
Set off a nuclear warhead
And hope volcano show up ever
Every single f******
On the ground
Otherwise
You're not building a
F****** wall
Also the idea that it's going to stop
What motivates a lot of people cuz the opiate crisis
By the way they're reducing funding for that
You see that overseas helping people with the LPR type of drug control office
55%
The budget
That was proposed
Hayirli dismantle a lot of the organization
Responsible
For helping fight the opioid crisis
Kissimmee country
So everybody who supports
You need to look at
The f****** mirror
Trump doesn't give a s*** about opiate
He doesn't care of your family they're struggling
You don't care that yourself
He cares about bigotry
He cares about
Symbolic
Hatred
Yep hears about this idea of promoting
Fear but Above All Else
What does
He care about
Dan
White nationalism making his own f******
That's true
Out of Alex Jones
Making a lot of money out of fear
I think that there is a part of these may be inspired by Alex a little bit
The only thing I want to say about the
Okay and this I think it's a discussion
Themselves
See that's kind of my thing I want to
I I want have compassion
Right
Because
It's very clear that all of these
These people who voted for
Where
Deluding themselves
Into thinking he was at
Very very
Yeah and no matter how many times we told him
He was the thing they thought he was
They didn't believe
They have
Begin to know that he's not that thing
Just like just like Alex Jones
He's gotten off track for what we thought he was going
Has kind of a Bellwether starting to turn on you
Them shitz
Until I think it's also an indication that he knows that something bad's,
Like
Well
He's his sources rdt Junior
Will not work
Rodger Stone all the f****** time
Give
In big trouble
He's a big escapes this one I mean
I mean he's a slippery dude he survived a lot of political just feelings
Seeking Asylum
Rather than
Actually doing it
If anybody is smart they will take
Now let me ask you a question
One smart
No
They really smart people working behind the scenes that we are unaware of
Here's here's the one thing though
Right
They are getting f***** by Trump and the Republic
Can today voted for faith
First
There is no there's no middle ground
Devote
For the people
Who are going to murder them
Right
I want to feel compassion
And for them because I don't want people to get
Pray time
The same time there is that part of my brain that
F***
We're going to die
It's not like it's a it's not a situation where they've only doomed themselves they've doomed the rest of us
Themselves more ice
Look for you and I are people who are in a position where if
You know we have pre-existing condition
The most
Point where our mental health especially will go off the rails
Real hard
If we don't have
Certain protection
Here's the thing I know that I sound maybe a little optimistic
That with the outpouring of attention
People calling
Senators
I I don't think there's any way that a bill including that stuff would ever pass
I don't think so either all of the stuff that I don't think has happened or what happened
Hold on
I'll be goddamned if I'm terrified by like 9
A little bit
Do you think that Alex Jones is just dipping his toe
In the water of trump
Denial
I don't
I don't think he is he's really into coil
Eddie goes on to say a little more right here
The Gorgon
Just remind everybody
Redundant
Last year on November 8th
Absolutely not
Absolutely
It's still
How he can be so good and do so much good
So much to expose political correctness
And then start going sideways it makes it even worse cellular gut-level dozen
Well I mean like let's talk about him exposing political correct
In the past Donald Trump has threatened to sue people over joke
In the past
Convicted for laughing
Totally f***** up
Let me give a tiny discrepancy
I'm totally against
This woman being convicted or jailed
But that's different than Trump
Suing somebody about making a joke about
In this case you can hide behind a very cowardly explanation that this lady was
Was disrupting
Senate proceedings or something like that
I know it's dumb but you can make
Consider that are
You are superb
Whereas with shop he's literally
Talked about suing newspapers that publish bad things about him ranked priebus was on a TV
You saying that they're talking about
Opening things up so you can sue the Press
Percent of the First Amendment
The most
The negative stuff we talked about with political correctness
This is Way Beyond
Be saying don't say tranny
Compared to I'm going to sue you for writing something I don't like
I'm going to sue you for saying tranny instead of
Right
Bucked up
It's so simple
Both sides need to protect
Right because all you have to
To do is like the religious liberty ship that they wanted like you should be allowed to
Discriminate based on
That is
Good for you
America is
Always a Christian Nation
It's the same Obama expanding spying in space
It's all good because then
Right right that kind of
Obviously
Stop
Divorce Yourself
From your b******* ideology
You don't want the
He's religious freedom bill.
Nope because an even worse
I don't believe in any of that religious bulshit
But you don't want me you it's like you don't want to do a religious freedom Bill there
Cuz then
Take over
Bucking we can do the same shift
Do you write English
This is me
This is never going to pass the course
Like it is
Well I know that
That is the wildcard
This wouldn't be into this
Because it does it would violate the Civil Right
It's so mad to me the bullseye are not like
They don't understand that fine distinction
It is
You passed this
This religious liberty
Implicit inside
If you're a business
And your beliefs
Is the black people
You can just say no black
Yep that's where we will be
If this passes
If the exact same logic
This is not a slippery slope
This is just the application
Of the lodge
Take the replace with
Is lgbtq now you have Jim Crow laws is absolutely discriminatory will never it will never pass
Attorney generals have come out across the country sayings
That if it does
Get implemented
We will immediately
Brighten so it will be a huge fight and there's no way that can pass and if it does
Again
Bedlam
It will be fire in the
That's the thing I kind of I am a little surprised we're not already at fire in the
Cuz we got this nice wine
Because we have
Many
Distractions
To keep us from
The time will come
Yeah it's on
See that's the thing though
I agree with you
I agree with you that it will never pass
And that they will Channel
They will do all of
But it does
Our reality has been
Eroded so much
That I don't
Have faith
Any see this is the exact conversation that was happening in the lead-up to the election in right after the election
The idea of resisting normalization of trump
Our reality becoming so f***** up
Before that were Unthinkable are now
Alright
Normalization
In your brain what you have to do
Cuz you have to think about empaths
Time what would it look like if
This individual event happen
Yeah try and hold on to that
If you do that if you evaluate the things that are happening on a daily basis
By putting it into like
Let's play
Even during Bush's gears
I'll give you give you go back to that and say like
Does this happen to under Bush
I'll be f***** up
He'll be crazy but
Feels
How weirdly normal people are being anesthetized
Do the
Super f***** up where
Will be our undoing
People just accepting Things Are
Does normal
Freedom bill is normal
Take away people's Health Care
Which is
Lie about the budget
But they're going to be proposing
Exclusively about the wrist
People that died
So billionaires
200 million more dollars it's 200 million more dollars that they
Do anything
If you have a billion f****** dollars what else do you need
They also want to get rid of the estate tax
Stuff like that
Being able to become the next
Old money
It's like
You know everybody
Fetishize is the idea like the Carnegie's than the Rockefellers and stuff like that
As opposed to
I don't know Mark Zuckerberg who has money
It is the distinction of royalty versus
Basically
Or something like that what it is about
Next phase of the game
For you and me it's making enough money to stay alive
For most people that is the case
We're engaged in a struggle
We have jobs that allow us
You know I'm
Broke
For the most part
Whereas if you're rich
You know you maybe want to buy a nicer house
Maybe want to buy a nicer car
When you're really rich
Legacy
And that's that's what it is for them it's not good I don't have to worry about ever being poor and not being able to worry about
Buck I can't pay my Internet bill to have something else
It's like Eman Alex Jones make comparisons to videogames all the time but it is kind of like that you're playing
In that
No matter how good a thing is
We get used to it and that be
Is the Baseline
Call Waterworks
Next Level Up
It's still
Do they
The things
Always
Boggles my mind
About
These rich people
Is that
Have they ever read it
Where rich people
Go to far
And then everything's fine for
Well my conflicted not know that everytime rich
Take one step two
How far all the sudden
Verify
And I think is that they have read those
They've taken lessons
In terms of safeguarding
From those things
Falling people like Marie Antoinette other people who have been f***** over by screwing
Unfortunately naked lessons you can learn
Depressed people are.
Push down even more
It's always
Like
Wytheville VA
With this type of
Situation
I believe in
Calling your
Sure I do
We're at the
Now where it's clear that
Theme
Represent the House of Representatives is entirely purchase
Yeah like that's the obvious
There's no other conclusion to make
Democrat
Is that the way worse part of it
Is
Well
They don't they don't represent their constituents
.
They are
Yeah I know so
Important is calling your representative is
At this point don't take 40,000 people
And March down
Wacker
Take 40,000 people
To your nearest billionaire
And surrounded f***
Yeah bringing cops National Guard
Hard to protect one billionaires house
Maybe people just sitting around there I mean
Isn't that very it's not the best
Optic 4 what the
Country is
I mean it
Sodium
Tire country
The entire
Nationalize military
Comes down on regular
Well here's the f*****-up thing I think more likely than the National Guard what you'd end up with
Feels like something like Blackwater
Please for the Keystone Pipeline
They're willing to
To torture and murder us
I think the biggest
Problem is that it still hasn't
Really touched White
Yep it really I like the Keystone Pipeline
100% the cops
Murdering
Peaceful protest
Doing everything that can be doing things that just
Luckily didn't leave UMass death
Which they very easily could
And the whole wide world
Sub-freezing temperature
Absolutely
If you saw the news
Tomorrow cuz they're brown
Everyone
Sitting here
Supporting them
As much as I
Possibly
It's sort of like I donated money I did I did everything short of going there and getting my ass
F****** Frozen
Eventually it's going to start happen
Two people
And it leads me to my next
Point
I think after this week
Should move on cuz we're blowing real hard
We got to get back
You and me complaining about politics and maybe it will be as the show evolves and people donate more we could do this every day
Right but for now it's still an Alex Jones podcast
Hitachi off and
Is going to happen
Is there will be
Decapitate style archetypical def
Have to embolic deaths that will happen
Symbolic
And unfortunately
It's b******* that we can't take
These people like Alton Sterling
Eric Garner people who've been killed
By the police
Motors that they are absolutely that should be enough
Should be more than
But
Or the Sandy Hook
Sure children were murdered
And we couldn't turn that into a rallying cry for
For gun control
Yes I mean like
Like the word complacent
Are we too far gone
Like once once I saw that we couldn't
Anyting
I was like
We will never have you know one of the reason
We can't turn Sandy Hook into anything is because of people like Alex
Usos
The doubt into whether this really happened right.
Want to take our guns
Is fake
Sedan
It's all a plan all along
Do you have these people I think
Again
But a nice bow on it
Yep why we do this show
Yeah it's in order to fight back against these sorts of things
Yeah people like Alex Jones
Complacency
There's a lot of
More stuff that we should be doing and I hope we will be doing
But for now
This is as much as we can do
Got to go to work
F****** capitalism got to feed my cat bro
Baldwin's first mine bones
Alright
It's just
Nesquik
Anyway very appropriate
About people calling themselves the resistor
I bet he loves us
Let's go ahead and start
7 months ago
Calling themselves
LaRosa's
I'm Stephen Colbert
Now I want
Stop they're really bad Stephen
I want to stop right there because
His bumpers that he plays coming out of
Commercial breaks
No but for less or less literally say that
If you're listening to this
You are the resistance
He's quoting himself ever said that
Stephen Colbert I don't understand exactly what you say
But I get the the sensor
Yeah
You are the resistance
T-Mobile band
Harmony / Porsche
Weather
Does it matter
In the closet.
The Paramount is growing Global movement in the world
Against unelected
Is over whistle dog with one
We have been allowed to celebrate
So long is Beacon direct to people and internet communities
It's like people who on Stormfront
I don't know if it's intentional on his part
But there is
There's a piece of that
That will
Lodge directly in their brain
Be like
Oh yeah this is this is
We don't have to
All the time
You see people with just straight-up Neo-Nazi regalia
That's what's going on
Nationalism is one thing
What is happening right now is not nationalism
Beyond white nationalism
Christian supremacist
Christening
Very heavy
Yeah yeah
It's made of anvils falling on the rest of our f****** high
Yeah so he talks about
This like coming out of the closet
Stuff
What have you
And is next
Clip is really income
God I hate
Hating people who are different than co-opting or terminology and ideas
You know how miserable it is to have to
Heidi Riggs
Have to live a lie everyday people don't judge you
It's the worst feeling in the world which is why we should come out
Also had to hide their very existence for so long
I hate it because it's so miserable to be in the closet all the time
Understand
For one goddamn second
Nope
Also this great Paul Joseph Watson
Send report about dear white people and what would happen if someone made a dear black people
What would happen
Somebody made a dear black people Birth of a Nation
It was called A Song of the South
It's all just about how white people are the people who suffer the most race
Betty White this next clip is
Back to the resistance
Idea
Historical lineage of Arctic line to nothing
And it is Alex Jones
Just a line Oak Cliff
No because it goes back to the fifth
Explain the sort of waves
Nationalism
And stuff like that
He also
Really can't figure out
Housekeeping plan
Going off the coffee
Placing people in the wrong
Wave
But also I'll come at the end of this
Explain
Why alot of these figures he's throwing in our
Are dumb
Include
Jerome corsi
And the Pappy Shannon
Scientifically historically Hangout
Truth
Phyllis Schlafly
60 years ago
Murderer
Phyllis Schlafly specifically was working to
Pose glass
Book
She publishing brought her into Providence was again
Rights for women
Absolutely was about how if we end up in the
It's going to ruin a lot of privileges
You wouldn't be able to
To raise your children which
Hundred percent
If there are women who don't want to work
And want to be homemakers
Are in an economic situation where that is possible
I don't look down on that
I don't think
To choose like if we want to be a stay-at-home
Wyoming dude that's like buying a shirt with Paul Joseph Watson face
It's not very much
Like her with her whole thing was let's not allow women who want
To do that to do that cuz
Cuz it's going to ruin it for the rest of
Subway
Two inches shorter than
I'm made of steel
He's starting his lineage
That's where he's starting his lineage
Is Phyllis Schlafly and Barry Goldwater
Area
Monster's Ball
The first wave
Paul's in the Ronald Reagan for the second wave
Then you come into the Third Way Matt drudge Alex Jones
How many coming to the 4th
Lipan
Horrible Nazi
Garages
You can appoint
Very very very exciting time
He couldn't keep his way
Straight you like lapan
In the fourth wave she's actually third
Spoken to people who are in England
About Nigel farage
Most people there know him
Completely failed politician
Like he's run for office multiple times and
Just been like
He would be like
I would I would guess a more discredited version of Ross
That's sort of wheelhouse
Or the Buffalo Bills
Buffalo Bills
This being is under between his legs
You think she's pretty
She's so pretty. So I don't know man like
I get I get what he's trying to
But unfortunately really reinforces the idea that there is a cabal
I hate to use the word
The ball cuz I'm
Very against
Did most count
But of the conspiracy
You might even say
And his
Is
Leanings
Britain and France
Putin in Russia
Trump here
What he's doing is combining
But aren't nationalism
Bear
They're a weird
0 weird globulus anti-global
Yeah exactly from all around the world have come together to say that all around the world
We shouldn't have these leaders
And they all are related to each other
Which is so weird
Signal we don't want the UN we want our own you
Yeah I don't know I don't know about that
The people who watch Black Mirror in Legos
That doesn't look like a dystopia at all I love I really need someone's Netflix
Flix password cuz
I watched
The first three episodes and then almost started crying
And I don't have a password I watch the one where everyone's on treadmills
Performance
Immediately and I'm like
This isn't
Retaining this is
Hurting me yeah I loved it but it still
Myself
Like I'd like
An incredible admiration for what they had achieved
I can only watch one every 3 months
Was just like him
Sorry sounded like Alex Jones
Handmaiden
Going like
Yep yep
I will watch that
Eventually going to need
If you guys want to treat me a password
This excerpt is what I would describe as anti-sexism sex
It's
Alex
Talking
About to Hillary Clinton
Record numbers of women
Yeah we do
It's what's between their ears
A vagina
And the Bravada at the hubris of the elite the try to sell
A drugged-out evil crone
With all of her evil record
It's like it's like
They wouldn't
It's
It's not about what's
Between your legs
It's that you're ugly
Great I like ladies it's your face that I do
Did you look at the breakdown of the vote
It was white with
It wasn't like women overwhelmingly voted
A drop that's not fair
White women over
Whelming Lee voted for
Turned out white is more important than gender
What are we doing
World
Happening are we sure we want to keep living here I don't know
Quip
He goes on to you know how Alex Jones is really into just headlines and not the subs
Love it
This is basically going to characterize
Explained
He doesn't
Just think of the news that way
Evariant
Oh that is
Put a package labeled
What's a very negative world will be back the 30-hour special transmission
So if we saw a box
Obviously
No I'm trying to call on us at all this guy who has a history of being a con artist
He said he was a patriot
What
Look what kind of responsibility what world we live in
You know
It's even more pathetic because Pandora's Box wasn't labeled all the worst things in the world
We went for the bugs that said kill us all
Skip this next clip because he's really just lying about poll numbers
The poles were skewed 30 points
Send Clinton favor
About the
Steve
The bias exists in pool
And generally what they do is that they give
Liberals like at 3% margin
Added onto
The poll numbers
Because of
Voting
Registration
Discrimination
Point number is
Patently absurd
Like that
Patently absurd no matter
You if you have been alive and you seen any election there's never been enough
Trump had a massive landslide
He was the
Victory despite the fact that it was nowhere near
So now
At this point in the show
We get into what will be
A massive narrative
Of the show
Right
News about it
This is dealing with the idea that Obama stole money
From Fannie and Freddie
In order to fund Obamacare
There has been
Some new Breaking pieces to the story
How can there be new brick
Pieces to something that is
Absolutely made up
Because our man Jerome corsi has been
Digging
He's been digging into it
This is going to take up a little bit of the rest
Of
Wednesday's episode
It's all bulshit
Right
Fully
You can listen to
Open
Without saying
What do you mean how would you even steal money from Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac
Well it's
It's actually pretty interesting the truth of the situation
And I'll get into it after he establishes his why
I got some other Hillary Clinton
Give us credit
They don't
Courtyard
Here it is
MarketWatch
We broke this
Dismiss bro
First two days ago
Ears. Decourcy article from yesterday
Treasury secretary confirmed infowars.com
On Obama stamps of Fannie and Freddie Mae close to 300 billion
Manchester document said in a release
Obama
Wait
And here's the original article
February 27th
That's two months ago
Exclusive literally Rob
Obamacare
Steve mnuchin clip later
Okay and we'll discuss exactly what that was covering
When he gets to it
Back in February we covered it when the first
It was pitching the
Meredith
Different thing
At that point it was about lawsuit
Government had
Be housing market
Add to the crash in the Bible
There were obvious that none of them wherever public punished
For and we should
A lot of these liberal organizations like
Getting people housing and that sort of thing getting a lot of money out of lawsuit
No
That was broke
In February that was the lie that they spun them
Now there's an entirely different narrative
It's being pitched off that sound but using the same
Bulshit that we talked about then
They just
Repurpose for this new bolts watch Montgomery stuff how they complete
Same Colonel to make a new story once the first one
Bogus right there doing the same thing with Fannie and Freddie
Fitbit deals
Resorts
Like how Roadrunner cartoon
You keep using the same background check
Right
New narrative is that Obama is whole cloth
Stealing from Fannie and Freddie
Are there profit
In order
To prop up Obamacare
And he did this
Because Obamacare was going
Phelan 2012 which that even makes no troops
Also it's based on an interview that Steve mnuchin did
I wish
Maybe we should just go ahead and play that clip from later
Does he have some con
I feel bad talking about it without it but she doesn't get to the actual clip for like 3 hours
Just love that Obamacare is going to fail narrative or it's like it's going to fail
Wait are you saying is going to fail because
You're going to
To defund it
Forcing it to fail
Yeah
You know if you guys
Works on is a fret you guys could work on it like you could make it
Little bit later
Yeah
That's why I was just pushing towards the next clip
My agreement with your rage
Fitbit 2
Like what
Further down the road
GM's up playing the music
Does not say what you think
On Fox Business
Obamacare
In the second year of the program before was even implemented fully here it is
Twitter and it has been for a long time
Oh I understand
Infowars.com
I don't know Alex is as
Strategic Reserve cut off
So here there was a more interesting line of questioning Those About to follow that we bail.
Yeah I found some good resources
That indicates that they're not saying what Alex
They're saying but just because it's so much more fun this way
I found
Breitbart telling them they're wrong
So you you looked for the batard they made upon which to hoist
All of this stuff is backed up by other non Breitbart sources but just because I want
Only use their weapon against them and they all right I'm going to quote entirely from Bart about how this is
Wrong
So
About that clip and Alex Jones is believed that this proves that Fannie and Freddie
Money was
Obamacare
The confusion appears to have Arisen because of the way Bartolo Romo where did your question that was the interview
Treasury
The treasury put out a statement Wednesday however that makes clear that mnuchin's answer was not meant to
Confirm any particular connect
In between Obamacare
And the profits of Fannie and Freddie
Because money is fungible
Which means
They can be moved around
Here's the same as $1 there that's all
Demon dollars
Dollars
Yeah it is all money coming in be used in different
You can use it
To pay for a different thing treasuries receipts of those profits fund everything the federal government does
From border patrol
Military operation
The National Endowment for the Arts in public
So
Basically what that is
What that is explaining is that the money that comes in from Fannie and Freddie because of a settlement
And because of the relationship
But ended up having
What happened in 2008
Government and it's just money that the
Uses the funded
Mercy
Postal Service
No but the Postal Service doesn't make money
In the past
So the postal service has many times
Surplus
Okay
Like
Chesapeake
Come
More Postal Service like it was used to pay for all the brick has posted a surplus in the past when the baby
Boomers were
Do out numbering the their parents
Like they kept putting it into other stuff
Money that comes into the government is
Put out into the things that the government does
Now let me read
Let me read
Description
Again from Breitbart
Of what happen
The companies were taken over by the US government 2008 when officials feared their collapse could further destabilize the housing and fine
Financial Market
Treasury provided hundreds of billions of dollars of fun
Meanwhile the federal housing
Finance
The fhfa
Became their conservator
Under the original agreement with the US Treasury both companies were supposed to pay a dividend equal to 10% of their taxpayer-funded
As well as a fee on the hundreds of billions more
The treasury had pledged
Freetress
For years however neither company earned enough to pay the dividend
Which force them to draw even
More from their bailout fund
Just to send the money back
To Treasury
I was at the dividend
This circular draw as it came to be called
Threatened
To put the companies
Slowly eating away at the remainder of the
The treasury back
In mid-2012
Treasury and the fhfa
Agreed to change
The terms of the bailout
So that Fanny and Freddy would no longer have
The fix dividend
Ending the need for circular drawers
Instead it company would have a flexible dividend obligation
That would rise and fall with their profits
Because the new dividend is equal to
To the positive net worth
Of each company
Small Capital cushion set
The decline each year
It's known as quote the net worth
At the time the net worth sweep was implemented Treasury Department officials noted that in addition to ending the circular drawers
The arrangement would facilitate the eventual wind-down of the companies by
By preventing them
Abusing Prophets
Recapitalise policymakers design to save
More stable mortgage Finance system
Do you mean very similar to what is going wrong with the Grease 2
Sure
Morgan Morgan
Finance reform legislation
Capitol Hill
Instead they remain.
Conservatorship
Supported by taxpayer backing for more than eight
A situation that nearly everyone involved in mortgage
Good Finance reform
Regardless
Undesirable
So we're in a situation
Where
Because of
How bad things got and how bad it could have gotten
If we didn't
Make a chain
Ram 2000 12
Situation where
Fannie and Freddie Gibbs the f****** government
Billions of dollars
200 billions of dollars a year
Out of their profits
In order to
To sustain themselves based on the bailout that was made in 2008
This story that they're claiming
Is some kind of
Is that money comes back to the government
Some of it probably did go to Obamacare
Yeah cuz you got to pay for that song
Well that money is
It's fungal ball
Well no not just that
The money that's coming back to the government
Is the money we gave
Yeah
If the loan
We didn't give them
I mean it's supposed to be alone
We gave them a great interest rates
Interest rate one that you could
Could say was
Possibly
Yeah that's how money
This is Jerome course he's reporting
Busted by
Breitbart
How f*****-up is that
How f***** up is that
Breitbart
Of all places it pointing out
The Infowars is making a conspiracy theory
Breitbart
Hello this is Keith Banning
Shut up I realized
No I don't know what it is you know what I wanted to go against
Type with Steve Bannon
Men's physique
So I went with that
But I realized I've never heard him talk
I don't think
Overheard him talking. Orson Welles
Dead yet so anyway
This is
Bulshit
Yeah this whole story is complete b*******
If you look into it a tiny bit
And there is that kernel of truth that we talked about on the 25th he's not as explicit about the car
Kernel of truth anymore
Sound even worse
Yeah or even scarier but he doesn't
What do you mean I mean we're still taking them
Like
They're still taking that money
And they're using it to pay for
And there's no end in sight
There's this
Will be Assisted Living place
Until this
But that wine.
And it's not it's not
Thank God it's not
Play worse shape if
If the
You know the government stopped
Yeah
It's not it's not an ideal situation to be in
But the alternative is still much worse
Much like we talked about with Tetris last night
It's a situation where you have to accept a negative outcome sometimes
These were just completely independent
Huge housing loan
Loaning businesses
Bratz
Watch people suck that up
And now we can't have nice things on the list of our problem
So he's going to get back to this narrative a bit and he's going to bring in Jerome corsi
To lie a bunch of
Before we do
I want tickets back
To the other day
We were talking about
Outed
Donald Trump's son
Cernovich
I think
Got intense
Blowback
You mean like
Keep f****** should have
I think he probably got
Much like the elephanta feet
Female bladder
I think crnkovich probably like a man
You can't do that fit
Cancel it
I don't know how to fake a list
Mike Tyson
I'm going to eat your heart
A ferocious
I love pigeon
My defense is impregnable
I'm just ferocious
That was that was
There's nobody said before a fight
Yeah
That sounds well let's not go that far
In terms of like
Hyping yourself up for about I'm going to eat your children
Right I mean music convicted rapist
But I mean
In terms of prefer
4 minutes so
Anyway this next
Eazy-E talks about cernovich
And the Soros group put out its articles
Come together
You do
Don JR says he should be
So before we get to his actual like walking back his cernovich
Paul Joseph Watson
In the past has been documented as basin
Stories on Anonymous direct messages on Twitter
B roll
Surprised
In the past
Jerome corsi
Has
Publish multiple book
I'm sure they end up as best sellers
But have been shown
Completely made up
Based on
Terrible sourcing
Multiple books
About Obama's birth certificate being fake
And what about John Kerry it is with
So like
Those are not surprised
Alex
They are not
If any of them win a Pulitzer Prize
For real-time to do
Just pack up and suck a muffler at that point
I'm resisting the call of the woods almost every
I got it
Define
Every every generation
Regeneration
Like it like
Very similar stuff happened in 1960
So what's going on right now
It's just more
That wasn't quite the last generation
Closest corollary to our time is it in the last days
Nixon
Whenever we had all of the Vietnam War protests
We had so many people be
Beat
For protest
We had all this
Sure president was
Is blatantly corrupt
Committee
The template for what's going to happen
Exactly right
Which arrives that
So I keep thinking you know what
Maybe we are over at overreacting
Maybe are in
Oceans are strong enough to protect us
Second that
Just f****** driving
And just hoping that I get to the woods far enough away where it's like
Number one if it up and come pick me up
True thoughts generator
That's fine
I have an ID
Solar
Exactly
Thoughts about your idea about generational
Yes
I'm not sure if we survived
The 70s
I'm just not sure that the right outcome necessarily happen
I think that it got to a boiling point
And then things got drawn back
As opposed to being pushed over the edge
We could have gone a lot farther
Assuring
Progressive
Movement as opposed to going back
I don't think that
Here's what I'm saying I don't think that is a demonstration
Strength of our system
Or anything like that
Institution
Degenerates
Always feel the things are falling apart
Every generation has that kind of narcissist
The last
Right
People
Should have some insight
Do that be like well maybe it's not
But at the same time
Eventually one of those Generations
Inevitable
Our American history has never been the same sense
Almost everything that's happened since then has been a backlash
Almost all of the conservative values
And all of the
Conservative s*** that goes on
Is indirect
Response to that
The fear that they have
That they sell
The colonels of the hippy chick
It still exists
In terms of homosexuality drug use
Fringearts
Stuff like that he's the stuff that they
Use as Boogeyman
And to be like
That's not American values
Blah blah blah
Communal living is b*******
The Civil War
Never end
Sure cuz we've been fighting the Civil War
No worries ever end
Think about it
Civil War hasn't ended
Literally the Korean War hasn't did according to
North Korean
B
Yeah B WWII hasn't ended we still have Nazis around
All of this and I wake up some days and afraid of nothing
All this is still going on it's not done in the
The same way though because we never
Finish the deal.
We have blue balls
All we have to attend Alec Baldwin speech
Brought over tons of Nazis because we knew that they had braid expert
Even certain areas
Big because we never really finish any
Anything we leave it open in our chicken
Are all here
They're all here
In no uncertain terms
You're looking for a final.
I'm not
How do you
Finished
Like if you're if you're
Progressive
How do we win
There's no win
Well here's the only going to
Create
More of this backlash
Say just in the case of World War II
It's b******* because I do also recognize
The pieces of our culture that have advanced be
Because of nausea
Moon
There's a lot of stuff that we have benefited from because of them but I'll World wouldn't be the same
We didn't forgive some of them because of their genius
You don't you don't make peace with your friends
Right
In a perfect world I think what you would have done is all the people who were responsible for the atrocities
People who work directly the one
Being like
Gas Em Up
Yeah those
You would kill all the
You have trial for them
And you would summarily execute all of them
But then
The people who were still sort of under the sway of the ideology you do everything you could do
To re-educate
And not like a brainwashing
Brainwashing however it is
It would be a process
You know I'm not saying put them in a camp and D brainwash them
But like
Provide
I'm not
Internment
Concentration
Provide provide people who are under negative sway with the information
Send with the reality of like these dudes are not your enemies
This Nazi ideology is something you got
Swept up into
And and just
Deconstruct
Every
Part of the ideology and
But like it's the same way with the truck and it's the same thing
Time and if someone actually believe him or likes him
It's not going to help
I think that's
Different isotopes differ
Confirm my
Argument based on which
You said is that it's very similar to
To the way that we
Deal with the drug
In that rather than
Creating the city
Situations 2
Deescalate
+ 2
Educate
Avoid using the word
Re-educate
Rather than using those
We go for the punishment
Like with the drug war
What we should be doing is building more rehab
We are doing is building more prisons
Snowy is it should be a two prong Things Are
Bmore rehab
I am van
More oversight
Doctors who are really Lucifer
And those are the things that are going to go away because
Trumps
In the Philippines is doing great things about drugs
Where he just
Kills drug users is a literal
Murderer murderer
Murder president of the Philippines
Has said in public
I have
Kill the man was at least
He said he's murdered people
That's some real dick
Was invited to the White House
That's that's one of those hypocrisies
Look how many times have we had
Doughty leaders
Sure how many times
What is
Dumb face
Has a picture with him shaking hands with
Saddam Hussein
The lobster
F******
That's toast
Brooklyn Bridge Park
The point there is that
We we spot off of it but I agree with you
In that
It is
I don't I don't quite know where
Your argument
Because you're your point to the WWII
Kill the people
No kill kill someone
Like I don't think
The executions of Nazis that we did do
For wrong
No
Outcomes were wrong necessarily
I think a lot of people have to die
Because of the thing
Having a lot of
People died big
I think a lot more people
Should be executed
Because of crimes
Against Humanity even people
On our side
In the history of the world
But I'm saying that Rumsfeld we never do
Second Clinton
Like I'm not it's not it's not right left how many civilians has Obama
In the Iraq War we killed more civilians in rehab
Much is he is a a politician in art world
Goodwill
Yeah I think
And did a lot of berries
You can't take away the war crime
He's every single one of them
My foot my further point is we never do a good enough job
Dealing with the people who are
Bhldn two-
Belief system
Yeah is that is super Danger
In the wet in the same way that we never really dealt with Nazis
American Nazis
During World War II
And it led
Two people going underground in creating Network
And now
Neo-nazism popped up and now it's being funneled into
Semitism was
A hugely popular thing in the United States in the late twenties and thirties
One of the people one of the big Boogeyman for our the Great Depression
Juice
Thanks
Things that is very important to remember is Hitler
We would be on his side because a lot of his ideas work
Cribs from American intellectual
If you knew that there were a ton of
Weird Networks
America
That just to put a button on my .38
So we can get moving
I just
I haven't been on I wasn't on last rhinos
If you want the day before 4 hours ago
But my point is
When
These
Harmful ideologies pop-up
Is a harmful ideology
There's no there's no location on map
Has existed
That there is
When you talk about small government
Talk about States
Right about a lot of things
You have a very
You can have a robust argument
There you can have
People on the other side that Believers thing
Edit
When when I talk about harmful ideology
I'm talking about
I mean now it's definitely the alright
They're going to
Need to be
Corrected
In the future
Militant liberal friends
I don't think they have any of those
I don't think there are any
In the past there were.
There were
Other groups
That were in that
And I'm into Atherton
The Alex Jones
People want to come down on me
I would say exactly the same is true
People in al-Qaeda
Or people in Isis
People who are
Militant religious
Then
Exactly
Those folks who have
The mentality is that we need to
The busts
In terms of like
To get them in
And kill them all or we need to
Brainwash them into our liberal way of thinking when they land
All I care is they don't have a worldview that's based on bigotry
Image-based
Not in fact
Like those are the parts of it that are really troubling
The Nazis were not operating on a fact-based system
Everything that was going on.
The probe Vietnam
Folk in the 60
We're operating on a very
Non fact-based
Now the hippies were too
Also a lot of
Turn on fact we're about
Aquaria
Therap
Dependability of free love
Curology
Virology is our way out of it right that's not harmful
Non fact-based sister
I think they system it only leads
Do you f****** more people and buying a crystal
That's not really nigguh
I think I think you've stumbled onto what
I would say like
The way that the way that you put it
Kind of click something
My Philosophy
No here's here's what I would
Based on what you
You just said I had
A little a little brain clip
It is not
Progressive
Conservative
Liberal
Right now our fundamental
Differences
AR
Reality
Yeah one side
One side is delusional Democrats and liberals all over the
Besides our
Reality versus non real
That's what we are really that's why
These Warriors have been
Finished no because we're not we're not we're not fighting the right War
You and I are fighting distract
Conservatism or liberalism or progressivism or anything like that
We're fighting a war with a man who is
Creating reality
Reality the same time because I don't want to appeal the curtain back too far but like
One of the reasons that I feel
So convicted in my
Fighting Alex Jones on his non reality-based system
I'm right
Good dogs
The reason is because
Like it wasn't a buzzfeed article and I couldn't
Talking think
I could not
Think that Accord is more accurate
He is a girdles of 20
Absolutely
Not about
Russia Taking Over America
It's not anything
Alex Jones
Is
Propaganda
Of the American win
Of a very dangerous Global movement
It's happening right
And it's going to continue
And it's not like you said
Liberal
Republican
Conservative it's not about any of that
Anyway
We got too far down the rabbit hole with guitar
Let's finish this clip we're in the middle of I don't know
Richest sources
And that
He's right source of info on what he says
He is not Services stores I have to do one of the sources he hasn't in the White House at 6.
Information night
Is the two obviously
It's probably
And so they give it to the big evil Alex Jones
Evil doctor
He's got three number one New York Times bestseller
Yeah that's not a credit
His propaganda is effective
John Junior wasn't
Like with this new story the one about Fannie and Freddie
He's like that's not our
Our sources
Treasury
Right every single thing
Throughout the entire course of this
Is based on that tiny clip
It being interviewed by Maria Bartiromo
I'm not sure I'm saying her name right
You know what I say
Let me confirm
I want
No no it's a Bartiromo
Play
What are the characters in a comedy Bang Bang ongoing storyline
I was complaining it with one of the assassins
Creed characters
Bartolo Romeo
I was I was complaining it with pitcher Bartolo Colon
Coloma
It smelled like Cohen
Anyways
Complaining complaining it with Bartolo some Sonu
Because our dumbass Marathon we are
Like his big thing that he wanted to talk about
Fannie and Freddie
It's completely
Compass bumper
It's just nonsense
It's b******* it's no good
But it's going
To be the new Naruto
If I started to try as I listened to the show
What are the things I'm trying to do is contextualize what he's saying
Yeah cuz every
Throws up so much b*******
I'm like
Is this going to be at a varsity
The storyline is this going to be a Jay-Z storyline or is it going to be a waypoint
You know what
Editori working as his editor at the same time
Yeah you would be the guy going through it like no this is your real a story besides characters
This is going to be I think one of his really Maynard
And yet because he's going back to it from two months ago
He thinks that enough time has passed
But no one remembers
The b*******
He's probably right except for us cuz we're walks
I think he's going to
To try and use the
Credibility really reinforced
Because the Google story is sort of falling apart
They're going to do list
Waypoint
No there's no wait
Right now I think the varsity storyline
Are going to be
This
And
Framing a Hamdi ulukaya
As a member of the Federal Reserve
I like this angle
Freddie Mae and Freddie Mac
Freddy Freddy Freddy
Because
It is concurrent with the Obamacare repeal
So your narrative
Just kind of slides in with the main
Screen GOP is failing
And then you come in on your back
And thanks
The reason
Failing is
As they were
Stealing money
From these p
Americana
Is not going to
I do that
That is
I think you're right that is
Accidental but I also think
That's one of the big reasons that has considering like this before
Before we even knew the boat was going to go down
Considering
Even before the vote
I mean we'll see how it plays out
Right now you listen to
I want you to know something very strongly of migraine
The point
But you know what
You know what
Know what
Don't stop f****** life
Serious business
You know why
Alex Jones
We need to expect
We need to respect that and I wish
Press play
I need you to escape from this character playing right now
One day there'll be a way for me to start playing clit with my brain
But for now I have to get out of here to press the button
So what'll happen if you should just get a lapel mic that's real situation there
Bi Rapaport
The report set
Donate to the show
Forever
The one on billion dollars
Infowars is right
Horses
Trump
Make some reliable
New York
And I've Been Told.
Getting into Fannie Mae Freddie Mac
The Muslims
Liar
Call far you'll be destroyed
It sucks there I want to actually roll this back
Because like I kept in a super long break
At the end
It just wasn't
Hilarious
Stop
The Muslims back off
I just love that
No way
Not not a fan
Mnuchin is not an easier name
No not at all
Can pronounce mnuchin
Prickly everytime. Everytime
He's he's done enough that it is very obvious
Is mispronouncing a little guy's name on purpose
And he keeps calling him
Just to just to recap by member of the Federal Reserve
Not he's the guy who he slandered
It's not on the board of the Federal Reserve
Every committee guy
In the upstate New York area
Total War
So
You know he's been threatened
Turtle dovin to
Turning on Trump a little bit
As beginning he was
Sandy's
Very 70% now
The video game
But really close to saying
When you look in the abyss the abyss look back
Look back
Shakespeare
Great America
Don't Give me liberty or give me death
Makes super confusing
Obstacle
Sometimes
Will Shakespeare
I just love Trump economy of Americana and
Bringing jobs back and I just get chill
It makes it worse
About somebody
People aren't doing what he says that's been
Because they just weren't letting the government moves
Dealing with
Stop he can't deliver
Yeah you are
So like this is the way that when
You are
Dumbass
Sleater-kinney
You're proposing things
To go against
Some of our most basic American values
But yet you have
All three branches
Is the government locked up and now the Supreme Court
And yet you can't get s*** done this is the way you pitched the narrative
That like
This is why
Right cuz there's globalist behind the scenes
It's the cult leader it's the cult leader predicting Doomsday
So then
It's
I made a mistake
Shred-it doomsday is 2 years
I missed
The two in the
Exactly
Sorry scripture is Caustic decode I have a broad stroke
Right but the details
The devil is in the details in this situation is coming to
2 years from now not today
You know Trump is going off the rails
Become a globalist
Is like
I love this guy
And now
He's the alpha
Email
He's the alpha male who can do anything
Always
Everybody else's
Whippet chicken never hold the person
But that and Alex
Also
Cuts into his
Entire narrative
Because he
He's done so much
Groundwork
And laying
Trump is a singular man
The globalist so if he
He starts to get corrupted
What is the idea that
The finger man isn't enough
Yeah
I mean what you would do is you would go
Straight towards
Because it sure seems like Putin is a singular man enough to do this s***
Right
That maybe what happened maybe
God dammit
Imagine that imagine if
Alex Jones switches to like
Well it's Putin the whole time
He's already had
Alexander Dugan.
And he's been on RT like
He's he's
Got the groundwork laid for being like
The only real anti globalist is
So this next clip Alex Jones is trying to read
Frame Trump like inasmuch as
He's turning against him
He's trying to reform him
Is my ear can tell in this clip
He's trying to frame him as
A tolerant immigration reform
But it did
Yeah it doesn't it does not pass me by
Was always
Immigration
For single moms but we killed half our kids in this country
Population
We're
So
Just a lot of Christians
Did you see the
That Muslims aren't allowed in the country.
Soccer
Ridiculous agree with that last point that is
Like if you want to put Wikileaks on trial you will end up on
Now is very much like
We're deciding who can and who can't
Be called news
Yeah
Cuz of that very same thing
Like if you are advocating that and your ally
Text Joan
Imagine what happened
If you are
Alex Jones and it's a
Liberal progressed
Politician
Like you're fake news
You're the problem
Could very legitimate
That idea of of trump
Immigration
Stuff is just
Bulshit revision
Revisionist history from a month ago
Yeah
Meanwhile Alex.
Keeps harping on like the idea that like
The problem is no one has a memory
Yeah you don't
You don't remember what you said
GOP person now who says like
Oh what are liberals protest
Sing about you know
Whatever Obama was President we never did that
Obama in effigy
Now I want I want to say
In terms of validating
Isaac
Complaining
Protest when Obama
Came into office
Personally maybe they did
Maybe they were tolerant
And God bless them for it
Projecting that to the
Society is not okay
Because
When Obama was elected
Ever been to a gun show
No I have
Please don't
Tell me anymore
Asterisk
Kill me before Obama was elected
Frequently at gun shows that I have been to
Blowgun
Because I wanted to
Shoot paintballs at my friend
I think I also bought like some sort of a
Stun gun
Tell me my friends good
Chucky's daughter while we were drunk
Great
It was full of Obama
At Target and then also weird posters of Obama
Photoshopped Obama into
Like weird old
Insulting racist
Tribal pictures
I don't know like
It doesn't work
Big picture
But those people individually might be okay told me this whole thing about how we win
Mama was elected everybody hope
You would do well
And she absolutely did not remember all the races schicchi
Herself set
Emailed me
Like so it's so f*** you
Do mammary like
Genuinely
There there wasn't narrative during the Trump campaign
There was part of people were like
You know Trump is lying
You know he's lying
So maybe he's lying in a good way
Play baby when he does get elected
He's going to go
Too bad
Was pro-lgbt
He's never believed
He's just a f****** opportunist believes in his own brand being pushed in his family make more
There's that there was that liberal narrative
Well you know what if he enriches himself but we also get single-payer healthcare
Looking great
The problem is he was lying to everybody in the deal with the devil never works
Butthole has interest
Whenever he was whenever he was elected and on that
Inauguration Day
New s*** was going to go bad
Sure just because of that that didn't mean that I didn't
Like I'm like
Imagine if
Pretty good okay dude
Could have happened conceivably he doesn't believe in anything
Maybe we find out that he just gives a s*** about
Do whatever he wants to do
You know it's possible like I genuinely hope the president succeed
The problem I have is that there's no possibility of that
He's a monster and he's trying to f*** himself using the Republican Congress
Traffic monsters
Well the problem 2 is that
Well the problem is it like
The world is so complicated
And we're deeply entrenched
In such a weird situation
Like even the best person
Comfortable coming into office
Will inevitably do
Monster is just based on the last
The Transit Avenue gotten us in a position where you can't extricate yourself
Some situations where you're going to
Do end up murdering
Now it's just an Obama Obama if
He was not
Faced with those
Decisions
Wood
Like right now
If you were talking to Obama
From 20 years ago
NSAID okay
Would you ever kill
Nothing
Not a problem
He would absolutely like if you ask me
Of course not
I would never ever
Miraculous ability
And then you get into that political
Your entire life
I could be
Batter up
So you have to
My party your lesser of two evils
Is killing
Still going to do some
Really bad stuff
And then when you get a corner
Uno
A fuk note
The cat
So
It's not gone well
But
A office pool in my head because there is no
Where I live
Like this for me is
Which
Doomsday scenario is going to win out
You're really going to do cuz you know that
Edgewater
How to start a war with each other
Or is it going to be any number of different possible doomsday scenarios and I feel like
Likely
Yep
You know
I do
So Jordan you might be asking
What would I be at
You might be asking why the f***
Are they doing the 30-hour
Marathon route
I knew the answer to that question
I've never asked myself
Less of a question than that
Possibly a different name
Then
The truth
Jerome corsi
Here in just a moment before I do that
We have kicked off
Mobile broadcast
Tomorrow
They're 41 minutes into their Marathon we are at two and a half hours
Recover that BuzzFeed article for like half an hour
F*** you voice in my head
Lester's online email on Facebook
At the grocery store
At the golf course
Globalism destroy Alex Chao
Tell the truth
How fun would that conversation be
At the store
It can be 11
8 look
Globalism is on the rise
Ugh
Starting to play with
Dollar bill or okay I'm
Backed I'm going to pay with fiat currency
This is distributed by the Federal Reserve Bank suing Alex
Fear ID
But if used by the globalist
Code not scan that I am a sovereign citizen
Alright we're getting to that
You see news we broke
A week before a month before a year before
CVS Wall Street Journal
You generally do the news that they've broken a little bit later I wonder why
Cuz it debunked could you give me contacts for a lot of times you'll feel like
Oh.
A lot of weirdos
Islam in the world and they they dig into stuff in to find out
Oh no
Come true at all ever fact-checked
Before
Alex Jones
Afterwards
Yeah it's it's
It's a really fun game to see if you could
If you could predict
The Narrative that they would spin
Based on
Wild while you're saying
Write a story give me a fake story I'll give you the Alex Jones
A fake story with Alex Jones Menorah real story that
You give me a fake
Real story
You give me
Do you give me just like a world news story and I'll transmit Alex Jones
Alright
Kids
Religious-based attack in
That's so fucken easy
What is it just doing this
Somalia has been placed with Black Hawk Down controls we all know that
Absolutely
I know this to go back to Barry Goldwater it's in a white paper
We all know this
Are these kids
They're part of a globalist Hillary Clinton
Saul Alinsky base
Are the kids even real but they're in a sex-trafficking operation we all know that
It's in that white papers you check out
Hillary Clinton's connection to Haiti at all in there
They are real they are real it is very unfortunate
And I've already forgotten what the actual story
You got Alex Jones here's my ears my ears are my dream Heroes
Each other now about your fake
Real world new story
What I heard when you were telling me that story that you were fake
What I heard
Was the country Somalia
Various things through history I heard there were kids involved
Kid trafficking
But Alex wants to promote or as a narrative
The little things
She does
Made
Now
Remember what you say
Like
I guess I guess dream would be like imagine
Instead of giving people that headline
You give them the headline
With every
Information you needed
Like the headline to that is
Radical sect of American influence Christians
Murder children because they have
The lgbtq tendencies that they've showed
They were very young
The angle that alt right people would take on this story
Is that it is this kind of globalist
Conspiracy
But instead it is not it is
Purely religious Bass
Christian ideology that
Has been twisted and warped
Now that's the headline
I do Alex Jones
I can't really sign off on this cuz
I'm still thinking about those poor kids in Somalia
Does kids
There's always
Somalia
Good morning
Word
Forward
Loading up the 300 billion dollars
Lose
Didn't publish
Athletic Club
Exactly as we said
Infowars getting credit
They didn't say that at all
Super fun and it was sort of a call back to things that
Keep happening
Entire clip Jerome corsi was on Skype Style
Being complimented by Alex
If you want to talk
We'll get there in a minute
A fish person at the side of the page with human terror Terror
So I mean
The implicit
He's also got some nice Twitter action like to give a shout out to our friends
A name
Who posted a picture of a mythological chimera
Realize that was the nope
Are you with the idea of a chimera was but I didn't realize the mythical creature
3 heads
B body
Dragon tail
Yes
One of the most important things
That you need to know
Is that the reason
The people
And the mainstream media
Attacking
Infowars
To know I need to know
I think Alex
Summer up Beth
I mean I have my ideas but
Here's Alex is David
Spell regular
It's so fun because Jerome corsi is on Skype
He's just like
Violinist bloated face Jerome corsi
But that's the problem there is that if you put if you put
In there I'm like
Yeah I am scared of that
Bloated ass ugly
Play motherfuker is running everybody don't know but that the b******* is I'm scared of Jerome corsi to I'm scared
The world
Isn't there not paying attention
I'm scared of
This trend
Did Infowars is a big part of paper
I'm going to f*** around and right away paper
That's code for
You f***** around and got a triple-double I'm going to write a white book
How would you feel if somebody wrote a black book huh
There's a great show that got bought by comedy
Yes during the Dylan Morin
Who we saw together who you thought was s***
He was alright
I don't just
It was it was it wasn't
Babies are upset
Jerome corsi might
Hot in Here I Go
Actually I just remembered
He dumb
They're scared of them
Because we are a focal point
20 minutes
Especially
Mukbang basically Delta donate
Good morning
Illegal
Register to pay for legal of him saying like what he said right before that
Research paper fact checker
You have someone who's like
Tries to tell you
This will get you sued
Their radar is
So I mean like there's no way
Legitimately
I took
An hour of my day
Working on this Fanny Friday
Yes and I found
A bunch of documents
I found a bunch of stories
That were wellsource
About
How dare
Interpretation their version of it is wrong
Then I found a Breitbart story
Specifically
Was about how Infowars is wrong
That's
Shwayze
To imagine the world fired is there fact check
Selfie
Imagine a world where Breitbart has more editorial credibility
Emphatically more
Credibility
Breitbart
In terms of the narrative APUSH
To agree with Alex Jones a hundred percent of course that is a step too far even for them
Which I think is why Alex is selling it as they told me
Because that story from Breitbart came out before this broadcast
So I think that it's like
He's trying to sell the like even the right of turned against us on there yeah which is good for him
Cuz if he's eventually going to turn it in
Then that's a great angle to start even break
Are now wings of Troy
Yeah like if you start distance
Yourself from Trump then you have to
Start disting
Yourself from
Probably because
You understand
In a very literal
Has sex
With dban
We talk all the way
All the way
Gonzo's nose but right up his ass I think you're actually wrong because in these earlier Clips he's been
Talking about how
The turn came
When Trump
Took van in office
Security Council
About how like
Open till
71 days or whatever
Geology and then that went away
Turn the light yeah I think he's still on Bannon
Okay like I don't
I'm not sure what the disconnect from
Breitbart
I have to be in order for him
Who cares
I'm not going to war games this for him be that he is
F****** riffing
And anything goes while he's
Randomly talking
I think the bottom line is that
He's acting like
Our 30
Of this telephone
After
Turdly long
Just on Skype
She finally lets Jerome corsi talk
Aaron play this play
4C is going to lay out
His sort of
Version of what
Pistorius
Bat Cleanup in case there's any
There we haven't gone over
This is hard news this is hard power structure
And this is why the Republican establishment is out to get us as well because they're part of it
Broken
What our trip is going to story we've been working on because it's
Yeah we found out that
Fannie and Freddie the two mortgage Giants government-sponsored entities
August 2012
All the profits from Fannie and Freddie
And confiscating them
Call the net worth sweep
It's complicated
Congress the house specifically had refused
The fund
The
Insurance
Premiums the subsidies for low-income
Wasn't going to work
What the
Into paying the Obamacare
Insurance subsidy they gave you and using paper
How's the money
Be able to pay the insurance company
Deputies ascribe
That nefariousness to the wrong Source Republicans refused
To do the thing that they were supposed to
Just a reminder cuz we talked about this like an hour and a half ago
Even for the listeners I want it
I want to point out that you talkin about
Is the thing called the net worth
Sweep and
Started in 2012
He said those things Jerome corsi said those things explain that to you
Read this paragraph
A little bit ago
In mid-2012 treasury in the fhfa agreed to change
Dividend
Ending the need for circular drawers
Instead
Each company whatever
The flexible dividend
Obligation
That would rise and fall with their profit
Because the new dividend
Is equal to the positive net worth of each company
Lhasa capital
Set to decline each year
It is known as the net worths
The net worths
Is
Sweeping up
Part of their net worth
Based on
How much they make each year
It's not anything nefarious
Eating order to make sure these companies
Don't
End up
Droid
By their repayment to the government
Like like
It's how Fox and NBC in the likeness
Their highest rating
That's a fun, I enjoy the work
Say you enjoy it with that
I enjoy it
I failed I need I need come I like I need to
Constructive feedback as much as anybody else Charlie
I like puns
Look
I'm a lot like Alex Jones
In which I am willing to admit when I am wrong
And I will retract
I am going to tell you I'm going to give you the
Most generous birth
I'm going to let you have a lot of baby
Because that clip was
So boring
It was so boring Jerome corsi
Can't do it
How is he part of this
He's worse than David.
These people are so bad
Because his name rings out in races
People really liked the idea that he was all neighbor
Who loved his work in this way
With boat like that
They love Jerome corsi
He held your work a 25
He has credibility
He has b******* liar
Credibility
A show every transition 2/3
Copper dalada
We already talked about a lot of the BuzzFeed coverage and I picked up a lot of Thursday
I have
Cut a number of clips
That are just good clean fun
Thursday I wish that he'd stayed up all night and really been involved
He went to bed
Same time
There's some really
Really dumb s***
So why do they want to the stories he's telling is about
Doesn't even matter
It doesn't even matter
Is a tertiary piece of news one of the stories he's telling is about
Enter Alex Jones story right here David Rockefeller who is dead
Naturally what he's up to beyond the grave
I'm still pretty pissed off at Janet Reno why not
I cut out a lot of that
There aren't a lot of ideas because he thinks they come through like German Transylvania
M stock
They are Leo
That means
That there
First of all vampires
Little different but Illuminati stuff Illuminati
It's insane
No
Walk back that
The Bavarian Illuminati
That's two words right next to each other that will always be
I love the variant
I love Illuminati
Open off
Here's the first clip I'm going to play from the Thursday show
Joulumaa francophone
Zapata
Yes you do like
I love French
You don't really
I do I do
It took many years
The French in high school
Conversant
Fluent
I understand if you ask me
To speak back to you
Nah
J'adore le francais
I do I will never be able to
To get
Phrase
The French
Archie's eating
Surrender monkeys
It will never Escape my brain good turn of phrase don't believe
I don't believe any of it and if
Historically the French of one far more victories in battles and all that s*** but goddamnit if
Cheese-eating surrender mug
Well at this point the French elections still has not happened
This it probably will have
But try we are we are we are prior to what could be the end of the year
And the world but we're both
Firmly on the side of macron
As opposed to the alternative
I'm not I'm not super in his camp but the alternative is a disaster
Alex Jones is super into lappin
And here is some thoughts about her
Her dad
Oh no not her dad her dad
So she destroys
We're doing the ss70
Paratrooper
Indeed
It's got to be sweet victory
Sweet sweet victory for
Jean-Marie Le Pen
Let me ask you a question
Did he support Vichy France
Let me tell you a little story
I think this is
This is a tiny piece of his troubled history
Jean-Marie Le Pen is
A f****** monster
Listen to this
This is
This is from a nice Guardian article
Admittedly
A tiny piece
Right
Is Monster it
Marine Le Pen
Who took over the party the national front
The front Nacional
Fascist
She took a look alike
They are fashion
Party in 2011
It is running for French press
The next year this is
Public relations
Drive to detoxify the party
And move away from it the jackbooted imagery
Anti-Semitic
Which are
Very real
After gears
With anti-semitic undertow
After years of working alongside her father in April last year
In a total spiral of strategy somewhere between scorched-earth and political suicide
Intern attacked his daughter
Criticism of his gas
A comment
You want to know what those were
You already said
Gas chamber,
If Marie Le Pen
Who sang Jones
Say those gas
I don't need to know what those gas chamber, dar
Because the worst
Is they start with
Good for gas Chambers and it even gets worse from there like that's the best
Scenario he said
Jean-Marie Le Pen the former leader of France's far-right front National
Has once again been convicted of a crime
Paper saying that used to kill Jews in the Holocaust
Detail of History
There we go
No big deals actually not as bad as some other people within the front
Because they are people who say that like
There's no way zyklon-b was
Reviews
Well he was still here
Do the politician
He was a monster but he wasn't going to tell all the
Yeah he was he was the head knot
Some function
You can say that
I'm doing
Jerome corsi
Kia
He interned attacked his daughter's criticisms of his gas chamber, saying quote
You're only betrayed by your own
Then in an interview the same month with the River Roll
Notorious far-right weekly
Jean-Marie Le Pen
Defended Philippe Patek
The leader of France is not
Treason after the war so he's a guy who
Call you knew that
We were getting to
Marine Le Pen
What's a fascist
Father
I knew that
She and her father disowned
Agreed
But from everything that I've read about
Separate
Like whenever she said
He has no strategy
That was the thing that I glommed onto
Yeah because
Estratex
I disagree with him
Doing it
This is unmarketable
Exactly
I don't
I don't disagree with advertising
Two children
Smoking is
I disagree with
How old your advertising to children
Brightly colored
To smoke when I do that again
He did
Globalism
So is a
F****** monster
History
I don't want to take away from whatever
Military service he has I don't know about
Who gives a f*** Zack
He's a month incidental to the fact
The back
He has
Publicly
And very emphatically
Supported
The Nazis
In WWII
The front desk and out is
Apart of that
He was the absolute party for a very Worthy
Is now the leader of it although
Recently she stepped down
After the first part of Eli
The first round down as before
National leader
As a PR move
Because she realized
I can't detoxify yourself
The party
Even though she still believed every single most of it but instead of
Semitism
The big front
Now is anti-islam
Show me the flavors change
The same dish
Basically
I'm glad no racist
Can can grow
That least I can have some evolution
This next clip
Just like
After Islam
I mean there won't be one we'll all be dead
Quest
And again
You think so
I don't know
This is what I keep thinking about like this idea
Cuz there's always going to be another
Like this this is the thing that I keep coming into like
Everyday
Volt range
Through my head are so varied like
Sometimes it's anger
Sometimes it's best Kaiser
What correctly submitted this podcast
One of the one of the things that I keep coming back to and I really can't
Figure it out.
I've sat down
I've been in the bathroom
I've been vacant
Think about like
What what is like
What's the positive end
Cuz with the endgame realistically is probably a map
If you look at the real world
But like if the positive end game that Alex
Seems to be pitching against the globalist
Let's say we take the globalist
Are we then living in a Utopia
What is the what is the world after the global
And I don't
I don't think he has a coherent vision of it
Free market market exist
We're going to end up in the glass ceiling
We're going to end up in the same situation we were in with exploitation
What's an implicit part of
Capitalism
Free capitalist
Well that we thought
Regulate
Can't
Govern without regulation you end up with slavery
That's just how it works can't like even in our own car
Country Within
Very recent memory we had
Child workers in mine
Right because
Industries weren't regulated
That's just kind of how it works
So you get rid of
And then
Nations have sovereignty
But
I don't know if that really gets us to where we want to be
Coherent vision for where they want
They how they don't like me
So things were idyllically better in the past
Things that drives me
Saying about
Labor Day
Is that people
Never celebrate the fact
Thousands of people died
Sherp
For you to work
8 hours away
There
Herter's
Because people wanted to go from
10 hours a day 6 days a week
2/8 hours
The day 5 days
Thousands of
People have died
Their words legit riots
The murders
Absolutely
Governments were overthrown
We've we've destroyed so many things just so labor
Has even the slightest bit of
Control
We reckon
Anyone take it away
Yeah the the argument against
People always come
Anecdotal
Real stories
And I had to wait like
The week for this guy
Does using a union
Brightright
These lazy Union guys
Argument
And I was trying it like I told my dad I was like
Yeah
You
Stand though
That those guys
Those very same guy
Died
And even though you're not in the
Union
You been
Only work 8 hours a day
They are always
He's fighting against
You
You just don't know you're always
Fighting against
Well yeah that's that's
Basically the reality of the world is that
Like the river fight
Fight happened in the past
To create systems where people can survive
Time goes on
Forget about the fight
And you forget
The fight led to the current state.
That were in are you started
Become complacent
Right
It's just b*******
As is happening now
And that's going
To keep happening all that she's going to get rolled back and we're going to realize we need
Need to fight again
We just should have never let it go away
The rich are
Always
He's fighting again
And we're only fighting again
When we get put
Right
They are always like even there are raised their tax rate up to 90
Percent
No one speaks
Yeah no one ever thought that it was that high there like
The rich should be taxed at a progressive tax rate nobody's like well after
F****** the Great Depression
90%
It is
It is never
Talked about
That even from that
F****** day
They were already working
Under my nuts
Scores from
Day one they have
Always been fighting
Don't win because we're not always fighting
It's,
But
Jordan
Let's let's have some fun
Let's have some fun
Clip is
Fun
It's I'm excited now
Weird
It's one of those
When I heard this I was like
Cuz it kind of Entry
Response
Do
Stephen Colbert talking about
But boy
Cock holster that sort of stuff
It's also sort of in response to these ideas that his anti
Adam Schiff
Was homophobic
He's kind of parceling all that together
Write this
This is
So
F****** we
So weird
And
I just don't know what to say Beyond it's weird
Putin's but boy
Budget mean you're bashing
Gay people
Universal you're on bottom is what that means
Liberal Society
What
Okay
Gay harassment
Liberal establishment Hollywood
But the liberal
I think he recently just learned about RuPaul's Drag Race
Or something like that something popped up on his gebo and he was like
Oh my God
Queer eye for the
The Straight Guy
The straight
I don't know and we're not nearly done with this business.
Done with gay harassment
It's so obvious what he's talking about
The term gay harassment
Harkins into your mind
Or home Erasmus
You would think
It would be legitimate
It is like it
I was at a bar and it came up and grab my balls and was like
You like this
That's right
If gay dude treated you like many straight dudes treat women have nothing to do
Do with your gender
Maybe what you talked about it
It's not what he's talking about
The societal idea that people force you to
Except
Dave Chappelle
Or whatever
And he's going to speak more on it and it's
F****** weird
It's so weird
I don't understand how someone can
Feel victimized
By someone else's
Expression of the
But Alex
Does
I like I said
Describe it other than weird
Cuz it's not really bigger than it is
But if that's not
It's more confused
Bigoted is
You know what your
Do a situation he's like somebody who's by
I don't want to put in his mouth
But like
It's a hundred percent
Definitely Morgan
Fuse then
You nailed it I think
In that like bigotry often
There's intent
Involved
There's like one just like our Ivy versus our livers
The stupid what
And stupid is your just receiving
Cuz you don't
Understand this is confusion versus bigot
Yeah he's really on the side of
Computer now that's not to say he's not a big
Because he certainly has we've already proved that meant
Wrestling is
Confusion
Listen to rest
Put up with
Along with
Company trailer
Driving to the middle of neighborhood
I mean we got to stop we got to stop already
I've lived in Chicago for 7 years
I've been to like
I think five years are going to Pride and
Naked people f****** each other in the street
Never
Nevers there's never ever been nude
I've even been to the naked bike riding that hasn't been that too
But there's there's never been nudity there are like shirtless greased up dudes and stuff but that's not the entire parade
Hetero hetero
There would be naked Sherpa
But there's also like Civic organizations
Just joining in celebrating it's not like
It's not all gay by all means
By the way
This premise of
Your neighborhood doesn't
Want this parade
Parade never go through neighborhood
Chicago Gay Pride Parade goes down Halsted Street
Which is
Street of Lakeview
I'm in Belmont and
Hallstatt
But people live there
Essentially
It's not it's not a neighborhood in in the sense that most people in America
Think of it like
Residential
Because I grew up
In a
Small town
And I have a pride parade
Yeah and so if you are somebody
Who grew up in a
And somebody's telling you about
To you that doesn't mean what it does to us
To you that means
I saw a marching band with
Dick's everywhere
That's what it's
That's what your mental
A version of a parade is
Is like the high school track
Field has the band is going around Circle
With your Narrative of what the
Pride Parade
It never connects to what
Actually
Because you never
My only complaint that I've ever had about the pride parade is like
Gay enough
Like I've always left the pride parade being like
I didn't see a single deck
I don't know what's going on here
I think a lot of people were co-opting
Little bit like I am like the stuffy old dude but I'm
Not a part of the community
It was gay or back when I was a kid
I don't know why but I do to me
What was it back in
This Supreme Court
Made the ruling about gay marriage the day before pride and Chicago
I remember and it was such an awesome party but even then
It wasn't
Just people f****** on float
Like it wasn't. It was a wonderful celebration and everyone hugging each other it was just great
It was
But it was a human
Pride day
Where
It wasn't about being gay it was about
Accepting
Everybody now Alex is going to get into other parade we skipped over the fact that he said
Trump
Equals but
Watching
Call I want
Cuz it's coming back
But for now is going to get into
Two more parade
Tinker bat exam
A normal parade for the military
So like it is for children
Patrick's Day Parade
Drunk as assholes
Throwing s*** around
Every time I've gone on the street
Not granted baby at the Gay Pride Parade people pissing on 32 but the
Every time
I've never seen a dick cuz everyone has been
Directions go in an alley
Street pissing everywhere
Marches work military marches computer good
Auntie Patrick's Day
In a bathroom that I
Ever seen
Super cool is it at if you live in a big city they have
Blotters
Like blogs
Keep track of
You know calls to the
The police look at it I've actually done some research on this I don't have to
But the numbers for like
The Blackhawks
When
I want they want
The Stanley Cup to write
Actually do it
The Cubs win the World Series
Was shockingly devoid of tons
That one was
It's a once-in-a-lifetime
You know it's celebration
Saint Patrick's Day
Consistently they have
Way more crime
That premise is flawed on
Now let's get back
Used wife
Your friend
Get a room
Hotel
I am so pissed off because at this point at this point my recorder
Bike glitch
And I am I lost
The next thing citycell
About these dudes
In a hotel lobby grabbing their asses
They're doing it just to show off for you
Let's play
I just want to have one experience with a dude like that
Definitely sounds like
Pac-Man watch
But he's using
The parade stuff is in the
Enter now he's using this idea of
You go out with you
Your friends and
You know this guy a couple and they're just kissing the whole time
That is rude and you're like Cheese's
Making out if we agree that that's rude
Whether it's a guy or girl or two guys or two girls
You name
I'm not sure the point he's making
I don't think government
I think he's trying to track
Back that
To Gay Pride Parade
In terms of being like
That's the equivalent of thousands of people making out in the street
Yeah
And all of these people are enjoying themselves at
Yeah that's right that's what it is
Yeah yeah
Now hold on
His rant isn't done I told you my recorder glitched out a tiny bit I walked that Chuck
But it picked up immediately
Here's the end of this
Around
Hopping around
And when I say something
Shifting globulus but boy
Is very clear
Lindsey Graham
Congressman
Peter Schiff
Just for fun
Trump
Has become the Butt Boy
Of John McCain and just to be clear his name is Adam Schiff not
Peter Schiff
Cousin
I just
I don't know if f****** love that like if I want to be homophobic
You nailed
I'm just on the back burner come on the idea of like gay people exist in public
And I'm sick of it
Horrible
I wanted to be homophobic
Say all the s*** I just said
So we got via two more Clips Jordan
The first one is
Another narrative that he was trying to pitch on
Thursday show that is
Stupid
And then the last one is one of the most unfortunate
He just said
Trump
Is
The Butt Boy
Of John McCain
And the
Globalist
I don't want to
He said
Trump is the Butt Boy
It's going to get worse
That's my favorite thing
Compass the butterfly of John McCain
Isn't that in the mainstream white papers huh
Hold on
Wait for it cuz
Be a coiled spring
The next clip I play after this one
It'll that's when we can really tee-off
But this one is another dumbass narrative
Who's pitching it's about Bill Nye the Science Guy
Bill Nye the Science Guy
LG TV out in the second
They said the chromosomes determine the sex
The chromosomes
No it's in your mind
So here's the thing that's going on there he thinks that bill gender identity with
Basically
What's the same time
This episode that Bill Nye put out in the 90s
Yay
Yeah
Heater
There was a meme that was starting to go around on the right-wing Reddit
About trying to point out that Bill Nye is a hypocrite
Because he said
But if you actually look at
The quote that they
You think it was not a quote
And then further they didn't actually watch
The new episode
Cuz
Is from
The human sexuality episode of Bill Nye Saves the World
Is news
Science is the process by which we understand nature
By which we understand our place in the world
How we all fit in
We used to think it was
Pretty straightforward
X and Y chromosomes
For males
Two x's for free mail
The Ouija board combination
In the real life
Even for people with just two sexes
Hormones can vary widely
So can Anatomy
That's what makes someone male or female is not so clear-cut
So even in his new episode he's
Discussing how science
Has progressed
The night
Giving you the scientific explanation for what
But even when I was in high school I understood there were people sometimes who have three
From xxy
There are there are people like that
Even tribal
Group understood intersex
You got look into Native American
Understanding the culture they have
They have
And maybe that wasn't
Science
Punk Bill Nye for this Bill Nye
Said ones
In the night
And at that time
It reflected
What he thought
Or what the prevailing scientific knowledge at the time
Yep
Amazingly
Overtime
It has been revised
And revise
Is something that reflects
The scientific knowledge of
Wolf
Alliance crab doesn't matter
One of the most important pieces of Sia
Is a lot of it's Up For Debate
YouTube
Experiments and that's how you come up with
With a theorem
Or
Like
It's never a hard-and-fast rule some piece of evidence
Mike show up in the
Future that changes the experiment it might change what your
Sanding and then
Everything gets reevaluate
Right
That's the myth
That I get from
Right-wing p
People
All the time
Which is that
If you
Believe something
That
And now it's different
That means
You're that
You don't believe in any
Right as
Supposed to invalidate your passport
Invalidate your current
You're a flip-flopper of the highest order
Where is if you are if you are just a physical
That's right
Then you say
Force equals mass
Acceleration
And that's true
But it's true most
And then came around
And he said equals MC
2 squared
Which is a very
It's a
It's a kind of connotation of that say
Formula
It doesn't invalidate
The prior
Force equals mass
So it is not that I don't
I think that that prior stuff
Supplies
If that now it is Morse
Specific
And now it is more a
And that is what scientist
Striving for More Acura
Not striving for changing it
Mine back and forth on this
Send SMS
If that within the available information
We have this is our
That's amazing
And I'm not a scientist
Then I'm not like that that part of my brain.
Don't really work all that well but I know a lot of people who are of that
Some friends were doctors
All of them
The essence of
What they're into is that like
Time everything can change
And everyone I know who's ever done a study is
What we're looking at
This
We're not beholding to the outcome
Proven wrong
That's even more
So there's nothing better than being proven wrong because then you'll learn some everybody thinks that science is like
Really stuffy
Right
It's all about
Equation
And it's not it and in the same way that logic
Seems really
Dry and itchy
It's not right
There's an art to both things
Darrell live
They're alive they're not static
Anytime saying
That ideology
Yes cuz we can take Alex Jones as belief
It's back to
Back when he was in the nineties
And his beliefs are stay
Right about the global
So he is
Frame of reference
Everything has been
Set
Sent Bill Nye made that first episode
Now culture has
Grown
Information knowledge has grown around
Belief
That no
There is a group of evil people
Destroy us all
I've used this
Eugenics
System in all this
That has never changed
Threatened
Him
It don't look like people are
Flip flopping around
I meant stupid
Looks like a
The climate denier argument is always like
And now they say were Heating and you're like
No that's
Your you're
Misrepresenting what they said beat
Because you didn't understand it
Right you dismissed it out of course
And then now it doesn't seem like they're saying
The same thing
Even though you did
Bother to look into it because you've already dismissed it looks like someone is
Saying the exact opposite thing
The science look at the map
Like the math is always
But anyway
Throughout
This
30 hour
Broadcast
NRA
30 hour
Spouted a bunch of bull
And like
Like I said
We don't need to know what I want Roy or did
We don't need to know what
Lionel did what it did Millie Weaver have any
How about Lee Ann McAdoo
How about your dearest love
I don't know I don't remember
I didn't see
If she was on
Tell if there were some ladies there were some like
Weirdo
Ladies
The hits special
People in the world
I don't know why I remember his name but there's a guy
Gerald Ford
Use another like
Frequent
Yeah it's a good name
But there are other like there were some lady
Pokemon
Female Ron Paul
What have you restarted
We started this episode with that buzz
B******* and then once we got to the actual
Alex Jones broadcast
You started spout
Dumb
Misgivings
News about Trump
Spine
And him but he's moving away from
That is last clip that I'm going to play
I want this on the Run
Eyebrow razor
I was going to walk this back and
But there
Is my party
King shot
Perhaps the most important thing
I think you said
During that 30 hour bra
And tell the truth is
Trump
Is the
Johnson holster
Neocon Democrats
Trump is
The Johnson holster
Russell complex
Good luck walking that back
Sucking their dick
Oh he was just using a euphemism
So what
Colbert said caca
Something like that
The cock holster for the military dust
Boy there's no walking that back though
Doesn't seem like it pretty much
Sad
Donald Trump
Your friend
His mouth
And Amos open
To be inserted
With the
Kenai
The respective penises
You don't think the military
Military
I would assume the 30
So in contacts
That cock holster,
Yes I'd like to put that
In juxtaposition
This
But you said
Back in
In February
21 years
Maybe friends last 10
But it's not the same as it is with Trump
Firebreather
So
Energetic
Sonic show real
And he's having results so amazing
But it just makes me
Me and dear to trap I'm ready to die for
Jeremiah
Fire breathing cutting Trump
I'm ready to die for Trump
Trump is America you dumb dumb sonofabitch
Oh boy
What are
Set powder and a half months ago
So stupid
They're also
What kind of things go there's no other way to describe it at this point
I mean it's
It's the question
Is
Not
Will they
It is
When will people
Who voted
A trump realized
Peacock holsters
Of the military-industrial
It'll just be gradual
And you know
Call Jones Isabel Weather
So
Jackboy
Like that's rough
That has
Do you think
Totally I think it touches right
Intense me about this then that about how Trump
Because of the globalist influence
Trainwreck
Trump is a cock holster of the military-industrial complex
Is him betray
Yeah
He is a
Hypocrite
And now I really think what I want my summation
Because of
Twist
Of that last
Flip
She's a bad proper
Yeah he's a propaganda
But he is disloyal
Hurt
I think he's an emotional guy never let feelings get involved
Like you're a sex worker right you know you don't kiss
Also I love
I love the imaginary self-righteousness of
It's homophobic to say caca
Johnson holster
That's not homophobic at all it's the
Word not
Intense
I generally thought cuz he's a guns guy generally thought like
I didn't realize that
Problem with metaphors when your second amendment
Brixton the beat
Yeah
Alex you suck
Mike cernovich is a mistake
It is a big
Your team sucks
I think I think bailing on Trump is not a bit
I think the sooner he does at the better for
I would say he should have done it
Before now
Before the
If if he was as brilliant as he said capable of seeing the future as well as he can I know that
He should definitely bail on Trump
I think it's a mistake now
Because he's gone too far
You think so
Yeah I mean
F****** heard him say he died for
Right that's insane
I would never say that about any politician even that I love
But I thought was awesome I've never
I saw you squint
Maybe maybe
Robert Kennedy the only maybe
That are really good run
Maybe rsk maybe Solon the history of the world
Maybe so long
And that's just because of his treatment of a boy
Cincinnati
He had a good run
I don't know
He was the guy who asymptomatic
Hiiraan
Great chili
You remember those ads where is like
Story of the guy who
Was a military leader
Became a farmer
Then they were under attack in
What is a ohm
Could be rubbed Cincinnatus is
The Latin name
Another Greek
But the general gist of the story
Guy is
Former war hero
Get on a farm
The
City is under attack
They go to hell
They say we're giving you
All of the
You do whatever it
That you need to do
And then the moment he's a car
His goal
Helioptile
That's very similar
Right
Very very similar this is not a thing that
Pens in real life
What happens in real life
Is Caesar
Real life bud
Well technically Cincinnatus
According to
The history but
To me that's that has the Ring of myth
That is the ring of death
Bright
So Jordan I think if I want to put a button on this
What's your button
It is the punch button from die-hard Ark
We've we've made a lot of hay out of this
Funimation
Laugh
That the reality is
This is a desperation
Can cash grab
This whole thing is
There's no stops
Find it is just I need
Money please give me money
30 hours of program
Right
Outside
The Alex Jones Show
The programming
Unwatchable
Complete
I think if Alex Jones
Togo's
Not if he's bringing in Cerner
Burbage's close all right I haven't seen cernovich yet
He has more juice than a b
Call it.
I don't know how to list
Knowledge fight
Talking to work
Diplomate again
This s***
Alex
I wanted
I want to start anew
Yeah
I would like to
And each of our app
Episodes with the promo
Wrestling promo
Alex
Your Fannie and Freddie
Narrative is
Absurd
Stupid
You got no leg to stand on
Coming for you
Gold
That's what the wrestling came out
Pretty regularly you were like I do like this
Like
That's not a very bombastic wrestling promo tired
For three and a half hours prior to really come up with
A full strong girl baby
If you're going to pull this
Knowledge bike
There was more. Much better
Stupid
Criticism not you
Alex you're stupid
Alex you are
You're in trouble
No matter how much money you raised
You're getting sued
You're Gonna Lose
I think that's
I think that is the
Like the greatest thing about the have BuzzFeed article I have a billion followers
You can have
10 million followers
I think it'd all be giving you money
But you slandered someone who's a billionaire
And he going to let you settle
Just like we talked about earlier
The rich are always
Exactly
He's one of us even though he's a billion
I think it is I think that BuzzFeed article is right
In that
Alex is that tragic
Figure
It is not that someone else's
Taking Alex down
No it's Alex's
Taking himself down and he doesn't know how not to
That's what's fascinating if you get to the
The end of that article that talks about his
Divorce and cuss
Specifically
And basically it lays out that all he had to do was show up
Say a goddamn word himself as a good dad
And he would have won the case
The judge
Specifically said
His job has no bearing on that way
And she did not allow that stuff
All he had to do was not be a dick
He couldn't
Couldn't do it if you couldn't do it he lost that case for
Oregon sell he's going to
Keep on losing
He is a we're watching
We're watching an archetype of a man
Laid low
Fascinating
Because we know he does
It's fascinating
It's funny it's inevitable and it is the most infuriating thing
Because it didn't want
Can't we just get
Future where you've already lost
Well that's like why do we have to
Put ourselves
Through it like well
He's going to be impeached something terrible is going to happen
Why can't we just be there already why do we have to wait and watch it
Because we know what happens every
F****** time
I because I think
This goes back to how we failed in every other test
Throughout history
To actually close the
Still listening
Is there still listening
Sweet
Acknowledge
Underscore
Subscribe to us
Now it's right on iTunes also if you're still listening at this point please send us
Tweet hashtag Rappaport still live
That's your trick to see if anybody stayed to the end
Monetary policy want status
But also you can check out our website, bunch of
Extra content on their
Imitation of Alex
Also biography in progress
MLS you can email us that knowledge fight at gmail.com and then you have a off
Me off I have a we have a
Really into
Everything new piece of Alex Jones biography
Episode in 2015
Being that we're not going
Going to cover
Oh boy
F*****-up okay
Butts
If you want to be a policy want donate to the show if you want to have us do
An episode from history
$10 more a month will do it
This is what happens when you do an episode when I'm not here I understand
Just f****** throw everything at it
It just so happens to that you were gone for an episode
And so many weird things happen
World map
But anyway
Which means in 4 days the most
Keeps happening
Fun Jordans been appreciated so much and thank you for everyone who's joining up
We see the numbers
Skyrocketing and
F****** thank you
New policy wonks
To all of the upcoming policy wonk
About our show
I'll send you a shirt
You got a shirt if you can get a celebrity not acknowledged it is going to be
Dan has in his closet to create a real debate about what is a
Celebrity and I'm ready for Sation
Please try and get celebrities to retweet arshia
We're dudes
Who like to
To get into it
Right where at
The mucky-muck
It would be policy we're in the new policy but like what would the noun before
Alexandra Thurston color