I have great respect for knowledge but I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
MoneyGram
College fight. Com
Everybody sit around and talk a little bit about Alex
Geraldine we are Dan
Dion Jordan your dulcet tones are incredible however I must ask you do you do any
Impressions or voices
No you never have to write
What do you mean why would anybody be like some different sound
No I don't
Believe that was ever part of my
Comedic rapper
Why are you never you never even goes further than that like
I handle mine
This is the opposite of
Know when I
I took languages
School like
I get to French
Greek
And like
Whenever I would try and speak those languages
You know to be like a book
Doing it acts like you do it exalts
Or that that
The feeling of like
I have to dress up my French sounding like a Pepe Le Pew
Yeah it always has been
Versed
I got to do a good Alex
It's probably really want a guy you've never tried
Give me give me a
Does Christopher Walken right
No I don't want to do that
So I don't know a lot about oppression
Jordan but I do know a lot about Alex Jones and I don't know much about
Give me a nickel
Man now I can
Wow
It's not good I don't do any Impressions either
Anyway today
I think a lot of people probably thought that
You know Trump got impeached
Attractive last week a lot of people would think
Well because true a lot of people might have assumed
Hey these guys are going to rush out a Friday episode
And one of the reasons for that was I felt like if we
Do we have to record it on Thursday
That means we could only have Thursday
Show to respond
Where is if we waited till Monday
Thursday and Friday so today we have December 9th
The 20th
From
The end of last week
And you know it's a it's a silly thing
This episode quite silly
Quite upsetting of course I imagine it either goes he talks nothing
Nothing but impeachment or he doesn't even mention it
Throughout the show was worthwhile to rush out some episode
I think pretty much everybody
He knows what his take on it
That is it route
Damn globalist
And keeping prepping his audience for it already like he's been saying that the house is going to vote to impeach so like
He has no reason
Freak out or anything I didn't expect any firework I didn't get the
But there is some really messed up
Stuff stuff that goes on
Particularly on tonight
And then also some fun
We need to steal all the House of Representatives shoes would be a more reasonable thing then
Take a moment
People who have signed up for
Spartacus show
So first of all John thank you so much you and I'll probably walk
Megatron next Doctor Activision Arie thank you so much
IU Dr Activision Arie
Lincoln Journal policy walk
Cara thank you so much you're now a policy wonk
Text Matthew
Matthew
And finally like say thank you to a couple people donated on an elevated level we appreciate that very much both
Fake name
Noms de plume you can't be sure I'm positive okay one of them
Fun
The other may be upset
The second juiciest Ice Cube thank you so much
You are now a technocrat and also
Chris radish
What's the business
Freakishly large
Skewb and piss radish
You're listening out there to thicken had your the showed liked these Jets
Complicated
For sure we would have
It would be lovely
So
We are on the 19th
Trump been impeached
Alex's
I have a lot of feelings about it
Got to do a little bit of out of context okay
Alzheimer's
Just a good out of contacts.
I love that
So inspiring
Did they keep good
You're at
Okay
So enthused
Listen
So we started the 19th
And we hear a very familiar thing
From Alex
And that is today is the most important show I have ever done
Now I've been on the year 25 years and as the years go on I've said many times this is one of the most important broadcast we ever done
I used to say it once a year
But I might say every six months because there's a quickening things are getting more serious more crazy
The human animal cloning the open devil worship the open pedophilia
They're going to be your old one
Play open destruction of the family
The open 5G
Fluoridation
The spiked vaccines
Trojan Horse takedown of humanity
Get drunk
But this broadcast
Up to this point
The most important broadcast
I will ever do
Until I'm not someone to get butterflies or chill cop
But I am
Sweating
Right now and it's cold
It's cool
So we got a situation where I mean
Cousin Alex thing
Know that I do say that this is the most boring show ever a lot but this time
It actually I used to say it in frequently and now it's because of the news I'm sure
Because of the news that I'm saying it every couple of weeks now myself into a corner where everything is
F****** Extreme as hell
Guys
He's coming down fast
So today is the most important show ever
And part of that is
Sure you'd expect that to be your most important show ever
Theory about what's going to
To happen is going to play out over the course of
Episode
Find a convoluted
Here is where Alex
These are the traitors easily sellouts he's the enemies of the Republic
And so there is a program
There is an operation there is a plan
Remove
The president
Within
The show trial
That the house is already had
Prodigy
Using that as a
Platform in the media as a show trial
The spring a bunch of other scandals which they're starting
To announce
Supreme Court members
Like the Chief Justice
The move in and say the Senate has not been impartial
Supreme Court make a right at the president
In a true judicial to really this is openly
By not long for this world against Berg
Coming up the ultimate cliffhanger
So I mean we still have these themes of like everybody's being blackmailed should now apparently
Chief justice
Roberts is
Being blackmailed or something
Talking about this plan sounds like her what a cliffhanger that sounds like her
A lot of sense but he'll get more indeed
Sterilize things
Go along
Here's a think there is a play
Obviously
Well but he's only giving you the broad Strokes
Alright okay so there are more moving parts
Do you want to have a lot of moving part you want this to be ocean 7,000
What is a many conspirators as possible yeah that's how you get things
McDonald's
Secretly
But look dude
Plan and Alex is telling you that the
And everybody's being blackmailed although he's not proven that in any meaningful way at all
But you don't
Need to
Blindly Trust
Alex
His track record
He's been right about Soma
Everything we covered here is incredibly important
Appetite
Footage of Epstein's
Suicide and the previous attempts suicide but I tried to kill him
That wasn't hard to deduce
They murdered him in cold blood inside there
Now turns out
But the videos Gone Missing
As we told you before
So a lot of these deductions are easy
So it was reported in the New York daily news on the
Tea that footage from Jeffrey Epstein's initial suicide attempt that Alex doesn't believe his real had gone
Sure that story was based on comments by assistant us attorney Jason swergold who said that
Quote it is our understanding that the video no longer exists
It was not preserve
In the initial article on the 18th
It was reported that the government was asked
2 quotes
Further into what happened to the footage
I need it because on December 19th to do New York Daily News posted an article with the headline quote
Missing surveillance footage of Jeffrey Epstein suicide attempt has been found
That new article included this quote
Earlier today the government confirmed with MCC staff but the video was preserved by MC
CC staff upon defense counsel's request
Who was that quote from
You guessed it
Us Assistant Attorney Jason swergold
Naturally the most simple explanation for this whole situation is irresponsible reporting based on irresponsible comments from Anna
Assistant us attorney
He spoke kind of out-of-turn made comments that were taken as gospel then learnt pretty quickly that he was
Correct in that assumption
The New York daily news turns around a post
The story that the missing footage
Even kind of b*******
Because based on these stories I'm not certain that footage was ever missing in the first place
It all doesn't matter because now the fact that a day later they were attracted the footage that the footage was missing will be used as proof
The footage
Globalist shutdown swergold would lie to the New York daily news or so
Alex didn't predict anything
Just foolish
Do they not know that reporting
That the footage has gone missing
Is going to be far more popular
Then the second day when they report that it's
The damage will be done
Bye
Call it damage
Call impression whatever
You will concretely put this into
People's butt
And if you're not going
Undo with a correct exactly
Printing
Is the deal
I don't know what the right answer
Because if that footage is actually missing
Then that's a story that you should report
But
Someone
Asserting that it's missing
Baby hold on to that story until you do a little bit more digging on
Well I mean your recycle bin on
What
Windows automatically deletes after 30 days it was only a couple of days after that I'm sure they just
Just restored the file
Yeah I don't know what the right answer is but I know that it's not
That's because Alex buy this
It's the 19th
He has every reason to have the access to the new New York Daily News
Correct
Situation
Because the narrative is much better with the
Erroneous
I don't know what
You should do if your the New York daily news and
Then I wouldn't
I guess what I would say is
Write the story as
It's just
This guy
Saying yeah yeah
I'm at well I mean
It is one of those things where it's like
That is an incredible scoop if the New York daily news got that actual information and they're the first to go public with it
That you just going to be a big deal
But also it tends to be a situation where
Holyshit this is huge news is too good to be true
All too often
With with conspiracy theories
Yeah you got to be careful
Cuz it matters
Oh yeah
So Alex is a big announcement
That is related to
To this whole impeached
He's really
Typing this out
Let me make the big announcement here
Sirens going on in the background I could have drum rolls I could
My hair on fire
Cool
Cut my finger off on are we get your attention to really listen to me I do it
I believe you
I don't
I love you my life right now
Pusher
The price to pay at by the way I'm not suicidal one Olivia 150 and
Love God
My point is I'm going to get my wife to beat these people because that's what it's all about
And your life is just
Experience but I'm done talking about that
This is most important broadcast I've ever done
And you can have a thought with thousands
Amazed
Cedar Point's
Hundreds of thousands of sub points in data
And knowledge and background understanding
It all come together with certainty
And when you have that certain day
And you see it time and time again
Come true exactly as you envision
That's called
Beyond wisdom
It's called discernment
Call site
The Second Sight
But 99% of it is actually the incredible lectro chemical brain
Supercomputer
Integrating all those data points but that
Little 1% of spirit
The electrochemical
Internet
Takes you across to the pressure
So what I'm going to do this is Shelby
If I'm just going to stop for this segment kind of mention some of the other news
And then when I come back in the next segment I'm going to come in it with precision
I have a gigantic story I'm going to ramble about nothing
The amazing electrochemical brain
What the
I also think if you listen
I think Alex is describing being
Confused
Who sang you got that you got a hundred different datapoints things I think he's talking about the difference between
Actually being confused and presenting it as certain
Whatever the case is it solve this
Like the beginning of this episode is all this like
I got this big news
Either next segment
Because I got to do it right
Catahoula good
Got to do a good job
That's that's so funny that
Like I just imagine going back
And seeing
Jesus giving The Sermon on the Mount but he's like okay first hour we're just going to do a couple little things I'm going to rip for a while
The big stuff is going to get you some big stuff after
It is next hour
Predator now
I really got to just rip this out
American historical figures
Yeah it seems like there's a message
Get it out but
Lyrics to some news
Like the other he said he's going to get
Somebody's other heads
Lionshare
And one of them I found deeply upset
Pearl Harbor
3000 people killed in a bunch of battleships sunk it was terrible and it was horrible
But frankly Churchill was working with
Roosevelt and I got the purple and blue coat completely and new
Even the day of the attack and ordered the carriers out to sea
So they wouldn't be shocked until the old obsolete battleships
No good for Pacific Warfare would be destroyed
Really a chakra 5-3000
There are any warmers your pan for 2 years in China
What bloody Howard hunt were there sniping people daily
Add
That's how you win Wars I'm not defend
What
But it was a Gamble
Would you sacrifice a pawn
In chats to lower your opponent out to win the entire
That's all Declassified
As not to classify
But the way he's describing Pearl Harbor there is
Exactly how he
You would think that's not what he thinks about 9/11
No because that a false flag right
It's weird I don't understand what do you mean
Okay but firstly not to split hairs but
2335 Americans died in
Attack on Pearl Harbor and 64 Japanese
I know Alex just being in vague terms but he's off by like 30
Kind of a big deal
Yeah
That's the bigger issue
And that is Alex believes
Attack on Pearl Harbor was a false flag for some reason
Since you splitting hairs and saying it's not a false flag because the Japanese did it right okay whatever I have no idea what his
Uses for Eddie
Everything are because I've definitely heard him say that Pearl Harbor was a false flag in the past
So the stuff you saying you're is not
There have not been Declassified documents proving that there was a stand down or even that the US had specific prior knowledge of the Japanese
Attack
I wasn't even playing fast and loose with decrypt
Because he's not specifying which Japanese
Coach me practice
Up till that point
Using the purple code
No that's largely true but yeah
Like those are some of the codes
Did we agree
But that doesn't mean that we have the ability to
Decipher the relevant messages
Regarding the attack once you decipher one code you decipher all codes and that's just like how if you learn
Greek you know all of their life
It makes sense 10 separate inquiries have been done to examine this claim
Before knowledge
And none support the theory that Alex is put in
The only real evidence I can find of truth behind the code-breaking stuff is it there was a coded message that we translated which was
Is intercepted the day before the
The message indicated the
Japan intended to break off negotiations
Informal relations
United States
Next day
That was interpreted by most as being indicative
The Japanese did intend to attack someone
But the military at the time it's been expecting them to invade Thailand
Or somewhere else
The Pacific
That would effectively break off negotiations
That was the kind of the interpretation to mess
Had the time
It wasn't that they were going to bomb Pearl Harbor
Sister gigantic leap to make
But it sort of gigantic logical leap Alex
Be accustomed
So most of what Alex is saying is 100% based on a book or pamphlet
Put out a 19
244 called the
By Pearl Harbor
Written by a guy named John
Slim
When was an extreme right-wing figure in the 40s
It was instrumental in the organizing of the America first come
You may remember that music group who are deeply anti-semitic and profashion but pretended that they were just
The intervention it I wouldn't call him rabbit
When was a bit of a propaganda for the America First Commission
Being involved in creating a
Advertisement
Not to sway public opinion away from getting involved in the European
Korean War
KFC dissolve right after Pearl Harbor
Do you have to join the war which made the whole don't join the war Arc
A little harder
Even though they've been unsuccessful in keep
Us out of the war the members of the AFC didn't just give up
And one of the prongs are there further work was to create the narrative
The only reason the US got into the war in the first place was because of it
Conspiracy
If it hadn't been for the meddling communist and evil forces within our own government that attack on Pearl Harbor
Wouldn't have happened
And then we wouldn't have gotten into
Horse whinny
Do you think about it
Axis powers are really the victim
Yeah absolutely weird
The other angle here is that the folks on the extreme right like John
I hated Str because of his social
Myriad other reasons and Roosevelt was running for re-election in 19
So this book was released as a large-scale attempted
We are going to derail his campaign
With accusations that he knew in advance with
This attack was coming
But he let it happen so you could go to war
Alex is just repeating s*** some dumb fascist wrote about 80 years ago to try and stop after yards re-election
He's pretending it's Declassified and totally real
The sad
The sad stuff
It's wild to me how you can claim to be in
Find WWII of all things
One of these
Most
Exhaustively researched events in human history
I can't think of anything that has been more exhausted cover-up would have to be
Owens dhanasekar
It would include
The entire world leader
Which I suppose is the only thing that makes sense
His for him graduate student right
Bellows
Yeah
Any wife
I just think that's kind of interesting and I think it is one of these really
Things that you find
That is
Would you trace back a lot of
Dumb conspiracy theory yeah what you end up finding is
People who were used
For political reasons initially
They may or may not have served their political purpose at the time
And then
They Echo throughout
People
Baby unintentionally
Picnic on a life
I'm past the original use of the thing it said it was being used
Or in this case primarily
To attack FDR's relax
I mean in some ways that is that is very similar to Alex immediately following the boss
Embalming where it's like
The cement hasn't dried
So while I'm there I can make up whatever story I want you imprinted going to be left in the sand
Yeah if that was an election
You're abusing more
Yeah cuz it is just politically-motivated it is to attack Obama
The globalist who are the Democrats
In that I think that's attacked
Standard operating commercial
There is two are
Mostly a political and what they are
Gunning for right or what they believe that they're involved
They takes.
But I think there's a lot more of
That is that is like
Alex
Yeah
So
Alex just gets rambling
I know you said he was going to talk talk
Get some news out of the way really
And you know he doesn't
Fake Jefferson quote
On the show
It was interesting on this that in this instance
You decides to swing
Further for the fences
Dig deep into the past okay
Cicero
Senator
Outside with open banners we can defeat
The city of stronger enemy that mobilizes
But traitors Within
Traitors within the Republic
Are the plague and can bring it down
And as it was 2000
67 years ago and he said that
My memory serves
It doesn't
It is today
That's not a real Cicero quote
I just accepted it is true but
Called a pillar of iron written by Taylor Caldwell in 19 6
Caldwell's Basin the book on a lot of real sources about
But the quotes that are passed around about Traders being the carriers of the plague we're all Caldwell's creation
Historically the far-right is use this quote to push back against greater social equality
Which is not surprised
Nor is it surprising that I was once again has no idea what he's talking about
Exploding things
Using just to make him
Cancel soundsmart
And you can hear that to even like 2067 years if my memory
That's just trying to be fancy
No that's totally that's totally
What is Ayo
The guy who named Mount Everest
The original like height is changed now
But he measured it at
25000 ft exact
And he was like
No one is going to f****** believe that it exactly 25000 feet
So he just told people as 25,000
M to feet
So I can look at how good I am at measuring thing
I got it all the way down to 2 ft
I understand that impulse
It's more for me it's more like Alex rattling off the name
Name of that subset
Thanks Bruce
That that's my way of impressing you into thick 9090 what I talk about
Upgrade my brain is 67 of your math.
When you are 19 years old and your first year of college
Yeah exactly
It's like you're not going to question me if I know all of that
I have an eidetic memory for one thing I will question
You read that to me
Anyway Alex
Has been trying to
He's going to get to the next segment
Time to get down
Let's enjoy right now
Best I can
And then I'd end up in the phones up throughout
The second third and into the fourth hour and Matt bracken's biases
The next one job last night
Covering more than folding until late in the evening
And
Hear a little about to break down but then I
Also have all the different ways and different Avenues and different paths
That we can break down
How they're intending to make this move because
They do intend on removing
President
Yeah they impeach him
That's
Yeah that is
Mariah
What would they be doing not
Trying to see if they don't intend to remove him what are we doing here
What do you think we're doing
If we're not in pain again all I hear Alex saying there is I'm
I don't know how to play this this is not
You really think this was going to happen
Or or whatever you know like
I have all the evidence but I don't know what the
Angles
Much true
Just do your job and say your s***
So Alex
But it's going to get down to business
Bottom line is they playing
Strop
We have a plan to remove him
What's the address
Is the process
They're going to double down though
And it all in
They do intend on removing
President-trump
And we can say all well it's blowing up in their face looking phone numbers
And I got plan
And so
It is
Bending towards failing spectacularly
You understand all they do is keep doubling down
Look at what a double down at this level does when it's an open public
Kangaroo court
Railroading
But what comes after that
Two kangaroos
Is that rhetorical
Okay thanks I just don't want to be like I've been for 25 years
Laying out very important things constantly
Gibbering as fast as I can talk
Trying to get out all the little factoids
Miss the forest for the trees
Aren't you part of the 732 do it I promise
Okay so we're going to do it next Sigma
This is
You know what I hear I hear temperature
Yeah I hear just somebody who's is like
Like my f****** dude the guy who I changed my
Walking career for ice
Took a
So many hits
Trying to go down this road because I thought it was going to go summaries
Going to kick all the
Mexicans out of the country I thought this was going to work out we were getting install a patriot dictator
How's the plant
The third president history to ever be impeached
God God what the
The fuk I just hate this level of
Set news like it's November 1963 there's some pretty big news about the president we're going to talk
Talk about this in the next
Like yeah
Yeah it's that big a deal you just
Say it right away you would think yeah you wouldn't think you have to wait until like
I just I don't
I am the segment
I need to apportion 2 minutes to plug so I
Can't get to this everybody remembers where they were an hour after Kennedy
You know you might remember to do the Kennedy died but you definitely remember the brain
4 Savage
Kennedy died
Yeah yeah yeah
Alex's got to be
Kind of feeling in a f*****-up place
Because
As much as he can make the argument now like
Sandy Hook is not who I am
Will not Define my Google what I remember.
A little difficult to disentangle your your legacy
From Thompson
What should
No matter what
Ends up happening
Trump is in the history books as
Is the third president
To ever be impeached
And so Alex is the champion in the mouth
Piece of
Cider press
That's part of his history to now
And if it doesn't work out well
Not a ton of invocation to come
He's he's the type of guy who
So far has done nothing but gradually put larger and larger necklaces made of rocks out of a snake
To like a hobby
If you were to fall into the into the river he would
Don't go to Barton Springs
Yeah exactly what's the matter hot spring are not going to save you
So Alex comes back from break
Time to get in
They want to establish and private corporate world
And they're very
Very
Upset
They're very
Very
Upset
That
Humanity
Is not
Going
Along with
And so they are going to try
What they've done in the past what other empires have done
To get the little people the average people fighting with each other
If you don't pick it up you're going to run out of time in this segment to like quite frankly this staccato
His got to stop
Yeah this is bad delivery I just
I find I found myself listening
Incredibly
Inspired
I feel I felt like he was being credibly on it
Good
The best high-end
So
Cultural division
When have you not said that like what
NetSpend
The talking point you've had four
Ever
Which which is ironic because the first president to be impeached
Was
Trying to sow Discord
Between the boards
For Rachel reason
You might be asking yourself why are these Democrats doing this in
I was a lot of answers to remove the president for committing crimes like what's really motivated
She committed crimes and we would like to remove him but interesting reason
The truth is slightly
Supreme Court Justice
But even if this removal fails they'll say
We're not going to confirm anybody that was
Justin Peak we're not going to confirm anybody nominated
By a president like that
I wish they would
This is so dumb they think impeachment is
Conviction it proof Trump is bad
Changing the subject
Incredible crimes that they've committed all the bad things they've been up to
Yeah this is how Hillary's going to get away with Benghazi find
Man I really wish she hadn't put that uranium one on there but here we are
So this theory is f****** stupid
But there's no big it was Supreme Court
Even if Ruth Bader Ginsburg
Republicans already set the precedent that an opposition party can refuse to hold hearings on Supreme Court nominees in election years
Now this process
I got a very difficult
Consequently
Process of impeachment
Is not necessary to achieve the goal of blocking the Supreme
Court nominee
Now with the Democrats do that
That's another no
The giant hours
Well sure hold on hold on because if you're willing to believe that they would say
Make an entire impeachment in order to reach that goal
You probably think that have no problem just saying hey you remember the rules you guys that four years ago while we're playing by them now
No nomination
Fidelity Alexa
I understand what you're saying but in the world where you believe that this is what they're doing
Sway public opinion
Destroyed
Anyway my point is that this is not a compelling motive that Alex is suggesting for Wyatt
Impeachment would go
Sunnyway everybody's being threatened
And
I don't know Alex
Trying to get
Is big
Reveal
Okay of what
The what hour are we in
Still in the first hour better than I expected
But it's if it's probably towards the end of that
Anyway
Senators being threatened
And the Supreme Court
Coming into play
3 months ago
But they will impeach him in the house
And when I get to the Senate
They're going to pull out the stops to Blackmail
Arm-twisting
Threats against the Senators
Did the Supreme Court
Could then be brought into play to claim that people work in partial
A cloud like the Democrats do with the election 3 years ago
To create the real civil unrest killing in the election year
Calms one to undermine the nation that for their plan
And so
They are going
They are trying to cause a civil emergency that's why they're going after the guns
Virginia
Hell yes we're coming for AR-15s
Because you can't
Beat us
Politically they are going to try to
Along racial and along political lines that will tear
The country
In
The pieces
That is a big gamble
And it's making the presidency survives an even stronger
But
They can't help it and have to do it because they're being so politically destroyed
Father Jeffrey Epstein information coming out
Really
Blue cities collapsing
And their alliance with a chai,
And the chemical warfare against the American people
That clip is really Alex Jones
Trevor was one scary ideas disconnected Notions that are being brought together for no reason
And most importantly references to obscure things
Things that are in no way relevant
Alex has failed to prove in any way that any Senators being threatened and until he does
I'm going to assume he's just
Make that up
The Supreme Court may actually need to get involved at some point
If you have one party that refuses to take things seriously but know they're in the majority so if they
Be fine if they just do nothing or they'll get their way what else can you do
I'm not sure that's the right thing to do and I don't even know how that would play out
I don't know if that's
The direction things will go but
Booking a thing
I wouldn't be too surprised if there was some sort of illegal challenge
Subway
But even so even if the Supreme Court
Get involved
I've literally zero believe they would do so in a way that would trigger the outbreak of civil unrest or Civil War
The Supreme Court literally decided the 2000 election
And though there were consequences of that which we still have not fully atone for it did not lead to Democrats in the street
Rioting
You can make an argument that the right-wing is much more insane right now than the Democrats were in 2000
And you would be great
But I still think this kind of idea that Alex is selling as a bit of a stretch
Plus it's a conservative Court
I would assume they would err on the side of following us
Process
Which favors
The GOP
Just part of the reason I suspect they won't even
Get involved in the first place
At every point now it's his career the globalist have been
How to start a civil emergency
Always has to do with going to
For the gun
Somehow this
Never gets old for his fan
3 *
Carry-all a new all over again
Men always getting into the guitar for the gun it was Beto said hell yes we're coming for your guns and he dropped out of the presidential
Race on November 1st
As best I can tell
He's completely irrelevant to any race in the country you didn't know this but he's
Quote is still running for president debate you didn't see a big sign that just say
Hell yes we're coming through AR-15 behind a podium
That it did still beat compelling argument
Beto's not in any office nor does he seem to be a major force in the larger left-wing conversation
It's not like he dropped out but his guiding the conversation
The people are having
As for Virginia Democrats won control of the state legislature in most of the the recent
Nobody's talking about
So when the Democrats won
The control of the State Legislature
Turn very blue
If there's been some talk of universal background checks possibly being discussed but their legislative session hasn't even
Started yet
But that doesn't stop some weirdo community members from overreacting to Democrats being in office by stirring up igreja
Paranoia
According to the hill over 50 counties in Virginia passed resolution
Declaring themselves Second Amendment sanctuary
Which is not in any way legally binding
It's just a symbolic act or
Paul Joseph Watson my call it
Virtue signaling
Nothing happened except Democrats winning elections and immediately the effort to frame any kind of gun debate as encroachment of essential
Begin
With these counties passing
What's resolution
Representative Donald mceachin commented that the governor may have to bring in the National Guard at law
Malaysian seasoning
Counties are refusing to
Forest laws
But
He wasn't saying
The governor
It was just a comment about how is that is a pop
Possible outcome
But there are law enforcement agent
Disease that are in essence
Going rogue
You said quote that's his call because I don't know how serious these counties are
And how severe the violations of law will be
But that's obviously an option
And he has
According to the car
That is an option the governor hat
Because he talks about it all the goddamn time
This entire Virginia story is not about actual efforts to come for anyone's gun
Although there may be gone laws that are discussed in the next legislative session
5 entirely possible I would assume even with a democratic majority
Some of that is still going to die
What is Republican f****** and say whatever the case this is the story of a severe pre-emptive overreaction
Bygone weirdos
The Democrats winning election
It makes more sense
For Alex to frame it differently
I'll get these these people they got out they got a
You know they have to do this because they're all there
Ships coming down
They're too much trouble
What's Jeffrey Epstein information coming out is destroying Democrat
That's exactly
Is it the bunk story about the non missing missing footage that he was talking about earlier
Which blue cities are collapsing
Did you know that
So which blue cities are collapse
Jordan and Howard triggering a race war helpful
Nothing Alex
It's all just a p
Steve Chavez normal talking point of imagery
He's trying to build it up to a fever pitch
It has the vibe of I know you've heard me say all these things before but this time it's for real that's the same Vibe is all.
The same thing as how he started the show
Like I said this is the most important thing ever before because
Listen to his voice I don't even believe he believes
It is a
It is unfortunate that Obama didn't
Do any of the things
Is that they said he
He was going to
Because now they're just always going to assume that
Any Democrat like
The Fox News and everybody spent
8 years
Saying that Obama was a dictator who is going to come and take your gun
And then when he didn't
They didn't just deflate
And think that all well now that we have different Democrat
It's they're going to not
Now it's just on Red Alert 100% all the time
Any Democrat is going to take your gun
Alldayeveryday they can't walk back from the facts
Reflected a Centrist black president and it drove them all in
I was that way
So Alex
Skip around
These comments by Ruth Bader Ginsburg
Which approves
That
Supreme Court's going to
To decide this
Teach my daughter
Alex
Certainly.
What is Bader Ginsburg
Play the club coming up next trackman
Senators
Can be disqualified
Upcoming impeachment trial in they are not impartial
Doubt she doesn't have that power this whole thing is political
So
That's not really what you
I assume that's what exactly what
She said word for word along with which she was quoting Cicero I believe
So Ruth Bader Ginsburg was being interviewed while she was being awarded the broken
Berggruen prize for philosophy and culture
In the interview came up that Trump is being impeached in the
GOP Senators at literally sat
They weren't going to be impartial
She was asked quote
Senator says I've already made up my mind and the trial doesn't exist at the moment
There's no accountability is
A response was quote if a judge said that a judge would be disqualified from the case
The day of judgement Ops being impartial and starts
To do things to please the home crowd that's the day the judge
You should step down from office
The implication is that a trial should be presided over by impartial judges
And that the impeachment trial in the Senate involves offenders B
Being sexually judges
Isn't the case so you can read that as her saying get Senators who
Indicate they've made up their mind pretrial should be disqualified
But the important thing to remember is that she didn't say
She implied that
And she did so by pointing to an example of a similar situation that we all agree with
If a judge in a different context was going around being all like
No matter what I'm going to acquit this guy
You would easily recognize that is a problem
Yeah
But
The claim Alex is making that RBG
That the Senators could be disqualified from the impeach
If they aren't impartial that's it
The problem that claim is a problem
Because it's not true
If that's what she was implying
It's very it's very
Forget the game he's playing is very very
It never fails to amaze me how much
The right-wing thinks
Shouldn't be in the Constitution
Isn't
And how much they think should be in the Constitution
Write like
They will cuz it in the Constitution there's nothing that says you have to be an impartial
You're if you're in a senate impeachment
Which arguably
Maybe there should have been
But they when they were writing it they just assumed that nobody would act like this
These guys were so stupid
Fathers were idiots
Also Alex's idea here is really funny because Trump tweeted quote
Radical left has no case read the transcript shouldn't even be allowed can we go to the Supreme Court to stop
So Alex is Nightmare scenario where the Supreme Court gets involved is literally what Trump is asking
Things that happen
I expected Alex to be all out of sorts about the reality of
This impeachment
But I really didn't think you'd be this low energy
Is narrative makes no sense
She selling it poorly
I think he's just beginning to realize that no matter what his name is attached
For history
And I don't think he thinks that's a great way to be remembered
I'll be bummed out if I were him to
I I can't read any I don't read any Trump tweets I don't
I don't read anything to talks about Trump tweets
It's because it feels like
He's sending a
Telegram
Paying by the low
Stop
If this isn't fair.
We're going to
You
How is that okay how is that not an impeachable offense
So Alex one of his big things
Like every he's already said
We've heard it you said that like are all these dumb down people think that this is a conviction
And Pelosi
Is not bringing
The
To that immediately
So it because it will technically be a kangaroo court and it won't
You appear like a
Conviction
That makes sense
And so there now
Having Pelosi
Say that she's going to withhold sending the Articles up
Certifying them
So they can just
Have that out there that old look
Trump
If impeached as if that's a conviction
Anna Anna Anna way the tea is discredited
Waiting
While they prepare to rollout women saying the president
Played some people saying the president use the n-word people claiming the president has preparation of tax returns
And all sorts of other things
I don't know what accusations Alex thinks are coming that is somehow going to catch fire and actually hurt Trump with his base
But I think you shouldn't hold his breath
I mean we've all seen people accused Trump of sexual assault being a racist and being corrupt in his business dealings
And none of his supporters
Pacific are up till this point so I don't
I don't understand what Alex's preparing for
He himself
Has backed up those accusations by saying that he did it
It does seem that way a lot of the case he's lying and corrupt like he said he was
Was in a debate
Cohesion
Committed sexual assault do you mean like
He said he did
If anybody doesn't think you send me Edward
Even even his supporters are like he said that
Yeah I just
All I think it is that what Alex is doing is
Trying to find a way to reframe the idea that the house has said that they're going to hold more here
And that's that's just
He's preparing his audience for whatever information
You could come out of those
I mean fine
Whatever
This is been the big breakdown
Gets to the end of the Segway
And so far I mean I think we've got these
Misrepresenting a quote from Ruth Bader Ginsburg you saying that people are being threatened naturally
Like they're trying to
Trump just because they don't want another
Supreme Court nomination
I don't really think that we've got much of anything
Nintendo remove the president and their real plan with their now
Suppose your rabbit can stop them
So we haven't gotten to the plan
We're going to get to the plan next this is all still just Preamble today
That's why I felt so meaningless
Because it wasn't the plan
This show
Is
Ridiculous banana
Cuz I thought that was the plan that's the only plan
Yeah
That is all that spawn whenever whatever Democrats actually do what
He says they're going to do he's like
And the plan is with we reveal the plan is going to stop at Menards
No it won't they already they've told you the plan the plan is to impeach and remove the president using this
You can't make up a if we expose the
The plan is going to stop them thing for
Well they expose the strategy of like if we reveal the plan it will stop them it works really well when you're play
Plans are nuts
Exactly because you say something that's completely outlandish
Suppose the plants they couldn't do that
You're the one going to do that
That would make sense
Yeah
So we don't
What the plan is
Yet he comes back from break
And
Expresses that you show
Truth
I am your host Alex Jones Infowars very existence
Pirates your support
This is information Warfare this is truth and on
Vicious life-and-death
That's not melon
As the saxophone crescendos
Where we are people take
Everything from Ash
Don't start standing up for ourselves our let me lay it out
So this is like the true reason
3 reason
Play You Belong To The City is a f******
Bangers
Second reason
Alex literally says this is truth
That's his opinion
This feeling
Great that is the blurring of the presentation
That's the only circumstance
In this episode where Alex
Really feels inspired is when he's doing these voice overs over swelling Saxbys
How come you're not the only time that you see life and Amber's what he's doing these
If we don't stop them
They will take everything from
Don LaFontaine he's dead
He's sober he just wants to do like overly dramatic
Threats yeah over over symphonic
What's Goosebumps
Yeah that can't do that for four hours
He wants to do what he was doing
In the past
Singing with along with The Highwaymen
And s*** like that that's the only time you see the spark of like this is a person otherwise it
Spiccato
This is
Are playing
They wanna divide
Pearl Harbor was fake
See I kind of think he would wind up getting more listeners and viewers if he
He did go back to that sing along with s***
I think people would tune in way more just because they like
This guy used to be f****** crazy and now look at how crazy he is
Crazy in an entertaining
The problem with Alex right now is that
He could be
Super
Super popular
If you would just drop a lot of this b******* would legitimately be
Be somebody the people with TuneIn and walk to watch
And he could do it
I think
But the problem is
How do you get from A to B
Is probably marketable in this climate
Have to figure out how to shed yourself as you describe it all of these necklaces is Rock necklace
Design for himself Better Way yourself
Can I put on One Straight yeah it's tough but if you can figure out a way to do that I think
You probably
Find a way to have the fungus over this
Saxophone
Not good not fun part where he has to try and come up with absurd reasons
For why his hero is getting impeached
Here's a here's how I would do it
Here's what I would do I would turn it into like the the movie Airheads
I swear it's like
We're going under a station restructuring so I wanted
Keep doing the infowar but instead I'm just
Anything over the highway
It's not me it's my manager is up at the top
Everybody I told Addison Claire
Want me to sing
If I were Sinclair I think that would be the way I would be amazing
What are you just to ditch our podcast where they like guys
Craziest
I don't know if we're going to keep going or not but we're doing this episode first we are keeping going
Karaoke from now on
The dream job
We thought we'd gone to the Planned Parent Lee.
Got to lay it out now though
Saxophone
Take a break
That'd take a break
A good swelling snacks
Is is a short circuit into anybody's brain is totally
I know Alex has inspired
I lay it all alright
Let me lay it out
Is really four different one
Tuesday really like
Those four scenarios busted really like what are they doing
Like if we got it we got it
Here's the first one but here's the first option
They created a blackmail enough Hysteria
Enough problems on a pressure on the Senators
Bring up while they're holding
The Articles from the Senate
Another Law Firm
And then
And they vote to removing they say for the better the country
Was just going on too long there's too many bad things.
Now this latest thing even though it's not in the trial
I just I just I just have to go to the present
What they really want
This is a stupid theory in space on nothing other than his own fantasies
Goes on in serious places in the world you would never be welcomed in
But this is really useful as a narrative
You need to provide some reason for your listeners not to completely turn on the GOP
In the off chance that some Senators do end up voting
Convect
Alex remembers the Ron Paul days
And how impossible it would be for him to ever be anywhere near power if you went with a third-party tried to
Create a party
It's just you know it
You knows it it's imperative
Keep things under the GOP wing
I tried to continue to corrupt it from the inside
The other path is too hard
And insisting that if any GOP Senators voted
It's only because the globalist or hitting them with hard with tons of blackmail
Often the backlash against
The party a little not their fault
It's not strong but they're not strong enough to kill their children exactly
Also this is never going to
What would you do in that
This plan is never gone
Just toss out that one
Most that was the one that they wanted to happen most that's implied you okay all right here's the second option
The other one
Is it
Supreme Court says it's political
Events so far
And that trigger civil unrest
And anger
Blackmailing members of Trumps cabinet and the Senate
25th Amendment to the United States
Beyonce concert becomes unable to the job the president becomes
Present
We could happen for just
The present time
Until the end
Incapacitated
So that's the
I want
Took buddy if the 25th Amendment hasn't been invoked yet it's never going yet
For the people that have political Rivals recently dead husband might be in hell and nothing happened so don't worry about the 25th
No he's it's because he makes too much sense
Stan honestly this option is really convoluted
If I understand it correctly Alex was saying that a part of the Supreme Court will save that they impeach miss being handled inappropriately
Really this was somehow set off civil unrest at which point the senators of people in the cabinet who are being blackmailed
Fifth Amendment to get Trump out of office
Now Jordan
I would posit that none of this is necessary
First of all as I mentioned earlier Trump tweeted that he wanted this
Supreme Court vote
What's narrative little
Secondly
Everything up to the point of the Senators being blackmailed it's completely superfluous
If the end goal is getting senators and people in the cabinet to invoke the 25th Amendment
All of that can be achieved through the black
You don't need the Supreme Court to get in the mix
Which then kicks off the civil unrest which then supplements the blackmail
Mail or something
It's an overly complicated overwritten
Narrative that makes no sense
From the standpoint of the imaginary conspirator wrong the blackmail
Hidden by the social unrest
That way the Senators don't have to say they're being blackmailed they're being
Influenced by their voters.
And page or retract your statement now
No one ever says I'm being blackmailed that's why I doing this
I suspect that this is just a way for Alex to prepare to delegitimize any left-wing protest
That might happen surrounding the impeachment
Process
I just try and put it as they're playing into the globalist and for something to happen either
Second option
Off the table not realistic in any way
I do love the situation where
Where in being so
Insanely simple
And yet
Spiraling into the most complicated version of Reality Week
Like here's how this should work
Because it's fairly simple
The house impeaches the president
The Senate access impartial jurors
The evidence is presented since there's no Excel pittore evidence whatsoever that anybody has brought forth
There's not being allowed to call them but
Select called I promise that allowed
He will be removed from office it's a very straightforward issue
But because
People don't want that to happen
We have 10 million different games
The articles
Hippie sent yet because
Mitch McConnell to corrupt a we're still need a drama public opinion to put pressure on him and it's like
This Is Us
The game the game between played by Alex is a lot crazier
Get those first two option
Bat
Not not going to happen
And those are the two they most prefer that's implied yes specify that the global
Where's the Third
See if you can
The similarities
Civil unrest
Violence
Breakdown
Kill the economy
And that
Causes of a crisis
For them to win the election
And or step down
This is very dumb
Trump thrives on civil unrest and no amount of it is going to cause him to step down from office
This is a doodoo leaned into the unite the right rally where neo-nazis chanted blood and soil in a woman was killed
It's not like he's a guy who would say a people are hurting
For the good of the country I've got to step down that point will never
Happened now
I think this is just a pre-emptive rationalization for the possible loss that will
In the 2020 election
Sure we could have one but there was that civil unrest
Stryker stock market so technically we kind of did actually wins of the globalist cause adult chair
Good way to piano no matter what I didn't lose even if I lost it's only because
Cuz you cheated this option mean
Nothing
Also this is the last scenario
Any Enter he said far
Rural areas
Alex forgot that there was four
Two are complete bulshit total.
Is meaningless
So he's not even
The sky is so over it
Like they'd find a way to win the election
Yeah
That's the entire thing I mean he's saying that they're using a bunch of different steps but it could be
The point in
Option number three is they win the
Right
In any number of different ways
Sure but they're going to do it by civil unrest that plunges the stock
I mean okay
I guess
Right
Or they could do it differently
There's a lot of different ways to win an election
Just come down to we lose we lose the election
But he's really focused on this civil unrest stuff
And he knows that the globalist
Planned this
And he can prove it
To you and
This is not this feeling
This is fact
How much civil unrest could they get I'm just type in
Infowars.com
And then
Obama. Michelle Obama planning martial law in Maryland 2015 we got those
South 19th
Confirm
30 pages of antifa secret documents
Hollywood go in and break things working with the police in blue cities
Police matters
Yeah
Wyatt it didn't work
Back on screen
So they tell me this is just the 4chan Soros antifa documents that Alex found online
They is presenting as like this is proof that it's been confirmed
Found that online
So it is next to B really interesting because Alex tells how he got those documents okay
And it's not
True
That article is more important today than it was January 2018
Please go read this
Vans family
We got threatened we got told
You stop that we're going to struggle to get lawsuits in man on week later they also get file
But they are so pissed we got those
Smoking Gun
Kind of criminal charge racketeering
Who is the headphones
Nationwide
So the guy that that was the story that was on 4chan I remember that was the guy's brother found
Yep I remember that one. How elex got them
I watch that episode
I remember this very clearly Alex's intern Harrison Smith
Kmart air said he found them on 4chan
Yep good now Alex's turned the story that was posted on for 10 today heroically got in touch with Infowars
He's turned it into his own story of finding the documents
This is this
Do you know what I bet Alex thinks that is what
Oh no I agree I totally believe you remembers it now because of like
Use mythologized
The retelling of
The story over and over and over again that it feels real to him
That this guy's brother is like
Is interred with lurking unfortunate foundries
Fake documents that they decided to pass off as real
It's like a fishtail but it with
Bucking potentially world-changing information if any of it should be real
Is like this big
My God that's the thing man
These documents
Contract
Between antifa and Sora and that's why you got to worry about sore
Because because of contract
Soros does sump
The contract
Leave a paper trail of his bad stuff like anything for an info Warrior 2
So because Soros is so bad it makes
Other people who
Here bad
They're not that bad
This is an attack
To take our country down
I mean they demonized Putin because he just has all the Soros ads you aren't rushing
And Rogers at work with him get arrested
Usher you can protest all you want
You get your ass arrested
That's what's going on as family show
I love listening to your phone's words with your tanning
Soros is trying to teach Karate Kid not to suck cock
Who
I'm going to leave that just sort of
Sitting out there
Russian
Absolutely
Demonstrate freely
Organize
Doll just
Zorro
LaRosa's instigating against the the Russian government that's amazing
That is the most fascist argument you can
Possibly know everybody has the right
To protest
Except for these people
Whomever they may be based on a fictional thing that I create and change it my win
If Alex is dying the entirety of anti-fascism
Fake documents imagine that anybody would be able to falsely connect any protest
Everybody has the right to free and fair protest except for
For people who are against
Fascism
That sure seems to be his
So
Alex's pretty mad
About people inciting violence
And he gets around saying that
Within a very short clip Alex takes issue with people
Inciting violence
And then
By the end of it is saying the Trump should get the military involved
So
This clip takes a little bit of a ride
If I was running around trying to get people to go kill people or burn things for a conspiracy
To commit Mayhem and crime and disorder and I spend lots of prison and I should
I'd never do that
Committing crimes
Enough
Job and I wanted to put them on notice
That's pretty extreme
Okay. All right
That's pretty standard for Alex that's pretty far for the course of where he's at
These days
You did this like this is the most important show I'm ever going to do
I'm going to lay out the globalist plan there's four scenarios
There's only there's only 3/8 just an incompetent display of
Dumbass
And then we now see
You started to talk about Soros and
Contract
All the civil unrest if you started to work himself up and now he's starting to get
Angry at the violence is
And you can start to feel it bubble
Throughout rest of the show across the Rubicon I wanted to drain the Rubicon entirely
Kill a trimmer
Working on a theory for a little while Matt is that Alex doesn't
No
Bolsonaro
Okay or at least has completely forgotten okay okay
And he said bolsonaro before
Wayback the guy in Brazil
Clip I think
We get more evidence
It may be he
He's trying to learn his name
This is scaring the hell out of levels were this close to taking this country down
Mouthpieces
I appreciate that he tried
Saudi impeachment is happening it's going to go to the Senate
Alex is a lot of feelings about this
Is being done by the letter of the Constitution
Yes
Support which it is being done
For somebody who's making such a narc
Really know what the
Constitution entail disagreement
Situation you got to know how the impeachment is supposed to be run
This clip does not Inspire confidence
Okay me that Alex knows
Anything about what he's talkin to
Curious Ginsburg
Suggesting Senators can be disqualified
From upcoming impeachment
The branches are equal so one doesn't take over the other they keep each other in check
Show the Supreme Court
Where are you
Supermajority
That's
Crazy what if
The 2/3
So it was two-thirds against 1/3 and they were somehow tied at the end of it there cannot be a tie in the Senate when a tooth
Majority is required to pass something I disagree this is super advantageous
This is because you would never want a tie in the Senate
Since the vice president is also the president
And gets
The cast of o2 tiebreaking situation
Do you never want that to come up is cuz the vice president becomes president
The presidents removed
Really don't want to have to deal with the Optics of cats
Tiebreaker vote
The Macy's present
But
It doesn't
Matter because
Anti braking situations and impeachment trials in the Senate are provided over by the chief just
The Supreme Court
The tie-breaking vote would go to the Chief Justice
Are possible
Conviction vote
Oh yeah it's about like rule change
Situations all you need
Simple majority
Edit those cases
The Chief Justice
Presiding over the trial would be the tiebreaker
Either way.
Vice president doesn't come into play in this
It's crazy that he really doesn't know what he's talking
Thanks for the vice-president we cast the tie-breaking vote or is there still a tie the Supreme Court
Get the ball
UB realizes in the middle that it's a 2/3
Wow and that makes even less sense historically just because the vice president president
Weren't originally on a ticket
Together right it was whoever whoever got the the first and second post book
Sew-in that's
Situation
If the vice president is the guy who got the second-most votes in was like
Hey somehow this one vote I'm going to test makes me president this is non-partisan guys
Ripped it all
Yeah so that
Inspires very little confidence whenever Alex goes on these rants about how they're not going according to
I could con
Tucson and he says stuff like that I just got to think like
Alright you're not good source for this or the information
I'm going to go ahead and check out
The people most likely to carry a constitution in their pocket or somehow also the people least likely
Play two of Reddit
Kind of amazing
Anyway the Dagobah stew desperate cuz they're breaking Constitution doing all this impeach
Stuff
And that means
False flag from stuff
Understand
I think you know this better than I
This is real
The globalist want civil unrest they want a war
They're probably looking to bomb Federal buildings and blame it on talk radio like I didn't 95
What they saw as the voice of the people
Tell me the internet this time
And so it was yummy mashed shootings or bombings
Brother false-flag to create racial and cultural division
We're entering the zone right now
Everybody's gotta be alert
Academy watchful
Woodlawn forcement because this country fighting for his life this is very serious
The next 300-plus days are Max Amore
Maximum
This country is at War
All I hear is Alex being aware that the
The community
That he
Inspires
Disconnected with
Yep are in such of mode
That bomb in the building is pasa
Yeah yeah yeah like all I hear is it like
Okay we are in a situation where
Extreme element of
Our side
Put very easily
So unstable person
You could very easily
The song tragedy happening to me is preemptive
Narrative building
Man the number of
Emails and
Tweets and all this s*** that he's aware of
All from his people pointing
But like all of this stuff is
Create an atmosphere where he's like
I know that somebody who listens to my show may very well do
And I better
Get in front of this request
Possum yeah yeah
It got everything that it's going to happen already knows that somebody is about to do it but the climate that easy
Can't not know
Not in my climate you're well
There's a possibility
Yeah it is the same way there was
Verizon
I understand that
L-lysine
Is crack
Yeah call IC is the the Geico awareness if there's a possibility we better be ready if that had him
So we'll go build this narrative in advance
I don't think it is unless you pay attention
Is I think
I think if you buy into Alex's
Probably would see that as like
Yeah yeah yeah
Lazarbeam
Right like I think if you're not aware that's okay
Here's where everything
Alex starts taking calls
And you get a caller who asked one of the more upsetting question
That I've ever heard
How do you shave
Your privates if not it's okay
Question is along the lines of
What is the time to start shooting people and
Follow up
Who should I point my gun at
Now I'm going to play this clip in its entirety the little bit longer
But I think it's important to see
See how Alex
Response to this question
So here's my question
Hypothetical situation hypothetically
Some point in the neck
Montpelier
The Democrats get their way through illegal means
What happened to go Connecticut
I've been trying to get through
People like me
You know I mean
Neighbors that are Democrat
People
I know some pretty crazy liberals that
Do some pretty crazy things but
We've got a Caballo.
Representative
People that call themselves Democrats
I mean the average individual is not in a position to reactive
Violence
Trump economy but old people hostage
Legislatively accept open borders and globalism
And and
Turn the economy back on like they did when Obama got in they turn the economy off
Drano bomb a partially back on once he got in so obviously
The police aren't yet
You remember when I sent the guy to try to kill the Republican baseball team
Caucus
Call installation other they tried
How to fire the gun right but he went and found
The leadership
So
What you have there what the
What did he just say
Right
Cuz all that stuff in the immediate answer to the question
Is buffer that's just
Valentine
The actual answer to the question begins when he says
Isn't it
The guy who went and shot it
Scalise
Had the right idea
Because it was the other team who did
Whatever the case
Alex's
Expressing to this caller
Democratic Leadership is where
Go go get them
That was when things get hot
That was a guy asking
Permission hypothetically
In the same way that he's that that some do to be like in 4 a.m.
Hypothetically if I asked you out on a date
How should I do it
India
Because if the answer is yes
You're like haha I'm actually do it'll be a no you're barely hiding behind hypothetically
Asking for a friend yeah that's
Bucked up
Anthony response
You know he eat
Equivocates a little
I'm not saying you should hunt down Democrats
Cuz I think he realizes we gotten into dicey water here
Anybody should go Target Democrats like that
Civil War guns and
Cracking down and stuff
These are firing tube
General
High-value Target
Wheelhouse
But everything that you described as being
Characteristics of being in that wheelhouse are the features of your rhetoric
Stay going after Patriot leaders hunting them down
All you talk about is how these lawsuits against you are the government and the globalist
Trying to take you down you are the leader of the Patriots of your conception that qualification has been filled
Gun
Every single day their stories about how they're going after the gun
Yep all of the qualifications for the
A situation wherein you might hunt down the Democratic Leadership
Is satisfied
If you listen to his show
You giving this
F****** answer that is so discordant
That is so out of lot like
Know what you think
Izzy's dance
Dancing around
You don't you don't know what the answer is
But the answer is irresponsible
I think the answer in his heart is
Is it bad for business if you start shooting people
But it's good for business if I tell you to shoot people and you don't
It's good for business if I make sure to not tell you to do this
Do it'll be a false flag
Yeah if you know
You got it you got to do what you got to do
This is really bad
But he wants you to know not to be violin
Offensively but then he also later talks about how a good defense
What is a good offense
It's a little bit murky
But
Hope you violent there's another solution
There's big riots in the street people
Take care of your children get the word out
It's all information Warfare at this point
To counter whatever they removed from
Vintage go confront
Chain Reaction must watch info Warrior
Citizen's arrest on Adam Schiff
Just as incredible as this
So the answer is make me viral content
Yep
Hey look I know you're asking me
Who I should shoot at if the trouble happens
Make me a video
Actually there are high value targets in the police had the right idea
Yeah right
Make me a video
Right
That is why the first try to get me promotional ads
Stop liking monetize
Hit me some videos
Bananas
Does bananas that anybody would act
It makes sense like in the olden times when everybody was f****** stupid and starving all the time but we're with we're now
You know who this is now this is not how you should be interacting with a caller who asks you who do I point my
Yeah please do not cosplay steampunk Civil War on a f****** radio show
If someone calls in and ask who I should point my gun at
You should either talk them down or
Get off the air gun at get them
The ground instead of a deer
Instead Alex keep stalking
Intuit and the collar
Reframes the quest
To ask
Where's the lion
Military
Do the right thing
I get the real question I'm asking what
What is the where is the the legal
Line that gets crossed
Stage some stuff make us all look bad
This is the bad guy
And then everybody that could pitch like me websites not going to happen
Happy
Alex already knows with the prior context of this question is
Who should I point my gun at
When does caller is asking where is the line legally
It's already crossed
He's talking about
The question is already at yeah
A Perales to emphatically in immediately
Interrupt
That is
Incitement
In a certain
Consent
You could
Read that as him being like
It's fair game yeah
Yeah
Alex I've already told you the smart thing to do and I've already told you that the conditions for it have technically been
He can't be this oblivious
To not realize that this is
A message that this caller could very easily be getting
This is so dangerous
This is really really really dangerous
Yeah I think this guy is a
Expressing
Common confusion
I ate like a very American
Confusion
About
When to do
Revolution
Because if you go back and look at the original Revolutionary War
All of the conditions that caused that
Are probably
You could consider far less extreme
In regards to
Debatable
So that confusion of like both lionizing and and celebrating the Revolutionary War as
The best thing we could have done
Ever
With
Continued a non-violent soap
You know it's really difficult for a lot of these
Especially these Gunn weirdo.
Yeah I think it is
Is it is
I agree
So the answer is really
Revising
The past
Is Trump should have just
Everybody up
So Alex
Says that he should have just jailed opposition
He's almost giving a list of targets
There should have been indictments a long time ago because there weren't indictment it created a vacuum relief people to run wild
Calling
Instead of calling your Senators represent
Portland
These criminals are acting against
And I go to these little C apartment they haven't been getting it safely long which they need that pressure put on them
Ford Foundation people in
If it goes Connecticut
It is another word kinetic
So yeah
Look beat the issue here
Is that the caller has already asked at the beginning of this when it goes kinetic
At the end of this is Alex's going out to break
Not only is he saying
Soros and soros's son
Everybody involved in the CFR
Liberal professors
American Turd
These are the enemies when it goes kinetic
This is he if you can't read that any other way than to say
Weather a first of all the line is already been cross guy
And
These are the people who are the enemies when you have already asked me who should I point my gun at yeah it May 8th makes
Even BB then see a fancy yeah
If they just
Kind of logical sense
He's telling
Is Guy a list of people who are the enemies
He should be pointing his gun at when it goes Connecticut
This is not okay
This is this is like
A black what's happening
Is I hear this discordant
Cognitive
Dissonance
Where it's like
He's saying what he knows he should be saying whenever the question is direct like
Who should I be trying to murder
And he's like you should not be murdering people make me a promotional video right but then whenever it's
Rephrase
He can't understand that the
Questions are connect
He thinks they're completely separate
So then he's like then he gets back into head legal now it'd be okay because of that someone
I still don't know who this is illegal
I think it
Something is illegal
It's just
Wrong there's no way
The only
There's no way that you can understand words the way they're meant to be understood
And not think that he is giving people an idea of who they
The only way you can defend yourself is that you say he doesn't understand the word
Or how to apply there so he needs to be taken off air a public safety
The message
He is dangerous by
Is on
Inability
Yeah absolutely it is irresponsible to allow him to
Ba-Ba-Reeba able to speak to this
Civil War is not Gunn Connecticut
Okay but one worth it is Connecticut Vermont
No okay we're on
Play the clip of
A crime committed
Well now College official don't buy Christmas presents
The fight climate change
These people are just sick
Is complete bulshit story here
Is about somebody works for William and Mary name
Calandra Waters Lake
Step back and remember that the reason for the gift is to show someone you care
So is buying a gift the best way to do that
Going out and doing something with the recipient spend time with that may be a better option
Now is some Christian puns
Where to say the exact same thing making the point that Christmas has become too commercialized in the Jesus is the reason for the season
Alex would 100% be in favor of that antique materialist mess
He believes in Asia Christian
Mutiso on board because this person was giving the same advice and then
Minding your carbon footprint all of a sudden it's devils
It should so dumb that even the article on Infowars had to call itself out
Ironically however some of her other tips are actually quite useful in terms of combating materialism and consumer
Prism even if that wasn't
Exactly the entire
This is which I say go to bed assholes f*** off
You're not good luck you not going to make this War on Christmas s*** work if that's the best
No this is
You can't have the when do we start shooting in the Civil War on the same episode as
When do we start shooting in the war on Christmas
Like you're there these people a cartoon
That's cartoonish
Consider that the war on Christmas which has been going on since the f****** late 80s now
Combined with the Civil War you're like well both of these are equal airtime
Tulsa with Neil Gorsuch people were more mad about him chilling a book on Fox & Friends and not other Outlet
Wow he's a Supreme Court Justice
People who pointed out that he said Merry Christmas we're all doing it to make fun of how he made a point of saying
The anchor said
I love how you say that
You're making fun of that because Fox News have maybe we aren't allowed to say Merry Christmas thing
Talking point in the last few years
So kind of makes it look like a wink
But he's making fun of that less actually offended that any
Wait so he's going on Fox
And friends and selling his bully who's Fox
Confetti was on Fox News
So
Alex
Is memory
Money talks about
Noah
Use the inaugural
He was a hero
On that day
I really don't remember him being
That day was war
What do you understand me
Which war the Civil War the war on Christmas or the war between Vermont and Connecticut was a lease permission
The Connecticut War on Christmas
At the inauguration
Paragon connect
Alright the story is not
You know I was just having flashbacks to
3 years and 3 months ago
4 years ago
January 2017 and they had a big
Steel fence around the whole Mall
8 a.m.
And
I didn't check where the VIP Everett was the ticket
I just want to walk the mall
Families with children video
Ran over a mob of them in the police ran over and arrest us
Scream out of my shed
But shame on you
Hero
The very top one in there with all the
Eddyville wasn't there
Agreements with the police where they could be
For the federal police
Just like in the documents we got
Front porch
Police that they're allowed to commit the crime certain areas
It's all staged
And I just got so angry
Cuz it took me hours to get in
And ice
They were all nice and there was no line that you just walk through
The American people are being Sat On by the DC police in League with the antifa
North Korea
These people are dangerous we cannot let them get control the country
Suggest the police are in cahoots
It's stories.
Through it all exaggerated version of the
The version of that story I've heard him telling
It's all just to confirm with the fakes
Soros antifa contracts that he found a match
Is false
Documents the story like that that makes me worry if at the end of this
We both go inside
Because
That is the least real thing
That I think I've ever heard from anybody
He's just
You just gaslighted me so hard I'm like listening to this
Using that like part of my my
Bring this like well you should listen to human beings York
Person that because you would act trustworthy so you can assume that they would act trustworthy towards you
And it's just such a lie
It's just not real it's a fundamental flaw of the shows
You should I don't know I think I've gone insane
So I think there's a good chance
We're in the clear but so far I mean
Man 3 years 3 years time it might say a code word
3 years has hard time I know but I mean when you're looking at
You know a dime maybe maybe your 7 is when you can go crazy would be so if you're rich
So Alex gets back on the phone we've already had one guy who's
Blackheads
One of the most f*****-up calls I've heard on his show ever
And he's very flippant and just nonchalant about starting the second Civil War then he
You get the caller who's got a
Right he's talking in this
Is brogue
Yeah and then
Parabolic
I'm like this guy's doing fake
Yeah and the middle of it
To his real voice
Like you know
How I sounded like I was Scottish
But I'm not that's like the impeachment
Sounds like
Yeah go to bed comedian I do Impressions like I was on America's Got Talent and
I wanted to play all of it
Yeah babe get these places that was in the small town and
No they wouldn't let me perform and not like
Wow and then I got hired by SNL and I don't want to talk about that anymore
Play all of it but it's way too long and just playing a tiny piece of
Wouldn't do it justice
Suffice it to say guy doesn't fix Scottish accent
Says he's a comedian and then Alex offers
Okay so that's
Great that sounds like exactly how that would work yeah it was very surreal
This guy sounds a little bit like fat bastard so I got to let him do the fourth hour from now on that's just
Videoshow
So I would get another caller who does
That's it
Plug Broward
What is product
Very excite
But then he has a pitch
Beretta shirt
That I think would be important
My God
You have changed my life turboforce has
Is changed my life
I was raped in 2016
Largely in part because of you
About a year ago
He got body
Super silver super silver for your teeth
Rachel + red pill
You changed my life
What I really want to say first off
I'm an artist
I was born and raised in the Kansas City area
But I moved to Northern California in 2011
I've been social-networking since 1987
And the information Warfare is exactly
Where we need to be
I had an idea for a t-shirt which is why I called
It would show it would be picture of Anne Frank
Olean AR
Or another kind of gun
And the caption would say
Anne Frank
Needed a gun
Hijacked our women
We need women
To totally agree we need women to identify with being strong and empowered and not
Slaves the global Insight or like that's a great idea
And Frank need a gun on the front
Don't let dictator take your guns
And
You're absolutely right that's a great idea sir that's a great idea
Holyshit yeah I did not know Banksy wasn't in for it
I would just I can't imagine how poorly that shirt would go over there's just no you just can't parody
You just can't they're just better at it
They're better at parroting themselves
Then I could ever I would never even
Consider that can't put a hat on a hat driver would never consider that
That's bananas
So we we have one last clip your from the 19th
But it's Alex talking about how you
Tell Dima
You can pick them out of a crowd
That's by their eyes designer shirts
With Frank holding a gun
And then Alex starts wandering and giving a
Biblical justification
For killing people who are demons
Is that right
Right which isn't good
Given the prior context of everything
Then if you look at these Global if they always have that look in their eyes like they're winning or so powerful
They're enjoying it those are haughty eyes and men have them too
People always have those eyes
Like they're going to get you it's funny
Absolutely
Hebrew
Blood
Killing people
That didn't attack you
Killing people that didn't mean
Killing
Human Sacrifice I want them all dead
Killem
And I'm not saying God for killing people
The Bible says
Flower
The Bible
Holyshit
You know it's the people most likely to carry around a Bible in their pocket who are least likely to have read the f****** bottle
I don't think you can have any less responsible thing you could say on are then I'm not saying you should go around killing people
I'm just telling you what the Bible says
I think you have entered in
Into witty
Bad territory
Jesus
The show wraps up on the 9th
I felt like
That's exactly kind of what I expected but actually Morris
Extreme
Response theme
Like I knew that he wasn't going to be
He caught like on his heels
Off-balance but surprised
I wasn't prepared for first of all
The angle that he has
To be so weak
Like the plans that the globalist had me so dumb
So poorly thought-through
It's so we're just almost
Winning it
It doesn't it doesn't indicate to me in any way that he sat down and thought like alright what are we going to do
Nothing like the Democrats in the globalist
Evil plans have a loose improvisational feel to them almost
I would have expected a Keno's that the impeachment was going to happen
At some point
For a while
Yeah get your goddamn writers room together
And have them come up with
Something inspire
They just hired his first writer
Scottish
Yeah and I did I did
Expect there to be some sort of a
Extreme
Violin
Undertone expected to be nearly that
Over that
That's f***** up but it does
Track with the disorder Verizon
Temperature of the show over the last couple
There has been a far more consistent
Discussion of the Time to Kill
When is killing okay
Who should we kill
It does seem like that conversation is normalizing
Very much
Tututix not that it was not
A while back
I think it's something to keep an eye on
Anyway Alex gets in
And look dude
Okay then I just been trying to pee
Peach Trump
Pence is also on the
On The Chopping Block
Okay
So it's now all happening this broke this morning
And
Open up article from flashback
January 2000
11 months ago
We're not going to show those articles. More
I'm going to go to rebroadcast for wild snowbigdeal
Because I need to get prepared for this and imma go with terminal
And I'm going to pull
Eclipse from 2017
Clemson 2018
Rodger Stone
Specifically
Laid out here on are exactly how they would trigger all of this how did you not do this pre-show
How did how little
Do you care
They're like I'm going to start the show and then within a minute within 2 minutes
I'm going to rebroadcast cuz I got to actually do prep I got to find those articles my staff can't do it they're not finding the right art
Articles nothing he does nothing
Prepare for this
I will just talk
He has the easiest job
Yeah and he's still f***** it up
That's amazing
Quite his his ability to fail
Is incredible
Yeah
So anyway the plants 2D pants
But then Pelosi gets in office
Then what
Pelosi president
Infowars.com
We told you that
I don't think of the president he's removed
Pelosi then who's ready to run for office
Democratic party wedding promoter convention
She becomes the first woman president
Hillary Rodham Clinton is in it's all set up it's all prepared we told you 2 years ago
With Cotto
Crustacean
We're getting the clips
Total precision
Alright whatever
Anyway that wasn't the plan according to you yesterday but whatever anybody
More wrong
Then somebody who thinks it'll literally total precision
Is that what you're talkin about I'm boggled
I'm boggled
So
Alex is waiting for those clips
Prison turns to find them who doesn't actually go off air
To do that at work
You failed to do before the show
But you know just messing around
Sites to get
Real
F****** xenophobic
Bucket white nationalist
So here's the beginning
Really they're just a salting
Reality
And then having you and reports out saying we're going to replace Europe with Muslims and the us we want 600 million
Brought in the next 30 Years the Us official un policy
Right here
The ATL says
They're lying in the
Upcoming UK elections is a month ago
They're saying that
There's a thing called replacement migration to
Get rid of
Muslims they specifically say
Middle Eastern Muslims and North
African Muslims patible with each other
Do they don't want any Christian mugs Christian Africa
They don't want any
Nature worship
Dieter
Does the Muslim kill them
We're going to have Muslims they're the ones that are compatible
Because there was an Austrian Hungarian Prince
Pull it up
That whole plant 100 years ago he's the guy that invented the modern Olympics
To bring in Muslim
Napoleon
Started the Islam had a plan to bring the Muslims into Europe
At 2
Because they were more Muslims than there were Christians in Europe then to you could take over
They're one group that acts as one
But Sacha Baron Cohen
As already
Cast the dice
The ATL doubt literally
Is it Islamic organization
Whatever
Alex isn't totally lying
Inasmuch as the UN did release a report in 2001 called replacement migration is it a solution to declining in
An aging population
The problem as it always is if Alex is that he doesn't understand what he didn't read
Executive summary of the document Begins by explaining that the report will layouts
6 possible scenarios they see as possibilities
Based on the current population Trends in France
Germany Italy
Japan Republic of Korea the Russian Federation the United Kingdom
And United States
These scenarios were differentiated by Computing different levels of migration
How it would affect the
Specifically in terms of population
And the report is very clear saying quote
These are not meant to be recommendations in any way but illustrations
Hypothetical scenarios
Alex takes all his numbers about you and recommendations for immigrants from
Because that's the one where the numbers were the highest
That was their scenario of how many immigrants would be needed to keep the ratio of people aged 15
64 the work
Forced the ratio of them to people 65 or older
The highest possible rate
That it would have been
Again the report is clear about what is
It is
Quote
Readers should keep in mind that the results of scenario 6 are for illustrative purposes only
Given the Assumption the current age structure of the population would remain unchanged
Future
The resulting large number of migrants
Needed should be considered totally unrealistic
Says that in the document
In the discussion section it's
Discuss how unfeasible this scenario is
Literally saying quote
This scenario is clearly not realistic
Therefore immigration cannot prevent aging of the population
The conclusion offered in the report is it
Exactly the opposite of Alex what Alex would have you believe
Also I would love to
To see how Alex
Explains that the number of immigrants
Needed in scenario 6
Is five times higher for the Republic of Korea than it is for all of Europe
I thought he was saying that this is all about flooding the Westwood
But I bet if you presented with a spoon of the sort of rebuttal you just say that
Huriya is
Yeah sure why not
Immigration North Korea is the east
South Korea is the West didn't you remember the Korean War that's where the Patriots 10K
Immigration is one part of the report but it's really about much more and as to do with aspects of the question of the changing age.
Distribution in population
They bring up issues about how the ratio of worker to retirees is affected by the age of retirement
And Country
The level the level of labor force participation
Change that.
And how the problems are of a higher rate of retirees to workers
Can be offset by increased contributions from workers into programs designed to help the elderly those swords
Solve all sorts of problems
On the Run
Airport is much much larger than what Alex presents but that's because he doesn't care about the wait what the UN is actually doing or study
We're looking at
You just want you to know
They want to bring in most
It's because they want to conquer you
And the best way to do that is
Bring again Muslim
This is on the one hand a horrible mishandling of his Swordsman
It shows that he has no grasp ignore any interest in
The actual issues that he's cover
More importantly on the other hand it shows a deeply internalized islamophobia
That's so far past the point of acceptability I don't even really know how to address it
If Alex thinks that Muslims all act as one
Then I don't know what to say about it except to say he's a
He's turning a minority group into a unified block
Which only makes his audience fear and hate the
Individuals can
Pain in that group more
They're no longer individual
They're mindless parts of a unified block that only exists in this country because the UN is using them
Concord
That kind of thinking is repulsive
And I really feel like that's pretty good demonstration valances
Horrible white identity leanings
And xenophobia
To drive this point home
I read the UN report and the words Muslim and Islam don't appear anywhere in the
Sure of course not that would it would be eat it would be too easy if they did one plate I would typically releases
Instead
Good God.
Alex is just a f*** you to me person
Alex Azar
So mad that it's not even mention
You don't even have the f******
Time to look for one spot where it might be measured that
Also the founder of modern Olympics
This is not an austro-hungarian print it was Pierre de coubertin French historian and philosopher so
I'm pretty sure Alex is just make
You shut up that he read on some dumb dumb right now
Man that is
Unreal
That is just
Totally and it gets worse
Because a caller calls in
And wants to bring up another
Pretty xenophobic
Narrative about the death of Katie Kate steinle
Which is the woman who was shot by a bullet ricocheted
Accidentally fired by undocumented immigrant
We talked about that case quite a bit
I wouldn't actually even
Include this clip
It would be background
If it weren't for how Alex
Tells this story
He adds
So many details to this story
That I've not heard him even report before and Arkham
Wheatley made of
Trump at a chance a long time ago.
Insurgency Act
Shut up.
41 was shot to death and what did they do they allowed Sanctuary cities
Well you're a Mexican
You've been deported five times you're allowed to murder and they said he's a victim and now he's suing the jail where he was held
The back for fun
How does that say
Does that make you feel in America
You don't want anybody because you just shoot a young woman in the back for no reason
Because she was beautiful
What
Is there a lot of people jealous of beautiful women
Gorgeous
Beautiful
And he killed her because he was pissed and jealous and thought that that was his her older
Boyfriend with her dad hugging her
They were crying and talking about family members that have just died
I saw that body song
This clip is a serious
Serious problem
But one as we discussed in previous episodes Kate steinle death is he
Tragic event
I am not in any way taking away from that
But it was an Autumn
A judge acquitted Jose Yanez garcia-zarate of first-degree murder second-degree murder involuntary
Manslaughter
And even assault with the
Semi-automatic firearm
Because it was clear that you did not mean to fire the bullet
It ricocheted
And then hits.
He was charged with being a felon in possession of
The firearm but that conviction was overturned by the court of appeals
Because the previous Jerry was not instructed properly
About what constitutes
Being in possession of a gun
Garcia Zarate found
Gun that was wrapped in rags
What you picked up not knowing it was a gun
In the process the gunfire
This is an example of a horrible tragedy
And I've nothing but a thief or the steinle family and what they've had to go through
That being said the way the right-wing media has used this case is indicative of a very extreme hostility towards him
There's no evidence that garcia-zarate was a possession of the gun let alone that he intended to shoot a wall
Knowing that the bullet would bounce off in Hit
Dying Light
And yet this has been the rally in case
Brezina phobic assholes like Alex and everyone at Infowars
And I think this clip is Alex letting it slip a little bit too much
As to why
The stuff about garcia-zarate killing steinle because she was beautiful is completely made
The idea that he thought that her father was her older boyfriend and he couldn't stand
The jealousy is absolutely not based on anything
Real but it does rely on pretty standard white-supremacist ropes
About knowing
What Alex is doing this clip is legitimately no different from
From pro-segregation
Propaganda about black men having uncontrollable lust for white women
But it would act out violently if not kept in their place
Yep without you
Too far out back off
Under this roof
Alex's pretending that he's reporting FAQ
But literally all this is him talking about his
Feeling
His feelings
Are f****** racist
He feels like garcia-zarate killed steinle because she was beautiful and a white woman he was jealous that he couldn't be with her
But that
All that is
Alex is feeling
He's making that up because he believed
Do you believe that because it fits
Internalized racism
Is it feel his head
Thank you presenting it to his audience
Sfac
Yeah no
And it is not
I mean
If that was
Anybody
With even a little bit more power
They worded that
That clear lawsuit
That's not even a little bit
Absolutely going after Hammerhead he doesn't have the brains or ability to go after them
Put Power inside I think you still might have a case
That's what I'm saying no they know they know or at least he should buy now
That that is clearly
Actionable legal
But there
Boy it's a good Target if you
Recognize how much money it cost to do anything in the judicial
Bright because
That is
There's no way that that's not
That's
He just told this bulshit story
About this guy
Turning him into the
F******
Raving lunatic
Immigrants who can't
Control himself around to a beautiful white woman is there on Thursdays though transformed
No way that's not defamation
That's my sense of it again
Not as a lawyer Point yeah
He has every reason to no it's not
That's just f***** up
Yeah that should be that dude deserves all about I've never heard
That
Version of this told and the way Alex is telling it is so full of like
Feeling
All the stuff we heard on the previous day or it's just
Wrote Going Through the Motions of this is a globalist plan
Beallsville
Yeah I know that's that this person
Sun was lusting for Kate
Steinle
And had to kill her that's so much
That's so much the f******
And to sort of like this is what we do and this is what I love
Send it.
That just do
That f******
Jim Crow era
We have to do this and here is why
Because
Imagine your daughter being around a black man
It has the same
You don't want that to happen
It relies on that tradition very heavily and I don't believe that Alex's
And some way aware that that's what he's doing
So
Alex gets to
I made this club I just Captain maybe as a palico
Cleanser because it's another one of these indication
Receive
Over and over again of
Just like such
When it's completely fake but it does seem like he's enjoying that
Just faking it you know in the same way is over the saxophone
Belong To The City earlier
Seems to have a good time when he's being a racist
And when
He is yelling
In and out of breaks the only times he has a good time or when
When he's singing
Drinking and being a racist
Now that's a good text
Expose don't say that
I know I'm just
So do you know what I don't do assume that every single texting is exactly the same and functions as
Is one single block and that's why we have no problem with the UN killing them
Goodonya I'm very brave
So Alex gets
Call
On this
Episode from a guy named range
And he apparently had to do believe you was on a boat at one time
Unlock Galaxy did not give it up to
No
This is interesting because
I think he's right here
Metaphor about what
Needs to do
Security
We were working on a boat one time a large vessel that was actually
Pirates Cay
Generally don't have a boat suitable fast
When that didn't happen the captain put the boat on lockdown that everybody went to their cabins and lock the door
Room-to-room
Clearing the boat out
Maybe it's time that
The president looks
Country on lockdown
Analogy
I can't imagine
Thinking like listening to Alex's show and imagining
Scenario where
A caller would call in and say hey you know what I think
Executive needs to
Unilaterally put the country into his strict lockdown much like you have pirates on a boat and got to clear it door to door
How could you even possibly
We can see that that would be
An acceptable line of conversation
On the show it's so far afield of what he pretends
To be about or pretended to be about yeah I know that
That is that is genuinely
That is I mean
That's genuinely everything that you've ever fought again
Everything literally
Part of the f******
God damn Constitution is that we can't
You think they can't force us out the corner people
F****** country
Started
Because somebody did that
Lot of reasons
I'm saying
Part of the idea is always at the Constitution
The Revolutionary War is amazing
And literally they're doing stuff
That the founding fathers were like
Let's make sure this never happens
That's insane
Which doesn't just say that's a great analogy
Doubles down
Pirates they're not Americans
Alex wants to record it to put out as its own Standalone video this guy saying
Calling in and saying the Trump needs to clear the ship
From Pirates
He does not do a good job
When they come back
Take does he also record play like a clip from him
You know like
They 2015 are saying that
The president is a dictator and a tyrant who is trying to lock people down and go
Door-to-door taking their guns
Did he put those two back back-to-back and show that
He's ideologically
Find
No
Examination the fight against the globalist
2 strong
Take too much time
He said that
He said that Obama was going to go door-to-door make everybody stay inside
He was a tyrant
Going to take the globalist gun
Oh I didn't realize that take a globalist
Man
You can tell the globalist
Because I didn't possess
See you there
Anyway Alex
You know he doesn't get the clean take he's looking
4 but he
He does offer
The exact
Excuse
You would expect from a crypto-fascist
For why you need to enact fashion
All out
How you did Security on a ship that I forgot boarded by Pirates
And what the captain did that emergency
Martial law
I don't want Civil War the globalists are putting
He made us do it is not it's only one martial law
So yeah
Stupid s***
Operating theory is that these guys would rather destroy
America then
Share it with not white
Who Woulda thought
That a group
Look for decades
Is Ben
Primarily anti-government
Yeah I would do I just stay over all of a sudden
We are super into this most government
We would like the most government we would like it to crack down on us
When I say us
It makes it makes you think that maybe
Just maybe
Anti-human
Holloman
So Christianity Today
Publication came out in support of removing Trump
This caused a little bit of
There is not a crisis but Alex now hates Christianity Today
Hard as real short walk to get there
Caller who actually Alex might not have brought it up at all if this caller doesn't bring
I didn't bring it to the table
That look
The way they're covering
The story breaking news
It's been coming out the Trump has had a love child with one of his
Closest friends
Teammates
And that he was worried about that coming out
And he actually he actually had him killed
Of course I'm joking ok
But hear me out
As much as a shock is that was the here
And I'm sure everybody was shocked by it
I'm calling out Christians today
Because
Christians will wave the flag of Christianity and
By the way
But Christians will will
Say that David was a man after God's Own Heart
But I see the hypocrisy that's happening now again
Christians
That are not standing with their
With our president
With their leader
Whether you like him or not the Bible says that we are to pray for our leaders
If you like him or not
Today
Top of drugs
Christianity Today comes out calling for the removal of
Donald Trump
He should be out there I think.
Completely disgusting
Whether you like them or not you pray for your leaders unless his name is Barack Obama
Hey Dan Dan whether you like him or not
You just admit whether you like them or not you pray for him unless you are there Democrats
This is such b*******
Really dumb for a number of reasons the first is that
David repent
That's a big part of the story
But he's just s***
Such such
Dumb.
But it's so indicative of like a you-know-what last week
Love Christian Dior
Nothing means anything
Yeah that is
Different l
You are now devilettes bananas
Take that
You're going
It's very much
I don't like you know what I'm saying
I think a lot of these
Christian people
Don't really particularly care about what's in the Bible
Don't feel that way they just want to use that book to justify the things they already wanted to do
So Alex
He's been saying along the throughout this
December 20th episode that
The Supreme Court has ruled that
Pelosi can't do what she
She's doing by withholding the impeach
Indictment
Going-to-the-Sun
I had no idea what he was talking about I was waiting for him to get to it
He never did quite a bit down the line
I'm in eat you for that in
With his
Ideas about like
Hey public so dumb they think
Impeachment is
Conviction
And all that
They do though
I think in the same way you could do a man on the street
Free videos
A higher percentage than we would like to think do that
Yeah but I would also bet
The third like
Lo lo engaged
With the news kind of think they're like
Not like stupid
Very likely but
I don't particularly care
About them as people that's not something
Yeah
I would respond to that
Sort of thing by Zayn
Yes education needs to be better that's about it that's
I Gotta Feeling
I don't
Really no
This is.
I'm somewhat inform so are you and she thinks everybody knows the house is just impeachment I just an indictment
Infowars.com
Questionnaire
Bet you can't do what blows he did
They can't demand rules be changed
Or
They don't care because it's a ruthless
Supreme Court ruling on Pelosi
Impeachment demands
The framers did not intend to impose additional limitations on the form of the Senate proceedings
The Supreme Court stated in Nixon vs United States
The fact that you cannot have the house
Telling the Senate what they can do
Supreme Court ruled in that in a federal
They got through at the Supreme Court
The whole article but people need
Don't worry I'm not going to read the whole article and Alex Jones story
Pelosi cannot
Hold up delivering the impeachment
Based on a flawed reading of the 1993 Supreme Court decision Nixon versus
United States
That case had nothing to do with the situation where it now but it does include that one sentence
Somehow
Still employed Infowars kid videos
Used as a hinge
To make it sound relative
The quote the framers did not intend to impose additional limitations on the form of the Senate proceedings
Alex right at the Cornerstone of
The article on Infowars
Out of context that kind of appears to be saying that the Senate gets to decide every
But really in regards to this specific complaint being heard it doesn't really
What is it with you and this
It's always like you should run understand things within the context
Sandwich they were sick and then they
The time. That's also
Damn it there's so much contact What If instead
I told you just don't believe whatever you wanted to believe
In this case a judge named Walter Nixon who'd been in
Sue to have a salary reinstated because he believed
Senate rules
11 had been broken by
Buried itself out
In the impeachment process
His argument was rejected in the Supreme Court held that
Did the framers really were only requiring
That the Senators be under oath
The two-thirds vote for conviction to pass
And that the Chief Justice presided over the case
When it's the president
It's not required in other MP
Yeah just in case
Is the presidential Inn
That's so funny that a judge who is
Impeached
Came up with a flawed legal
Other than these three things
The framers did not intend to impose additional limitations on the farm
This legitimately has nothing to do with how and it beats
An indictment is transferred from the house to the Senate
Is there any actual case law surrounding this I would assume Alex wouldn't come up with this
Completely unrelated cases
Smoking Gun
Really too bad the Barnes isn't
I'm still around to ramble about lies and libel
That's
Just what do you need a constitutional lawyer
Literally like that you can make your own f****** rules
That's the whole point it now
So
I'm going to skip these next couple clips
Cuz they're just Alex
Rambling about Howard this
Whole planet
Give Hillary is president
We kind of we kind of got it we get the tattoos idea if anybody actually like if we ever got it
Into that situation
Hillary was
Somehow tried to sneak in
I think you get a
The backlash from the left I think that would be the one thing that causes an act
Will third-party too high
When is everybody on the left is being like
We got it now
F*** this you'd like to think that that's what flakka the Democrat like to think that's what that would happen in
You know it's a nice thought maybe it would maybe it wouldn't
But I think that you would have
Incomplete
Breakdown on the left
Yeah from that saying nothing of what the right
Response would be
Just
Within the last you would have
Disinterest
Honestly that might be the first time that I mean it whenever I say if Hillary Clinton becomes president in 2020
I'm moving
A note
Eat my hat
So Alex goes back to the phone
You take the caller who as all of these
Long
Plug for his product
And then Alex
Have a string of Lies
Everything that he exposed
Nobody knew about Bohemian Grove nobody knew about ft nobody knew about Bilderberg
Nobody
I'm sorry wasn't Alex's the color Hood the string of Lies
All those things are not true of Alex
Some of them are just not true
Like the Bohemian Grove was covered in reported on a dryer
Other things
Those are not sure if Alex either
Picture of Bill Cooper
They are they are true of the person
Whose Legacy Alex's
Stealing destroying upon himself burning
Yeah it's it's really interesting
Interesting dynamic
I'm interested in looking more into that in the future but it is very
We went over this weekend
The most honest way for a man like that to go I guess
Yeah I hate I hate it but it's
Exactly the end always said
I don't know you're very close to Somali pirate territory
So Alex
He's talking a little bit
A little bit more about that
The Christianity
Needed anything and he sees it as quite a betrayal
And like I said already
You turn on Trump
And you are now the devil
You see that you're in this
A lot of great people are evangelicals the Grassroots
But the leadership
Christianity Today
Billy Graham's son supports Trump Christianity Today is not run by them
Globalist Trump's bad
That is devilish
Trump defending Christians right
Christianity Today is a den of deviled
Are there works you shall know them
So I mean you just
If you fall out of Step your devil
Definition of Christianity is supporting Trump
According to Alex
Emerging of religious and political ideas which is
Like we are already had
Suck leanings of
Authoritarian dictator kind of
Feelings for Alex
We are we are merging that Theocratic I yeah pretty hard
If they remove Trump
You know and
Got him out of office
Then
You know the next
The vice president of course would be
I don't know and
Real den of hell kind of hiding in the bushes
F****** pain you might you might you might think the Christianity Today is
More of the Mind
Trump has done the damage he can do do a lot of the institutions
Inception you know Mike Pence is a pretty good option for us evangelicos maybe it's time to cut bait
On the bull in the china shop and go with a more steady hand
That would be a good start
Decision if you are a zealous
Chris political
And it's not like a Mike Pence's going to suddenly not
Go after abortion Focus
To pretend as priority everything that he just said Mike Pence would do if not as well
Twice as hard bro
31 last clip
And I was just talking to a caller
And this caller has
Horrible
Horrible cousin
And Alex
Seems like most Republicans do overwhelmed
Impeachment
84 walking down the country
Smoking
I'm just taking control sometimes was a dictator
Criminal
Alex
Whether I love that passion because you're not lying down you're awake and you're not just screaming and yelling
Focus point about what's happening
Not saying program points except
You kind of are just nevermind
Reprogramming talkin coin
I love that pants and I love that you're excited about the b******* I've gotten you
Down the line of colors
That's one of the things that
You really see if you look at these colors
Look at the colors that we've had on this show
We have this guy who's internalize the message of
Trump should be a dictator
Clearly puts out whether he
Expresses it that way or not
You have to call or called in about Kate steinle who's expressing this xenophobic
Anti-immigrant position that Alex's
Very clearly fostered in his audience
You got the guy calling in
Who's the Scottish comedian
Now it's clear the air once
People who are
Meyer minor viral stars that he can try and exploit
When is the time start shooting people
Just something is a question that Alex is audience would clearly have based on his
That's the only thing that I imagine that every show they think about
You know you don't have callers calling in
Really robots conversations about how do we ensure the treat peaceful transition of government throughout not just this
Election but all elections to, assuming that we continue to be a democratic Nation
I didn't hear that
You didn't hear that
So
I mean I think at the end at the end of this episode he got like a real problem
And it's the same problem and it's growing
I don't I don't mean this to say like
Something bad's going to happen
Because I think it's entirely possible that one
I don't know if Alex is colors are we
I can't prove that either way
Make the claim that these are all fake all right
But a lot of radio shows do used
Yeah so that's within the realm of possibility
Yeah because
There's an entire possibility that Alex has a miniscule Audience by this point that
Whatever either way what are you putting out into the world
Incredibly talk
And
I do I do think that as
He is irrelevant
To a lot of the larger conversation in the world that is definitely true
But this show is getting BoRics
The things that are
Being much more openly
Disgust
Are the things that are really really fun
Yeah the over white nationalism that is it
Best through his retelling of a
Fake version
Of Kate steinle murder
Is
Insane the
Unacceptable in without doubt legally action
The way that he expresses this
His misreading of this 2001 un
Population study
Into being all Muslims act as one
Is it incredibly dangerous
Yep not to minimize it because I think he's very serious
Kind of Fairly
Standard for him maybe that one's not as much of an escalation pads
Islam islamophobia in
Anti-islam
Yeah but
Did the open discussion
Mission of violin the open discussion of when is the time
To kill people who should we be targeting
Those conversations
Are starting to happen on his show a bit more than I recall
Yeah so that's that that is my big point
It's worth noting that yeah
Those guys
Probably work
Where other people work with them
Right and those people have no idea that's sitting next to them is or maybe they do or may well yeah
I'm just like
I'm sure they tried to sell him brainforce
IDK I don't have
A lot of people who are Alex Jones fan
Hands are open
Right
Lebanon future either I don't know maybe there's a lot of crypto info Warriors
I have no idea
I just think like
I don't know it's really hard for me to put a button on this but I'm I'm trying
The express
That this is Escalade
Yeah the tone
And
And what is okay
To talk about on
The show
Whether or not that's because Alex is allowing those conversation
More or the audience is
Picking up on
Anything but you also do notice that a lot of these things that are the worst
Are the product of his colors bringing stuff up
Alex is terrible on his oh don't get me wrong I'm not saying that he's off the hook
Write the parts of this episode that I think are the most f*****-up
Are things that the callers have brought into the conversation without question
And to me that indicate
The audience
Is responding to things
That are on the show
And be like well this is
What's going on let's talk about it
That's really bad
That's me as a really bad sign
Cuz if Alex is audiences diminishing
What is he going to do what's the business decision
Follow your audience
You don't lead the audience anymore
You can't afford to
Also if you're in a civil war scenario you want to be at the
Yeah I don't know I just you know what I wanted eulogize Godwin's law
I really think that it was a valuable law for internet discourse early on
And now
You know it's dead because
It only functions if both parties
Are not actual
When one party is just like yeah we're not
Well I guess it's not valuable anymore
Game over
I don't I don't I don't know what
Outside of
As this process rolls along
Lesbian p
Richmond trial happen
I just expect that trend
Continue but I don't know if it's at
Like I don't I don't
I don't know how scared anybody should be about Alex putting this out into the world
I mean obviously shouldn't do this
But I don't know I don't want to be alarmed and I don't want to scare p
Cuz I think I think ultimately
Maybe no one's listening
Yeah
I'm not even that worried about
What happens there
It's only because
The only way the Trump is going to be removed from office is if he
Does if he keeps talking
I mean it
Pretty clear that he's the only one who's going to incriminate himself past the point of them defending
Like no matter what evidence bring brings forth right the Republican party's going to defend him
The only person who's going to make it impossible not to remove him from office
It does seem
So
Then all these fears of like all when they remove them when they get rid of it are all going to deflate
So hard
Right
After after the towels over it
A little bit not really because what's going to happen at least based on my understanding of things
Things that have been said like the house is going to continue other investigation
Sure is going to be stories
Coming out about
Think about the Trump Foundation or his businesses
Right
And that
Because of the framing that I would
Will be
Like even though
Trump is going to win
Yeah these are the attempt
Still remove him
Yeah
Prophecy is still validated even if the end conclusion is
Him not being convicted in the right right
They'll be the Colonel's
Reality of his narrative the old made manifest
Best in the world even though
The inevitable conclusion of him probably
Never
Being convinced
Even though that is still descend go along the way there's still the validation
That goes along with it and then once you know the Senate trial concluded like that we were just too strong for
Globus we stop them from being able to
Play their tricks
So now there is a need for a
I just don't know how long that
That this media environment
Can continue to redline
Like I just don't know how long
Trump and how much money
Because they're up there always redlining
They're always getting people
Closest possible to demote like
Every morning on Fox
Or whatever like you're always Redline
And I just don't know how long you can Redline people
Floater the car runs out of gas
I don't I don't I don't even answer that question
Anyway we'll see what happens but till then we have website
Go to bed Jordan we're also on Facebook
And other podcast
Cool apps please download leave a review
Emilio Emilio
I am the juiciest Ice Cube
Alexandra Thurston color