I have great respect for its knowledge B
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Everybody sit around and talk a little bit about Alex
On this day
To ask you one
Have you ever been he's risen
Sorry
He's risen from somewhere
Have you ever seen did you ever go to like a nativity play at your church Christmas Eve or Chris
Christmas day have you ever seen a good one
I'm not positive I could critically review any of the
He wants from my past
I don't know exactly I would say
I have some vague memories of going to like me
Midnight masses was not Catholic
I still think they exist another
Denomination
Never lose beer
Fun I don't know why it is like you're up late
Yeah later than you would be you know that Christmas
Misses that much closer younger absolute
Listen to novel thing
You know you're going to church at midnight
What is weird I don't know why I
Think of nativity scene there's something I drive
Past you know that's that's right that's right
The place that I put something in someone's yard
Somebody in the place
The lights
Another version of that that's along with Christmas
Mysterio
Halloween decorations
Cal decorations
I don't know nothing sticks out in my head
I've seen a bunch of stuff
In-N-Out that manger scene
It has yeah
So I don't know I'm sorry I don't have a great answer for that but I do know a lot about Alex Jones
Methodist podcast about you got it
So Jordan today
I wanted to celebrate this holiday hear this
This Christmas Day by giving myself again
Okay good
That's the reason for the season
I don't know I think you'll be you'll get a charge out of some of this stuff that we end up talking about
I'll be the one to take a step away from Alex Jones
Take a take a
Take a date
Get something else that I want to look into
And then also the other thing that it is that I know that Alex has a tendency of getting a little Buck Wild around the holidays
But I don't want to I don't want to rush it
I want to save that for Monday Monday will have an Alex Jones
I was looking forward to finding out whether or not he thought that Jesus was an internet interdimensional alien.
Internet
No I believe it was last year he threw hatchets
Turn the studio on Christmas Eve
And I will see if you can talk himself this year
What else is there to throw
But that'll that'll be for Monday
Okay
To do all right
Before we get to that that I take a little moment Jordan 6
So first
Jason thank you so much you are now policy wonk
Next
Palmeri on the Christmas episode come on
Domino's
Next Jesus
Powerless EU Wonka thank you so much you are now a policy wonk
Dude
Just Stu thank you so much
And I've also walked
Next Jr from the Derek Zoolander Center for kids who can't read good
You so much you are now policy wonk
Sarah
Next Sam pick his up
Journal biology Wang
Text Satan's little monkey but it's spelled Monkees or my
Be Davy Jones Michael Nesmith okay
Which one of them worship Satan Micky dolenz
You were born after the Monkees
Take as much you're not probably work
Somebody donated on elevator
Thank you so much you are now attacking
Business heroin
Freakishly large
Figure out there listening everything how I enjoy the show.
If I go on tour website knowledge fight.com
It says for the show we would appreciate any lovely
So Jordan today what I'm doing is I've been in a bit of an identity crisis with the show
A little bit
Because
I feel like we've been in a situation where
We've had our wacky Wednesdays
And there've been problems that if it's there have been
Quarters we've tried to go down to half what are we doing
There's a fine balance do exactly what is
Is good to cover and what isn't and it's really difficult to walk that line
Like Reverend Manning is super interesting and I'm glad we covered him but I don't
Thinkers value
Covering him anymore
Prison
Project Camelot does not Charmy anymore I'm not sure exactly how interesting it is to cover any more of that
A lot of people are in prison on that's that's really difficult I don't know what to do
And so to remedy that problem one of the things that I came up with was
Coasttocoastam
That's going to be a great idea
And I got to tell you
It was a better idea than it is in practice
Ab Coaster
The coast and they're very boring most of the time they're very boring and not worth talking
Yeah
So you end up
Eating tons of time it is preparation of things that go nowhere
You're sacrificing 15 hours for the possibility of
Maybe 10 minutes of our show being worth talking about I can't keep up
Now we're going to be able to do this
So in the second thing two is like I started
To realize as listen to more and more coasttocoastam
Your George Noory sucks
He definitely sucks
Yep a bit of it subtle
The thing that you
It comes up much more
Is like
Colors saying really stupid things
I don't want the
Us to do
Episodes about coasttocoastam where we're just like
Look at this dumbass
Shocking collars that holds no interest for me
Except for when they're Alex's callers in there
Saying like
Should we start shooting
Terrify
It just didn't feel like it would be satisfying and anyway like it's a it's a
The ton of work for very little
Content content will be like really
Not what I'm comfortable with what I want our show to be so that is turned me off a bit on the eye
Idea Coast-to-Coast we need something else
And I realized
What is what interests
Like what is something that I
Think is going to be in line with the show interesting
Add to everything
And the only thing I can come up with and the only thing I really want to do
I want to talk about Bill Cooper
Just fit more in line I was way off I want to talk about
William Milton Cooper
William Milton William Cooper
Really a good idea to go by Bill
Yeah Bill Cooper is a guy who is on shortwave radio for years and
Is basically what you call the Prototype
And
He has
Years
Worth of his radio show available
Z93 when he started
The hour of the time
On wwcr shortwave radio
To his death
In 2001
And I think
That this
Would be the Avenue
Beyond down which
We can find the most wackiness
The most relevance
And the most that I'm interested in
We're going back to the beginning
We're starting at the beginnings of this I wouldn't save the beginning because I think there's even further back
There are other things that probably are influences that maybe conscious subconscious
At least Oracle
Irrelevant
And maybe that's something else we could do but I want to talk about Bill Cooper
I've been listening to a bunch of
And it's it's fascinating to
To me because
For the last
You know weeks
I've been listening to his show in addition to
To listening to Alex
Show in the present
That's why it's just
Depressing
It has to be
It's so staggering to see the difference
Between like
This guy who is at the top of his game doing the shortwave militia show in 93
Alex and 2019
Does the Dead the juxtaposition is
Almost unsettling
Bad Alex
So what I've got for you today Jordan
Is we're going to be listen
OoVoo
Premier Apple
Episode okay
The time
Is that what's happened
Very little
Bill Cooper had been on some form of
Pirate Radio for about a decade
Up to this point already
This is considered the
First episode of his more mainstream
The legendary
The hour of the time
On January 4th 1993 Bill began airing weeknight
Saint wwcr
I believe it was 11
Hawkcentral
I was at Wendy's Sherwood are at the Primo time slot
Exactly where you want to do
So w.w.
Ccr's probably larger
Shortwave radio station in the country
Broadcast out of Nashville and the shows to be heard all over the United States
It brought Bill Cooper to a much wider audience than he had had previous
Wwcr is also the shortwave station that got into a business relationship with Genesis
The communications Network eventually ended up Aaron
I don't think so but it's 1993
2 years before Alex ever was a bill is on the shortwave station
Rod knocking it out of the park
Bring in the militia Community to
To the world
Build a gigantic topic
And from the amount of the shows that I've listened
I think
It's very complicated figure
He's the one with the
Orangeview
Yeah on many topics
But he's also a person who is Miles Ahead of the right-wing on some topics
You would not expect
Okay alright I find it very interesting
Right when I look at it as is I think he's a human
As opposed to someone like Alex who's full of
Yeah yeah
And in many ways bad
Person
Yellow person
It's so much more
Yeah Alex
Is more of a constructed this better many things that I know about Bill and there's many things that I don't know about him
And I don't want to let
Those
Color
What the topic it were talking about today
So today is about this episode
So we'll talk about what he brings up in this episode
Are plenty of other things like
I could say hey this show is interesting it's would like
Well what about his age denial
That's something to talk about on
If you think we're defending it
The shop
This is the this is the premiere this is the first episode
January 4th
Every show his
Starts
With air raid sirens and dogs barking and terrifying
Soundscape okay
Very upsetting
I want to pause here really
Fast because it's just go on but it it's very interesting to me that in the last
Couple months at least and probably a little bit further back than that
Alex has been coming out of brakes
Sometimes with just air raid siren
It's very reminiscent of
The beginning of Bill Cooper's hour of the time
This was recorded at Disneyland
I don't do goes on a while
Stop
All over the world
Hugo award
From here on
Go to your leaders
Tell you the truth
Toward the mark
The world
Vlog
Chipotle
All
40 News
Worldwide
Democracy
Supposedly is doing a lot of work in that shirt
First episode of his mouth starting this new show on wwcr
The premise is
You see the dropping of the Iron Curtain all of this it's
All in service of a one world democracy of world government
Is dudes all about
So
Look the problem in the world it seems external but really
It's it within
Each and everyone of us
Alright
Seville
Drops that on us
And then
Man
This guy
What what I would have brought
But don't get down
Hope all is not lost
The problem lies within
There are multiple my
The answer
William Cooper at your listing
Albert r
Air raid siren.
They are all lying to you about this song
For the listeners DNA's lips
A Cooper so much better
I wanted things I've noticed for listen
Listen to his shows that he's not afraid to make it show a multimedia
Experience
Bill incorporates music into his show that has a theme attic connection to the topic that he's covering
They need to keep
Preparation
It indicates intention
The other topic that he wants to cover and he's going to help drive his points on with artistic
In this case in his first episode of The Hour of the time Bill chose
Open show
With you long-forgotten Beach Boys
Quote-unquote hits
Make it big
From The Troop Beverly Hills soundtrack
The song was also on their 1989 album Still cruising
Which was almost universally panned by critics
Is being trash
The review on Rolling Stone open
This line quote
If you've been waiting for the Beach Boys to hit rock bottom the suspense is over
Okay
That's that's a generous opening this is the album included their cover of Wipeout
Featuring The Fat Boys
That gives you some idea what they were up to at that point
I'm prepping this episode I went back and watch that video for Wipeout
And I can report that it is embarrassing as I remember to be
Oh so they hadn't yet hit rock bottom
That was
Part of it
Anyway the point here is that bill is the kind of broadcasters down to open
Can you show with a full song you play the full song
In order to set the mood
And I'm here to tell you
Variant rules
This kind of thing honestly makes me super giddy
Spending so much time as I do studying Alex I'm like a man starving for someone who's
Trying at the fact that bill open
When's the show like this is just awesome
Yeah the way I feel about Alex Jones that he's mostly checked out
He's going through the motions of trying to spend
Conspiracy theories but he's too confused by his own ideas
He's in too deep but he doesn't even know what he's doing
He can't be bothered spend any time for parents who just yells convoluted nonsense on air plugs his pills gets a bit racist
Then screams about the literal devil for a while
It doesn't necessarily feel
Good demonstrate how he's wrong about stuff in 2019 it just feels kind of sad most of the time
The Bill Cooper
Here is a man deserving of my attend
Here is a guy who is
Trying to stop
Just short of saying that like Bill Cooper
But he's definitely much more serious
In a competent person an hour
And on some level I definitely admire that
Even if I disagree with just about everything I know he believes
Very close to you got to give it up to the Smalley pirates with no Dairy close to that. Got to go to the go Cooper
Is opening up his show with a f****** Beach Boy song make it big
I know it's probably confusing what I mean by thematic connection but you'll start to understand it as
As we go along the same response to you I was laughing
And I was like
Yeah yeah yeah
Of course
It wasn't a long walk from Aries iren's and dogs barking and f***
Nazis marching
That's not long enough
Right and
I have to
Think that bill is in control of his showing outfits on shortwave yeah I wouldn't have
Cayo Largo
Egypt statues exactly how he wants to present the show and it's his first show
On this night
Syndicated
Shortwave show
Lately
How am I going to prison
That myself
This is a
This is a statement song
Weirdly plausible that
Dennis Wilson could like
A half axle half as backwards as way into being like hey
There's this new show if
Got this really great host
You got to be on it
We just got to pay him a little bit
Just a little bit of touching
And I think it's
Just great
This guy he gets
Dinos
He knows how to do radio
And I admire
Okay cuz I like right here
So the song end
And Bill gets down to introducing something it will be the
The theme of the episode
He doesn't get into it immediately
Again it's another great broadcasting trick the Alex thinks he's doing but he's not
Which is the bill introduces the subject
Talks about something else
Then
Really digs into the sub
Right Alex
Brings up and teases the subject
Talk about other stuff then
Forget about everything
Yes thanks
He's gotten into the subject in fact has not really does believe that he's already taken
In care of it I think what Alex is doing is
Is almost bad photocopy
Of this sort of job
So here is Bill introduced
Send the subject that we will be getting into a little bit later
Call Paul the problem
Are within us
And all the answers
Are there any
U-Haul store
Pirate weapons
Technology
From operations
Roo
Strategy
Practical methodology
Developed under the military men
Broken English
During World War II
The first
View haircut ever
Heard of it
We've got the keys
We have silent weapons
Technology has been developed by or operational research we've got this
And now
Bill
Starts
Speaking start
Talking
About the show itself
It's going to be unlike anything you've ever heard in your life already he's got to Garrison Keillor
I find screwball much more attractive
Listen to than Alex
Nonsense rambling feels also in the same vein as I was saying that he feels like a real person
The way he speaks feels like a real person
Yeah
The Alex has all these affectation to his voice
Things like this is
Ridiculous
We've been making
Tufano's lately all the
The fake passionatechat like all that stuff
When you listening to and where is Bill
He seems like he is directly communicating exactly how you would
If you were talking
There's something compelling about that as well
But this show
Will be unlike any other
You ever heard
Who got the introduction to the thesis
And now we get into the witches what you're listening
Sing to it will be unlike anything you've ever heard almost a sales pitch
On the pilot episode
This is not
Any current
Radio program that you've never heard before in your life
For nothing is sacred here
On the line
Around the bush
I'm going to tell you something
There's nobody here
It's afraid
Do you want
Anybody
Criminal
Interest
In a career in radio
Hope you get thrown off the air
Bother
Iroquois
Irregardless
Of the pressure
This is why he started the show with naked pic
This is the theme attic
Like benizi silent weapon
But he's going to get to the store
The topic of the lecture as it were the other message that he wants to drive across
Is served by almost
That song being farcical like the make it big
Is in service
It's so good so good
It's the opening of Pride and Prejudice
Say you open with that line isn't ironic aside yet
A real impact
It's like if you're a little
Oh that's why you played
That song or you don't notice it when you get the unit that subconscious exam
I'm going to get you get it but if not you might just like
McCook that Beach Boys album is terrible but that's all
So
Bill gets down to his standard
Admonition
30 gives people
And that is
Don't trust
Anything that you here not even on my shirt
I love it before I go any farther though
Where you have to
To give you my scanner Dad when I send it all goes well
Come to my life
Has been listening to the Show on satellite or on WWE
ER
Inception
Fourth of May 9th
We already know that
Mini Melissa
So I'm going to give you this admonition
No matter what
Not believe anything
What you hear on this show
Are on the truck Carter show
Parmatown Valentine show
Are on Larry King live
Car from the lipstick Dan Rather or George
Are Bill Quinn
Anyone else
This entire world what you hear it on the radio or on television are from the
If someone
In front of you
Virtue
Listen to
Everyone no matter who they are or what
They aren't real
Saturday
Numark
Open calendar
Listen to everything believe nothing until you can
You yourself
You must
Learn
How to find
The truth
Improve it
If you can't do that you might as well turn off your radio
If you have to call someone else to ask
Today Show
Turn off your radio
Now
So when he said that he's on wwcr
Before
Michelle but not weakness
Every weeknight
Still a figure
Here before like Behold a Pale Horse
His big book was published in 91
Wrapping a gigantic
Stick figure
Since at least I point
Even before that
But this is the
Launch of the nightly show
So just to clarify
I heard that is like what
Hey White
He's telling people not to believe anything
Mentalities absolutely Universal
Conspiracy theory community
But something I find really interesting is how it plays out differently depending on the personalities
Of each individual
Conspiracy theories
For instance the way Alex presents this is by saying that everything you saying has been proven salty classified in the white papers
Just made it go ahead look it up
He's basically suggesting that if you don't agree with him your uninformed
And if you go ahead and do the research he's done
You'll get up to speed and recognize that he's right
It's a strategy that's deployed to make his audience the last likely to actually do that research into steaks
Stephanie might be right or you must be right
There's no way you'd be so insistent that I researched these things
If you knew that when I did I realize he's making s*** up just a bluff I was thinking the exact same thing
Is the inverse of Alex saying everything
You go look it up
A bills position is like at you like you're saying it's a little different but ultimately the effect I think it has on it audio
I agree
If he's on are saying that you shouldn't
Anyone says without researching it on your own
Kind of stands to reason that he himself wouldn't trust anything he hears without researching it on his own
If you think bills
Credible at all I'll probably subconsciously except those research is good enough
Text telling people to be skeptical of everyone as a way of getting people to only trust you
It's an authenticity of shortcut
Based on some of the stuff we're going to get into later
I don't believe the bill practices what he preaches
The other thing the bills doing gear saying that if you aren't going to prove things for yourself
He doesn't want you listening to the show
This has the effect of creating an inflated sense of self in the audio
Bill is straight-up telling all the dumb followers to stop listening so by definition if I keep listening I must not be one
Exactly creates an imaginary us-versus-them of like
You insulate the audience of this I give you are
Still listening that you must
Be one of the
Champion truth
Producers
You've researched
Everything yeah
So I may I think I think
The strategy employed
I don't know how much that
Conscious strategy
But that is the effect that you have on people with that sort of thing
I think what's
Interesting about that like
But that statement he made of
Don't trust anything anybody says without having research yourself and all of those things
All of that sounds on a surface level 2B
Fairly good advice you know
A skeptical mind you should be capable of critically researching everything
Thanks yeah but at the same time within that statement is the
Stuff that makes it impossible
Like if you can't trust
Anyone
On anything
Exactly then you're you're going to lose your mind especially if you take the other piece
Advise that he hasn't as you have to listen to everybody
Believe anything that you will always be looking
And you got to consider to this is 93
That wasn't what it is today
Actually
The audience getting into some of the stuff would be a lot more difficult than it is
Let's say for me
To go back home
E3 I probably couldn't do a show critically deconstructing what he's talking about cuz I couldn't get my hands
On some of the documents right that he's rapper
Now it's all been
Photocopied stand it's all online
The bottom like
This is bulshit
Yeah n93i imagine to that if you're the type of person who would tune into Bill Cooper show
The stuff that you would be looking up
Because of the limited availability of infinite knowledge would probably Hugh more towards the stuff that
Reinforce
Bill Cooper
A idea you might be driven toward certain data streams
Send that information
Sources
Like Patriot message boards and
Like that that have
The appearance of confer
Formation
I think that's probably
Strategic little Bill's Bar but on that larger communities fart for sure
Fascinating
That idea of you should listen
To everyone
Because you're going to trust
Yourself more
The information that you are going to research and look into
Is going to most likely be counter to the narrative that you passively
Hear all around you that also kind of insulates you from
You know I am listening to everybody but what I'm looking
Looking at which I think is more
Yeah
Is it something that I'm going to trust more than whatever the f*** Dan Rather
Yeah yep
All that is that is in the mix
So
We get back
Back to build not wanting
How to make it big
I
Expounds on this a little bit more and hear some fairly
Familiar
Refrain
I told you
It was not a radio broadcast
Ever heard or ever will
You see most radio personality
Simplest form mean
Teen Mom
I'm going up the ladder career-wise
And making a lot of money
None of those pictures
Prevail here I can assure you
Power Rangers
Are in Saving
Freedom
For the world
Play the Constitution
Of America
Tooth out sounds just like Alex
Yeah but I believe him
I believe he believes it yeah that's where I
I believe there's an authenticity to him saying like I'm not looking
For money we're not trying to get rich here it's for krill oil
Nn
And shitzo
Bringing freedom
They're better.
Presentation
From Bellaire
Do you strengthen
Rich no I agree I think you would have behaved
Much differently if he was
Tom and Jerry
He's not I think you would have died
Difference
So he's gotten his we're not trying to make it
Speedo out of the way and now we get to the
The pieces already been introduced there's these silent weapon
Amanda
We now enter the lecture for
Continue
Technology
Preferably
Develop
Operation
Research
Found out that
Recognize
Titles and positions
Coward at the same methods might
Useful for total
Better tools
Alright so silent weapons I'm assuming we're no longer talking about silencers on
No certainly not now this is much much larger than that
Insidious
I'm going to go with
They need a better tool
Turns out what they needed in order to
To achieve this
Control over the entire population turns out
It was
Computer
Coco engineering Chelsea Nelson
Party
Requires the correlation of great amounts of
Constantly changing
Economic
Information
Dallas
Computerized
Portuguese
Predict
Party
What arrived
Electronica
Computer invented
1846 by Jacob forever.
John W mousley
Still bill
So bill is clearly reading something here like first time through this because I was like
Absolutely he's reading something I'm not sure what it is
Go get to that later
For now it's just relevant to point out that will bill is expressing
When is that in order to control Society the elites needed to create
Computers we could process data and tell where things were going in the future
So they could plan ahead and be ready for the point when Society catches up with their predictive calculator
Right
Alex talks about this a lot
He often makes
Obscure references to actuaries and how the globalist use there too
Computer system
Using social me
Media to predict
The futures of the be able to know what to do with advanced
I have almost no doubt that he's taking it from the same Source the bill is currently reading
From because I've never heard Alex give a real source
It doesn't match up with the reality that I understand from what I've looked into the field of like
Modeling tistical modeling
So I I find this to be another real thing
Ematic piece
All of Alex's stuff that I've never really understood but you're hearing it echoed in the show from 93
Yeah Bill does give sources
Yeah so what I'm finding already
The pattern that I'm picking up here just a little bit
Is
He is much more likely
To put a solid
Kernel of something that you do agree with
Surrounded by and you know
Globalist so you know
Well that's like Alex doesn't work
Conspiracy theorists 22
Competent
Conspiracy theories start from a place of like a universal truth
Translate
We all feel like so
Something's wrong
And
Here's why
And this was only a year after the Unabomber so distressing technology is right on board
For this group of folks sure but this actually has nothing
Things to do with the Unabomber and Southern
Far more obscure
Google get into it
Just be you up Almer
So with silent weapons
These Elites
Are able to carry out
What's known as a quiet War
The population
And what do you know
It started
It 1954
It was carried out by
A name that's very familiar
The quiet War work
International
Everybody meeting held in 90
So now this is something interesting because I was talked about had no one was talking about the Bilderberg Group before he came along and started
Exposing this stuff this is two years before Alex was ever on air here is Bill Cooper directly saying
The guys who started a silent war in 1954 were the Bilderberg Group
Alex's
All of the things that he takes credit for are all things
They either Bill Cooper or the larger Patriot Community was already
Open arms
About
Before Alex got on air
The legacy of this guy
That's brutal it is
It is I mean I don't want to lionizer or like
Turn
Bill into some kind of hero but like
He got done Dirty by Alex
Not going to be like you stole his legacy and that's bad
You can be a bad person in
And still get done wrong
Yeah that's what I see here
So the Bilderberg Group CSS food
Is he human this
Food
Let's talk about all the time
We're cattle they just want to just eat us
Moral issues were raised
In view of the law of natural selection
It was agreed
Are world of people who will not use their
Animals not have
Intelligent
Search people
A burden
On the table by choice
And
Always have been
Always will be
Consequently
In the interest of future world order
Are tranquility
BBQ privately wage
Bart war against
The American public
Permanently
Shifting the Metro
Opal energy
Harwell
I'll be
Individual
Self-disciplined
Possible
Ed worthey
So you picking up why what's going on here
Yeah but I'm just so distracted I don't want to compliment this guy but he's such a better broadcaster that
Immediately after that first line
Pause was the right length of time
It was just so it's such a good part
He's going to do
Yeah right here
Like I said the beginning there's intention behind what he's doing as opposed to reactive flailing when I see from Alec
Right I don't want a
I'm going to try that is broadcasting
Cuz he's obviously certainly he
He's a more serious person
What do you mean the steaks on the table
Okay okay
Obviously he's reading something
He will say what it's from
Talk about
But for now
Something okay you're keeping us in suspense reading something
Okay
It's all about the silent weapon
Sure they're obvious
To the trained eye right but You & I we would
Vietnam
No obvious
Causes no obvious
Physical or mental
Obviously interfere with someone
Unmistakable
Physical
An unmistakably
Unmistakable to train
Windows what
The public
Cannot comprehend or cannot believe that they are being attacked
Miami weather
The public market
First perfume in rational way
Arkansas
The problem
Intelligence
Therefore
They do not know how to cry for help
I do not know how to associate with others to
Against
Peerless Tires 185
Applied Gregory
The public adjuster
This is classic
Conspiracies
There's this massive thing
Explain everything
Trained eyes
Like mine
This is just red pill rhetoric before the Matrix ever
It's an attempt to deal with a very real issue that that what you're talking about makes
No sense to anyone
It only makes sense
Trained Observer
The second part of that clip is also pretty standard conspiracy manipulation
Already touched on
Minute ago
Every conspiracy generally starts from
Fairly Universal released a Feeling
Like it's universal truth
Many people feel like there's something wrong with the way Society is structured
There systemic problems
Keep power in the hands of a particular class
While the rest of us are left to play games with our boots
Everyone recognizes that's not fair
Another is probably a better way to go about things
They aren't sure what the cause of the problem is
And this is the feeling
Conspiracy theorist
By providing an answer to that fundamental question they're able to pass off anything they want
Is part of that explanation
Everyone feels like something's off but they can't quite put their fee
Synchronic the answer of course
Is a silent weapon system set up by the Bilderberg Group in 1954
That sounds right
There's a reason the Bill Cooper decided to cover this on this first episode on wwcr
The whites the subject of the first chapter
Of his book Behold a Pale Horse
Which is
God's Own book
It's the first chapter of his book that's actually a republishing of something else
The Mysteries still not entirely solved
And the reason he's doing this
Because it's something
Like a thesis
This is what's at the root of a lot of his
Conspiracy
The explanation for why things aren't the way they should be in society it's a silent weapon system that's being too
Floyd and you can even hear so many wrinkles and shades of Alex in there
Supply gradually humans address
Alex talks about that all the time
All the time
Talk about meeting with globalist or like a publical acclimate to
Everything
King is just like oh wow
All of these ideas
They're all just
Repackage
So
You know we're talkin about this this
Things
People like Bill and Alex are able to manipulate from
The starting point of feeling like something
Wrong
And what do you know Bill meets a lot of people who feel that way
The reason why would I travel around this country
Did you get my messages
Find me
Do people come up to me and say
Terribly wrong
Don't know
And that's why
Everybody is waiting George
Realizing
Who is the same
What's this very are what's this
All political parties of the same they're all controlled by
Cool
7 that's pretty pretty theme attic to
And it was things is like on the right wing
You ever want imagines that everybody is his partisans
Angop
Right but these large figureheads of the butts particularly in The Patriot militia vein
Are certainly not
Yeah it's just government it doesn't matter who's in there
It's simply the fact of governments
It remains to be seen if they would ever like a president
Yeah like maybe there are Presidents in history that they've enjoyed more than others
Jackson baby
But they are certainly In Our Lifetime all of them have been bad
Like really a tragedy is
Because Bill Cooper died in 2001 we have no idea what he would have thought of trump
Like I really write the Mind reels
I don't think you would have been onboard I think you would have been
A voice
Very strong like
F*** this
Yeah I mean
Anything 20 years ago
20 years is a long time
I just don't know
We can't know
But I do think
That if
Trump
Was elected in 2012
Alex would have stayed again
Yes that's what I
You you're probably right but I think also that it you're right it is it is very difficult to tell because I think if you
You would have
Cast at another point in time you would have said Alex never would have done that
Years of the principals don't mean anything maybe I'm just imagining the bills convictions were much
Stronger than they actually are
He sounds like he feels like yeah
He died because of
Is refusal to pay taxes around being a real gun dick
Yeah that that is interesting
I would be interested because I think I'm more interested to know how he would have dealt with
The years of w
Sure, I'm more interested in that kind of
Situation
I mean we got a couple months of it
Yeah baby before he dies about his approach
Zombie butt
We'll see
So in the next Clipper Bill reveals the source material of what he's talk
Erasing our world
Intelligence
Are no better than animals
30 people are beast of burden
Jake's on the table by
Choice
You fit that category called
I certainly hope
Because I believe
Get ourselves out of this
Situation if we will just open our eyes out here
Wake up
Stop bleeding
What you told what you read
Give me to find
For yourself
What are you doing
Giving you
Half hour
Is just
A couple of pages
Out of the first chapter of my book
Airport
Animal shelter are puppies
A document
Entitled silent weapon
For quiet Wars
An introductory programming manual operation
Call Manuel
F.w. 7905
One of
The document
That was prepared
Subjugation
America
Start a secret
Power
Group
Who Wants to Rule the World
Dispensary
So a lot of the beginning of this episode has to do with Bill reading from the first chapter of behold a Pale Horse
Which he lays out his pieces
Largely the foundation for this world
According to builders an evil group of Elites were waging a war
It's called The Quiet War
Against the pub
Like mostly apparently
To control the
They want to completely predictable economy
And the only way to do that is to remove any instability or chaos from the public
The best means to achieve that is entirely pacifier domesticate everyone to the point where
Even thinking of straying from the path
Is unthinkable
As the story goes in 1954 choir war was launched by people like the Rockefellers
The Bilderberg Group along with elements of the government in order to achieve this goal
This story is largely based
On a document that's taking on Mythic import
Anti-government militia world
A document I've heard Alex reference many many times
Even to the present day
Like I heard him references document maybe a week ago
It's called
Silent weapon
For quiet Wars
And Bill Cooper founded on 4chan
May 1979 the document is meant to Mark the 25th anniversary of the launch of the quiet
And to describe how said war is
What strategies it employed
And exactly what techniques have been used in carrying out this war
Right off the bat
This just the premise of this should be a gigantic red flag
And I thought that you just yelled Pez dispenser because it is very similar to the way
The protocols of the Elders of Zion makes no sense
You can argue that this document was that
To be top secret and all that but in what world does a
Super Evil cabal put together a document that lays out literally all of their evil plans to enslave Humanity
Just to Mark the 25th anniversary of this plan B
Motivation makes no sense
If you consider the actor that play
Childish
Stole the PowerPoint presentation
Write the conference where they all are agreed that we're going to do this evil play
To murder all the people or I got you next slide
I got out
Oh no
Put simply I do not believe that a group that was able to speak
Control the world
For 25 years
Would also be
A group of decide
Like to celebrate that achievement by
We are riding how they've been secretly controlling the world for 25 years
Any group that would do the latter would be by definition ink
Incapable of carrying out the prior
Just does not make sense
So Bill claims that he'd seen this document back in his days working in Navy intelligence
In fact he backs up a lot of his claim to the pills to having seat or being aware of things through his time in that branch of the service
It's unclear if Bill was actually in Navy intelligence
But he definitely was a sergeant in the Navy and did serve in Vietnam and Saucon play
Combat
He got to service Metals in 1969 but beyond these facts the rest of the story just comes from billing self
He's claimed that he was discharged in 1975 but it's really hard to tell what
Real and what's embellished
Given that it ate it's definitely true that he's not making up his service and that he was in Vietnam I'm going to err on the side of
Not questioning his time in uniform
And just believe him
Four at the most
Yeah this is no Stevie peas.and.
We're letting this one.
It does not appear that he is just making s*** up
However there's a problem with his claim that he saw a copy of Silent weapon
Things for quiet Wars while he was a Navy intelligence
And that is why he did not exist
Before he was discharged
Because it's
1979 was in his written he was discharged The 1975
I suppose you could say that the actual document of the 25th anniversary edition he saw an older version of it
First edition it was signed by Rockefeller worth millions I should tell you
There is no older version
Of course.
In 2003 a man named Hartford Van Dyke
Tomato very credible claim to have
Silent weapons for quiet Wars
The document has been featured in a magazine called paranoia
And haven't read their article VanDyke reached out to them by letter
It turns out that he'd already revealed himself as the author of the text on the radio show in 1996 but people didn't really take note
And if you look at the surrounding details it seems very likely that he was the author
Especially when you consider the apocryphal story that goes around for how the document
In 1986 a publication called America's
Promise newsletter published in Arizona
Where Bill Cooper live
Printed silent weapons for the first time
It's probably worth pointing out that this newsletter was published by Lord's covering
Church with Pastor Sheldon Emery
Was a high-profile follower of the Christian identity movie
My day we got weird how they keep popping up all over the place
They're like herpes
Haha
In the intro to the document they say it was quote founded and IBM copier that was purchased at a surplus sale
I'm sorry what's for this document
Rockefeller Bilderberg plan
So how well did way up in a f****** garage
Sale
Surplus sales
It's important
It's a surplus sale because the implication
Is it a cop they purchased
Does copier from the McChord Air Force Base which is nearby
I'm at the cellar.
Just been too sloppy
To remove the world
Conspiracy demonstrated document they just copied begin put tray
Leave that like it like somebody removing their wallpaper and finding a hole with Nazi Treasures right right it's like that's not how
You want that's the story that they want to ruin your brain
It's nonsense it's an absurd story but one that's very similar to other origin stories for bulshit
Documents
So many of these things have
Completely nonsense origin
Like have so many of Larry Nichols official documents are just things he founded his mailbox
Ever giving out his
Address on Alex Jones Show a bunch
Yeah I got to Larry Nichols
Ridiculous figure
Just silly
I mean the same thing as the background story for
For the absolute
That story is likely not true
But the story than Hartford Van Dyke tells is a bit more plausible
And that is that he was a real Sovereign citizen tape weirdo back in the 70s
Who is preoccupied with the idea that Roosevelt had foreknowledge of the attack on Pearl Harbor
And allowed it to happen.
U.s. into World War II
This weirdly
Came up on our last episode from
The present-day of Alex Jones where he was
False flag
I swear to God you're a demon has already touched on this a little bit narrative was popularized in 1940
34th chapter book came out called the truth about Pearl Harbor by John Flynn
Which definitely had a big impact on Van Dyke
Refresh your memory Flynn was a major player in the group called The America First committee
Which I'm pissed off cuz I'd listened back door last episode
I kept saying America First Commission
Delano America first
Committee there were group who Master anti-Semitism and support for fascism by calling
Auntie intervention
You probably be unfair to say the organization was
Pro Hitler
But they definitely were pretty vocal about how they weren't
Anti-hitler enough to think that good
People around the world
Navigation to fight
Yeah
America First Committee of dissolved
When the US entered World War with the people involved in the organization
Just give up on their goals
And one of them was to paint us involvement
In the wars being apart of the
Conspiracy
This large
You scratch the surface but most
Conspiracy theories
Outnet fashion
Seem to keep
Popping up
Kind of weird
So this guy VanDyke according his telling of it lived in Hawaii
Where is father's uncle had Direct involvement in the event of Pearl Harbor
He told him about how Roosevelt had three dissenting military officials held at gunpoint until the attack it happened to prevent their ability to
Sound the alarm
Van Dyke wrote a book called The Skeleton and Uncle Sam's closet about these another Pearl Harbor Revelations
Presumably self-published Back in 1970
Around this time
And I got his hands on a little book called a report
From Iron Mountain on the possibility and desirability of
Which conspiracy theorist believe is an official secret government report
About how it wouldn't
Good for the country to enter
. of long
Peace
The document itself the Iron Mountain document was released in 1967
Anna 1970
Me to a man named Leonard Lewis
Came out revealed that he had written that report and it was mad
Is it working
Political satire about how absurd
Think tanks are
Simply put it was a hoax
1 vets
Suddenly probably became 100-percent real from some dumb thing to
I don't know about that but if you can't breathe
Later I think tank came out with the exact
In 1990 the Liberty Lobby
The organization founded by outright Neo-Nazi and Holocaust denier Willis carto
We can't selling copies of that book
The Iron Mountain report
This prompted Luanne to sue the Liberty Lobby for infringing his intellectual property rights
A suit that he would have won accepted Liberty Lobby wanted
To settle out of court
And agreed to pay luena
Stop selling his book
They likely settled because Lou and definitely had proof that he had in fact written this report
It's considered one of the most
Successful literary literary hoaxes of all time
And no serious person who has looked into it believes that it's real in any way
So anyway VanDyke right about half of this fake report from Iron Mountain
It started to put
Together
Ultimately leads to the inspiration behind silent weapon
Sims for quiet Wars
A very large part of
Primary list of sources for silent weapons
Is references to the report from Iron Mountain
A literary hooks
In many ways silent weapons is itself
Represent itself as an official internal document being used by people within the secret government program
The Familiar Eyes new initiate
It's into their program
It's clearly not
To the extent that people believe that it's a real document
They're falling for a hoax
Although there's a very important to stinks
Between this hoax
And that of Iron Mountain
And that's a difference of intent
Luann Road Iron Mountain is a piece of satire
To make people consider how absurd the arms race is
And how we should consider the ways we could as a society transition to stable
Peacetime economy
It's a lampooning meant to make the reader think
Conversely VanDyke wrote this hoax.
To try and trick people into thinking that there was actually a secret government program that have been in place
Enslave the population
To the author it wasn't Santa
It was an expression of something totally real
And his intent was to
Persuade the reader to adopt
His view of the
So
So his
Motivation in writing that's
Specific piece
Was
Falstaff was to pass it off as a real doc you
Okay so then
That's
That's strange to me
I guess I guess what he is he's not
Cuz I feel like
If you
Sing it together from other b*******
What do you mean
This is what the enemy's plan is and has always been right
And then
Passing it off
As an official document from them
Then you have to know you're lying
Please write
Probably say I am
Lying in presentations what I'm saying is true to an extent that it doesn't matter
They've no one will take it seriously if I don't resent it this way but what I'm saying is true
So I presented this way in order to make a splash
But it's it's a fundamental deceit
Even from his part
In order to achieve the outcome that he
Desires
But it's
It's ridiculous
If you read it it's just like
Who would fight
F****** believe that
Like One giveaway for anyone reading silent weapon
For quiet Wars something really should tip them off at the reading app
Conspiracy theory rant as opposed to a secret government
Product
Is a section called
Theoretical introduction
Dissection begins with a most likely fabricated quote from Mayer amschel Rothschild
The way this document obsesses over Rockefeller philanthropy and the Rothschild family is a gigantic red flag
Good Providence
A red flag that all these dumb dumb conspiracy theorists just seem to ignore like yeah absolutely
Secret government programs would really talk about the Rothschilds a lot
Another problem they overlooked is how this supposedly real document ends like this
Quote
It left of those few who are truly willing to
Nothing can survive is the fittest to survive
To solve the problem for themselves as the few really care
Otherwise exposure of the silent weapon would destroy our only hope
Preserving the seed of the future true Humanity
Dot-dot-dot
This secret government documents
Either that or the guy who's in charge of writing secret government documents
Has a novel hidden always aware that he's afraid to public
English major for the cartoon and he died while finishes
The ellipses in blood
The secret government document as delicious as particular
It's just unbelievable that anyone read this and be like yeah that's
Flo-Jo
It's just scream
Fake even if I had no idea that Van Dyke
Made a pretty solid public case
That he'd written it
So the main premise of silent weapons for quiet Wars is that the elites want to completely predictable economy and so they use silent
Train the population into
Conforming to make them predictable
Check these weapons are things like paper currency social welfare programs advertising
Public education
They're the input
What's the government create
Switch then produce their desired out
Like the government
I controlling everything and everybody being
It begins as just being about the economy
Document
Before it's over at there's so many suggestions but
Technology and teaching revisionist history that the reader comes away thinking of these alleged silent weapons could be just about
Of course
And this is why Alex will sometimes use this document as a
When talking about things like
Soft kill vaccines
These are also silent weapon
The unfocused nature what's being discussed allow this document to be used however the user wanted
Which is another super awesome
Feature of conspiracy theories
It's a bit rangy
And it doesn't really make sense as presented but that doesn't matter
Haycock fire the Patriot militia anti-government circles because it confirmed what they already believe to be true
Namely that the government has been carrying out a specific
Quiet war against
The population
A decade
With the goal of enslavement
Which can only be fought
By fighting the government itself
America's promise
Newsletter published silent weapons
To November
18 * 86
I meant Bill Cooper put it in his book Behold a Pale Horse published in 1991
And from that point on it was conspiracy Cannon
It definitely proved the existence of the secret evil government programs
Involving Rockefeller philanthropy in the dreaded Rothschild
But none of it's real
It's just a work of a sovereign citizen who was tricked by a well-written piece
Political satire
When you get down to the bottom of these sources of information
For the
Larger umbrella of the worldviews that are put out by people like Bill
And Alex
You see like oh there's nothing here
Yeah it's like if the onion was the reason we had Q
Yeah I don't know
I was always think of like this just
Really
Gets to me whenever you have a guy like Bill Cooper starting your show with
It's all about if you know what to look for
Know what you mean there is if you start with what you want to find
And then start looking
King for that you've trained your brain in a particular way to see certain things and now everything is filtered through that lens
I'm like this is why I was saying what
He's he's saying like you shouldn't trust anything unless you research it for yourself like I don't think
You practice what you preach
Because this is the first chapter of your book
Silent weapons for quiet Wars you don't
Like in 1993 sure Hartford VanDyke hadn't come out and said
On that Radio Show in 96
That he had created this document
Whatever but even so if you read that
You definitely need
Much more concrete
Proof
And I find it hard to believe that
Over that time span
Nobody with a
Hey critical I had look
The other thing is that bill claims that when he was a naval intelligence
Document they couldn't have
Existed while he was in the Navy that part
To me implies
You're making that up
Which is which undercuts a lot of the author
Intensity
That I
Fiocchi and body because there's also things like that
Yeah what was
That was that
Cool cloth
Meet up
My my feel on that my read on that is
No matter what you want to say
You know like
It requires a significant amount of ego for you and I to do this show just the idea of doing a show at all
But whenever you are the font of all knowledge that requires a significantly larger
Grandiosity to it
When you're that grandiose
It is impossible not to self
I wouldn't doubt that he believes that he saw it but that was like a retroactive addition to
You know like when you remember like when they do true-crime documentary and the neighbors like
I remembered seeing all these weird things before it happened you're making that s*** up
You're revising your own hair
History yeah that's a problem probably a good point with these folks
What's to like
I know I experienced it was Alex a lot that's like
You've told this story so many times that you perceive it to be true
For sure so there's two more
Important points that I need to bring up about this
Silent weapons
For quiet Wars
And the author
Hartford Van Dyke that I think are really
Crucial to consider
The first is that report from Iron Mountain wasn't the only thing that inspired vandyke's right sign
From his letters to the editor of paranoia magazine
Quote
In late October 9th
1972 I met a man who gave me a copy of none dare call it conspiracy by Gary Allan
The book inspired me to write my own book
The book that he's referring to their is that book that he wrote about Pearl Harbor
None dare call it conspiracy inspired Van Dyke to write his first absurd conspiracy book and then quote
During the last phases of that books production
I began reading a book
Call report
From Iron Mountain
According to his letters he only got halfway through report from Iron Mountain
But then later
He was reading a college algebra test
Textbook for whatever reason
And decided that the equations are similar to something he read in part of Iron Mountain
It's a completely nonsensical path for him to take
But that's what leads him to write silent weapons
You read part of Iron Mountain then saw an algebraic equation it decided he practically
On a secret government operation
The reason I think this is important is because once again we find none dare call it conspiracy being the spark that sets off an explosion
Well I'm sure Van Dyke was not the world's most critical thinker prior to October 19th 7
32 things
He read that book and it inspired him to
To create his own anti-government propaganda
This is exactly the path Alex tells of his own life
Reading none dare when he was like 12 open
When does mind the world of secret government
And set him down the road that he can
Continues down to this day
None dare call it conspiracy is a super dangerous book
But not because it reveals
The truth behind the globalist
Plotz
It's dangerous because of a
Rhetorical Style
The way it's written
Is almost hypnotic
It relies on oversimplifications
An excessive use of repeated phrases
Did almost become a chorus within the
The text to the point where it clearly has the potential to negatively affect people who read it
If they're a little bit sad
Adjustable or if they're not prepared to deal with what they're reading yet
Yeah
Well obviously not solely responsible for this phenomenon
I feel like in my experience
Someone reading none dare and believing it is
Is an act
Prepares them
To uncritically receive other anti-government information as fact
Grimes
Alex believes all kinds of
Completely fabricated things are true
Because they conform to the narratives
Internalize
Van Dyke believe the Iron Mountain document is true because it can
Conform to the worldview he'd been
Initiated into
Even Richard Belzer is an example of this in our experience
I am starting to feel like none dare call it a conspiracy is
Is almost like The Velvet Underground in
Not a ton of people have read it but everybody who read it wrote their own crazy
Conspiracy theory
So far Alex has written a book that was written a book Van Dyke's written about
Yeah it's it's
Yeah it is
It's one of those things that like I never expected when
We set out
To do this show that it would pop up in such weird places to look into the silo
Weapons for quiet Wars
I like all this guy did the stories wild I just did
This is just something
Some guy who had some stupid ideas wrote this it's not a government
And I never expected like he's interview be like
I read none dare call it
Beersy
The more I think about it in the more I
Experience
Even the reading of that text
It's
Sensitive
The the the way they're like
Catchphrases
And like
Appeals to very oversimplify vlogs
Yeah that just
Drive home points in your head
To the point where if you're read
It it does
Get to be like
Chorus
The chorus of the
The catchphrases are the things that
Gary Allan wants you to
Internalized right if you're not paying attention
He wrote a book and almost calling response
Yes that kind of yes
Call Anda responsibility
Yeah it is outside
The call isn't attack
And so is the response
As you're reading it
You started give the revivers
And everybody gets real comfortable with that
I mean a lot of persuasive writing
Is
Sort of in that
Vain
A 22 up to a point
But done there is far past
It's a pity
Like I don't want to put it
Like two extremely butt
Comfortable saying it's almost
Most called brainwashing
It-it's
Think about it the more it pops up the more I realize
I think we've just got to do
How long it ends up being
Everything's at Alice back from doing today
Might be 6 hours long I think we just got to do it cuz I think
It's probably important to address some of the
But we make it to that event
Anyway the point is that this guy that first
This guy is inspired heavily
Buy none dare call it
A e
The second point I want to make is about why Hartford Van Dyke was writing letters to paranoia about his authorship of silent
But he's paranoid
Because at that point in 2003 the only way
Communicate with anyone
Was my letters because he was in prison
I thought it was going to be in the forest
Going the wrong direction
Van Dyke was at that time serving an eight-year sentence for fraud
He in a co-conspirator and tried to pass off over three million dollars in fake currency
Van Dyke also didn't pay his taxes for years and when he tried to deal with it by sending
The IRS $600,000 of his fake currency
Things kind of Escalade
Battle color the defense team
According to an article in the Associated Press VanDyke
Quote claim to his place
33 million dollars and liens against the judges property
Which is
Unfortunately a common Sovereign citizen went over
Never not going to like the balls on these people fraudulent liens on
So Hartford Van Dyke has a person with a well-documented history of very dumb beliefs as well as
Fraudulent Behavior
He's exactly the sort of person who's Mo matches up
But someone who would write a document like silent weapons
Quiet
And because he wrote so what he wrote
Mostly matches up
With what people like Alex and Bill Cooper
Feel
Is how the evil globalist work
They've accepted it as gospel
Is an actual government
This case study
Example is really it's a damning indictment of these people's ability to deal with sources
Instead of accepting that they've been fooled by a hoax
What they do is what so many people on their side of things
They insist that every piece of information
That they're wrong is actually part of the
Conspiracy itself
I remember whenever I
Still was
Was young and
Idealistic and I would get into these long emails
My dad about
Play some of his conservative beliefs
And I remember this one Exchange in
Ticular was
Me just sending him to all of these articles and
Looking at
How many words were hyper
And then he would send me the response to it
And there were no words hyperlink in there were no source
You realize the
He's like I don't believe your sources
Well the f****** fine
Exactly what's then we're done
You know the other thing that you hear a lot is like yeah okay sure Hartford Van Dyke wrote that but everything in it is true
Exactly he was channeling the truth on that larger point
Isn't true
What is the government
Document saved by this secret program
And you guys all safe it is a reason it has credibility to you is for something that
It's not true
So if you guys
Bright you got you can receive
If you ledwith
A weirdo Rosa
Right and that's why you don't do that
And also there's a lot of Nazis and fascists lurking around in the background of all this stuff that is weird
Yeah they don't know why I don't know why there's all these Christian identity
People poking their head up
Publishing this newsletter I don't know why
This guy is inspired by Gary Island who works for the George Wallace yeah I don't know why
Seems like
All of these conspiracy theory
Trails
The people who are Nazis
Segregationist
Or both
If you do something that I've been
Wrestling with is
Especially with all this conspiracy theory stuff is not that these guys don't want a One World Government
It is that
They would rather a One World Government run by one guy
Then bye
20 guys
Like it's a it's a rhombus individualistic like I want a supreme leader who can cut through all this b******* thing
I'm sick of all these globalist discussing thing
Really don't like discussing I will agree with you on that seem like every
Every one of these conspiracy theory movements really focuses on the the number of people that gets everywhere the building
Think
Some of it comes down to be oversimplifying a
So please don't take this as like
Me saying this
This explains everything
Think there is a strain of it that is like well you know how the European Union work
You know there's all these countries and there's free travel between
You can just go wherever you want to go with your EU passport so there's a one-world government everybody
Can go everywhere and that would be like
Really bad for these people who don't like minorities people being around
I know that that's not everything that's not the whole
Story but it would be ludicrous for us not to accept that is some part of it
Bill Cooper
Because I'm from a lot of the stuff that I've listened to him
He seems
Pretty
Emphatically non-racist
I don't know if he has
I don't know if it's fair to say that he doesn't cold races
Believes
But he is pretty vocally
Against races
Yeah
So I don't know
He doesn't strike me as somebody who's one of those white nationalist e-types
But I do think that there is a large
Contingent within the people who are afraid of
That is in place
It's not so much that there's nowhere
Can go to escape the world cover
Everyone else
Can come to me
That's fast don't think I ever took a
Get that far as to what
Their fears of a one world government would be but
Why do species X but immigration demographic
Pick a number isn't s*** I just don't get how they don't also include geography as a
AB
To this whole
All we get rid of border so that means everybody's going to come here because it's the best ones like
Anyway
Bill
But it is spoken
About to
This time weather
Quiet Wars
And so have I
It's nonsense
And
His first episode
The first chapter of behold a Pale Horse
Largely a thesis statement
It's meant to prove that this
Conspiracy exists right
Is bulge
Right
So congratulations
So we're off to a good start
Coming out the gate hot
Yes but
You don't believe in a lot of the stuff that build as you probably a sheeple
Probably she
Quiz
For you to figure out if your
Yes please
Wells Fargo
I'm not one of those
People
Well let's find out
Shoot the messenger
Because you can never solve a problem
Recognize
Is it for what it is
Okay
It
I'm just asking a few questions
To find out
If you are really
People
Or not
Questionnaire
Do you believe in before
Purpose
And
The articles
Selfie
Second article amendments
The Constitution
Love the United States
America
The Rite of peace
Bear arm
If you do will you agree to go
Always any effort
2/4 American
Register their gun
Wouldn't you
No
Never
Will I ready
Play weapons
So that seems to be the only question in this quiz
Is is are you going to catch them
Seems like it's just that if you believe in the 2nd Amendment you're not a sheep
Bridal
So I mean he is a pretty big gun absolutist in the same way that Alex's
That's all you have another
I think they're
He discusses
Some of these gone beliefs are also very reminiscent
Of ways that Alex
Experiences gun
Issues
That are
Seem out of lockstep
With what you
See as the right yeah he is the GOP
Let me ask you if you believe there
If you would never
40 movie
Register
Our weapon
Bmra
If you do
Why
Because let me tell you something right now though if you belong in our a you have already
Register your gun
Goku looks like Alex Jones
Is anti-nra
Especially and Alex has gotten more into the NRA in like a very recent days but Intel
Fairly recently in his early career he was very anti-nra
He was very into people like Aaron zellman's Organization for the preservation of firearms ownership
And Larry Pratt's gun owners for America America
He was very much against the NRA he felt like they were a gun can
Control organization
As opposed to being
And that is not something that's very consistent in the the right wing
Except for
This
So is Bill Cooper's main point here that if you are a member of the NRA you are revealing to the government that you have
Have guns
Thus you are Bass
Sickly registering your
That's one big part of it
Absolutely that is where the these lists will be already
And the other part of it is an argument that he has about the NRA misleading
What gun owners
Ship is for would you get them to in this
Minneapolis notices discarded
Registered Young by Journey
Like what
Indian poker
Hurt
You weren't going to be easy to
To get rid of the gun
Cloak
Emergency
Protecting animals
Journal Review
Connected with the animal
Somebody out there
Besides the very few of us were dreaming thinking
Begin to think along with us
So that is very similar to 22 Alex's conception
Yeah mischaracterizing gun ownership as a being about hunting
Can lead to a way to take away cup
Yeah our enemy is playing four dimensional chess where in their supporting us with their controlled operation opposition in the
NRA who gets everybody to register their guns and tie at The Hunting haha
Is there
Under their control also
Is there anything you can't hunt anymore instead of removing the needs for guns guns the attack
Egg hunting at night yeah because we're how you kill these animals it's so cruel man
Play in football and also largely explains why there is such a position
Things like licenses for hunting and
And game restrictions
And see right
Poaching rules
Attack on guns
By virtue of
The characterization is guns being
Right it's all very weird
Itsfunneh
Sovereign citizen
Extinct by imagining an enemy that is so incredibly devious and intelligent they themselves are.
Intelligent
Well the same time not realizing that their enemies devious intelligence manifest
Double really stupid plans that don't make any sense
And I don't think that outside of some like
Pretty
Far-out circles
People have a problem with hunting
Within
Recently we don't want to kill a population around
But there is a there is a part of nature that you can
Be apart of people are at least capable of saying
Okay
If we hunt all the deer away
I won't be able to hunt
And there'll be ramifications for the larger ecosystem and then I won't be able to hunt that and I won't be able to do that right they can
They can understand that naked self-interest stop
And how regulation is I think a lot of people
I think generally people are in the
I'm at but I'm not sure that I know of
Too many
Prominent voices that are like no one should hunt anything yet I might be wrong but I don't think I hear that argument
Too much did the bigger point is the bill has this
Gun position
Very similar to Alex's early gun position
There's just
It's every
Yeah almost everything is like this it this is
This is
And obviously Alex
It's good here
He had Bill Cooper on his show
So yeah yeah yeah
We we find out
The bill has a little bit of an organization
But he runs
And
Explain why
He has a bad information
Go to be like
Information tracker
What we're all about what we have to
Offer some of the available material that we have
Information about
Joint intelligence
What year was already thinking that I started years ago
This moment
Pavilion in Commerce
During organization in the world
Golfer the most
A lot of the information
You're going to hear
Program
Country
Unsung heroes
I prefer to remain in the back
Constantly Gathering
Putting information
Central
Clearinghouse
Where we are the process
Alison Brie
Tupac
What is the deception
What they want us to believe any other issues
So bill has the citizens agencies joint intelligence
Which is just his
Stocking listeners and Weirdos
Not good
That's not a good Clearinghouse that's not a good system I would first give people a taste for about 1
Sent and then go from there but
Sia
This is only a good system if you had
Intensely rigorous
Standards
In place for
Scrutinizing that
Yeah you need to have
A default position of everything that comes in his
Bulshit
Or else
What you're doing is he saying like
Hey sometimes stranger send me things and I believe he literally said his
His
The whole thing is I have a default position of everything is b*******
So
But based on that I don't believe that exact
Don't believe it
He believes silent weapon
Quiet Wars
So I don't believe that you could handle a Clearinghouse event
Information that has tons of people sending
Nope
So you got to sleep
That's the that's the
Or happy
People send the truth to you by
That's seeking it
Fries
Nothing else
Whirlpool Duet
Nothing
Chandler police
President of the United
Not Rush Limbaugh
Four were all manipulated
We're all
Red
I'll say
Wow
Now I'm starting to think this guy
There is something
We're all mislead
Is a really fun thing
To say about your best friend at the end of this episode about
Document that he was misled about
Yeah like
One thing to say we're all misled and none of us are perfect and
And that that's what that's all good
Well it's another thing
To save that sort of
Like glibly as we like as a toss off on an episode that you or misled about
ADI would you
If you're Bill Cooper
View
Make silent weapons for quiet Wars the first chapter of the old Pale Horse
Use it as the source
Material for the first episode of
The hour of the time and then a month later let's save like guys I was
Miss lied about that you would never do that
Too many it's a keystone
Yelp
The building
Of anti-government
Paranoia
You can't afford
The question
Right so no I don't believe I don't believe
The premise at all that you got a secret
The truth I don't believe it
Yeah that is it is always interesting whenever so much of what he says is
Is based on
Stuff that I got you know we're all aware that something is
And I get where he's coming from and I get what he's trying to do but unfortunately his entire theory is built on
Something that's factually inaccurate and so no matter what from there on out it's
Color you know
It's like if Paul was a Satanist
You are the rock of my church The Devil you know like
Yeah it's ya uou have
Your
Presumably honest work
Digging
It's based on a hoax that was inspired now
Yeah so
What are you do
Yeah. Nothing
You pointed your
Quote unquote rigorous mind
Beginning from a place of reality truth maybe we wouldn't get there
Maybe he'd be a weirdo militia that believe reality I don't know
Monroe
So building
Next clip expresses vet
Interesting
Approach towards broadcast
That I think Alex probably also believe
If you weren't here what you cannot and will not here anywhere else I don't care who are the other what they prefer
Politics are how loyal they are the Constitution
You will not hear anywhere else
Maybe angry
Then I have a concrete
One of my goals
People to ask unless they have strong feelings about what
I think that Alex has a very similar approach that you're not going to hear any of the stuff that I talk about anywhere else
Yeah certainly
That's in line
Then the other I want to inspire strong emotion
Continue
Yeah let's talk about that all the time about how he's you know I ain't got a gravelly voice of abrasive
Trying to wake you up
I am trying to be vocal
Emotion in you
Guy disrespect
Tatooine
I don't know I don't know if it's always wrong
But when it's based on lies
I think it's very wrong
I need you're trying to short-circuit
That you're trying to take a shortcut in people's brains
To get them to override their critical thinking skills wow all your doing
Talking about how important critical thinking
Bear bear
They're cheating
The game
But there is there is it is true that you cannot inspire people to mass action without
An emotional element that you know that the women's March
Doesn't have as many people as it does if there isn't a strong emotional connection
2 what's going on
Real
That strong emotional connection isn't their overriding the
There is a
Yeah and I just think that
I think that these strategy
Leading with
That being
An emotional response
Is
It should go the other direction
Not good
Probably a dishonest
Strategy at its core
Yeah if you want if you want
Good things to happen it has to begin with cradle critical thinking
That leads to an emotional response
Ideal
You know by looking at
Certain policies that are like
You know there's no immigration
At the very beginning you know Iran is none of these people can come in
Right
There's no critical thinking there it's just
Emotion I don't
Feel like these people are good so they have to go out
Where is people's
And that is
Know what you're really doing
Is trying to exclude an in
Higher religion from this country
And that gives me a strong emotional react
Not the emotional reaction being
Bob
You know
But if you listen to our of the time
And you have a strong emotional reaction it's positive
That's great because you're just going to
To dig deeper in and find the truth
Negative
Angry angry
That's good too
Heard anything
Try to prove that what you hear on hearing wrong
Most of it will always be right on the money
And where it is
It will turn you around
You will begin to realize
That you are bi
Getting
To think for yourself
Samantha revelation
I'm right 99% of guys I heard exactly that I heard it
You know even then later on it turns out I'm right
And also Bill excludes one possibility and it might be a very rare
Response to a show which is Delight
And the desire
To learn more about the things he's talking about with a skeptical eye
Angry nor delighted
Rejoice like I'm not
It's very rare response
It's the one I have it
Probably not good
His bottom line
Although I'm not sure he's concerned about that in 2019
I don't know
Probably
It probably is bankrupt
What are you die
Call the monkey
Even if it would even if it wasn't bankrupt
The moment the government was like oh s*** you always
What's a lot of money
It would then be
Yeah he's winding down
Down here and then giving this Dismount that is like the
You know we're going to stir up strong emotions and if you hate me you're going to dig into this and most of the
But I'm going to find them right sometimes I'm wrong maybe about gigantic thing
We're all human he likes to imagine that the things he's wrong about is a date or
Document is fake
That's the thing you're wrong about at
Right right not superficial details you're wrong.
It's not like I'm sorry
It was Lee Harvey Oswald by himself I apologize I thought it was the Russians or whatever yes
Who's to say that like the government's on the up-and-up and you
You stuck everything they do is good
This conspiracy
That undergirds
So much of the
The militia paranoia that one world government
Is
Based on a hoax
Bogus
It is not really
Strong
Evidence
Any of this
So I asked the Dismount goes on Bill announces that everyone
Wednesday is going to be a special show
On his broadcast
Every Wednesday night we're going to devote
Threat
Criminal organization
Internal Revenue
Denver Federal Reserve
Turn Revenue Service
Russian Asia
Don't worry about it all
That's something that's not true but it's all good Alex Jones believes he talks about it all the time the IRS is just the collection are
I can see the seeds of his own destruction sown in this
So
Constant
Like
Like beliefs that are like
It's not
Real
That Alex has we can just Trace back almost directly
Two things of Bill Cooper
The last clip and I think it also is another thing
That
Alex
In his repertoire
The bill probably has a little bit more
But also I believe that's because Bill was a little bit less
Of a coward
And he was not trying to make it big
Conspiracy
Yes
Are we being manipulated and 10
Old and guided into a new world order the new world religion
Yes
Is there a group
Charger charge all along who bring this about
Yes
Where is old
Are the followers
Prevision
Oh no
Elizabeth
Evergreen
No
Future
Leaffilter
Our
So Bill know
Oh okay
Esoteric mystery religion and always and always
And far be if
For me to say that he's not
Somebody who also uses Eddy's medic tropes
To characterize is villain
Listen to enough of him to have a larger sense and nothing has
Stuck out to me as overt as a lot of Alex's
Stop but the episodes that I have heard where he talks about this
It's straight up like Babylonian mist
Nicole Coates
So it it's
But it's
The point I'm trying to make with
This is that like
Alex
Clearly believes that as well
And in present-day you talked about how everyone's demon-possessed and it's all this the devil is of operating so
System that lived on forever and
And all of history is had all these
Eat Valdez
It's very similar in a lot of ways
But Alex when he was starting up
And even into fairly recent times it's all been like
Now that's all mumbo-jumbo bulshit
Because he wanted
To differentiate himself
Bill does talk about UFOs
Bill does talk about this esoteric mystery religion
Wingstop
The core of all that
And Alex clearly believed that to admit it cuz he didn't want to
Be treated like yeah you didn't want to be put in the box
That was like oh yeah you already UFO guy all you believe in
Lizard people you believe in
Mystery Cults from
BC that are still running the world
Treated like that because on some level he knew that that was silly
He wanted to block now I'm just a meat-and-potatoes guy
I'm just a guy who's out here talkin about hard concrete facts
Documents
That's that's the presentation that he wanted
But as time has gone on that mask has slipped
A ton even see that even this
This sort of
Mystery ancient culture
Is something that he believes too and he probably always have
Yeah it does Bill was not afraid to wear it on his sleeve it does seem like if I was listening to the show with
With an i
At his at his age with an eye towards getting into this kind of thing
It's a real short
Leave to go
Okay I'll do his show
Rain in some of the weirdness I'll add some more bombast to counteract
That I'm talking about Les
Crazy ideas I'm going to add more crazy antics
To balance that out
And then I got shot the crazy Antics were even that much of his earlier
I guess some of that
The public access.
Supposed to
Everybody
Yeah and it's not it
It's a gold
It's not something that I would ever think
Is a
Like an intentional choice
But
You could easily see a way for you to fit in
Into the market
Yeah
By taking a lot of the stuff that bill does taking a lot of the elements
This and repackaging it a little bit maybe you had to give his dad a detailed business plan of how he's going to do Bilco per show
Show before you got that initial
I love this show
Yes I know I know
Find it to be
Be fascinated
Cuz Bill Cooper is
Crying
It's refreshing to see a person who has a point
He attempts to make
And even if the point he's making is dumb and the oven
Currency has forward is a hoax
He's still trying
Regardless of the reality unreality of the
He's trying
And there's a measure of
That's what he's doing even if the competence isn't in the
The research are the sourcing or anything
The presentation is compass
I think I'm struck by
Is how much of a statement bill is making
In this inaugural episode and how come
Complete the messages
Most of the episode of how they're about how there's a secret War
The public which bill is
Committed to fighting
That's a point.
I require some support
So Bill provides the underlying evidence
For his claim namely the silent weapons
Quiet Wars.
It's not real
But if it were
Then he would have made an
And supported it with evidence
Which is exactly what a show like this is supposed to
He's doing his job anyway the Alex
Refuses to
Or is unable to
Absolutely
But here's
That there's more to the state
Then just that
There's another statement being made and that serve by the musical q that he chose for the intro
Bill Cooper play The Beach Boys make it big for a reason
That wasn't
Just some arbitrary station
That wasn't the single
It wasn't played on the radio and the album
It came from came out
34 years prior to when this episode was recorded
Build shows that song to be played in the introduction
First episode
Cuz it speaks to his philosophy
Humble lyrics
Quote have a little faith in yourself in everything that you do
You know you're going to make it big if you want to
If you really want to
You can make it big
In the song whose lyrics are about becoming the big movie star and singer name in the bright lights
The bill is using the song
Flip the meaning
It parody
He's using the song about becoming a star in the entertainment industry to make a point
But he doesn't want to be a star
And never will
The fact that he's out here talkin about silent weapons
For quiet Wars
Make it impossible that they will ever allow him to make it big
The very idea is a farce
But he has a little faith in
Himself and everything he does
So Bill Cooper is going to make it big
But he's going to make it big on his own
It's really remarkable
Between his actual words and stylistic choices
In this episode Bill shows you who he is
Yeah
It's it's
Good radio
It is
Kind of infuriating yeah it's kind of infuriating on a on a certain level just is like The Grass Is Always Greener
Kind of like
We spent three years talk about that a****** whenever this a****** is available what I do and I don't know if we'd have
Wrestle with a lot of this stuff if it wasn't for
No that's what I say The Grass Is Always Greener
It's not to say that this show is going to become all the hour of the time all the time
But
I want to pursue this an atom
I have been listening to a ton of him and I'm going to keep blessing
Something to it because it
Really intrigues me
And I think
B u c
Because we spend as much time with Alex
We have such a
Familiarity with a lot of his rhetoric and a lot of the choices that he makes
Going back and listening to this stuff you just see the bloop
You see the
The things that Alex has stolen
Things that
Alex would never own up to being like
This is where I got this idea from
And I think
The more I listen to bail the more I'll be able to
Oh that's what Alex says
But he never provide the source
Rental provide source
They'll be able to track down a lot of cross reference
I think we'll be able to do that and I think that
That will be
More fun Wacky Wednesday
And because as we mentioned at the end of this
Bill does talk about alien
And Bill does talk about a bunch of stuff that fits into the wacky Cannon I'm in for it so this will be able
Leave the most fertile ground
And it won't be a situation where we'll have to
Cruel
To the collars coasttocoastam
We can just enjoy
The man-made Alex possible
And I learned a bit more I think I think it serves all our fur
You know we were talking about this
Just slightly
Recently I've just like
Now agree with you when you said
I don't agree with Bill Cooper but I do feel like I could
Could sit down and talk
Yeah I couldn't talk. I couldn't sit down at a bar with Alex and I talked at all not a person
Rights and all that he doesn't live
Where doesn't appear to live
As a fool
More than a character sketch
Carries himself in like you see it in interviews on his own show
Videos that he shoots out on the street
Eventually all of those
Situations are performance spaces
You can make the argument that a once the cameras off
He is a completely different person he's thoughtful consideration are all that you could make that argument
But you can you can say that
I see Bill is much more of a full human like someone you can have a beer
It is
Tumi
Bye
Just like
Comedy wise
You can tell
Forever I can tell doing it so long is just like
When somebody walks up on stage and they start talking like
That's all bulshit
That's
F****** b******* you can tell when somebody walks up and their beer
And you're like
Got it
Almost instant I felt that with Bill
That that whole like yeah you can have a beer with him is
So used by like
Trying to rationalize bush
Like I said
Tons of bills pinions that II would disagree with him
Aggressively to have that
But I think he could engage in that conversation
It'll be great if we sat down to my cable silent weapon
Prince's fake
I don't know how that go
I don't have that beer would go
Feels like there could be a conversation where is Alex or just yell at you exactly talk about how you're a devil and that's because you have a cross
Alex at that bar is a
Coward who would run away from a
Actual conversation and I think Bill would lean into it and be like okay
Let's
Figure that let me tell you what's come into
It's all right though
I built
Let's hear about pageant
Signed by the president
That means it must be real
Alright Bill wanted to give myself this gift is
I need I need things
Inspire me
And I realize that the things that I'm most
Twisted in are the things
They give us a larger understanding
The propaganda and the
Media specific
Quickly that are at the root of a lot of this page
Patriot militia anti-communist right-wing
World
And with Alex
It's so muddy now especially in the present day because
Everything has become so
Anyone can create their own media
So there's hundreds
Hundreds of
Dumb YouTube shows
That are all espousing very similar message
The back in the 90s
There was
There were only a few
You show
Yeah like a lot of them were on this wwcr shortwave
Broadcast
But
In terms of ones that are influential
A lot of people don't remember and never would remember
A lot of these other shows is known as
But people in that world
Were listening to Bill Cooper
This was a bit of a bottleneck
For a lot of these ideas being disseminated
What I find particularly interesting
Thing is going back in
And scene
Like we don't know what Alex was doing in 1990
B3 necessarily wasn't creating a
Product
He wasn't we don't have a lot of Records or any
But we can get a sense
Of him by
Is what media was he taking
Yeah and if we get a better under
Understanding a Bill Cooper and the hour of the time
I think it gives us a much larger picture of what his
Created
This
Gross
I agree I like adding him to our Rogues gallery
Immensely
So we will see where things go in the future but
Until then Jordan
We have a website
ITunes or other podcast will have to leave download leave a review or donate or whatever
We love you
But until then
Anil I'm Leo
Dzx Clark
I am the chairman
Of the citizens agency of joint intelligence
Holding
Alex