Damn important sweat it
I have great respect for its knowledge B
Dot-com
Everybody likes it around
A little bit about Alex Jones
Jordan Jordan Red Mountain
Of material for the show over the past anything in 2019 that you would enjoy
Moving on
No
Have Nots
It started out the year with an intention of having for recreational reading
Read as much Philip a dick
As I was going to try and figure out what
Went wrong
Where did he play
Did he start out completely insane ride it was a gradual process
And I made it through like
Maybe three or four of his books before I just got
Too busy with
Didn't have a whole lot of time
For that
Recreation
Life's crazy certainly when the late 50s would you
It started with like
Bring yourselves together I believe it was the first book
Forestview just kind of left
Nicole's
Start back over on the list
But yeah maybe I don't know we'll see
Unfortunately
Discovered I do enjoy reading
Stuff for the show more than I enjoy
Necessarily
Society materials Van Nuys Syfy so
That's where we're at
Not at death
Jeremy Alex Jones Christmas
Ocular to refresh everyone's memory on Christmas Eve
And through hatchets around the studio
It was
Maybe one of the more fun things we've ever experienced if you've not listened to that episode I highly recommend
And everyone go back and listen to last Christmas Eve
2018 Evansville
I couldn't save the bazaar Alex
Tries to hit one of his cameras
One of his own married
Pretty high
Today we're going to be going over December 23rd through 27
Alex's show
And unfortunately it's only actually the 23rd and the 27th
Because Alex took off
For the holidays for Christmas Eve
That is the best out of
The business for the holidays this year
So 1st Peter thank you so much you're now probably want to come
Melissa
Thank you so much
Janina thank you so much
Kevin thinking about you and I'll probably walk
Next I downloaded
Tik-Tok as a joke
Now I'm hopelessly
Thanks
I downloaded the doctor the broken
Next
Thank you so much
Text Leanna
Journal about
Thank you so much
Journal ecology walk
I'm a policy wonk
IU Morgan
Text Elizabeth
Elizabeth woman finally
Thank you so much
About Willy Wonka
I'm a policy wonk
If you're listening
Dorothy's dance website
Bruschetta
We have
2 out of context drops
Christmas indeed
What is
But here's the first one
Of course we're crazy
That seems
Pretty
I mean
The flip side of that
Can almost feel like I'm being a little whiny b****
Okay
Tops and downs
Christmas music swelling behind
Merry Christmas Merry Christmas
So Alex starts on the 23rd
Complaining
Because everyone that he knows any work
Is shadowbanned
They're all home
Well they're all doing such great investigative work but it doesn't matter
And honestly this just made me laugh
A lot because
I would describe this is Alex having a.
On the episode and getting getting the penalty
You know one of my greatest frustrations of my greatest joys
It's that my crew are reporters are researchers just turn out 5
Star research
And information
John bowne reports
Shadowbanned
Millions will see it if not
The footwash
Shadow
I feel like it's at.
Sober
Let's take this one more time I just complimented too much
Start it over
So I would say about the first 20 minutes or so this episode is just Alex trying to stress that the audience
He can't do anything
He keeps using this metaphor that the audience is
The gun and he himself
Does creating bullet
For them to shoot
These bullets are useless without gun
Anthony really needs you to shoot people with his information
I don't like this metaphor
It's. If you're in an infowar
It's
Particular Focus
Guess on this episode of this idea
It almost feels like there was a meeting behind the scenes where they decided that they really need to focus on raising engagement
It needs to be the focus
My s*** you need to shoot the bullets
Alex also promises there's a big report on Epstein
Incoming
Babies working on with alleged whistleblower
Sources
Is it going to remove a computer chip from
I've seen Scorpio or Heritage Studio serger
Alex also promises a big report on the evils of vaccines
The drop on Christmas morning what you can post all over social media
Uno's holiday
Christmas isn't saying happy
Holidays
Producing nonsense anti-vax social media content for everyone to put all over the place
You wake up you're like what the fuc
Yeah that makes sense
Christmas lunch so much better
Do the first 20 minutes half hour of the show is just this
We got this Epstein report coming
Back specialist exciting
So it's very dry territory
And then Alex
Let us know
We have big things
It really was a spy Chief really did overthrow governments on record
The character Jack Ryan based on
18 years 2002 Switzerland 2002
February 2015
He's going to be on with it for now
I'm starting to bottle that I found
Under Cover the Waterfront
Just wants to get out
Ford
This year ends
And he's ready to release a lot of information
I'll just leave it at
Steve
Chris
Information
He's got actually a really big revelation
I will I will say okay
Admission that Steve makes on the show that it for the I don't believe
True
Would be
Internationally important
Zodiac Killer
Heads of state
Something definitely
To the other Christmas
So his next 12 hours.
A lot of people are awake
You know there's a lot of people are awake
Shark
Is it well
When you talked about it being a real victory that all these people are awake
2 Powerstroke
Picture and what-have-you eat comparison
Is it to a different
Historically
And I do feel like he's comparing that Victory unfavorably to the current victory
You know it was 3% started in
Saw through the Revolutionary War against
Empire never been defeated
Blazing gentlemen we probably got
30% of the public to hardcore aware now know how
System works
It was probably
10%
5 years ago
Check
You got 30%
Where what's going on
They decide to move and take action you cannot mccleave militarily
Spiritually
Explain something here
This isn't
Overly positive statements true
We have one
We won back at Calvary where Jesus Christ
God took on our sins to sacrifice
I gave us an example
Kalimba
We really won now
And the globalist know that they want to take as many innocent people with them as they can
20 Souls
So I don't know you wanted a couple days before Christmas particularly wanted
Jesus died for your sins that was a victory but now
Just based on sentence
Structure that Alex believe somehow 30% of the population
Believing what he believes victory
Jesus dying for our sins on the cross
I believe
I believe he is comparing
His current
Tim Chipman little bit on the Revolutionary War 2
Anything. Also an insult to the 30% where he's like it only took 3% to start the Revolutionary War
Percent 10 times
Yeah there's a piece of
The Revolutionary War
Integrating
What should be a pivotal moment in history for him
Jesus
Write Jesus on Christmas
You have to throw a little shade on him and tell him that he's eating to s*** right
Did you started the victory but the real Victory is
Did Jesus dying on the cross tell 30% of the population of
No no
3%
Praise Jesus on this his
Aaliyah's birthday
Maybe next time you'll treasure up to me but
I got this one buddy
Weird
So Alex got news
Just tons of it
Stuff to
Like
Comedian Michelle wolf tomato joke
Alex is not happy about it
This is cancer
And wants to normalize
It's up to you
But here is Michelle wolf in her latest
Event on stage in front of a couple thousand people cheering
Talk about a mother
Killing her baby
So that she has power and place God
There's never been a more safe
Mechanically pure statement made
This is the definition
I'm Satanism here.
So negatively that you feel like you should have his sense of Shame after you get an abortion
Anyway you want after you get an abortion
Very powerful
You know people say you can't play God
I like a baby like Morgan Freeman
Don't knock it till you try it
Really knocking you going to get that baby out of there
Normalizing that are mothers
Power
Is killing her baby for her own satanic selfishness and enjoying it and
Sharing it
You can see what's going on if this is completely bizarre like
Very recent past
Speech type
Especially as it relates to Comedy
All the people complaining about racism or just
Tide sjws
PewDiePie's just joking when he has people hold up signs that say kill the Jews
It's totally a fun joke how count dankula
Comedy
But now Michelle wolf has made a jokey disagrees with so it's pure satanism
It's just sad
He is lazy as hell
Alex provides Michelle wolf made is normalize in something
Any other jokes
Arnot
The exact same line of attack he's taking here applies equally well to count dankula suppose joke
He's normalizing Nazism
Here Alex is embody in DeBary Behavior he claims to hate so much in the left
Call Joseph Watson
I would make a video
Complaining that he's virtue signaling
This is ridiculous is he
Went out
His way
After
Promo
Asian accent
Cuz the lives
And now we're getting
I can't handle it
All I hear is exhausted screeching
More offended
That's it
Good Times
Is there
Did you hear more news about Michelle wolf cuz I feel like that's going to come up with
Probably just come back up later bye
Not in any greater.
Detailed Michelle wolf is a Satanist
Did you know
Subway
Town of cannibals was discovered
Because it wasn't
But Alex's report
Civilizations are discovered
Had plenty of water and plenty of food when they collapsed
And there's not even signs of disease
They're all gone
You know they always find
Giant
A skeleton
That have been
53 months ago archaeologists in Germany found
Town in Germany
It's about eight thousand years old
Tens of thousands of
Skeletons
LMN butchered and eaten
And the scientists studied and found out they were
People from all over Europe
Some of them
Over 2000 miles away
I want to cover that story on
Are you going to talk
Stone Age
Found found
In Germany
Cannibalism in like why would they do that
That sounds
Out there
Just doesn't seem like a sustainable model really
Alex is talking about a recent discovery in modern-day Poland of a site
Well me to be fair the Germanic tribes and so there
Computershare
At this site archaeologist a sound 12 burial
The first-century BCE
What are the things that they're saying is really notable
About this find is it
People
Different types of
The funeral rituals
That isn't super shocking since Poland is in the middle of an area where there's a rich archaeological
Very old sites from various Germanic tribes
Beantown fairly regularly
Would still not
Why that's the case is not completely answered
Why are there so many different styles of burial
In the same site
So the varying funeral tradition
Does the presence of trinkets were pretty far away
Are both aspects of
To the site to make it a very compelling
Literally nothing I can find about this
The story involves
There's no indication that anyone was brought
To this town from far away to be eaten
There are no archeologist to resetting the actual site or saying any of this
Got to stop
Quite frankly unless there's some stories that I'm missing and I've read a number of them
I'm inclined to say that I was literally making all of this
That's not fair you have to
Take cannibalism a little more seriously dad
Not something you can joke about
I have two possible explanations
Think might be going on
The first is that he might be making this up
Because I know that you never read stories
He's just irritated lines and I'm Rick's on them
The headline in the express about the discovery of the site is quote
Archaeology shop
Gruesome discovery of mass Graves and mystery Ernst tons archaeology
Would you could see Alex turning into a story of finding the remains of a cannibal community
It's gruesome
Express
The rest of the details that Alex repeats
Most of them are in
The sub-headline
So I will be a pretty easy
But Alex just saw the headlines
His brain interpreted it and turned it to what we just heard
Another that's based on anything
Acceptance f*****-up head
The other possible explanation is that Alex has taken
Details from this new dig site and combining details about her
A very famous Graves that was discovered in 1996
And definitely showed signs of ritualistic cannibalism
Taking place
The time about 5000 BC
A 2009 study
Did strongly suggest
But the inhabitants there
Is cannibalism based on particular
Sound on
IPhones
But that's not really a consensus among the academic
Some believe that it's more likely that the Dead
They had ritual performed
For being buried
Which isn't too historically archaeologically unheard-of
The point here is that
Even if I were to just combine these two sites into one even the most ghastly stuff about her side is not
Concretely proven
And there's a large element of the story that absolutely just coming from Alex and his imagination
They all collapsed
Absent
To cannibalism Define
Alex will always bring up cannibalism if he is hungry
That is my new theory that I'm working on
Cuz everytime you bring do cannibals
He does have a certain amount of like
Things to eat people Easter just nausea
They pull the marrow out of their bones
I want a chicken
That's just how I feel about it
I don't know how we would test
Maybe we start sending Snickers bars
Whovian for Studio
Language stops shut off the Snickers bars
Cannibalism
It's the it's the 23rd Alex knows he's going on break after this for
Holiday
There is not
Much Christmas talk
That's not surprised
Surprising to me I don't think he's feeling great Christmas
Dover Mall
Is not enough atmosphere is coursework
There's a little bit of religious talk
The same standards.
Base better than when was weird that was weird
But dear God gave him a mission
We've got to strike
God isn't giving us this time
Providence
Directions
Because we're so great
It's happening because we're willing to do it
God will use these imperfect
We have been given the commission
We will carry it out
And I'll tell you this
A lot of people can see that I
It's almost 40 lb now
The same way I was
Except
Religiously taking the supplements boo Christmas spirit
The reason for the season is a lot of
Episode
Constant
Goddamnit Mission I'm going to carry it out and I'll tell you what I've lost a lot of weight everyone knows it
More like supplement my friends actually
It's really intense
That's the level of pivot
What's going on
Episode
You know these guys they just
These are the same people
Materialistic
Sewing material
Alex goes back from break
Talk about some of the good stuff
The tapping in the world some of the signs that things are going well
And one of them has to do with the
Making up numbers
Bowling numbers
But something I want to get into right now it's a very good news
Young people in major polls
At several articles on it
Against
Abortion
Anytime
And it's accelerating
The younger people get
And the teenagers
About 70% in mothballs
Amarillo sexy
A niche
Women
Girls that are leading
The charging that
What shows all their propaganda is backfire
Until the attempt to say oh it's fun to kill babies try it out well that's not going to work either
Volition
Against Michelle wolf
Yeah
Michelle wolf
I can't even find anything close to the data that Alex is using no idea
Like nothing I can find comes
Close to the contention at 6
Sixty-two 70% of young people are opposed
Abortion
In fact all the credible data I can
Find on this issue is the exact
Opposite
A Pew research
From this summer
61%
Which is the highest point that question is pulled at in over 20 years
The only groups that have levels of opposition to abortion there
Close 2077
Percent Republicans at 62%
I honestly have no idea
Talking about never says I can't find an article
Just making it Up song meme or something
I don't know
Youth Bible Study Bible study at the church that he doesn't go to
Something like that because
What
Yeah
I don't think people are opposed to all aboard
Daisies
I don't know any every single article that I can find as headlines like the neck
Generation is leading the charge
Reproductive health
Like all of them
I don't know I don't know about
The next generation is either
They are leading the charge in the fight to make the world a better place or they're destroying
Craft Brewery
Those are the only two types of article about
There's more ideological diversity in
The young set
Then some articles May painted to be
Can't find
Actual indication
Sixty-two 70% Universal opposition to abortion
Especially among young women
You know
I don't know I don't know
Citations
It is not given
So
This is interesting Alex plays Special Report
Baby was hungry needed to get a snack maybe around enough
Alex play the Special Report
You can call it a special report
It's really just a segment of Howard Stern Show
Compression making fun of him
The whole thing is a guy doing the impression he's at Hawking products shamelessly and saying stupid s***
Pretty accurate piece of parity
Honestly I feel like Alex would only play play that if he thought his
Politely on the hook
Because the risk of them seeing something make someone making fun of how Alex Cel shiting realizing
That's not parody
A high likelihood
F****** making you tell me I'm wearing clothes I don't even give a s*** anymore
But I suspect at this point Alex needs to
Self-aggrandizing
More then he needs to pretend he isn't just running an extended conspiracy info
So the fact that he's important enough to be made fun of by Howard Stern
It's something he could Bank on
Yeah but he's the biggest radio show ever the last
Did 20 years yeah they make fun of me because I'm relevant
About me is people not talk
Hey so is it that yeah
I get that
The whole cycle
That's crazy
Extended
After that
We get our gas
Merry Christmas to all our audience and adopters
Heilbrunn
That's how long he's been around
Delta Force
A whole bunch of stuff since then
These are record
Call in federal court over at I mean it's so we got to be careful.
Here on Arabi, source
Is always Q fantasies a stuffy this is a real guy
Okay
The Steve is on
Episode
You really good.
He's defensive
The first time he went through Steve's I was like are you telling me or you telling you
Because
I'm not convinced
Either way
I swear to God
He's not busy
I think he might have gone to Korea for me guys
Think he might have
He didn't but I think it's really interesting that Alex
Preface this by saying
Leo says something he should not say on air
Israelis did not know
This is a first
DD's right hand man
Assassinated
Because he was so.
Function
I don't want to play games where I start taking anything Steve says seriously
But it's fun
Is he Brown yeah it seems like it
I'm not even that he was just he just told somebody that
You seem depressed and then they assassination sentence
Explains it later anyway so Mike Massad guys
Just so you know I'm worried about I guess we should get him some help know you killed okay well you know there are two ways
To solve that problem
In the Clinton years
Steve's fake story
No no
Into the Clinton
I assume that
I bet
Man I don't know answer
Maybe it is part of his mythology that he was there under Clinton but either way
Neither ship
Alex
Really want Steve to talk about Epps
Episode really wants
How to get Steve take on it
Meanwhile
Steve wants to
To promote his new memoir
Oh my God that is going to be the greatest
Workout Alex is not
All that interested in helping
Steve
Okay really want to talk
He gets a little bit more than he asked
Because Steve is still on the air
Epstein is still alive
Kik
Epstein was working
The compromised people on behalf of the Mossad Israeli intelligence
Is not a road
In the past we've seen Alex be confronted by
Conspiracy theories coming from Steve
Who often resistor Insanity for a little while but time he starts to weaken
Stevens very persuasive
Alex is gullible
We start to see this Dynamic playing out
Again
It is true that
The body they took all the stretcher
Mainline photos AP you name it
Is not the same here that you're does even look
Everybody ran
That is a real photo
And it's not
Even the same
Ear looks nothing like it
So Alex is now helping Steve create
Support for Speedster
That's wild
Riddle
Even if the pictures used for comparison had no obvious problems with them would still probably mean
But they do have serious problem
The picture of Epstein alive
The use for the comparison
Is was taking 15 years
The only facial features features that are supposedly suspicious and being different in the pictures
Are the nose and ears
Wicker made of cartilage change in appearance over time sometimes significant
Changes over time is cartilage
Your ears are all
This is some super flimsy Superdome conspiracy clickbait
Pieczenik
In the past I've talked a lot about how Alex
What's keeps getting food by Steven
Honestly
I've seen it happen enough now and I key
Keep seeing Alex.
To himself
I don't know if he thinks that what he's doing is Playing devil's
Reality
I was just talking
Sailfin to believe in Steve
Just been a huge disaster I don't know why he keeps doing this
It seems like he's always doing a two-man game with Steve that he doesn't know he's a
Depart of
Because
He is
He is respecting Steve for being
Probably is involved.
You have to believe that he set in motion literally every important thing that it happened to the geopolitical scene
I feel like last 50 years
He's the most
Important figure in the world
I can't even put it into words everything from prior to and Post 9
Including nidal
But
But Alex is always trying to like
You liking that cuz I was like okay well you said something that sounds crazy but
You know when you think about it the ear didn't look the same so I you I suppose you know that part of your battery is Iraq that's the
Even Wednesday.
There were actors
Alex was
Maybe that's why I think
Try to play Devil's Advocate
It is not good at it
Yams of tricking
Himself
Mulder shouldn't play devil.
Advocate
So
Dino steps
I'm still alive
I also
The temperature is
It's as if the Swarm
The swan song for the Democrat
Also
Into
Impeachment
In this movie where is Columbine
This is her swansong that this is the swan song the entire House of Representatives
What we really don't need
We're not a democracy if we had a democracy
Computers
And just voting
Abbott
DeSantis will become more important
So representative government
Processes
The stripper whale
Fascist
10:58 that I-5
Doesn't seem to at all recognize that what he's talking about
Like pretty much come
Complete deconstruction of
A lot of the structure of government that
Is in the concert
It does seem like
Alex loves
And defend the Constitution against
All attack
But
If he likes you and you say you want to remove the Constitution entirely
He's like yeah that sounds cool if you want to knock down pillars of the West
Due process to as long as you are fun
Adjusting like you just wants to rewrite
The Constitution into
Just the second
The Constitution that they all want is just don't take
Yeah that's
Also Steve is responsible for the chakra beam
Big news
He was depressed I can't believe this didn't make all the disintegrator
I really would have time to talk
Spy chief
Kill you
Jon michaux
That's a big bombshell another another
Michelle is it apparently
I don't know I guess
Steve is a member of The Screen Actors Guild
Hollywood is finished
When you get a movie
The Irishman 180 million
Education
Decent decent shoots his mouth
Largely to give you a Flavour of like
This is kind of a lot of house
Steve talks
This makes no sense
Knossos T votes for the Oscars
Kind of believe that maybe if I don't know if any of the movies that Tom Clancy's had made
Did Steve has anything to do
Force or cyberteam or whatever novel
Siri right
Like what he has a producer's credit
Give me the PGA was involved in the TV show
Tom Clancy was trying to make
Sorry Terry Hamblin
Maybe
Is the most maybe you're in one
Assassinate but I do think he is in the academy
Even that being said
I don't trust things that you saying is why he wouldn't for the Irish
And they're both weird one is budget
The other is
Robert De Niro's political views
That is just ramble
Yes just a rambling old man who wants to tell you about like I don't like his movies. Does he talk s***
I killed Yitzhak rabin's and Robert De Niro talks too much
Also he said he would vote for
For Harriet
Sure
You're voting for Harriet
Because it only cost 3 million
I didn't I didn't think that was a huge huge
Whenever Steve is allowed to talk
For an extender
Stretch of time
Alex
The science that he starts to pick up on them
But
Not good
Pushing back at it like this
Secede from the Union
Florida
Secede from the union wouldn't eat the rest of the Union
The South
Size of Abraham Lincoln
The 12 Days of Christmas seeking salespad come to Infowars
The rise of Lincoln
So I think it Steven super super naive about what it would look like for either Texas or Florida to secede from the United States
They would then become independent
Countries made after workout trade arrangements with
With the rest of the United States
As well as other countries difficult particularly
Without being able to enjoy
Rate of the rest of the US economy that really helps
Create those
Trade relationship
I'm pretty sure he is assuming
That they do not even need those and they will self-sufficient Nation
Obviously
Because they have all the resources
Are some resources economy
Geographically neither Texas North Florida is what you call
Optimal
Possession
Florida's basically a peninsula of the United
States and Texas wouldn't even be able to block off transit to and from South and Central America
Since Thursday New Mexico and Arizona border
Consider even be able to
Create some sort of a blockhead
Create essentialness for some kind of Leverage
If they leave the United States federal government guess what else have
The US federal government stop sending them money
Because Red State make all the money and give them
Everybody knows that that's been backed up over and over and over again please do not to disagree
The past year Florida received over 237 billion dollars from the federal government 2100
Dollars per resident
Of the state
Texas took in about 200
69 billion dollars
These are the second and third highest totals of
Any state in the
So sure
Keep yelling you're dumb dumb s*** that
The South has risen again
This
The reality would Steve a thing
What are you suggesting would be a complete disaster
Pastor for the people in Texas
With all due respect
Florida and Texas
I care about the rest
To both of those States
Maybe a relative inconvenience for the rest of the United States
Yes
The restaurant
A conference somewhere else
We are Georgia
To make that work
It would be a disaster for those dates
Inconvenience
To do it obviously is yours
RX-8 United absolute prices of stuff
It would be a
Bummer but after after a while we'd all be like
This is the new reality let's move
Be Wild
Texas
I guess
I have to go bankrupt like Moody's
Remove their credit rating and turn it into just a
Stevens
Taking responsibility for killing eats a krabby
Claire's the end the representational government
The Oscars
You said the South can rise secede
Answer now
He starts rambling a long time but how he took down the Soviet Union
They are really is and I did I want to know about the technology that Scorsese
Nothing
So he just talked about how it was him
The first person
Singular
Took quite a bit
I think Alex is defensiveness
Set up again
A lot of this sounds like the people like this got some crazy all these guys race but I've actually went to the history books you did run
Do work around talk about your intelligence often sit around a bar bragging and patting each other on the
Still a little bit
Cigarette
Recognizing
Completely unhinged
There's no way
All of this is one person's lived experience
It's
Gila Steve I know this sounds like there are only two actual
For what you're saying my show and a mental health facility
But I really do believe you when you say what did you just say again
Got to get you off my shop
Has Mexico
Start taking some
Scholars want to talk
Steve
Harassed
If there's anything they can do to get
Get Trump to get
Is that the one Steve isn't
And he needs to toughen
Needs to get mad
Needs to bring Steven to run never fire everybody
To make Melania Secretary of State Driver
Yeah
Scholar
The answer is
Is there anything we can do to come together
To show President Trump and no matter what were with him
So he can start
Expediting his
Excellent point
Becky should
Together within your own group
Twitter
Communicate
We support we need to have
Trojan the next Administration
When you have a chance with present value for the general public says that's a fact
There's some real comedy embedded there
People can do to help get Trump to toughen up on his enemies and Steve's
Answers write some letters
What a lame answer
Now it says the Trump really listens to people
Good plan
You may recall
The trumps campaign was characterized by
Tells me that's about as strong as message you could give
If Trump is going to listen to chanting crowds I doubt he's going to give a s*** about your letters that he's never going to see to begin with
Is every Latter-day Saint
Every letter he also keeps a list
Who's been naughty or nice greater message do you need crowds chanting lock her up
What what more would you is there a paper trail
You can't prove that that you can't even prove he was there no one wrote lock her up
The real problem
So
It was next clip Steve talks
About
You know he has a bit more of a Christian Street
Disappearance than I've heard in him lately
Sing weird
Leading religious
Like I watch them
Milo yiannopoulos interview Nick Fuentes
Not too long ago
And Milo is very Catholic
I don't remember being part of his
Rams
Steve is is talking
It is nice Kobe's lamenting that
Fundamentalist Christians
Can't get along with each other
Fundamentalist Christians can't get along with each other
There has to be an ecumenical council we're in in America
Understanding the most powerful tools
It's not my ability to manipulate
True
The 12 Days of Christmas super sale has come to Infowars
Christmas sale now
Just keeps happening
Yeah so Steve believes that
He doesn't have a
Even thinks fundamentalist Christian is a
Troubling term
Believes it to be like that needs
Get together and if you listen
2D saying cuz he claims that he overthrew the Soviet Union
Christianity
Lead YouTube
Fundamentalist Christians to overthrow our
Yes that does sound like
Exactly what you were
It's not good
That's that's not good
That's not good
The colonels of what he's putting out
To imply something very scary to overthrow the United States government
I guess he thinks he's going to be somewhere in the ruling Council when it happens
What is
Carmen
There's a picture of the world that he
In his mind
I don't think even he
Find it to be pretty
You know it's like
People are holding hands and s*** like that I really feel like he's just
People up
Flicking their nipples
Feudalism
At work
Steve pieczenik appearance on Alex's show
Steve
Flatter the s*** out of Alex in order to make him feel validated
Prediction
Before 9/11
Blessed individual
What's the big building
We take a ride so it was all just at all lined up you can see it
So you just listen
Annabelle Cooper you guys are wrong it was Leo zagami we know this
There's so many details
Alex's want to be flattered by
Steve given what he needs
Oh yeah so there's going to be
Just coming back on good terms
It's very interesting to watch
Like there is a
Pretending we didn't have a falling out
Analogous
Gracefully getting back
Testing the boundaries he's throwing out Epstein still alive should I killed in soccer
It all five
You got it I personally got the
The pope to help inject Christianity into the Soviet
Steve pieczenik
Soother
Cope Whisperer
Break on the 24th 5th
Comes back on the 27th
I'm going to say he's coming in hot
Number 27
He claims that it just because he hasn't been on here for a little while so your team
Reality
Because
Giving a press conference
Where
He was asked about pardoning Rodger
Firestone and he said he hadn't really thought about it
Is really pissed off
Christmas 12 days we took off
Trump at a press conference and he talked about
Waterstone because of the question really thought about that which means he's not right
Obviously he has talked about it did you ran out of sight with a Rodger was obviously wrong
Close minded
The Congress that's a formality and that's not
I know you won't know that but
There speaks the whole issue
The trouble started doubting me
Frog
Herman agency
What does it say if they're just left
Stallone
It says it's open season
Supports Trump
It's okay Sean Hannity's Ray lose his job so soccer Carlton
Alex Jones
Prison
It's doing the hell out of man
What about my family in
Play Informer poison tell huge lies so I'm going to have to sue
Other people
Shmoney
Into this and Trump in the moment and I love Trump
But his biggest failure is that he can adjust apartment to do their damn job illegally spying on a candidates doing it
Monster president
That's what got CIA hearings and defense department hearings
Military coming after me it's the ivy Leaguers that have intelligence
Clarence's
Literally calling me on enemy agents and talking about how they're trying to shut me down
Newtown
I'm American citizen
Run over by a bunch of America
Openly say they hate this country
In Congress and I'm not
Allentown
Use Me Lord
People should be
These people
He's a God damn them
Cut that out
In the version
They do have a delay
Because they were able to cut that out
Used pickup
Clips from
But he does say God damn them
Clip
The right of it was
General
Two specific
Very very personal
Very very much Erin of grievances that were about my own trouble
Personally so hot
I would like him to fix that
Yeah it starts with like the justice department
People are being sold
You make that
Even at exactly even longer just
Complaining about his own s***
I meant he has to clarify
Kind of making this all about myself
Vengeance is God's
We need action
And it's not for me being under attack
Because criminals are getting more bold
Enter intimidating a lot of other people
Getting them to give up
I don't know I think it's just
Himself letter-writing campaign could get
It's true actually Alex launches something of an initiative here on this episode
Clips that I have
But it's more or less
Let's start protesting at Trump rallies
Okay he does he talks about a little bit he's like I don't want this to be like Nick Fuentes going out
Messing around with
Leading to a scism
We want to be friendly
But also inject our message
Protesting
You guys are just doing the sectarian 8in to create more
Like extremist savior communities
Inspired by Aldi
Go ahead
It's like they're falling ass backwards into understanding how protest
It's so
Yeah it's so
Step
So Alex is not doing great
Trump is going to continue throughout this episode here on the 27th
Confused State about his support for
For Trump
Susie Astic yes
Of course I support him but also like
I'm really pissed off
I'm starting to get
Really frustrated
Which is inevitable
They just hate people protesting so much whenever it's
You're not on my team you can't protest
But then whenever they want something they realize that the best way to get it is by
Protesting
It isn't
It's not going to go
Alex
Complains
That like
Justice not doing their job
And a big part of that is they need to f***
In jail
It's open-and-shut
Giuliani was on TV talking about how he's going to eat if he just had two people
And they put him in a position where
Prosecute all these dirty actors
All of them
And Alex agrees
Based on
Peter Tork Giuliani
He all he needs a two people
Thinking about all this supposed to totally true
You could convince these people
With your eyes shut
My God they went all over TV and said
Well you're their investigating my son so I should have that guy's not tired all the time I leave in 6 hours
Billion dollars
Sumbitch
Sit here and put up with that crap
Is really mad easily convinced that the case against Joe Biden to be open and shut because like
Classic television
And confessed his crime
If you pay close attention though you'll notice how Alex Jones
The gauges of narrative sleight-of-hand
He's so worked up in his feelings
Inflows
But he's very intentionally inserted Ally in there that's meant to support the very passion that he's expressing
Prosecutor fired
Because they were investigating his son
But the rest of the stuff that Alex is saying is true
It is much as I did give a speech retold the story of threatening to hold up money to Ukraine
This truth is only there
Damask the presentation of the LIE
Which is the bike
Motives were personal
Interrupt
This is a pretty important trick or propagandistic
Conspiracy theory
Most of the time and audience liked Alex's probably wouldn't even notice
Most of them are probably they already believe is true
Intertwining lies with real thing
Things you create a situation where you can
Play play
Saying that they had until he got on his plane
To fire the prosecutor
And your audience will experience it as if the motive
The part the part where you trying to stop investigation of his son
That's what being proven
The clip the Dozen
You can prove the true part
But the LIE is a lie
Connect to the truth to a lie
Then demonstrate the truth
And plenty of people accept the alai as part of the demonstrated true
I'm super basic level
This is kind of what I looked up all the time with headlight
You can prove that line by flashing YouTube on the screen
Can't really prove
Nonsense bulshit that he rips about the story
So when he tries to establish something he says is true he just references headline
Example consider Bill Joyce article in wired
Why the future doesn't need us
Alex is that a thousand times that article was about how Bill Joy went to a conference of high
Checkpeople
They do if they debated whether to kill off Humanity or turn us into a dumb dumbass
Sucked into video games
That is true
It's not in the article at all
It's completely a fabrication of Alex in Spanish
But his listeners have heard him talk about it so many times
But it's becoming internalized true
I've listened to thousands of hours of Alex's show
In the most I've ever heard him sites
From that article is the headline
Because for his audience
That's enough
He tells the story of what Bill Joyce
Supposedly said
And then shows the headline
The truth of the headlines
Combined with the story
And then all you need is that headline in order to
Approval I
This is a really important
Fundamental basis
Sick trick that allexposed sometimes it's kind of hard to disentangle some of
The pieces of it
It's a lot like
If you were
Injecting a vaccine with
Poison
Giving it to
Interesting way to look at
So Alex like I said on the 23rd he had a
Big piece that he was promoting we was going to have a special report about Epstein
Right sure turns out that Alex has decided
That he has evidence
That Epstein's operation is still running even though he's dead
Those
Wow Steve.
Think so
It's hard to keep you
Is convinced that it's
Still up and running
And I hear you talk about that
I mean it's like a bottle commercial
Are you going tomorrow
21 Alive
Either you pick the one you want
They look like they're 15 years old
And that's on YouTube
Do you
You know what's
Down the rabbit hole
We're just supposed to sit there and put up with it
And then the whole media is covering it up and running whitewashes and attacking us
All these people have signed on to this
Fox News
Signed on child molestation
That signed on with the Devil
Debray, tell us your sister again
You're the reason we're here you're word-of-mouth
Your Prairie Irvine sport
We got products you absolutely need
Blow you away
Wow
Great
I keep that quick because I want to demonstrate
Fully and very specifically
Using
22 mark
This is not something that is necessarily
Well fleshed. Certainly something he's doing a good job
Interested
In the story
But he's taking these
The sensationalising things about it because he knows that it's very popular with people on
He's using it to draw attention to his
Increase engagement
About here
He thinks he's cracked the case and discovered that Epstein's operation is still up and running
Because he just found out about a company called Blue
This is an aviation branding and likes light School
Classes operation
Business
It's run by women named Nadia Ybarra shaneco
I have no idea about the larger picture of her involvement with him nor do I know if a cantaloupe has
Anything to do with his crimes necessarily
But I do know that you was a figure was questioned about this matter as far back as
Is 20/10
New ground on the subject
The aviloop aspect
The story isn't really vanu either
Have you published
What's an article
Discusses her weird commercials commercial
Conspiratorial
Kill me for covering this b******* to it
How to put on a special report there was a little over an hour on Chris
He's just being an interview with the Whistleblower
Like I would he mention.
The 23rd at
It was a empty cherala Clint Eastwood
This
Metaphorically
This wasn't a whistleblower
It was just a guy who done some digging into the eps
Steve's story from a
Conspiratorial
Insisted on being filled in the shadow
It's just a guy mumbling through suggestive information but as a loop as if it's breaking news
A couple times
Not like that last night
Tell if it's like nervous last strange things on inspire
Also there are multiple commercial breaks in this special report
My point here is that Alex and his shadow on whistleblower
You're not bringing anything
Explaining it to create publicity for Alex
And I find that pretty distaste
Not only because
Cuz I had to watch most of that special report
Whistleblowers
Is very annoying
It's alright
Nonsense
Anyway
What are they up to
Want to face scan
Okay that's bad I'm against that sure
Coming to Las Vegas
This year
Which is I don't know how I don't I don't know what to say about that true or not
Representing
I'll leave that for another day
Because Alex
Get through talking about this story
Without
Veering
Into something
Barry rice
2019 NFL
Starting in Vegas
Starting in
Places like that cuz I know you're going to Vegas to have fun
Until you'll put up whatever they want you to do
Face scanning
Illegal aliens in anyways
Illegal aliens are allowed to hit-and-run rob steal kill
They're just given driver's license in New York
Another place at LaGuardia labor
Starting
JFK LaGuardia
Chicago and that was JFK
Wow show all of this is going on all of this is happening
In your face
Illegal alien
Driver's license
A driving test only citizens have left how it would be racist if you're from another country
Wild
Let me see the footage of thousands of men
Wind-up
To get their driver's license
You don't even need the test
Just like you can shoot a woman the back and she dies for no reason as long as she's white
Shooter in the back at the pier
Who's your dad
It's okay
As long as she quite
Yeah
Alex is completely misrepresenting the issue by immigrants getting driver's license
Because of course
And of course he's turning it into a narrative it's primarily about how he feels like he's a victim because he's white
Right off the bat it should be pointed out the driver's licenses are given out by the state not by the federal government
6th April very a little bit
It's generally true but there might be slight differences state to state
They're currently 15 states are undocumented immigrants
Can apply for driver's
And there would likely be more ads that lists
In most of these cases all that was really done is to
Sephora
Application to be substituted for the regularly required Social Security card
Is a form of
Be given to drivers
I did not know I don't know what the breakdown is on the state-by-state but from everything I can tell this works exactly
The same as if you
Just was slightly different document required
Right
You would still have to take the written
For sure
The driving test do you have to kill
I know that in some states you don't have to retake the driving portion of the test if you're applying for a license in your old one hasn't
Or if it just recently expired
I assume there may be some states that allow that in these cases to
Like if you have a current driver's license for Mexico let's say you might not have to retake the driving
Portion
Maybe
But I feel like circumstances like that aren't the norm
You still have to take the
What are the main arguments surrounding these measures
In favor of it is this
Some research has indicated that licensing immigrants were previously unauthorized safety
Obvious reason is that they're required to pass the test
Yes that usually yeah
Just pretending
He's just making that
Another reason that is important is
They can get car insurance
Which makes things way safer for everyone
Most of the metrics you really want to focus on
Insist on documented immigrant
State revenues increase overall safety improve
Able to pursue work
Opportunities more easily than connected
The only real way to be against this is if you really want undocumented immigrants to be miserable and ultimately gone
What's going on
Beginning this episode Alex was mad at Trump
Yes
He's
Here's the thing
You meant for that to be a
Clean take
So he could post a video with a
Flashy headline to try and get Trump's attention but he got sidetracked
Replaying about Epstein style thing
You think it's them up with a very simple headlight
But
Fear not
Editor
He discusses how they should edit this video
Rodger Stone information
In the next segment
This next segment in
With segment
Smyrna post at 2
Banned. Video
Alex Jones
Blows up at Trump
Did I know those have a messages
To the president
Why isn't the president standing up for himself and others
President Trump's greatest failing
Message from Alex Jones
President Trump please stop failing us
Help us
Gobus
We're good Americans are under attack do your job dependents
Trump Lilly title that video
We'll figure it out
Why right now and
Forget that video
I'm supposed to send it to the campaign and the White House and then
Did the Secret Service
Send it to the Secret Service
Alex fields
Desperate
Yeah
As bad
I need Trump
Detention
We have to make a headline that sounds combative
It does seem like Trump likes to fight with people
If I say something he gets messages like
Yeah yeah
The title
Instead
Really freaks out about
Accu
And I think one of the reasons they get around this
The 27th there was
The number of
Queue account
Trump was retweeted
That's true pissed off about
I want to see action I want the Q thing the greatest human movement of private
Okay well that deliver some indictments
Greatest things Americans ever did
And you know I thought all the gas we had
Do anything on the show we didn't
Creed the boxing punch the present
We didn't influence Stephen Miller
No
My mother didn't give birth to me you did my father and skills
Who is God
Curious
Next week everything's fine
We won go we all go it's like you guys are welcome to call into next time I get the number of
Tell me tell me how I'm wrong
That
She was up here on Christmas Eve
We salute you too thank you
2 weeks
Call Edwards
So far so I want
Talk about all that too
President's press conference
Alex is soap
F****** jealous of
Twitter bot
Anella
Does he understand man
Also doesn't it there is a bit of a personal
I do feel like he was convinced MyQ for a while
BMX
I was hoping for you I wanted them.
Necessarily think that's
My sensors
In the feeling is more like
What I could have done
Yeah it's almost there
Wish I would have worked out a little bit of it,
I was in AAA
I was in AAA in a venti
Promoted one guy to the show and he wasn't as good as me and that's why I honestly also feel like
That
It's it's the same sort of thing is like
If only he'd listen to like Max
Kyser way back when he was telling him to get into Bitcoin
If you would have just gotten in the right way
You probably could
Made a killing
And I think there was that
Missed opportunity
The opposite of buyer's remorse
It probably feels
All of these accounts
All over Twitter with huge massive audiences
He's got to be furious
We live in a weird world
Where the president
Is basically a chain email
May I come to life
Man want to talk about that a little bit later
Crazy do not play
So I need to send
It's that for headlines to get to
So we got to get to the news
Conservative Publications is telling people
Encourage your wife
I have sex with other man in front of you
Encourage
Relationship
Literally
You don't want me anymore
Literally I got stacks of that new to Redbox today weather
The family show
Wow this is
Yeah man
Tell your wife to arrive
I mean
I don't know what conservative publication
Swinging
Is manly
You better about this
Not in front of you
Never do that
Keys in the bowl
But not while he's watch
Exposition
The need
To cover that butt
When he gets back
From break
Down to business
To do his video that he's going to direct
It's basically just like the same thing he's already
I'm saying
What criminal keep doing what they're doing
But you didn't lock him up you let him go organized again and try to rob the bank again
Us
Paulie scams
Roughshod over conservatives and Christians
Bully everybody
I'm not going to sit here
Lead action press
Centrum
Number of
I want to get your take on what
Probably to do with the new year
That's really sad to me is that he's absolutely
Absolutely everything that I've seen it
He says though
Make a stand
Is it always just
Talk
I don't know if it's
It's infuriating
To watch so many of these guys
Alex and and just come so dangerously close to realizing that they've been scam
That they've been Griffin
They don't
They just can't cross that line he's so close
To realizing what
Everybody 25th
What
What are you doing
Trump with Griff
He's a liar
To make his own money
It's really tough to tell
When you're on this ride when do you
When do you sell
Bitcoin avoid the downside
Trying to figure out what that is
And it's constantly not yet
Reviews on that line I think he does know that eventually
It's got it at
It's not going to work out
I think I'm at evenwood through job are not happen
Clearly
They think he's trying to say Victory from the jaws of defeat as it were
We're like trying to get something out of it
Maybe I get back on Facebook
Roblox up Hillary
I can't out that none of this is because right now
It feels like all of this
Has been a massive waste
Convince
Stop
I think he's trying to acclimate a little bit
Almost that Trump is going to disappoint
So you talk about that
Trump World still needs
Me
Imma go to break I'll get to the Press, just makes me so mad I could think about it
Cuz if you leave Rodger Stone out to dry leave anybody that's right I believe you do the right thing
Look what's happened to Assange
We got Trump elect
Okay
He needs to protect the Republican American people it's his job plus
We
Went through hell to get him in there you did
We put Trump in there
He just one waving his fight
We're getting
Global kicked out everywhere we're having surgeries on planetary scale kit critical operation stay on here
The Cavalry from Trump is never going to
Start thinking
The Cavalry incoming where the cavalry
And you're the cavalry
Do standwithus ladies and gentlemen do your shopping and infowarsstore.com
Silky smooth
Frontline's at
Ww.w.
Sometimes
The sales are funny
Sometimes it is like boring like yeah gif
The krill oil or whatever
Whatever
Sometimes there
And we were blessed
On this December 27th episode
Was one of the funnier moments that I've ever heard
We have the very best supplements the very best books
In film
A lot of really great
Patriot apparel
T-shirts so they're okay
Apparently some pictures are the best infowars.com
Or 888-253-3139
I got the new don't visiting for sure I love that
Black Panther
Kill yourself shirt is a piece of History
Dcec monetizing
Stop really aggressively
But I love I love the idea that he's like
Get some don't get subs
Humility yeah it is a very strange place
He's always the best in everything but I think he's blaming the shirt people
You know the manufacturers who make the actual shirts
All right I got to check p.m.
Tickled
That is such a weird place for the
Come back after the break
He's talking about
Earlier he said that he was trying to brainstorm
Two name
Detention
And I think he realizes that whenever he gets mad
Trump
He gets drunk
The temperature whenever he lashes out
He gets the attention
Explicitly says
And I'm just telling listeners
The White House listen to you
Everytime I get mad at Trump he pooped out to enforce videos
Okay great thank you mr. president
Because I want to get those videos
And defeat
What show solidarity
We appreciate
That's great mr. press
Dashiki stuff every week
The media doesn't even attack
I don't know what to do
What to do
He's not doing that's wonderful
I want to see indictments
McCabe
Call me
Hillary
Let's start with frock
But start with Paige
Let's start with or
Let's start let's start let's start let's start let's start
I haven't really looked at Trump's Twitter account in quite a while
See if he tweeted out any of Alex's stuff lately
Holy Ship
What a mistake
Twitter feed is just drowning in stupid memes and retweets of obviously fake account
This would be really upsetting as a feed like if you decide from anyone
Let alone
The president
It was not a fun clip
As well as pretty much most of social media
Disaster area
But it's my journalistic duty to at least scratch the surface of these thing
Went back to
To see if Trump really did push Alex's stuff after Alex got mad
I figured that
The time
Treason
Recent example of that
December 4th
If Alex's promises correct and you'd expect to see some info
I did see two tweets where Trump was retweeting the Trump organization
Promotional tweets
For the 2019 season
Be there in 2 weeks the southern
!
Totally constitutionally okay thing to do
I also sought a tweet.
On my way to Hershey Pennsylvania for a rally see you soon
I love Hershey's chocolate
Really
Like a child I can't
I can't do it can you imagine if we had a break-in in 86
We're able to tweet
Bananas
Like the the mushy brain of these two guys
Hershey chocolate
Christ you're plenty of retweets of Breitbart
Which I didn't know existed podcast podcast
Information.
I think Alex just perceive the Trump throws them a bone whenever he starts getting mad
I don't know if that's
True
Stretch
I think that's the illusion that he likes to live in
Whenever I get out of line Trump gives me a sign
True
The squeaky wheel gets the oil kind of dehydration
And now the show gets
Weird
Now
3 years of our show or
This episode takes a turn
I don't know what prompted him to save it
I got really excited when he did
Richard Reeves is in here at the bottom of the next hour
My nose I'm bad about doing stuff I say I'll do on everything
Get busy and forget
They're going to put on screen over here
Dodge dealership
I'm going to tell you
The big secret of the New World Order
The big enchilada
The real deal
The factions are
Decision you gotta make you want to have a happy happy stuff
You going to get it today I told you no more games like still much
Everything everything's going to come out
No more games
I swear
He said that directly to you and he is not to deliver
With you I swear to God
Did I swear to you right now but anyway
You know he's not going to deliver
Don't do the words almost word-for-word
Exact
Tell you what you're saying not that he's f****** with your clothes so that would be silly
But I did hear that message
There's no way I can
Let me put your reminder.
Does
Okay
But it's
Forced
Brief
Probably
One of the most insane things I've ever heard him say I like it
2017 steel Megyn Kelly
Dude
There could not be a more invalidating thing for Alex to say is the heart of the New World Order
Pixie
Episode
About nothing for awhile
Mostly I mean
Mafia goes and harasses say
All the cleaners in a certain part of a city
If you don't pass protection money
Something bad's going to
Happened to your
They're picking up
Laundry
And then when they don't somebody firebombed the laundry
Or the grocery store
The FBI goes and they arrest
The members of the mafia that came in and threatened the store.
So this is my to be like I do got arrested
You got to rest all of these people
Clyde Mafia like that never took off and places like that
Texas
Because if you walked in
Dry cleaners
Texas with a Texan on it
You said
You're going to give us money or something bad's going to happen to your business you would be killed right there
Yubikey
Did you came into their business
And said we want money we're going to kill you they pull a gun out and shoot you
I kill you just like that
People that I grew up around the last group of Texas wood
Kill you
Just like that question of it
If you mess with them
Olivas Mexican Mafia
Stuff here because that's not what I was
Alex is full of
Denton Texas
Dallas crime family
Coincidentally because
Alex grew up in Dallas so
When this is all over operation was up and running to saying is true
The Texan
His ego is so wrapped up in his legendary character that seems impossible to him
Did any Texan will be shaken down by a criminal
Let's just as feelings
He's talking about makes no sense
Shouldn't he know that there was bumpy and Texas based on his JFK conspiracies about Jack Ruby
Gymkhana Joseph
Don't even worry about it
How could you not
The myth is the cowboy
And in the Wild West
No one was afraid of criminals criminals definitely didn't go from town to town
Because everybody there was a tie
Everybody's fired on
For no reason
Open for a bit
Gibbstown
Do saying something pretty shocked
Is that
Doesn't
Purge the
Abyss anime
Trump's got to go
Okay and also this clip involves
Wannabe longer pauses
So your phone
Fair warning
A very long.
Trump and Republicans
Are going to go to war with the Deep State and they're going to remove these devil worshiping stomp for Trump needs to be removed
.
And we need to get somebody in there
It'll do something about all this
Because I'm done
Free number to join us
13 second pause
Realizes
The government will get somebody well
Yeesh I have always been
That was supposed to be
Edit it out and put to put in that video
Hey.
Might be the reason for that
Eatzi's has a little bit more about it and like
You pissed off either
Enemies out of government
But he's also wants to make sure they do
I still support
These people
So stupid
The president
I pray for justice and I support the president
I support him
In this campaign for another 311 days
But man
Am I going to feel suckered
He gets in the office again in these people are
I'll get in trouble
They are going to kill sucker
You sure this is the same thing you said
Is the real deal has been tricked
But I'm going to feel sucker doesn't solve our globalist
Crisis immediately ask her it's
Stop it
Oh man-seok
The place
Really the reason Alex can't let go
Is because
Like
Trump only won because of him
Everybody
Within Trump
Orbit during the campaign
Was just
Ripping off Ally
Alex is
Basically the present
Really think about it I really do think
There's a lot of Demands we need to make of our president
We're not the cult here we put him there
He adopted the Nationalist
Patriot movement as an operating system to counter the globalist
Because the Pentagon came to him
He called the operating system America's always had
Jones's popularized it
We've we've written it into a codified plan this evening the New York Times They attacked
Steve Miller
Got adopted by Bannon man I didn't come up with all this
Is a movie screenplay writer
Okay they wrote a screenplay off this show
Total left so pissed they got all the phones tapped they know
I know the White House still listens
Everyday
Okay
I'm not a screenwriter I'm Alex Jones from Texas for real for real
I just I don't even
I don't even believe that you believe that I know
That doesn't sound sincere
But you saying you mean this I don't think you mean that
But I do think he means it's even better sounds a lot like a
Great
I just feel so much
Anger
Bactrim
Yeah why does it is petty reception
Seems to be like you're not paying attention to me you're not doing what I want you to do
I'm going to lash out I'm going to start talking about how it was only me that led to you getting where you are now
You are everything to me and now you're not taking care of me
Sad
In this next clip
Early did you know that billares leads antifa
I did not know that
Nowell we saw him just recently at the Chicago teachers strike he was not leading into
And I didn't realize
Stop all civil unrest
This country
Is
Bust some antifa leaders
Right because find their contract
It's like the one he found on
Fortune
It all the way up
I refuse to believe that he so dumb
The feds
Gobus any local antifa leader they're led by the weathermen
In Berkeley they're led by famous professors in the weathermen
It's the weatherman
That means.
Officers and everything
Let me go on our methods and idiots don't know what they're doing
Organized crime racketeering ladies and gentlemen
You didn't always off-limits if you don't got them they persecute you they ban you want the proud boys or Imports
Because they're decoys
Stage makeup
And soros's Son runs if we got the secret documents BFDI confirm they're real
No it didn't
Planning to violate citizens civil rights to keep people from having her speech trigger race riots
Target local government Police Department
Overthrow city government install
Globalist over cities in blue cities are under their total control
And some red City
This is
So disconnected
Man contracts
Confirm a lot of stuff
It is
This dumb
Really wants those contracts
To be real
Text that they are
They go against
Every
Possible
Reality
Motivation that any actor is the
Situation would have
Contradicted
The only people who would
Ever consider making those documents
Are out are you
But he needs them to be real because they are proof that Alexander Soros is basically running a terror
First organization
And that as he's talking about it that leads him to
I'm going to save this
I don't think
People to kill
Soros fam
Sure I do think it's debatable
Whether or not that's a message
You could take from this clip that's not a good
And neither is this
Do you understand. You can't leave Soros and the globalist
Going around the
Villages
So they need to know
We know what to hit
Do you think they want us off the are we
Have the Death Star plans to use that allegory
Man
Put a devil worshipping Aleister Crowley pedophile I'm not going to sit here and let these people run my life
What about you
About you people
Real I think that's a potential reading of it is
Is normal tone
Starting what you can't allow people like Soros
Wandering around on the streets
Tulsa Lake
I think you could take that
Context clues
To do to
Satanic demon pedophile
You know you could
You could make
Pretty strong case
Pretty
F***** up I mean
I do believe
The townsfolk
Upon being confronted with Frankenstein's monster
Decided to hold a free and fair trial
Let him out on bail make sure that everything was process
Yeah they were really into that if I recall correctly that's how they wanted
Yeah I'm intuitive Oaks
Violence
These people
It's just not good
Good going on
Jesus
Tradition in our modern
Episodes
This is much more
Regular
States on that topic
Too long cuz he's got to get back
Petty grievances
Temporarily
The weather
I'm not backing down
Whenever
Grandmother you know what thing everybody was turned on Trump
I said it's all boats out of context locker room talk
Everybody cuz you're the one
You're the one
Little Talks
Contacts
Do you have the Mossad assassinated
He's not racist
W3
They were trying to panic everything right there to get folks to turn on front right at that moment
I think it's hilarious
That is a
Big swing
That's all Ludacris purse is
I started
The funny thing is Alex's take on the n-word tape
Because if you recall
Capybara
Was someone trolled Paul Joseph Watson
By sending him a Twitter direct
Message
MBC
A copy of the
Or had seen it and the media was going to run with it
Disgaea
F****** with Paul
Deliver this message to Ali
And in January 2017
And recorded
Probably on a plane you can hear people in the background but it was such an emergency for him
That he needed to get ahead of the story
We are now about three and a half days house
Event taking place
Call Watson Road
Score yesterday
Concerning a nbcsports
Quality horses
Anyone might be under open
Take compilation
Whatever
The Apprentice
With him sitting in the chair
Things like it sounds retarded and
Shelves
And supposedly the n-word
A long time
Does white
Basically tell dirty jokes getting tingly comedian would do
Austin
Almost
Believer
Break the ice
Portraying at the house
Started Locker otaka graduation
II
I refuse to believe that a human being exists who doesn't
Look I don't care if there's a tape or not if you think that
Trump doesn't say the Edward
You're insane
Crazy if you look at the decisions he's made about like renting his Apartments Central Park
I think you'd be
YouTube
Beyond credulity
Plenty of people believe that and support him for it
I think you are a Beyond ridiculous
If you don't think
I mean that's just silly
Alex just silly
On Twitter was to say that he looks credible
And then do damage
Because obviously he would do that
Control for the inevitable release of the tape
Thinks he's coming
He's not
It's not real
Alex Goes to call
And this first caller is
Upset
I think Trump needs to call out the Marines
I think he needs to arrest people they need to be tried for treason
We all hate the police States the police state is what the less doing lawlessly using the apparatus against American people
Election
What you do they let us to this point it's the default position
I need to be arrested they need to be cleaned up and the American people will support it
Yes I will there be behind him 100%
1 Seasons crossed safely his second term Alex
He needs a third term
He wants or needs a third term we need to add mediately after getting a second
Well that would certainly draw them in a conniption fit
You see a little bit almost exasperation from Alex after this guy was like he needs a third term
I think that's a little bit too much for Alex
Calling out the military cleaning out his enemies
Alberto double-down on that
Yes absolutely
Also he needs a third term
That would freak out the laugh
God
Stupid hats
They just
Also never read a history book also that implies that this caller thinks that situation
The equivalent
After World War II
Exactly
This is what's great
About this imaginary war with these imaginary enemies
It never will be done
The premises we can rationalize keeping him in office as long as this war is on
Use back door to dict
Damn right you telling me no s***
Every
How do they how does it
Still happy
The idea that you would trust
The guy who's currently in government break
Reason to get rid of their enemies
Even if
Even if it's real
Always use to turn everybody into a dictate that I would tell you that ten years ago
Years ago
And they still do it they still cry for it
These people are insane
Tried
It's best you can to get
Trump's attention on this episode he's threatened
Steven title on one of his videos
Maybe I'm out
After you get reelected
No I think he's just sending to implied threats
I want Rodger Stone
The day
The
Sentencing February 7th attending
Simple dammit
I need my God Rodger Stone if he wanted to
Destroyed
Add stop just what the what the media knows about Trump
Wood would wood would really hurt from poke
Jellicles and others it's not like Trump gay or something but
For not being a gun
Rogers just well-known okay
His wingman
Get your buddy out of jail man
Do jack
You didn't lead with a didn't do Jack crap he has damaging information about you
Ebel's
F*** you over it
Exactly blackmail
I mean it's it's
Handrblock
Not good
Garlic sticks another caller guess what this one's upsetting to
Young lady
We're done sitting here on our hands
We're done we're done with the talk
Millions and billions
There Will Be Blood
OKC
I would say
Play past the point of where people
You don't have a right to take
The problem is they set it up
That's why
It's critical
Put that violence in the action politically
Just imagine how much energy you can spend waking people up letting Trump know that you want action
Had to use that type of energy
Innn win
Offensive op
False flag us
Obviously we never Target innocent people to Walmart obviously wouldn't get Target the police
It's people like Nancy Pelosi son people like Hunter Biden all these Criminal
Bubble off some of their nose at us
Why are they the ones
Staged
But go to a trump rally peacefully
Just wait till he pauses and then say Rodger Stone infowars.com
Know your friendly they'll agree with you and then
Message to everybody
Holyshit
I'm happy
Alex didn't offer him a job
Quite frankly
Tired
When you create a really highly intense and then give
Citations
Hey the thing that you were really angry about is going to come in this guy is going to deliver it when you know full well that then.
Any other Outlet other than this anger
Expression
Is manifest
It's The Logical endpoint of a certain amount of people
Who gets sucked into things like Q
Gyro Express
Alex's response to that isn't so much
No
Hey
They deserve it
Of course they do way past the point of deserving it
It'll make us look bad if you do hate those people first things that didn't
Happened
You respond whole thing to say
Context
And then it leads to pay Duffy's Island
Give me free press, make everything better
This is really bad it's really really bad
That is that is
Like if you have people up into that much of a friend in public
Saying that to all of his fans
They would have
A round
There is no
And then go
And no
You guys are acting all crazy
I need to focus on you put up signs of my show
We just need to
Put up sign saying no more witches here
It's absurd
Do you see that
That's what I
What's keeps
He's trying to transmute this violent anger that is the natural
The disappointment
These
Aspiring authoritarian followers
How can I monetize
Is this
Instead of recognizing it as a really dangerous sign about what
Community
B he
Speaks to his wife
Create very high percentage of these callers are
Deeply disturbing
Prank calls
And
I've never found his calls to be
Great
4 healthy number of them lately has been along these lines
Sky and it's not
It's not something that you should take lightly
Orbi
You should feel respond
No it feels like
For the past
Wife
13 years
The right-wing media machine has been
Edging
18 to 35 year old men with white match guns
With all these guns and then just never let giving them that released
And now it's really coming to the Boyd of a boil
Yeah like so many of these guys
You've told me that there's Tyron
Gif
Where do I kill people
It kill
I find that to be upsetting
And I think Alex is in a situation where
He has a responsibility to
Deal with it
Settings not
Betty White
We'11
Because I was promised
Esther reveal
The big secret
Of the Illuminati
So here's the thing
He is Richard Reeves
Richard Reeves I don't know he's a friend of his
Being back in the system
He's credited as a reporter I don't know if he is
You was just somebody who Infowars head out it like Trump rallies back in 2016
He doesn't come up much I don't I don't know
Marcus Theaters
Trump supporter
He keeps wanting
But in but Alex is like what you want later
Steve pieczenik
Text Steve
Plug is Bucking up
Has something he wants
To get out
And it's Bass
Sickly
That we should bring back America
Can Empire
So
Yes
Wow
Where Alex goes with that
Is very upsetting
And I think invalidation of his entire career
Because the secret of the New World Order is upon
What I wanted missions before you leave I know you got to cut out you got a lot of work to do
But why is our flag only have
50 stars
You know recently it came out in the news 23 months ago that Trump was looking at buying Greenland or whatever and
Corcino
Now the whole country whatever is fine.
Why don't we just go ahead and
Do an expansion Safford
And potentially make
Bring another states of Union all over the planet
You know in the street
Design for not expanding or Contracting, just taking people over
How about we say hey you want to sign on bringing in that way exactly we can have 100
Population
Weekly rally Nation
The country has a big secret of the New World Order is
Sold it as that
But then it wasn't what it was over now make it hottie logical and people want to join without being made
There's no reason why we can't have 100 stars in that Bluefield
I think it would just have to Haile that countries we should
We should approach countries that are most like ours that the people are ready I mean what about the
Get with the program
Maybe get with the program
Shopkin takeover the new world
World government
I am no
Reviews
The big secret of the New World Order is distinct bad
Cybertruck
You shouldn't ha subiaco
To send these guys to some sort of school
Any sort of you should have to eat
No community service no jail time you have to go to classes
And learn about the s*** you are saying because you have nuts
Do you hate emigrate
So much
So let's just let them
States and then they have free right
The Traveler
Future. These people are so f****** stupid
Extension of
Expansionism
Bring back the days of colonial Empire in
And whatnot
Which
Probably isn't a good idea
Whatever it is
Question that I really hate
Is is is that
Alex
Who's going to reveal is the big secret of the new world war was that improvised
If it is
I'm flummoxed by The Secret of the New World Order
Can make an ideological
New World Order Guide
If that was intended that's insane
If he's just riffing around it that's what is Braintree
I think it applies on something
One World Government
So
Every single thing about like what he pretends to stand for it's completely invalidate I walked
One World Government
Asterisk
Wagner's list
He is saying that if we don't do it China
So at least he has some excuse there
Secondarily
You not necessarily talking about a One World Government
Just talkin about
Countries around the world that are now all America
The other countries that are now China I guess he wants
To World governments that will be in a battle for
It will end with one of them being successful
Most likely both of them
This is dumb
Go to school
This is very
Is there a child
Is Christ cic a very weird
Mixture
No singing Have Yourself a Merry Little Christmas
Nothing better than Jesus that's at least one
You know there's Justice
Mixture of
Really
Petulant child
Stuff like the I want Trump's attention so badly why won't you give it to me
Yeah I must Crush my enemies
And you're not doing
For me
You have that mixed and
Sweetly
Luda
Chris ideas
Like Steve
Coming in Target
The end of representative government
The South has risen again I killed Yitzhak rabin's
Basketballs in that is coming in have a conversation about a need for us to be alone
One World Government right
You have these completely ludicrous ideas being presented
But how would you explain why
Florida secede
Okay we're going to
Texas if we are going to add in let's go with
At one's ours now
I'm going to go with we split Australian half
I will take Sydney
They get Melvin
What else
I think that's what they're doing
Exist
As ideas
Just talkin
Bulshit
To the audience like all these ideas are
Yeah
And then at the same time the third element of it is this input
Callers isgro
To appoint of
Really scary input
That mirrors some
Pretty scary things
So you have these three trends that are just
I don't even
The show is
Is it very bad
It is interesting to me but only inasmuch as like
I just continue to be just overwhelmed by the idea that people listen
Come to it and take it serious
Especially in the present-day the more this intuitive
I can't believe people can't see through
What he's doing
He can't see through it Trump is doing I guess so he can
You can see that he can he can
He can't he can't bring himself to
Too and I imagine that's the same thing that so many others
He can't bring himself
To because there's a financial motive
I'm not sure how many of his audience members have
It sucks
To admit you've been
True it suck
Admit that
Person that you believe so mode
So much
Is actually a lying piece of s*** grift
It is a
Common response
To just say
Doesn't matter
Denial
And it's
Reading
Towards
Dangerous
Conflagration
Absolutely we will see what happens with that
Hooray Christmas
I will throw a hatchet
But until then
We are notorious at knowledge in the score fight and I go to bed Jordan we are on Facebook
Castrol app
Please download donate review the horse
Girl doll
Amir
I single-handedly took down the Soviet Union
Alex