Air Jordan X swetik
I have great respect for knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as if through the good guy
Stripe.com
Play Everybody Dance
We are recording this of course on New Year's Eve
Let me ask you a question
One has anything good happen to you this year Dan one good thing
Good things
This has been a really good thing
Grounding video
The growth of the show and the wonderful things that year from listeners and
Oh that's it's very
And I'm moving
Are also playing a sexy
It's been tough 2019 is a rough year.
Back about other stuff will you be in a touchdown on the show
Like I you know the plant
Still no right
Still alive doing okay as last
Plantera
What no what no fruit I don't know what's going on yeah do we need to close up any narrative arcs around 2019 that we ever been
Still no fruit
I think I've hit I finish
The rough draft of a novel
You just finished the first time I finish
Now I'm rewriting
It's terrible.
You can always
Like pretend that that's what 2019 was for you
Forget about not worried about getting fired in the whole drama
Protecto none of that
The background and all that's left
And that leftovers left
Right now I'm going to be poor
Let's leave this year behind hell yeah
The faint memories of
My plants are still alive intro to rough draft
So Jordan is a show where I don't know much about the
But I do know a bit about Alex Jones
We're recording this on New Year's Eve
And ID
What what what should we do
What should we do here
And I thought like babies
New Year's Eve
Uses of Alex's
Will be better than the Y2K
We already did that we nailed that
So I thought that why not see how Alex closes out 2019 on his own show
December 31st
Really interesting show Alex
Houses in bad shape
I was unable to avoid the very very bad news
Steve today
That news we were talking about is there were articles that came out yesterday as we were recording this on the 30th
Yes that Alex
And Infowars had been
Basically
Contempt
Of court for their deposition Behavior among other things
And so it added up to
Penalties of about $100,000
But Alex and Infowars
And and for all intensive purposes
Infowars is Alex
Absolutely so he just got hit with a pretty sizable
Fine
Has nothing
To do with the outcome of the case so like what if he ends up being found
Guilty in the Civil Trial
That's going to be whatever that is plus this hundred dollars or hundred thousand dollars
Lucy's on the hook forwarded no matter what
And to what the thing is I thought about that and I thought about like a course we got to do the 31st cuz I got to get Alex's
Response to that but if you read those articles that ruling came down on December 20th
Yeah so
You could go back to our episode about the 19th of 20th and now listen to it with that content right where you can sense
Any additional anger
You just seemed a bit racist I don't know if that was because of the Jeff
Everybody's going crazy
Now it seems like he was
Yasuke
Episode today there I don't
I thought about the possibility that like Alex could be responding
To the news of the fine Ryan him
Isn't news
Define he's known about for 10 days
Course up to this point so he's had plenty of time to adjust to it
I don't really see much of a response
Fox to the news break
Watch episode in general
I mean this world is crumbling around him
I do think it's really cool though that
The courts do have a mechanism to punish Rob do
I screwed is this legal
And like
Well he's not going to jail but no it is not legal to be that old
Yeah turns out there are consequences for basically
Quit playing dumb
In
In a situation where you're required to not play dumb
Toledo
Yeah so that's that's a positive
It also really indicates that Alex is scared of rhabdo
It's cost him like I think that portion of it is like something like 60 something thousand
Either he really doesn't want to answer those questions or robbed
Is worth
$7,000 fine
Because he knows too much
Whatever the case
It's nice to see these
These consequences
I will see you how much more
Hands up, there will be more
To see them pulling out of his debts
If past is Prelude he's got a lot more fine
Coming up
Oh yeah so Jordan will get down to the 31st
There's some actually kind of interesting things going on in here along with
I would say that most of this episode is
Sort of like
What is the clock strikes 12 those fines don't mean anything not nothing to do with this really feels like
Trying to run down the clock
For most of the ship
Imported becomes why even do it right
He's just staring at the clock without somebody waiting till 3 p.m. at
Clock
And we get down to business on all that before you could take a moment to say thank you to some folks who signed up and are supporting the show
So first
Emory thank you so much
Watch you are now a policy wonk
Exemplary exemplary
Text Zach
Thank you so much
You are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk keep those documents coming back
Whistleblower
Not the secret
Space Program
Absolutely Alex
Has pretended he never existed
Text Abigail thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Michael thank you so much you and I'll probably walk
Lexmark
I'm a policy wonk
A strand of change up my
Like pronunciation they're little bit man I missed it
Vista Market
Sorry Mark
Thanks so much
Rondy thank you so much
Watch Journal about what you want
I finally like says thank you do somebody signed up on an elevated level appreciate that very much
So very special thank you going
How to be
Gable family life
Support page
Thank you so much you are now taking
Regrets
How's your 401k
We got to go.
Business
Heroin
Is freakishly large
Things about your
Debo family leftists
Support payments
DirecTV
Green Gable
If you're out there listening and you think it had like this you would like to support these gents website knowledge buy.com
Belovely
So Alex starts off the show talk
A little bit about how he's getting a lot of prey
Press and he's gotten
Surprise
And you might think while some of its prices coming from articles about how you just got to find a hundred thousand dollars you think that
Some other press
Is coming from other Avenue
Alex seems to think
Give it a lot of it
Do with him getting that
2 weeks ago
The very seriously what is that One Winged Angel
Very intent
I was standing on the maze
Infowars musician Austin Texas and I was watching the armored vehicle roll out
The Sun
Knowing that Owen Shroyer
Airplanes and fly
The East Coast
I can't focus
Trip
Was fabulously
Successful
Imagine if we had
Cruise
Marcia Cruz
Everywhere the leftist
Taking over the media
All because of one little innovation
An armored vehicle with mounted bull horns
Blasting out
I don't think I've heard almost anybody talk about Alex having a tank
I believe we are the only people who have ever talked about Alex have a good time
I've seen a couple tweets every now and again like looking his ass
And I think that really goes to like a Hillary rally people yell at him in the tank but I think they'd yell at him anyway
IPhone speak to nobody
Like a Tedesco escalation
Sublevel
I have not read anything is that Hill about
No
Certainly as not been
No one's getting it into a fit about it I think most people think it looks desperate
She has to be the I don't know
I think that the news coverage that Alex has gotten
Largely is about these
Stalling tactic
But he's trying with the Sandy Hook lawsuit
And then another one was Will Johnson one of his reporters
Pretending to not be an Infowars
Employee let me know that you didn't got on the other mainstream news
So like yes okay
You doing shity things in
This lawsuit
And you're reporters acting
Blatantly on ethically
Yes that is getting people a little bit like a what the f***
Cuz wrong
Write the tank does not know a believe it was
Non-factor know everybody saw that tank
And they were like unlike whenever people get a
Massive Homer or something like that clearly composite
Waiting for something
He is getting that tank because he is right on
Dababy
He's trying to make up for his desperation
So in this that in this next clip Alex talks about how like this
Is people waking
Outrageous
That's why Infowars needs
Stay on the air
More life sales pitch
I really think that there's something very interesting in this
After the clip I'm going to translate for you
Actually say okay
Is it sounds
Like you saying something but he's actually saying something couple
And we understand just how evil and just how corrupt just how committed to evil
Blood blister minions are but a lot of people are sick
Still naive that
They're awake they know they're being lied too but they haven't really
Gotten their bearings yet
People are ready to be fully awoken
We have to be there to do it
Dangerous
Gamble
The technocracy the Chinese social score system
Early
Across Europe
The UK
I'm here as well
So for those of you who don't speak Alex
What Alex says the people are waking up but they're naive and don't have their bearings
That's why Alex needs to be on are to guide them and help them
What he's really saying is that things like the Epstein didn't kill himself meme or serving his prime radicalization pipeline
But he can't exploit if he's not on air
Things like that grow and touch the lives of people who would be otherwise
Completely unacceptable to Alex's bulshit
And seeing people starting down that road and not being able to guide them into his Revenue stream is driving Alex up a wall
He's basically saying that these people are money on the table if you can do
Just direct them into his
Hey the globalist of the bad guys
Yeah I was just
It's just money on the table
When he needs to be on there to collect it
People who are awake but naive are just
An untapped Revenue
They are a market I am not in and I need to be
I would prefer he brought back John Williams
From now on when
As for the social credit score stuff that he's talking about
I was just saying that he's mad that his actions have consequences
Companies like Twitter and Facebook don't want him to spread his bulshit on their plant
That's not a Chinese social credit score that's just what happens
People who show that they're incapable of being trusted with platform
What Alex
Just talkin it all sounds like big
Talk and isn't there some sort of a geopolitical truth behind what he say
Ben reality
It's just that he sees money on the table
And the people taking him seriously has made it harder for him to
To get that money
That's all he's saying
It really strip away a lot of the veneer in the pretense in the
The decorations in the
Stupid
Turn the phrase It's just
There's a lot of f****** suckers that I'm not being able to talk to her
To get me to the
There is there
They're waiting
There there
Ready for me
The Primes
To take what I say
Might be
I have bring forth like
What happened
My former lawyer very similar to stimulants
So let's get everyone on them
Yes
It's kind of an unfocused beginning of the show but Alex
Text the whip on him
Southend Claire's
The dis
It's going to be
A disciplined broadcast okay
Discipline
Podcast
Because 20 years ago I was actually
15 years girls were disciplined
Stroke
Grounding
Game-changing transmission most hated
Broadcast worldwide
And take the show seriously and be doesn't want to take bets on whether or not he follows through this
For the whole thing
I think he thinks
He specifically talking about
Today's Show
December 31st there's going to be a discipline show okay
What's the overall I'm going to go with
3 minutes before he goes on a ramble
I made it might not even be that cuz he starts to get really pedantic about whether or not tomorrow and we're golden
January 1st is that a new decade
Yeah that's a discipline
It's really really
Hyper focused on this really if by the end of this clip you'll see that it's actually
Adjust
A way of getting into bigot
Told that it is
Do you know that but the fact that it was a debate
The media couldn't wait
To say that
We
Ended
Christ death
Resurrection
They were so excited about staying we were into a new
Millennia
Not just to New Century that
They told everyone
This was the end
20th century
We're not doing
Men can have babies
They cannot
Okay alright I didn't realize
I realized it the dick at a party in New Year's Eve is like well it's not actually the news
If you real with there is no year zero also
I don't think of trans people exist
I'm going to misinterpret that entire conversation the people they're having cool
I think it is really
Fun
The way Alex
Really focus
Kristoff
Because I have a really hard position on this on the decking is this a new decade
You know what it is
Who cares
We're having a good day
You know how we group time
But it's also very
Up For Debate you know a lot of people who believe that the the 70 is obviously
Didn't start on in 1970 and end of 90
Same with the
The 70 started in 68 and ended in
Or whatever
Didn't we colloquially talk
Decades and in a lot of different ways
Who cares
You don't need to be this dickish
Epoch
Eras
They're all based on the base 10 system and how dare you you're totally right there like
Like it just like it
If I were to hear
Somebody talkin
Yes I would either try and f*** with them
Orally
I've no interest in this conversation of
Do you know next year's leather jacket really start
Birds 20
Just don't care
So Alex
Is mad that the people are saying that
But men can get pregnant
Sure of course and that it's a new
Here's where it gets strange
I believe that a lot of the
Conversation
That goes
Surrounds this issue
Is about people assigned
As women at Birth
Trans
Yeah I believe this is
The conversation that I've heard people have
Okay
Do you know someone who is a man
Right I can get pregnant but still has a fully
As we've seen a couple cases of this that have been in the news
These things come up every now and again these
Situation you are
Now Alex
Seems to think there's something else going on
Which
I find
Trouble they're putting test tube babies inside men you back
Aldi genetically engineered artificial
Can I rig something up and grow some shriveled poor human in there and like the Bennetts lilac
Baby
Yeah they can pretty much already do that
Man didn't have a baby
Human soul was abused and tortured
Hell-bent on playing God
Could you back that up with anyting
Hair
Tornado on Airline
Forget about it once I get on air
What
What is Abaddon
Does jarring
Mad scientist
The doctor
Frankenstein
Torturing
Open Solid I really should have put my
Where are these people putting the baby in the man
Where are they putting the soul
Birthday
Shriveled
I don't know I would like him to yeah I would like a citation on that I would like
But it does
It doesn't know
Because there's big news that is broken
In the morning
Evolve 31st and of the
Protester militia types I'm not entirely sure what the correct nomenclature would be
Still sort of an evolving
Situation even as we're recording
Storming the embassy in Iraq
Yes yeah and Alex because they have
So many babies in their Dilaudid
They got a
They got to get out
That might be a part of it
That's not Alex's report
I think that this should be a little bit of a if he case for him
I believe they're based on the things
Who's that he has espoused as his belief system
You should
Not really have
A hard take on this okay
But
It seems like he does
And it seems to be that he wants
Like because Trump has blamed Iran
Shadow Alex's to that's kind of out that's where he's at
Continuing there's a Washington Post
Protesters chanting death to America
Breakin the US Embassy
Protest
So I guess if I went down to federal building broke into it and beat people up and Amy guns out of and then burn something down
Armed protesters
Kids
Weird lime okay
I would start to all the time about how like once this ship pops off they're going to go around killing all the
Pocopson Lake how the book unintended consequences of going to come real
Oh that's
They would be well within their rights to murder him immediately I believe is what he just said I mean I guess
Yeah
At the same time
Talks all the time about how are illegal or in a rock is
Killed 100,000
Civilian
And there's no reason that the civilians would have any interest in screaming death to America
Nuanced case for Alex
I don't care myself
You should have
The position of like
This is the globalists trying to do what
Trying to the
Make it the Ron's the bad guy but he's awake
He's playing it
Weird
It will
It will never cease to amaze me how
Many
And very
End
Tim near-infinite the amount of a mistake
Pixar made towards Iraq and Iran
Based on
Singular snap
With no nuance
And how committed they are to
Continuing to make
Yeah that's one of the reasons why I don't really want to talk about the actual event all that much because I have I do not have a
A good handle on what's going on
Hood at the time that we're recording
So I
I'm speaking primarily from
Alex likes to make Snapchat
Right Alex
Express various positions in the past
You'd think that this input would lead to a certain output and get it doesn't
We cleared it is very much focusing on
Aaron being a bad guy
And that he's insistent
Enroute
Heatedly
Repairing it
To the Iran hostage crisis
In the 70
Oh that's not good
Right and so he he brings it up as
The only way he can really
We frame it is
You know if you don't go in
In the just shoot these people who are trying to get into the end
You're going to allow them to pay
Take hostages and then we're back
Into the 7th
And so you talked about that and then you blame you will be able to get onto planes easier again
Any blame Soros
Specifically
The Deep State derail Trump's another
1980 hostage crisis with Iran
Iran's runrepeat that obviously
The Deep state
John Kerry George Soros Hillary Obama
Jab Shadow policy and the derail with Trump's been doing they've admitted that
Prove any of this
Can't do it there's only one guy that we can
Specifically prove has
A shadow foreign policy in place
And it's not the people he knows
No I know that later in this episode Alex says that
John Kerry was involved with the Iran deal with you no more
One from the 80s or nuclear
The nuclear
Any piece of evidence
Throws out in terms of like these people are working with Ron to create another hostage crisis
Work that's not enough that's not enough
Yeah I mean you can put your it to shift your little finger pointing to Soros and the Deep state
Whatever it's very thin and he doesn't support this at all
And I think that's one of the reasons
But he ends up
Stalling
For almost all of this episode
Is good to really doesn't want to talk about this story and much specific detail
So you just Rambles about how great his staff is
For a little bit
He's not talking about Rob
In this clip while bragging it's better on
And in service of talking
Samoan
Alex ends up saying a few things
Michael Jordan
Call either top Hollywood people in
Oh
For my future my children's future that's a guy that
Has the will not
Global's do to him but he platform-wide about or BB
He just gets stronger in the face of it
So fake
I think Owens got blackmayo on Alex
That's
That's an insult
That is not a comp
Compliment Owen Shroyer that is an insult to Owen Shroyer the idea
The very idea that you would legitimately entertain
Michael Jordan but let me tell you something about Owen Shroyer that is a veiled insult
Two gigantic problem
Navigate 3
One is Alex's Michael Jordan and other top Hollywood
Favorite movie
I don't know why that's the grouping
Bestway
I don't know what that's the grouping of people Michael Jordan and big
Top Hollywood
The owner of the Charlotte Hornets
Of course Robert Redford
Second problem what the f*** did you
You meet Michael Jordan
It's on Bulls game at San Antonio or something you can't play the Spurs and you yelled at
No baby when he was young
He was he was taken to one of the Houston Rockets Bulls playoff games
In the same way I met Kobe Bryant
I got his autograph when I was 16 or 17
Not mad at you met Kobe Bryant and Radford you know everybody
Foreshore
Yeah I don't believe any of that show
So Alex gets to his top story and of course
It's that the Chinese government is
Is taking over the world
Car as is a story Everyday right
And I'm only keeping this clip in because Alex says something weird
In the middle of it that I want to unpack a little bit
I just don't understand
Walk up and say hey what you want to call the article
Everyday
With a headline about the live feed of the show in what
Maine
Really is the shy contact over the planet
Abortion
A metaphysical abortion
Horrible monstrosity
Rolling out from between his serpent mother's legs
So I would like to kill Grendel in utero
What's metaphysical abortion let that
Set just
That's a piece of art
I want to admire that I want that quote to be on a poster I would look at it whatever I'm
Disappointed in myself he does continue on with like a Beowulf riff
Like we need my walls becoming choked out Grendel's mom
Sir
What was the greatest mob or something
Oh boy
I don't I don't know what metaphysical aboard
I just don't I just don't know
I mean are we talk
Because some metaphysical abortion
Can still be done with with a pill
Could be any vacant even be prescribed
Across state
But some metaphysical abortions require more
Involved process I'm thinking that what are you saying
Is that he is in favor of nipping things in the bud
Like the Chinese World takeover and then he's calling
That abortion metaphysical abortion
It's strange phrases
I think if you were like
Stridently anti-abortion like Alec
Maybe not good to call some of your aspirations
Metaphysical abortion
Right well
Seems weird that he wanted to kill Grendel's baby in the world
Ilana boarding fall on a boarding when does a monster become a monster
Frindle become Grendel
I don't know probably waiting
So Alex
In service of not getting to any news
He goes to calls
Very early at the show
Right almost
Maybe within the first half-hour to go
Discipline broadcast
Yes so here is I
Launching a
Calls by this
Canada
Rehab in Canada
Is our first caller thank you sir for Johnny's go ahead
So Alex is lying this is
Is not the first time in a few years that he's going to calls really early
Wasn't Jeff again
What is an All-Star
Okay bye
Alex
You might remember
That recently promised he was going to have an in-studio surgery
A microchip homeless person
Alta Vista Avenue big news is coming on Tuesday with nobody
That day that Tuesday
What causes yellow
EXO
I think there's a thing when there's a pattern
I think we're
He has been going to cause a lot more lately
Red is definitely true there's a tree
Towards more calls
But I think whenever the show is almost all calls
It's because I don't want to f*** around I want to do it
Yeah I said I was going to
Cut a chip out of somebody
Let's pretend I didn't
Yep just talked to the people
Subject calls in
It's like Judah
It's a little bit like
Hey they think that I'm going to get this but you know what else they'll really love being able to talk to me
Write themselves
These callers
Jackalope
Yeah so Jeff
From Canada gets on
He has an interesting
Sing idea
For how
I going to win the battle
I do not a f****** doing caterpillar
Here's what I was thinking
What would it look like if Trump would look out into one of his rallies
Elisa Hunter
Thousands of people with duct tape on their mouth
Sensor for
What looking at Infowars I was censured for
Target
Maxine's power sensor for whatever
What I'm seeing and I also met this deal.
Just an idea
What about the the armored vehicle showing up at a trump rally early
The big lines are out
And gold handle
Duct tape
Talk to people about
Essential
Free speech is going
Do a silent protest
Trump rally
People putting duct tape over their mouths would you like to fly to Austin
Meijer
300 days
Operation
Actually
Giving this guy a job love it
Couple problems with this truck would never be able to read the word words that are written on duct tape on some
Someone's mouth I was thinking that maybe he meant maybe
He didn't specifically say written on their mouth
How did he maybe you meant the application
Second
Give a f***
Although it would be
Really f***** up as a visual
Brother mouth
Because I knew I think in this scenario none of these people will be able to stop themselves from also class
And yelling with their bowels duct tape
Excuse me I can't I can't hear you you guys your guys
You guys need to take the duct tape off your mouth
So Alex Rambles for about 10 minutes
About why this is the greatest idea
And why you going to steal it
Knockout this guy's not getting
But Alex is going to steal the idea
Like I said there's a
The couple Bravo
The first is a truck couldn't see the letters now
The 2nd
Duct tape
How the f*** are we going to monetize that
We're going to put number out today
Go to the hotline bling 1000 calls have to go through all the other calls but
Send email to show tips infowars.com
I pledged 100 stickers
1000 stickers
We'll just pay whatever it takes
You know what I just believe you
Whoever goes to show temps infowars.com
Address
Will call for those will send you those
I'll man the damn thing myself
Destiny
Bill passed us and we need to go take over those compliments
Conservative
Remove
Neocon never trumper's be removed
Elected be defended by their president
Is a serious solution
Dot-com hey there
Debate about all of that couple problems
How you going to yell infowars.com if you got duct tape on your mouth I believe they have stickers on their the bumper sticker
Get a little bit of juice out of that
Yeah this is really stupid
But it is a good way to possibly create an absurd spect
I was out I figured
Once
It's probably funny in a movie in the real world I think would be a really scary
Directions to yell
That does sound like the beginning of a
It would be funny the first time I think it would be hilarious
The second and third time not funny
Before Time very scary fifth time
Hilarious again it's The Simpsons rake effect
Silent Bob in reality
You might end up seeing is like
Two people with bumper stickers on their mouths of the Trump rally and don't want to understand what's going on except us and then
I'll be drowned out by everybody with their cute t-shirts
Weird thing about where he's at now
Is
I personally would not want
Do those public call to
Just because now I don't think his audience is anywhere near
The level that it was before
So you don't want to find out exactly how small your audience
And those calls-to-action
In the past have often been things
That have been
Potentially financially advantageous
So someone who's not even a fan might want to go and yell Bill Clinton's a rapist
Jiraiya to try and get $1,000
Yeah so you could see how anybody might be inclined to do that even if they're not
Onboard
And not yet you wouldn't want a public
Demonstration of how we
Weak your s***
But the bumper stickers on the map
Let's do it
So
Could this Jeffy
In Canada
Compliments Alex
After Alex Rambles but I was going to take his ideas
And then Alex
Gets mad at him
I'm forgetting comp
I can kind of relate to I sometimes push back when someone compliments me
But Alex Goes little bit too far
You know I think there is
A truth that you guys are the tip of the spear you guys are the best and that's just the way it is your insurance
You just gave the order
Central Texas
Disinformation hub
You had the idea
Most the time it's you I was driving around in 2015
Homemade sign
Yard
Hillary for prison
2016 and I went with that idea and it was a third of the shirts at the RNC
You understand that the orders come from you that's why
Always want to hear what
Supporters and always getting notes and demanding the Secret Service get all the stuff
You loyal
Come from you comes from us
Don't you get it I steal ideas
Has revealed that he has no ideas of his own and he just
Trolls around
Stealing individual's ideas and not giving them any credit for it I am the tip of the spear only because
Steal from you
You you are great do you not realize
All I do
Do now is talk about mediums and try to jump on their back
And I try and get whatever traction I can out of fly-by-night people who
Make a f****** video with their dog
Zika Highland
Count dankula
The guy who hit things of hammers are they
30 year old who got kicked out of his parents
Basement I just try and
Attach myself to whatever dumb
Bulshit is flying around in the right-wing media sphere
I was saying Mike Tyson
And then I steal things and make money off it
Jeff
That's not a successful business model Jeff
Don't don't join Infowars
You should stay in Canada
So Alex freaks out two more about this and I would say that this is pretty unhinged
And I do not know why Alex
Please respond
Nothing like this to Jeff
Trying to be nice
It's very
Text is his backlash
You're getting the orders here
Praise God for us
How big it is
Feel important you are
DeFazio really quick
One thing I think it's really in
First thing I think he's doing there is being like
We're going to do this
And you're going to let
Jeff.
If you don't go along with this big idea
It's not so much me
It's not Trump it's not the West
You're letting Jeff
You're going to let Jeff
From Canada Downs weird sort of Shifting of guilty
Just for me now
Very strange
If you can afford the plane to
Viewers I am online now
I don't want to sit here and watch as overrun by these zombies and their controllers
I know you are supposed to be
You're the tip of the spear
Femi for the inspector personality
They said John
Little out of breath
Something
Because I was waiting for you inspector
Wait for you
What else should we do Jeff
Jeff Jeff
God damn what you all when you saw only one set of footprints in the sand it was you okay
Gary Young
I remember back when I was in drama class
When I was in like a Maybe Junior High or so
Aaron's
Skit and I was a little overboard with the
Jim Carrey dead
You know
You only went over well. Nice reaction from the audience that but
Afterwards we're getting notes
The teacher the teacher said
There's a difference between acting and overact
That's a lesson that I would like to bring
From my youth to the present date
Discuss what Alex just did
It reminded me
Nothing so much of
Joe Pesci asking like
What what do you think was funny
Rethink was abusing something funny happened I make you laugh do I amuse you
Jake Fromm
Dammit
There's a method to that.
Text Alex this is just over the top
Alphalete
Apparently like
Yes
Calm down
Very much so
So he goes
How to break after yelling
To Jeff
Study you know
Why do we do jack
Was not expect
I just wanted to tell people with duct tape on their mouth
So I was goes to break and he comes back there's a longer clip
This might be like a form
At some point but what happens if
Alex his favorite song plays
Is it comes in
God for the Renegade song
There's a little bit of a return to the Alex Jones karaoke
I like it
What I think is particularly
Important about this is like
This is all Alex
Can do
Anymore really well
It's the only thing that I think he
He even enjoy
Which is
Dramatically about b*******
Over swelling inspirational music
We'll see if a couple minutes
Because I don't think you care
Bird dog
What's this fellow's name
Remember, the show
He's like yeah cuz every reason to know who this dude is he's been on the show most
Full-time
Who playing the song for over a decade on his show really likes
Yes come up with Steve Austin
Ridiculous
A long time. Your phone calls
The Renegades
Call Jose work
Failed against the crown
Direct Eggman declaring independence
Bodies down
There is new there is news to get to I should point
Dude is waiting
The embassy is under siege in Iraq
Very disciplined
Spiritually in you now
Beer that Spirit of avalor
Spirit gives life part of life
Paradise oil
We must take from the soil with God
Ancestor
Just real quick Alex
Not for nothing Alex is kind of rambling about blood and soil
I wasn't stoked about that but I'm trying to focus on the song
Night
Becomes the heroes Renegade to mine without the Renegade
Where we be today
Renegade in the world today
Renegade Renegade
Was the next lyrics of rambling to be like who are the records where are they now it is
Yourself that question
Setting up
Put-in-Bay
We won't even live to see the things our sacrifices buying
The enemy has not even begun for suspect
The resources that they paid forward
Spiritual Dimension underground aquifer
And the enemies of God do not have
Birthright
Yesterday
Nothing much
God will finally make them pure
When all they do is produce death
And sickness
Buena state
From the foundations
Airmaster
They are all their father the devil
Supergirl for the Renegade
Can save them because they have chosen
To follow
Father
The devil
No more pretty original rent
Call Josh.
Okay
But you could see all the ants
Could feel
Freeport hours
And the fear that anyone fears
The devil has Peter should not be
Find yourself
Of the show
Isn't a tire commercial to commercial
Singing along yelling
Nonsense over the Renegades
Then getting into preaching about his enemies are damn that yelling at himself about how he's
Got to stop preaching and get two calls and then get to the news
Itza
This is this show is
Just
How to control not be
More
I could have
I could have the whole thing was
Fell apart for me because what should have happened is the drum fill from I can feel it coming in the air tonight
And then we could have f******
Nail this whole thing
Amazing this would have been the perfect segment
If they attended with that drum fill
Or just something quirky
Do you like Easy Lover by Phil Collins
Something else like a jaunty like
The crash test dummies full believe
The Doobie Brothers
Gotta be great
Used chastised himself
No more this preaching bulshit I got it
Knuckle down absolutely
So he that we just heard him go out to commercial
Here's how he comes
Backup commercial
Why does fire we have lit the fire he will take them all over the world
Bastille the fire
Really we're doing this again
Empire
Fire by our creator
Never
Only summon their destruction
Will directed all the great man with sturdy little will be torn down
Will beg for redemption in the end but it will fall on deaf ears
Are your phone calls I'm going to head back down the railing I said but
Not quite yet here on this final transmission of
Let's go right now
New York
You're on the air welcome Jeff from Canada
Is partially the producer
You know you could turn down the music.
Everybody there is like it's New Year's Eve let's get the f*** out of here let's see
Some songs have the stronger suspicion that Alex is in a bad mood and he just needs pump up Jam
Yeah like I can't even get into this
F****** play some
Like really inspiring music and I'll fake
Fake it
A new form of preaching where the
Instead of bothering with reading the Bible and learning in
Providing wisdom
You just play f******
Classic rock
Can talk to it as if it's talking back
Amanda work
I think that'd be great
So liberal calls in
Liberal
And so what liberals got to say
Is Martin
Everyone enjoys the Patriot Rock
Liberal asks
Along the lines of
How are we
Tending
Trump is doing a good job and is anything other than what we
Been accustomed to
When
He re-signed the Patriot Act
Yuri sign the ndaa
What
What when are you going to recognize these things
And call it out for what it is right
And Alex
Is not
Doing a good job
With this call disciplined broadcast
This is what I'm speaking with regards to Trump why is it that he's renewing The Patriot
Being great again
We Revere the Constitution and our freedoms of
Speech and things of that nature
Why is it is Tyrion
Can you explain that to me
Totally agree with you let me finish this piece of chicken
You talk
Well
Looks like our theory is confirm
Check that out check that box off of the United States
Even when other people are talking
Pretty regularly on air
Cannibalism earlier because I feel like that would also check it out
Metabolism
And it's some form or another
Hey man I won't answer your question about why Trump is good but he renewed The Patriot Act but I got this chicken in my mouth
Is brass that I got in the mouth
And then I got a great answer for you
It is not a book
That's not surprised
Know this color is pretty good but it's it's a bit long
Really tough to dissect
The pieces where
It's ultimately unfulfilling it's on gratify
Because the answer those questions as he can
And so he won't
And you're not going to get the answer you want
Him saying he can't and Alex's never going to address
Never going to give a
A solid answer
Liberal is talking
Trump should do
And the answer is basically
Take the money
It's being spent on these overseas Wars and them reallocate them for infrastructure project job creation
Some pretty
Write redistribution all rains of what stupid liberal to say those things
That is a pretty little that's a position that you'd hear on the left
I think a lot of people on the right my
Be like let's just stop spending the money whereas on the left
A lot of people are more towards
Putting that money towards things
That will create greater outcomes
For people who are in
Bad financial
And reinvestment in the country itself public spaces yes
That that sort of s***
So it's really interesting
To hear Alex's response
To Liberal saying that that is what that should Trump
Subdue
Because I've totally agrees with him
Counter to every libertarian nonsense
Then things get ugly
And the call ends exactly how most of these calls
You done your research what is in 30 seconds
Omnisd
Creative
Shadow whatever
Explain to the country that busy League Awards
Pulling these troops out now
You have given them couple with respect to the actions of
Subordinate
If that is the case I like you
Call Tim
Call the troops out
You agree
Sign or relocate the money that you bought
Twisties
Rebuilding infrastructure in United States created drug programs
This is what people need totally agree totally agree with you
And look
He said take Brennan security clearance date didn't do it
You said leave Afghanistan
What does he do when he's around it
Koala Kids one
When Obama was in power
It's the same Reese
Singani legally under him will be at
She has to take the reins now Ali
2020 RV dealers
No Alex
The part of the
Journey still going on
Great point about get his number and info
All the news I said I would want your calls
Powerful cars
Guide job
That's all I
All I hear is I need you guys to continue talking so I can
Finish my music
So that call didn't go
Well
I don't think because I think liberal was making
Decent points
Didn't have anywhere really to go with
Because
They are
Points that are real problem
Alex
He spent
Years
Yelling about the Patriot Act in the ndaa
Write and do very idea
That Trump would
Get rid of them
Is really counter to Alex's
Narratives
About what Trump believes what he would do what he will do
Into
Best not to talk about
Oh yeah you don't want to you don't want to worry about it whether or not the guy you said was going to do all this stuff is actually doing it because
You can't say that
So Alex
Comes back
From break and you know what
Going to do
Oh yes you can
Got to be honest
I'm liking it
This is a good New Year's Eve note
Beating transmission
Proven to be transmitting
Applied Anna hummingbird from Canada down to South America
Magnetic
Universe
Belong to Satan we belong to God
Nailed it
Straight at the Provo
People are scared.
Pretty awesome
Lino
Everything looks right through yourself
Down to the tiny items
Free will
The powerful.
See your old man
Get out of bed
Landon
Stronger
Embryo
Does he know who it is yet
How tall is this
So it is
Powerful words
Powerball
I really think this is my favorite show the year so far just so you know I think you belong to the city
He must have just gone into public domain or being
Like whatever
Lease agreement he has with songs to a record label and a bunch lately
Are you listening
Are you listening to that text and it might
Taking over like Quarterflash
My number one spot of sacks
How you could that mean hard my heart's pretty great there's no stopping
CIA
It's good news
That
The devil is old
But not I'm depressed
That means you can run away from it
Setting the other is not omnipresent
I hope
I don't know
If the devil isn't omnipresent
I guess I never really thought about it
I mean I never thought of
You know what that's good boy
That's a good boy
If that's
The case then there have to be places where you could go to get away from The Temptations or whatever you know like
Don't have to be a thing
Right here is here's what I'm going to say is what I think
He thinks
Crying terms of omnipresence
I believe he thinks
God is everywhere simultaneously all around us and within us but isn't that where is that
Can go anywhere
But he's not always everywhere
So if the devil is tempting me he can't send me temperature
That's a very inefficient
What you mean based on what you're saying
I think that's what he believed
I'm not really sure what I've ever considered I guess I always thought it was kind of more of a metaphor
Never considered
Logistics
Physical properties or attributes
Giving him mutant powers can he can he multiply can there be a million devils
And he can send
All of them to eat
Individual place today
To have that could be us
Subordinate
You know
What's what's the infrastructure
What's an opening salary for the devil I will say that I agree with Alex at least
Conception of the devil that he is
So
That is where we can find common ground
Can you agree on Howell
Pretty old
So it does make clip
It's kind of old
At this point but Alex is just as old as the devil
Not that
He's constantly displaying these pump up Jam
Is not going to go over babe
I do you enjoy research and almost nothing to look into
So here you eat pumpkin
Some more and then he's like
We're getting to the end of the sea
S h a b l e
And I think he has to rationalize why he hasn't gotten into the news yet
IQ
Now I'm going to do it I'm not getting the Iran News
Socratic
Gary
I could totally do it I got a hundred percent doing I'm totally ready I've prepared everything
I can't do it until I take the 15 calls
We are at the end of our 2 and he's taken 3
I do not believe you will get to that 15 I cannot stress enough
That the only reason I am singing along and talking to all of these songs for what amounts to
A half hour at least at this point is because I'm actually too prepared
To talk about Iran and Iraq
Who prepared guys holy
How it does say that sometimes like I'm 24 Paradise information
Nobody
Forcing him
These calls we do for years he's just said he's going to go to Carl's and then never does
For that but now for some reason there's an arbitrary
Rule that you must take these receiving calls before he gets to the news
It's it look
There's pressure from the higher-ups
Eric Church
Suspicious
I have a question
And this is a hypothetical I know you can actually enter this on
But I like to imagine
That
This is his production
Instead of knowing that he's got a little button
That they can press where it's like we just play this song for 4 minutes
That's four minutes ahead of talkative
The song we don't need it there's no previous
Discussion
He doesn't
Bad and I
Hey Google
It's an interesting Theory it's possible but
Obviously
Approval
I think it's more Alex is yelling at them during the breaks you play these goddamn Jam
I could go either way I'm running on fumes really good
I need some
Silex says start to take
More calls
Some guy and
He just gets off on a riff about how
You know what the drag queen story times
Some stuff they're going to have their Satan
Demons and they're going to come take your kids share
It's a weary start in media res
If one of those ran
Towing you
More thing Alex
Obviously we're in a retriever
Mimics and counterfeit something's you don't think God's people have a rage 1000 times more powerful than them
We can take out 100 of their best people one-man Focus
So we're obviously
We got a short time of reprieve right here with President truck to get right with with God and Jehovah
And whatever your name for God as this is our short time or reprieve
What is my name for God is Allah
What happens
President-trump
It's gone
What what goes on from
From there
Question God bless you are incredible caller
Lenny says that he's going to answer when he comes back from break because I think this is
40 Chicana certain level I don't think he wants a direct question
Except for right up again
Hamster break
Justin Case
I mean was all good well with
Canadian guy with the duct
I don't
He doesn't want to do that
Not so
I think there's a strategy to the ranting
In order to delay this question until you can look at the
The clock and see like yeah okay there's 40 seconds left till break let him get the question out
I can come back
What do we do after Trump great
Yeah that's
That he doesn't really answer
This is
That's that's a bad job
The director be like okay
Do do more or less because you suck at this
Let's go character
Yeah
It's uninspired
It's transparent
Lion
So if he goes to break and comes back in his answer is largely this
Same sort of mealy-mouthed
Thing but he's been doing for a while
Is the you like we put Trump in focus on
What are movement
It is not Trump as a
The person
That's all you've been doing for years as folks
As a person
Do whatever
He's trying to pretend that didn't happen everybody has the right to live
Sterilized whatever
I'm not going to I'm not going to dance
It's too hard on
On on that one
The time my high school English teacher called life lie
And he said it was the most dangerous thing to interfere with
To the point where he said he told his dad off once when he was like
And is that just punched him in
Take them out of the house
That's his idea
Interrupting
Sleepwalking
With the saxophone
IHOP
So Alex
Gets another call
Call from a guy
And we've talked about this a little bit in the past
Like you suggested sometimes when people call in to do
Egregious sales pitches yeah they're fake call
I don't think that's necessarily what if
Fake call on Alex's show would look like
Sure because I think the audience is trained up well enough to know
That
Did you plug the product you get 22
This is a good way we
Scratch each other's backs that's worth
It's sort of a formality with callers on his
I never really sets off red
Flags for me
This call I don't I'm not
I think that this is fake
Super well could be real it could be someone
Coming up with
Fun way to talk to Alex Shore
But I am saying that if there is
Afaik
Kind of call on Alex's show like a plan
It would be like that
What the color
Ehlers-danlos
Infowars is totally on it in there until I just recently got out of the military
This part of the Special Operations community
And red black we were getting ready to invade North Korea
You were right on with your timelines I was listening to you the entire
Your time and I was just blown away that
I don't know where you were getting your Intel from but
But I was listening to you it was like I was hearing and I was hearing
Other information privileged information that I thought was
No.
Secret but somehow you got it out
Anyway
Surprise me
It's all these different
International entities are
Or listening to you constantly for what's going on in the world
That is worth far more than any money 2 hours
Does he have the appearance
To somebody who has high-level clearances Saginaw
This information is exactly the sort of thing you hear
I could also see that not being a setup
And it being a caller who is Listen to Too Much Alex and misinterpreted things they experienced in the service
Or it could be
Temperature
Shut up I don't buy there's a girlfriend
Yeah but there's a number possibilities but
If I were to bet on
Something being
What Alex
Would want
Ucreate
That would be a
Yeah yeah cuz it creates the
Credibility
I'm the like
High-level heads-of-state listen to my show
Did Alex's desperate
Cultivate
But it's
Complete
And now is a good time for it
Karaoke
Why wouldn't be listening to him
Don't worry.
That are like
Former Special Ops
Or he can credibly
Read let me
Start that over
At this point in time
He can't
Get any guest
Credibly say that they're special
Not
I think that Bracken I don't know what he was in but I believe he wasn't list
He was in the service
He wasn't listed but he was
I don't know yet right
Mikey was Branch une
Nothing but if you wasn't in the service
He's
Everything about his character implies
Disability
So I don't
I don't know
Going over the roster in my head and I don't think so no I don't I don't believe so and you can only be told that you are
Listen to by the leaders of the World by Steve pieczenik so many times
Before you start thinking
Steve
You're lying
You dumbass all because it comes packaged with so many other bowls
So you going to call her there's no bad he's Spec Ops
Holyshit we were going to invade North Korea a thing that many special ops people would absolutely say
Upon leaving the military
You know how they do
To be clear I'm not saying that was a fake caller any
But that genre
Yes what Alex would create
I believe based on his personality based on the needs of the show
Cuz that
What that does
That establishes this dislike
High-level credibility with the people who were listening to already on the hook
Maybe people who are
Almost on the hook
It gets them deeper into it like all this guy is
Did Alex's shoot is credible I don't know I'm not
Special Ops
This guy it serves his purposes really really well
That's pretty good call for Alex but that one in the Wind
That was good
So Alex still has not gotten to
Promise to give you mine you on the situation will be able to bring attack such a big deal with my
Grabbing man on the position of all flags and now I know they're going to head up to the bar to get us that way in there now
Moaning out the message
That one two three four five six seven eight nine 10 collars online
I'll try to get all of those
At least you're on the line I will tell
Covering those those topics during the fourth hour
Thank you all for joining us please don't forget
The biggest sales of our history are going on right now
And when these are over we'll never have them this big
So
Being lazy at
He's in the fourth hour Alex is hosting the fourth hour himself
And he's in the fourth hour here now
And what he's doing
Is saying
Halfway through the fourth hour I'll get to the news but in this half hour I'm going to take time
10 calls
None of this is going to happen
Know you know that none discipline show
10 calls
Half hour
Bang about
They're couple questions
You can't be that complicated
Not noticed that there's a bit of a jump there like at the end of the second hour and then now we're already at the store sour
The third hours
The disaster is it
The long diatribe about the
By Las Vegas shooting
Reborn Colin it's already the stuff we've already talked about
Conspiracy about
Any good track
Not really however in the fourth hour
Listen Up song
Free worshipper
Is planet about the devil was the lightbringer
Sean it does Set Me Free cuz Alyssa Bryant
The Morning Star
AutoCAD he ordered all that Satanism crap
Go back to God
Are Christians Dave Mustaine the Christian a Megadeth
All those guys are like
Scared to death of Satanism is a been around and they've seen it
Sure
Also there the lamest living rock stars we have I don't know if you've noticed that too
Also good luck getting through those 10 calls
Very disciplined show.
Talking about how he loves the sun 10 minutes
10 colors half-hour we got a little bit of the music out of the way so that gives what 26 more minutes we can still banging
Let's do it Nike commercials
18 minutes come on
Bang it out
1.8 minutes per call
So Alex Goes to the cause
Roll the dice
It comes up snake eyes
He gets another critical collar
Yeah yeah man I've been listening to you for quite some time Bandits
Remarkable daywind
You and John V
On the same page with regard to what's going on in Iraq
Ocean you know it's like
What does Trump
To get you the
You know baby
Indignant
Madeline
I mean
This is the same place to buy chicken
Massing troops in that region
Why are you here now
Critical mass
Looking for Annex
Used to go in and hit a run
Kushner is there linked to Israel I mean come on man
Oh it's okay for Iran to overrun and attack our Embassy
Go ahead and repeat mainstream media.
Rocky Point
Exactly what to say
See how Alex pivots there oh yeah
Not going to deal with Bolton
Going to talk about whether or not you're faking the
Call the video
Get to being as I got was a fake video out at the embassy
That's so sneaky and so lame
The color doesn't really fall for it but he can't really make much Headway without
Alex isn't willing
Engaged
Things that are being
Brought up
So he Rambles a bit
He says this
He's trying to explain that he's not for offensive Wars
Kind of makes a
Location for attacking garage
Okay well yeah
Tell me Jeremy
Now you saying
Music
Starting offensive
Fish
It's okay you're not for offensive
You think it's appropriate to start a war
Because Aaron
Is running around acting like the boss of the Middle East
Yes these are in congruous
Positions to have it's not an offensive War if somebody looks like a bully and you don't understand what or why they're do
And then you just
Super 8
I do think that Alex is position makes no sense
Yes I agree
Okay
J.p. licks
So Alex wanted is Jeremy that scholar was brought up that he sounds a lot like John Bolton
Yeah hang on hang on I'll let you
And I got to quickly remove a computer chip from this homeless guy though I will get right back to you
For the past three weeks on hold for a little bit
Cuz he's got to ramble about
How this is not
The beginning of the decade
How to go live
Infowars
Dot-com live feed
Everybody cuz it is a big deal 2020 it's not
Starting but
If This Is War on knowledge the war on calendars it's an obsession
The war on Commodores
Jacobin Illuminati Jacobins want you to think that it's the beginning of the decade
They have been waging a war on calendars
Since Gregory
That is such a crucial plank
In there
Attack
Making people
Say it's the decade
It was the night
Templar who first weaponized the calendar did these are your enemies believe it
These are your enemies people who want you to think the decade starts a year earlier
What are you doing
Fighting against
Hallmark cards
Chowpatty
So I don't know why he gets
Down this road necessarily but Alex
Decides that he's going to
Address the 8th
Out there
And I should
Should say that Alex is cleared
Okay
However
There's a problem
Literally fighting devil worship
If you're really
Because you don't believe in invisible things and you really don't like being fake churches
Other reasons
5%
Just like you
I don't think you're a bad person
Totally understand
I think you're about receipts the people up above you
Teacher
It's my Buffett atheist
When I was 12 13 14 15 years
Okay
So freaky that would even tell my parents about it
Try to get away from it
Lost Boys
Just like the grandpa shows up
And they're not physically living forever but
Virus
Okay I think you just
Watch The Lost Boys
Hey hey atheist cuz you're turned off by churches and all that rag get it I don't think you're a bad person
But you should know that all of your atheist gurus are vampires really bums me out to know but I'm glad
That you broke the news to me
I just don't even
I don't even care like I have to research any part of that
I did look into docking know everybody
He's a vampire
Sam Harris and not positive but he's not a vampire from what I can tell
I do believe the Christopher Hitchens was of a
I will give him
This is the point where I just like
I get frustrated and maybe it's
Because there's too much of it elation
In a single over the songs
DeSoto it really is a let down
Yeah it's kind of
African back to that was a vampire fang
Why is it whatever we're the highwomen
Oh that is great question
Because I don't want to tease beat
Ono Hawaiian
Crazy Tomato
Even stranger no highwomen
So
Alex gets back to the scholar who said that he sounds
He Rambles quite a bit
About the situation in the Middle East share
Just trying to
Stop a big war
Right so you might attack Iran in order to stop
Stop a big war or something
Not entirely sure
Nicer put down
Alex
Is really slammed
Trying to stop
Giant War
Are you a real threat
And the globalist you're trying to stir things up in the Middle East
That's my educated view on this
Me is a pragmatist
I just support the president
I don't know I think the way you take the word picture you just you know
Drew is
Great
Sounds great
Problem is though is that that that isn't the
It doesn't appear to be the case it appears that were actually being
Alleged to be the fool that once again
We're going to be sold a bill of goods
We're now we're are striking in a rock because of a contractor
Essentially a higher
Blackwater guy somebody that you actually would have said.
A relationship with her
That you would have said you guys are
Derek Prince
Frontier Services work for the Tricom
Both some of the pedophile rings
Kane Brown
You've made it sound like there's a little bit more than that no
If you misunderstood it was an intentional misunderstanding that Alex implied contact
The path really highly of him
Especially during the early drop years
He's been
He talks about how he
Blackwater guards
Purity and stuff like that
Be the change
Whether or not you want to try and make an argument that Alex
Actually has presented that he is friends with Erik Prince or not whatever
Leave that aside
Comparing Alex's
His prior position about Blackwater in the mercenaries and stuff
To where he is now on a lot of those issues
Just that alone is plenty
To make whatever this caller is accusing Alex of
Very valid
Alex has taken a very different
Position
On a lot of his stuff that he would have
I don't care
Erik Prince has a
F****** Stone you wear around your neck forever
There's no there's no repentance
It's coming from
Like
I only like two
Prince for a while is still a go f*** your
You know
So this call Ann
After Alex
Saran balls about how you didn't
Claims that he has a tooth
Pick up broke
The night before until he's bleeding in his mouth
Really
Seems like a
Contact that is it that is my grandma died for the 4th time this month of
So Alec
Still has calls to get through
Still hasn't really gotten
To the news I guess he was yelling at this guy about the situation
Moving on
I don't really met
To lead the show with c
Some big news
Fourth hour
Play through it no less man
Jamie didn't news
Alright I was already going to basically start broadcast
And then we got the embassy attack by the Hezbollah Iranian
Militia
Apple prices blowing up
Is planning to try to trigger a civil war here and call the United Nations into the country
Oh really that's the big news that was the big news big news wow
Holding pattern he retire
We have accidentally teleported to anybody on Allegheny
You know this one
This one is the big one
This was the big one and it happened
Actually
Three and a half hours
It's unfortunate but he got to it a little
That's a bummer so it it turns out that Tom pepper
Has a come up with
Some do some news
The Croods
Going to be getting involved
Just to give you a rough sketch
About this is
Tom pappert is found a job posting
On the UN website
Right that involves
Disarmament someone who's like
Like as X
Sporty's and disarmament sure no implication that it's
Being stationed to the United States
Yeah but they've decided
Did it is and the
Used disarm denied
Red States population are looking for a disarmament expert they're not looking for like an
Academic experts with
Some familiarity that if you have a job posting for an accounting job maybe
Some years of experience
Excel
Sorry but he digs
That this guy is an expert this person will be an expert in physically removing guns
Pan's that's that type of disarmament
Not nuclear weapon and overall
Further
It involves
Using these things on the United States
So there's a lot of assumptions being made
But it's just like Tom pappert the crack
The big news
So now this news
Which Alex is going to leave the show with but didn't
I didn't even bring up in
Until the 4th hour
It's surprising that he was going to be disciplined broadcast
Imallexx
Who decided because of this news he is now going to join Owen Shroyer on the War Room
And keep them
I don't know
So in order to make that
Can possibly be
You realizes that he's going
Need to get Tom
Papr
To be on the show
And
Why not call him on air
Matt Lauer
All this downhill have the first hour I want to call Tom pappardelle I'll just call myself but I know what I want in her
Boom
So I can call him
This is so massive but we knew this was coming
That whistling is
Is an attack
Beyond Barrett
No
Now that's
You're a dog.
You went
Anyways so casual that's right time you're coming on to talk about the coming end of civilization
How you doing
So Alex does call Tom
Course it does
Hey Tom I got you live on there I wanted to make sure this happen
Destroyers live would be a war room
Cohoes because I was already going to make this my main show today
The UN try contact
Embassy situation
And singing
Can you come on with Owen
In about 30 minutes
Come on
Absolutely Alex will be there
A little bit about this massive story
If it's not something we're just saying
This is openly the UN recruiting troops for America
Kicking citizens Alpha Street saying we own and control this now
We are sovereign in the world
Incredible they found a job posting
Anyway I don't care it's a real his voice is terrible so
Said what was he up
What do you mean what was he
In-depth research
Used to know what kind of
What was he doing and what kind of Demands does working
For Alex have that you might
Just get a call and Beyond
I am here now
Probably just
Brainstorming dumbshit
What can I make out of this
Anyway
Alex
It realizes that he has about 10 minutes left.
Of course he does
And so of course
Here come the excuses
Okay
But
Everybody somebody calls
37 42nd Street South
This is exactly what I knew would lightning that was
100% is exactly the clip I knew would end up appetite
What he said at the beginning of the episode stories but I need to get through these call
You're going to get to the end of the show to be like I didn't get to the news because it had always had all these calls
It's a formula I swear to God
If you told me that clip was from
Any of our previous episodes
I would believe you say stuff like that a lot
That that has that has
Has no time
Stamp that is Evergreen
So he lightning rounds it tries to go to a couple more calls just a bump that number up a little
Or whatever I guess maybe there's some like
That's being captured by the police
So he he does that
And
This is how
The show ends
This is the last bit
Infowars
Alex Jones Show
20 Mai 2019
Wild stay there
You're viewing rabbit-hole all these colors went amazingly Muscat every caller Andre Wilder
Infowars.com live show everybody watching
Message and data rates may apply
Help seriously I'm too young for hair loss
There isn't any music there is no Fanfare nothing it is just Alex yelling at the board Ops 2 transfer
For the calls
Over to the War Room Owen Shroyer can answer these calls that he didn't get to during his show cuz he's tried to put off
Cover again
It is
This show
Like the end of tour 2019
This December 31st show
Is almost
A perfect encapsulation of how
Bad
How unprofessional
Discipline
Operation this is
Yeah that's really disappointing there should have been a lot more pageant
No but I'll tell you it it's exactly what it should
If you were trying to get a spiritual sky
Catch ride
Alex Jones Show is
The only thing that's missing really is like
More racing
And
Probably some violent collars
Sure
I don't know how he man
Undertaker
Like as many colors as you did probably like 7 or 8 without anybody being like
Woohoo E tuning
That's good maybe they started screening
Baby pee pee in the car waiting list for Alex B
Just real quick
Do you are you going to ask him about killing people
The sense I get is it like there is
You have a broader sample of
Calls and there is at least a certain amount of the people who are in
Inclined to call into his show that are like
You're full of s*** yeah
You are full of
S*** this is nonsense
Trump is not good
I think that's an interesting development and into 2020
I wonder
What that'll do but
You know like
This guy
Alex is
Trash
His job
This is so bad
Funny on what level to hear him sing with these songs that just
Pump up jams
To get him going
And a couple of them like you belong to the city
Straight up
So it's that
Pleasant
On some level
You just see it
Transparent this guy
Is beating like a
Sweetly
Unable to cover these stories
I've no idea where to land on any of this I haven't read anything yet so what I'm going to do
Is put it off
And pretend
They are not putting it off
When you get to the end of the show what are you going to do then I'm going to go on Owen Shroyer show and do the exact same thing
It's
It's predict
80s
It is I mean
If there were more malicious s*** and weird murder stuff in the third hour I would say this would be a
Microcosm of the
The entirety of Alex's
Career
You know it ends not with a bang but a whimper
Balding Carnival
On some level I agreed to you do you want some fireworks
And the herb it's almost more fitting
Absolutely just like
Yeah it does seem like that's how is shovel and is well if just like and we are not going to be here
Tomorrow by
It just ends with like
Like a slide whistle
A real sad saxophone
Happy New Year to you all absolutely out there I hope you haven't had a good one
Will be back
Indeed
That's true
Aw cuz we're already back
In 2020 through 2020
I will see you but until then
We do have a website
It's not right.
Come better does brazo on Facebook
Not go to bed Jordan earlier I said we're on
We are on Facebook there you can find such crucial information such as it is not
At the beginning of a new deck
Debatable podcast
Can be downloaded on iTunes
Other podcast
Accenture download Lee review
Donate have fun
Sure until then
Dzx Clark
I am
I just completely blank
I Belong To The City
Holding
Alex