Air Jordan 5 sweat it
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Knowledge fight
Nike.com
Hey everybody
Alex Jones
How old was your first
Experience with
We being legal in Illinois
We became illegal on the 1st
Of January and that evening I got a text from a friend and
Remember who it was it was Jordan
Sent me a text that he wanted to go and down
The Dispensary on the 2nd of January
And I thought hey I don't smoke weed why not
Which is a stupid decision
No not really so down there and
Enzo's
Springtime is a bit of a long line
Professional processor
Pretty smooth
Considering it was the second
Today they were in operation
I got a couple of gummies and
Seeing if it helps with sleep how is it going for you so far the results are inconclusive
Like it's helping a little bit but
I'm not entirely sure if that's
Sibo Factor whatever but
It's interesting
Yeah I'm driving my my ability to metabolize things is a little bit rough because they said
Said that the average dose for a the gummies would like a half of one that's so the people at the place
I-82 and it barely
Registered
Like it
It was bad you may have a problem that might be on my end not there
Almost no interest in using any of this
Hyper say so I don't really even care about your trouble.
You're inside
Super 8
We'll see what happens
It was surprising
I've never waited 4 hours for
That long
And they allowed
You like it you had a really interesting
Sting set up where you would sign in
And then they were text
Text you when you were it was ready for
Come to be light in that was brilliant
And I wandered around
Andersonville a
I wasn't I wasn't like you standing there waiting
Which would have been a deal-breaker
I was already ready to leave anyways
Yeah so anyway I don't know I don't know about that but I do know a lot about Alex
Today we have an episode
I'm not really positive that I am wanting to do at a while to get out of the present day
Yeah well I mean me to keep her many different I keep having like a
Like a while we've done a bunch of presents episodes
Time to go do something else and then something will happen in the world
Like Alex's depositional happen
You know it'll come out that he lost $100,000 in
Confused to the court
Trump goes ahead
Assassinate
Not cover the outside of the public
I'm not sitting here complaining
To be in the presentation
It is a slug a little bit I think it probably is for the listeners to I apologize about that
As soon as we have a chance to do an episode that is not the present day I promise you
We will do WhatsApp
Development
Situations
Positions on them
Are interesting to note generally speaking when the when historians will look back and say this was where we
Highly doubt that
Yes
Say thank you to some folks
Signed up and recording the show
Do first
Vero Headhunter Tom
Thom thank you so much you're now about to walk
Very much Sparrow Headhunter Tom
Arrowhead hunting
Is that the right
Knox nox thank you so much you know about the walk
I'm a policy wonk
Next kylo Ren
Thank you kylo
Text Stephanie
Next The Alex Jones dollop thank you so much you know about Willy Wonka
Text Alex Jones
Dylan like to know if I was finally Hannah
So much you are now about to walk
Gahanna
Yes thank you very much
To our website
Extremely
So today is episode they were going over his January 3rd 2020
Hey
It's Friday of last week the day after Trump
Ordered the strike
Dua LIPA
Steak-Out sulaimani
Get into some of that a little bit before there's not a complex dropped
Today Show
I'm Alex Jones at this year's 2020 he's ripping off Barbara Walters
Do that everyday
What a dick
Acclaim for weekend Today show I want to give a little bit of a
Disclaimer
I'm not an expert in geopolitics
I can really only go on the information that's available and I can
Can find witches oftentimes limited particularly in the case of evolving and ongoing
Situation
Some potentially major events unfolded over the course of the last weekend
Things will come up on this episode
I want
Rest I'm going to
Try my best to stay away from over
Analyzing things
Too much
Since I will probably be a little bit irresponsible of someone like me to do
There are many other great places where they kind of work
Is being done by far more competent hands and I would encourage people to rely although sources
For more nuanced
Discussion
The geopolitical C
I don't know what Iran is going to do to respond
And I don't want to stay
If you're off track
If you and I playing guessing games it's not productive
Yeah
That being said I want to offer two very strong positions that I hold
And it'll probably best to acknowledge up top
Before we get into anything
Whenever I say that you're welcome to speak your piece
Pieces well Jordan position
Alright the first is that I'm absolutely
Categorically opposed to a war with Iraq
And I'm equally opposed to the actions that makes such a war more likely
I understand that many would see the invasion of the US Embassy
Being a rock is ground to a response
And I understand that position where that's coming from
But I think
This level of response seems way out of
Proportion and Rec
Second from everything I've read on the subject
Trump crosses very serious line by killing soleimani
In the to the money was an official of the Irani and
This is an official of a sovereign government who Trump has openly admitted
You ordered the assassination of
Which is a really f***** up
I have some discomfort with the idea of drone Warfare generally speaking but when it's being used
Commit political assassinations on government
Figures Within
Countries that we are not at war with is a very serious matter
In an article in the Atlantic owner Hathaway
Professor of international law at Yale Law School
Applying that the strike to kill soleimani was a breach not only of our constitution
But also international law
Because Trump did not inform Congress nor did he approach the UN Security Council before make
Decision
These problems could be resolved
If the attack was done to stop an imminent
Which Secretary of State Mike Pompeo is claimed
But no one is produced any proof.
Support that assertion
It's my feeling that
Leaving aside how bad a guy soleimani might have been or may have been probably was
What Trump did was wrong and profoundly dangerous
Given all the information I have at my disposal I don't see
Any gray area there
And Trump's actions sense
The Killing have only made me feel
Concerned even more so
It's probably debatable if the assassination count as an act of provocation
That would justify a Ron
Declare war
But what's not debatable is that after all of that
Trump took to Twitter and literally threatened to
Commit war cry
He said quote
Let this serve as a warning that if Iran strikes any Americans or American assets we've targeted 52 Irani and site
Representing the 52 American American hostages taken by a Ron many years ago
Summit a very high level and importance to Ron and the Irani and culture
And those targets and around itself will be hit very fast and very hard
The US wants no more threat
Brett's
The part about a roni and culture being targeted is a massive red flag
Targeting cultural sites as University
Considered a war crime and not for nothing.
People you generally
Killing by attacking
Cultural sites
Are noncombatants
So the very idea that a president would say something like this
Is absolutely unacceptable territory for us to be in
The way Trump is behaving is villain
This is authoritarian level s*** and I just don't even know what to say
There's obviously more to the story than we know right now
And putting singular blame on Trump I think would be foolish
He's ultimately responsible for the decision
But I think you'll be naive to think it was
The decision was made in a vac
Obviously advisor
They're surrounded people court hearing him and direct
Score for me to speculate on the
The precise precise aspect of that
I think at this point would be
JustBats regulator
One thing that strikes me is that I feel like Alex and I should be on the same page on this
The fact the trumpet
Kill a government official from a state were not at war with
Without notifying Congress
To be everything Alex is against in an executive
Alex is an anti-war guy release pretends to be
Food should be pretty clear as a case of
Trump stepping way outside the bounds of acceptable action
And doing things that tend to make war more likely not less
This should be a slam dunk for Alex's way to leave Trump
But I think we all know how
So these are sort of the position
That I'm coming in with and I don't want to necessarily litigate a lot of the
Like
But what about
Right now
The angles of it
I think
Leaving everything aside
This is not an acceptable action now and then the way Trump has behaved afterwards has made the action itself even were
And so I
That's sort of the position I'm coming
I I suppose the only thing that I can say now that makes me
Field I guess
Istick
Intruded my prince
Supposes that
W Obama and Trump should all be prosecuted for work
Like I guess I guess there's no other way to make
Extensive list sure
You know
Like it's if we hadn't done anything if we did something to process
Cqww for his war crimes
Maybe we would
Maybe and we didn't do anything
And we just allowed it to.
Deteriorate so
Our government should
Most of them being tail
I guess that's
Yeah we've had
How many
My life has been spent at War
You know how many how many opportunities have we had two to do this and
The extent to which we've
Given the executive branch
Carte blanche
Has led obviously to a
Situation where the Mad King can do whatever you want
This is a this is the endpoint
Of
What happened
Yes it's The Logical conclusion of that
And like I said I don't want
To overanalyze stuff because I'm not
I'm not equipped
I'm not I am not
I would be putting on a
I'll be back Sunday
Some sort of capabilities
Without getting too deep into anything
Until things come up along the way I do want to say that this episode
The total mass
But honestly only half of the situation
That makes it a mess is because of what's going on with her on
As you might expect on a day like this of international intrigue
Alex and Steve pieczenik on to get his expert
And you not think
And that interview deteriorates into territory that even
Shocked meme
What you're saying a lot considering
These recent appearances on the show or he said that representative
Permit to go away
Due process is stupid
Yeah but he was involved in the death of Utah crabbing
That one was a little bit of time slot for Steve to shock me
Suffice it to say somehow he managed
To do I'm surprised
He's not claiming any involvement in the
Okay cuz I really think he might not in the present
Although he does
Say that
Repeatedly
That he is he knew the Ayatollah
Before
Okay I got
And they said I feel like a maniac said that his son was stupid
Okay alright
It's an interesting
That's that's f******
Bonkers
Dad said when he gets in about the 2nd hour
For now Alex starts the
Show off in a very weird way
Because this is Giant
News breaking
And having conversations
About
Shades of 2,000
3 people having
Conversations about what
Does this mean are there like this legally justifiable in anyway
So I'm going to go with
He's going to talk about the movie Oblivion
No
Now this is what
13 East forgotten about the way to go if you don't want to talk about this
Forgotten that that's a movie and now things
This is a white paper
Do you start out by bragging about how he's getting a lot of traffic
The Infowars servers are laboring
Record traffic As the World Turns in
Myself and my guests are going to break down and say and what colors
Broadcast
You're going to say about the historic
Credibly bold move
That we witnessed yesterday
So Alex starts out on a pretty
Like Hey we're getting tons of point is that we're getting record traffic with first of all
Maybe a
Recent record of something
Record traffic
Pick from your yeah yeah
But it is a
A selfie
Aggrandize
Using opening
Hey yes there is a lot going on in the world
When big things happen in the world everyone wants to know what I'm saying
I think it is
On the other hand I think
The last time Trump bombed somebody Alex got really drunk
Cried on air so I think
People are thinking like call God
Yeah yeah yeah it is a certain amount of
Training the people have gone under the
Crazy's going to have to be surprised if he did get a lot of eyes toon again to be like what
Going to do
Is he going to finally break with Trump over this he's already the last time he said he crammed Isis up
A dirty a*******
You got to take it up
Not you
I would believe he's getting increase traffic
It's not people who are like I need to know what he's going to say
I think that's what's going on but
It seems to show where his priorities are released where his head is
Yeah as
So Alex said you heard him say that this was a bold
Trump drone attacking sulemani
And
You know that
Continues he keeps
Calling it Bowl
At the beginning of the show he's trying to walk a line here where is
He's not
Into donating a right
But it is a bulge
Decisive move by the
The sense that I get from listening to this and it doesn't change
Really throughout the
The entire time is it
In favor of this
But doesn't want to be in favor of
Doesn't want to be like overly like you're right but is
Pretty in favor and I think
Wants to go to war with Iraq
He also doesn't want to say he wants to go to war with Iran
Defensive
Quite frankly he sounds a lot like a lot of the people I remember Becky
Beginning of the Rocks sounds very similar
Which is weird lot of those folks are coming back up
What I'm showing backup makes total sense
Alex Jones
Becoming one of them is a transformations
But anyway
Here's how Alex or two starts this
If you eat encourages of Siri
Febrile response
Really pull back and be cerebral about this and I'm trying to that myself
Also really quick this sound is terrible
Do we need to stop now is atrocious
Just I don't I don't know what it I don't know what the problem is the audio is
The disaster
How much for myself
Look geopolitically what's happening around the world and what message President Trump
North Korea
Obama and Hillary and John Kerry that I've been working with Iran
Against
President Trump and Congress
Against the law
The fact that they been encouraging Iran to
Attack ships
Engage in massive military activity across the Middle East
So I don't I don't know if people are actually doing that
Yeah
Don't don't you don't do that well it's only because Obama actually made this all so I can
The second thing is like this is a message to everyone
Message to
Yeah yeah yeah
Alex starts talking about a Ron
He starts talking about the country is in some pretty glowing terms but also at the same time
You know how licking pro-wrestling
A really good
Opponent
We'll talk about how great you are if you fighting
Right because they want to beat someone that they have built up
You're like a person you're in a few to get a piece of s*** you
You suck now. Either of you no matter what ends up happening
It's the Travelling Ronin looking for the greatest swordsman in the land in order to defeat him and test his true powers
Someone over
And that's kind of how I feel a little bit about
Alex
At the way he talks about a wrong
This episode is very much like
Building them up
But also like
There are worthy adversary
Won't it be glorious when we defeat
And the Iranians are where the word
Aryan come from
Models of the Aryan plan
Believe for 3000 years they have a right to rule the Earth
Iranian people are very smart
They founded what is Modern India today
Pakistan they invented shafts much of language astronomy
And a mixture of that was
Islam is a good case of cancer
Anyway you slice it
So we already had one guy last century
Going to take over the planet
We we do have that going on again I'm not saying I want to have war with Iran
Either the devil
That the
Hezbollah militia
Islam
Dinner working with globalist deep state
Trump and America
That's not being discussed the news why this happen
Well that's cuz this is convoluted not is anything that he just said true there is one little colonel
Send Ronnie and culture cuz I'm pretty sure they didn't invent chess
Exist
As a name for one of the 16 Nations mentioned in the zoroastrian text
The avesta
It denotes the Central Asian group that was known for being good and lawful people
It's not a racial or ethnic designation it's more of a cultural descriptor in the tax
And the oldest known copy of that dates back to about 2
224 2651
Who's a really easy
I text you
Absolutely not Beacon
Confused with the racialized
Concept of area that's associated with Hitler because they're
Completely separate ID
The notion of an Aryan race didn't come into being until like the midday
It was largely uses
Vehicle to Ark
For Caucasian Supremacy
Referencing back
Prince's India Vesta
That was one of the pillars
Evidence that
It was used to bolster the
Caucasian
Aryan race
Bulshit
Obviously Hitler had a plan that involved Aryans and racial Purity but I'm not entirely sure there was ever such a thing as an official
Plan called
The area
10 plan
I can find
No references really
The Arium plan in any official writing
Things are serious places
The only place I can
Find where the term comes up is
Make some Neo-Nazi blogs
A book called the holy book of Adolf Hitler
For some context that book was written in 1950
E2 by James Laurent Battersby
Who was a British fascist
Who believed the Hitler was Christ
One wonders if that's one of these gift
2000 books about World War
What's claims he's red man you got to be you got to be bones if you think Hitler's is the next Messiah
Call Dan
A lot of the stuff Alex bring something like
Complete muddying of historical Concepts in linguistics that I really have the page
To address
Cuz there's a larger point
Worth mentioning
Alex is literally saying that last century we had a guy who called himself an Aryan who wanted to rule the world
That's happening again
He says that he doesn't want war
Everything you saying justifies war is being the only
Only possible outcome
These are the words of a warmonger
Who's also too much of a coward to be pro-war when
Mayfield's
That's his position that's it that's the sense that I get its
If you're if you're saying that there
I like that's just
Setting them up as the next Hitler
You didn't even know that they were going to be the next Hitler yesterday and today all the sudden you're bringing out the zoroastrian and
Mistletoe prove that we need to bomb
The mask
So Alex every single time there's something major in the world
It's a false flag
This one is probably not a false
This one
Is absolutely not a fault
Clear
This is not a false flag this is not a staged event
Put a white person did it
F*** you
So getting that makes it seem pretty positive strong message from the president's not at fault
Flag
Shiite militias have been killing all over them
It seems like he's
Justifying the act more than he is analyzing it any meaning for what
Like I really don't like the same like
Propaganda push in 2000
Three I'm just feeling that
From so many side
I-it's
It's just so creeping
Insidious
I hate it is frustrating
But if it makes you feel any better
You should take some comfort in knowing that Alex
Isn't taking a side
True
Very much
He's not taking the side he's at work
Just reviewing all the ankle
I am not going to come on this show
And
Choose a side
Crime against the strike
And I'm not doing that to be lukewarm.
Take a side
I'm doing that because I want to look at this
Perspective
Government
And the individuals running our government and talk about the different players that are involved
And what has brought us to this point
Then
At the bottom of the hour I am going to give you my personal you
I think about this situation and where I think it's headed
What my
Richard Menendez
Spiritual gut-level
B is
So he's not going to take a side with the bottom of the H going to take a side
Sure
Sure I like
Hey I know what is what I'm hoping for
I'm hoping for
One-on-one combat
Trump versus Khomeini
We take it that everybody's taken
Right
Nah
Winner-take-all.
We we become Iran if they've Khomeini beats up truck we become Iran Alex would love that because he thinks
I got to chastise for that because I
I am
Yeah
I think that
He doesn't
Need to say that I'm a
I'm not going to get on the show and take a side cuz you've already taken
Yeah
You already Empire
All you can do is
Break that's all you can do
You can either just
Do what you're going to do whatever mealy-mouthed nonsense
This is
Is just a continuation of the side you're already on the only way you can
Can say anything meaningful as be like this is it
Yeah and he's never going
I don't never but he's certainly not doing it on this
Surprise
You say you're not taking aside
You're still then giving tacit
Permission
For them to do that
That you know either you are against it or you are passively
Adore active
So Alex begins his sort of analysis
About the situation with
Ron and Ann in Iraq by talking about
Syria
Emotion
Included
I want to analyze the facts here
We know that there have been six different chemical attacks that have all been confirmed
3-stage
5 years
Before
The office I'd say several
The Isis and Al-Qaeda operatives would fire the chemical weapon
Videos wanting to get
Rockstars
The Assyrians
We would come on Aaron say that is not the case that is a stage chemical attack
And it's all been confirmed
So when I was just a chemical weapon
The taxis not talking about a Ron this is just about Syria
Endlessly complicated topic
Disingenuous fired
Present myself as an expert on the topic but I can
Tell you that I've read up a bit on the relevant literature
Anythink
These attacks were faked
Defensive
Alex believes that the rebels in Syria attack themselves with chemical weapons in order to sway World opinion
It against the Assad regime
Impromptu us attacks on Assad
This is not based on any evidence really it's just kind of Alex
Got feeling in the gut feeling
How much is gas
It's kind of the same thing as when I was
It's predicted that the glow stick
Because that's what he would do if you were there
He's discussing these artists for in Conflict so little of it is based on reality
And so much of the analysis seems to boil down to what Alex would probably do if you was in the rebels place
Is desired outcome
So everyone must be similarly inclined absolutely
Kind of Howard
The real giveaway that Alex is talking s*** here
Is it he says that the UN has had to admit that these chemical weapons
Is that extra staged
That's a bald-faced
Reply
The only sliver of truth to it is that Russia has consistently vetoed measures in the UN Security Council
Investigate the use of chemical weapons
Syria
Which seems weird
All Alex's doing is repeating Rush
Russian government
Going going back to at least 2013 Russia was arguing that the chemical attacks
Being staged
Sway public
Opinion against
Facade which makes sense given the he's a major Ally there's in the region
All credible investigations done by groups like The Human Rights Council in the organization
The prohibition of chemical weapons
Do not support Alex
And Russia's conclusion
Anyone
Has not had to come out and admit because Alex was so bold
Report
The truth I'm pretty sure that would have been much bigger
News
If that would have been a real big news dad remember that twin
24-hours Michael actually great dude
Yeah no not happened
Strange but that's the perception
To have
I will get back to this a little bit later cuz it comes back up
Just got a tiny bit more.
Detailed but
Suffice it to say I just find that
That's Tuff
Yeah when these guys
Talk
You can see how much
Damage
Is really possible when Alex starts talking about 4 in
Because
You know when you get
Sure you can
F****** our ability to get Medicare for all
And that's going to ruin
A lot of people a lot of
People's lives but when he starts saying nonsense about foreign policy
This how we get into a f****** War
Where hundreds of thousands
The people die
I've been violently
No fakes
Actually I think he's irrelevant enough
Probably isn't having a
Any like actual impact on decisions that are made but there is
You know it would be Hazard considerable audience
Deleting them as a block
Block as an electorate you know of some sort of voting
That didn't able
Facilitate
Negative
No information or on no factual information
Yeah exact
And that's that's not good justo is opinion
Admitted it must know but he feels like
Alex believe that
The message Trump is sending
And this whole thing
Is about
China is the real issue
Middle-east isn't even an issue we don't even give a s*** about them anymore
Yeah there's if there's a kernel of it okay
Pragmatically saying we're not going to do this in the Middle East is not an issue where are the energy independently
You asked
China they're the real threat and the globalist want to divert us and our military in our blood
Trap
I don't touch it on this in the past but Alex is parroting a disingenuous Trump talk
I'm going to hear that
Is unacceptable to like Stan
He's trying to present the idea that Trump is above The Fray because now the US Energy Independence
Sorry about the Middle East
Kind of a f*****-up notion on a
Let's face and it does seem to imply that our only interest
Booby yeah that
If I'm
Yeah something that Trump himself
But the reality here is that we're not energy
Dependent person
Alex is confusing that with our Trend towards becoming a netex
Exporter of oil
The same thing
According to foreign policy we still imported
Proximately a million barrels of oil per day from Saudi Arabia in
The generally agreed-upon definition of energy Independence is that we would be producing more energy than we
We consume
And during couple months of last year that was something we achieve
But this isn't the Trump thing though
It's been a long trended process in the process of
The steady rise in energy production and relative stability and energy
Consumption
Going all the way back
Text through Obama's entire presidency
I don't believe that Alex is using the term energy dependence
Independent in that
Contacts though
It feels more like you saying that we don't
Import anything we can just create all our energy ourselves
Which is defended
Yeah it does sound like
He saying if
If United States were suddenly cut off in the entire world
That is
The image that he's hoping to
The present that's not true
Like weed
A lot of the energy that we produce so in order to meet our
Assumption needs we still bringing a ton of foreign energy
LG products
Why was that
So well that's why when you see the Strait of Hormuz taken down 45 hours a hundred million dollars
And all that so you know that everything is just
Disrupted right massively anyway
Anybody for a net exporter of oil
It doesn't mean that
We're immune
The fluctuation
All this stuff is interconnected in ways that Alex is a sort of poo poo in
It's not a good
Perspective
I mean again that comes back to this type of
It's like if if you are incapable of understanding the new one
Just like you know
Not neither you nor I are going to claim to have good policy-making ideas or experience for for Impala
Countries that we have no
But somehow this dude will f******
Do you say he knows what's going
Simple
If ya simple like
Will you hit him there and then that. That's done he's cracked this
But he can't explain
Unless he had 20 pages
The paper that he could give you a
Brief sketch of it
But you knows it all is that
And that's why the input
Create such easy output
Of course it's all very simple in his head
So much that
Use
Just it it willfully ignoring or unaware of whatever it is it stupid
Anyway we're only at this
Is red right now with Iran
Because he's
Double-dealing globalist
I really don't feel like that's true I think the people who got us here were very straightforward
Directed their desire to start a war
Double-dealing level
So why we got to this point
Because
The Deep state bureaucracy CFR
The Bilderberg level is leftist arm of it
Neocon
Everyone but the guy who ordered it with Iran
Barack Obama
Hillary Clinton
The only Hill the general McMaster time
They have been working
In Shadow diplomacy
Derail everything the Trump trying to do to bring real daytime
Stalemate
Fire
Africa and the Middle East and in the global strategy
Flooding turkey
Stabilization
Backflip is a prime example of Alex saying nothing
He's accusing vague factions like
The quote Bilderberg globalist a leftist arm of the CFR with a run for
Stabilization what did he say what does that mean
What the f*** other than salad is Bilderberg globalist electus arm of the CFR
Things to work with neocon mean salad it's a very very
Specific group of people
So dumb maybe three or four people fit that
Right when you get that many qualifiers and do it because
Inclusive it everybody everybody everybody
Modify
Globalist
Even Beyond
Concern
What is a Pakistan rating about
If you talkin about
What are Obama Hillary Fiona Hill and the general
Master types do it
I want to sing the working
Publicly in Shadow diplomacy but what does that mean
It can mean whatever you needed to mean dear listener whatever you think it is
Iran nuclear deal that's talking about
It's all
It's all just him throwing it a bunch of words to give you the idea that it's
Anybody
Sport.ro
It is not his fault
Nothing is his fault that's a big piece of it but
I think the larger
The thing is that
Vagueness is a weapon for someone smart alec
You can just rattle off a list of his enemies name
Make some meaninglessly vague accusations about things they're doing
Whatever
The hot-button topic of the day is going to move along acting like he knows everything and he said something
But you haven't said s***
ISM doesn't mean anything
Nope
Anyway I wish you'd be more specific
Feel like it does
So did the big is it
What Trump is doing
Is that he's letting these
Government
Like North Korea
Is the carrot or the stick
You can okay
Isleta
Tyranno just like
Situation
Maria's at the stick
If you stop all this the sanctions will go away and will work with you if you keep escalating and working with the Deep state
The international global system for the icons
Baris America into sabotage
And to bankrupt our military and our country we are going to
When you're militarily expanding and
When you proportionately start attacking us we proportionately attacking you it's going to ask you later until we
Bunker-buster bombs
Kill the mulas
Anti Ron
That's something
Please
Individuals understand
This Is War enabling nonce
Incense
Like for one thing Alex is saying that these countries are working with his globalist enemies so Trump is putting sanctions on that week
Play play ball
Seems like a pretty Far Cry from the sort of Auntie intervention is posturing Alex used to engage in
A far cry from his
Constant reasonably Fair attacks on the United States government
Were there at the end over the sanctions are applied to a rock that killed so many Sevilla
Absolutely
The f****** time and just seems very
Not in line with that
As for North Korea I don't see how that's a good analog
If you look at the real world Trump's meeting with Kim Jeong Hoon of not really done
Anyting
There's no positive outcome in it for the United States and only positives for North Korea
Just the other day on January 1st
NPR reported on a speech carried by the Korean Central news agency
Or Kim Jeong Hoon had announced that he quote
No longer feels Bound by a selfie
Imposed moratorium on nuclear and long-range
Missile testing
The Story Goes On to say quote
Kcna quoted him as saying there was no reason to remain committed to his moratorium because the US
Not reciprocated
But it continued to hold joint military drills with the set with South Korea and send advance
Best weapons to the South
In situations like this with Trump is doing is not saying I hate
The character the stack
What are you doing is providing
Pretext
Which Rogue actors
Used to just
5 horrible s***
Trump pulled out of Iran nuclear deal unilaterally and imposed harsh sanctions on them
What according to all experts on the matter of Ron was
Complying with the deal
Trump made some kind of it
Beetle with Kim Jeong Hoon which Beatles are
Has not been honored
Both of these are examples of really shity for in relation
Witch makeup
The possibility of
An outbreak of hostilities more likely than they were before
Trump isn't trying to create peace he's f****** with people
Civilians are the ones who are going to
Pay the price ultimate
This is ghoulish stuff
And for Alex to cheerlead this order bulshit
Really upsetting
Yeah
Pretty bad
It's
It's kind of mind-boggling
It really isn't even that thought process of like
Oh well we did something stupid so they're going to respond proportion
Finally and we can respond for porch
Let's just
That's just dumb
I mean it's just really really dumb we have
All of human history to point out how dumb that is
We can't
Boiled down global conflict into a Hatfield versus
Is The McCoys
Situation where you take one I take one we just do this forever and ever
That's f****** incredible
Yeah
Not
Right
No
No it's not right
It's not regular truck just f******
Presses a button and a dude dies in
That means but
Because of that because
Trump is a f****** lunatic
No people who have nothing to do with that s*** are going to
That's just a thing
The situation we find ourselves in is one of escalation
Supposed to
Closer to
To progress and there's no way that you can negotiate anything with Trump
It's like it doesn't seem like it with if your Iran
I don't know way to negotiate
Anybody
You're anybody why would you
Yeah you can't trust anyone
Okay we've
Negotiated this well
Anything that he
He's ever negotiated he's just redic. So
You can only even deescalate this war
After Trump is gone
That's it
And even then you probably be a little bit wary because
Decide to tear up this agreement to
Yeah
I don't I don't know
It's at
Desert adopt
Pics of it are really traveling
I guess that's kind of
The end result of us having such a
Addie emphasis on diplomacy
It's just it's just a mess
It is well and truly
The thing is
Global
The ones are doing all this stuff really feel like it
It's still just Trump and who's his guide
No but I really do
Okay never
The globalist wanted to embarrass
Trump with the situation
At the embassy
Anorak
That was that was their plan
But now Trump has gone and done this
Assassination right
Switch ruined the globalist
Plans are blocked it somehow now listen to this clip
I would posit that the way Alex is framing this is very much a positive thing
If he's
Blood enemies are the globalist
And they were trying to embarrass his
Hero and his hero stopped of their plans to embarrass it through this
It must be a good thing
They want to use Iran to embarrass from
Is winning the political war
Are you afraid to go to the mailbox because it letter after letter from the IRS
Cut up by the break their man get a lot of commercials about tax settled syllable away from
Cutting a cutting to break on time and it
It's just
Gastly
I just I see that Alex is cut
Lucky's pretty regularly giving lip service to the idea of like we don't know what kind
Next
That kind of know how they're going to respond
It's a dangerous possibility
Sometime everything that he's
Putting this
The language surrounding it is
Trump made a big political win
Yeah that's a bold move
Surrounding
Adjectives reuses are very Potter
It's it's a soft
Pressure campaign 2
Influence people into thinking that regardless of whether or not they want war with Iran
Trump is right
To do what he did
Right and you know what its defense
Because the Ayatollah
You taunted Trump
What is the Ayatollah say to Trump
I said you can do
Nothing
You can't do
Any
Then why would you say that again about
The treason
John Kerry
Barack Obama
Who travel the world
Korea to Japan
The China
To Iran to Israel to Germany to the UK
Canada
Argentina
Brazil
Don't listen to Trump
He's going to be gone soon he's a loser he's an idiot
In fact if you embarrass him
Sinking some ships
Strait of Hormuz
Remove him back at home and he's not going to get the bike
So John Kerry and Obama apparently not US citizens because they're globulus to run all over the world like little
Legos Whispering into world leaders years if they should have Barrister you listening to this childish
Bananas
Here again
And Alex is using
Vagueness as a weapon
Okay
So you're asserting the Kerry and Obama told these foreign heads
The state to sink ships
The Straits of Hormuz
Prove it
That's a serious accusation that Alex
Skidaway
Substantiate
Leaves
Get the f*** out of here
Yeah or retract
Good present a episode where I don't think we have at least middling grounds for a libel defamation
Other public figures
There's a part of our relation
Community that almost certainly has been putting out of vibe of like Trump going to be gone eventually
That's probably because he's threatening long-standing Alliance
Relationship
People who dedicated their lives
The international relations work aren't going to see
See Trump get elected watch him
Rap about how our closest allies are paying enough into NATO
And just shrug and be like well I guess who's the boss now this is what we do yeah no kidding
Against their lives work
Course they would be trying to reassure people that they have
It was a long-standing relations with
Like a please
Please look look
I know whatever
But the accusation that any of them were going to go around until countries to commit provocative actions like sink
You can ship that really needs to be
That was never going to do that cuz
Who's making this s*** up
Look the issue is to that the these are Ronnie and mullahs
Other
And talk about that Alex drops in
Rephrase
CentraState
I mean when you think about the Iranian mullahs
Quadruple games of cats
Strategic
It's mental illness
Break shooting is the most sophisticated
University
Sophisticated
It's so
Simplest complex these guys don't get it
They don't get the Christian
Saxon Legos or
Access or orgenesis
Very sad
Firstmark close
Just appointed I've never heard Alex talk about logos
Before and you can tell that he's new to the concept because he pronounced it Legos
That's e Michael Jones
Alex's drift
And a territory
Activities talking about these are Ronnie and Milos mulas not having Anglo-Saxon Legos
Not good
That's a pretty bad sign
What is
Then now
I guess the most
Complex thing is this Simplicity yes shut the be like
Right
Whatever you don't even tell me about straight-shooting when you're just lying to my face all the time later
And later he's going to talk about Trump like being engaged in this 4D chess stop where it's like he makes a boob
Really about something I like
That's not straight shooting assholes
Yes but straight-shooting is the best way to
Trick people
Everything is like a f****** convoluted nonsensical
Accusing
Obama and Kerry Estates General McMaster types
I'm going around and telling around 2
Sink ships and stuff like that
It makes it more funny when he says this about why people don't want him on a
Please remember
When you share the link that infowars.com live show
. video and Alex Young section more
This show because we're really covering real facts
Establishment
Outside well we do have a side it's called the truth
Like the reminder
I'd like to remind you that under oath when asked about the show he said that is mostly opinion
No they want me off here because
Truth. Telling you how the world
Works
So
Alex comes back
Break and you talkin about how
Ron is muscling through the Middle East
And how eventually that
It's going to be
Essentially saying that this is a world domination
When you're using
Rhetoric like this
This is the way your framing things
It really is
Adjust application for
And I don't
That is an unfair way to characterize what's behind what he say
When is muffling its way through the Middle East
Blaziken topple
The other Islamic regimes
And if that happens you'll have an organized Islamic Force even more deadly with three billion Muslims ready to take over what's left
West
Long-term
Taking I ran out of the control of
The captured
The secular country
And we can take that away
The radical islamist
Wow
We are I mean like the unpopularity of the regime in Tehran
It's not really a just
Application for this at all
I don't know I don't I don't feel like this argument
Is very good well all I can tell you is that
Every other time that the United States is f***** around with regime change in Iran it is worked out
Perfectly every time that you press
Things with like
You know hey the people would really love it if you did
Weird
Not really worked out though
There's a
If you
Watch
If you watch those videos of people screaming death to America and you don't at least go well
I understand how we got
Then your disingenuous liar
That's the only way
What are the things I think was probably the
One of the hardest hurdles that Alex needs
Queer is the fact
Did Trump do this without informing concur
Right
Pretty problematic for Alex's beliefs about the war powers that the President should or should not
Not have right he likes
The Constitution write love
Loves it
Can't Get Enough
Bathe
In the Constitution
Truly is not
But it turns out that the secrecy was totally fine
He's not telling
What's going on he fired the moles National Security Council
He's really
Pelosi
House and Senate intelligence committee what he's doing now
Tell why because their globalist a lot of them
The information
Oh fun
I didn't know that that was all you needed that's all the excuse you needed to support the Constitution I need everyone is out there almost
I've just decided they're all Global they're all moles
What we should do is Target political enemies call them traitors and remove them from Power that's how
How you get a more perfect democracy dancer
I guess that all of Alex's like protestations about former
Military actions that were taken without the approval of Congress
Just be noted it's no big deal as long as
Congress
It's really kind of funny
Timmy that
As as brexit is going on it's
It's like Boris Johnson is trying to sell England into a United States colladay
And at the same time the United States has a bunch of people trying to turn the president into a cake
So it's a it's a twist
Austin events
Weird
So Alex
Get down to
Business
And he keeps calling the decision to Trump made
I think that's something worth highlighter
Not just stick some Iranian Patrol motor
Melissa was some more
Fighter jets that's what
Bill Clinton did when he was very unpopular in an impeachment
Yes
Bring up that parallel
Dot-com
Bill Clinton impeached
Bombs Iraq
Impeachment vote in house delayed as Clinton launches Iraq airstrike
I need to move
Nothing actually happened
In Iraq when he did that already Bond aspirin Factory in Sudan
Distraction
This is real
What Benicar
Embassy was attacked
Because they've been probing and we've been putting up with
And so instead of bombing
An aspirin Factory
Boldly
Killed
The leader
The organization that has sleeper cells
Inside the United States
Now that's
Even though that'll blow up in their face
And the UFO and even bigger
How to connect a light into a wider Regional War
And so this is a really bad decision
But it's one of the best decisions you can make out of a lift of even
Worst decisions
So just for fun Steve pieczenik when he's on later Alex brings up the ideas sleeper cells and Caesar
Feel a little better
Disagreement
On the show
Largely I would agree with Alex at this was a bad decision but I'm going to take issue with the characterization that it was the best
On a list
Awards choice
Considering there was an actual list according to the New York Times and it was supposedly
The worst on that list at almost
Topically the worst on that list
Except if he did this
I was on the list
US Embassy was targeted and that's
Not good
And you think that you need to do something to respond to that
Assassinating
I really think that should be on the list of possible choices
Particularly considering that that standoff at the embassy had already ended by the time Trump
According to USA
Today quote
Militia Leaders with
The popular mobilization forces ultimately ordered supporters to retreat
Declaring the demonstration to win in the battle to expel US troops
Iraq
There was no immediate threat there was a
Situation to deal with
The target assassination
Probably not appropriate
I'm not certain I knows but
Pacifically what a good decision would have been
But that's only because I would never be in this situation we find ourselves into
To begin with
None of this would probably have happening if Trump hadn't arbitrarily exited the Iran nuclear deal
Your sanction
Which kind of destroys the framework that was building for our two countries to become a
How does a stronger understanding and hopefully
Some sort of progress
Between the two
After that point yeah I guess all options are bad
But still this
Not the best of a list of bad choices
I just feel like Alex is trying to rationalize the
The possibility of an
Upcoming War
That's really all I feel
He's setting the groundwork so he can be like
It's the Final War the whole
And create at least some sort of
The pretense that he didn't want it
I I don't know what would be the best reaction but I know if I were somebody who went on air everyday and screamed
About Jesus and God
For several hours at least look into what
Jesus would feel about
The war
Drones don't come up in the Bible that's true I guess Jesus would be fine
Said
Alex has been very against drone
Stop
The Pasty
You took it probably fairly rightly
Obama to task about the Drone program
Alex doesn't seem to be too concerned with that
Now
And now he calls this peace through strength
Let's roll some of the footage of the strike
Re from the
Reaper
Drone robot detailing
Animal show you some of the footage
From the ground
As well but those guys
But they were touchable they thought they were working with the Deep State they thought
Well now
They think death
Will restrain
On the Deep State trying to set him up with this Iran
And tell you better understanding when you have Colitis going to get a lot more serious than their non
Campbell
What's wrong
I don't care about any of that stuff
It's nonsense
So Alex already has brought up a parallel to Clinton
What he was under a p
Stuff
And apparently AOC
Alexandria ocasio-cortez has come out and said the Trump is wagging
The dog
And Alex takes great issue with her comments
Swag Dog
Clinton was super unpopular
Trump super popular
He's just
Insanely popular
Every Democrat I know
That is a ghost sad person
Stop it
Temperature
Lake with the Democrats everyone knows they work for the globalist tonight America
I don't I don't know like what kind of self-selecting Democrats
Hang out with Alex
Are you probably just be like yeah
Yeah yeah there's no way to get around there's no conversation no and if you don't want to maintain
Seems like my family
Doctor fun you guys have kids grades so nothing else
I don't know if you know this Jordan puts a Gallop keeps historical data of presidential approval ratings week by week
Pretty much all modern present
Look up which I decided to clearly if I recall correctly in 1998 Bill Clinton
Had
Negative
5% approval rating
People dead
Did not approve of him
Right Alex is going on about how Trump isn't wagging the dog
Because he's super popular where has Bill Clinton was because he was
Super unpopular
When I went out to Bob
Froggy Went A-Courtin
Clint without a bombing
The right now Trump has a 42.5% approval rating with a 50
3% disapproval rating according to
The aggregate compiled by 5:30
RealClearPolitics a listing of recent polls
Literally none of them have Trump with a net positive approval number
The average of their poles have trumpeted - 7
And the old
Glimmer of hope is a recent Rasmussen
The end of 2019 to put drop-in even numbers 50
D50
And it should be pointed out that this was not a poll of registered voters
So
Listen Pulsar you got a what
Three bias on that a little bit
Conservative friends
Not terribly
The political is trumpet negative
NBC Wall Street Journal azimut - 10
Economist at -9
His numbers are not good
His approval ratings are decidedly underwater and with the level of dislike Trump has
Pretty high things around aren't good
They're just not many people
You could sway at the
Yeah I didn't Bill get up to like
70 at one point that dude
Wildly popular for a while so the movie Wag the Dog was released very shortly before Clinton
Operation in
Infinite reach which involve bombings in Afghanistan and Sudan
This operation began on August
20th 1998 at which point Clinton's approval rating was
65% approval
If thirty percent
Cent disapproval
By December 1998 Clinton was admits to his impeachment trial
In that setting he started bombing Iraq
Switch again made people think of the movie
That bombing campaign started on December 16th 1998
At which point Clinton's approval rating was 63% approval
33 +
Disapproval
After that bombing campaign his numbers jumped
To 73% approval
But they quickly came back
To the item ID
Almost
After January 1990
86 Clinton never had an approval rating lower than
Ain't no point during his dog wagging phase with Clinton
Approval rating in his right now
How does he drink
Complete denial or he's gaslighting his audience into thing
Is euro is actually beloved yeah there's no other way
Whatever the case is real
False that upside-down real
Complete inversion of reality
Absolutely
So we can more talk of how bold was
Drop here
And then after this Alex starts taking calls
And I think this is where the show starts to get a little bit like
Oh no
Okay Ono alright so here's our last sort of
Normal
. of the
The show where Alex is
Pretending to be covering the Iran situation but not really doing much of any
Well President Trump did something very bold yesterday blowing up some
He killed soleimani
Islamic Republic of Iran
I know the song now got a joke
So he's now Alex is escalating this to he is the head of a rock
Yeah so like this
Even more of a severe app
Yeah we assassinated the leader of a Sovereign Nation and that's a bold move
Be something that Alex says
No no that's fine it's me it just be like if we assassinate energy drinks that be fine then
Okay fine let's go with
F******
It's a very serious thing even in reality and Alex's framing it escalates things
Further and he's normalizing the rationalizing
That which is
Pretty scary
What what
What is
Too far
So Alex Goes to the phone
On his first caller that he takes
Is a fan
And
He feels like Alex's
Betrayed him a little bit
Thanks for calling what's on your mind
I don't really worry about
The direction we're having right now
Real quick just so you know that
Wife says I'm your big
We're divorced
Give you the best
Barely besides we are
You like that
I can't do a push-up
I thought I was just
What's your take on YouTube, sleeper cells due process
The real quick before we get to his answer at that moment is heartbreaking
That moment of
Push your products
Yeah I've been your biggest fan I spent thousands of dollars at your store my wife's is under biggest fan
All this like
And Alex is like oh this is going to be eaten even recognize the alike
I ate like she doesn't know the meaning of that no
Now's not the time
Understanding me
To tell you recognize this
The Call by saying we drifted a long way from the Ron Paul days
Caller is not calling to compliment
Recognize
I'm here
Years of color
I just feel like we're just a long way from you now
I understand but they've got us caught sir they've got that
I don't want this War I don't like what happened yesterday okay
Video doesn't make me get excited
At the same time
You understand
That would love letter working with Iran
At a certain level to try to make Trump look stupid
They can only make him look stupid by
Coerce him into a war
The best way to make
Very different
From where we were when we were with us
So I think this collar
Something really interesting which is a rebuttal within Alex
Does framework yeah because even if you do believe the globalists are trying
To manipulate this s***
The answer within
The framework is
Well the only way that that is successful as if Trump goes to war
You don't support this s*** even within Alex's
Constructed
World of
Of intriguing and cancel
Seriously
Still he's doing the wrong thing
I think it's called her like I mean
Yeah I think his point that we've come a long way for Ron Paul
Behavior is
A contradiction
So much of what
You
Backed his brand to be if he's been a fan of his for a long time
And it would be completely different if Alex
One day
I got non-air and been like look
I know we've been one thing for a really long time
But I realize that's not it
That's like what I was saying along
If he invalidated a large
Portion of his past intentionally
Do I have recognized
That the true path
Is flu
Antagonizing the Muslim world
If you have something like that then it would make it a lot more understandable for the fan
Assess
Do I want to come along for this
Or do I want to say
Hey
This is
For me anymore
Announces allowing
Is audience that Opera
I think that's probably not
Yeah what he just said they're IAAI
Iconstituent is almost
Like that like
Then he recognized
Oh no I'm I'm getting attacked from my own
My own folk here from hyper massive failings if you'd like
I don't want to war either
But we have to have a war
And you know
Nobody you've never heard that before you never heard anybody say that they don't want to war and we have to have one day
They always say they want
And this isn't the only
Express disapproval
Pretty good disapproval is got to be like
Listening to that has to be a massive
Betrayal of everything that
Dave Lee
Yeah I think I think it's getting to a point
I am only guessing
It just imagining what it would be like
To be one of his lesson
If you are somebody who has
Modicum of awareness
And I think
A bit yeah
It would be very difficult to experience
Constant
Dissonance between what this was
Supposed to be and what Alex is
Is doing
And I think it'll be really difficult to not feel like
When
If Alex isn't going to say enough
At some point when do I
Yeah what is the point at which I realize that this is off the rails
Yeah and if I say enough to Alex
Do I say enough to
What am I saying enough
When I say enough to
It's a it's an interesting
Situation that I would imagine the number of his listeners are in
I don't I don't know
Just guessing say like it's a lot
Episode
It seems like there is at least some of that sentiment
It's getting through on a
It's pretty interesting
Anytime I try and put myself in that mindset
Regardless of
Like the beliefs or opinions or anything with no
Contacts there
It just has to be an identity
Like that's the only way that I can
Like empathize with a
Alex Jones listener
Beyond
You know it's just
Imagine if
All the sudden Bernie Sanders is like
Actually this war is f****** great
You know that's an identity crisis
Like what the fuc
Yeah or something even more so to Slippery lie
Like
Alex is doing this we have to do it
Yeah I've heard those words before from the mouths of people you said were Eve
So Alex takes another call and this guy believes that
Wioa Ron
Overthrowing their God
Because of
The shop or something
Cuz of the other times we've overthrow their we did bad the last time we need to make up for it right
By getting rid of the Ayatollah
Repeating history is a brilliant idea
It certainly is
Joseph they got rid of the Shah I think us
Always stay raining
People
Basically a payback to the Ayatollah because they brought him in
And I think you asked me to help that uranium people just empowered
So this caller claims to be the child of former Irani and counterintelligence couple like his parents workout
Counterintelligence in the erotic Museum
They were driven out of the country
The Ayatollah
Came to power
I have no idea if that's true or not this is just a random person calling into a very dumb radio show so claim however you feel like
Whatever the reality is I'm certain that Alex would have argued against
Two parents immigrated to the United
It states if you had a chance to
The only reason I got this clip is because Alex at the end
Support for something
Express support for which is the restart a run
Restart A-Rod was started by Syed Mohammed hossain
A former game show host who wants to restart the country
According to 2018 peace and Bloomberg
Today he lives in America and urges Ronnie
Rossini began spray
Snow in Toronto
I'll send you began spreading his message on telegram ultimately having a
Rocks through government building
And film it
Supposed with his hashtag
With telegram considered
Vandalism contest
That just got him a warning though
He raised the stakes and told his followers
Cocktails in tomorrow
That might be too
Oh no it seems like a pretty f***** up dude
That sounds like a
Really want to litigate the properties of violent protests in the face of an oppressive regime
Play except there are good arguments on both sides of that discussion
However I do think
It's someone like hussaini trying to encourage that kind of behavior while living in the United States are not ever
It's something that I find
Do not be a good model for positive social progress
Probably
I think that Alex just likes
Because
He has publicly compared himself to
Trump a number of times in the past
Highlighting how they're both former TV stars
Alex is painfully susceptible to people who make their brand
IMAX
Country's version of trump
Yeah they just can't eat the catnip to I love you
Yeah
Ridiculous
And if their favor
He is very much a star
That doesn't
To be the case
So this
Colored says Vapes
Hey
Trump
We got our support
Because there's got to be a maginary intelligence
That we don't know about
Doesn't when will people learn
There doesn't
Have to be imaginary until
They're willing to lie
There's imaginary until
And then this person the conversation
Steers into
Divine Providence
Warren issue
Should I not go
Forum
We cannot believe it because there's
There's so much going on
Everything that's going on
I completely understand
Believe that
Okay
Stop believe
I strongly disagree
When you're on a show that's complaining about a theocracy in Iran
Say that your president was
Chosen by God
There's a slight
Problem
That's
I would say that
That is
Purely unacceptable way of think
Yeah you know like yes regardless of
Just that idea of like
Well you know he made one bad decision so we still have to
Support head
Is like okay
Put
Green peppers on the pizza that
And you don't like green peppers
I get it you still support the guys
As president
He starts World War 3
I think then we need to start talking about other options I even understand I even understand that kind of mentality
Being acceptable in terms of like kind of
Border Collie
Yeah there's some time to do political decisions that have really negative consequences that may or may not
Abby
Justifiable
As you can kind of take
The position of
Hey that was really bad but
That's it
Make you right
But I don't think that applies to Prince of process versus results
True you know like
That's why it's hard to show your work and that's why it's important exactly on vague ideas of imaginary
Exactly
Promise that the caller has a ton of stuff we don't know
No
Is left to be seen
Until we know
Whether or not
The secret stuff
Extra
It's unclear
Guys instant assumption is they like
Wow yeah everything that we don't know justifies all this
That's why we got a keeper
Keep supporting the God can
Boggle by
That idea of
Anytime somebody has asked for evidence from Trump
Regarding
Any
Possible thing
It is operations
Right there is nothing
Nobody's ever been like
It's either we're not going to share any of it into or the evidence we do share makes him look like a psycho
Seems like
So there's a preoccupation that the embassy
Situation
In Baghdad was supposed to
2B Trump's Benghazi
This is something that keeps coming up this
Comparing Benghazi to the Embassy
Do you see that you're a little bit
Daniel Khan's in the CIA
Wanted a war so they made a little packed with their leftist
CIA
They could have a bye
You know what the situation but either way the Deep
Say when
And then Sean
Trump comes out of
Field has killed our leader
Dino ranus IHOP
On the beach
Dayton 1 a.m. projected American
Power boosted at 3
It's him I get chills I mean
I mean I agree it smells of him
Let's not start you know what yet my clothes doesn't Pulp Fiction but
Right now looks like a masterstroke by Trump just saying
Masterstroke
This caller is laughing about the the attack
This is all very
Positive stuff like I isn't really
Outside of a couple of callers who are like expressing the thing like the guys that we drifted
Ron Paul
I typed that there's
Not as much
Negative
Expression
And what it does, comes in like really f***** up ways I
The next caller
Let's just go ahead and get to that because this is kind of
A negative like this
Attack wasn't
Good
But the way it is it
It's Express
Is deeply deeply troubling
Herself with Iran
We need to treat Iran like a bee's nest what do you do with a bee's nest in your yard
You have two options
Ephraim it
Wait until the evening comes every become home to nest
Kill every single one and destroys an s
Iranian
Literally believe
To bring
Apocalypse in the end of the world
We believe that the twelfth Imam is just going to show up and Iran and save them all
So this caller is Express
Sing like this attack isn't
Good
Because we need to do is leave them alone or commit genocide
This is not
Acceptable stuff to be disliked
Discussing on this radio
That is not like Alex shouldn't be
Alex engages with
The bees nest
Metaphor after that
You shouldn't be doing that
You should push back on that
This guy is explicitly using a metaphor
That is
Eradicate
One of the two those are the only two options
Because all the Ronnie ins
You're the one
The world and that just is not
There's no way there's no way then
That that can be
Appropriate
As Converse
No I
Just don't
I just don't
I don't I didn't cuz I
I'm on a very
That's just Psychopathic murderer
Like you can't talk
Disguises disguises
Whatever she's never going to be able to do genocide or anything but that thought process
Is very much
In his world
F****** Psychopathic murderer
Domestic Relations
My complaint about it is too full one
It's horrible
Perspective that this caller has
When Alex allows callers to call in and express these sorts of things and not push back on it but not
Discuss why that is a dangerous idea it has
Effective normalize
Effective like oh that is a position
Spit Alex deemed worth it
And for any impressionable listeners they're going to
Much less shocked
By the car
Concept of extermination
And just the way that
It's being discussed
Yeah like this.
This is
Tragedy
Even if you think that even if you think
Honestly in the long-term that this is better
This is all a f******
Tragedy
It should be
Talked about it
Yeah
Center on
The civilians
Disposition by
Geopolitical ship
Yeah
So I would argue that
On the 5th
I'm not into it
I did think the 2019 was a bad year but 2020 is really shaping up to be a dude it's a small sample size
So
Maybe the year will get back
Pandora getting to the hear Alex has a slightly different
For sure
2020 has to be amazing
Every way
Dr. nography
I just
The numbers alone
Incredible
Call here
I think it's going to be incredible and
Because it's amazing how to restart the show
Record traffic
Yeah these sorts of events have a tendency toward
Giving him hope that is business
Viable
Right nobody knows what the hell is going on
So
Let's see what the crazy person has
But he's willing to give us cold comfort
Sure
Let's take a little boy
Sure from the show
And enjoy a commercial
I was listening to I accidentally left it on during the commercials
The feed
And it turns out the
No
The guy who runs
Genesis Communications Network and formerly Midas resources before he had his gold sale license
Provoked by the state of Maine
Minnesota and Alex said to
Probably help him
Pay off some
The legal fees
Maybe
Anyway
This guy
Still running scams
I kind of thought he faded into the background
Why I have a reason to believe that he was the reason that Alex did that
Sort of the infomercial with jeunesse
Because Alex
And the Infowars brand
The end up working
Right
Communications Network debt
Okay
Speed of Alex's show you'll hear commercials where George Noory
Promotes
The Infowars Lyfe Genesis
Life
The George Noory from Coast to Coast AM
Has cut a commercial for them that airs
Seems to be maybe the
The scam that Ted is on board
Has more on the pier
It seems like an MLM multi-level marketing age
Is there
You got another thing cooking
It's a little bit of a sweet
Steaks I would you like to hit the range tomorrow with a brand new gun
Because the United States Concealed Carry Association wants to give you a free gun right now
Completely free
The uscca is here to give every responsibly Armed American the education train
Legal and financial protection they need
And today they're giving you
Not one
But for free chances to win $1,000
Simply text juicy on 287 to 22 to get entered now
Can you get for free chances to win $1,000 for any gun you want
I think they have to do that cuz it might be illegal to have a gun
I don't think you're allowed to just give away gun
You think about this
Is this is
22nd
It tells me that Genesis communication
Can't be a good financial position
Because if they were why would Ted Anderson do this voice over himself
No he's not
That leads me to suspect you can't hire a voice-over actor
Or I don't know I could see him thinking he was great
See him being one of those like local car dealer guys is like
Amazing on TV that can probably hear some sort of Music in the background
The Fingerprints of an editor
I don't know whatever the case it doesn't look good any sign up
To win a gun
$4,000
I'm fine with the thousand dollars when you got to say I guess I guess just needs to be attractive
Could have been prevented by concealed carry
Targeted advertising
So Alec
What's comes back
From break
With a new gun
We've not heard him talk about the news
That broke about his section
In the Sandy Hook
$100,000 or so that
He brought upon himself
That was the day to get into that account
So Alex decides here on the January 3rd episode where he is
Ben
Bulshit about Iran
Like that's the version that's his version of wagging the dog.
So
Alex's
Emmett Idaho
I hesitate to explain this ahead of time for fear that it might ruin
Surprise
But Alex's position on it is that
There's a message media blitz
About this story
They're trying to present in people's minds that he lost
The Sandy Hook lawsuit
And that the CIA is behind
Basically
Disagree with all three of those but
I think he's got a good movies
And I haven't spend all the time on this
I really need to make him into a special report tomorrow just on it
They put me on every News Channel
McHenry newspaper
What
I'm constantly
They had me on
From 9 at night until about 2 a.m.
They drop the red Scrolls
Sing Alex Jones found guilty of lying about Sandy Hook parents that's not even true
The judge said I
That's not accurate either like
$7,000
It's a joke
That turns into Jones is guilty of the Sandy Hook
Why would they do that at 11
That have been the local paper that meant nothing was a blast year of this judge
View
Warriors
Imagine deposition I asked you a question and you don't know
Seven-year-old videos
Violated the court order
You have
Go to school
What is $1,000
In the rain should have scored the first amendment
Trump derangement syndrome
Yes I paid people tell outrageous lies about me
Why
Amazing calls
We really know we're talkin about
I'm right about everything and that's why I say under oath that my show is mostly opinion and by emotion
I can't allow my feelings
The only thing that it attorney would say
It would respond to with
This is unbelievable I've never seen this before is Rob do
Right that's the only thing that you could say otherwise everything else make perfect
Like reviewing Alex's behavior in this case
Unbelievable
Barnes is going to work Barnes
To take over this is unbelievable
Payday
Keep disease
That's unreal
Yeah I mean
What I find really into
First thing is that like the news of his didn't break on New Year's Eve
Clearly
I'm guessing maybe he did
The stories when they
I just had no awareness I guess not I don't imagine that the ball was dropping and then recovering
Nada
Is the narcissist
And he's having a little bit of a breakdown about it
In the middle of the show he really does
I don't know I don't know what it is but
He's convinced
Let the CIA
Is behind
Pushing stories
About him being sanctioned
Now that is one possibility
Another possibility is that people enjoy these kinds of short
The people. You got yours
I don't listen to that what confuses me is
I really do think
Fundamentally doesn't understand some of what's going
With his own
This is the only read the headline
That's probably Fair
MacGregor's like but there's some stuff he's lying about
I really don't think you understand
I know I really think you just doesn't
Can't be explained to him what's wrong
You can't say I don't know in a deposition
Corporate representative
Right
Can't really give me a source as well I don't have to have sores that no
You were required
To provide your sources or you are violating me
Court order
The thing that I keep
I keep bumping my head up again
Is
I think it's
Impossible
To discern whether or not
You understand
This or not
Be some sort of
Batalla venture
Maybe but
At this point I find it
Tubi
Opaque
Yeah and
It would just be guessing
Is it it's a possibility that he doesn't.
Understand what people are requiring with him lying about everything
I think folks are going on
We could be element
Anyway
This leads to Alex
Ranting about how great his show is
Cuz they really know what's going on in the world
And you know what it is
Is evidenced by how great is callers are and hope they don't like him today and how popular
They don't think of you
Better than
He's really got the thinkers
Got the best gas
You got the best crew for real
Number one podcast
Number one podcast 2019 Joe Rogan
Number one in 2018 you didn't have me on
So when Alex says that it's in the news that his appearance on Rogan was the top podcast in the world in 2019 he's being kind of a day
It wasn't in the news
He's referring to a blog post on National file which is a website run by his employee Tom pepper
Edit it didn't
In the article it says of Alex's second appearance on Rogan
Quote the podcast is uncirculated over 16 million views on YouTube making it the most
You podcast in the entire world in 2019
Elon Musk episode of broken head
Has 28 million views
But In fairness that wasn't September 2018
So doesn't count
The 2019 tour
Resume comparison
Gordon Ramsay Shaq and Billy Elish has episodes of hot ones
All have way more
Ben Alec State on
Billieeilish is sitting at 29 million views and Gordon
49 million
So I don't know I guess it comes down to what you call a podcast
I'm sure there are other examples of shows that got way way more views and Alex on Rogan but I don't have the patience
To come up with more examples
Because
Now I have to watch all three episodes
Cuz I'm fairly certain Shaq's has to
To be the best one
It's pretty good it has to be
I think most recent one I don't really watch that as much as I used to I was really sharp for a while and then
Guess by Guess Bass
Stone Cold
Steve Austin was on nebulon.
Anyway
The national file post
It really is just
An absurd Act
If navel-gazing being carried out by an organization with
Explicit ties to Alex
Themself
It's just a puppy
Piece that really comes off looking
Since it all that really covers
How many people watched Alex on Rogan
It also includes a graphic that Rogan put out that included
The most liked and disliked
Episode
So the year which the post comments on saying the Alex's appearances quote
The most
Joe Rogan Experience YouTube video of the year
Of course the graphic also shows that Alex's episode is East 5th most dislikes right but the article doesn't
Rub the good times
It's not about press
It's about all press
If I'm being perfectly honest
The entire post is just begging Rogan to rebook Alec
The giveaway is a comment that Alex very generously provided this totally legitimate news Outlet
He is not answering a lot of calls
Quote
Speaking to the National file Jones saved
That just shows how popular Liberty and freedom are
The only question is will Alex Jones
Be back in 2020
Rebook me
Right
Ask desperate
Also I don't trust the last line of this article
The websites are often vague about releasing the total number of plays of individual
Podcast episode
National file was able to confirm that Alex Jones
Returns was the most list
Most downloaded Joe Rogan
Experience podcast
Of all time
Exactly the baker
Confirm that
The only person who gave comment for this story is Alex
Himself
So I'm guessing the baby he confirm that for him on background
Because I just
Cannot imagine Joe Rogan
Giving this kind of
Private business
Detailer
National file
Alex
Texted him and he was like that was the most-watched ever right and Joe is like yeah sure whatever
And then you confirm it with us we'll file done
Put simply this
Rampant narcissism in desperation
Turn on full display
Alex is feeling he's having a breakdown about this like in the middle of the episode
Make no mistake about it
You just start screaming about how you can't lie.
People
Freedom and even my obnoxious loudmouth
Texan
Because I'm real
Obnoxious and all of it is endearing I know just like your obnoxious in season did is enduring
Did you know what eats real folks there's nothing fake here
You think I'm so damn real
I totally real he says in control texting
Eli's
Author they can't stand that
They can't scare me
Probably
Special reports I don't cut it in a broadcast I'm your calls but
I think they're getting ready to kill me and I am only seven.
They don't do that once I got something back to me
Every
New Station
Country
What does that mean
Randomly
How did you check 100
I need the folks running the show there fighting from the beer talkin CIA
Highest level Brennan and
They got a plan
They're assassinating my character in my name I had a trying to kill me
Alex does this anytime there's like some bad brass his name before they
Really
Tired stuff
He says this a lot like he has four
For quite a while now
But like it's really
The level of like
The way he's delivering this the
The pressured speech the Mania to it I don't normally see
That doesn't
Strike me as meaning that he
He feels it
There's more of it
Stream this to the performance of this narrative that he's used
Many times in the past
Yeah like whenever he was going through his custody
He was saying that to all these stories about him
It's all just a setup to make him look bad
Trackitt just Kant
Andover Andover
This is Dorset
This is Beth that's all this is
Bully
On display
The CIA
Planted stories
About Alex
Having to pay $100,000 for doing a bad job in the temposition being like really an affront
To the court
And they're doing that
Because they're got a job
John Brennan
Has a false flag plan he's going to kill Alex
This is this is childish it
Right here this is the dis in the middle of an episode
That is covering some
Serious
This is
I would I would
Venture to say anybody listening to this show like 8 if you take the
The first let's say our so seriously Alex
Getting into the
The geopolitical seeing a truck made a bold move
And then out of nowhere
Just starts talking about at the cia's going to kill him and have a false flag
Like really
Step back and be like
Is someone who is healthy I am pretty sure those are two things of equal historical board
And
Also you know
They say in an infinite Universe all things are possible but
A malignant narcissist admitting that he is at fault for his own
Demise
Doesn't seem like one of the
Well I mean his demise
Predestined
Okay you made in the rain
Intimate with God
It turns out well he's going to talk about it in the next like already we had a situation where it's like
What you're saying is
Is disturbing and now it takes on like an even more disturbing
Character
Every newspaper
It comes in
They did that
I'm not sure exactly what's going on but
Do that when they overthrow your government
It's not a pride thing it's a satisfaction thing of a job well done that well I really counted for something I really
Or whatever you know
I'm not a loser they don't win by killing me
Whatever is I got plan but it seems bad
I just thought I'd tell you that cuz I just got to tell you
I'm not doing okay
And up
Whatever
5 my life but
It's nothing to me
Because
Long time ago
A lot of times and I said
I want people to wake up
And and I literally told me it was like after this for 20 years
Going to trigger
The whole movement
Take down the globalist to do it
So you sure you want that
I've literally heard God's voice in my head
No time you know what I mean it's like
Okay you want that's because you're going to get really Torn to Pieces at the end of it
Really good
Whatever it is but you know what
This is a mess
You talking to me are you talking to you buddy
That's what I thought that's an internal monologue somebody Haswell
Sad looking out the window on a
The bus
I mean like
You already have
I got to be honest when I look at stuff like that the way I look
Is presenting all this like the CIA is going to
To kill me and do a false flag because I'm
Going to write about everything and they hate
How popular I am in
I've made a deal with God literary review's ago that I was going to trigger the end of the globalist but I would be just
Destroyed in the process of very reasonable
I kind of feel like maybe
He's going to fake his death
I'm something like that
I think he's thought about it
I would be probably thought about it
False flag attack and kill me is like
Are you going to say I don't know
I don't know it it makes me feel like I know that
Probably a part of this is that I find Alex
Pretty boring person make my mind sort of go off in directions of like
What might he try it be trying to say
Preparing the audience
And it seems to me like this would be
And the audience for you
Someday to not be there
Obviously the CIA John Brennan isn't planning to kill Alex
Ludacris
But if I find a way to kill himself that would implicate John Brennan
Yeah that's a cool right then I become an idea
Debbie Carroll
I'm like some
General murder
So
Alex has the
Little bit of a breakdown
Where
Is narcissism is really just running wild
Disturbed
But not nearly as disturbing as
What happens when he sits down with one
Steve
Jay's to know how course you're going to have Steve on his back in your orbit of course
Some of the stuff he says about what I would have
Expected
Some of it I could not have expected
In a billion years
I'm the king of South America now
Have a great day enjoy that that would be fun
That would be fine so here's Alex just introducing
Riding shotgun with us for this Tower is dr. Steve pieczenik you can be back on
I really appreciate him
I know a lot of history and just amazing how many things this guy has been involved in
You didn't even read that
I don't believe Alex read that more of it is I will I will say
Not having Reddit
It is amazing how many things he claims to have been part of
Steve would be opposed
To death
Sure probably be in favor of it
I also kind of figured he would be against
War
Actually with Ron
Right that seems outside of what he
I wasn't too surprised by his reaction
The issues of going to war
The problems that arose
The Iran hostage Siege is 911 really has come to fruition right now
I am for the assassination of soleimani
Would have done it a little bit more elegantly
I would have done.
That's kind of what I would have expected though. The f***
The response I expected
Yeah
Define but
A little bit
Little tacky the way this is Carrie.
That's
That's that's f****** b*******
Spy version of Mark Wahlberg saying he would
Stop 911 if he was on the play
State that we do know that he was involved
Was not done elegant inelegant
So
Great and it sends a message
But Alex has been talkin about the sending a message
Would you like North Korea and other heads of state
Even more focused on how it's going to send a message
Switch to the youth
A-Rod
One thing to do
Let's play Double Deals in Iran against the US
Is a message in North Korea on so many fronts Trump made the right move
That was really wishing but we will help them delete
So I'm not sure if
Steve is just talkingshit
But this is very reminiscent
The lead-up to the Iraq War
Coming out coming out of the mouths of people he hates liberators
Has a terrible terrible dictator what get rid of him the people will come to us in plaka
And say thank you America there's absolutely no way that the entire region will be screaming death to America
Yeah
So like even leaving aside the level of that stupid parallel like recent data assets and put out by Ron
University of Maryland
86% of our audience have unfavorable views of the United States
Percent favorable views
That low
The favorable number has been steadily heading downwards
The high of 31% in August
And the unfavorable number has been similarly spikings
Hello that's a month it's
67 /
I'm going to go with maybe something happened in
2016 to 2017 that made that
Opinion
It's what it's
Yeah maybe
Stephen Hawking absolution
No matter how bad the router in a ranas it's absurd to imagine
Particularly at
Disappointed history after all we've been through that any country is going to be like the US is here deliver
That's just not a response you should be selling to people because
People around the world have been plenty of examples
Things didn't quite go that way our boundaries
Dino not a good not a good thing
It's a strange
Position for Steve to have because it's
A lot of things that
Has been
Rhetorical tempo
For them over the years
So Alex realizes as you stalking
Steve that Richard haass of the cfra Council on Foreign Relations
Has worn
The Disco.
Lead to war and Alex if he responds
Money raised that article up on infowars.com
Watson
Singapore president says the world will be a Battlefield
After iran-us relations
Richard and Hodge
And they are really at the establishments trying to
I thought they loved were so much
They didn't make this call
Like what just happened under pechenik
Couple quick points to raise here
First Alex says that Steve left the Council on Foreign Relations after 9/11 cuz he knew they were involved in the attack
This is complete
Bulshit
Wildly irresponsible
Steve not to correct Alex in Media
And Steve's first interview with Alex from April 24th
Alex asked Steve about being a member of the CFR
He replies that it used to be an elite organization like 15
20 years prior
I haven't attended a meeting in well over a year or two because it's
Become very much a rotary
Club basically it's the same people returning saying the same thing
And eventually I found it a very little help
It was an organization basically designed not to
To influence our directive
Steve clearly was telling Alex
He hasn't been to a CSR meeting in well over a year to and even if you take the most
Conservative estimate of time that he's describing that would be pre 9/11
So what hour to saying
Is b*******
Maybe it's b******* that Steve has sent a toll.
Like some Alex doesn't realize it's
The contradiction of Steve's original story
Or maybe I was just making it up knowing that Steve probably won't correct it
There's a bond of two Liars who are both totally aware that the other person is
Is Justice full of s***
As the other
It's the safest relationship in the world
Two people who know the other one could f*** the other guy
Prisoner's dilemma here it's just two guys knowing where
Second point maybe Alex thinks that all his globalist CFR Democrat enemies are all in favor of War
Because that's the characterization he's imagined of
And this characterization is not in line with reality
Maybe sometimes you end up creating an enemy to fight but then the real world version
But how you pretend they act
And then you find yourself in this situation
Drive to come up
The conspiracy
Why this present
Cfre supposed to attack
B.
Lipstick
Cartoonish sketches
Nonsense
He did not leave the CFR because
911 and knowing they were
You have a responsibility to correct Alex on that
Because it's b*******
It's totally wrong don't even know I can
Confirm that he was even
Confirm you believe I found his name in the membership roller
I will believe that for sure
Okay but that makes sense I mean
Department of Fairfield
He had a Consulting business and
I know I'm sorry
Tons of people in a
It's not like
Some sort of 100
Two-person shadowy group
Thousands of members
I understand
NXT assessment of it like being a rotary club or at like people make
And stuff like that
That's not too far off from an atom
A lot of people I've heard talk about it
No
Steve does not refute Alex's
They did 911 and that's why you left
In fact
He says
I did lie
Because of 911
Which is not activated
Now
This clip also includes
Steve saying something
I find
It's nonsense
Not only because of 911
Because it's
Aesthetic organization
Paramount aesthetic Jew
Talks-a-lot
Never served our country
So why does Steve feel the need to call Steve ASA Paramount pathetic Jew
Houses jewishness relevant to the conversation about the CFR at all
I didn't bring this up before because Steve is Jewish himself and sometimes
Hasn't felt this pronounced
Does best
Translate lyrics
Pointing out people's jewishness
Particularly when criticizing or insult
I give it a pass but in this instance it
Really glaring
There's no reason to bring up whether or not the head of the CFR who your painting is a nefarious International cabal at
There's no excuse for making
Can get a compound insult
Steve.
Pathetic
Jew
I don't know what this means for say
But it really worried me
When I heard that
That's not
That's not good
They are really done
They're done saying the quiet is that like they're all in on saying the quiet part loud now
It felt when I heard him say that I was like
That that that was jarring
I didn't expect to hear the hard J
What is vociferously
Yeah that was somebody was tearing into that
Stay cover J right there
So Alex and Steve decide to take some
Calls and they get a call from a farmer in Virginia
Who has a similar approach
Or similar feeling
Sort of
To the caller who chastised Alex
The beginning of oh okay good
Okay good he has a year the sense that
For you to be like no place like when there's the first Frost
Droid the sun in order to make sure
He is also
He has a bad egg
He is not
As sort of grounded as that other color percentage
He is not the same right
This guy has a little bit of a worst Chris
B
Really sucks out
Thirty-one-year-old bomber Virginia
And
Community
Has really been hit hard
In my lifetime
Population has been replaced with
Brown people that speak it
Different language in me
Family have died
From heroin overdose
Farms
Throwing away
We believe in Trump Beezy supposed to be America
I believe in you and
Brian right now
Because
Your Infowars stickers my truck I'll buy your product
You really let me down
With this whole situation
Did you sound like a fool going in circles trying to cover for Israel
And trying to make
6 of all this when you know it's
Not right
And I love you Alice
This isn't right
You need to get on your hands and knees and
You're all in
And apologize
This is nuts
So I told you I was a bad boy
Because he's yelling for his
Really really doing all right there for a second I mean I was disappointed but that's the angle that it took but I
Kind of should have known cuz the guy was saying
Surrounded by brown people like
Clearly
Of course it'll be like you just work for the
This isn't good
But
Alex is very sensitive to those swords
Criticism
Is there any reason
Especially on a high-tension
Today like this
He has
A bit of a
Like it doesn't happen immediately but it's Frozen Four
Complete Loop where he has to get
Super defensive
Absolute about in fact
Every time every day
Is a meteor
Which I would say is also not good
Okay
I'm fighting the fentanyl coming into the country and since I was from
And
Tater ship that just mowed down 600 their own people
The communist China is a dictatorship million Muslims in concentration camps
I don't want these wars
My honest review
Dead
Are one thing or the other
We're trying to have a discussion
Okay show show
Wodify
Why aren't you to get down on my knees oh my God are Steve pieczenik take on this
Because what I've done
That's not a good response
Because no he
The arguments that he has are we're fighting The Sentinel coming in but that's not all the opiate
Much larger picture to it than just the Fentanyl
Fentanyl is bronfman
Absolutely
It should be a part of the
No secondarily
The other thing is
Ron has
Dictators there's dictators over there in China as a dictator
Response that I mean like
In this
Alex Jones
Nationalism world
The correct response is who cares
In terms of
Just strict nationalism yep your response
My response
That is not who cares
But it should be
Alex exact
Yeah yeah
It kind of should be you know why and and that's the other thing is that
When your dad's know why he should get out of
Maybe he doesn't like it
Like I mean
I disagree entirely with his collar but that's the problem when you have this
America first
Obsession
This nationalist
Focus becomes very difficult to
Have a meaningful
Understanding with people
Sing to you why you should care
Foreign affairs
Why you should care about what's going on in other countries
Because it does appear to be not nationalist doubt to the adherence
Alex is trying to walk this line is like we have interest
Elsweyr even if it is America first
Evans College
About it
I am still bad
That he thinks that I was just doing this cuz of Israel
I was really
Close to being able to like I feel bad for the
For the caller ID
Cuz he's very clearly
Please call us to talk about this buyer's remorse
Yeah
How much money have all these stickers
We got caught and I hate it
You know it's fun when rich people
Will get conned out of all their money cuz f*** them
But this dude is just
The Stooges live another the s*** life with the rest of us and he gives a racist farmer in Virginia
It's too easy to
It's too easy to con races farmers
That's just a reality
Steve has Summit
Because Alex does go to get
Steve's take on
And I would say the Steve
Devices
Next to meaning
With all due respect
Is he has a problem I understand
I moved to the South
I move to Florida to Texas
Northeast virginia-maryland New York California Virginia
I'll be finished for Sim prediction
Governors Court
Sexual
Michener's
Do roses do anything else you can complain sir
It's very simple
Texas and we carry guns
I think you'll be a happier man
Blame Alex Jones don't blame Alex Jones
Slowboy
This is a
Great example Steve
Not addressing the issue
Addressing the wrong issue
We think it may be
He's not a good hostage
Negotiator
Today the conversation and you'll see in this next clip the color is
Not interested in that level at CoCo fuckyourself
Soylent
The beginning of the stuff Alex is trying to express that he feels like what happened was a measure
Did Trump carry out
And then there's a bit of a backlash
The color cuz he kind of
Ignores that
Response to Steve telling him to move to the South
I got really mad when front bomb that little chemical base in Syria
The Hawks
And to then make the enemies back off and it was a measured response
Works really well
Okay I'm not going to be happy
Bad but but I don't understand how
How how how you think
Betraying you being pro-war I'm not telling Trump what to do
Juicy
With Steve because
Steve
Staying in Virginia because my family's been here since the 1700s
I need a fight
That's all there is to it
This is an America first we got to get out of all this stuff
Eight is Enough
Alex and you know it is
Geno's down
Ron
That will absolutely stabilized a lot of them and you won't have them
So yeah we just need to install a populist leader in a run and that will settle everything
Boggle
This is Ludacris
I mean like I disagree with the color
The other caller
That was like
Well within the framework that Alex
Is constructed
That is
The response you're supposed to have
This caller is more true to what Alex has
Presented at right
Revere long time and so there is this dis
Between
What are the colors being like this
This is what we were
This was about this is what
This is The Logical endpoint of
This s***
You are now no longer
On board with what you have left
The audio
Yeah
And that should be a big
Warning sign
You would think
Instead he could
Really mad
It is it is
Because it is a little bit like
I don't think what we should do is switch to a socialist form of government based around economic safety
For all of its people and not just focus on the few
And that's because we need to stop is really like no
I guess that's another business
Conspiracy space
Especially when so many of your narratives a ReliOn
Anti-semitic s*** from history
Like a ton of this stuff is going to appeal to
The people who are like
Not just
Politically against some of the things with the government of Israel does
They're going to have a much larger view of that
Right
Conspiracy space and that's Danger
You'll end up running afoul of it eventually always will be turned on
Yeah it's especially dangerous now because
Of a certain listlessness
You know
On on the left of somebody who's very much
Hey I'm anti-interventionist I'm anti I want if I want to follow new sources that give me this anti-interventionist
Rhetoric that I like and it all sin it turns out that
They're also at the
The anti-interventionist are also not
You know you just wandered in and now you're
It's the same
Ecofascism of overlapping URI
New York you should not
You should not make common cause
The enemy of my enemy is not my friend
2p fire keep an eye on
Very careful about
Is it is
Probably going to be a bigger issue
Forward
Unless I mean
There is a possibility
Ron does not respond
In some super provoke
That is a possibility in all of
And it seems unlikely possibly in the
As we sit here right now
It is a possibility
In that case all of this
Will be much less
Pronounce less height
But we'll see
Anyway Alex wants the benefit of the doubt
Listcawler and I don't think the color is having
Any of that s***
Doesn't it will start getting upset
You got to give us a little bit
No
Listen stop
You just called
Nautical. But I am going
To insist
Give me the benefit of the doubt and when you
Start responding and clearly or not I'm going to
Talk over you and hang up
So cool to have like a little bit of
And stuff like that on the show when you're not really even engaging with it it doesn't
It doesn't really
Castform
They go to commercial
I may come back and Alex gives a very defensive rank
About is
And it's pretty standard stuff for him
It's kind of along the lines of like everybody's upset with Israel that I always make
Accuse me of
Just because I do XYZ
It's pretty standard stuff I don't find it notable it all goes on
A bit
I've heard it many times
Only notable
Because Steve
Is there
And their Sarno
Make Steve start talking about some of his feelings
That is real
And
We've already got a hard J from Steve I don't want to hear about Israel
Oh boy
About Judaism
Is Biddy
Israel
Put them in prison
I would say name names then
Being alone forcement
Capacity after 9/11
Are you talking about
F*** off now beyond that I don't want to put this
Too bluntly so I'm just going to come out and say
That Stephen Hawking
The more worried I am
I don't know too many people outside Holocaust denial communities
Who talked about the Holocaust
Is a myth
I know that he's not saying that it didn't happen but what
Gauging in here
Very standard Behavior UT from more Savvy Holocaust deniers are revisionist
The Holocaust didn't happen I'm just saying that they inflated the numbers to make it look
Like it's worse
Then it really was
Look I'm against
Any Holocaust but
I'm also against
Liars
I don't recall this being part of Steve's character
That we've seen
On the show previously
This really
Really freaks
Is it
It is like that has this always been there or is this somehow he's even more radicalized than
I think it's probably something in there but she hasn't come out
I don't know I don't know it has to be something that he's felt
For a while I can't imagine you being a new revelation
How many
People are suddenly you know if they I you used to be a Republican and then three years later we need we need a religious Bo
We need to get f***** up
I think calling the Holocaust a myth
The state of Israel uses that's a weekend thing a lot of freshman college girls do that they go out
Florida they spend the spring break Holocaust
The method come back to get back to work so I'm on who
Pretending to be such a geopolitical expert and Steve I don't feel like this could be a late career development
Also
How is it that how could you possibly Square the events of his earlier career in there that department
With the ability
To believe that
The Holocaust didn't happen
He's not
Well he's not
Becky's not on
No
So
It gets worse
I'll just say that
History
You going to be a fool
Israel's Holocaust
He said do you want three to four hundred thousand
People in the camps he said no I'd rather have
Steve playing a little fast and loose
Details here
There were many Jewish refugees were not allowed in during
And after World War II
Place
It wasn't Israel
Primarily because Israel
Yeah
At the time the area was the Mandate for Palestine or mandatory Palace
It was run by the British
The British government put in place restrictive immigration
Policies in the form of paper of 90
Which set of Maximum 50
18000 immigrants who can enter the mandate
Ear
If you look back at that. With present-day eyes
You would think that the countries of the world would immediately open their doors today
These people were being systematically killed
But that was not the
There were very few countries that were willing to take in a vast number of refugees fleeing from Germany and Austria
And this continued even after the war
Hundreds of thousands of people who
Just revived something Unthinkable we're putting
These persons can
Having nowhere to go and very few options
Then
In 1948 the state of Israel
I'm in the first few years of rocks
Emily 140,000 Holocaust
Survivors immigrated there
And we're late in
David Ben-Gurion was the first prime minister of Israel
Until its formation in 1948 he had no formal office in the
Mandate for Palestine
He was just a prominent figure in the Jewish
Community there
You have literally no authority to negotiate immigration deals with
Aikman
Who incidentally was living
Hiding at that point is
Before fleeing to Arjun
What I'm saying is that there's no real point in history went Ben-Gurion an item
Could have had a reason to negotiate
Something like the
I was trying to find places where this 300,000 number might come up
Cuz you think they had to 300,000
Rather have pigs inside
I want to know me places I can
Can find it at that number is an interview that Ben-Gurion dead in March 9th
You published in the spring 90
97 issue
Of Israel
Studies
In it he says quote
12 years ago the Jewish state was established
First we took in 300,000 European Jews
From the displaced person
Basically opposite with Steve is saying that we we did
Right
I don't want to say that Steve is making this up
But I kind of think Steve is making
I do
You can definitely make an argument that the nonacs
Has powers did not Step Up
To help refugees who are in desperate need
During World War II
And that argument has been made by many scholars
Like David Wimer
In his book The abandonment of the Jews
That's a fine discussion to have it honestly having that conversation
You should really make someone like Alex or Steve
Rethink their current positions on him
Immigration
What's not okay is what's
Unless he can cite his Source on this alleged negotiation
Between David Ben-Gurion
Iseman
But I have to assume is that just b*******
It's designed to rewrite the event
Holocaust
There's a name for that
I don't know
Not good
Steve starts
Ranting about other a bunch of Jews in Hitler's Army really don't like Steve
No I used he's really going back where I am at
We've got a long way from Ron Paul that's for f****** s***
I don't think that's
Steve is a fun crazy anymore anyways is not go home and tell your mother
Marantz a bit here
Ironically guess who was the leader
I'm taking away the Jews
A man by the name of Hydra
An Austrian Jew
Like that
Drew Adams
Commander's I'm getting tired of this
We're really a Rothschild and I've looked into it it's true
So
The idea that there were serving within the army of the Third Reich
It's not like
Controversial
It's not something
That you'd say a b
Right now Steve sounds like he's auditioning for a role in the f******
Supremacist
It's a phenomenon that happens
Your brain doesn't make sense
You're not there in the contacts whatever you what's happened
Steve blaming
The Jews 4th
It's coming out here which is not good
I think you might have taken a real serious turn
Maybe the past better to Able better able to hide this part of his beliefs cuz I
I'm shocked by this is crazy
Whatever the case is I'm primarily interested in that last clip and Alex's claimed that he's looked into it and then Hitler was a rough day
Altru
Wonder where he's looked into this
Because it's absolutely 100%
Bulshit
Insecurities I definitely heard put forth by
Barely neo-Nazi
Recite
Hitler's father died
Hitler's father at Louis shekel Gruber
Was born out of wedlock without a father on his baptism
Registry
Which makes his
Parentage a open Quest
Who is Hitler
Grandfather
However the theory that his father was a Rothschild
And I stress
All the rumor that is Mother Maria and shekel Gruber was
Servant for some
Unspecified time
At the home of Baron Rothschild in Vienna
There's no proof that you actually ever been
Been a servant there there's no evidence that this timeline would match up even if she
She had and there's no proof that Maria got pregnant by Baron Rothschild
Birthday Adler's father
Is this fantasy stuff
And it was kind of tabloid rumor s*** in the 1930s
Is not true and is just
Continue this conspiracy.
To the present day
This story got a little bit of credibility after the Nuremberg
Trials
When Hitler's lawyer Hans
Frank told the tale waiting to be home
Use going to be Expo
You wasn't the court-appointed
Defense lawyer
He was just born
The Story Goes Hitler can find it confided in Frank
That he was being blackmailed by his nephew
That he was going to reveal that Hitler was
So he enlisted Frank to look into
To the accusation
Frank said he found that Hitler's grandmother gave birth while work
In the home of a Jewish
Family in the City of Grand
And I also
This family was by the name of
Frankenberger
Frank claimed that the head of the household and paid child
Support seborrhea for years
Cuz he knew
His son was the child's father
Sure
None of the story matches up with historical records.
As historian Ian Kershaw points out in his book
This would have been in the 80
1830s but Jewish people weren't allowed to live in Cross
Until the 8th
So there wouldn't be any Jewish families of wealth living there at the time
There was also no family name frankenberger living there at the time
And the next closest thing was Frankenreiter
But they weren't
No serious person takes a story as being any
Even close to accurate
And this story
Credibility
Rothschild
Completely made up
DNA test to show the Hitler probably did have some Jewish ancestry but that's not surprising
Given
The time.
The geography of the area
It doesn't prove anything close to what Alex's
I've seen this argument presented in some Neo-Nazi leaning circles
And that immediately doesn't quite make sense
Are these guys supposed to love Hitler
And some of them do
Sure sure
Best I can
Well the best that I can make of this is that these people
Not so much
Right so believe that Hitler was secretly a Jew allows you to
Anti-semitism
While still having a handy reason to not feel so bad about the fact that Hitler lost WWII
Yeah it was a setup
So I think
There is a certain
Subsets of that community that scapegoat
The loss of World War
The fact that Hitler was a Rothschild secret Jewish
Personality
Just leaving all of us Noble White's down the path of destruction
Bastard
Super racist Blues
And this is one of the handy ones that I've seen it
This segment is flying off the f****** rails
Into an episode where Alex just talk to me
About how Trump is totally cool to go to war
Steve shows up in this f****** thing turn Super
Crypto not
Yeah I did not see this one coming up all the things that I thought might have happened today Steve
Pieczenik showing up and denying the Holocaust
Not on the list
Totally
This is what I say
I was like
Okay Steven going to shop
Still didn't see Holocaust denial,
Still didn't see it coming
Yeah that's pretty amazing to put it plainly Alex
Control of his show
And it's tearing ever closer to being like
An out-and-out open
Play anti-semitic program
Is inability to screencast
His unwillingness to break ties with Steve
Vagina Kenny's underline big
But he refuses to examine
Really starting
Come to a head and I find the result to be
F****** ugly
That's worth seeing
The next clip
Steve says that
The Israel came up with the alai or the myth
The Holocaust
Austin 1965
I didn't make this
So they came up with the story of the hollow point
You're doing this for Israel
When they don't even know what they're talking about
Meanwhile you're talking to somebody
Who is
Engaging in Holocaust revisionism
And Alex is too self-absorbed in his feelings
What about this caller say
You can't even push back on this very clear
Super disturbing shitz
Coming out of Steve's mouth
It's real bad
It is
Incredibly bad
Yeah it's the one-two punch of somebody insinuating that he's working for Israel
While somebody is saying that Israel is the worst thing in the
Cuz he can't say he can't defend Israel
We are looking like he's defending Israel
Maybe Steve knows
Exactly like that's a
F******
The show is like
The show would benefit from
You know I've never considered what it would be like to
To run a half Nazi show before but now I feel like I really know you know like Red Ice
It seems obvious you're just a nut
You know I Fox News
You're just pretending not to be a nut
But here you're
At pretending to both be
And not be enough
Yeah wild it's wrong
You can see what a toilet
Yeah I think Alex
Hook got a f*** you up but you know what I mean straight shooting is really
He's really busy
The next clip Steve is talking about how he was there when they sold the gas to a Rihanna.
But if you listen
He gets the gas Rock
And Alex correct them
If he's really this
Geopolitical expert Shirley get the right guy
Hey we all make
Like 29 the house
Airgas
Area
I was there when they sent it
Mustard gas
We shan't mustard-gas now you know and your and you're
I think anybody in the news is talked about that
No
You think anybody in the news goes back to the Carter administration of the Reagan Administration of a Bushman
But nevertheless
For somebody in Virginia say oh I'm disappointed
What happened
Jamaican
Better
Do you think they're mad about this caller they're really mad
Yeah really threw them for a f******
Well because
He's not confrontational he's just
Disappointed in them
Hey David
It's that you don't hate look
I'm not angry with you
You know if you eat what I am is disappointed
Yeah they don't like that
No mirrors very scary you start revising the Holocaust history by accident
I'm overwhelmed by what you see
Oh my God it's a monster do s*** that's
Migos net worth
Spell Steven
Quite a showing
I'm here
He's going to come back on Owen Shroyer show
I got highway I know I said this
Just a second
Brittany
And if there are producers
They are really like
There are ways you cannot do
And that would be planning
Some sort of
Qualifications
Some pre interviews math
Instead of just like well we get on whatever happens happens
Figure which I'm very glad that we
Don't have to have those pretty
Dakshin meetings where it's like
Should we have Onan.
Not our problem
Do we know if this person
Yikes we didn't know that Carrie was a little bit of a
So we didn't have her on that's true
I guess the most unethical thing we did was talk to Larry Nichols
Not stoked about him
So Alex comes back after saying goodbye to
And
Claire's
Again that his lawsuit
News
It was all people were talking about as the ball was dropping on New Year's
I'm doing it
Hook nose
Unusual
Who the hell is giving that order in in in in your view and what is that
Science are you still talking
Steve there I forgot that he was
You still around Steve's like
It's not really all that
No but it's the Alex preoccupation with this being V image
That I'm the most important thing to send me up to be killed or whatever
Sawbones
So Alex
Now he says goodbye.
Sure and he makes clear that
He's Prince of Peace
Mini introduced
Another game
Syrian girls really smart lighting
Over the years what you want since she's been on
I'm glad she's here
And you can find her on Twitter at partisan girl
Syrian girl
World Pastor who she is I'll do a little bit of that does she have a name yeah she does I'm going to respect
Actor given name
And a very easily but just because she's
He seems to like to go by Syrian girl I'm going to
I respect works for that
Siri girls are online commentator and wildly unhinged conspiracy theory
He's going to Gaston Alex's show dating back many years but I haven't heard on the show in a really long time so the timing of her resurgence
Pretty weird
Is she somebody who's going to help
Mollify critics and
Say that it's cool that they bomb people
I will see
For years Alex has relied on interviews of Syrian girl that justifies believe the chemical attacks in Syria are false flag
While the International Community has arrived at the
Conclusion that Assad use these weapons
Syrian girl is
Decided that is not the case
And the rebels attacked themselves in order to do the International Community into sporting
Honestly I
I think she's a horrible voice
In this conspiracy ecosystem but I've never really found her all that particularly interesting the other times I've heard her on the show long
In the past
I think part of the reason
Is The Chew doesn't seem to have any credentials to speak on any of the issues other than
The fact that you was born into Mass
Australia when she was very young
And the fact that she was in the graduate program for chemistry
But you never finish
I'm not sure this will make sense but I
Kind of always seen Syrian girl is more of an Alex Jones caller who got elevated to the status of having an alias
Kind of like Zach yeah yeah I can see what you're saying
That's the way they treat her like a cat
I guess
She has something going on
Outside of in Fort Worth
Was just an
In-house production
But I in the past I've never really
See her as anything else other than someone who just
It comes on and says things are false
Could you play ball
Yeah
Primary area of importance on Alex's shows today
Deny that Assad had anything to do with war crimes
She's on the show today
Probably because her you know she has
Her support of Assad it goes hand-in-hand with Hezbollah
Since they're fighting for Assad in Syria intern is in a roni and black militia
Trickle down to a sport
So there is like a weird dynamic at play here even though she
Syrian girl
Intersection where that support
And that's being on the side of the the the Syrian Army and I
Come into play with it
The issue that
Hexiron
I answer it's not an unbiased party
At all real
But she's against
Wagner on goodbye
Oh no
If you show me all because the Holocaust didn't happen to know is that if you show your work there it is
Conclusion is a little bit different
Right so she comes on and
And she says that this is like 2003 all over
Right
Fair enough
Pictures of Mick also a pretty decent point in the fact that like
In 2003 there were allies
You're not there where the Kurds there were other allies on the ground
That's a
Made the situation not nearly as bad as it could have been right
Now the prospect of having another War
Probably not they're not have that makes the situation worse
So I think she is
The kernel of a decent point there
And then she just talked
2020s
No
And who is
Supportive
Nancy Pelosi
It was needed
I mean this woman her father actually was one of the
Founders of Israel
The original terrorist organizations
That was
Before Israel was created
Organization by the British
Really
Convincing me because
Because you're dumb you are very dumb certain Nancy Pelosi's father was named Thomas d'alesandro Jr and he
He was not one of the founders of Israel member of a terrorist
He was on the Baltimore City Council from 1935 to 1938 and member of the House of Representatives for 1930 929
And then the mayor of Baltimore from 1947 to 1959
So unless he was the mayor and Moonlighting halfway across the world sister city of Baltimore
That's right Jerusalem day on crack
What is true is that delasandro was a very vocal supporter of finding
Place for the displaced Jewish population
To be taken in
Odds with the policies of his
FDR
Is it at that point
Certainly not what d'alesandro
Still Thunder opposed British control over the Mandate for Palestine and he lobbied for the United States
Prioritize saving
Choose
He was instrumental in helping
Can get the war Refugee board established which I helped rescue effort
Alessandra was a proponent of the creation of Israel by the time that was happen
He wasn't even in Congress anymore haven't
Become the mayor of Baltimore
The weather is fair to say that he was into the formation
Israel
Much to say that he was a sound
Yeah he wasn't involved in any terrorist group
He was potentially connected to the mafia though through a friend of his
Which derailed his attempts to get reelected
Is Mayor but I hardly think that's what Syrian girl is talking
I don't I don't think she's
I don't think she's doing
Tonight in that anger
More important
Kind of get a sense here the level of s*** that Syrian girl bring
To the table
Vig misleading accusation
Things about one political figure being used
Justify
Ridiculous conspiracy
Theory like
Nancy Pelosi wanted to
Impeach Trump should be forced
It's a family bad thinking but ultimately
It's also meant to imply that it is Israel that's the reason to close he does this stuff in the first place
Kind of
Now that's what this boils down to which is
Again the same mentality that is
Not good on the
You know it can be funny
I can be funny
These kinds of
Ridiculous Wild
Stupid thing
Whatever on the on the
I am in Woodward on the precipice of a
F******
Potentially
What do you even
Call it
Possible tensions are high you know that kind of situation to then do everything
Impossible
To avoid
Giving any
Blame
False
To the guy who is
Crowing about it
As though it was the biggest victory in the world
It's so transparent and pathetic and sad but it's not funny
Now it's just
Tragic because some people
Yeah the rationalizations for Trump extend even to the pool
Point of
Invalidating why you should be in power just even to make it to
Defensive him you have to basically be like
Did you hear what he's saying that's
Here's what
This episode of Glee was
For the queen
30 sent out threatening to attack cultural sites they don't have that
In their body of information
Yeah but still
I think I think there's enough
It's not even I would say
Here is the excuse
The Syrian girl gives
In order to
Not
Really blame
Trump
Which is
I would argue
Dangerous and bad
What do you think
Don't think she's doing is my question
Good question
Think I'm
This man is one of the most
Most powerful he was the most popular and most horrible
Moron reportedly
Really was he we just killed the head of the Iranian government
Something along those lines and so anyone in
Any of the world's leaders
I'm feeling personally on this trip
So this is a pretty bad look for a propagandist
Essentially the best angle they're coming up with is
Someone told Trump soleimani was bad so he killed him not realizing the gravity of the yeah yes
But basically boils down to sing the Trump is so unaware of the world so dumb
So malleable and gullible
Quick political assassinations without understanding the stakes of his act
Just because someone told him it was a good idea
Their defense seems to be the Trump as a
The f****** idiot
What shows how thin the soup is got
Yeah yeah we've been telling you that from the beginning
And it's
Now that you agree with that somehow you think that's a good thing
Not good
This is how ineffectual the defense
Has gotten in January
I can't imagine how strained these people are going to be by the Alexa
Moron who killed members of foreign governments that he totally shouldn't just
Because I'm adult
We got a boat for
When Alex says the Ayatollah is a moron
That's a reference to something
Steve told him earlier
The show in that interview
Steve kept saying the back-in-the-day he'd been to the Ayatollah Khomeini house
Negotiate the sun with stupid luck dealing with him
Oh my God
God
That's what I was working on
Great coolout grow up to be
In some sort
He needs to be an assist
Student living home
I think you need somebody to take care of his brain and keep your mouth shut
Incarceration
I would say the witness be happy.
What happened
Like he's a name that people need
To know
Yeah like people need to be more aware of the dangerous
Insidious influence
That. He is on the lot of
And one of the problems that I think is so pronounced with him
Is he is able to be a bit
Chameleon like he's talking like this on Alex's show but I walked
To Zone live streams
Extreme that he does little video
And they are a bit pretty different tone
When he goes on other shows he has he adapt
City environment that he's in
Based on what would be appropriate
There and that makes
Particularly
So
Alex is talking to Siri and girl there in a great time
Ham2 Alex wants
Get to some calls
Egypt pants
I promise I'm going to get you one way or another I love you I appreciate you and I respect you and I apologize I've been gone to the other Carlos
Josh your buddy I'm coming to you next with Syrian girl
Real politics is not really complex it is complex
Pleasant house Martin Grady's guest stars
Steve was revising Holocaust history and I didn't even recognize it as it was happening
Syrian girl that sings impeach him it was just a
Set up to get Trump to attack Iran
Trump is too stupid to know what he's doing
Either not good guess
Good politics is bananas
So
Syrian girl has presented the Trump was told that sulaimani was bad and he didn't know any better
And now is I believe that something that The Intercept reported
10 minutes later or so Alex is talking
To her and you can
Can see that this is a narrative that Alex is crafting
But I do think they can just like Siri has bad guy
He does all this public execution
Hanging people and stuff
And and Trump said well get that guy
I'll do that
So that's my view and you know you're also making that up
I was just making that up you can see how this works
Crazy
Sounds good
The Alex he has a flight of fancy
Start imagining
Trump
What he hopes
Trump field
Possibility of real thing that this is probably what happened
Yeah it's it's
Very dumb
So what's your girl complains that Trump is surrounded by Swamp Thing
Creatures of the swamp
He is all of the swap
Yes
And then she gets into
Summerford
Discussion
But her position
About chemical attack
In Syria
Is being surrounded rattly by mormor swampish
Husband
It actually has not been confirmed it to Facebook
I guess that is not been
Iproven
Chemical weapons attack and tumor was
I kept that clip-in because it's one of the times that Syrian girl is more specific about the claims that she's making
To deny Assad's involvement
And chemical weapons
Phone number Lisa vop
Pcw the organization for the prohibition of
Chemical weapons
Their report about the attack
Wikileaks release of documents from inside the investigation
McKesson
On their conclusion
Including an email from a member of the sex binding
Dissenting View
And felt that his perspective was ignored
An opcw report
These documents are used to argue that there was a massive cover-up
The opcw which Syrian girl and Alex are now transforming
Proof this is a false flag
But none of these leaps of logic
Actually earned it anyway
The opcw director-general Fernando areas came out and explain the quote
The nature of any thorough inquiry for individuals in a
Team Express subjective views
While some of these diverse views continue to circulate in some Pub
Book discussion forum
I'd like to reiterate that I stand by the in
Independent professional
Conclusion
I honestly feel like it would be almost more suspicious if there was absolutely no.
Voices in an investigation like this operating from a predetermined conclusion
Disinterested other possible explanation
The presence of alternative
The best I can tell is more evidence
Did the conclusion arrived at in the report is the result of invest
Navigation
Counter hypotheses were there
But the evidence
Supported the sporting that were not good
That's what it seems like to me
Everybody knows that the most legitimate elections are 197 person
Santa 3% everybody knows most legitimate form of
Sure
I've looked into this a little bit and like I said I'm not an expert from the credible information I can find disappears
Pretty clearly not
To be a false
I would say I find
Very little compelling reason to believe
When I weigh that again
People were saying
Is a false flag
Asad Malik
Jones and the Russian government
The picture of which side to air on I think
Becomes a lot easier Tanger out
I just don't
I don't care for
I went hurricane
Example for what
Prove definitively this was a false flag
Is those open
Bcw leaks
They don't prove it
So if that's the
The tripod you're saved at your camera on
You're not going to fall over and I lost track of that metaphor in the middle of it
Don't worry about it it's not a good foundation
Yeah narratives that you're trying to put forth
It is
I don't know
Let me I guess I guess I want to put
Somehow this way
And it seems
Edible to me but I feel like
To a certain extent up until
I recently
Be
Conspiracy theories but they spawn and the the fanciful
Possibilities that they threw out there
Somehow seeing more
Andaz
The insanity around them has become
Even more insane in order to just
Fire now it's just turned into unicorns
We might as well you know like we're in pure magic territory now
You know it's true that conspiracy theories
Used to have
Is slowly getting smaller and smaller and Spa
The political sphere you have the overt
Open window
And like what
Where where is the topics of conversation
Inappropriate
Even the same way that is true these
Except the wonkavator
There is no tracker
That's absolutely true
What's required to push
All these ideas that are are being discussed
You're so much more
Yeah
And there's no need to scare them with
What what is just no need when when Serta polite Society is having a conversation that's like
Level
0 crazy
5 is 5
When Society is up
Five or ten you got to go 20
Otherwise people like
Alex only thrive on the appearance that they know some
Open secret right
And
Everything's crazy
You got to come up with the crazy secret that you know
Hence all of the everyone's a demon
I want everyone's a vampire
A gray
Cool it's just escalation within the rhetoric
And I don't think it can be us
Gleipnir
Not without a harsh crash
So it is next Cliff Alex uses a weird idiom
Discuss a little bit
Things to do with anything
And I promise you
Carlos
Tell her you're thinking about the ride shotgun
No
Hairless bear
I've never heard that before in my entire
Cuz it's not express
Complaining to be stalking about how like
I'm going to get to call
Alex was looking
He was looking for isn't here lips the admiral-general formulation of it is
The governor
That's an old southern expression which basically just means come hell or high water
Yeah I'm going to do this even if it harelips the Jenner
Making reference to people with cleft lips
I think it's probably a pretty insensitive
Expression that I don't think would be appropriate
Use anymore
I can't imagine that Alex is apologizing for that politically correct
So that's a level of sensitivity that Alex is
Far from
Okay so then let's go to the
The second part of the body
If the water doesn't rise over bear
Is not a popular expression
It's kind of a formulation of Lord willing and the creek doesn't rise
Which is a slang term that there was actually uses a title for Spike Lee's 2010 documentary about the aftermath of hurricane
Trina
The thing is though that those two idioms mean
Completely different thing
The first is an expression that no matter what come hell or high water something is going to get done
The second is an expression that says this thing is going to be done provided the
The creek doesn't rise
By mixing these expression
And Alex is basically saying that he's going to get to
Calls come hell or high water but not if there's high water
Yes
It's super weird
It probably completely meaningless
I honestly find us a
Conscious truth buried in there
Just built to make
Pronouncement about what
Do do matter what will simultaneously baking and reasons why summer is never going to get done
Honestly this a accidentally
I think it's pretty good ATM
Describe Alex
It reminds me so much of the Chobani lost
Yeah where he was on are screaming goat I was going to win that case or die in the process and then he settled like a week later
I'm not entirely sure what he thinks is Politically Incorrect about
About it though I've no idea for you to throw out some sort of Reconstruction Era racial
I thought you were over Edwards Creek is like I said we all know who Edward
I thought that was what
What I expect
No and that you're you're absolutely right that is so weirdly
Perfect that's so weirdly perfect
It could not have leaked out more of that like
Combination of even when I'm telling you something I am also
It's 2
Mouth
So Alex Goes to call with Syrian girl and he gets
The caller has
Some very important
He's going to calls with
Syrian girl
With his list
Yes okay get a very important
Very real
Until I really wanted to let you know that there was another thing that I was more concerned
About that I got window from some of my mileage
Africa
Some of the fs alk2 back operatives
Down in the app
There's wind about them
Ebola and trying to use it
Listen
Don't don't
That's amazing it's amazing we're doing the bowl again guys
Great running back to this weaponize Ebola
Picadillo of Syrian girl at the past
She is also disseminated narrative
Man you just can't do that right now
You just can't
So that's where we're at
I just call her
Either
Express this
Based on his Intel
This dude
Actually know a guy in Central South America I can't tell you what country is from his name or
General appearance or if he is a human being at all
But he does say that
England is about to release the smallpox Bond
On Bots
I mean you can do it that invite like immediately
So I'm Alex
Takes this Anonymous caller
You know pushing this b******* and you start to build ameredev office
Again and
Person brain and thousands a week to Texas alone
Stopham federal judges let him go they go
California jury let him go they go
And
So
The last isn't a war against America is
The thought that precedes directly after his b*******
Racist lie about being able to shoot white women in the back if you're in a grant
You see how all of this stuff is filtered and eventually comes down the drain
And the drain
Is white nationalism
It is
This alacoque
What are we going to do
We're going to come up with a narrative about how l
Tida
Indices are going
To Africa
Get Ebola to attack us right
That all that is in service
Keeping non-white people out of the
That's all that they're doing
I'm here that's that is the end result of
The end goal
Of this sort of rhetoric
Yeah
I will let Trump
Do
Anyting
Because
I think
He is going to give me a white Chris
.
That's that's the mindset or get us closer
Yeah
So Alex another call and
China
Ron
And the Bee
Together
Right
No and that's what led to this attack
But there's a reason
Which has not come up on this show at all yet
Well I mean I don't know
And Alex is Intuit
I was thinking the baby
China
Iran
Amazon
Intertwine
And trying to throw Trump off and make him look weak right before going into this first page of the trade deal
Yes
And maybe there's some more facets
Get to the other colors of
And this makes us stronger
I think they were planning to manipulate this and get this a lot bigger butt
Which is that it's an escalation
Not good
Do you have Alex they're getting this information
From a caller who's like this was just to make him look bad for the trade deal
Yes
Unreal
Real
Unreal speculation
Good top five answers on the board guess what that's number one and there are no others
Depleted
I'm boggled
So like this is been a really f***** up
Situation here and
It's a
Syrian girl is discussing how this is an escalation
You're killing
Yes
Is enacted escalation
I think that you know
All other things
Being left aside
Yes
You can't
Really make it solid argument that it's not
FairPoint or Fairplay
I told you that she
He used to be on
And I haven't heard her on in a long time
And
I think there might have been a
Fallout between an Alex and her okay
And I base that on how this
Escalation
The Arab world and seen as a boogeyman
Atlantic Monthly
I don't know I don't know why you haven't in awhile
Next week
Your perspective on things very very thought-provoking
Partisan girl on Twitter
And we really appreciate you joining us thank you
So someone told Syrian girl that Alex doesn't like having her on Atkins I mean
Why would he say that unless
He had heard that
That from somebody something going on there
Is Mystery I have no interest installment
Well I would tell you if he did he did give her the
It reminded me of the Texans like
Bless your heart
Like that that likes
I want to have you on weekly is the meeting is inverse which is I don't ever want to hear from you
I disagree I think he does want to have her on regular late
Because
She is an extension even
Further of
These old gas
Coming back
The present is
Being
Invaded by these people who Alex is left
Behind right
Steve pieczenik is another example of that this show has
Old-school Alex people on it
Sometime well you have these old school people coming on
You have these old school colors were calling in expressing this
Disappointment with Alex
There is a real tension Brewing
Bank in Infowars itself
But I think it's
I don't I don't know what it's going to lead to and I just think
I mean
If I if I had to sum anything up I'd say this shift sucks
It's a disaster
His analysis of Iran in that situation is trash
Stupid
He has no ability to push back on Steve saying
Wildly inappropriate
Inoffensive thing
Syrian girl is probably someone who we should
If he does end up coming back on the show at
We should look into
Do a lot more
Deeply
Because I know that she has a
Play pretty
F*****-up set of beliefs okay
I just think that this
Is
Bad show
I'll go one step further.
Not only does this show suck
But
The world
The surrounding environment of the show so far
I don't know I don't I don't know what
What's going on I don't know what's going to happen but we will see
Jordan website
We already told her that doesn't score fighting at go to bed Jordan we are on Facebook and you can
Can download rcob go to iTunes podcast apps or whatever donate you
Nothing to it all
Until then
I'm near
I'm Leo
Dzx Clark
I am the juiciest Ice Cube