Damn important I sweat it
I have great respect for its knowledge by I'm sick of imposing
Knowledge
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Nick.com
Hey everybody
Like sit around and talk
A little bit about Alex
Indeed we are
Dan
Jordan have you ever
Physically Escape
I mean obviously if you'd been in prison before you
Brought it up
Before now I don't talk about that
I will say I have not escaped
Imprison I've never been in an escape room
Although I would do that it's too but I don't want you out of character for me and someone who's kind of like
What's down upon me
Best.
Yeah
Probably would do one of those axe throwing things
What do you mean by that
If you never been there are places where you can throw axes you can throw axes
Sure sure
Well let's do that sometime to make a list
Eventually every wall Falls to ask
Times when I've been like
Exploring
Creeks and caves and stuff like that in in Central Missouri when I was growing up it at
I have feelings of like like
Vague memories of
Feeling like I was trapped
But I probably wasn't do probably just a like really childish
Panic mechanism
But I don't know I don't know quicksand
A lot of fears about of years ago
Generations and then we all found out that
Not even that big
Good deal I guess what I'm not opening up to like natural phenomenon
There have been multiple times
But I was even younger than when I was in Missouri if I lived in Honolulu Hawaii times that I
I got caught in like
Undertows
That is one of those like really scary
Just trying to jump around and waves
Is a giant wave
And you just get
Caught
It's
Remembering that was like as a like
9 year old videos
Escape
My God it's just like
Feeling your body
Ripped around by the water and likes
You you know to tread water you notice
You do those things and it doesn't
Or if I know that's terrible
I guess that's the best I got terms
Escape
Thanks
Text Joan
The podcast
Today we are back
Staying in the present day
Thanks for that is
You know there's been a log
Long periods of time on this podcast where we've just sort of
The presents in Sydney
Fat food yes
Suet
Rodger Stone
S*** about nothing
And I don't really care
I think there's a lot going on in the present
It is much as
Summerville
Awful some of its
Dumb I think it's probably in our best interest in the show's best interest
To keep an eye on it
And see what Alex's take is on
Uncertain
January 6th
Damn
This is 20/20
Outside of a commercial
No I don't know if it's
About Jones
Just cool
Absurd this is
Interesting
Episode Alex
Alex had some interesting
Positions on the assassination of qassamsoleimani
Wants to not appear to love it but
Appreciate
Alex
Is not continuing
Read so much
And I think I have a working Siri
I think it's because he watched the Golden Globes
I think that that is going to
Inform literally all of what ends up happening on this episode
I think Alex watch the Golden Globes
Okay so here's a frustrating thing
That should be
A joke listen to that and I'm like
That makes perfect
Watch the Golden Globes and now we're going to ignore
Irene house sometimes I don't do this but
Sometimes I'll watch
Like Dave Rubin like a Rubin report
Just to be like talkin about
I enter it knowing this is Jesse Lee Peterson interview
I just like this is going to make me kind of upset
I think Alex might do that with like the Golden Globes
I think like a wart
Suspect that he did that and then now we get
Oh no I don't want
We won't
F*** that guy
Alex thinks he did a great job
I can either
Confirm or deny that cuz the best job ever I'll never know
I just don't want people to
Might have had a great set
Not going to watch
That's going to look back
So I'm down to business but before
Books who signed up and Reporting the show
So first of all Maggie thank you so much
Journal policy wonk
Next very special shout-out
This episode is released
But tomorrow
Happy birthday kcur now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Happy birthday Casey
Next thank you so much
Bye thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Charlie
Hi Charlie
Bratz
Journal
I'm a policy wonk
I take a breath before this one
Is it Sugar Ray
Okay except sponsorship
I just want to fly
Johan
Campbell putty Devon Austin
Sweater crespin Bond fries
Johann gamble buddy Devon aspirin
Shut it down
Literature
Bright
Rain finally code
You're out there listening music
Or these guys can do that website knowledge
So Jordan the show open
With
Alex announcing that the world
Metaphorically
Metaphysically
Spiritually
And literally
Is on fire we are already is 6 days in
The world
He's on fire
Call Shirley MacLaine
And yes physically
Job now text come in
From listeners and viewers in the great continent and the great nation
Don't under
Show Infowars live in Australia you're not in Australia
No you're not
This is one of the reasons why I think Alex is really responding aggressively to the Golden Globes
Because the situation with the fires in Australia for a while it up at all
Now at the Golden Globes the number of people gave speeches that by Cate Blanchett
Phoenix had some comment
Supporting
The effort
To fight the fires in Australia
I think this is a backlash
Hollywood talking about this
People to set a new fire in Australia how can he be worse about
Well
His position Chantix started all of the fight
His initial take on this is that
It's no big deal
This is what this happen
I think the
He's being a little bit glib
I think it's important is the Alex is a
Position on this
At the end of the show that he doesn't.
Beginnings address
It is positioned at the beginning is
They're just fires in Australia it happen
No big deal this is
This how
Farmers they burn their fields in order to
Potash
Rights
This is
This is sort of the beginning of it and of course it's all just like
That's what's going on this is a normal situation but the media want
Tell you that it
Climate change
So they can get carbon taxes
To pay the roster
We're going to start here with that this is Alex's take
At the beginning
Which is dismissive
It's very much dismissed
What's happening in Australia obviously of the millions of Acres burned obviously many deaths
Obviously a lot of Prague
Pretty lost but the big story is
The concerted corporate media worldwide is saying its global warming or climate change
We paid carbon taxes
The UN and the IMF and World Bank and literally the Lord Rothschild
And Al Gore and Obama and Bill Clinton who owned climate exchanges
In London England in Chicago Illinois
But they will save us
I'll just buy Australia is China with no environmental control Lobby
Carbon dioxide come out of coal plants has nothing
Nothing
To do with the fact
Did Australia has always had Giant
I can sense your anger bubbling up
There's no big deal here it says no problems before before we get into any of this
I think that
Having any kind of tape
This video is the leading
Part of the yurt your perspective
Had a lying about climate change
I think it is
Really bad
Primarily because your focus should be on the people that are affected
Yeah
Your primary focus should be on the people who are suffering
These people who lost their homes
That is the immediate crisis
I know that there's a lot of people who listen to our show who live in Australia and
Obviously
Our hearts go out to you and you know I hope
Spiritpact
Littlest
I hope I hope you're okay
Okay yeah yeah but
I just think that he's on the focus
From the people affected and turning it into a larger conspiracy or
Dismissing it out of hand is a great disservice
That you can't
You can't open with
Okay sure
Are there alot of Acres that are burned
Property is damaged
Yada yada yada this is about Obama and
And taxes right
F*** you
F*** you but Alex's
Alex is not totally
Incorrect In His statement the fires of always been a part of Australia
The continent has a long history of bushfires which has gotten out of control causing severe damage
Black Saturday in February 2009 is considered the worst fire in recorded Australian history
Killing 175 people and destroying more than
2000 lb
At this point.
The current fires in Australia have killed 27 people but some estimates of it already destroying property
Then the worst
Bushfire on the books
Already millions of acres of land has burned in the impact on things like the environment and animal population
That isn't something we could even really quantify it
This point
Put simply eat even though Australia has a history of fires that is absolutely
No excuse not to take what's unfolding right now definitely serious
First things
No one is saying the climate change is causing
And the fires
That is a strong
The argument at the experts are putting forth is that the effect
Some climate change are
Intensifying
These fires
Phys.org spoke with Stanford University Environmental Studies director Crisfield
Explain the connection
Between climate change and these fires
Coincidentally
He also described the fires as quote
One of the worst if not the worst climate change
Extreme besides he's ever seen
What's happened is that Australia has seen decreased rainfall in reason
Sent yours while the summer is brought record-setting high temperature
These dropped
Conditions create dryer fuel for fires
Which can be started by ax
Accident or by a lightning strike
At which point the fires
Are started are far more intense
And spread much easier than they would have under.
2019 was the hottest and driest year on record for Australia according to their Bureau of meteorology
These pieces in place for what
We're seeing now
There's not a lot of mystery about this at the expert
Community but somehow to Alex
Discussing the impact of climate change has
I'm making these climate events for severe
Somehow proof-of
The grandkids
Does nonsense
Alex always make
Text climate change into a
Conspiracy about people like Obama and Al Gore trying to make money off carpenter
But now that I actually think about it
I'm not sure I've ever heard him
Actually layout there
Profit strategy would be
I realize that I've always just heard him say that in like
Don't worry about it
They are exchanging climate box
Support about
That's how they make money dance
Something like I know he says that they own carbon exchanges which isn't
True but even if they did I'm not positive how that would make them Rich if there were carbon taxes implement
Because in that framework the money collected would go to the
The government
I think that Alex is mixing up two different
Potential plans
Been floated about reducing carbon
Carbon taxes
And cap-and-trade
Carbon taxes would just
Taxes the polluting businesses whatever
To pay to the government based on their level of carbon
Working theory is that for this
Is that there's a bird
That's a larger population
Takes on this caused by the pollution
So the taxes would be the polluters way of paying to help mitigate the damage
What's Don to ever
They're people with different views
On how that tax money would be spent
Some people think it's
Should go to subsidize alternate alternative
Resources
Something could be paid to
To the citizens in the form of carbon dividend
Others advocated being used for more General
Construction improvements to make Society more able to
Deal with the consequences
But the basic idea is that pollution hurts all
So the polluter should have to pay to help a larger
Society deal with those concert
The independent recently reported on a new study conducted by
A coalition of 15 health and environmental organization
And this
Report found that your risk of lung
Cancer Rises approximately 10%
If you live within 50
Demeter's of a major road
And that there were additional risks
Childhood lung development from
The air pollution of living near high levels of track
This is why emissions restricting regulations are important for the automobile
Which incidentally something
Trump has been signaling that he wants to relax
Considerably
These are the sorts of things where there is a damage to society
Therefore we need to
To do these things in order to help
Mitigate that
Damage
How about this
All those people can die
Still get all the profits
Behind the carbon
Texas ID
Conversely cap-and-trade involves the government's setting
The cap on
Which each company could
Theoretically
But let's say you're running a factory to make improvements that'll sure that you don't end up hitting that
In that situation you could sell those permitted emissions to another Factory
It's going to end up
Feeding the cat
This is the word
Overalls
Feeling for a mission
And make it so that limit is not exceeded
Currently 9 states in the United States and many countries around the world have cap-and-trade
Systems in place
Granted there are other cap-and-trade models that don't have an overall feeling that ceiling is sort of variable
But
The premise is largely
Do you have a ceiling Atlanta
Of those available allowances people could trade them
Right and if you want any idea of which one would be better for the environment
Currently most of these companies are lobbying more for a cap-and-trade
Well I think they're putting their money behind cabin
Betrayed over carbon tax
Texting I think
We we all know
I think a lot of the people there
Don't get me wrong. I think a lot of the people who make the most sense that I've heard
From
Seem to indicate a mixture about this
Probably
Best
These are two
Plants
In the tax model the amount of carbon emissions would
Would fluctuate Where is the
The price of emissions would be static
Conversely in the cabin
Country Market
Determine the price businesses would pay
To buy or sell carbon allowances where is the amount of emissions
Would be static
These are intrinsically different but not mutually exclusive and like I said a lot of experts Advocate using both
Comes in some form
Kitchen sink at it
Cap-and-trade
Is the system wherein Alex's Furious carbon exchanges would be more relevant
Since I presume
When he's talking about Obama and Al khor owning the
These carbon equivalent to stock markets
That's where they would make a cut-off
Off the trading of carbon
Ben credits
But Alex never talks about cap-and-trade
He always talks about carbon
Taxes
Which I find weird
Under the plan involving just carve Texas
That wouldn't necessarily involve
Exchanges where people are trading emissions as a commodity
Whenever Alex talks about Al Gore and all of these people owning climatic
You always talked about the Chicago climate Exchange
Like you did in my last class
This is probably because algor it invested in that Exchange
Through his generation investment fund
My son
However
What else fails to mention ever
Is it the Chicago climate exchange stop trading in carbon
Credits in November 2010
It's almost been a decade since the Chicago Exchange that anything to do with anything
Closed without the socket
He has an old piece of information
Namely that Al Gore had invested in an exchange that was engaging
Carbon
Credit Trading
He has no idea that he's just
Regurgitating
Conspiracies that are long
After expiration date
Honestly this kind of thing is embarrassing
It's just muscle memory for him
He doesn't know anything you just as phrases you can whip out like Al Gore owns the climate
Chicago Exchange
10 years
Have you considered
That they might be laundering
Okay so what they do
Is and they're still secretly doing
They just named it something
It's I'm running out I got nothing that's f****** stupid
Right
There is a climate exchange that's based in London
It's called the European climate exchange and it was bought by a large commodity trading business called intercontinentalexchange also
In 2010
I know that none of the people that Alex listed own Intercontinental Exchange
But if any of them invested in it
Cares
It doesn't prove anything
Jay-Z actually on that one
I don't
I don't think so
Is it like this retired
Conspiracy
Is it tired conspiracy with no legs
Alex talks I'm not convinced that he knows the difference between carbon tax plan to cap and trade
I'm further not convinced that he's aware that the Chicago climate exchange stop trading carbon credits of almost 10 years
I strongly suspect that he has no idea what he's talking to
But he has a lot of climate denial catchphrases that he can repeat
But they ultimately mean nothing
Larger picture like I said
Alex's first
Response of the fires in Australia is
Concern for the people affected
Not a call for help
Not feelings
Condolence
It's the launch into how the media is saying
The test
Is climate change related
Which is just a plan to get Al Gore
He's a bad person
Yeah I mean this is bad
He's basically saying that they're false
Fires in or
Are there
What is just lying about it
Climate change when in reality it's normal
His angle on it is that it's
It's just a normal
This is just what happens with controlled Burns
The farmers do just like in California you know sometimes in order to grow redwoods everything's got a burn
Lauren stuff
Like that and that's why it
It's totally fine that we've had so much of California on fire for the path
So Alex is trying to make this argument that it's normal and in service of that he breeds a Wall Street Journal article that I
I don't think you ready
Before the show
Because
Kind of tense
To contradict that this is normal
Kind of angle
Hiding in plain view
Australia's catastrophic
Threatened up in the way people live Wall Street Journal
Igniting too much earlier
Usual start
I'll be Australian
Fire season the Flames of torrent
An area about the size of West Virginia
So it's not
At least 20 people
Crowded cities in Chelsea Hayes in
Stretching firefighters the breaking point
So that's bad
Minerals things
Into the soil to grow again
So then you can see the likes order the theme of his main argument at the beginning of the show just normal
People doing controlled Burns to make sure plentiful Harvest shots
Unfortunately decided to read that Wall Street Journal article without pre-screening any accidentally contradicted
Entire narrative by pointing out that the fire is two months early this year
Generally if
The fires of the result of
Control control
The new respect
Gigantic Fighters 2 months earlier that's why we have early because that's just
Early normal it's just normal but a little bit sooner
So if you're paying attention to Alex and know their words mean things
Explain why farmers are doing these controlled Burns 2 months earlier than they have ever erupt
He knows he can't do that to me just move forward
Pretending that he didn't just read that line that is kid a real problem
The important Point here is that Alex has absolutely no idea what he's talking about
He just feels like this is a result of farmers burning their fields
Improve the soil for the next season
It's just his opinion
Which is not shared by any Source I can find
It discusses the fire
Add to that the fact that he seems
Completely unaware that
These fires are out
Season 4 normal fire pattern
You've every reason to think that this is just a dude talking
Just talkingshit he's reacting
He's reacting in that pre-programmed wave
It's so many climate denial is
Exist now because
At this point we are in it while I'm Jordan This is 20/20
And we are in a situation
You can't avoid it is
All of the denialism that you did
You made this worse
So now you can't do anything but look
Burning fire
That is
F****** world without admitting it and you don't want to do that cuz then
You have to admit that you played a part in
Well the basketball
The reason is falling apart so you keep tonight the best strategy is just kind of need your denial and hand-waving
It seems like that is what Alex
Intended to do
When he started the episode
And I keep implying that it's going to change
Because it is
But he's probably read The Wall Street Journal
Do this this will back me up no big deal
Why you do that I have no idea
You got to read these articles before you talk about amalec you start reading the Bonaire
. that would be nice
So the thing is the climate change is the
The greatest weapon against Society
Right
If if these choirs greatest threat to society but I suppose that could be weaponized please climb
Change people get their way they will be able to destroy us
Quite frankly is Hitler
Had Environmental
Regulation
Could never get bombers over the United States bomber
But if he could have lobbied environmentalist before to tell us we were all guilty and bad. Did not have any
Well he could have dominated it's just like China
Many more times coal power plants that we have they build new ones every week
We shut down under Obama
We have thousands of years of Clean Coal
Wow facts is carbon
Outside
Water
So for a long time I've heard Alex say that all called in the United States
Clean Coal which obviously isn't true but I've just kind of assumed he was just lying
Now I'm becoming convinced
Steve just doesn't know what he's talking
At the end of that clip he says that we have all this Clean Coal and all that comes out of
Power plants is CO2 and water
But that isn't what Clean Coal is
Clean Coal Technologies usually refer to Technologies
Is that don't allow CO2 emission
For instance there's carbon capture technology
Capture all the
Sims 4 burning
Send text to least be stored somewhere
Plus retrofitting existing
Coal power plants to make this technology is
Insanely
Expensive
And if I was his primary concern is the carbon taxes would make operating power plants too expensive
This is not
Play Andy should be enthusiastic
Pre-market dad
Have the government in there I don't think he understands this stuff at all
Cuz the way he's
It's freezing this all the comes out as CO2 and water it's
Well that's the problem
You have accidentally gotten this
Exactly right
Singer that is what clean
Doesn't understand
He doesn't understand
The premises
He doesn't understand the
He's discussing
I mean to be fair there are some promise
Sing ideas by carbon capture but honestly based on
I don't think he has an idea of what those the
Things Are
He's just saying we have this clean call stuff going on and I'll plan submit or CO2 and water
That's
The point
I'm saying
Honestly
He's talking
Especially on this more so than normal
I don't think he knows
What he's talkin to
No I don't think the words that he's saying makes sense
Here's where he gets into trouble
Is that
He accidentally reveals
What everybody knows which
Is that clean call Ezra
It's just not
Turn number things in some of them shows of the cross
Alex
To be like a concept that like you take a little toothbrush
Yeah well that's the way that it
Used as a propaganda tool
Do you think Cole is bad
And thank God we're not using that anymore using clean call witch
The same thing took a bath
Exact
That's what they're trying to
Convince people
Actually I can make things
Involved
I know I know it's not take
In terms of like cleaning some cold rag and make things
A little better but not nearly enough
And somehow the worst way to solve this problem is actually to burn the coal plant
You would think that that would work but
Cruel irony
I just don't think
Galaxy
Severely out of his depth
And the talking
Points that he's using
And the way you present
Big things mismatches even itself so much
Did I just
I hear this
Sad
But actually I
We have a moment here where
We got to give credit where credit's due
Alex jumps to talkin about the evolving situation with Trump and Iran and Iraq
That sort of
Triangular
Situation
And I actually think that Alex has
A pretty good thought
I hate to say it
Do we have
Streamers do we have to celebrate
Never I will never celebrate Alex having a decent
Position
Because
I know that
You'll probably be invalidated tomorrow it's and it's so Elementary I'm not going to applaud him for
Eating a sentence basically is going to play
But credit where credit
The fact that Trump has come out and said that he's threatening sanctions
We will not leave until they pay billions of dollars
The United States invaded Iraq United States overthrew
Earlier
I understand from saying we should have had to pay for all that
Royal
When I see something
Security for supporting Trump
Because he's a nationalist
Croagunk
He's he's he eat he's calling the shots. They loved ones
Poker Face
So f*** the end of that but
At the beginning I think he's
He's on the right track
He's on the right side of the idea that Trump wanted
Extort a rock
Before removing troops
That is bad reason I don't want to give too much promises because I feel like there's a pretty obvious
But I do think
As we are such a Negative show about Alex
I think it's
Pretty important
The point out these very rare occasions
When he has a decent thought
Because I do think
Like treating him as a guy who's always wrong about everything
Welfare League
Isn't really fair and it would turn him into a monster
As opposed to a human who's
Monstrous
I don't have much
Interest in
Like doing the podcast about a caricature of somebody urur rights
That
It is a very
Simple an elemental thoughts that we shouldn't be running an international
Protection brick
It does seem like that the
Simple
We should
Just be going around country to Country
Hey be terrible if your gum
It seems
Almost I mean if you're laughing you're laughing
So what's happened here is that in the aftermath of the assassination of qassamsoleimani Iraqi parliament passed a non-binding
Resolution to expel archery
From the country
They're seeking to cancel the rocks
Request for us
Isis
Validator reason
To continue to be there in the country
This is one of those
Consequences do the sulemani assassination
Seems like
America will face consequences
It seemed like
No one really had a plan for this
No one has any f****** clue what's going on it's kind of amazing so the parliament is just requesting that the government of Iraq do
Which would make one think that it's not going to go anywhere except
For the fact that the resolution was passed after prime minister Adel Abdul Mahdi
Ask Parliament to act
Stupid spell foreign
In response to Trump
Threatened to quote charge them sanctions like they've never seen before ever make a Ronnie NSYNC
Looks somewhat
He also said quote we have very
Extraordinary expenses Air Base
Despair that's their it cost billions of dollars to build we're not leaving unless they pay us back for it
Trump is being a huge a****** and acting in ways that are very unhelpful so it
It's good to see that Alex can see that
The thing is though
Really different than how Trump always act
So it's unclear why this time Alex is hedging
I would bet it has something to do with realizing that supporting this kind of shape
Probably alienate whatever base Alex has left
Those calls he took on Friday when
Not a good
Sampling of his audience
The temperature
And he recognized
If you realize it's like okay this is going
Possibly
Stan
Tend towards
Trouble
And if I support that
I will lose any of the
Ron Paul
Auntie interventionist
Type
That
They were the people who
Theoretically have been around the longest
Yeah that there's a line that Alex
Across
And that's probably starting a war it's really frustrating
Sing to me that that line is the difference
I'm fine with it him terrorizing
Black and brown people
Well here but not in other
You have to really
Bucked up
Little Lion they live on
Well yeah I mean you know just goes
The show like
People are different
People have a different truck
That is not a priority for him it's not
It's a it's a tough realization
I don't know I don't I don't
I guess
I guess they do love war
They just don't like
The fact that there is an
That isn't
It's like
We unequivocally one
Like they never like the people who wants
Who want these kinds of wars or even who don't
Who have this anti-interventionist
It's not because of the war
It's because it's going to cost money and last 20 years like what we're dealing with now
Yeah perhaps what they would prefer is just like we win
So now Iraq is
51st state
You know like it's over
Sure like never have to worry about franchising America
Alright
Bad idea
So Alex
It's back to the climate issues
And Australia nonsense here in a little bit
But he's mostly complaining about
China
In this clip
Complaining
Because
Like I said I really think that a lot of this has to do with watching the Golden Globes
Because his way in for a lot of this stuff
He's complaining about Cate Blanchett share hand and others and their speeches
He's complaining about how Blanchette said
It went with one country faces a climate crisis we all are
Sing that
And his rebuttal to that is what about her China puts a lot of trash into the ocean
That is a very grown-up an adult way of dealing with that
Criticism and I have a little thought on the other side
Another one of these
Real quick
I don't think we ripped
Consult a professional actress
Being a script reader
You idiot
China is responsible for over half the trash in the world
The ocean
Buy those big
Super chefs
Chips
12 Mile Line and dump it
That does affect the whole world
Never hear a word with these environmental groups about telling
Yes you do that's all the time that's what we say all the time all the time
So
I don't know if his
Pixel right cuz I didn't
Bother to look into them I'm not sure if they are I know that pollution is a problem n
And all that
About that quite regularly
And also largely
The problem with Alex
This point here is that his worldview doesn't have a solution
Intuit but globalization does
He's recognizing the interconnectedness of
Actions that are taken by other countries and how they affect
Okay so you're saying you're saying that that's our nation which I love that there is hibernation
By virtue of what they're doing is hurting me personally so how do I tell them
What to do
We'll see
Problem is
I can't do anything
Inside Alex's framework that's
Completely nationalist about
China puta
There's nothing you can do other than I guess start a war with them
You can impose sanctions but I don't know if that's going to work
Trade with them
Globalized
Framework that would be International mechanisms in place where the responsibilities that different countries have to each other
Should be handled
Things that Alex is passionately against
Like the Paris Accord
Even to some extent
Impossible Within
Like obviously not talking about a one-world government necessarily
In terms of international
National bodies
That have enforcement mechanisms in place
You could do that like a China you are polluting in ways that are affecting other
Countries
Whether it would end up being a
Like a financial
Punitive thing
In order to help
The country that's affected
Did cleanup from the message out
I'm kind of
Putative
Measure that's taken to make them stop
International bodies can do that
Nationalist
Countries
Independently acting
Cannot read the only way that one country would be able to do something like that is if a
Where the entire world
What if
We have one let's not do it let's do one nation
Will Jace just the entire world
All nationalist
Now see populism iFixit
The issue 2 is like okay Alex
United States could put pressure on China in order to make them stop
That's not going to work
A group
Nations
Sovereign Nation
Could get together to put pressure on
And you see how that already is stepping down the line
Eventually what is the ideal solution
Group
Nation's sovereign individual Nations working together
It is good
Better is if China was also one of those patterns
You're slowly making more and more sense and I'm not liking
But that's what I should recognize as well obviously
Like it's in his face
Can't even ignore it. Really
Why some of these ideas are very dumb
It is it used to work
But now the world is when the world was big
Nation seems
Like you could
Exist
Solo
Another world is very very small
Is far too much interconnectedness for assault
To ever really
And we know a lot
Absolutely
About the ways that let's say
Air pollution in
Most northern parts of America can affect Canada
It's
The lines of borders
Don't
Stop
Real thing
Can draw it on a map natural forces or not
Beholding to
Then that's just a reality
Do we need to deal with
We want to move forward
Good for nausea
Alex Gordon
So he's complained
Is larger about China
And
What is things that he brings up here is that like
So if you have a motor
Cycle
It is really bad
And polluting
But yeah that's
Bad we have catalytic converters
And now Motors
Cycles have to have those
That is a good regulation
The first we learned that there are some good regulation
Which
Means that he now has a responsibility to differentiate between what is a good regulation
What's a bad one in what makes a good one and what makes bad want to see
Alright I'm straight up lies about you
Play lecture everyone
Don't fly on airplanes that don't have a car
I don't have a motorcycle with bad finger
So getting he's complaining about Golden Globe speeches
Having a dirty tailpipe not having a catalytic converters bad for everybody
Regulation
Brown smoke in the sky
Engineering
But we don't
Want to do that
That'll make us not competitive
I'm trying to just now getting around to saying catalytic converters
No controls on the smokestack
Don't get the river catch on fire
Really
So I sincerely think Alex is completely relying on entirely out of date information
This narrative
I say that because what he saying about China is completely inaccurate to the point where
Kind of feels like he's just making it up
I will say that he's not making up and think about a river catching on fire in China but also have added 24
Incidentally that same gear a dude in North Dakota caused a bit of a stir by posting a video to YouTube reset the water coming
Going out of his faucet on fire
So I guess it's not just a China
And it was only 1969 when the Cuyahoga River in
Set on fire here in the United States
And that's not so long ago in the big picture thing
Oh and also that's a mere 1969b Rouge River in Detroit set on fire
68 the Buffalo River set on fire
This would still be happening regularly in the United States if it weren't for the Environmental Protection
Action Agency
Which Alex is not a fan of
Weirdly
Exact
David sandal hours Columbia University Center for Global energy policy released a 169 page guy
To the Chinese climate Paula
Does Reese
Is reflecting the State of Affairs in 2019 as well as initiatives the Chinese government has undertaken to
Counterclaim
Suffice it to say
They just got catalytic converters is not
The conclusion this paper
One thing that's important to remember is that China is a massive country
Has been
Experiencing a boom
In the past decade
When you talk about one aspect of their energy policy
If crucial to consider other aspects as well so you can get a full pic
Princeton
China has added a lot of coal-fired power
Cassidy in the past years
But it's
The same time they also added quote
43% of the world's new Renewable Power capacity
In 2018
China is also a country that is 45% of the elect
Vehicles in the world
And ninety-nine percent of deal
Bosses in the world
Another aspect of this that has to be taken into account as China's giganta
Population
In 2018 they were the largest
Emitter of
Heat-trapping gases
But if you look at the numbers on a per-capita level they were only emitting
6.6 metric
Per person
As opposed to
18.7 metric tons
For America
What I'm saying is that there's a complex picture
Climate issues
It's not easily captured by single stats are vague Notions
Like Alex Drive
To put Fork
It's probably
Only true the China had previously taken a really dismissive posture towards climate issues but they've been a bit more responsive and recent
Leaving Oz
The plan to achieve
Peak CO2 emissions by 2030
With goals to hit that
Exooter
A goal that most analysts
Think is very achievable
They've committed to
Creating
4.5 billion cubic Acres of reforestation B
20/30 and they actually
Accomplish that goal 11
7 years ahead of schedule
There are the best
Programs in place work
Sing in the right direction
In their Five-Year Plan covering
2016 to 2020 they put in place regulations that work
Require quotes
All new coal plants must
Use super
For critical or ultrasound
Supercritical technology
And the oldest
Technologies were to be retired
Bye 2017
90 of their 100 largest coal-burning power plant
Ultra super critic
They launched
Carbon trading program
An eight cities and provinces
Plans to implement it nationally in the near future
That is quite literally China
Placing a price on emitting carbon
Which Alex is claiming they refuse to do because they don't want to be competitive
Are they only uncompetitive
Additionally they put in place to build
Standards to make residential and public buildings more energy-efficient
And quote as of September 26th
Steve roughly 4,500 building
China
Did receive Green Building label
I could go on and on about this stuff but I think the point is pretty
It's just not fair to say the China is not doing anything about climate issues
The primary conclusion of this report is literally quote
The Chinese government
What is taking significant steps to address climate
There are negatives in the next to like their uses
Synthetic natural gases which is not good
But the general Trend seems to be in a positive direction
China news
They were countries it's particularly vulnerable to the effects of climate change
From their long history of severe drought
To all the more reason
Phenomenon of horrible air pollution
Nothing but Alex is saying at all depict reality
But I think it might to pick reality
A little bit
Closer to
The truth
The last time he actually cared about doing his job early instead
Maybe even longer
I think this is all just remnants of the time when he actually cared to look into things
Members this stuff
And hasn't ever
Check the updated
Same thing with Al Gore in the Chicago climate Exchange
He's just never checked into
Is this
Still truth yeah I know I was yelling about it
In 2007
It does
It just seemed like maybe one of the side effects of
Taking too many of his supplements
Is the inability to turn short-term memories into long-term
You know
Long-term memories are Paramount
What I mean is he can't replace new long-term memories you know he's just a memory disappear
Disagree because I don't think he has a short-term memory is no longer being true
Doesn't care
You checked the Box about China doesn't care about climate change
He doesn't even care to
To check so there is no short-term memory
There's no
There's no updating at all
Mm2 B2B
Totally said none of this is like
Chinese government is doing everything right of course
Absolutely issue
Let's just say the Chinese government is doing everything
I think you're
I think you're in trouble
You in the climb
I take is that what I was saying is not true
There is a complicated in larger picture
Sure to Chinese climate policy
Alex
Refuses to engage with
Because I think it would show that maybe they are
At least indicating the stronger things than
Trumpet
Absolutely
Anthony's day they tend to invalidate his entire narrative about trying to just wanted to shut down
And refused
To do these things
Domestically and internally
Because it would make the monkey
Competitive
Yeah there is something of a
Benefit to having a nationalized
Enacted
With
I mean not
It's not like unilaterally but
Very aggressive
Sibley and the parties pressure
Sure can make it happen
Quicker than
If there's I need to have a year of debate on this in my Batman.
Preferably one of the things that that system is capable
Will doing that
Simply Mount your comment is descriptive less than
Prescriptive
Yeah cuz I think was really interesting about reading that climate report from the Columbia
Energy policy
Elsie Center was
They told me that they highlighted a bit is
How what are the things
The China does the
Really affect
Is that they set variable goals for the various provinces
Insidious
Depending on what is achievable within those
So they make this forward progress
Within the dissection sectors of the country
That's progress
Appropriate
Apparently
It seems
Like that is a very effective
Approach that they've
I mean it tastes similar to I don't know if you ever had to sell cars but one of the things that
They do with the bunch of salesman is
If you're a really good salesman they'll be like your goal for this month is sell 12 cars
Have your bad when they're like your goal is to sell for cars
Just because
That what you're setting
Achievable goals for yourself which makes you more motivated to do so
One of the principles of productivity
And if everybody's trying to get 12 I don't know there's some sort of Bible verse
You have to
Actionable items that are itchy
Feasible
Probably going to
To dismiss them as like All That Pie in the Sky
Exactly
So I just think that
You know Alex's
In the same way that I think it's important
To give props
The Alex when he says something like Trump
Is trying to extort a rock
This is really bad
I think that's important
Because it deals with Alex
He is as opposed to
Do a cartoonish sketch China just got catalytic
Converters
That's him treating his enemy as a Cartoonist
And you see how ineffective and stupid
But that is
He's very dumb
You just hates China
He's turns them into
A new Big Bang
So Alucard
As we started the show Alex was saying that he's live in Australia
Take calls
From Australia
Does he know there's a
The time difference
He does only brings up repeated
Used to be doing the night shift
Do annihilate later radio heat always be called
Australia
Sure sure he would I leave that aside
I don't care
Nick kyrgios has got some
Tasty Asia
It's not coming
Don't doesn't
Okay so
He's at he decides he's going to take some calls
Two calls from Australia
And they're both
Great
Yes okay
So here he is
Here's where the narrative starts
Your phone calls right now from Australia
Calling in
But these record fires Witcher
Been man-made
Happening in
Where what
Crazy people
Shmoney
So now Alex's angle on this is at the fires in Australia arson
I can't stress this enough
Up to this point in the show you saying it's a completely natural thing we're farmers do controlled burn
This indicates to me that I was talking about when he started
The show so he's planning to just hand
Big deal but when he saw a headline that indicated baby there was some arson
He decided
I can walk with your way
That's my way there are some people who have been arrested
For setting fires driver what's going on in Australia
A large part of the push
For the narratives itself is all around an online conspiracy theory that
Climate extremist reciting
The fire is a false flag climate change is real
Which I expect will be Alex
This position eventually work
Stoneware still around will you be on that right now
Baby
Maybe I don't think so no care
He's got other issues
Even if he wasn't going to prison. Other issues
IAAI think that Alex has seen some sort of the headline and now he decides to make a break in his coverage and go
This way
And so now it's
Conspiracy
Hey starts rambling
About stuff
That just makes no sense
California
Say Ruel
Takeout mountain lions eat people
This is the rewilding projects so how bad is it going to get in
Do you know anything about mad lions eating people
No
It's a serious problem
16 years since anyone has been killed by a mountain lion in California
In fact
Only two people have been killed by mountain lions in the United States in the last 12 years
A 55 year old woman and a national forest in Oregon
Andy thirty-two-year-old woman in
The foothills of North Bend wash
So what you're saying
Is that mountain lions are hunting women in the Pacific
Ignore
I guess I'll just
Good because you can't kill mountain lions now they're eating people all over the place
Alex is weird obsession with the idea that animals are eating people in California
He's brought it up about like what was the other animal
I guess he just knows the California is a completely foreign land to all his listeners
So it doesn't matter how real anything he says about the state is
Lookout don't go to California get eaten by a mountain lion
I did not realize that predatory cat
Very serious very serious brows
I just should I be worried forget about a certain Chicago should I be worried
Forget about a rock
Text
Another movie movie was predicted program
Herbalife talking to you so. One day mountain lion guard hey how's it going Rum Tum Tugger
Text
You're eating
Battle happen
I'm pretty sure Judi Dench killed at least four people and making them
Undoubtedly
There a lot of reasons my fire breaks or not
Particularly, California
But it's not so much
But the state won't let you do that
Because they wouldn't
California's geography is pretty mountainous so finding
The right place
To make the brakes of
Be pretty difficult
But more importantly one of the primary characteristics of California fires is that they are wind-driven
The wind spreads
The fire to such a great extent the firebreaks
Really have the desired effect
Stopping the fires progression
The firewood
Just jump over
The campfire is actually a prime example of this
Have brakes in place but it didn't matter
The fire cross the brakes
Super easy
Paradise California did exactly what Alex's suggested
They spent millions of dollars to remove underbrush and make fire breaks
100ft wide
A from the firework easily carried across that Gap and the town was basically to
Destroyed
Every one of the 10 most
Destructive California fires
I've been driven by the wind
Which is not something that Alex's solution helps with
For that all
So once again we find out stalking
Complete
Having no idea of the topic that he pretends to be annexed
But will make fire breaks
They go up in
Into the sky
Very tall
What is great again start
There is no State ruled Advance fire breaks in fact Cal Fire director Tom Porter till the LA times recently
We continue to do that
They helped us get people out of the way
They serve some purpose to slow down a fire but it
It's not really a full preventive strategy
When wind is a factor
I was just making s*** up about firebreaks a mountain lion
It's at the point where I don't even know why he does
Yeah like I don't know what the
The point is
He's not helping old made of
Nobody even like his
Denying climate change is like
Yeah I really needed that mountain lion B there
You could have just ignored I think he just thinks it makes it more interesting
Yeah I get the sense that he just
A little a little inflammatory like 10 days a week
Mountain lions over there and everybody's and I think a large piece of it too is
The other ring of caliph
It seemed like some kind of a cake do you got the
Governor out there that Democratic globalist I know he doesn't care about people he wants these fires that happened
They're putting
Things in place to make mountain lions eat
You know it's just that sort of
Nonsensical
Over like
Cartoonish version of time
Is the only time to vases
Is going to come up at 8
Alex's take on this is really funny
Happened
The Golden Globes
Wisdom in Canadian
Debatable coming out
Housing Hollywood has a bunch of
Pedophiles
That would have been really big news I feel like that would have been really big new Maiden
Seeing Joker
Ricky Gervais
I love it
I love it oh man
Cowboy
I fell it takes Epstein
Good2Go in my good books
What a phenomenal job amazing happened at the
The Golden Globes
Tonight
Focally annoying atheists in the world made of
Epic joke about episode
I dunno what amazing previously like the figureheads in the big figures in the air
GPS community
Vampire
Hey brother man Alex make some f****** sense for 1 seconds
Just some some consistent
Some continuity from idea to an idea
I need something
It's not important
So Alex
It goes to this verse
Caller from Australia
I just turned 41 in the I'm living in
But I've never seen anything like
Before and
Deliberately
Something
You know I randomly paper roll here.
Nothing like these
I have been writing articles.
Eastern Shelf
Coming from Brisbane down to Melbourne
They are actually planning on a high-speed rail
My alarm down there and agenda 2030
Agenda 21
A long day
So I have read a couple of theories at
California
So this is a popular conspiracy theories
It's flying around. That's the updating of Agenda 21
Right there's nothing to back this up other than that Australia has talked about building High-Speed Rail line
Let's just released
Alex get the caller from Australia and the main things he brings to the table is that she read something on a dumb blog
This is not good
Is bringing the heat today
Isn't good
So Alex talked to her a little bit
It's mostly more of this
And I still
Really bad
About how this call I don't want them
This person too much
Cuz she gets pretty emotional
But I think if you take the
Content of what
She saying
This is not somebody that you should take as a good source of in
O'Reilly's in Berkeley
Coup d'etat
Australia's New World City
Australia
Doesn't mean
It doesn't
You know what I mean
Batman
This is true
Doing that
Melbourne to Brisbane
Thank you for calling and waiting to hear the emotion your voice Rachel please call back again God bless you and thanks for staying up lesoto show
Airline you're up next they wasn't what she said it's what I was what people are already saying
So
She starts crying there at the end of the call but what she's putting forth is that
Being set on purpose in order for the New World Order
Create a
High-Speed Rail Line throughout the country
And
It's all based on
Maybe
A slicker
A promotional campaign
Guess you could say it now World City
You could say that can't say something like that without it meaning something
We have thousand
Years of human history of
People saying eggs
Exactly that the new world
Did you could you could say that it's a new world order thing
Or you could also
Take the words a little different
Currently like you consider things like London New York those are World City
Those are cities that are part of the their Metropolitan they're they're part of the Worlds
Community as opposed to
The lesser extent that a small town
So Wong Kong is a world City
Right you can say that this is a new
World City
You could look at it that has the promotional campaign being about
We're going to build up Brisbane to the point where
It is
Relevant on the global scale
Yeah you could see it that way instead
She takes it as a cube that novices the globalist
Coming in and taking over Brisbane
And it's just like
I just feel very sad
For her because
Clearly Effexor this emotionally
But I do feel like
What she's bringing to the table is irresponsible the
Conjecture of
The Arts
All this is arson
And it's all a conspiracy in order to build this route
But
Alex is going out to break
And as soon as he comes back from break
Those details are now his narrative
Is mounting that the mega fires in Australia
Orchestrated by multinational forces to clear out she corridors
Future development and four light rail going in that's being financed by the comment
Chinese
So he just has this caller who's called in with some
Speculation that she's giving him secondhand from weird conspiracy blogs
I found a post on Reddit as part of this
This is not good
No big deal
Natural thing
Now the Chinese
Evidence is mounting
Now the Chinese an International Group
Fires on purpose
I don't want to make fun of
She's she's dealing with a mess
Tragedy
And unfortunately
In that
Reaction to itzy
He's just
Didn't like
Push towards this
Is awful information
And so
How to how to like balance
An actual tragedy
With what your imaginary reasons
And then tube
Call Alex
Is
So
It's compounding the tragic
All you're really doing is ensuring that nothing will be done to help
Word solver
In the future
Locked up
Alex is making this stuff up evidence is mounting
That's the fastest I think I've ever seen that Fox News
Tucker Carlson says something stupid and then the next morning
Some people are saying that the evidence
Right but there's other evidence
Is there
With all the viewers out the
It's not like I'm just saying this is my opinion
There's a big story up on Drudge Report.
Cam from Summit. Net
Deliberately starting the brush fires it's a big article
Got the police
Got the newscast
Sting reporting on the fact
That is almost all deliberate arson
I just people burning with left their crops to put
Done
Watch it unfold
That was
What hour will
MS
That's a contradiction of how you started
Don't deal with that at all
But look the article that Alex is talking about on Drudge
Is on Summit. News it was written by Paul Joseph Watson
This is kind of the same thing as Alex just reporting on his own coverage
Which would normally be like alright let's
Dismiss this out of hand
But I wanted to check in on the article to get a sense of the information PJ dubs
Is bringing to the table
Firstly
The headline of that article or the article that's up on some of that Australian police say arsonist and lightning
To blame for bushfires not climbing
How to change
Then
The sub-headline is quote
Sit down global warming alarmists
This is a little weird
First of all because of the tone
Is this supposed to be reporting
Or is it a dishy block Paul slams people
Because it definitely sounds like the ladder
He's trying to step into that because I guess
The other issue is that even if some of the fires might have been set by arson
And others were started by lightning
That in no way invalidates the argument the climate proponents
That only refutes the strawman argument that Alex and Paul Joseph Watson are using to attack climate change advocate
Play me the people are saying the climate-change literally started
The fires
It's really easy to win an argument when you just pretend you're appointed to saying something they're not
Yes how exactly would claw
Climate change startup
Matches do they think
Climate change
It like it's the Earth gets
Hotter than some things are just so hot they burn
I don't know because they're not clear about what
People are saying just seem like they're being
A fleabag about
So I'm going to look at this article and
And I don't believe that it proves the point that it's making
But I want to clarify
Before I
Get into this
Even if
Every single fire was started by arson
That doesn't refute the climate change Ark
It really does
This is not really even engaging with that level of things
This is just trying to see what Paul is up
In the article Paul rights quote
Police are now working on the premise
Arson is to blame for a bunch of the devastation caused
Does this brush Bushfire season
Report 7 News
This is a reference to a tweet
7News posted on January 3rd along with
The video news
The news report includes footage from police representative but he doesn't say anything about the scale of arson
In fact in the video the reporter who's doing the peace
He talks about the
Suspicions of arsenic
And you talk about how it turns out it was actually like
It's not that far
The only proof here is something that's in the tweet
Itself
And I can't really find
Fancy asian of that quote
Or anything past that
So I decided to check out 7 News
Twitter account
And there's plenty of coverage of
The fire is on
Videos post
The Press
Princess being held by police and fire officials
And wouldn't you know it
None of them are about how this is mostly arson
Tweets about a couple fires being considered
Suspicious but nothing on the scale of what Alex has put in for
There's also a whole lot of coverage about how two people were struck by lightning on the same
Someday though
We're considering light
Get started
Pates
The most arson you can have
Have right if you get struck by lightning and
Get lit on fire and then
Trip and start a massive
Bushfire
There's a lot of coverage
This to people being struck by lightning
It looked at odds are slim that guy looking at a double rainbow got a whole day of newspapers so
Now again I want to be clear
Paul's anti climate change argument is not made by showing of some fires were started by arson
That doesn't matter to the larger point at all because the real Point people are making is just a climate change affect
Persevere
That being said
Article to see if you was making a good argument against even the strawman
No
Alex exciting is number of almost 200 people arrested for arson but that's not even in this article that Paul wrote
Who wrote another one
Or maybe he
He could have written the second article at the topic
I'm not sure but I decided to try and track that down
This comes from right-wing blogs like zerohedge and post-millennial recovering an article in the
Which purports that since the beginning of November 183 people
Have been
Charged or cautioned for Bushfire related offense
However the article also says that only 24 have actually been arrested
Biddeford deliberately set
Setting fires
The rest of them were probably given a ticket for flicking a cigarette butt in a high fire hazard
Area
Which courses
Not good but not the same
An article in MSN seems to indicate
The 47 of these people at work
Exactly that situation to starting a cigarette or match
Inappropriately
And 53 of them were people cited for not following
Complete fire ban
So they might have been making a campfire or something like that
These numbers Alex's you are using
Completely misleading
You're meant to make it seem like they're tons and tons of arsonist out there and that's all
What's going on
That's not the case
This post millennial article on the subject
Concludes quote
That's 183 people who have been arrested for arson results
Catastrophic bushfires displacement property lost
People and animals
You can't you can't say
It's at very least in a dreadful overslept
Occasion
Some of these people who are arrested
Starting fires
They might be completely unrelated to
The bushfires
Princeton
Two separate arson
Took place on January 4th
5th in Elizabeth North
One on each side of a duplex
These work just completely old-fashioned arson
One day was once the next day it was Abby other
I don't know
They did arrest the guy who was holed up on a roof
So in that neighborhood so
Pretty good sensitivity
You might like that has nothing to do with the larger tires
At least one of these people whose arrested was a 36-year old man who set a fire in
Johnsonville which was
Contains that's not really related
It's the larger situation
Two teens were arrested for arson on January 5th because they were trying to break into a shed
They were trying to rob
Which has nothing to do with
There was another case in Melbourne
Of a guy who's
Arrested for arson
But that was part of a fact
He was trying to
Maybe cause a distraction in order to
One of them was a 50
Before your old man who was using
Power Tools in Barstow
Parkwood cause Sparks
It's edifier Paul would know that if he consulted
Is primary source 7 News who covered the topic
7 news also reported on a 79 year old man who was arrested
Super setting fires who's believe
To have dementia
The point here is we don't know the
Stances of the 24 people who arrest
Open for delivery
Play setting fires
And this goes back to November
Not necessarily related to the situation
And it would be irresponsible to jump
Too many conclusion
Irresponsible
Tantamount to
A massive scapegoating campaign that could seriously get somebody killed
More than you know
Look if somebody if they put a like if we're talking about the Boston bombings
Situation where they just put a random person
Picture up in there like
This is prob
Probably the person did it
Imagine if it was your entire fun
Continent was on fire
There are probably some indication
They're probably at least some people who are deliberately setting fires and are pretty f***** up
Do they call them firebugs
It does seem like
There are some people who are just
Oriented that way
Setting fires true
I am also some of the people might be trying to create independent
Blackburn's where they
Think that what they're doing
Helpful
But that's a possibility
I don't know if that's
The case might be making that up
Right now Alex doesn't know either
He has no information to go on but he's relying on
Misrepresented headlines to craft a narrative about the
Is tragedy
Biddies
All these people are just
And you're totally right to is really good
Matt is that scapegoating LMAO
Because there are people who are getting arrested
Stood for this
And from the articles that I've seen
Wisely I believe
A lot of the identities are not God
Because you could imagine how that could get like so incredibly odd control
Guy who said a fire for whatever he did Johnsonville that contain
Like you imagined
And now it's
Yeah no it could be incredibly
Yeah cuz you
Look I just lost
1.2 million dollars in property
Yesterday
So guess what this guy's got arson
In-N-Out
And the other issue
It would be dangerous
Like scapegoat
Stop is it according to the BBC there between 52 and
T4000
Bushfires in Australia every year
13% of those are deliberately
Lisset
And half of those that are deliberately sat are set by people who are under
Which make some
Playing with fire
And if
Some of the
The instances of
The people who are arrested
Fire-related offenses are
Like 50
Teen
That you could call you Rosa Mendes consequences in their life
I mean you obviously got to teach him not to do that
I don't want to create a Frankenstein's monster situation where the town is
Please, Lady a lady tweeted a bad joke about Africa and lost her entire life imagine if
Somebody just decided that you caused a Bushfire
Destroyed
Oh man-seok to some of this up into
Conclude
Some instances of arson
Is relevant to the actual gigantic fires that are going on is unclear at this point
Enter reported as such as
Irresponsible
Picture whether or not a fire was started by arson is irrelevant
The issues The climate-change Advocate
It's a brand new but
I decided to engage with this a little bit
And it seems like something Alex's obsessed
It appears
Do you know like I said there aren't some fires are intentionally set
But Oz
Filling the gaps here with his fantasy
That's bad
Yeah
That's real bad
That's so annoying
That's so annoying that whole like
Are you guys thinking
It's climate change that's doing
And
It's at
It's just like if let's say if Alex was a witch
Right and we had to burn
I don't want to but the Lord says that it he would agree
That's
Bad
That would be 10
Imagine if that was all if that witch burning was also surrounded by everybody that you've ever loved who is
Split on fire as well and then surrounding that was every building
And they were all covered in gas
That's the climate change
It doesn't matter if you like them on
So
Leaving outside he's a witch
The interesting thing is that like they don't crystallize what the argument there were shooting is that climate change
People are putting forth and so this argument that I gave those people setting fires
It doesn't do anything.
To the climate change argue
But it does
Contradict
Alex is
Prior
The only thing that's
Be refuted is things that Alex is already said
So that's cool
Get to know that
You can really
You synthesize new information
And at it as a good job
And now he complains more about
Golden Globes
Caroline then I'll get those clips I mention
Phoenix
Insufferably obnoxious with his
Fake autistic Accu does everywhere
What
He gets up there and talks about donating
Flying on private jets all the time
You really believe that bad
Then
Dockside
California dumps the most deadly fluoride the water
10:00 weather chemicals in it
Seattle waiver
With one billionth of what's in the water
So you out of existence
The Golden Globes now they're not for you not for me I don't want
So as for props
65 Oz
Backing up the thing or California has a waiver to put fluoride in the water
65 requires that people provide warnings for the present
Certain chemicals and toxins in the product
They sell it wouldn't need a waiver for fluoride because it's
It's not on the list of ingredients that require a warning even if that was relevant
Alex's
Making that up
The issue here is that California has far more rigorous standards for supplements
It's been a lot of the rest of the
It also has by far the largest population
If Alex doesn't meet their standards with his product
He misses out on approximately 39 billion
Potential customer
But it also cost him a bunch more to produces down pills
If it weren't for California prop 65 his profit margins would be
Be a lot higher
Because you can just make trash and sell it and that's always complaining about
Upset about
Saveriano
I have to have
So much less light in my products
Because of California's prop 65 and it makes me really pissed off
Is insufferable as actors and celebrities to be for the most part
I wish more conservative knew that the main reason they are
Their fervor to hate
California's drugged-up
Because rich people don't make as much money
It is a big part of it
So now we learn more about Australia
In this next clip
And received
The crystallization of this
Narrative
Has happened
Alex is now
Report 100-percent reporting
And he said it wasn't his opinion
The chai, government and China's right there
Really
China runs Australia
Right over there in the middle of it as a place with babe so
Cars are very strategic they are arson
So I'm sure what's the Golden Globes last night in a regular globe
He was like holyshit Australia's really close to China
Also ensure Queen Elizabeth is going to be upset to hear the news
The China runs
Clip is important because Alex is asserting that these fires are arson and we're done strategically as up back
This is not a person put in for that opinion
He's reporting
And he has no reason to do that
An hour earlier you saying is just natural its
What happens if armor sets
The globalist want
Do you know they want to tell you
In Spanish lesson an hour on air
He's completely changed his tune and now he's
Pretending start the show saying it was no big deal
Now this is a gigantic
It's the biggest but the Chinese government is paying arsonist set fires to clear the area and
Prepare for High-Speed Rail lines in
Agenda 2030 whatever
It's so easy it is for Alex
Convince himself of something
The thing
But I want to highlight
Is that this is not a product of his stupidity
This is striking while the iron is
This is crap
Alex sees an opportunity
There's a massively traumatic world of
Getting a lot of attention
Have you seen it get a lot of play in the Golden Globes
Set the perfect place
For him to plant his flag
That's what connects his initial position with his new one
They're both
Contrarian
To the point to the rest of the world
Position
Annie's
Pushing back
They're meant to be opt
Subversive
A that some kind of elevated understanding of what's going on in the rest of the world
That no one else has access
When the show began Alex didn't have a good angle on the conspiracy
That's because he's not that creative
He's still pretty much every idea he's ever had from
Is 911 prediction
Hillary for prison bumper
Stickers to the catch phrase about the answered 1984
Steals everything
Alex knaub
Create
You can only absorb
So the best you could do at the beginning of the show was doobie a contrarian
Is that you don't understand how controlled Burns work
You getting all hysterical about climate
He said he knows that this will just lead to better crop
You got the call from a Nutty Australian lady
Anyway she reads blogs he doesn't even have time to read anymore
So she repeats the popular
Conspiracy lying to me recognizes
That's probably got more juice in it
That is condescending
That's a good stuff
This is how it sounds to me
I might be wrong
For sure is that Alex isn't based
This narrative on anything
He's making a strategic decision based on what he thinks
To make him more interesting
And probably lead to a better
Financial
For attention
Or anytime there's
Hot button issues
Staking some sort of a
Proclaim
Latest counter to what everyone else believes
Is a Wade
Trion filter
That's all this
That you see how it how
Bill
His ability to go from
Like listening to her
Thinking man I wish I
I thought of that
2 an hour later being like man I'm so glad I thought of
I'm so glad
I'm so glad that I am
So well-trained and no Global stir up to that I was able to deduce
I thought of it
So Alex is now securely in that position
Carbon taxes to fix all this
All the fires arson
And they busted a bunch of people
Waiting till it dries time of the year
Setting the fire
Burning up all these corridors
Where the Chinese are putting in light rail
So now you can see how the narrative is evolve
Yep where is it the beginning of the show
It's no big deal
Biggest fire ever
And that changes because now he has an angle on it
Depended on the globalist
It's no big deal to him at sapphires or big until he has an angle
Now he's found a way to blame his enemies
Crucial that the event
Be as big as possible
You can't do bigger than biggest ever
Now we sing the
The police say that all the fires are arson which is not true
And they busted people in the act
Which is at least not accurate in the way Alex
He has his motive
Thanks that color
The Chinese
He's got a conspiracy that he gets
CL about
It doesn't happen too often but this is a really clear-cut case of Alex improvising
Conspiracy
This feels really similar to the Boston Bomber
Stuff where you can almost see the gears moving
His head is honestly sick
Affectionate
It is unfair how about a symmetrical
Infowar is
You know like we have all the info
He's like a high counter you with none
Somehow I'm
Still winning
F****** unfit
Fair
And then you get them under oath
Sunnyside shows
I just talked about what a thing
Another caller from Australia is
20/30 globalist
Florida
I we don't need to listen to what time today because it's
Just heard of them began during
Conspiracy basically
I want to play this
Sklep because
I think
This is
Sort of people say
Stuff like this
And just like you shouldn't be listening
Two people also believe these things
Really don't you think
Coming from
Mobile
Infowars.com Carolina thank you so much
U-Haul
Somebody who's talking about this Chinese globalist
Conspiracy for Light Rail and all this stuff
Lazarbeam
You kind of have to be like okay I should take both of those things as being equally
Play Store
I got to say if you're going to go around with the laser beam stuff
I'm going to treat your thoughts about the light rail
Conspiracy with the exact same to stain
Dismissive
I love that
Rye love and loving Australian person downplaying what should be
The single most terrifying thing that you can describe
Like if what you say is
She believes what
You saying is true
She thinks somebody use laser beams to set a fire
Where are the laser beams coming
Is it UFO
I heard that I was like
I feel like Alex has got to be disappointed but going into brake like he's got his
I got lazarbeam
I did not cut that
Call us sooner
Jesus what am I doing
Anyways
He's basically done with the Australia portion
The shower now
And
He gets back to talking about A-Rod
Sharan
You know on the on the next day on Friday
You got to get Steve pieczenik in there cuz he's got
Got to be done
I'm still not over that by the way
What
That the Holocaust didn't happen
I feel really guilty
Guilty about like
Not knowing I had no reason to know that
Believe
Besides show for quite a while
These sorts of Revelations about it make me feel
Pretty
Mixed
About 23
I feel like if we found out that to someone else
That
You know we know I guess like
She has
Definitely some 80's metal cleaning
But I haven't heard her go that far
Platform people who deny
For sure
In this entire Community I just assumed that a matter of anti-Semitism until
How do we Now operate from a position
Of not just assuming
Eventually these people are going to
The Nighthawks
How do we get
The benefit of the doubt for a little while
Eventually
Not right
That's
You just don't know how many people deny the Holocaust until York
Confronted with
Rustic relative acquaintances
Devon on Friday
Powder to get to
Another geopolitical expert
A for a while but now he's coming back into the pool
And that is Joel skousen
So Alex
Introduces
Joel
Here's somebody who definitely believes the Holocaust happen and wide-ranging knowledge
Tom
He's the editor of worldfree4u.com to X1
Shut up for Marine Corps officer and Naval aviator
Globbles from 60 70 years
I wish we wouldn't even
Bachata
So skousen zone for an interview and I don't have any clips of it cuz f*** that dude
Exceedingly boring
It's just that he comes on and says that every single thing is a false flag that's like all he does
He's on to tell Alex that traps f***** up
And fell for a globalist trick by killing soleimani
It appears that he thinks that this was a deep State setup
Now Trump is being a real dick on Twitter and making things worse
It's dumb interview but Alex's pretty receptive to skousen
Anti-trump message
Particularly given the circumstances where I was realizing
Provoke Irani rock kind of
With his threat
They pay us
If there's a recipe for a Dismount from trump it feels like this could be a passport
Who is untainted from the time that I was spent with
Cuz he had credit
And he still has a good rapport with Alex
Respect
Between them hasn't been to me
Is it a good person to latch Your Wagon to now right now
Plus
Joel skousen is anti-communist of royalty
Cuz he is W Cleon skousen to nephew
If I were Alex
I would make a move
Now
Get on board you have Joel skousen
You might got to get rid of Steve that going back to that wild night of 1000 is still there
Get back to your anti-communist bulshit
With this like
This is a rock
You can build on
If you want to save whatever you can
The rest of its
Just going to be destroyed
Like it's the right the rest of this
Is going to fall apart
Just naturally
It's doing it it's
That you have built your house on
So I hate to give advice
Alex could work
Leaving Trump with skousen
Is your Best Buy
Mayhaw
Leaving the planet with
Klingon skousen
Would probably be the better way you're not going to know
Propelled heart
I stab at the IRS
That's what else you got
We doing this
How to speak Klingon
So I lied I actually do have one clip
And at its them talking about qanon
Skousen
Blossom Porton
Alex
In this clip
Actually
Confirmed the theory that we've had for a long
Nothing
True
This is a pure disinformation expert
Supporters
Because you're definitely a delusional issue
Sucking up show many good people
So Alex is literally saying that his plan was to
To co-opt and then use it as a vehicle to
Pretend que said certain things should you be saying this out loud
I'm inside.
That would you keep up in the brain
I was planning to defraud people
You don't let that one out
That's what we've been through
Attempt exactly that
Like this
Alex is basically saying
I had a grand plan to use this very successful in order to manipulate my audio
And it didn't work
Why would you say that I have no idea
Because it's a because book
I think that's the real I think that's what we should take away from this
Is it this point nobody's
Alex
In Subway able to rationalize this it's the greater good I would be
Be using pure
To give good messages
And that's just delusion
Using it to sell your pills
He's literally saying I was going
To defraud I was going to lie to everybody
That was my
And if I had done that Joel
I wouldn't be telling you about
Kind of hoped
To take over Cuba
Now
What's interest
Think about this is if you look at the history it's
Absolutely
Very likely that he did make serious gestures to that
Zach is one of them is a fake intelligence guy and then the other one is Jerome corsi was
He started to become a big
You guy
Really started
To decode Q Clues
He was going to write a book
About
Probably only ended because Q started
Started turning on Coursey
I think Zach and Coursey were both attempts
2 coop
That stinks
And this is exactly what Alex's pattern throughout his career is
The Tea Party
Qanon Trump
These are the things that he recognizes potential in
And gets on board with in order to a
Absorb them
Or Co-op them in
To his revenues
That's the same way that I was talking about earlier
Alex can't create he could only absorb
This is the attack
To do that Feud meaning that that was
Who's playing
That's f***** up yeah yeah
He's saying that he's like one of those cleaner fish
For a shark
That's all they can do is
Egypt's where it swims around and cleans off the Sharks back
I was thinking more than
I thought
So
Alex while talking
Skousen
Do you know the ideas that Trump got set up by the Deep state in order to do this
Alex starts to sort of manufacture excuses
Completely make stuff up
About what Trump was going
Through in order to sort
Trying to rationalize his the decision-making so he doesn't
Was
What's what's what's hurting level Trump's real numbers were way up and I agree
So it looks like I'm you know I've been indicted
Who wants to change the subject and I and I
You guys just say
Donald Trump
Blamed
And that's what I'm predicting so surprising Iraq he believes
Stop
Play activate Sleeper Cell
When those things happened they didn't like you know they're helping Engineers old thing back
Alex is making all that up wow that is a fantasy of his
That is because
He still needs
To make the globalist
The bad guy even if
He is recognized in the Trump trying to extort a rock
Is.
Okay
So I think that what he's doing
He's trying to
Judge
Trump's actions
By ascribing them
To the global
Now and the best he can do is that like Trump is gullible
You got tricked
Because he was so up
What about the impeachment his numbers were going down
And so he
Political assassination
Shouldn't be
Okay but tell how you was put in that position it's
There is look if the Democrats hadn't impeached
Then he wouldn't have assassinated that guy
Clearly that means it's
The Democrats fault it's cockamamie nonsense I mean the best
Best strategy I guess he feels that he has at this point is to
To say that Trump is incredibly weak
It is well
Attention
Potentially International crimes
In order to
Distract from an impeachment
Exactly what
Galesburg
When all the time I don't know if this is nonsensical
If it's leading to him
Leaving it makes sense
If not if you stand on board with Trump
And
Using these
Sorts of
Thin
F****** rhetoric
In order to justify it I don't know
I was listening to a little bit of the show.
Today Show today
And cuz I want to get a sense of like
What's going on
I just turned it on for a little bit he's screaming about how my
Mike Pompeo
F*** Pompeo I know that in order to do this show we both kinda
Tacitly agreed that
A razor should stay outside while we record
Right right but this one
Could not be
Look at all the made-up nonsense that he
He tries to
Blast into one
Sedation when it's just very simple
He's a
F****** evil dude
It's you're so simple
Exactly what we've told you he was he's a con man who has
Psychopathy was willing to commit war crimes
Like he said he wanted to do during the campaign he did say that about
I think that's probably too and then also just be
Not like
Singular in the folks
Like you also obviously has
Terrible
Reality is like
Yes this is
Take all that aside
He still responds
Before this decision
The Democrats impeached
Even if the globalists quote-unquote
Tricked him into doing
Still his
Responsibility
President gets
Tricked it doesn't count
Don't you remember that was Nixon's to
The buck stops
Over there
The buck stops with the Democrats no matter f***
Right so Alex is another gas
Kris tanto paronto
One of the survivors of Benghazi
I think he's just on to promote his new podcast
I don't know what is going on this is
I'll be looking for guests this is a weird interview
Call like I said he's one of the survivors of Benghazi
The interview is not very interesting to me outside of
Contos main point
Which seems to be that he's not happy that people were calling the situation
Timothy Rockey Embassy
Another Benghazi
He seems to take that personally which I think is fair play I have no problem with that ankle
Because Alex was saying at the globalist
So he's kind of guilty of exactly the
Tonto is taken
Issue it but for me this is a little bit of a
Who cares situation
All due respect to Tonto Forest Service
And I definitely see where he's coming from your being the Benghazi Survivor you wouldn't want your experience to
Be used as a political
Also Alex tries to get Tanto to back him up that it's f***** up
The Trump is going to pay for
For the base for withdrawal
What's that
He sees he says he's seen us leave bases before and he's like
That's a lot of money we're leaving behind
It's the little one come
Alright Alex is big hero guy that's on the show is
Invalidating his
Lying with Trump
Downtown
Stupid and pointless
Alex does say one thing
It's pretty funny
Tanto paronto is our gas
Thinking but again that's down for one of the heroes and survivors in Benghazi she pointed out that the man that died
Fish
Play gentlemen
Almost nobody was getting award cuz it was
Really President Obama
You can't just do that
Did you know that Obama gave up the most
Presidential medal of freedom
Advertisement
BB. Number two on that list
Reagan by 21 medals
I was going over the last thing one thing that stuck out to me is it Obama's list of recipients
Is pretty Broad
From like Maya Angelou to John Glenn to Bishop Desmond
Blisters
Mostly app
Athletes
Trump is giving out 14 Medals of freedom and 7 of them were two athletes
The only non-athlete she's awarded are Orrin Hatch
Edwin Meese rosewe Reagan attorney general had to resign after a corrupt
Options
Scandal Sheldon adelson's wife Miriam
Antonin Scalia
Economist and Trump advisor Arthur Laffer
Posthumously
There's also a former Justice of the Minnesota Supreme Court Allen
Paige who got an award but he was also
Professional football player Nixon and Elvis were friends and Elvis still.
Can get a presidential medal of freedom
I guess that's
That's f***** up Nexen also
Everybody else a murderer's row of evil
Truly
If anybody
Deserves the presidential medal of freedom
Those six names
Are the bottom of the list
I suppose Eric Prince's down there and hatch
Innocent witches
Edwin meese
I don't remember
Tiger Woods
Presidential medal of freedom aren't necessarily military awards
Military figure in Trump has not at this point
So even that all your magic imagine the next guy to commit a crime is going to get a medal
Other Awards
Surely Obama gave out some of those
And of course eat
Legion
Obama gave up plenty of Medals of Honor also which are specifically for a
The point Alex wants to make is that
The people at Benghazi have not been awarded any of these Metals yet
But he's extending their points
Far past the marker where it becomes a
Complete lie
Which it is
It's completely if you want to just talk
Specifically about the people who died in the survivors of Benghazi not getting these Awards yet
You can have that conversation
And it's what
Tonto is bringing up and
He does extended even to Trump not giving these
Absolutism
The fair conversation
It's not fair when you turn into
Obama's trying to demoralize the military by not giving out Awards
It's just a lie
They just
Don't
Just don't like
Anyting
And everything that
Could possibly be pinned on Obama
Dice
He's he's a he's just he's just a black president and it doesn't make him
Infinitely evil
It doesn't mean that he's not giving out
Battles what's in saying to is that like
That could be May
Coming from Alex
Ever
These criticisms they do come up
For either lies or just
Plead misrepresentation
And you would think if you really wanted
Make
Hard-hitting
She would go with
Real criticism
And somehow you don't
You know it's it's
A bad day to criticize if you're if you're a trump supporter
The bad data criticized Obama's
Expansion of the Drone program
Without mentioning
Yeah
So we're one last that one time
I'm so nosy
So we have one last clip here and it's Alex get into wrapping things up
With the sales
And
I find this to be Gray
Our audience is an audience
Incredibles
We can Finance we can complete this year going the next year antifa
Really want to shut us down don't let them win pokeweed stay in attack formation
Yesterday was the last day of the super end-of-year magazine
Sunday specials
Jackson thing
So you know a company is doing well under CEO is doing an ad reads they will never have sales like this unless we're going
Like I always do it's totally because I'm super busy running
Very healthy business that's not about to collapse
That inspires confidence
Also this episode
On the 7th
When I was listening to a little bit of the show
They ran an ad
Cut from this
Is already in an ad on the 7th
How busy are you like and he does things look like
I tended to days because the editors have to put together the ad
Editor was the put together then add the Arizona 7th
Infowars
Employees
Up to this day clearly shows that whatever the holdup is is not
What you say it at all
Might be inventory Texas
Texas is one of eight states in the United States where companies are taxed on all their carried over inventory at the end of the year
The reasoning is
The state doesn't want to
Incentivize businesses
Is to produce large amounts of inventory they can
They can f*** with their workers
Decreased hours and layoffs during
Slower times
Alex's letting you slip a little bit is gigantic sale at the end of the year was about a voice
Inventory tax on the products left his Warehouse
Come January
That's some sleazy s*** right there but I would also
Kind of bad that he did that because he can't afford to pay
Hey those tax
We're in the show Alex
Cancel that new show that he launched Firepower
Because they couldn't
Afford to pay the boar.
They just launched that show like a month or two ago
This is an impressive failure speed
Wow David Knight is still managed to maintain his show for a couple years now and I'm certain that no one likes it and it is not
Body positive
Return-on-investment
Either Alex isn't really bad financial Straits
Right now
And he had to manipulate his audience
Is pills so you wouldn't have to pay taxes on
Or
He's doing okay but he's reached a point where
Pretending that he's going out of business
This is the only play he has left
The milk sales out of his committed base
Neither Ops
Action is great
So
Good luck Alex
Hopefully 2019 is the last year you even have
I think about him
Inventory tax
This is a mess
Yeah whatever it is it
He's manipulated his audio
That's that's why I'll never I didn't know that a radio show could run
The same way that mattress stores
Going out of business
Forever
That's crazy
Eventually that
That thread will be less compelling
Going to his audience I don't think it's a good long-term strategy
The definition of diminishing returns
Yeah
This brings us to the end of the episode I think it's really interesting cuz you see like this pivot that happens
Just
Over the course of like an hour
Related to the Australian fires
You see the bulshit you see the
Attacking
The climate change
Advocacy position
Bye
Extraneous points that have nothing to do with the arguments being made
You see
Do that that's really fascinating to me
And then
You see this weird thing with a Ron
Clearly has a line
But also even if Trump is past that line
He has to make it the globalist
Yeah you can't allow
It's too threatening to the last years of his life
To accept that Trump
Is doing these things because he wants to
He said he was going
So I think that's a really interesting development and I am
See where that goes
Speakers
Combined circumstances are correct
And they work in the right way
I do think
But if Trump carries on this way
Continually
Keeps
Going down this road
It could lead to Alex
Having to make
Decision
And I don't know I'm also
I'm at the point where I'm so f****** Jaded by idea
This'll get him to lie I know it's until until Trump doesn't have power
That's it
That's when he'll everybody everybody
Trump is out of power be like
And I could call of the things and I don't like the way
But he's not going to criticize him
It's very possible until I will see
I don't know
Never leaves
But
Back Jordan
Next episode but until then
A website
Ross on Twitter
We are on Twitter that knowledge a girl fighting at go to bed Jordan
Download podcast leave a review say nice things donate all have a great time
Give me back but until then
Dzx Clark
I was eaten by a mountain
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work