Damn important
I have great respect for knowledge B
Knowledge fight
A little bit about
Drones
Have you ever been to a lively
Have you ever
No
No Irene
Have to say I don't like reggae at all
Nothing
I respect
Today's good music to South people
Alright not because
Way to relax
It's relax
I do not care for hot chili
You don't like any of that makes me really nervous
That makes
Perfect
It's perfect sense position that was kind of
Anti with a lot of people I know and people around me just like
Reggae mix me
Like just kind of anxious because of the music the music so laid-back
Around you
October
2in to reggae I also
That's larger personality issues
PennDOT
I I I can I can
Appreciate it
I'm not using it as an art show
For the way my head processes
It's just to chill man could not make more sense that the chili the music
That is a perfect encapsulation of why we all
Should you be worried about something Bob Marley
Flhtk
No it is not sorry about so this if I guess right do not process reggae well but
Do know a lot about Alex Jones
And I don't know much
Too bad either special episode
It said it seemed to required
Because of the events going on in the world
We had to
You know there was a killing of qassamsoleimani
January
Aaron shots of missiles
Targets in Iraq
Not knowing exactly what was going to happen was Trump going to
I wanted to check back in because
I thought it would be pretty important
The cover of the January 8th
Episode where Alex
Who's responding to denied priors
Rocking to The
But I knew that by Monday probably something else was going to happen
And this is going to be sort of filtered and processed out so I felt like
Exactly the reason we leave these Fridays open
In this way this is exactly what it
So
So today we got a little special Friday episode for you before we get out of business on this
The folks who make
Episodes like this possible
Weird
Alright here we go 2020 also because this is a special episode they're putting out Oscar
Additional to the end of the episode to try and help us
A little bit closer to current absolute
Care2 please do
Thank you so much you are now policy walk
Thank you
Text Paul
Thank you so much you're now
Mason thank you so much
Next Michael thank you so much
Michael
Text Jake ice I think
Very close to Jay geils who had a band
The centerfold
Are you not a game
Thank you too
You are now
And radically
Yes yes
And write a clue thank you so much
You are now attacking
Money off that heroin
Are you pimp so good
Freakishly large
Thank you so much.
Score with these gents website
DeBary
Jordan
I do not know what exactly I was going to
Encounter looking in on the 8th
Alex's
Coverage has been all over
The place
It's been very bizarre
Sort of
Holocaust denial aside
Absolutely
He had Alex being a kiss is a bold move and then
Waffling around a little bit on the 7th he's trying to blame Mike Pompeo for everyone
I didn't know what his angle was going to be after 1
Retaliate
Tubidy respond
Sure Alex is on Trump
Gave his speech
Sort of
Ramblin slurring
Some have described it that way
So Alex discusses
This speech
At the beginning of the show
The president just about
5 minutes ago
Completed a lengthy
About 45 minutes
Where he attempted to deescalate the situation with Iran
Stop playing large excerpts of that speech today
So Alex thinks it was a 40-minute speech
How long was it was like 10 minutes or so
Alex
Situation he just thinks it was a super long speech
Good to know he prepares sure sure
That's just a good
Indication of how much he gives a f***
About what's going on in the past
Years I've heard Trump speak for the longest concurrent length
The time was two-and-a-half minutes
And that felt like 45 tonight
I will give him that shirt
It does time dilates a little bit
Breaks down
It's okay for you to not listen
To that much or Trump because you're not a guy with an audience
Screams about how great Trump is and how everybody should bring back
America in all this
Alex is kind of an obligation to listen to
They have nbnm
So does know what
He's actually saying sure he's cheerleading the guy
Bear butt
Oh well
Alex
The speech he brings up something the Trump says in the speech
Should be in favor of
But he does
Seem to be a little bit weird
Hey you did you get a lot of money
Are in Europe
You're a lot closer to this problem you need to come in and you need to pay for it and you need to stabilize the Strait of Hormuz
Weed should be there paying for it
Where energy
Independently an out-of-state
So Alex is saying that it's a good thing for Trump to call it for NATO to take care of the situation
He should be staunchly opposed to International bodies resolving these
Make no sense you believe that NATO is the right to intercede at all
What are the International Community has a responsibility towards each and every one of us in order
He doesn't believe he doesn't know he's kind of countries to the unelected
International border globalist coming in and battling
Because it's somehow
Extricate strup from some nonsense user is all in favor of
And all of those people control you probably lateral
So we sang the Builder grouper group should take over Iran that's what he say
NATO to get much more involved in the Middle East process
His ankle is pretty much exactly the same as Alex's
Like we're only interested in the Middle East because of energy-related concerns
And we don't really care too much now they were supposedly energy
And that's some sick s*** that gives a glimpse into how these people think
Let's sing the loud
You couldn't even get away with being dad albeit
It's absolutely not a surprise to learn his deposition Trump
But Alex would probably think a little more about the Opera
Sexier he made a large part of his career by screaming about out bushing
His cronies were evil to carry out these wars in the Middle East for oil
Now he's totally fine with Trump basically saying
I kind of see a whole lot of face-saving going on here it's all pretty thin and full of s***
But honestly it's probably the best thing
To do
Attorney for Trump or
The two of them like rattling Sabers or militarily respond
I kind of prefer the idea of them just talkin dumb s*** yeah might be the least damaging
Of the options that people like them or
Capable
They're they're kind of acting right now like the guy who
Is is like
Really grabbing his friends going I called me back hold me back
And they're not there like
You are f****** crazy man
Yeah it does whatever it is
The fields
Today in the news
Black
Silex likes what he perceives
To be a joke
I don't know if
Did Mike
Let's Make a Deal our missiles are bigger than yours he actually said that
He's really smart
Nordschleife
I'm pretty sure that this is exactly the same sort of s*** Trump was doing with Kim Jeong hoon and we see how fruitful that was
Yeah
I don't know what to think here
Like in the case of a very tense World situation out seems thrilled that the president of his country is making
Make jokes
Baffling that is analysis is taken series by anyone in the situation that were in
Guess so everybody wanted a president
Got a big old dog
Fiddling as the world burn
Just baked a picture take a picture of the world Birds
That's my job dammit
Trump speech and I don't think he was making a picture
I think it was more of a
Threat than anything else
Also Trump announced quote punishing economic sanction
In addition to the sanctions that are already there
This will largely Alex knows that
I know that he knows that because he's yelled about sanctions killing the Rockies
These many many times in the past
When doing so is healthy
Tumatak Madeleine Albright
Alex knows damn well what Trump is doing
Engaging an economic Warfare that'll tend to hurt
And killed civilians in Iraq
But he doesn't care
You'd rather
Focus on an imaginary picture
I
Really f***** up by that
If a economic Williamson thing
Because of the way that the world works
And I'm not some sort of expert and I don't know
But it seems really obviously f***** up
To me that
Everybody goes
A******
If
We if Trump murders a guy
But everybody's like well it's the safe option if he imposes economic sanctions that are going to murder rig
Like
Fox me up
If that's the case
There's that distance that people can take who's like the idea of the sanctions to punish the people in power
Maybe there'd be a stronger argument for it but it doesn't
Seems like that's the way it works track
Yeah
So I think all Alex's done is read a drudge headline
About
The speech because he
That's the only thing
You can really say
Well I'd say drudgereport.com is the best of the minute
Global newspaper headlines
Trump speech about 12 minutes of them
Live feed of the White House collector nearly up
Way to say everybody
Winter White House
So In that clip Alex revealed he has no idea how long Trump speech
B12
It was much shorter so try to save things by saying there's a half-hour static shot of the podium
I guess
Is he implying that he watched the podium for 30 minutes and considered it a part of the speech
Is a clear indication that he just seen these headlines on
We got on Aaron was making things up
Also
Even though Alex is making a correction here he's also make
A new error
He sang the Trump was speaking for the winter White House
Which is Mar-A-Lago
Cows
Alex should be ashamed of himself
Calling one jumps
Properties of winter white
What would Thomas Jefferson think about something like that
What would they write in
The Federalist Papers about an aristocratic sending to the presidency has properties
The US government
I'd suspect
He would not be able to Intuit and I would love to make up a quote
Then come on everybody knows that when they were writing those papers and then the Constitution and all that's
They were really just sad
Nope I got it they f****** hate
Trump all of them except for like Madison he was weirdly into that s***
Adams John Adams
Monica some of those guys were
Samba cryptominer
Yeah but
Jefferson would have been very again
I assume that anybody who
You've never heard of before get cited by Oath Keepers like
Tench coxe
He would be into it
The weirdos from the Revolutionary War
So this is all been kind of Prelude
This is all Alex responding
The Trump speech
Kind of
Talk about news stuff
It's not really what's important
Is as Alex gets into the second segment of his show
He launches into
A profoundly islamophobic
Forno
He dives into
I hate you
VIP spirals out of
Control and will
Come back up later in the episode
And leads me down a bit of a road that will
From volcanoes
There is some stuff that I think is interesting and and worth noting
But as this goes along I ended up going down a couple of Road
That will lead us to some very interesting
Information but before we get there
We just got here Alex be a bigot
And the left that's always telling us that
America's bad Christianity's bad
We oppress women sick of it
Anticlea worshiping something that basically put garbage bags over
Fundamentally
Scares me
Pisses me off it makes me
Revile
So you get a sense here that Alex is starting off this Ranch
I am scared of Islam
Rizzial
Right I hate it
That is mainly because of wardrobe
That is that is a big part of it
Yeah
I was wondering why is
Is he going off into this why is he starting this up I understand that there's a conflict in the Middle East that is a hot-button issue
But if you went to that pool supply store again didn't they
You did not just point it but you're very close
I live in Austin
I went last night after I got off air
At 9
And
Gregory sand
Took over
Pulled into a mom-and-pop hamburger place
Unreal
There wasn't one group of Muslims in there
There were two groups on separate sides
And a place I've been eating hamburgers
Since I was
5 years old
To Dan's Hamburgers
Ben White and Manchaca
I hate those people
Yes it is
It's that anywhere Islam become 10% of the population
They began pushing
Everyone else out
Not if they began conquering that
So Alex is a complete intolerance toward seeing Muslims in public
As you mentioned
We've trimmed
Discussing Muslim women in pool supply shop
2015 children I think it was teams
I'm not I don't remember if you was very specific about the age of the people but
Whatever the case now easy that he hates
Sissy Muslims at a hamburger place that he likes
He doesn't want to live in a world where groups
He doesn't like
2xist in public spaces
It's just that simple with them
This 10% thing seems to track back to a book written by a missionary named Peter Hammond called slavery terrorism
The point of the book appears to be the country's need to keep their Muslim population under 2%
Because if that number gets any higher the Muslim start to act in predictable.
Disruptive ways
I read a breakdown of the book and it's not even an idea worth engaged
Mostly because it makes no sense on its face
Hammond is arguing their various levels at which Muslim populations will begin acting differently
Like at 2% they start to make Street in prison gang
Or it's 5% they push for supermarkets
Stauffer Halal option
Event list countries Ani
Each level
And it makes his point make no sense at all
It is break down the US is listed as 70.6% Muslim population
A really big halal food
In this country
That not be happening yet
I'd like the
I don't know when it was written by don't think it was
It wasn't long enough
It wasn't like
It cuz it sounds to me like he's trying to be the islamophobic
Harry Seldon from Isaac asimov's Foundation I'm not positive that this is where this idea
Yeah but it's definitely something that's reference
On a lot of these blogs you can find
Cover this this 10% idea
Still linked back to his bookcase
As a source I assume he has really
Quality
Sourcing and all of his
If you follow up on him
I'm sure they all make sense these distinctions
Between the categories of 2% percent tip
It's all meaningless stuff
Because the bigger issue is due at Hammond is doing is taking
Very like
Very comfy
Located situations in different countries and different regions
He's boiling it down to a single variable
It is
How many Muslims are there
It's the sort of argument that plays really well in like white nationalist in Christian identity extremist circles
Serious person would even consider that theory is having the second
Thought
What you see here Alex is except
Accepted that is true
It's just a reality to him that if your country goes to a 10% Muslim population there
Start taking over and putting in Sharia law
This is gross rhetoric and the end result of this kind of thinking has to either lead to extermination
Dislocation
Or eugenics
It's program
Alex isn't stupid enough not to realize that he's just fine with those things being directed towards people
He doesn't want to see what he's trying to get a hamburger
I mean yeah sure
You can look
Directly at the interconnectedness of all of these different countries in their individual context
Histories and all of that stuff and consider on a Nuance level what it is that it means and how it really is
The different spaces
Or dad
You could
Estimate how many Muslims there are in a place and make long and stupid pronouncements about
You could which is easier
Right
The problem for Alex's that Islam is expansionist
Or something
He cites a reference for that.
Expanding
Thousand Years
Almost lost Europe to it
Holy Roman Empire
Taking over the men killed one and put on slave ships
And sold all of the world
It's a group conference
Does Alex not realize what he's saying here
Why do they think that turkey was part of the Holy Roman Empire it before you answer let's focus on that word empire
I understand what was it before
So
So turkey used to be part of the Holy Roman Emperor
While still maintaining its status as a sovereign state
She's good
You know
There weren't any more worlds
To conquer and it turned out there were so Alexander wasn't that great in the first
This is
If this is your argument this is what it goes back to you need to
Stop
250,000 years ago in the mitochondrial eve are birds from whatever
Play she's coming from that was when she was taken over by his evil
F*** off
Just f*** off
Oh these are so
Such thin arguments
Is we could go case-by-case
All of these places
Trace it back to
Love it where do we want to go
That would literally take us all day
Between the Tigers
Euphrates there was a part of me that was like looking at that dude's book
10% number
Complexity
Now I will just end up having to explain literally all of world history
We got him
So
Here we go
Alex
Even know how to
Describe this this is
Beyond
The pale kind of
Bulshit
It's a group conquering people
And they're very
Alright The Roommate
I was against the Warriors going in the Middle East
Removing people that
A lot better than what the global for putting in
Wanted to destabilize Islam to break it for Radicals in
Have been used as a weapon against the West
This is a very sophisticated problem we face
But
Give me like
If I would say
Jewish
This is going to go well
Germany was 1939 Germany and I was another country
Here-we-go Parish in Oneonta
Restaurant that there's a couple Nazis in there
I would argue it's not similar at all and days before the Steve pieczenik on tonight
Thought so calm down this b*******
This isn't same levels of
Say you get afraid of people who
Don't look and act like you
I don't even hear any of this poor thing he said I'm scared of
Justify it with this b******* justify it and he's also trying to rationalize why him being afraid
Hey doesn't make him weak
It's going on giant cowardin you're afraid of engaging with people different than you
So you go on this weird wild nonsense and you makeup b******* right order to justify the fact that you
You alone with white people
In a nation of them
Jesus
But the thing is that Alex is recognizing some differences
In the world
And that is it now he goes to hamburger shop
Macy's Muslim
Where is in the past
He didn't I mean it at McDonald's
Dan
I cannot my hamburgers yet
Mall
Sometimes it'll be at night
Lemon in full Marcus
Restaurants on Route
My daughters in the Muslims are looking at my daughter's cuz they're not wearing the jibs and their women have
Cool
Face mask
Darien Halloween costumes
Will f*** you
I don't like it
You don't like
Do you think there's a possibility that
Alex
Is
So singularly focused and bigoted towards Muslims now in a way that he wasn't before
So now he notices them in public
Then he did before
Do you think it's possible that
Maybe there maybe there are more Muslims around maybe that's possible
But maybe they didn't anger him in the same way 10 years ago
Mattress stores every around here but when I got them at the store
I don't even know where mattresses anymore even better example
I didn't notice how many mattress stores there were until someone
Made a joke around me about how many mattress stores they were that I started noticing everyone with Plex
Hanging around with a bunch of
Goddamn aggressively islamophobic
Certainly gone
Much farther down that pathway
10 years ago
Who is every single
Time he sees a Muslim it's a threat to him where is before it wasn't
This is not
Good thinking on your part
No
So cute
And the thing that bugs me out is that maybe there's no better example
Or
Like representation of
A culture assimilating into America
Then going and hanging out at all
Ifucking ball America's
Shittiest export and if you're there you're in
That's an important here in a second
And one salad
Talks
This is just
I mean it's
I can't really
Introduce these clips
In any other way than
Colon
The next clip
Preemptive like just harsh
Condemnation
No.
Here's what Alex has to say
We don't wear Halloween costumes in America
Halloween
We don't make women wear bags over their heads
Promoting it
Face mask
None
How do you feel about none
Is that the real threat is the oldest border and Trump's been trying to shut the mass of Islam
Were they live in the Stone Age
It's important to remember that would spark this rant is Alex talk about seeing two groups of people he assumed
We're Muslims
Hamburger place the night before
He's talked about how these people need to go back
To their countries
And more important to Alex stay out of his country
He's not talking about anyone is guilty the sort of behaviors he's describing
Killing women or pedophilia
This is the response that he has two people he assumes are Muslims
Being in a restaurant
This is he
Deep level of bigotry and I want to say
From my assessment
From everything that I
No from listening to so much Alex
This is the real Alex Jones
Weak scared and hateful
Yep he's unable to
Enjoy his food because he's around people who are members of a he doesn't like
He's terrified to see
The people who don't look like a live a different way than he does allowed to eat
Existing Society
It's a childish seething rage
And you should be embarrassed by heart rate
Apparently pathetic
You always wondered
Like
How is it
That somebody could be
In the 19
And
So
Urea
That a black person just wants to eat at a restaurant
Weird
How is that possible
Alex
So crazy to me and then it's 2019 and Alex's doing it
I'm like
Oh it's just cuz you're a f******
Coward your age
F******
Pathetic
Weak Health worthless human being
Is that your Civil Rights era probably would have been able to make very similar arguments that that Alex is making
Of course
We don't do that to our women.
We can't allow that to happen
None of this stuff isn't
Did you get the thing I do I do think
Doesn't real
That somebody is feeding and poison into your spitting
Get back up at us but
But he's feeding it to himself as friends are free to go
Then you added his supplements
What is an olive
So when Alex gets back from that break
Picky recognizes I want a little bit hard
That was a little bit of Thanksgiving
Spy trying to address for Saturday just went on a islamophobic
I needed to go to beginning of Trumps
About the islamification of the last
Thanks just are not compatible
And now they're not
Our ways are trying to make us about their ways and it's a fact
I completely reject Alex's argument
About these Muslims just making whatever he thinks our ways are
And your
Totally right exactly that's the reason
That's the reason
Because when he gets the most mad at specific Muslim
It's generally a situation situation where he sees Muslim
Integrated
He yells abstractly about Muslims and Islam
In general quite a bit
But there's something different and more intense about these rent that he goes on
What do you seize
Like Muslim women at the pool supply shop
Them at the hamburger store
This is the thing
Alex wants a holy war between Islam and Christianity
He wants a new Crusade but he knows that in the modern civilized world
Create
Constant narratives about Islam begin
Compatible with the West
A picture that they're already
In a holy war against
Him
This is why Muslims in a pool supply shop or a hamburger stand
Completely fuk him up
It's because there proof that Muslims are
Perfectly compatible with our way of life
When Alex sees Muslims engaging in the exact same behaviors as he himself is engaging in a strong indication that
Distance is not only possible but it's
Happening
And that's threatening to his believe in and desire for civilizational level
Alex isn't really mad when he sees news of his Islamic
Extremist carrying out like
What's a knife attack in the UK
That can
They are that conform to this world
He can use that
What infuriates him is things like this
Muslims getting a
Hamburger
He's a pathetic
Sack of s*** this is disgusting
Where is the heart
White nationalism
Railing against it's not possible for them to assimilate and then when they do they're like
Bien
But Sir Alex
Onaga
That would be racist
Just for you to say that hehe
I would bake
To differ with his assassin
Except for part of it
Like
The first part
I disagree
Second part of the statement
Completely gray
Concur
Well I don't agree with the last part but I do agree that he's scared
He's very scared
He also hates
Oh yeah
Muslims are really bad
Alex
Right but there's some people worse
And I think I might
Ideology and political Islam it's expensive it's a lot better
Then the left hey
Islam is better than
Call te Clapton
The Americas well if you're watching Hollywood
Over there
Culture
Suggested Monday talk about that
Stuff they're not talking about movies they're talking about foreign policy
Not is
Petty and stupid as him like Alex
Gets bogged down and cultural issues
Petty grievances about women in lead roles in movies and Shay
That's not
I think they're operating off of its
What we have done to the Middle East in the past
20 years
But have you seen Oblivion
So Alex is
Sing a bit about how Islam hasn't
Evil spirit
Right that's kind of
Jerk something
Ideas
Have spirits
Places
Spirit are we getting
But plate or what are we doing
Places have energy
Example
Francisco
Terrible spirit
There's place
Where the spirit was pretty good too
Dan's
Nope
Francisco has a hellish energy
La has a hellish energy
Hillary Clinton she has Ellis energy
Reno has Alice energy energy
Psychotically powerful at Stonehenge without it was a placebo I like
Granger's a battery goes yeah but
30% of people have
Have that effect
El Dorado energy
And you don't
Seduce
This is just a ridiculous show I don't even
I'm I'm the professor of walking across imaginary line
I would love to been there on that trip
Stone heads
Download Adams by connected to my druidic road
Might be a calendar I don't know
Alex
His
Belief system is not compatible with America
That is not true
I don't know I had to get away from Stonehenge because you're that feeling was wow like and I don't want to
I want to get away from this
Did baby feel violin
Bug
What is Hunan in the world ladies and gentlemen
Submit
Great
It should be pointed up at Stonehenge in Wiltshire England
It's not a site where experts believe human sacrifice was scary down
However there is another similar site
Germinate
Which is closer to italics
Just talkin about
An article in the Smithsonian include this line
Quote
It's your similarities with its Fame cousin in Britain
Perform many of the same ritual
So they added a new twist
Human psyche
The words new twist
Certainly to get the message across to people who study people who studies Stonehenge don't believe it was used as a human sacrifice
Even in the case of the German site the only human sacrifice
A likely scenario
Well pointing out that the trauma of the bodies found their could have alternative explanation
Like inner conflict
Intergroup
Conflict
Raves
There's one skeleton that was found around the year 2000
From Stonehenge
Theorize could be the Vic
Sacrifice
But other believe that the evidence
Good point
And plenty of other directions
And also the person that this skeleton is up
They would have died in around 6
600 AD
Which is way too late
4 Stonehenge
Given that this is like one of the only real pieces of evidence that tends towards the conclusion of human sacrifice taking place at Stonehenge
You be pretty irresponsible jump to the
The glitch just from that without any supporting evidence
A lot of the beliefs that dumb people like Alex said about Stonehenge come from 17th century historians
Whose theories about Stonehenge being a druidic
Temple
I've been thoroughly debunked
These ideas are really popular for a while
There's one stone there that was nicknamed the slaughtering Stone because rainwater would pool in
Turn red
The imagination I was you know that is proof of long lingering blood
It's really just a result
Does algae and iron
They figured that out
But it is
It was really popular
And it gets into people's imagination
Giant Stone hanging around in a circle from the past what are you talking about
Surrounding Stonehenge
Able to whip himself into a frenzy just by being near it and I should stress
With himself
Into a friend Magic
Country video ever goes to Israel
Messiah
I'm certain Israel declare itself the Messiah
God somebody somebody GoFundMe to just get him out of
So there's the spirits and energies of
Absurd
Islam is bad
Christ is good
Sure
Submit
It's around it
Energy of Christ is pure
Clean
When is good and is peaceful and is the choir
Play some most high
Tom talked about
That's the place we want to go so I'm glad that
From the escalating
Islam's been set up and
We need a wallet off at home
Text themselves
But it's not going to be all the Muslims must conform to them
You're going to fight it
And Islam will not Prevail against
Stop reaching
Cuz this is
Knock this is not good I mean. Nothing you saying
Makes any sense
Wallet off
B talking about
Here's the problem
Alex is operating off like a really dumb assumption
And that is
Expressed in this
I don't want to be an enemy of Islam but
Christian converting
And I know you want to conquer me
Not in your country that you took
Christians
And then others
What
Defending myself
But I'm done
That's it I don't want
I don't think
Islam
I don't I don't think I ate any Keys operating off of false assumptions
I don't think so
I think that is just
Weird paranoid
I don't think Islam has recruiters
Just do not like not army base recruiters leg
Like the guys you'd Senior High School lunchroom I don't know I don't know enough but I have been to
Before and I have not felt they were trying
To convert
Make a say no no no I don't I don't know how Alex is doing
Occupied Texas Fortified Compound all the Muslims trying to get him
Morning prayer
The energy is really good
According to Alex
It's really good
So he gets off this islamophobic chunk here and starts talking about the night before
And how the media was covering
Please rethink sza gotcha clip
From I believe MSNBC of possible fatalities
AMV attack
On the bases in Iraq
Pictures of gacha
But it's not
Play this clip because
Last night I'm up here and I noticed
MSNBC
Shane 20 dad 30 dad
I just said listen
I say that
Surrounded messy population we're not hearing those report
Sure enough it turned out those
Which is a normal but just saying we don't believe
Thank God it wasn't true
12 MSNBC Amplified fake news Iranian attack
U.s. soldiers here it is
We're just getting reports
Irgc
Ayatollah Khamenei the supreme leader of this country was in the control center
Coordinating Addy's attacks this is I'm not sure about that
Tyronn State media is claiming the Searcy US soldiers have been
You killed in this attack and outs this is not confirmed this is just coming from Iranian media
We have just left that part out
We have entered a very unpredictable time we have to see
What the response is going to be from the United States
But we cannot step over the precipice
Could mean any number of things
Something necessarily specific
You're right you should have cut that part out because a guy's clearly saying is it a grain of salt
Yeah we are not clear on this
Might not be true
Responsible reporting
Alex is saying
MSNBC f*** this up in there a lying fake news where is he did not
And this is what I realize Alex probably did a live stream tonight
Before any almost certainly absolutely
I thought I would check in
So now we're going to do a little bit of Alex's livestream
Here is Alex speculating that an all-out war is starting
And are they playing for portly were launched
About an hour ago
And
Obviously Iranians know those are coming I'm not giving out any cigarettes or like a roller Rivera
Midlothian
Second Iraq War
This is a big bold move
And all hell is breaking loose
Anacortes yummy bombers and stuff wash my other areas that she have
I am the shepherd
But tonight is one where there's a very good chance all that working Breakout
We pray that is not the
But the shorts on Thursday we're going to call her about 10 minutes to get on
I said it's going tonight if they're about to head there any leadership
Japanese says
Sleeper cells are activated whole nine yards he was just in Iraq
Imma leave it at that
So Alex has a source that's telling him it's about to go Connecticut sleeper cells or episodes
Chance
Is breaking out tonight responsible
Amplify fake news from around State his is really
Solid reported
Call The Source
To figure out what's going on
Start speculate
About things
The Narrative is
Soleimani killed
Some people
It's good some people
Think it's bad
Welded wire going in
In Iran or Iraq
Now you feel that you have to retaliate
You do
You strike are
Us bases
Is in Iraq
I've been
I've read reports up to
20 or more dead US citizens
And so now what will now what is Trump have to do I mean
Looks like one option
Not responding to this
And then
You really
Cross your fingers and Hope
I mean
Say it folks
We know how old
Really really
The whole country of Iran
Yes Man
That was a good plan speculation
Yeah you know here's a little bit more
Here's where things get really interesting in the livestream from the night at 7
Alex is talking about this you know some people are saying that there is 20 dead
But he has a more important narratives that he wants to pitch
Which is his way of making
Himself
A major part of the story
Now we're going to go over all of this is his unfold but they're all over the news saying
Look for Counter-Strike look for attacks
Reportedly
Did you said something 15 something 18 something 20
We hope nine people just type in
US troops killed US servicemen killed we're not sure
We're going to continue and there I can go up there again to go search
Myself
Pull all that up tonight as we're alive but I know this
As all this was about to break we got a giant denial
Of service attack
That was definitely institutional for the establishment
Is Iran launching this does not want us on air
Cuz Dana will try to figure out what's going on
Hey we're we're we're victims in this too big Target
Cuz we're going to tell the truth in the man doesn't want
What's 2
Alex is speculating about the the death
But at the same time he's not saying
He is giving it a little bit of a we don't know I guess
That's your speculation that's going on a responsible specific
It's not
He's not handling
Exactly what MSN
Yes that's true
We hope it's
Not which suggests you do that
Could be
And Alex goes to a live feed of Fox News because
He gets kind of
Like I don't have the information let's go to live feed I'll look into
A little bit
And then
Wow the MSN Fox News
Part is playing
Alex
Caught on hot mic
Let's go ahead and go to Ally foxy right now
Given the intelligence
Starting to come out
Tonight I'm at a top-level meeting where
The gang of eight was given some information about
What that intelligent Township
I'm going to learn more about that
Potentially tomorrow
You can hear him say I'm not going to do the show until I get numb
Because I think he knows
I got to have this
Yeah
B
That's interested
Why would
Why was Mike
Silat
Are there amateurs working the book
Does he have a diminished staff
Is this going to be a problem later
We'll see
So Alex alright comes back
I'm starting to think those were rhetorical
Does Alex comes back from the Fox News Feed
And I think I actually can
Looking into initially why I jumped through the livestream
Was to see if you was being unfair about his own coverage about the death
Right and I think he's not I think he's
When he comes back
Here's what he says I think it's totally fair
We are alive
And there's been a bun
We're glad to tell you
Enotfound
What is documenting
We're just glad
What has bacon for
Credit
Talk about this we can't find confirmation of it
You know Alex
Yes Zack
You bet
Zach is back I knew it was coming I was going to make a return Journey absolutely
Livestream Alex did this evening on the 7th
In response to the missile attack he had Zack.
For those of you new to the show Zack was Alex's fake intelligent Source who was an attempt to take over the Internet space is occupied by Cuban
Also the star of Saved by the Bell
I mean when Zack was on the show back on January 5th 2018 Alex literally called him quote
Are Weedle qanon absolutely
Alex
I think he's controlled opposition so there's really nothing you can do to win them over
Strangely enough Mark-Paul Gosselaar is q
It's a really weird working with Screech Screech is doing the attack stuff
Maybe
I haven't heard Zach on for a while but interesting Lee whereas in the past
Alex has been hiding his identity
His name is public now
His name is Zachary Lee klawonn
And credit is official title that's given on the Chiron
16th engineer which I think is
Mysterious I don't know I don't care
One thing I noticed is that Zack doesn't really sound the same time
His voice itself is close enough that doesn't make me suspicious that it's a different person
But the way you speaking is totally
Back reviews anonymous
He spoke with authority
But now it's
What's more suggestive
Hinton
He's making the argument on this episode that Obama sending money to Iran
Which was a Ron's money
Finance this attack
But he's not saying that
He's hinting at
Which seems weird
If he's a high-level intelligence
Guy and all that you shouldn't use the same dumb rhetorical tricks
Alex.
Also he called the irgc the Irani and revolutionary guard corpse
Which seems weird I feel like every military person in the world knows how to pronounce Corps
In the interview he says the word problematic
About a thousand times
Also he just keeps saying things are problematic
Like a dump sounds very problematic
Anyway
Now that I have Zach's name I can tell you a little bit more about it let's hear about that
Before there really wasn't anything to go on
To look at you who he was like I just had the name Zach and
What time is it in Morocco
That's not allowed to go on
But now I can introduce
Duzak
Klawock
Zach went to high school at Braden River High School in Bradenton Florida
It's the childhood home though
Great Carlton Fisk he's a real piece
You also have a great name
And there's a rapper
No Limit Records
Funny that this guy
Choosing a rap name just chose
Carlton bucket baseball
Zack and I
Common
And that we both didn't finish High School
I dropped out
But Zack was actually expelled from school for having a gun on school
As reported in a 2008 article in The Herald Tribune
The article was about how 10 students were barred from graduation ceremonies because of explicit and
Threatening rap songs
They performed and posted online I believe as they are closing on MySpace
Apparently they were pretty antagonistic to their rival High School Lakewood Ranch
In the song
Included lyrics like
Lakewood boys is going to bleed
Zach even kicked out of school for having a gun the year
Pryor was still one of the rappers on this track
Threatening his old schools rival
So that tells me he's
Very cool
To be clear
I must concerned with the rap song
Do whatever people do dumb stuff
Done
Rap song YouTube videos
I'm just more interested in the fact that he had a gun it's
To me is much bigger of a deal
I just think that this rap song is a big dork
If it was reversed
I would assume you were Rush Limbaugh from the
I'm more angry about this
Rap music
But I am about to
You be you should have guns on school campus
What does
Rap music
So after this listed in the army
What's the rank of specialist by 2010
Which is the rank
Just directly above private first class
That Year's Akron public with allegations that he been harassed in the service because he's a Muslim
Any an article in ABC news story being the subject of abuse as soon as basic training started
With his drill instructor singling him out in mocking the idea of attending Islamic religious service
He was specifically selected to portray a terrorist in training exercises
A fellow Soldier desecrated is Quran by tearing out pages in Tulsa
Sometime around
They would call him quote ragheads sand monkey
And Zachary bin Laden
One day 3 weeks into his time at Fort Hood
Zach found a piece of paper in the windshield wiper of his truck
It's a quote hate carpet jockey go back where you came
From
After the Fort Hood shooting
It got so bad that he had to be moved off
The base for his own safe
In 2010 there were memos written I could I found these memos
That were written by the office of the under Secretary of Defense
Regarding Zach's allegations of harassment
In the Bible does it says quote
The attached letter address to the Secretary of Defense concerns alleged harassment of a Muslim Soldier assigned to Fort Hood
The letter is from the Council on american-islamic relations on behalf of army specialist
Zachary klawonn
Alex has repeatedly and consist
Italy called care a terrorist organization
Was dealing with a very serious situation
He was they were who he went to for help sure
After this Zack went on CNN aljazeera.net
And how there's a serious problem with islamophobia in the military
I found some blogs talking about him having a lawsuit against the army
But I don't fully trust those sites
And I wasn't able to find concrete evidence except it's probably true
He probably did
Have this lawsuit
I don't care to come through Zack social media posts or anything like that but a couple of them
Think things do come up if you Google his name
One is his LinkedIn page
Which says that he's retired from the Army
I'm not positive when you left but I would not be surprised
It wasn't too long after he started going red domestic and foreign news programs
Talk about how the army training
Includes propaganda against Islam
They usually
His word
Yeah well I mean
I like I like it does
Like I don't believe that right
Another thing you can find is a profile for Zachry klawonn on Explore Talent
A website for people
To book Act
Gigs
Very active and honestly I can't even really be sure that it was
Made by someone else
Trying to make it look like
He's an actor
I have no fun
Idea
But it does come up and who knows what that mean
I can find no indication that Zach has any relation to the military at this point in his life other than that he used
To be a specialist in the army
I can find no evidence that he was in the intelligence field and honestly a lot of that stuff just
To be made up
My heart goes out to him for the harassment he said he had to endure while he was enlisted
But I can't help but wonder how he could
To possibly be the type of person
Would go on the news and do interviews about anti-muslim bigotry in the army
Meathead also the type of person who Bok associating with Alex Jones extreme anti-muslim
I could speculate on that
As it stands now I just don't think there's any reason to take anything he's saying to Alex
Seriously
He was formerly in the military but so what
So was the dude who lived next door to me when I was 19 or smoked weed
Yeah
B
Ideas
I did too
The last time I was in Columbia I did go find him
Yeah it was nice to hang out again
Yeah it was just a situation was 19
What's up what's the news for wasn't
He got clean
Which is actually pretty good
Nono from drugs
I was happy for him
It was a situation where I had a lot of weed
You're living on a controlled in common
Cherokee word
I would love to come over bring a joint with smoke and Heat
You just tell me stories as like
His life after coming back from Vietnam
Handsome
Pretty interesting
Bi-Rite
As seriously as I'm going to
Take anything that Zac said
So
Zac is on
And really it's an interesting portrait because
I think the fact
Front bun to school and got expelled
Is
Relevant
But also like
Not the biggest
The world
I don't know if there's any indication that he brought it in a threatening way I still think it's
Way out of line
It getting expelled for that is
A hundred percent
Worth
Get the f*** out
A good response
It was a situation where anybody could
I mean I think it's entirely possible that maybe it had gone
In his car
Still
Sure not the same as bring it to school to threaten
I think the most
Important thing is this
There's a lot of Trail
In his life
That is speaking out against
Anti-muslim bigotry
Tree in the army
It makes no sense
For him to be on Infowars
There's something up
I don't know what it is
It could be a situation where he lost
He completely
Also you could see a situation where
Because of his
Experiences
Because of the inaction on the part of the army
He could have a
Really serious resentment
Against the United States
Government
Sure you could see
Gravitating towards Alex
It's because of some sort of an anti-government
Fascination that he is
Built because of his experience could they
Or could you be something yet
Entirely Craven
Like I don't know
Eileen I mean
Eileen immediately to if you are on Alex's show today
There is some scam activity in your path
I don't know what it is I'm not going to say that
And is going to I'm not going to say that his harassment stuff was fabricated or any of that nonsense
I don't know but
Everything is suspect
Everything Is Us
I don't
I don't trust
Any part of what you say has
I have no reason to not
Trust his experience in the army
Like I don't I don't have any reason
To distrust that other than he's on
Boatworkstoday
That's my that's my reason
It is tough
Stop that's where that's where I come from
Sure
Zach is on most of it is just this
She's trying to imply that the Iran deal
Obama giving
Itsfunneh back
Is funding these attacks
It's really basically his
Big boy
In 2000
The Obama Administration allowed one
7 billion dollars
Verified by the treasury
And now we
So he's just spouting a fairly popular conspiracy theory among the right and that is that
Obama is
But his funded this
It's it's
This ridiculous
What
What idiot says 1.7 billion dollars
Flooded
How did it flood in tiran
Oh okay then the money the money wave
Took over
Here is where I think everything gets
Incredibly
Suspicious and all
The pieces sort of come to
Alex is earlier said there was this denial-of-service attack going on on Infowars
Alex earlier got caught on a hot
Zach
Is a suspicious character
All of that merges
Into play
In this next clip
Put your mic down for this
Just because
This is
So f***** up
Talk about
Country around the world
Is 2
Pictures of America
Platform
Political figure
Eventually
To hear that
I think I heard a burp
No hear listen
Just that part where you got caught on the hop by earlier in the clip
Table animated
I know when but I hear listen to
He saying brain-dead
This is pretty good
This is pretty
Good yeah I heard this is Brandon
Is pretty good it is pretty good
Severe problems with his mic is on during this livestream
It's because you can't afford to pay the whole crew to be there for an office hours impromptu live stream
Whatever the case he has that prattling on about how social media influencers and Defenders of America are the real targets
According to his Intel
And wouldn't you know it
I was just pretending that he was having a DDOS attack earlier in the Stream
It's almost like this is all planned out
It's almost like they're all working on
Some kind of a narrative building things you all of these things put together
Would suggest
The conclusion that they want you to draw that I don't get why I would strongly suspect
I would strongly suspected I was being paranoid and making things up and clip you can hear Alex
Thinking he's off Mike's a 20-inch
This is pretty good
What's pretty good
The idea that Iranians are going to attack social media influencers and Patriots
Because if that were true
That's absolutely knock
That would be bad
Especially for a patriot self-identified social media influencer like Alex
It's super good however if you know that it's b******* and you're trying to run a pageant
It does seem like a very
There's no fear of act
Alex is saying this is pretty good because he knows it
The angle is pretty good one
To make the story about himself
Hopefully boost traffic to Infowars and make some money
Exact is clearly a participant
But I'm not sure how much of that is based on like collaboration between him and Alex are how much
It's just him knowing what it's like suneet
Don't know what's going on here precisely
Whatever it is falls directly under the headline of
Manipulation
How to talk about the DDOS attack earlier
It's possible that Zack was listening to him looking
4 clues of ways to build on the narrative and he's operating completely on his own
It's also possible that when Alex
Called him earlier
Before having him on
He was saying like all right look
Angle we're going with is that Ronnie and they're going to be attacking me
Right and so Zachary is presenting his until like that
It's possible that it's a collaborative effort
Possible that Zack is
Is just intuitive enough to understand
The fact that Alex
Thinks his mic is off
Pretty good
Is
Now I will posit
One alternative
To you
And I will admit that it is
Unlikely
It certainly makes
Less narratives
Since then what you've got
Got going on
But it's more likely than zero
And that is
That Alec
Text did Burr Parlier
And he's telling Owen the
The sandwiches eating
Is delicious
Camera is not on him when this is happening I can't say that but
The camera does come back there's no food or drinks
It's possible and I will always I will always entertain the possibility that he is eating or turkey tips
It's important not to jump
To conclusions and so like
Yes there is other possible explanation for why you would say this is pretty good
Owen wow
In the middle of his
Fake intelligence or saying that you guys are the real Target
Possible other explanation
To eat while he's are there
What I know cuz he went to Dan's Hamburgers after this
Dangerous yeah absolutely
I mean look
He's actually eating some Halal strangely enough
Whatever's going on here is depleted
Suspicious
I wasn't good
Just thought like
Let me first of all attention
Now we know who Zach is
Is get a picture of him
Is he healthy
Incongruous what he's doing now is
With what he was doing
Let's say eight years ago you got to wonder what is the reason for that
Why why is that going on
Obviously
F******
Codes for
Attacking Alex really not as interested with social media influencers
Zach would have you believe or dumb radio shows Alex's using Zac his hi-pro
Profile intelligence
Fake qanon guy
Push forth
The narratives that he's intellisource
Are going to be the target
It's just all very suspicious
It was weird whenever I looked up anti Alex Jones podcast and there was ours and
The cuts there they have their own knowledge fight
I don't know I don't know how to say it in
So Alex
Say we not jump back
Create because the rest of that
3 visit
Disaster you take some calls
And then leaves
Greg Reese one of his employees and Owen Shroyer takes more phone calls and then
Oh and leaves and gets replaced by Harris
Smith Wright
Who cares it goes on forever and they just take much.
Trump calls people who were Muslim in
Later
That's the headline
Alex kind of just leaves after detox
Zach cuz I think he's gotten what he needs out of weave
Tomorrow we're going to run
I don't think he's running with it then
Next day though I don't see him
They're going to attack Infowars
Because that would be too smart to run with the narrative that you establish the night before I don't I think it's more
Like this is going
To work for the immediate and allow people
Or it'll lead people to keep their eyes glued to this
I think it's more of that and then fundraise
This is best to cannibalize stream
I get the sense if that's okay because the next day he's just
Hedonism
Brian
Hamburglar
So he comes
Who's back on the 8th
Can calls from Finland
Who said some really f*****
What is the world is doing is
Like a church mission
Find
Get Revelations from God
Trying to get Revelation and then you get emissions based on. And you go out and you act
And that is in my opinion
What's a Buddha doing and I
I really do believe
Is important.
Tithing
So we got to church
It is very strange
I I don't like it's disturbing
If you are from Finland
You're not allowed
I would specifically Finley
I don't know why
Finland Optical some strange lights
So that calls great Alex Azar
Another call from guy named Scotty in Virginia who's calling in to tell Alex that he star
Because of the gun grab
Call
The 20th consecutive year of being a nerd
Virginia Beach
The extreme-right is very paranoid about this
Appropriate measure
Which of these guys calling in
And he's going to start a militia
And Alex's
Something really dumb
Last time I checked
It's only a couple counties that are Northern Virginia
Democrat
Hundreds County Commission meeting
Local government saying we don't agree to the king of England taking our guns
Pictures of king of Virginia
Northam
Start a fight
Was it going to be like
We're sending in the Army's little black girls to go to school everybody
You didn't or wouldn't have
Alex is sadly not too far off
There are a lot of counties
In Virginia that have passed these gun sanctuary resolution
Is not sure
Granted this is completely symbolic gesture and means nothing
Legal perspective
I would say it's a pretty good indication of the mood
Mary McCord the legal director for the Georgetown University Law Center Institute for constitutional advocacy and protection
Recently wrote a piece in the Washington
You can post that have interesting take on this gun sanctuary Trend that's going on
You moron
Virginia state law prohibits local governments from enacting ordinances and resolutions that are inconsistent with state laws
More directly specifically prohibits
Local governments from regulating firearm
That's going to be a problem for Alex
So I wonder why that's not a federal law that is a state law
So unless he's going to amend his position that the constitution
About the County's or something
You got to recognize that these County resolutions are meaningless now there's there's only one thing that these guys
Believe which is that democracy is great
So long as everybody agrees with what I say
And if
By some evil of circumstance.
Evil Democrats who disagree with me
Steal their way into office ignore them completely because democracy
Isn't democracy unless everybody agrees
States rights
Except except
So the article goes on to mention that
86 Supreme Court ruling pressure versus Illinois
Does not prevent
The prohibition of private paramilitary organization
Which it's noted are actually illegal according to the Constitution
The 48 states
Including Virginia
This is a problem
Because at this point episode like I said Alex was on the phone with this guy who's literally talking about how he's organizing a private
Russia
This is a public discussion of an explicit crime
Violation of Virginia Constitution
People like Alex and The Oath Keepers are whipping Gunn weirdos into
Complete frenzy they could lead to dangerous
Results
Their argument is bad
Local governments can't do anything close to what they're pretending they can
And if a local government is in opposition
The laws of the state
Their only recourse is to
The challenge the state law in court which would likely not work
This case
They kind of know that path wouldn't work
It looks like you're committed to angling for some kind of a standoff
Which is a really bad sign
It also
Alex
Himself pretty much everyone supported Eisenhower sending in the National Guard
Protect the black students in Little Rock
When the schools were
Desegregated bulshit
Watching Coronavirus
Newspaper articles after newspaper articles decrying how evil and
Your real high was that Eisenhower would have
The Gulf
Call to
The Constitution they loved so much and I would ask this
Question right off the bat
It pretty much everyone is for it why was it necessary to send in the National Guard
Single School
Maybe it's because the whole lot of people are super racist and not in favor of integration
I don't want to send too deeply into this issue but you know who was super not into Eisenhower sending the National Guard
AP students
John Birch Society
Six years after Eisenhower sent in the guard then governor of Alabama George Wallace held his
The schoolhouse door event
We're racist tried to keep School segregated by physically blocking black students from entering
This was part of his philosophy which if you were called was
Segregation segregation tomorrow segregation
Can forever you can't prove he said that unless there's audio
I bring this up because Wallace physically tried to stop black kids from go to school in 1960
Which brought him a bunch of attend
It also required jfk2 federalized the Alabama National Guard to get Wallace to stop being an a******
What was being a national star among races
After this point
Ascendancy
Any parlayed that into
Presidential runs in 1964 and 9
So many of Alex's spiritual ancestors
Where George Wallace supporters
Gary Allan the guy who wrote Alex Jones's favorite book none dare call it
Conspiracy served as Wallace's speechwriter during
Both of his presidential campaign so agree with Eisenhower
George Wallace
This campaign deployed rhetoric.
Mirror that the John Birch
Society and he actually said I have no problem
Full of Bircher
Any almost chosen notorious Furniture as written
Benson
As his running mate
Benson as a prominent Mormon
And anti-communist
Provide the link to W Cleon skousen
Did George Wallace campaigns
A president or inexorable from the swap from which Alex's worldview emerged
It takes some brass balls for him to pretend
That pretty much everyone was for Eisenhower calling in the National Guard
Everyone admires in
Considers a hero of modern history actively fought against
The man who wanted to do the opposite
Which again I should remind you is
Keeping black kids out of school
Yes well if they are
And the argument continued
It's little
Ludacris for him to
To get on a store that quickly they do that
It's so amazing how it only
Takes one generation of separation for everybody to be like
Well obviously I would have
Supported Martin Luther King jr.
You're of course I would have no I voted
And I really do love the build the wall to keep out the brown people rhetoric
But I love Martin Luther
Love it
It's even worse
Even worse than that say that you would have been against Martin Luther King Jr already everybody knows
Everybody who shaped Alex's
Worldview his
His narrative
State formative
Writers and thinkers
Of his his upbringing
Like his parents were
Clearly inundated with John Birch Society material if they weren't actually members a very much
Support at Eisenhower
Sending message
He believes everything about global
Conspiracy and all this ship
Because of the writings of Gary Allen & W Cleon skousen
There is
No
Part of what
He believes about the world that isn't
In some way
Very closely related
To George Wallace's campaign
That also is connected to
Kinds of other
Portable shed
In favor of Eisenhower doing all that stuff pretty
I'm sure he was when you got arrested at rally he was also protesting
Eisenhower Disturbed
Shirt
So
Go fuc yourself
Now Alex gets
The talking about
Is legal trouble
His court case
That these legal sanctions that there are applying
Or just because they know they can't win
McKay's
So they're trying to destroy him
That way
Just like I wasn't behave differently that and they can
I don't understand
He's also being sued
Gilmore
Who is a guy who Alex
Defamed after the unite the right
In Charlottesville
And
I believe
Based on this
That there might be some news coming out about that
I think
I think Alex is where there's going to be some bad news and this may be pre-emptive control
The system knows they can't shut us down these lawsuits because they're based
Indian in Bologna show they want the
Process to shut us down
Climbing knots
Virginia
Sandy Hook
Oops banana in in the process of discovery saying we're criminals
Battleborn found embedded on emails we never opened sent to us about Sandy Hook since the suit
Hidden code
Course they got
Put on the news
Alex Jones said child born to the Sandy Hook families
That's the type of stuff
Law enforcement out-of-pocket lawyers
Now there's no doubt the Democratic operative
They're the crooks are the bad people
We got to go defeat
No weapon formed against us shall prosper but
And I've already tried to plant c********* on a slope
I got a call from DC yesterday if that's was run out of and I said yeah this is the word
Mixed up next week out of the
Virginia cash show
Be ready for some really nasty stuff next week
Because they are
Shift
Very pissed
So look forward to Monday product headlines
That's great
What are you doing are we going to get another do position
That'll be great
Agency like
Such
Side spinner that's not good
Because there
Bright
Alex starts rambling about various news headline
And this one caught my fancy
Cuz it's
Very dumb
Juveniles can't be arrested in California if they commit crimes
It's crazy
Is California mountain lions eating everybody children can't be arrested
It's a state you never go to shut up about something
But you desperately want to do
No it you don't care just don't
In September 2018 Governor Jerry Brown signed two bills
Adjusting how children were treated by the courts
One of them Senate Bill 439 made it so except
Cases of murder or rape
12 cannot be prosecuted in court
There's still obviously subject to some kind of
Psychiatric
It's just at the state recognizes that it's probably not cool to treat an eleven-year-old like they're old enough to be exposed to a criminal Jeff
No I think it's a good idea to expose
Children under the age of 12
What's 2
Lawyers in the system that is
Cruel
Yes
I like it the second bill Senate Bill 1391
Try somewhat younger than 16 as an adult
Still be tried for the crime
Central Juvenile Facility instead of an adult prison
If convicted
Justice system already at mechanism
Someplace to hold someone
After they turn 18 for circumstances
Require it
So it's not like these offenders
We'll just be getting free pass if they could a crime
What's 17 / number
This is what Alex has turned into a narrative that you can't arrest minors in California
I think it might be fair
To say that in addition to lying
Alex is also being kind of a racist
According to an article in the Sacramento Bee Jerry Brown said it was a hard choice to sign this bill but you was swayed to sign the bill
Disparity
Part of what these bills aim to do is to work against a trend of criminalizing behaviors and young and on white people
Directions to Mike call
Precocious
Were they
This is part of the conversation surrounding these bills
Assuming Alex knows anything about this
You should know that
Any stops we opposed
The Bells
I hate the bills
What I'm saying is ultimately he either has no idea what he's talking about or he does
And he's lying about bills meant to make the Juvenile Justice
The system more fair and equitable
Neither is
He's an a****** people really don't want
To admit
White people
Really don't want to admit that
Most problems have a massive
Racial element
In the country there are very few problems
The don't have a massive racial inequality
Particularly legal and criminal justice
Something they just do not watch it at all white people but people like Alex
Do not want
Fats Domino
And it's
Because if you start
Pulling that thread then you go all the way back
I can do like the very beginning of the Criminal Just
The system is purely discriminate
Back you have to admit once again.
The United States is a fundamentally
Racist country
So Alex dial starts
Talkin about
How
I don't quite know how to set this up
He believes that there was a source
That
Was aware already knows about
Billion people in the world are suffering
Sure now he can only find
If you can't find that source
I don't even think he can find somebody who has an ID
He starts freaking out about this
It's kind of funny
I told shoveled earlier I was going from memory I don't think three billion people but un says have
Deficiency
I have mental disabilities from it
The latest numbers I've got
National Institute of Health
Really
3 million
First of all
It was from Wikipedia
So that's
Number one
The idd
Sharda Public Health
Children am I
Are the most vulnerable categories
Global scale
Resent the clinical manifestations
Daily food intake
I'm going to go to the Wikipedia entries and see who remove that
Lynx
Government reports
2 billion
And I know we even did shows on that
About a month ago
Wikipedia
Do-it-all pause
Oroville Wikipedia to stab
Megaton bomb
Billions get brain damage
Found it
Zach to the boom operator found it
National Institutes
What is Tiana's phone
So
Again that's a big deal and it's a bigger deal who's going into Wikipedia and removing the entry that said 3 million
First I love the idea
Sherlock Holmes pipe and playing Detective
Wikipedia
I have no idea what he's talking about and honestly it's totally possible he's just missed misremembering something he read on with the
Wikipedia or these embellished the number two
To begin with
It's an
Out-of-date Source or something
Cuz there's a lot of progress It's
But made globally in terms of
Iodine fish
Correct there are serious problems that come from
Including physical and mental disabilities
According to a recent
Report from UNICEF
The number of people suffering
From us do the iodine related
It is probably close to about 2 billion worldwide
However
It's important to understand
Where these two billion people are
People suffering from iodine deficiency are almost
Exclusively in the developing world
Countries that practice salt eliminate almost
In between 1990 and 2000
34 countries achieve the elimination of iodine deficiency through Universal salt
Ionization
This is a very fact
Solution to the problem
And generally the countries where this is the biggest issue or countries that have economic barriers to importing iodized salt
Or I with producing a domestically
Or there's another issue like their war-torn
To the point where implementing these sorts of programs
Enviable
Possible to have like a large disconnected rural areas where
It's somewhat infeasible
I'm sure there are
Several parts of India that ends serious iodine
It's a difficulty but it's many
People
GYN or working towards solving
Vast numbers of people with iodine deficiency
Increase risk for it are in India Pakistan
Sudan and Afghanistan
According to the CDC quote iodine deficiency disorders
Cretinism stillbirth spontaneous abortion
And retarded physical and intellectual development
Have been virtually eliminated
This is important because Alex is only talked about any of this cuz he's trying to sell his iodine
Compelled
And the way you
Pretender
Is Visalia
Statistics
Two billion people worldwide
But the thing is
The people who are iodine deficient or almost
Entirely not a part of the market that Alex is selling to
He's trying to take a
Very serious issue that people in developing countries are struggling with
And that the UN is working to resolve
And he's using it as a prop
To try and convince his audience
The baby there something wrong with them that iodine pills
Consult
This is super abusive marketing
There is a slight decrease in iodine intake in the United States population that experts
Some people who look into the stuff
But that's kind of a part probably due to the sea salt
Trent
Seasalt doesn't generally contain iodine using mostly sea salt
Taking in as much iodine
Use table salt should be doing
Also certain diets of increased in popularity recently like veganism
And those also increase your risk for decreased iodine in
Take based on
The things that would be part of your diet
I find it unlikely that there many vegans
And Alex's audience
Said the solution to the problem is not Alex's pills
Assault
I halfway expected the decrease in America experts are like
And it's all anti-vaxxers again those guys are f****** everything up
It's yourself
So Alex talks about some articles here about
And
I have the responses to both of them
This is such sloppy amateurs Bowl
I was kind of running around here all aggressive during the break I pretty
This makes me angry
By my old folders on iodine and Actuarial Wikipedia
They removed it because there's a lot of
Jonathan Perez retardation a million sufficient nighteye New York Times
Anymore
Mothers
Stop raining
So angry
Controlled and yes
Because the call or talk about the
Text to exterior both axles horses I-90
This is all sales that's all this is man
The first article is talking about China for 1996
The Chinese government only introduced in 1995
High risk of deficient
Since that point iodine deficiency is becoming much smaller
World population
Also when you talk about you it's a gigantic country with the huge population that they all live in
A lot of different locale
China's learned that the different provinces have different
Requirements so in 2018 China announced that they were going to enact
Iodine standard Pentagon local needs
Princeton
Some coastal areas have diets that are higher in iodine rich foods
So their requirements for supplementation would be lower than people in one
And you can end up with like
Some Studies have shown that some of the populations actually getting too much iodine also is
Isn't healthy
Tweaks to the program based on results
Either way I'll dare they
Alex's referring to a
Twenty-four-year-old article
This one's from 1996
Little talk about it
Alex
You know why they do talk about evolving Scituate
Balancing out the iodine diet
That's the Scituate
Address for the article that pregnancies that also makes total sense
When someone is pregnant their dietary needs change
What with another person growing
Inside them
Some estimates are that other iodine intake should increase around 50%
And the American Academy of Pediatrics recommends that people take iodine supplements while pregnant and nursing just
Be safe
It's not a surprise at all that Alex could find an article that iodine and Pregnant
Just doesn't say what used for
Pretending it says
Again
This is all about
Nothing you saying two pics reality
He's trying to create a sense of his listeners that they themselves
Might be iodine deficiency
And it's a grand plot by the globalist
Saddam everyone down
This narrative only exists
To get them to buy his pills
This is deeply abusive marketing
Creating a feeling of lack
Something's wrong with you when it's not
It's just
Gross
Yeah I mean it's it's just mark
That's what it's super abusive
Yeah but that's how we got
Mouthwash
Sure
They invented
And then use floor cleaner but it feels minty
It does
Back
He starts taking
And he decides
To go to
Take call from liver
If you work all we heard liberal call
Love it he called in and had some
Pics of Alex
It is a position about a rod
Rebel days
Now liberal calls back in does he have his own show yet
And I don't think he's going to get one after this
So he calls in and I don't know exactly what point he
Was trying to be
But
Alex
Think what happened is that he forgot that
Who Heat this caller was
I think you forgot that you called in and it's
Judgmental words for Alex
Air Penny hears The Voice
Any remembers
And Alex starts screaming on here and it turns into a
Hensley islamophobic Ranch
Who's Ronaldo longest
New York liberal what is your view on the situation
Alex
I wanted to speak on the run at 2 but then I heard the level of
Nothing I hide nothing I admitted on a friend
I'm scared of people
But the reason why
Good morning Christian why am I bothering
Okay
Brock Lesnar
Tell me I have to figure out
Give me the efficacy of galavant
No I understand Alexa
Can I get a word in edgewise I just wanted to
The answer that
But in any event Alex
Efficacy of
Pagando
Timer for 5 minutes
And I apologize to you
Disgraceful Western man that needs to be given
Salvation and completion by you
I'm going to let you take over
I apologize
Imma stop right now
Man it feels good to go crazy
This is not a person who's okay
That's one of the most stunningly racist things I think I've heard
Yeah
It's big and it's not
To uncommon for Alex you notes it certainly like
But I think what happened is he heard liberals voice
Remember Dosha.
This guy took me to the woodshed
He has to scream over him because he knows he can't let him talk
Then Alex assumes that liberalism Muslim because he's criticizing Alex's
Terrific anti-islam
There's no reason
Like based on the things that
Liberal has said on the show
This is just a performance
Alex is doing this intentionally
Not because he's so overcome by Passion
He's he's you're able to rein it in once time to get to the brakes
It's not so crazy that he starts
Swearing on air
Like this is just disgusting
Piece of s*** person putting on an act
Yeah he might as well put his hands over his ears and wet lalalalalalalalalala
So he comes back
Alex comes back from the break and he does allow liberal to talk
Color eleison his point which I think
It could be summed up as saying there's a there's a reason that there's a tension between Muslims and Christians
When is propaganda
And Alex has a responsibility to his audience
Do a better job covering the topic
Alex admits there are good
Muslims but there's also
Political Islam that's evil
Sou decides what he's going to do is he's going to get up from the desk
Map
He's going to show the spread of Islam on the map
And that's where this are we going to get the Warner Brothers
Song is this
This slip
Is
It entails
Intense
Insane freak out that Alex has that really
Startled
Why was my place
Walk over here
Who is shell people
Animal shelter map of the whole world
About where we were 14
100 years ago
Wealth
I appreciate that sir you weren't still on Wikipedia
Whatever your opinion on Trump
We can all agree that the most
Was the Avalon
Free memes
The most crazy thing is what Alex
He just stopped off
He did and I couldn't
See from the camera angle
Just like
He is such a f****** rage-filled a******
This is so unacceptable if I were working in that studio
No
Be subjected to a boss acting that childishly and frightening Lee in a workspace
Would be terrible
Alex
November
March of
When the Alex gets back he tries to claim that liberals point was that Alex's pretending that Islam is expansion
But it's really Christianity that's expanding
Thanks which wasn't liberal the saying at all
I suspect this is one part Alex just trying to save face but that blow up when you just listen to
And another part of him having no ability to synthesize information
The people are given to a man either way that's some scary s***
Like that that's a that behavior is
He's
On the job
Yeah
I don't know who this new like this boom operator is who doesn't have a name
And I wasn't
Boomer Esiason to not have to deal with it
Unionized
Philosophically I'm against unions
I'm starting to see why
Boom operators 435 local
You know I do
I do
Feelso
F****** broken down by the show any other show if the host walked off
Holy
What is Matt walked off in a huff
Giselle pissed off
Hope you like holyshit
Alex ending in shower
He's barging offset
Ostensibly because no one gave him a handy walk around by
Get so Furious
It's also in the middle of trying to explain how Islam taking over the world
Yeah
Right
You never stop talking
Canceled
Not canceled like in the social medias
It is funny
Bet he exemplifies why
White American men
Should be allowed to do something while at the same time telling people
Islamic date
Should be allowed to do
He also exemplifies why I like
Standards
In media res
Like and why it's good to have a boss because someone should be
Chastising him for that up solution consequence
For this kind of behavior cuz it's not okay
I don't think so according to him
And what's interesting to me is like Alex comes back
He doesn't leave
The show
You're done for
We'll play some do whatever cannot be on the air
Until you called out you have shown yourself
Two gigantic islamophobic rant and this blow-up offset like you car not
In a place whatever
Whatever's going on
Whatever it is
Maybe you're mad about this
Wikipedia iodine she knows maybe you took too many yourself
No one knows
No one cares
For your own sake
You can't be on a
No one does that cuz no one
Conair is really fascinating is he takes
Calls
And no one is like
Are you okay
No one
Treats what just happened on the show
As if it's something
To be concerned about I think they know what I just did
Crazy
That's the appeal
Yeah
So Alex before he gets back to Carl's starts
Nationalized
You know like hey man
I'm just mad about Islam expanding
I really got to emphasize that this is all just
Because he saw two Muslim family families in a hamburger
She gets back to that so everything comes.
Islamism
Basically a male
Offended
My
That little restaurant
Eating food
Anime man
I believe Western Civilization Superior
You know it my wife and daughters didn't do what I said
Says Western Civilization
Women are happy with that either
You know how you don't do that
Like a man
But it doesn't mean
Weird line to draw the left loves that
Watch this in Austin restaurant literally this guy
It's not literally that
It's people eating hamburger
You dumbass hole
Like
He's he's responding as if he just saw a stolen
It dams hamburger
You didn't see it you didn't see anything
You saw people having hamburgers
This is so important
Because
He can pretend all he wants
Betty just has a problem with
These
These critiques
That he has of Islam
But he doesn't
He sees every single person that he identifies as a Muslim
Indicative of the worst
Thing of Islam
Is all Universal
It is
I don't know I don't know what to say it's
It's awful he's an awful awful person
Oh yeah and even then
He revealed his big
Like oh they dominate their women and they make them wear hoods
His criticism is
A sense of scale
Not philosophy of course you need to dominate women
You need to make sure that you can
Control their behaviors
But you don't put a hood on them that's my biggest issue with Islam
Wow
I should tell you
Alex has Steve pieczenik on again
And it's worth
It's just you saying that it was a surgical strike
Everything is fine
It's very Bland and dry
But the thing I think it's notable is it at no point
Everything even talked about
Him being on a couple days ago and it nope
Steve real quick
I understand your feelings on a run
Question you want to talk about
Do you know
Alex Alex doesn't care
Or doesn't even realize
That was
Some of the content that Steve brought to the show
I'm flabbergasted
I have no idea
He did just storm off of the show with no consequence
On Stroop
It's Alex
You know talking about how he's
That's blow ups
Call Michelle
Yeah you would describe it as having Riley still did the show
Alex describes it is
Fun
Don't like going crazy
And if you watched
Actor or that's
Really
Blowing up on
Something I feel like
That was real
That's insane baby
But I do want the dog
Fun because it felt good to run
Yesterday I
Hummingbird
Handsome
Jump around the house and I did it on Ellen Show
Serious subjects
The collars calling thanking me all your great your great know you're great
I want free
Yeah
Where's the majority
Let's come together let's do it
People on TV that take themselves so seriously they don't have some funds
What are you talkin about
You stormed off your f****** now because you're now
Seriously
I'm f******
Real that is behavior
Such a horrible rationalization for his
Petulant outburst
Implicit
I just let myself off the chain just having a little bit of f*** that's what you just cried will then like
No restfully islamophobic ramps
That's how you
Is that how you have fun
I mean
Vegetable
You know what that says about you yeah
Yeah
I mean the place that I
The
The owner of the company was also the boss and he was a giant
At the same way
But even then
That's
That's like
At least you know when to be ashamed of
Did you know
Yeah you can be a petulant child and you can be a f******
Shity person
You own your own business so you get to avoid
Consequences for your actions
But at least be ashamed
Alex is kind of expressing like
Like a little bit of
But he's trying to
Co-op
Anna just
Howie Mandel
How do you trying to rationalize like
So I wanted to do this episode because I wanted to check in on
Evolving
Situation analysis response
Is really just
Aggressive islamophobia
Like it now this is transition
The show is
Is just
Alex freaking out in
And screaming about how bad Islam is
And I don't
No in tireli if that alone would have been worth
Episode
But Alex
Having Zach on
The livestream I think certainly
Makes it
Every time you dropped your
That definitely
That definitely is like
I say go support Dan's Hamburgers
These these are the things to that like really are important
Don't understand
Like
When Alex screams about Islam
Grooming gangs in the UK
And that's important
But I think more
Is understanding that
Him seeing Muslims in public
In places
That are indicative of integration
And like you said being at the mall
The pool supply shop enjoying a nice hamburger meal
Those are the sorts of things that drive him crazy
And lead to disorder that outburst
It's the proof of integrate
If the proof of coexist
Infuriate him
Because
Maybe
Those are indications that we can get along
But everybody can just be fine with each other
We can't handle
Because he wants a holy war
Book of Revelations is never going to happen Dan if we all just like each other all the time
How are we going to get the
Rapture
If everybody just fine
Stop them
Angry bull fight
So
Let's shout out here before
Thank you so much
Ariana thank you so much
What's your name
I'm a policy wonk
Chris next Steven
Journal
Hi Steven
Text Carissa thank you so much
Thank you Carissa
Next tray thank you so much you are now
Ice tray
No I am not
I've definitely never watch Laguna Beach Four Seasons get new trade made hats
He was pretty cool
Trey was like having to take points away from his social conscience
I think we have to give back trays don't know you made hack I'm sorry also had a guy
No but I'm going to have to give you your donation
He also had a friend named Polster
Holster holster
Works for us
There was a bit of a joke running jokes every time poster was on
Naked name would come up on screen would be a different
Busiest excitable guy
Do the Hat
Detroit
Text Katie
Journal policy wonk
Thank you Scott was 1T
Thank you so much
Thanks Lenoir
Colleen
Do you want to have a problem
Thank you very much, and finally
Thank you so much
Business
Money off that heroin
So good
Is freakishly large
We've got a long way to go to
Get back to
But I think if we did much more
Exhaust
There's a balance between exhausting everybody who didn't
To celebrate the people who did
And not celebrating the people who donated and I appreciate everyone's patience
We will get that
We do love
Ghost of You
Totally just only think the people who donate
So let's give a blanket that I wanted doesn't obey appreciate you listening to the show
Will be back but until then we website
We do and we are also on Twitter that also on Twitter
Fighting that go to bed and your lies
Ross on Facebook
We are on Facebook and die if you'd like to download the show you
Go to iTunes
You could leave a review
Donate do the whole thing
Thank you
We love you
Emilio I'm dzx Clark
Stonehenge makes me violent
No big deal
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color