Air Jordan
I have great respect for its knowledge B
Knowledge vype.com
Everybody
Zariah likes around technology Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex
Jones Jordan Jordan
Los Tres
Late but has there ever been a musician whose death
Got to I can't
Ask question because I'm realizing
As I say Jordan
Oka discontinued say Jordana Brewster
Who is in Fast & Furious
I got lost In Fun
Characters the fastest
Fury
Two together Paul Walker's character dies cuz he passed away tragically
That was pretty emotional at was back to your original question
I guess maybe 0db
Yeah yeah probably hit me pretty hard
Amaris probably what
2021 somewhere around there when he passed and you know the last two years of his life were very sad
The end
You know he was
The instrumental part of
Me liking the Wu-Tang Clan I really appreciated his
His aunt
Perspective
I don't know if it's probably not a great dancer but that is I didn't get
Heading to Wu-Tang until after OD
I grew up in middle of nowhere
Small town where everybody was like
Rap music is
It wasn't until I left that
I was like oh that's right Wu-Tang
Yeah
I'm trying to wreck my of course obviously there are people like Bowie or
You know I definitely appreciate
Wasn't as much of an emotional connection is is per se like
My youth
Andrew
The chaoticness of his character and I mean granted his real life
Really matched a lot of
The feelings that I had as a younger person
The explicit drug use test early or B
Surdyke service
Circumstances of life or the old dirty moniker
Things that I could connect to and
Seeing
Yeah I'm dying
Yeah yeah
Alright well
That's my answer well I just realized with dying cuz that died
Hobart
Kind of serious sir
But I just realized that we're in the decade now where every major Rockstar from the seventies is it
Yeah and I think that we've been in that for a good bit now
The 70s hits
50 years exactly from then they all they were all the 2025 when they did it now they're all going to stay
Start dropping like flies
Yeah yeah that is probably true
And forever like Paula White Cain
Is great above a lot of their work
Is a little bit silly like the trees
Susie was a great great great Lyricist and
Sad
Interesting character
Rest in peace Neil Peart
Playing with Buddy Rich
Shut up
Stupid ass B everyone does their
I don't like that kinda
Hubert but I do love
Appreciate
I know a lot about Alex jobs
We are I don't like that kind of humor either and I don't know anything about Alex yet
Sweet I'm so George today we need to take a break from the
Because it's just been too much we've been
We're on like three straight weeks
No cuz we have that Bill Cooper episode next day
But it's been a lot of present-day
Especially lately it's just beginning overwhelming
Weatherby Steve pieczenik coming on and denying the Holocaust
Alex doing
Just outrageously islamophobic
Breakdown of an episode
Hey Jessie got a you got to step back a little bit
I wanted the things that I realized is that in the wake of
All of this stuff happening
In the present-day what are the things
That we really let slip
Is the 2013 Sandy Hook investigation
Sure and I know that you and I've had conversations not on the show about
The feeling that like this is going to go on forever
We are going
To just keep going and Alex is going to stay in this wishy-washy state where he's
Basically saying that there are actors
But not committing to it fully
Right
Is probably not great for us or the show
It doesn't really lead us to where we want to go
Ultimately I said out doing that investigation
Starting on the day of the Sandy Hook shooting
And moving forward
Because I wanted to know what was the
Zach day
That Alex started saying that no one died there they were just actors
And all of that
And like 5 months later we
We still don't have the
Exactly
No but I've also realized in the process of doing it that the question that I was asking doesn't
Right through I felt like there was some Merit
To knowing that again
Exact
Going to go through that Haystack.
Find the needle
And in doing so I realized that the haystack is mostly needles
Yeah that metaphor
You realize that even if Alex is it
Babe
Do you know
Definitively these people are actor
Yeah he is justifying suspicion that there actors by saying that people
Who died or survived the Aurora shooting
So
Though he's not
Directly impugning the experience of these people in Connecticut
People who died at the Aurora shooting
We're Someone's Child 2
Right people who died at the Aurora shooting where other
People's loved ones
He's committing the exact
Text same behavior in relation to another shooting
In order to justify
Suspicion of this shoe
So long as words have meeting
And literary devices
Is R-Truth
He is functionally said
Exactly what we were expecting for some reason
He's not willing
Make that leap
As it relates
The Sandy Hook
At that point ultimately meaning
The same
Disgusting Behavior
Already absolutely
So
Don't care
Alright
Don't along the way it is great
Good that we were able to
To find the time of the Boston bombing
And I think that was probably one of the most Illuminating things for me
Researching Alex
Conspiracy in realty
Time adjusting to information
Crafting things out of thin air
Pretending that the world is
Acting in response
And whatever he's saying oh now they got to adjust the right hand
That kind of thing was really really fascinating
And I'm glad that we were able to
Find that
Not necessarily accidentally but along the way of doing the Sandy Hook investigation
Yeah I think those
A few days were probably some of the most
Exhilarating episode that he's ever like the way that I react
To them seeing him create those
Conspiracy theories in real
Time you could feel
Add so
I want
2 a.m.
The investigate
Quite frankly
I know it's a little bit unsatisfying inasmuch as
We don't
Have
The specific
Day
But I also
I just think
But we will be doing this
Committing to
This
For the next
5 years yeah his episodes
Some of the reception slog
That's I just I want I want to
We got to put a bow on
Got to put a bowl today
About Shelby place
And what I'm going to do is I'm going to jump forward in
And take us to
Mate when
Where Alex Jones
Invites Wolfgang halbig
Onto his show for an interview
Wolfgang halbig
First appeared on
An episode from March
He shows up as a leading school safety security expert
He has his theories but Alex isn't really all of that like
Fully willing to
To jump along with
I don't believe I believe that some people died
Right
Then
On April 20th
Alex released
Best of episode
And included
That interview with Wolfgang halbig knows part of the
The best
That's one of the best
Wow yep there's Sunday transmission
Is revisiting our best interviews
How man I wonder how many potential how many potential lawsuit
That could have been like outside of the statute of limitation
Would actually be pushed back in if
You just went through all of his best of committed on a best of
Leslie
I don't know the answer
That but I do know that eke considered that interview a month later
To be the best
That's gotta suck
If you got interview that year
Look back on there like wow how big made the list ready
Never has it this is your lifespan
Special
So on
Amaze 30
Alex Jones
Has how big back on
On the show
And the reason for this is because how big is
It crashed a Newtown school board me
Oh no
And so they're discussing the aftermath in Fallout
It'll be interesting and we'll get into all of it
Before we do not take a moment to say thank you
People who sign up
Long
Intro
There
Connor Thank you so much
Journal policy
I'm a policy wonk
Patrick
Next next
Bet thank you so much you are now a policy wonk
Crystal
Spelled khris
Tle thank you so much you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Journal biology Wang
Sandro
Thank you so much you and I will probably want
Right now
Second best name I know
Jordana Brewster
Thank you to a couple people who signed up on an elevated level appreciate that very much
So Chris thank you so much you are now at
Hannah thank you so much you are now a technocrat
And John thank you so much
You're now
Heroin
Freakishly large
Thank you so much
Chris
And John Cena and John are now honorary members of the
Conspiracy of Chris's
Abducted along with
You're out there listening and you enjoy the show to like sport we do you can do that but don't your website knowledge feit.com clicking the button
Show
Alright
Indeed May
We're also going to be going over a little bit of September 25th
2014 when how big comes back
Got most of these will be covering
May 13th
Set the stage
Before May 2014 The Mamas & the Papas have just retaken
Pop music
Entirely everybody's really back on that
Let's do it
So here's that Alex is talking about some other kind of news
You planning to cover on this
Last night
What am I going to cover not because there isn't a lot of news
There is just too much of it and it's all just gets crazier
And crazier and more interesting by the minute
Well. It's been discovered found after 500 years of the wreck
The Christopher Columbus Flagship Santa Maria
That's the type of news going to be talkin about here today
From the Chippewa down with the big lake they called
Need to do me
The lake it said no giveaway for today
Skies of November turn blue
With a load of iron ore 26000 tons more than the Edmund Fitzgerald
Used to be a karaoke song am I
Alright I had long instrumental break so I could just yell at the audio
Totally
That's awful
And it's depressing
Oh it's real sad
Is there a Roadhouse karaoke bar one time with Nick
Icaregifts
Naked gifts
And we I was singing The Wreck of the Edmund
And an instrumental breaks I would often proposed social
Raise my glass good many women went down on my boat
Brick
So what I was doing that at this karaoke bar and this lady was in a wheelchair was screaming at me
What do you know about good man
Alright alright that's
That's pretty fantastic
Text Jennifer point I was I was being a prick
Anyway
Alex announces that he's got Wolfgang halbig on the show and I would say that based on those eyes
That he's giving off
He seems like he's okay with how big's.
Eastpointe and consistently
How big
Point has been
No one died
Is all fake
And Alex seems fine with
Guest joining us Wolfgang
How big Pharma state police officer
Runs one of the largest school training safety
The organization said the countries also Middle School principal
Address of the state police
And I was Florida
I'm at the whole point is that
He's under investigation he says looks like Sandy looks totally staged
And we know they've declared State secrets on it bulldoze the school
He win
And I actually turn the cameras off
I speak even a lot of time she'll there acting very
Very
Very suspicious
No they will pull anything off
We're going to get an update from him
So we've got like this
Rationalization if he'll pull off all these other things
They certainly do this
Sure he gives for various
Suspicious
Qualifies
Is very very very very suspicious 85% more suspicious than
Just one very or like what are we dealing with
I mean is it a logarithmic
At this point
How big is a non Quan
He's a known entity
Connecticut guys all about
Board meeting would not be interested engaging with him
Is not
Suspicious
It is almost
The most predictable and absolutely correct
Move for them
So he
Alex talks more about how big going to this press conference
And he seems to take great issue with the fact
An article
I believe discovery
Call Wolfgang halbig a conspiracy
Galaxy YouTube
To take
Offense
At this
National news
They shut down that school board meetings will report that article as well
And I get to that
Is that line Newtown school board shuts down
Conspiracy theorist discovery.com
If you don't believe known certified Liars
Any question Obama saying
There is no $5,000 fee per employee
Who doesn't get ObamaCare
Kicking in in 2015
And many businesses in 2014
If you don't believe Obama when he says a bald-faced lie you're a conspiracy theorist
Speeches you didn't build your small business
He says raising the debt limit doesn't raise the national debt
You say it does raise the national debt your conspiracy theories
If you say table of 2 equals
You're a guitarist
Thought you said that birds fly in the ducks quack your conspiracy dinner team more examples
The exact same thing he's really
Pounding
Yeah it's pretty clear
So I mean if you take what he's
Clearly expressing their AIDS
There
How big is talking
Pure truth
Conspiracy theories
How big does 2 plus 2 equals 4
The only
Conclusion you can draw is
You also the
In this case we know what that is a stand-in for that is
Right
So it's it seems to be every
Everything in Alex's presentation in the
Teasing of this interview that's coming up easement
Without it
Explicitly saying
I believe the same thing he does
It's to say
Are you right
Yeah with the upward everything he says has the tiny little upward inflection at the end so you're like wait is that a statement or question what are you
You doing here
You know and I know
Something interesting
What's going on on this episode here in 2014
That it was absent
From when we were looking
Stephen 2013
And that is Alex does a bit of infomercial and
Oh really coz.
The group is around house
He's not on the show but he has arrived
Okay Alex
Is now selling his brother
I cannot stress
Do you
The fact that I'm under more stress than I've ever been under
And I'm performing better under that stress than I've ever done
And it's undoubtedly and I'll tell the story now
Is it selling for
I ran six miles every other day
I
Lifted weights every other day
Very important and I ate like a pig
I drank as much beer as I wanted to
Went out with the bodies went out
To Stephen all that
Why did you need
You tell me my weekends
And
Look like
Mr. universe or something
Dedicated
I just around that long I might as well just quit working out and just work eighteen hours a day many days for years I will take
18 hours a day
Put olive film
Building on media organization everything
And it worked okay the first two years or so the metabolism slow down I gained 60 lbs
Now I look like Greg
I went up from about 180 lb
About 240 lb
Is the biggest I've ever been
I was about 275 about 56 years ago
But pretty good for 275
Didn't need to say that down to 230 lb
Here's the thing about five years ago I started working out
Swimming 2 miles a day several days a week
2 mi open swim
Began doing 567 mile hikes
Stop clicking stuff but didn't really change my diet as much as I should
Organic
And didn't lose what about 10 lb
Then I did some of the Infowars health.com youngevity stuff
Sr 25 lb or so
But when I got the super male Vitality developed by doctor gribbin
I've lost another
20 lb
And I have more energy
By his own telling of this long
Infomercial pitch
The youngevity products works better
Seems like put the numbers in 2520 I don't know I've no
Dietitian nutritionist. I don't know but that mean the numbers
Right I don't know what it is it easier to lose 25 lb when your 375/20 when your 350
I told you I'm not an expert in anything you need to find out
Look the issue here is that
The show is becoming more of this
There is more it and it's
Noticeable if you jump from the 2013 to do this
And it's
The incorporation of the
These products
Migraine today
Time back when you were looking at the
2013 error there would be
Times when the entire fourth hour
Or when you go into overdrive would be like one of those
Youngevity weirdo by
Some of their their product
Teen Vogue
It's not totally for it
To his program
But there's more
There's more of it
It's noticeable
Yeah so you got this
Vibe going I find his
General tone and demeanor
While telling us
New Superman Vitality to be hilarious and
In the context of
What super male Vitality did to him
That we've seen five years later the ex got a long cogent story with one story line boring boring
Finish it but it's all about the
Same thing you got your good point that is a great point
It's all about the
Same thing as dull as that story was and how many times I thought
Denis daily
I left all this it is because
Full story does lead to be
That's a phenomenon that we rarely get any more
Man that's s*** f*** you up
Stay off supermale
So Alex is doing a bit of teasing
Throughout the show about how he's going
Interview Wolfgang
How big
And
I think if you listen to this you can kind of hear him talking
Himself into
How big is positions
State police officer that runs one of the largest most successful school safety
Training organizations
Sandy Hook I know it's
Flaming was there I just don't know exactly what they say
You know the stories
Top experts Disgaea
Even threatened by the FBI at his house
Now barred from being able to ask questions at school board
I mean they are really and you can see him with the kids going in circles
Going in and out on helicopter shot
Looks like a drill
They might have killed a few real kids in there I don't know
But we know they're having a drill we know they had weird SWAT teams dressed up like the shooters there
Government connections to the
Colorado shooter ladies and gentlemen
Our record was under a top military psychiatrist
I don't even have time to get into it it's coming up I mean
Okay and and they're doing this to come after I got
So I mean you can you can hear that that's basically him repeating some of the things
But he's comfortable with
Yeah it's touchdown seems comfortable with and it leads to him talk
Be able to talk
Midstate
Sticker gun
So he's
He's just chipping away at what it is
He will say
He's already he's at the point where he's like yes it's staged
It's just a matter of
Scale
Did they say everything or did they say stage just the Anderson Cooper interview
What all was
East is chipping away at whatever the resiliency has to jumping off a
Right
To Alex
Starts Meandering a little bit about how there's a slippery slope of political correctness
Going on
Immoral
It's running
And this leads into him
Talkin about
Soros
Is a Nazi collaborator
Great so he's on that point
Here by May 24th
But what's interesting
It's less of that
Although it is fairly in
What's more interesting is that in talking about that
He has a Counterpoint
Of someone else
Who's cool
But everyone thinks it's bad
Let's get Chinese food nearby
If you don't call it the Orient you call it Asia
You don't call it Asia you call it the east
You don't you don't say
African-American now you say this it's just all please you
Will you turn your
Can you give money
Okay
Do you also
Are Nazi collaborator
Like George Soros the famous one and then you get awards from ATL
Even if you fight the Nazis
And the government will send white-supremacist our government controlled after you of your Alex Jones
Reply you're racist
Dwight supremacist after you were proving to be government agents
Arnold Schwarzenegger
Belts Nazi Dalton said that he loves Hitler
But
But if you make a movie about Christ
And make one comment your baited into
Hellboy
School
So we're defending Mel Gibson
That's where we got from all of this kind of galaxy
So yeah
He was baited into it you're a Nazi because your dad has a whole weird anti-semitic thing that you
You bought into clearly for
For 30-plus years
And all the sudden you say it out loud one time and who played it
Repeat it
And it's all because you made a movie about Christ
Great
So Alex leads into is interviewed here with how they
I'm just going to I'm skipping a lot of
Episode
It is
More like that story
It is not great
She gets into the
Interview by listing off a bunch of
Quote unquote
Inconsistency
About the Sandy Hook story
It's important to point out that these are not just in
Consistency
But he's listing that are like
Hey here's some questions
And smokes have
These are Wolfgang halbig talkingpoi
He's saying that this is exact
Likely what happened.
Maybe this
No
Enzo in leading into his interview he's doing
Some Lifting for Wolfgang already
Ladies and gentlemen we have massive breaking news here
Dealing with the first amendment in this country
If you look at the situation in Connecticut with the Sandy Hook shooting
That were used to collectively put guilt on the American people
Gun owners collectively had murdered
A bunch of little children Elementary School you can see it was a psyop
Come out that Bloomberg put out emails the day before
Get ready with our Twitter with our media
Have a big push against the next 24 hours
Very suspicious
Then you got the local or Regional SWAT team people hiding out in the woods
In the same outfits as opposed to Shooter
You got the whole story changing the most incriminating as you got the helicopter footage
Of the of the people with their hands up coming out of school
Emilia in the evacuation
Hours Everett supposed to be happening
Going in circles in and out of the school
Going in circles
Declared State secrets
The photos the video
There's weird Anderson Cooper video where he claims he's there on the ground of the Town Square in
He turns bigger than Dallas and it's a green screen
He's shimmering around the edges his nose disappear
You can see
Flowers and things blowing in the wind and then they do it again it's the same footage being looked behind them
I mean
I don't know what happened there
But I know Anderson Cooper's admittedly member of the Central Intelligence Agency
And they send him out on the dicenzo pieces
All this stuff is these things that now Alex is like wow
Yeah I mean of course it's not a blue screen
Of course
You know when
Confronted with like
What is this footage
You say it's people walking
The students walking in circular
Well yeah I guess it's not
Like all of these things are things that he's now just
Of course
Not standing by
Very serious and very proven
I'm here in May 2014
Macy's leading into this interview
Anza
I mean it's that I mean yeah sure he said he was he was just having debates while saying that
Very true
Thing that happened
Yeah
And the other thing that he's doing in addition to
Establishing
The talking points of Wolfgang halbig before actually getting into the interview which
I mean that gives
Him a cakewalk basically
For this interview
He also Alex does
He goes out of his way
To establish
Credibility
Wolfgang
In order to frame this interview as
An Intrepid
Investigator going out to dig out the
Truth
As opposed to it being like well
This guy has questions
Is there validity to them
That's not what he's doing
He's presenting him as a
The hero
He's not a kooky guy
Him asking questions last year
Just lost a lot of business for the system
But he doesn't care
I'm guessing
I know how the system works I don't know that I'll ask him out a minute
Buddy's exact
Who goes against his own interest
Monetarily
To go out and tell the truth now here's the bombshell news
This is Jen discovery.com
That's people that don't believe the official story
So that's
Let me we got it again he's not he's just doesn't believe the stories of true known liars and just ask question
Wolfgang halbig and his crew were not just asking
Questions at that Newtown school board meeting in May 2014
They were going there as part of a rally for their Sandy Hook
Conspiracy not
An article in the Connecticut Post
Describes the sort of behavior
He was engaged
Quote
A half-hour before the meeting started how big's followers rallied in front of the municipal center
What man dressed as in a revolutionary war-era uniform wave to Hanging f
Fuji of Governor dannel Malloy
That's the sort of s*** they were doing
That doesn't sound exactly like just asking
I feel like asking questions is a maybe just one step below hanging things in effigy
Yeah so at me even then it's it's a close
Close
It's still not there
The day prior they drop by the offices of the United Way of Western Connecticut demanding records of how charity fund
When's the donations
Only to be told that all that information is already public
They don't need to ask for it I can just go find it very easily
It it look me in the eyes when you lie to me
Interesting leave that article goes on to say quote
Seven members of the group
Some carrying
Still in video cameras
Then visited the offices of the news-times
Asking to meet with a reporter
A news-times editor met with one member of the group who asked for a story about their visit
To the United Way
But the request was denied
These people were engaged in a publicity
Restocked and their Acts
Pretty well spell that out
There's really no other explanation
For asking the newspaper to write an article about how you went to the United Way demanding records you can
Easily find online
The same could be said of how big the pier into the board
The Connecticut Post describes his group of being about a dozen or so people who each got three minutes to ask questions before
They didn't get what they wanted out of the meeting
Quote board members refused to take the bait
Remaining silent
Through presentations by how big
Taken several of his supporters
Who followed him to the micro
The Connecticut Post describes the audience as quote
Paxful but thoroughly discussed
The reality is that this was a mentally unwell man trying to pull off an explosive poop list
Restart along with a small group of follow
Look for someone like Alex
This is suspicious
This is stonewalling
And probably evidence
The cover-up going on
According to the New York Magazine after the school board meeting
Lenny Pozner emailed how big request
Into talk
An associate sent a reply saying quote
Wolfgang does not wish to speak with you unless you exhume Noah's body
And prove to the world you lost your son
These are sick
F****** people were talking to
No
Yeah I mean I can appropriate response to say to that
Note
Go away for good
Also
An important point to bring up is that on May 9th
Infowars released a special report
Recorded in Newtown
The video was Infowars reporter Danville.
Also known as the Kraken
Interviewing Wolfgang halbig
Make outside the school board meet
It's unclear if the video they show of Wolfgang addressing the board was actually shot by badonde himself
But it's presented with an a
Infowars watermark
Emma Campbell work
Is not good
So it seems like
This is an important
Point
Wolfgang how big was trying to drum up publicity
He and his group tried to get the news-times
To cover their activities that no one took
Debate he tried to antagonize the school board members and they only gave him respectfully silent discussed
But Infowars was not only happy to cover his filthy s***
They were there
Without him
This amplify
Application
It probably would have just been in
A****** asking
Listen to the meeting to a disapproving audience
Dan badonde
Who Alex has repeatedly described as an employee
And someone Alex
Cenzon
Who's using an Infowars Mike for the interview who clearly identifies himself as an Infowars reporter in his sign-off
Is going out of his way to make this a story
They're working
Hard to frame this is a heroic
Intrepid investigative running up
Into a conspiratorial Stonewall in the form of this board
The point is this is not report
This is not hearing both sides of an issue
This is a group
Infowars
Masquerading as a news Outlet in service of helping
People like wolf
Ben Helbig
Disseminate their theories
This is
Clear Behavior
At this point
This is this
Would like a live broadcast version of project veritas
It's it's they go in there
A fuk up
Regular
People day
Not doing anything but it's coronavirus in order to broadcast it and lie about
So days before the episode they were listening to now they put out the Special Report with Dan Fidelity was there with with
Wolfgang and now Alex's
Reporting on the sort of dramas
Surrounding Wolfgang not being allowed to
At this this board meeting
It's integral
You can see the way that
There's almost like
Alex threw Dan Vaden
Is causing trouble with the infant
Mirror of his
Sitting in the studio as there is a
Professional
Is
Talkin about the Fallout of
Blue degrees
Who's covering
Godzilla
Tokyo won't allow Godzilla into ask them questions Woods
Suspicious is going on here
The Kraken
I think we know
So they talked about this trip
The United Way
And I think it's just f***
Hilarious when you realize
The Dynamics
So here's the headline School Board shuts down
Conspiracy theorist
And Wolfgang Meghan documentary said he'll send us the raw footage
As soon as it gets here my copies on memory stick or whatever
We will get a special report out
Does it need to be seen
Of them
Please shut down the school board then trying to go to United Way and others
So
Do you understand what's going on here
Wolfgang and his group tried to get a real newspaper
To cover their trip to the United Way
Knock knock
You tells Alex and Alex
Oh my God this is red meat
Why did he go to Alex first
I mean he probably talked about dondi
While he was there I'm sure there was
A plan to do both
Varying
Standard
White people work
Ride news-times
Now get out of here this is
Nothing Alex
This is the biggest beetle in the world
Yeah we can
McQueen office if you're how big do you you're thinking
Well I've already got Alex on the back burner for
For sure
So why not take a shot if I were you
A real news Outlet
Yeah
So
How big gets
To talkin and
He expresses that
He doesn't want to be
Jessie
I'm sort of a crystallizing moment
Of why
He's on the warpath
Understand
I want to be doing this absolutely not I'm retired
Gators not come to my home
For Christmas
Newtown never heard nobody would have ever heard of me
We go back to that time
Connecticut Freedom of Information request
Simple questions
Any of those parents who supposedly lost a child
This is interesting and honestly if I were Alex and I heard that I would take it as a sign that maybe
Is a little overly personally involved here
Sounds like he's mad about the police showing up at his house Alicia showed up at my house so now I'm going to dedicate my
I like to harassing victims of a tree
Yeah
You saying that if the police hadn't knocked on his door he wouldn't have gone on this investigation
Alex can hear that and think
Yeah
All he was doing was sending out legal and legitimate foia request in the police show up
That's a clear sign they want to silence him
However that is not the reality
According to a piece in the New York Magazine intelligent
Two Florida police officers pay to visit
How big do quote relay a message from Police in Connecticut
But he risks
Being charged with harassment
He continued contact
People in newt
This was not the result of him sending out for
It was because he was doing things like sending Sally Cox the school nurse at Sandy Hook who survived the
The shooting by hiding in a closet
A message saying quote
Why close your eyes when you seen
Blood before you are a nurse
By any standard that sort of message being sent by a
Complete stranger who's bent on denying a deeply traumatic event
That you lived through
That counts as harassment
So by my metrics Wolfgang is Super Lucky
But he just got a polite visit
It was a warning
From the police
But Optics are everything
So this visit
Please
It played a big role in legitimizing Wolfgang in the eyes of the
Conspiracy world
His work is so dangerous that
They're sending cops into
Intimidating
It's such b*******
But that's the way the stuff works
And Alex's buying Intuit
Completely
Does he not know what a foia request
Does he think that a foia request is just like as long as long as you stay at the
The top of it like deer foil
And then you said you tell the nurse that she
She seemed blood before into
She's lying so like
Just like with United Way like dear foil United Way you send me these documents are okay I think he doesn't
Recognize that there is like a processing rules with Toya and it just me cuz it means that I have
A free access to all information
Information
That might be the misunderstanding
So how big is convinced that the United Way is skimming money because they wouldn't talk to him
Somebody want to visit or something
People are getting rich
Bye
Giving money
Probably true for literally ever
Well I don't care too much
About that
Rebuttal that you're making
Because it leads somewhere deeply disturbing
Nearest him to Lang's
Amtrak to point out that Alex not only doesn't push back on this
It kind of supports it
Can I take when you look at the amount of money that has been poured into Sandy Hook in Newtown
Old stores that do United Way Western Connecticut to actually
You saw that advertised three days before the shooting
Money three days before the shooting and I think the big red flag is the kinetic
Attorney general's report
Want to talk about that Wolfgang Seth area and end
All-Star today before as well I mean they were licking their left shoulder right back
This is Hardcore information this could bring them down post-hardcore information this isn't opinion
Just discussed
Hardcore animation
This is hardcore
No that is an issue
As far as information goes that would make it more hardcore I suppose
So the United Way is up to no good
According to how big your auntie gets
Listen to a specific about it
Is particularly
Disgusting on his
Why are you saying another way of showing portent
What are the biggest Smoking Gun cuz I know you're inside this investigation but
For folks out there what are the red flags
Looking at 29 million dollars you got to United Way Sandy Hook promise and there are 39
Community nonprofit organizations within Newtown
Animal shelter in Newtown Sandy Hook
Animal shelter have to do
Can you sing a motive for the locals to go along with the fraud is money I get that
Absolutely
If Wolfgang halbig or Alex Jones were sincere actors in this they would point out that the reason some Sandy Hook related donation
Animal Sanctuary
Is because it was being built in the memory of one of the children who died in the shooting
Roman mnn article published on January
24th 2013 long before this episode
Quote the family one of the students killed during the Sandy Hook Elementary School shooting is asking people to donate money
Need to build a new animal sanctuary in her name
Jenny and Matt Hubbard's daughter Katherine died in the shooting and was very passionate about animal
So they decided a good way to honor her memory was to
Create an animal rescue and welfare center in her name
The reason that the money may have flowed through the Animal Center the existing animal organization in Newtown
Is it they were associated with
Project
They had an infrastructure but they didn't have a shelter
Which was part of this A Hubbard plan
Somebody was meant to help
The VP the vice-president of the animal center Harmony Verna made a statement
This Sanctuary will be a place where neglected abused or homeless animals can get a second chance
Fitlife a place for children and adults to connect with animals in the natural world
Animals have an amazing
Capacity to love
Heal the human spirit
We hope Katherine will thing
The most beautiful place
It's on Earth
In 2014 kinetic
It conveyed some land across 34 acres to be the home for this new Animal Sanctuary
Which is
Continuing construction to this point
It's a huge project to that's. Really
Particularly surprising
It hasn't fully been
Completed yet
There's no reason for Wolfgang halbig did not know this
And Alex's responsibility
To not passively let this dude lie
About grieving parents trying to memorialize their daughter with an animal sanctuary
F*** both of these dudes
It is super
Yeah man it's been awhile since we've done 230
18 sidelight like when we were when we were doing bat both of
Come back and forth you know
As acclimated
22 differ
Types of monkeys
Yeah yeah and then I kind of let
2013 go after a while we haven't done it now I'm right back to it
Jesus
I hope many different ways can you beat
Disgusting monster
You can't be in the present and we and be like all this
Disgusting monster is doing s***
Like that and then go in the
And find a completely different level of disrespect
Stopped Wolfgang halbig is absolutely no
Excuse to present this information
There is a very easy
Accessible explanation for why
An animal sanctuary
Is getting some of the Sandy Hook donate
That makes total sense
He has a responsibility to know it and the fact that he doesn't
And it presents himself as an investigator
That leads me to the conclusion
You consciously omitting this information
I guess the other option is lying and those
And if you're if you were former State cop I believe you're doing both at all the time
And for Alex
Doesn't work
Work that hard
So
The fact that he
He doesn't know this
Doesn't have this information ready to robot
Wolfgang
Is on Fortune
He should
I don't think
I don't think he would
Use that information
Probably not
Lesson indication that Alex is lying
And boring indication that he's not equipped to have these conversation at
Unless the point of a conversation is to
Passively allow
And help
Answer that
For money or what's going on
Hear that hearing both sides
Okay guess if you hear both sides or something and one of them is a lie and then you don't actually even really here
Hear the other side
I said what are you doing
I got nothing really sore bad he's a f****** bad
So I
I posit that if you listen
This fool and review one of the things that you walk away with his kind of that conclusion
This is not hearing him out this
Do not ask me questions
It is
Alex trying to direct
Wolfgang in such a way
The talking points that our desire to get out
Got out
Clearly there was a stand down
Website but I saw that
The same people
Helicopters that look like a fake Grill what about the guy in the woods
What about me just go to those points
So what you have is Alex
Trying to serve up
These are the talking point
It's that are kind of safe
For the audience at this point
So what do you build from there
Build your credibility in rapport with the audience
On these
Topics and and endpoint
That we've all become accustomed
Show me the water too hot yet
There's that kind of a vibe
But get with the program
Not like it it's Alex
He's checking anything like that he's doing is like there's a way
And this is the way to do it
Yeah yeah that's this is
This is
LeBron and Anthony Davis in a pick-and-roll
Is an alley-oop
I'm going to wind up slam dunk
So
Alex
I hate this clip
More than I hate many other
Okay
Because the reality is in the world
You know the real one
The ship pile that we calls the reality is that Wolfgang's Behavior
Where is causing
A lot
Of damage
Emotional
And otherwise
It's too,
To the survivors
Victims families
In this clip Alex allows Wolfgang
To complain
That he is being threatened
Andy's
Your last wolf came to present himself as the victim in this entire situation
That's all the time I got some crazy people out there
16 simple questions and I wouldn't even be talking today it's it's
Wolfgang halbig hit his harassment behind this
Thin veneer
Of having 16
Supposedly unanswered questions which
If answered
You shut up
Naturally some of the questions are unanswerable
Or meaningless
Spore already or perhaps most relevant Lee
None of his f****** busy
Question 12 for example is quote
Why did the parents of two children who died at the Danbury Hospital will not allow their children to donate their organs
Text other children waiting for the gift of life
Go fuc yourself yeah that's a good one if that's one of the questions that makes your toe
Top 16 that you base this
Is conspiracy
Organ donation is a great thing
But it's a choice
I have no idea if he's parents
Did or did not donate their children's organs
I didn't look into it because honestly I don't think I have any right to know that
Nor do I think it has any relevance
The question is meant to imply
The beef cube
Did not exist to begin with
Which is why their parents couldn't own a
Their organs
This is not a good face question
Insinuation
It's an accusation
And no answer would
Ever satisfy someone like Alba
Imagine these parents saying
Something like we didn't want to make that decision on behalf of our child
Organ donation
Is an individual's choice
And we didn't know what their wishes would have
Have been
Do you think how big would stop
Asking the question at that point because I think
Keep f****** wouldn't
Probably not that's very doubt
Yeah that that very reasonable explanation
Probably mad that I made up that explanation I have no idea who the parents.
The explanation could just be like hey man we were in a f****** days
How about go fuc
Yourself how about that
Why didn't all this s*** happen because what
What do you think
Bright
Any answer is not going to satisfy the answers of the
Excuse for the behavior
Question number 13 is quote what happened to the 500 children and 60 School staff members from Sandy Hook Elementary on December
That's an insanely broad question with approximately 560 different answers
If he actually cared there's plenty of accounts that you can find regarding people
Experiences that day
But he does not care
That's the point
These questions were Shield that Wolfgang halbig used to deflect criticism
His behavior was
Repulsive
When he was
You get told that he's hurting people you just Trot out this list
Questions that no one will answer
And then he gets to continue
Pretending he's the heroic figure in this
This is what people do why don't I know what her favorite flavor of ice cream
And then if you answer that you're like what why don't I know what her second favorite flavor of ice cream is this is this is
It doesn't matter
It's Turtles all the way down
That's what it is this is this is what you do you
Engage in this harassment campaign where you're doing things like emailing the school nurse
Nonsense b******* right and then people would like a why you doing this
That's Gabby
Defense mechanism
You see it
On
The part of
These more
I don't know I don't know what the right word is my mind Ultra
It's between like out there and dangerous conspiracy
Little baby girls like you
You just answer the question
I'll shut up
Now you won't
Answer the question
Which justifies
Everything I do
Right
Set
Yeah
Like
It's like the stand-your-ground
Defense for
Conspiracy theory
Like it doesn't matter what you ask or what you do
It is always
Is there doing it on the Deep
Yeah I'm only doing this in response
To be attacked that you've brought
On me
So good.
Yeah
So Wolfgang start
Disseminating
I'm talking point
It's about how the school was a tux
Waste dump
Basically
Which Alex would pick up later
And definitely run with
Yeah
So when you look at the school itself
I wanted to talk to the
Here's what they didn't realize they put it in their own newspaper before they
Sandy Hook
Groundwater is
Connecticut Law requires
Notified
Children
A that moved into Newtown in 2009
That stuff is all bulshit
But Wolfgang is pushing towards here is that these parents would never enroll their kids to go to a school like that thought they must
Not of this there were no kids enrolled
Open Sandy Hook
In reality you can find copies of the schools inspection reports
2011 a year prior to the shooting
And learned they were in compliance
So the epa's indoor air quality rules
Further you can find that asbestos is list
It is not a problem
The air quality is given to three on a scale of one to
Before
There's no evidence for any of the stuff that Alex is letting Wolfgang
How big
Mega circuits
This is just really sloppy horrible shape
Okay I've got a I've got a solution
Alright
Let's not rip we can't restrict the
The speech
What we should do
You have to get a license
If you want to go on
Public meat
You got to get a license
How big
You got to get a life
Maybe it takes 5 minutes just
Answer a few simple questions
Baby just one
Did Sandy Hook happen
Can you get your
To go on
TV or radio or whatever you do by Alex impression that would have a chilling effect
If it has a chilling effect on people who disbelieve this should be chilled
So Alex asked
Point Blank
The how big
Do you believe
Happened
And Alex knows
What Wolfgang Police hat
So that's not a question
I would like you to tell my audience
What happened
That is a set up exactly how big to say what he thinks happened
Now
Wow he's asking this question
That he knows the answer to
He goes out of his way to salute
And build up
How great
Wolfgang halbig is
Which you would
Do
If you were crying credibility whatever answer you know
What do you think really happened at Sandy Hook
People can see your 16 questions at Sandy Hook Justice
Dot-com
Salute Your your will
Tagalog there in at 8 police cars blocking tonight away and
School Board
At the commission
But bottom line what are you is a
Almost 40 years investigating police officer you name it
What do you think's Happening Here
I can tell you
Children teachers did not die on December 14th
That's I mean
You wouldn't do that unless you wanted that
Point to be made by someone you're presenting as credible
Gyro
You salute his will
That's that's as good as Alex saying it himself
Absolutely
So they get back to talking about the United Way
And how evil it is sure
And things get a little silly
Nobody ever
More than half the money goes to the executive
A good charity is the Salvation Army
Are they
Salvation Army is not even one of them
9 nonprofits
That's right it's always the same players
I don't want to go off on a Jag here speculating about why someone like Alex might be in favor of the Salvation Army but I think it might be
Baby puzzle
Put that together yourself
Instead I'll prefer to reach you from an article published on December 19th 2012
Just five days after the shooting
Quote
The Salvation Army being part of the community is provided food in
Support to the people of Newtown Connecticut
After 26 people including 20 children lost their lives
Pentagon attack
Sandy Hook Elementary School
This article is posted on the Salvation Army's website
They sent out mobile food unit
State Health Services
Is they had a representative who appeared with President Obama at a vigil for the victims
They even ordered the victims
Isn't that yours world record bell ringing
We're after reading those bells of theirs for 80 hours straight they held a quote
27 minute long moment of Silent ringing
Directions Nuys each of those lost
That day
Anyway I have no idea what these assholes mean by not involved
Put my two cents in here it's a the Salvation Army
Was very involved
In the response
These guys are
Talkingshit there's just no real
Now there's just no accepted
Just can't win
It doesn't matter
So the interview ends
And Wolfgang is trying to so-so
Conspiratorial
Nature2
An event
That happened
That is that one police station
Found another police station
I was like hey
Wolfgang and his guys are coming around
Which I don't think
Is it all I think if I were, I probably do that too
Fly out yourself one of those
Cheap
It also ends
Ends with Alex praising
Walker from Danbury over to the Newtown Police Department
Police chief Michael Kehoe
Danbury had already notified the police chief and Newtown that we were coming
They're all working together it's a cover-up no doubt well they better watch it
Come back and play the report
That we put together and Scott your spirit your comment
Powerful information to the school board
Thank you for the work that your dealings her will continue to track everything you're up to
I God bless you
Okay
Wolfgang halbig ladies and gentlemen we got his website up on screen of her radio
Listeners
It's just really important for you to go and visit
The site will put that
On screen
Really important
Did you go visit at
So Alex
Goes to
He gets done with the interview with how big
And he starts ruminating
On
Did the nature of Sandy Hook a little bit
And I think you'll see
Familiarity
Here in terms of
Alex's tone
He's he's doing a bit of Hedge
While still at the same time being like
It's fake
Blue screens it's fake
Again we don't know what's going on
He goes further and says it's just completely fake I don't know
Laughing
I mean it's ridiculous
Started laughing and I mean like laughing
When the state police when they're giving press conferences I mean it just is the fakest thing
Change the $3 bill
Fakest things in the $3 bill
Real quick question
If
He is
Buy if he say well we don't know what happened
Then that means
He believes there's a possibility
That
People did die
Right right
He is mocking somebody
Tears
Possibility that they are real
Now don't you think if you thought there was a possibility
That's
It was somebody who would
The last thing you would do
Is make
Fun of the way they
Even if that was a 1% I probably would err on the side of not doing that
Cancel it was real
You still wouldn't make fun of
There
Turn off
Chances are
The only way you would do that is if you were one hundred percent sure that it
Yeah
One of the two
What are the things
Like listening to this interview really crystallized
Stormy is alike
After he gets done talking with how big
He sounds fairly similar to how he was
In most of the time they were listening to in 2013
It's like this is all fake
Who knows what happened what happened
Made me realize that there is
He's not really a discernible difference
Between
This behavior that I find
Incredibly important
In terms of him
Helping
And pushing Wolfgang's narrative
And how Alex was almost the entire time
In the same way that I realized
Howard
Little it matter
The specific day
Who first sputtered their actors
Doesn't
Matter
If he is literally saying
And asked if all of his behavior is pointing people intentionally towards X
And I think that he's been doing that pretty consistently through
Is is covered
So
Yeah I suppose if the Practical effects of what you're saying our ident
It's a call to the Practical effect
Text of what you
Of what people are accusing you of saying
It doesn't really matter
It's a In-N-Out semantical different
Exactly
And so the last whip here from the 13th is Alex
Expressing
Globalist
Would fake
Nothing like this which is just to be like
Possible
So you should believe this very credible guy I just had on
Pictures of government
Caught secretly sterilizing hundred thousands of Americans
The government caught
Secret medical experiments on blacks whites from the Appalachians to
Georgia
Northern California to Texas
These are global
Of course they would say something like this guitar gun of course they would
That's not
Fair that's not fair yes the government is f****** evil I'm on your
Dino don't make
Make it bulshit let's let's do something about the FBI tried to Blackmail Martin Luther King jr.
Yes the government is f****** evil but don't use
Denies Andy hookman
Right don't do that
So
It's a cheap Patricia yeah I'm so mad
God dammit
So Wolfgang comes
Back on September 25th
Alex has him back on
In 2014
And the reason for this
That someone has uncovered that the FBI crime statistics
Artistics
List
0 murders
For the city of Newtown
The reason for this it was
Is there this is just a skeptic
Is the jury was a jurisdictional issues so it was
Not listed as murders in
In the city it was a state
Issue
It's very easy to get to
To the bottom of this
But Alex
I think is
Is suede
By this
And then give us what happened you're doing that to gation and then let's talk about
Important
Can we get a response from the FBI thank you looking for joining us
Do you know I did get a response I called in New Haven
And their responses well baby in the ass by the Connecticut
Put those numbers on their data sheet
State Police
Call the turd
This is important because they already have access to the information
That explains
Spell and instead of that's why
Alex has
Wolfgang on to spin it
This isn't
Looking at the
The fact
This isn't looking at
The the the
Is this suspicious
Or is it not
It's saying this
Here is the guy I'm going to have on as my expert somebody believes
If this whole thing was fake
Idiots not what you would do if you're hearing both sides
What you would do if you were desperately craving
A way that you could justify
Being like this guy being like wolf
And I think that FBI statistics thing is probably as good as Alex
Could get you know like to hear is
The SBI
They say zero
Therefore no one.
And
You would even though you just spent the last segment telling us all about how the government and the FBI would lie to us
No
With no compunction they lied about everything
Yeah it seems like people like Alex do that sort of thing a lot
The Deep State always lies
Except when they help me out
The interesting thing is like you here
Wolfgang be clearly aware
Of what the dynamic is here why that number 10
And he's like his
Response to it is come on
And Alex laughs and that's good enough
That's good enough
Stay up all right moving on that's pretty fun
That shitt
Address
Trope in every movie that the FBI and the state cops
Get into a fight
Every time
Eyebright
It's a whole thing
So in order to have
How big on and this is new
Sort of way because I think Alex is now
Onboard or at least indicating that he's getting on board with
No one died thing
He now needs
To justify that in the internal Universe of info
And one of the best ways to do that is to rely on
Trusted source
Dr. Steve pieczenik
He's a Jack Ryan character Kombat
Situations at least 10 times
These are Heavy Hitters
Psychological warfare
Are the CIA basically in the Pentagon
From the state
Totally Above It
So it's so what you have here is Alex has
Steve pieczenik we at this point
And now again
Apparently
Thanks is the most credible person in the world everything old is New Again
Might be saying some wild out the
Steve pieczenik
Above the military or
Or whatever who cares
He said
Day one
That no one died
And so maybe we were late
To pick up on this maybe we were exercising
Too much caution
I knew it stunk I mean why would Anderson Cooper turn it be a green screen
His nose disappear
Why would they have kids going in and coming out clearly stayed
I just didn't
Rihanna
I mean this stinks to high heaven
I just all I hear is Alex using the exact same
Yep from ever but now with the conclusion that no one died
Great all I hear is
Alex losing all of his
That's what I'm that's what I'm that's where my head is going now whenever we're listening to this
Truly
Disastrous stuff my head is just going to him Bruno
Anylist in the gutter
So we get back to these
16 Quest
And you can
Can clearly see
How this
Allegation that these questions aren't answered is used as a cudgel
And for 15 months Alex refuses to call me back the refuse to answer the question
I spent over $15,000 trying to get for your request answer
PS1
Not one response to shut you up
Don't you just
I'll go away
They just answer these questions
You Google your answer
Right I'm positive that a lot of the people
Probably would have answered his calls at the beginning
And I bet
Because of his behavior
I'm not going to talk to
To the sky
I'm guessing
I can't speak for the people who received his his calls and emails
But I would assume that a lot of icono
I know what's up
Up here no
Not engaged
And he
Fruits that is like a they are too afraid
Answer my question
Optics
This is what's important
You're putting on
He's acting like a child
He's acting like a chat the first time but a child ask
See the question you like
This is the answer to that question let me I'll just take you through real slowly and then
What about this
No but what about this
So you like your f****** child get out of
That's the conspiracy strategy
So Alex is like he's continuing his consists
Infrared
Benny's going
Far out of his way to present
How How big is
The best
Yes coming out this is cut into your business
National experts
You see the truth
Didn't get you blackballed of God.
Yeah
Didn't get your blackballed this guy cuz you're standing up
But telling the truth
And me tell you
Look man
Anybody
Anybody can
You come out just say whatever they want
But this is a man
The Great
Perfect reputation
Who's come out
He's risked his livelihood in order to give you all the truth
I should tell you that prior to
To becoming the Sandy Hook
Conspiracy theory World Center
Wolfgang halbig was working on a movie about the founding fathers
Traveling in
Into the present day
In uncovering the grand
Conspiracy
Into the process of trying to write this movie
He tweeted at Jimmy Fallon
Trying to get help with getting his project off the ground
Sterling Prudential
That did get him blackballed with
But that was what did it.
So I mean I guess this sort of like
Trying to break in
Hollywood aspect of his
His career
Deserted missing
From Alex's
Equation
Little bit yeah
But otherwise perfect Witness
He was a principal one time in Florida
That is one thing that is fair like he does
From everything I've been able to tell Jazz have some
History in
It might be a little more sordid
It's very difficult
To the bottom of some of that stuff
It does appear that he did work
In schools
And s*** but
It's irrelevant bad on this Behavior
Yeah you know
Now
Sure
So this
The Great Piece of foreshadow
For Alex's present day
This is a clip that makes
If I'm wrong I hope they sue me and I get all my money
Actually in 1 Clipper from an interview I didn't
Take clips from
Because he's a naturalized citizen
He came from Germany
He does say
But if I'm wrong
I will renounce my citizenship
Check
No cuz he still thinks he's right
Dammit
But that was a pretty bold.
The Wolfgang
Complaining about how
The released
Information about the
Shooting but it was a gigantic amount of information
Right right he had some complaints about that and I think this is
F****** hilarious
Alex's respond
And Stephen sedensky the Dead
Danbury State's Attorney
You'll spend the rest of your life trying to read it to try to understand it surely that's a tactic in depositions is a dump so much
People that can
Oh is that right Alex
Is that how you said to her
Super how that accidentally lied to Skaters finding a child Porta nosey
Play one good deposition deserves another repair
This is just an indicator
He's keenly aware he said so this is a strategy the people employed
And
He doesn't like it when they're doing it but you was
Happy to employ himself course
If he doesn't do it then they're going to do
And if they do it well then obviously
He has to
So even if they don't do it they might do it so he's got to do it
The update
Makes perfect sense
Yeah
So Alex seems to be pretty much on the hook
Westside
With Wolfgang because of this
This FBI
Statistic
But he has one sticking
And he needs to get over that
And I think you guys are pretty
Pretty easy automatically do most
And I guess they just picked a group of State Police and others that they knew they had under their control compromised
I don't know about Kroger
Pro gun controllers fellow Travelers
I mean that's the only sticking point
Is the criminal operation
Historically it happens it happens
That was quick
That's my only stick
Point is how impossible it is to get this many people doing it
But it happens
My sticking point is how almost universally everyone who's around there is on the same
Same page as me and my crazy friend Wolfgang
Against
And that stuff because it's almost like everyone disagrees with
With me but that happens
Yeah that's true
That's not I could dwell on that
Or I could treat myself to ice cream
So this is the last clip but I have from the September 28th interview and
It's Wolfgang saying that he wants to Alex
To be there in court
Without
You're looking at it the other way
He's talking about when he sticks it through the
And
Alex
I want you to look at the
And you're going to be amazing
All of your listener
I mean you're a great voice out there but you need to be apart of
Being a part of that room in the deposition you'll be amazed
How long until you do this lawsuit
Well it depends on the phone that gives attorneys one you know money's up front I'm already spend 15,000
I don't care what I'm going to I'm going to finish this
They shouldn't come to my house
I'm not going to stop.
They should not come to my house and shouldn't have threatened me right before you scared my family
It just seems like even
Through his own telling of so much of this this is
Personal and Petty
He feels
Offended that the
Police game and was
Hey man
You sent
Fucken email
Do people like that school nurse
That's harassing people you need to stop or else
Something you know you might get charged
Do something you like
Someone might press charges
That turns into a years-long quest
That hurts
Tons and tons of people
Cuz
Yeah
Don't know why
How big is picture needs to be in an
Text-to-voice did buy my own petard
Like that is
You're going to love being in these depositions
Wolf
Your router does not love it right now
So I don't know I think we end this 2013
Now in 2014
Investigation with a little bit of a
No it's a little if it's mildly unsatisfying
Because I don't think
Vets
We can't necessarily say
I can't tell you exactly what happened
Between May and September what
So Evolutions Alex add without spending another year
Yayoi
But I automatically think
You know as I've already expressed
The initial thing that I set out for
Is much less important
It turns out
I believe then
The the larger picture
Missing the forest for the trees that sort of thing
No I I don't I don't
Accept anything other
If that statement
We could be wrong
What is Speck
Look at all the things that are fake
I don't give a f*** about the
We could be wrong functionally
You said it was fake you might as well just said I think
Sandy Hook nobody died there
Do with a tiny little
I could be wrong
Not in our capability or are like
Exerted
Mandate relief
To assess things from a legal perspective
Yeah so it
You know if none of this is necessarily him committing Act
The defamation
The interest
Is more in terms of like when did he
Change things
Twist and I don't know
Now looking back on it I'm not sure they have a really did all that much
Never answered there was some immediate
Disgust
Towards people saying
That's a grieving father was
By acting
And faking
But that seems to have gone away fairly quickly
Not even in 2013 you speculating about Robbie Parker death like that didn't that
That's not that different
All of it is to say that I think that his editorial line whose
Been pretty regularly can
Consistent
And
It's not that important
Come to me when he
He says these people didn't
Turn on 11/11
But in terms of
That being sort of behind a lot of the coverage
Even if he's not explicitly saying it.
That that to me is as damn
Iic
See him
Trying to be
Like he is
Way past
Cast The Line
But I see him stretching a tiny little toe and trying to leave it on the line is like
See no I'm not past the line
Your entire everything is
Bass line you can't
Just leave a little toe on there
So we wrap up this 2013 investigation
And say Alex
You suck
Tragic
I don't I don't I don't believe
Do I believe that the most
Generous way you could look at this
Is that
Alex is
Woefully unable to do his
Like the best-case scenario
The most
Kind
Complementary thing I can say
About what he does
Is that he has no business doing that
Because if you allow someone like wolf
And who you absolutely no
Believe that no one died
There
If you allow him to come on your show and say things like
It's suspicious that this animal shelter got money
You
I have a responsibility to either
No
About the topics that you're going to be cover
Or
To say to him
I'd is there a possible reason
Ask a follow-up question
Instead of just be like haha yeah f*** the United Way
Further
Because you know that he has this
This position you have a responsibility to
Picture frame things a little bit more
Responsibly
For instance
If you're going to ask him what do you think happened
You can't
In the middle of asking that question
Say this guy is amazing we salute him
Do that because you know the answer
You are given those compliments to the A
Answer you know it's come
I don't necessarily believe
But that's an accident
Something you would do random
But on the off-chance
Something that you would just do
Your you're
Can't be trusted
To be your commentator one of those situations where
The
Sometimes your editorial statement is
Booking
Like the motor the moment you booked how big you made your entire editorial state
And laugh in the difficult personal interview
Because you can't
You're absolutely right
I'm just saying like a with with the where we are right now
With although iraq-war Liars coming back on TV onto all of the shows it's like
You've made your editorial position clear
You want us to get light into another War
The interview starts like this
Excuse me we have from Former Intelligence official alright now you're a f****** liar who lied us into a war
Are you f****** lying
Why shouldn't you be in jail
Right I mean that's a different conversation
Uno people people like
Young Turks having David Duke
Bebe
Adversarial interview
It's okay
So I don't think that Alex
How big on.
Is necessarily
Onnit
Own editorial decision
But having him on
Praising him saluting
Building him up as this great expert who's
Not only a champion
For free speech
And I'm the victim of a
Conspiracy against
Damn but also given up
All of this
Material gain
In order to
To pursue this
Truth
That's the editorial
The framing of how the interview is done alone
Speaker volume
And I think you can also see a little bit of the difference
It's between this sort of interview that Alex
Just giving here in May
September 2014
With the you can juxtapose that with Paul's interview with James Tracey in the months after the shooting
Where is Bolton do a great job of pushing
I'm back he still did push back up
Explicit repeatedly that I don't agree with you
That wasn't necessarily an adversarial interview but it was at least
Pointed cover his own ass
Yeah
It's somewhat critical that doesn't
Seem like
Nearly as big of an editorial choice
I have something like these
Very very
Good
Yeah absolutely
I think one thing that I learned from the
Since we're now basically on
Three different
Of Alex we got
In the present day
Cuz the ones we looked at
The most
With 15
Watching him
Leading up to an election
Is a way different type of monster than
I've been
Team and the present
Because he doesn't have that thing to just heartburn
Now he can
Throw is f***
Disastrous
Bulshit anywhere
Well he didn't know
He had a
Piano as it went along and 25th
He had the Spectre of Hillary Clinton
Coming around in order to
To work with
And they made a lot out of that
They certainly did
Yeah
I don't know I'm trying to reflect on
On this a little bit
I think that like
I'm
A little
I don't know
Nonplussed
About to be
The realization that the literal words coming out of his mouth
Are not the most important thing
And the fact that that was
The road I embark
Maybe
Feels like a door not fully closed
But at the same time
I'm I'm super grateful
To have been able to
Encounter the Boston bombing
Stuff
Because that
Like
I don't know how anybody could listen to that and not
I think that Alex is
One of the most manipulative Liars
Basing his s*** on nothing
And I honestly think that
From my perspective
His behavior in the
Aftermath
And evict the immediate
An ensuing aftermath
Of the Boston bombing
It indicates
It has implications
Spare his Sandy Hook
It really does
It it it's such a full picture
Picture of just taking whatever piece of information not wedding anything
Israelite fukkit we're building a narrative
And the narrative
Evolving to no one died
Sandy Hook
Is important
But it is just an evolution of the narrative it was already there
Which is
Something's fake
Write this is all false flag
Yeah I think the I think what we
Answered
You know
The 2013 it's just the question was
Not worded
That way you know when did he say that Sandy Hook
Was fake should have just been like
When did he functionally say that Sandy Hook was
Because it was
Real quick
Yeah you know in the
And the post-mortem here's another sort of decompression
You can one of the notes
Chicken takeaways Maybe
In the future if we ever do try and look at
Good stuff like this maybe
Have a better idea of what you want to find
Well that and I think we learned so much about
Like
You don't want to speculate on what's going on inside somebody's mind while they're say
You know whether or not
He's telling the truth or he believes it or he's lying you know you can't just speculate
Save that
But when you see the same techniques being used in the
Sandy Hook aftermath and the Boston bombing aftermath you that gives you a clearer idea of when
The next thing hits
We're not speculating on what you think
We're going back to
To the context of
Situation
And this is what
You're doing
Regardless of whether or not you believe it or not
Not we know exactly what
You're doing
And that means something
I mean something
So anyway
Just need to take a break
From present
The manage to do that
And I guess we'll be back in the present day
Do we have to
Can we get a time machine
Maybe what we got to get
Wolfgang halbig
Replay
Whatever
But we have a website
We do have the website it's knowledge
That's correct
We are on Twitter that knowledge underscore fighting at
Go to bed Jordan
That is right girls on Facebook
We are and you can go to iTunes
Games download leave a review donate to the show all that fun stuff do it we'd love
Absolutely
Mdzs cork I am the juicy
Ice Cube
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work