Air Jordan
I have great respect for its knowledge B B I'm sick of imposing
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Everybody
We're couple dudes exit around Jack novelty beverages. A little bit about Alex
Jones
Jordan
Let me ask you a quick
Sure
How have you traditionally dealt with being in a
Creative
Not well
I mean there were a number of years where was booze
Certainly that would be a go-to of like I
I'm stuck I can't get anything done
Certainly that didn't work
No I've known
Weatherforyou
I guess actually I kind of do have an answer for you
Incredibly unsatisfied
Is just keep working
That's the only thing that I've ever found
Americans like it in pastimes things like meditation and mindfulness
I have
Yielded some positive results
But I would be kind of putting on airs if I use that is like an actual
Actual piece of advice
It's not really a consistent part of my life
But
Just keep making things
Keep moving forward
It was something I was impressed upon me in some but I believe some like creative writing class I took Longo's like
You can't control
The quality of what Euchre
Sometimes things will be good
Sometimes things will be bad
But you can
Control
Quantity
Answer if you create 100 things and
Three are good
That's better than sitting around and trying desperately to create that one good thing and not allowing your
Yourself to do any
Anything get anything done
Unless it's
Is good as white
Sorry I would say
That's probably that ice just keep doing stuff keep work
Eventually exercise
Uno oversight of what you put out or what you release
Well drive
I see those 97
And they think that oh my God he's crazy things they're all amazing
That's the key
That's the trick
So
This is been my episode of masterclass
I think you did great
Navigate to Fort Gordon Ramsay
Just keep doing things
Amanda lot about Alex
And I know a little bit about books
Right so Jordans a bag of the present today
I wanted to check in
Since we had the 2013 episode on Monday and so I started
Listening to January 12th
That was Sunday's episode
And I got incredibly bored at stop listening halfway through
Only to be here
Right in the face
With something terrifying on the January 13th Monday episode
That is what would be going over today
I'll before we get to that we can take a little moments say thank you
Some folks
So first of all John with no h
Johndee last initial D thank you so much you are now policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Did you know that that's the name of the original Wizard
Of the beginning the guy who first dressed like a wizard
Merlin he was he's the bases form
I can't remember
The court
It's also the John D Rockefeller Foundation grants Reading Rainbow possible thank you
I like the difference
Straight to wizard
The foundation
Help me read
Although Jerry Jarry thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Play very scary next
Thank you so much
John with no date
No jobs no age
Last initial
Thank you so much you and I'll probably walk
MacArthur Foundation
Thank you so much
Next Sylvia thank you so much you're now probably walked
Sylvia
I'm off
Almost certainly mispronounce
Aha Kon thank you so much
You are now apology
Thank you very much
Who donated on an elevated level
Soleri technocrat
Craig thank you so much you are now what technocrat
End of Hitler thank you so much you are now what technocrat
Money off at heroin
Why you pimp so good
Freakishly large
Tulare and thank you so much of LA
Thank you very much to all three of
Bonjour website
Knowledge
Maybe very
Now Jordan before we get down to
Today's episode
Cause of dissension in the ranks
Between you and me know
I want to split the audience to out-of-context drop
And I would like the audience to sound off on which
They think is a better out of context drops her but I
So here's the first one
Is a little bit too heavy
You know what I really think about the world plus a on there like I say things on air I never
The whole world
The secret place
Is this Buddhism what is happening right now
The only place you really can be private and public
Set the first option one here's the second.
Innovation horses are psychic and that's been proven
Psychic horse
Secret secret horses
Team psychic or public place
No f****** rat
Okay.
So we're starting on the 12th
Because I wasn't
It's it's interesting cuz this is a Sunday show that is absolutely
In the mold of the we're going to soft launch some narratives this is definitely that
Sort of Sunday shower he's
Doing a trial run
You know we're not on the main show
World Neon vastation
The carry the Sunday show whatever
Diminished viewership psychic horses
Let's get down to it
And see
How this feels coming out of my mouth
So I would start a couple of narratives writing
At the top of the show and
Pizza Fair
Absurd
January 12th, Sunday broadcast 2020
We have definitely enter the quickening everything hit is now beginning
They revealed she's going to be a bumpy ride
Californian textbooks for 8
Raiders officially have blood-drinking and vampirism as part of sexual pleasure
The multiple pages
That's coming up
All right how many years have we been in the quickening now so many
This is a difficult story to tell exactly what Alex was talking about cuz of the phrasing of it it's
No that's not
Super
Easily googleable
Okay so it turns out this is just an article that Alex is employee John bowne wrote for the Infowars website
That's all
That's what we got
Even if you believe everything that's in John Brown's article which I do not Alex is still wrong
He's here on are saying that the stuff is being taught to 8th graders when the article specifically says that it's part of curriculum for
Through 12th graders
Alex Jones cannot help him
Himself he just reflexively embellishes literally everything he talks
It's you just
Got to lie
Adelita
Now as to whether or not California students are being taught about blood-drinker
A sexual pleasure
I'm not sure that this article johnbowne route established
Does that
According to bounds article
He saw Facebook
Post on a page for a treaty out
A post on the Facebook page for group called informed parents of Washington they claimed that there was a book called
Sex that was on the suggested reading list for high school students
McDonald's
First problem this is just a Facebook page which is not a sturdy Foundation to use as a base for your reporting
Second problem
This is the inform parents of Washington talking
S*** about education
California
Which seems like them working across purposes
Doesn't seem to make a whole lot of sense why this is
Susan their purview
Truly informed parents group
From wash
About Washington
Yeah that they could be in a
At my work all right except
Quote to the textbook allegedly contained a chapter on anal sex and vampiric sexual practices known as blood play
First of all this is not a textbook and even according to that article it wasn't required reading
Is just on a suggested list
If you know anything about high schoolers most of them are not going to do much reading or homework that is not required
Also
Blood-play is not inherently satanic or vampiric
Do some participants May liquor even drink each other's blood
But my position on this is sort of like
If they're doing this responsibly in both parties are Intuit who cares
Alex pretends to be a Libertarian so he should care even less than I do
The issue here and what are the reason
I could see this being very valuable as like
Some information
You're being there in a sex-ed program available to
To the student is that kind of play Canby
Be pretty dangerous if you're in if you're not engaging in it responsibly
It's a pretty wide
Spread kink like that super Universal but it's 12
The number of people I have
Which tends to imply that it's not just going to go way if the right-wing pretends it doesn't
Exist due to make sure people who are drawn to that cake
Best thing is to have them make sure they have all the information they need you do not understand the right-wing sites
Sex education
All right person for me
Abstinence-only
No gloss
Bien
I could see why you definitely don't need to make blood play front-and-center in yourself
Curriculum but it feels appropriate to have some resources
Is available for people if they want
That is fun the idea that everybody coming into the sex-ed class is already so very so it's like well we got to find something new
I just heard about
Blood play on a Facebook post let's get on this
Facebook page for inform parents of Washington and let me Begin by a review of it by saying
Probably be a bit embarrassed if I use this as primary
As best as I can tell from scrolling all the way down there time live this page first posted on December 9th 2019
It's been about around about a year
Airome s220 followers
It's completely anonymous
Obsessed with anti-sex education news
There's very little emphasis even on washing
Your theory about it just being
Informed but not about Washington
Might be accurate
This is barely even a real group
An Infowars is picked up his Facebook post from them and relied on it too
The source of their reporting
This is really embarrassing
Stuff
And later I even learned I think the John bowne article is based on an article on National file which again is
Run by Alex's
Employee Tom pepper
Man so they're even laundering it through a second but it all traces back to this Facebook
Oh what
What tangled webs we weave when first
We spout bolts
Also even according to this Infowars story on this
Following a massive public outcry it was removed
That's right
Facebook they're still offended by
Who is Betty was on the suggested reading list isn't even on that list anymore because they complained really loudly
That's classic info complete bullshits been on a poorly sourced
Story covering a non-problem that they've already got their way on
The bunch of assholes just a bunch of clothes just never going to
Empires are in the schools superpro vaccine
I'm sure children
There we go
The un's had officials admit major vaccine deaths and Andre cover-ups
So that's the next arrogant meaning of x
Scene cover up
So this article or this story appears to be based on a national file article like I said run by Alex's work
So this is a story about doctor
Soumya swaminathan
Giving a speech
She's leading you and World Health Organization doctor
And researcher site is just giving a speech which is basically about how there's a lack of
Thorough safety monitoring systems
In many countries around the world and it creates Optics were propagandists can latch onto
Some ambiguities and use it to attack
There we go
She's not saying there's a cover-up just advocating that the international Health Organization to do better and more comprehensive
The job so anti-vax people can't wiggle into
To the Grave
She does say that their deaths
Actually could be traced to vaccines but no one disputes
Alex's pretending that this is some kind of a giant admission
When it's literally just how medicine
There isn't a medicine or treatment on this planet that I'm aware of it doesn't have some death
So this is definitely not her slipping up and revealing
There's some kind of a cover-up going on
You know it's funny to me that I think
Alex prefers doctors from
The 15th century who would be like bloodletting is a great idea
The cover-up of how leeches are real men
Exactly one hundred percent
I don't doubt that
So Alex is pretending
He and his crew been poring over hours and
Hours of footage
It's from this world
Health Organization Summit where this woman gave this
Speed in reality the only thing ever produces is a video that some anti-vax group that he doesn't name create
Which includes a very short clip of doctor
Hasan minhaj
How to
Contacts
I find this narrative super run
Compelling is Alex really had some kind of a smoking
Gone like he's claiming he has
He would have released the entire raw footage of this meeting
Like is he saying I'll putting it out and we have copies of going over it
I'm going to go out on a limb and guess at the reason he's not doing
What is casinos
The context
Did the larger conversation
What time does contradicted narrative he's building it's not in his best interest
To write
2 allows
Yeah that's what happens whenever you start stealing Facebook post from the informed parents of Oklahoma
Write a lot worse anti-vax it going
There's actually more to this that I looked into the will get into little bit later sort of Trace down some of the roots of
Where this is all coming from but for now I
Just found like
And bring this up like this is a very uncompelling narrative
Just sloppy work and is anti-vax
Crusade
But
Little did I know
CI work
Quite a bit like on the show I do a lot of reading a lot of preparation added a lot of
Just sort of wine I'm not complaining
But I didn't know how much more Alex works
Because I hadn't I hadn't
Considered that all this time that like
I think he's sleeping
He's actually working
I don't believe
Making stuff up here
I don't believe that either that the time I'm dead on Act
Let's just move on from that
Play the people that I do
Blow smoke
I really lived inside
I had 8 hours of rain last night
In my dreams
Delivery
Clarion Murray Central and I
I was working the whole time
On what was going to happen what we're going to do
Fully committed
Look I'm not one of these guys who's like real like
Wet blanket e about the potential of the subconscious and I just don't believe Alex
Doc invent
Time travel in his dream
Does this imply that maybe he was going over some of the footage of the World Health Organization it is green
Who was the original inventor of DreamWorks Animation
There's only one explanation
I would I would say if there's some explaining Tori power in the fact that he works in his dreams
The fact that you
Afraid of vampires
Able to draw a line between his obsession with vampires
And Nightmares 58 hours
I'm that makes me angry
I can't get 8 hours
Neither can I
I went to bed at midnight last night and
And got up at
Too because I hadn't fallen asleep laying in bed for 2 hours straight
Like I said
Alex is afraid of a
They talked about that a little more here
Let me tell you the next thing
I'm so freak
Vampirism
The drinking of blood
Is the heart of holly
Movies Reno
Within some movies got involved went there and have people tell me
And then I thought
California textbooks are now teaching at your old and broke today so I'm forced out.
To drink blood
Nikeshoebot
Blood blood
And I went wait a minute
I was told that by
Samurai little FBI
Bulshit
I looked it up and the other teaching children hardcore Satanism I'm going to show you that to folks believing
You don't want to look at it but you got to look at it cuz I believe people are these are
Jewel
Devil worshippers their bodies only forever
Desparasitar in them
Transcend
We'll talk about it when come back
Immortal evil spirits are teaching your kids to be vampires in schools and Doughboy
You can put
Dramatic music all you want over that that's still lame bull
Yeah that is weak tea pretty it's pretty lame
Also Alex starts rambling about
How you know this sounds
Crazy
But really like
As always
Is been the case sure
Like you remember how there was that whole satanic panic in the 80s
Now you're shaking your head at me that was true
All of that was real none of it was made up of
Hundred percent real and the FBI has admitted
Was growing up
Leftist
Aldi's
Squares
That don't you have a girlfriend only a drink a beer.
Weird music hires at who is doing this
I don't know they're all paranoid
Nahum Hysteria
Doesn't exist even though law enforcement was reporting at their work
Convictions of human sacrifice murder satanism
Exist
Titan isn't hysteria the Satanism panic
Those files given classified
30 years later and it's everything
Police were warning us about was real
Irvine satanic panic
Well I mean there is a shorthand for something
Silly saying this in this clip but I know for listen
Going to the show
He says that the FBI Declassified stuff that proves the satanic Panic was a real
What are you talkin about is the recent release of the files on the find
This is just short-handed he brings up all the time at any consistent listener of the show would know that when he brings up the FBI releasing files
House approved this stuff
It's generally accompanied by discussion of the group Define
Last October the FBI release their file on this group
They were a group that was the one of the central focuses of the last big satanic
I'm absolutely certain that Alex has not read the
These files sent its
324 pages long
And there aren't any dank memes in it so
They should let dankula take a pass
Yeah punch this up
Do you know anything about this
No I do know about the losers weepers
But I don't know anything about the
There's there's not keepers
So according to conspiracy lore two men were arrested
The Tallahassee Florida back in 1987 on child
Abuse charges
They're found with six children who weren't related to them and they were uncooperative with the police when they were asked about who the kids were
Provide their identities or anything
These men were part of a cult called
Finders who were based in washer
A run by someone who was called
The Game caller
The feds would go on to raid the finders and find proof
So how they operated as a child abuse ring with kidnapping and Grooming
Taking in children
Somehow us intelligence is involved as like using them as like
Cutouts or something else is in on it too
Since they're in d.c.
So the FBI files on the finders they're pretty much a
Dot-dot
Actually reveals how much of this narrative is based on Paranoid fantasies that were very common in the cultural psyche back in
The 80s
There's a full investigation of these two men were arrested in Tallahassee the police were able to find the parents
Six children and quote
The mothers were all aware that the children have been taken to Florida on a trip
They were familiar with him thoroughly Trust
Did the man in whose care the children have been placed
The man who go on to spend about ten days in a local jail and then were released
The US attorney's office declined to prosecute the case largely because there wasn't
Strong evidence of any specific crime
A special agent whose name is redacted from the files quote advised
Did the media blew the case out of
Proportion
That's basically what you find have
Opening throughout a lot of the issues in the satanic panic
Yeah it bums me out that while it's happening people don't realize that they are redoing the witch
Yeah right the witch burning
Things like guys
We've done this
Before
But I mean you didn't have to go back that far I mean if you just look at that
Like Lark Voorhies to relate to
Being in the 80s
Supposed to
60 and under
So I read over most of the finders files and it seems like they can
Conclusion one should come to is that this is a group of people who wanted to live in alternative lifestyle sort of
Communism
Kind of vibe under the leadership of a weirdo called The Game caller
I mean hate if you could work if you can get it running to call this easy stuff
Apparently what do you do if you would tell people
In the group things to do in order to
To gain experiences because he would learn through their experiences
I'm sure there was some
Like nefarious angle to it too
I'm sure it was a
I am sure there was not great things out of course it was loot box
Boxes all over
It's entirely possible that some abuse was taking place in that environment and I
I am not saying that there wasn't
But also FBI investigation failed.
Produce any proof of
The rest of the ship the stuff that Alex believes it's all just cultural exaggeration dude what would happen
Sitting at the United States at that time with that book
Michelle remembers
Speed release
And the McMartin
School trials creating
The fever pitch of fear
Around satanic child abuse
In particular circles in our
Yeah what has those two
Daycare people was a f******
Travesty
Remember how long that trial was to
It went on for f****** ever
So that's all that's going on like this is just a remnant
Of that and Alex is trying to re bring it back up
We talked about it even
Like the ways back pretty consistent thing that I was into in the present-day electrifying to whip
These things
Bitter meaning
He wouldn't
Do whip it up into a frenzy
If
Vampires weren't
Teaching
Kids vampirism in school
I really don't like it when you say that sends and I'm supposed to take it like it's a
Okay
Well I mean it's what this is reality
I'm in like a news reporter
And cover the
Sing
It's in the fog
If it's hard to
That all tied together with all the things that are happening but
California 8th graders taught anal
Bondage sex
Involving blood in sex ed class
Now I saw that National file article
Bounce It Up on newswars.
How come
And I thought
What the hell is
What play
About yourself
Sure as hell
Batman
And it is what you do
Somebody
Research on that episode that I wanted to forget and it was sure as hell going on
They're going
Directly
The most
I can't
I would love to know what the research
Chantelle there
Hearing jargon for from you no like insulated communities when you get a view inside
I like to find out that that's what vampires call it when
Alex has a lot of high-level vampire sources
Naturally he doesn't hang out with blade though
Plainfield Delight still has to drink a little blood from toy
A good resource for information
It's true
I'll tell you I was getting
I'm pretty impatient with this
It was probably because you were forced to take vampires real
Probably about half hour and I was really losing my will to live like
I got you a commercial that Alex did this is what made me turn it off
I was like I'm not losing you this episode anymore
Knock on wood I am not tempting fate but everybody around the office
A long time have noticed that I really don't ever get sick
Tomorrow I'll say that again
Alex
Yes
So sloppy and lazy he's rambling about how I saying if you ever get sick of going to make them get sick of these superstitious about
Bad that you can hear from the background he's recording this in his car
Alright
I just put it up
I just can't imagine it like I imagine now McDonald's putting Ronald McDonald in a commercial just him driving ban like
I'm telling you McDonald's food is the precious now I may be wrong tomorrow I may be wrong tomorrow because
You know the everyday changes everything is do tricep
You know what
I'm loving it
But maybe not tomorrow
You know what I'm saying anyways
Just hit my Breaking Point kind of has like there's nothing good that's going to come to this episode like
Obviously he's teasing he's going to get into these vampire s***
And like okay
We've heard you do this rant before this isn't new yes fabricating a new story
To enable you to do this ramp
Play the hits Otis baby
Stocking
Listen to it
Use for a product that's already on the market I have better things
Things to do
Then wait around for that
So I dropped the Monday's episode
Holy
The
Individual that I believe controlled opposition
Richard Spencer on the show
Nope nope
Snoop
You know the okay to milk
I don't think it's okay to punch anybody
That's a punch you first
Unless they're not
I just reached
So when Alex first said that Richard Spencer was going to be on his show I thought
That sounds about right
Alex's shows in the middle of spiraling the drain of plausible deniability so why not make some of this s*** super over
Then Alex said that he's having a mom because he believes that
Dispensaries
Controlled opposition
Which could look like Alex having him on for a confrontational interview but I assure you that Alex
Has not equipped to have that kind of interview with a slick
Media polished bigot Like Richard Spencer
Do not think that Spencer's been called controlled opposition like a thousand times by now
Do not think he has a million deflections and rebuttals to that criticism at this point
I've seen Richard Spencer in a number of the debates and conversations
Both friendly and
And in hostile environments
And when I heard Alex teases interview all I could think is that this is going to be a
Disaster
Spencer is much better at Roderick stuff than Alex and Alex is very gullible
I just imagined Richard Spencer becoming be like new geopolitical expert and Alex's whacked
Like honestly that's how badly I first saw this going he's going to give him a job
I see this ending the way that Stefan molyneux
Special report in Poland and varies just like Alex
She's just like you know what you convince
I'm a Nazi now
In reality let's just got through the b******* I think Alex is probably having Spencer on mostly because
Spencer recently tweeted that he regrets ever supporting Trump
They're now on opposite sides of the white identity seen so there needs to be some kind of a smoothing that out
A meeting of the minds
If you will
That's the sense I get of what probably precipitated this
And also they're both pathetic enough
At this point in their careers they would appear on the show together
A couple of years back
In other career circumstance
Maybe even some 2018 2016
Spencer would his
Seen himself as being so far about going on Alex's show you would not have done it
Spawning
Duffy's dress well and at the same time at that point Alex wouldn't have seen himself
Lesbian
Interposition we're having Spencer on could be anything
Worth doing can't go full not two yet
Or even like it's not worth it to even if I were to present him as false opposition or whatever
Not even in my best interest
Neither of them had a steak
In that and now their lives of
Did you real to the Pirates like
F*** it I'll go on Infowars f*** it I'll talk to Richard Speck
So
We know that Alex
Has had David Duke
On the show
And so this is
Sort of a
Second
Run
Facts about that about how like
Spencer Richard Spencer is probably the most famous white supremacist
In America outside of David Duke
Solid says things by David Duke and keeping right he's not defending
David Duke Richard Spencer
Other than David Duke is one of the most famous
White nationalist white supremacist in the world
I do not believe David Duke is a fed I'm not believe David Duke
Is an operative
For the Deep state
Of the media to demonize David Duke and call the worst person on Earth
Because
He is racially-based when all the minority groups are being taught to be just as racist
Wow
And then I'm out here defending
Baby due date
Before
Alex says he's not defending davidiuk but that's exactly what happened
In August 2015 Alex had David Duke on the show interview that I'm sure Alex that would be a big chance to prove
That he wasn't like do
It was a miserable failure because David Duke is a guy who's been attacked for his horrible but
A decade
And through that he's gained a little bit of an ability to out argue people who aren't prepared for debate
What I find very interesting is that here in 20
20 Alex is saying that he doesn't
Don't agree with
But that Alex is against the media saying Duke is bad for being racially-based when all the other races are racially-based
This is interesting because when David Duke was on Alex's show just
Four-and-a-half years ago
Alex made the exact
The opposite argue
Alex's big big disagreement with Duke
With the fact
The Duke was race
Usually based
And that focusing on race was a globalist distraction
That's all changed
And Alex is okay with racially-based identification
Grouping
This is a fundamental important pivot that Alex is made whether or not reflect
His true opinion or not
In 2015 prior to joining up with Trump
I want to show was explicit in its position that grouping based on race was a globalist trick
Now Alex thinks
It's cool for David Duke to do what he does because he feels that other races are doing the same thing
Alex's show has always been profoundly races
Stand white identity heavy
But that changed presentation
I think is important
Yeah the only things they disagree on now are like
Seafood choice
Optics Alex doesn't like oysters
You know Optics of choice
David Duke does love hello it's weird he's got a weird thing
So
A David Duke is not a fed
He's not fake
But Spencer
The guy is as phony as a three-dollar bill
I'll just say that
Michelle
Behaved
It's just like somebody that's controlled opposition
No s*** you don't
That's
Great
Yeah I'm pretty sure that means that Alex is going to spend all of his time agreeing with Richard Spencer but still
Band like yeah but you're here to make us look
It doesn't go great we'll get to that when we get to it
50 emails
Pretty well spelled out in
Nightclub in that is that I have a big accusation to make but I have nothing to base it on and that will be very easily
That's kind of what
Going to happen
So Alex gets back to this qnx
Story and the reason that I
Taking one from the 12th and here one in 13th
Is that when he was talking about another
The 12th I didn't really
You know how to get a handle on what he was talk
I don't really understand
Where this information was coming from necessarily
But when he brings back up on the 13th
It gives a little bit more detail and he
He gives me away in
David
To the full video on the UNC
So Alex here is saying that he's gone over this 20 hours of footage from the World Health Organization Summit about vaccines
And that he's going to link the videos on Band. Video
Play that's all I wanted
I don't mind going over hours of footage to get a better understanding of what's going on here
For the video awesome
So I run over bad guy video in the first video about the um vaccine shed that I click on the link for the info
Store on
And that is not going to be helped
Cyclic on a second video that Alex put out about the this story
And that one does have link
But they aren't linked
6 to 20 hours of footage
What is 22 minute 49 Second clip of doctor swaminathan which is devoid of context and meaning
The second one
Mike is much more relevant
Since it's clearly
Entire source that Alex is working
This is a 9-minute video that highlights multiple short clips
The Summit
Here's a video produced by a show called The high-wire with Del bigtree
Which appears to be largely a show that produces anti-vax
For some insight
They had Andrew Wakefield as a guest
Four months ago which is a bad sign
Everybody agrees that he is still the foremost expert on why you shouldn't take back
Del bigtree is one of the producers
Pictures of the pseudo-documentary VAC
Which pushti discredited Wakefield vaccines cause autism
Narrative
Victory has no medical education or training
He is a TV producer who formerly worked on the doctor
Sure Phil Show eventually learned about Andrew Wakefield and was swayed by that bullshittin went fully down that road
In March of last year big tree caught some heat
From Jewish organizations after he gave an anti-vax speech wearing a yellow star
Meant to compare the plight of the
Anti-vax Community to that of Jews during the Holocaust
Iraq
Sure buddy
Is the founder and CEO of the
Informed consent Action Network
Anti-vaccination group one of the most prominent
In the country
He started the group in 2016 receiving a $100,000 Grant from the cells Foundation
A charitable organization run by Bernard cells and his wife Lisa
Who coincidentally is the president
Of the informed
Consent action
In 2012 the cells gave
$200,000 to Andrew Wakefield legal fun
Which kicks off a rash of big dollar contributions
The anti-vax
And went on to provide much of the funding for that pseudo-documentary of his vac
Which is produced by Del bigtree
It's important to remember that rich people are all f******
It's also important to remember the 22 others 2 years after Wakefield
I was convicted of
Professional misconduct
Denied his license
Revoked
It's not like he was a guy in good standing at these people just wanted to support
According to Business Insider $1000000
Or 3
Three-quarters of Del bigtree budget
It came from the south Foundation
In 2017
And that isn't even close to all the anti-vax stuff it sells Foundation to support it
They've given billions more to other outfits
Is it spread misinformation about vaccines
To the point where it be pretty fair to say that without their money funding a lot of this stuff
Anti-vax it wouldn't be nearly as
Is probably what does it
It's unclear exactly what their motivation is and spending billions of dollars to push debunked and
Discredited science
But what is very clear is that these are the people who are largely behind the popularity of anti-vax narrative
People like Alex love to pretend that it's all
Does the Grassroots thing we're normal everyday people were given a voice
Social media that's why the conversation is happening
But it's not
Well-funded facts by the
Multi-millionaire
I haven't seen her like so many people like to mock that
That
That white lady who's like
Group and all that s***
Whenever it's f****** these people who are the issue
It's it's boils down to like
Who is astroturfing what
And why are we making fun of the people
Who got
Tricked by
Instead of going after
The people who are
Right2know
What is one of the reasons why I generally try to
Approached some of the stuff with more empathy than some people
Think is appropriate
And you know I'll take that
I'll take that criticism
As a being
Fine but I disagree
It's one of the family obviously that person
It's been tricked by this is
Still perpetuating and pushing
Narratives that could have the real world fact
The people being heard of shells
Something to take seriously
Yeah so Alex didn't watch 20 hours of footage on these hearing
Do you watch that 9 minute video released by Del bigtree and pretended that he done the work
He accepted the out-of-context Snippets from Big Trees video without Quest
I presented this is a gigantic bombshell
And on top of that Alex's pretty
Presented
Investigative work
He's doing when in reality he's just regurgitating
Propaganda put out by a multi-millionaire
Funded
Anti-vax front
Do the worst I mean it's just
It's it's
So a
He watched
All 20 hours in his dreams Dan
Dreams you can watch 20 hours of footage in only 8 hours of Dreams
It's the dream skate but sells Foundation
And paid for those dreams
So anyway go f*** himself
I mean it just leads to a breakdown kind of like just complete vaccinations
Analyze
Science
Flies
You know back in the 50s that gave millions of American women in French
Type of
What type of
Caused hundreds of thousands of children born with arms and legs
Do not remember the name of that
Never pull video
Just keep giving them to you and telling you nobody ever got hurt
So Alex has no idea what he's talking about in terms of vaccine recalls
Cena has ever been both
Happens all the time difference
In one instance they
There might be a recall on a specific batch of a vaccine
Do the internal quality assurance testing indicating
There might be a contamination or some other concern
This happens not super regularly Beacon find plenty of examples of it
In other cases of vaccine might be discontinued because of better vaccines
Undeveloped effect
Other times their reactions that are not anticipated
And oftentimes can't really be anticipated
Discovered after vaccine begins being used
Princeton
In 1976 there was a fear of a potential epidemic strain outbreak of swine flu
At Fort Dix
In New Jersey
Scientist at the CDC went to work on creating a vaccine due to the severity
Of the possibility of what could come once flu season
After administering
The vaccination program it was found that a small number of people who got the vaccine to come down with Guillain-Barre
And the timeline of the
Condition made it possible there was a connection
In between the Centrum
And the shot
There was no causal link established
But the perception was made by the media that the shock is caused
The gion beret
By December according to the
CDC quote
Federal health officials decided that the possibility of an association with Guillain-Barre syndrome and the vaccine
However small
Necessitated stopping immunization
There are other examples
But there's one of them
So what around to saying is a lie
Health officials are absolutely willing to
Chipotle discontinued use of x
Nothing Alex is saying is based on anything
He just feels like they never pull vaccine because that better conforms to his dumb worldview that everything is against him
Given everything is a plot
Bulshit
Yeah that if it's just like the best response
Some
Some kids remembering some fake bulshit
Is to create a satanic satanic panic
Across the entire country
It's also a good idea to
To confuse correlation
Causation in any and all scientific
Right in and then you also want to take correlation
Causation
And then also just lie on top up absolutely and the media should accept your claims
And just spread it as far as NY.
And if there's a way to demonize a vulnerable population
Ariel
Jersey New York
Illegal aliens
Brought in from Central and South America
Yeah no kidding
If you actually read the actual fine print you know that Alex
Just making up the part about undocumented immigrants causing outbreaks
We've been over this a bunch but what you talking about is that measles outbreaks those what's happened last year
Some of them are thoughts
Because by people who traveled overseas to areas where they were outbreak
Princeton's the Orthodox Jewish community in New York
Cases were brought on by Travelers who'd been
Israel
According to the Pan American Health
There's a big difference between
People traveling and emigrate
Alex doesn't care about this
He just sees what he decides to pretend this fine print saying that there may be a foreign origin
Disease in the United States
That's automatically understood to be undocumented immigrants being carriers of disease that the left is bringing into the United States to attack why
If I was really interested in these sorts of issues I would expect that you should
Recovering how there were another severe overcrowding in detention facilities near the border
It's led to internal outbreaks of mumps and chicken
Chicken pox never seem to hear you don't care too much about that I don't know if I've ever even heard of Bring It Up
I really feel like a simple rule for all media should be
I did grbl save
And let's not say
I like it's to my larger point that I want to make
Gearing up to interview Richard Spencer a noted National
And here he is yelling white nationalist s*** about immigrants bring in disease
I eat you can pretend all you want those irrelevant difference between him and Spencer but there's not he literally said
Immigrants are infested
Communicable disease introduced Richard Spencer
Who is controlled opposition
To make us look bad
Right
Good
Alex gets into
Tomorrow
Dubious science
Stuff just about China
Is making all our pills
And that's bad
On that China makes the majority of our drugs
Deadly Fentanyl
What's the number one killer in the US right now
Not true
Is is a
Absolutely not
Surpass automobile accident
Conference
Alex has a really interesting angle here on Pharmaceuticals in China
I'm a reading here from an article on Infowars
Quote
If we're dependent on China 4000 of ingredients in raw materials to make armetta's
China could use this dependents as a weapon against us
While the Department of Defense only purchases a small quantity of finished Pharmaceuticals
China about 80% of the active pharmaceutical ingredient
API
Used to make drugs in the United
Midstate sarstedt
To come from China and other countries like India
Oh wait I'm sorry I mixed up my notes
That was from an article in the Council on Foreign Relations website published on August 14th 2019
Where is Alex's gals about these sorts of issues
His big villains
Cfra
Explore them in Far More meaningful ways
Princeton
This article points out
A quote that I read
That these raw materials are coming from quote
China and other countries like India
That 80% number is not all just from China
It's the amount of apis that are imported as opposed to being domestically sourced which is totally different
This article
Discusses how we're almost certainly also overestimating the number of these ingredients
The amount of it
It's coming from China
As of 2018 trying to claim 13
Forbes
Percent of all import line
Defined as distinct regulated products
Within the shipment
Through Costco
Among countries that export drugs
Biologic
It's the United
So it's probably lower than
You even assume
Alex's version of the story certainly more exciting
Anil drive more clicks and pill sales
It doesn't reflect reality or any careful analysis of the subjects
Seat covers
The evil writers for the CFR
Do engaging a little bit of that
Look at things from different angles and what have you
Also Alex is completely making up the fentanyl alone is leading unnatural cause of death
The United States
Some say there's no data to back that up he's just a real piece of s*** co-opting people's deaths to push his efforts to attack China
Go fuc yourself I wouldn't be
Surprised if
Killed more people than
I don't know Alex jumps to cultural issues
Facebook
People that weren't women saw the ad them
About women
It's like city buses in a major u.s. city last week
The word
Mother
Ban the word
WordGirl
What's a scientific
Tic-tac-toe
I legitimately have no idea what to talk about with his bus s***
I can't find any proof of a major unnamed US city or London Banning feminine words from their buses
I guess if you can prove it or give you a source I'll look into it but
For now I just talk
I don't even find an article about this on Infowars
To be fair his sight is almost done navigate about
So I don't know if it's there and I just couldn't stay or what I can't find anything
Think about this we have been hearing about people Banning the word mother for 7 years now at least
Do purple penguin's know kid
This isn't the same thing is true for the Trump ad at least it's not that I can't find any
Proof of it it's just that it's b*******
Alex knows damn well that I had got pulled because it said the Trump was quote looking for strong women like you
It had nothing to do with the women part had to do with EU part there was counter to Facebook ad polish
You can't Target advertising people like that
And Trump's campaign that every reason
Them to know that this is against
Policy
This is just internet
Intentional
Because it plays better to argue that Facebook won't let Trump promote to women
Then it is to say Trump doesn't know Facebook's policies and he broke the rules
I like
I don't know
This cultural stuff is very soft
Very weak yeah
But it gets interest
Okay
A little bit
All right I don't know
Alex is talking about here is
Very good
I don't know your phone will make
Montages
Of photos
Who's that you've got sure right you know like
I realize that this club up cuz I have no idea what he's talking about
But I believe that there's probably a real
Thing here
You know cuz I've seen Facebook
Do this morning you automatically generate like pictures from
That you posted over the last year of
Stuff like that
But
His angle on it is lunacy
Completely insane
I have one of these devices because it was used as what I know what it does
Faraday cage
When I'm not using it
Wocket pocket Priscilla divorce would I come don't know if that's a faraday cage keeps tell Faraday cages
Quote unquote
Have you noticed that if you have a Droid or you have an apple tickly Apple
That
It's getting really good at it
It takes your photos
Or your wife or your husband
Rip you went on
Put together really good timeline
There is good as a human can do some of these look like
Steven Spielberg Direct
With the music and just how they do things bright the birth
Your baby daughter's has one little thing right at the end
It looked on
My wife's phone is this
Thousands of photos and videos
The very best of
Frightening
Is it done locally on the phone
This is just the interface
AR system
It's being done
The main computers for Apple
Just say iPhone
Our mole that's all I hear they're I am old and I don't under
Tuesday
I would assume the reason that they're the other kind of higher quality photos and like they chose the best stuff is because
You've interacted with that stuff more than the photos that I guy that was a mistake
You sent it to more people over that there's some sort of a metric
There's more engagement on this
Therefore it
The phone or Facebook assumes
This is something more important to the person
That make that is very easy explanation for this that doesn't involve
Over-complicated AI invasion
No no
Is there something that
Tubing disturbing
Perhaps later on
You can take a look
Things are becoming far more complex and AI is coming for our jobs and yada yada yada you can
Go on that tip not the
Beijing is controlling your phone it's also because of Alex's misunderstanding of the like youth
Fix it all all of our phone information is in China
As opposed to the reality of that story
But you're still not good
No I mean the future is more terrifying than the 1950
These people could have been
You don't need to ask a late it like there
That doesn't get us any
Embellished there is no way around it
I'd like every single story Alex Telles
There is
A necessity
To amplify
Sensationalize
Even if like
What the f***
Who cares like
They're teaching 9th graders to be vampires
Just Go With It
That's what's the difference between
13 and isn't going to be like
High School
You were young
You brag Tavares sleeping with like 100 women by the time you were 14 or whatever it was
Are you
Kids grow up fast
I don't know
Just completely unnecessary it reminds me of like pathological
People who lie about things that have no
It reminds me of a Mike Birbiglia
Bad about the the guy in his school he used to just lie about stuff that nobody even cared about like
My cousin is a
Springbok boogie boogie
Do you know that's like
Why are you lying about that too eighth-grader to however old
Have to
So this is scattershot should like it's all over
Talking about like anti-vax stuff
Chinese Pharmaceuticals
Your phone
Creating photo montages
Little bit about climate change stuff
I think so
He has
Like a big narrative about like there's a Facebook glitches that revealed
Greta thunberg's Dad Run
Is her Facebook page
And she's dressed that by interesting
Yeah I use his account
Use this face
Easy administrator of the page
What's the big deal
It's so anyway I don't care about that
This clip just involves Alex talking about how climate change
Existence
Create a priest class
That will eventually lead to us sacrificing baby
Okay now the Steve pieczenik become a Duke in
Only I wouldn't even keep that in if this was that was all
Weaves into a Bible story
No
And I think Midway through talking about it he realizes like it means the opposite of what he wanted to anybody
Members of the details
Baby believe the carbon dioxide is so evil Tracy
Because it's about
Economic Warfare
It's about control
And it's about dumbing people down with the Superstition like the ancient Aztecs the ancient Druids and others did
The sun didn't come back today
Because you're been evil
So do what the priesthood says people would believe
Even unto given the priest class for children in every culture
Human sacrifice
The Old Testament Abraham
Oh here we go
What God says get your son up here and kill
First born
Thought you wanted so bad
Come on
Are you forgetting the
That's because every other cultural Society that's what went on
Do you eat wild Paws there is indicative of Alex being like Wade Abraham was going
Paralyzer
Plan the whole time for no reason
Yeah he was going to do it yeah
But the angel stopped him so I guess that's fine
So he was the one who said he went ape shitt at Buckhannon
Stonehenge
Yes
You love The Druids
He loves the Drew can't get enough
It seems you got violent
Because 30% of people
Experience
Psychotic break
It's interesting that Alex is saying that this priest
Glass
Exist the tells you the things
You can't observe
Are happening you know like they know when it eclipse
Was going to happen today they say they're going to block out the sun if you do what they want
Well but not back then
No they did not know
Not the not The Pedestrian people who are fooled by the priests class
Okay so that's the metaphor that needs met
That like
These are authority figures
Will tell you things
That you can't prove or disprove
In order to manipulate you into doing that
I find that very funny
Considering this next clip
What are evil spirits the things we can't see what Science Now prove
Nothing holding this dimension in
That many times stronger the dimension
We're in
What
We can't see
Is Maspeth 5-10-20 time stronger
They cannot read it
With
Devices
Read what
Proven all these dimensions
Joanna Bob
Multiverse
So
Science
Evil spirit science
Has proven evil spirits
So you got to buy some pills that sounds right you know what evil spirits actually science has proven
Iodine
The soul weighs 7 lb
Little morsel
Wow that's f******
Stupid
Alex is obviously really anti climate change guy
He's really in
In favor of coal
And all that
And we know that
Does Mexico has a really extreme version of him expressing his
His feelings on the subject
Fossils of alligator
Crocodiles
Campbell
Yes sir
In this era
It's a bones album
678 thousand years old
The middle of the Sahara Desert was African jungle
I look Atlanta
Healthier
Carbon dioxide
By the time we found
Carbon
What's the time
Wait till we need to save the planet
Waiting for us
What do you believe in God or not you understand me
I think I do a little
But also know if I understand correctly
Not only is he denying climate
But insisting that we need to pour more carbon into the atmosphere total in order to fulfill God's
When
Geoengineering
To make sure that
Campbell's can
Be in the Sahara
I got to say I've generally been onboard with you and your climate change stuff but what Alex is sitting here just makes me
Max
Sense
And Greta
Are out there trying to stop us geoengineering savior
You know what I was what's the earth dying from
What what do we need to save the Earth from
From not having enough carbon glue tell you about Abraham
I do do
That's a pretty interesting as much as
You from somewhere cuz I was reading everything goes through like 20,000 your Cycles at the Savannah and then a desert
There's some parts of that that's natural
That isn't relevant
Said the larger cam
I do think he's revealed that he's a young Arthur
Right
Cuz he's saying 678 thousand years ago
So I think that's about when the last time it flooded
Sure but I do
He's describing
Based on what I'm hearing is
The massive
Carbon dioxide in the air during
Cretaceous or whatever
All the plants grow so big that's why the dinosaurs could grow so big
So he's like the atmosphere is
Maybe I'll admit that I'm not really well-read on the bat
Subject so I wouldn't really be able to assess whether Allen
What is in line with that
I'm not positive from what do you think
Because
The last time the Sahara wasn't the desert desert desert defied
Is around that time frame
That's kind of how I read
Entirely possible I just
Can't say either way I just see him thinking that the dinosaurs are only
Center 8.
That's possible
So is this
Next clip Alex gets back to the Australian fires
And we know he has a bad perspective on us
And it turns out his perspective
Has it
Department press releases
And a newscast about Muslims being arrested
And indicted for setting fires they believe in there laughing outside the court
Laughing
Fake photos
Snopes says that that's a fake
Chipotle
Directions
Turnt out
Got it from a major
Public Library
A portal
I got to say I definitely saw this Development coming
Yep when I first got it covered this narrative on Alex's show I read Paul's article about the Australian fires
There's and he didn't linked any police
Supporting
I was just one tweet
From 7News that he was using as a source
Now however you know the narrative is pivoted
He's blaming Muslim
So I thought why not see if Paul has written a new article and see if there's any updated information
I went to Summit. News and the only thing I could find is a new video the Paul shot with the title quote
Who started the Australian bushfires
With the subtitle quote
The question the media won't ask
Beastars manga
It's Angie we sure it's not
A laser
I could be a laser
It's just you know Paul Standard mobile
Stop
The first 5 minutes of the video is Paul getting really defensive about how people criticized him for writing the most
Celebrated the Notre Dame fire
Like Facebook
Event weaves in a Breitbart article that involves some official from Israel saying that are some could be considered Terror
A Daily Mail article about Isis using fire as a weapon in Syria
All of this is to imply that the fires
In Australia are Muslim terrorists
It's not even close to subtle
What is insinuation
Engaged
That's brutal
That's just
Hold on
After rambling about Isis using fires as well
Paul as if he's a man working for a dude is getting sued by literally everyone says and I quote
It's not to say there's any evidence
But this is taking place in Australia
But a zebra can't change its stripes quote
Here's the full quote
That's not to say there's any evidence that that's taking place in Australia
But we have
To ask the question
Ohmygod translate that means I have no reason
Proof that Muslims have anything to do with these bushfires but
The only reason I haven't
Careers to satisfy bigots
Do I need to try and make some kind of insinuation here to keep them happy
This is legitimately sickshit and you can see how the
Pipeline works
Paul does this mealy-mouthed we got to ask the question s***
And then that's taken by Alex who pretends that it's reporting
And that it was Muslim
The only think Paul has to go on here at the Gateway pundit article
About a couple of Muslim teenagers who are rest
Super starting with I
Paul is is walking that suggestiveness line is always
Trying to play with
The edge of a are these kids are secret Arrow
Breasts
Unfortunately he's super sloppy
Any accidentally flashes the article up on screen including the portion of the article that says quote
The brothers set off fireworks that started a park on fire
Probably sounds like a
His big angle isn't this picture of one of them
Apparently laughing after they get out of court
Did I say
Who cares
Would Paul cover it if it was a white kid who is rest
Super Starting Fire laughing after he got out of court
Would you do a f****** 10-minute video about his kid might actually secretly be a member of some white extremist group
Psych have doubts
But he would
I just don't
Yeah also I think Alex just admitting that clippity didn't pay to use that photo that he stole from Sputnik
And also I read the Snopes article about the Notre Dame misinformation and they don't even mention Infowars
They don't even mention whatever picture Alex is talking about they're more concerned with an obviously doctored video that was making the rounds
We're someone put audio people yelling Allah Akbar
Over video of the cathedra
I have no idea what Alex's
Projecting about here but if I had to guess
It's the stress
It's brought on by two decades of being full of s*** yeah
Man that remind cuz that's such
Like they just put out a the results of a poll where massive amount of people
Think that I ran around already has a nuclear
Because
Because of that disinformation and just the mashing together
It doesn't matter if you're saying that they do or not
Just put them right next to each other often enough
Just like with this
Did Muslims start the fires in Australia repeat that question and people won't even bother
Bother answering it
Just assume that it's already been
Inquiring minds want to know exactly
Exactly
And 3 years from now you're like a do you remember when the Muslim started those fires in Australia and you like
You didn't even bother answering the question
Right
Teases this interview with Richard Spencer Seymour
It's really important to understand how he
He thinks this is going to go
Before it actually starts
And there's some interesting wrinkles here
AAA surprise
How much racism we've already got in total
I think that's also really important to point out
Richard Spencer most famous white nationalist
$3 bill
Cadillac funeral
Fruit looks like a blast
And of course you walk over to plastic
Maybe he's for real
Thinking we get to you.
Richard Spencer get slug
Which I don't agree with
So I get this sense that Alex is like
He thinks that he's going to have like this
Gotcha moment where he's like
You work for the globalist
Richard Spencer
Like I think he thinks that that's
Maybe a possibility you really think he believes that he's going to know but I think he thinks that he's going
Going to be in charge of
This conversation hand somehow
Secondly
I get a sense
Listening to the way he's framing this
There's almost a disappointment in the idea that he's
Yeah we'll see if he's real yes he's for real
Almost like
It would be good if he's real
Yeah well you want that apple looks fake but you want it to be
Right you want that apple to be real haha
Because you're friends with that apple and you're also a Nazi
We'll see
If he's real
Alex Goes to College little bit before
Spencer and this caller is talking
Think about how
You know like immigrants
They come into the country
There's a vote however there toll
This is this is a weird thing
Because this color has a
Respected that Alex should just
Agree with right. That part but somehow
This is weird
People don't have
Hillary Clinton
About how they're cold and they're brainwashed a Isis and I hate white people
That's why I feel that brainwashing stops
We have to get control of that and then truck has to bring those folks out of the Shadows
Just like Abraham Lincoln was attack
What they call Abraham Lee
You know what you know I think that if this guy
Paid attention to Alex's hear what
Alex calls Abraham Lincoln
What Alex is not in favor of Abraham Lincoln
No reason decided to fight his ancestors who Alex also is
Alex and guests like Steve pieczenik and be just like within the last week's B was talking about how bad Abraham
The Infowars line is
F****** Confederate
Guess guys should
Understand like
Oh yeah yeah they're saying bad things about Trump but you should see what they said about Lincoln back in the day as if to imp
Apply what Lincoln did was good and misunderstood
All of those
Things about Lincoln
And if you were and if you were listening to that show back then you would call in and talk about how much you hate Lincoln
Total that's what you were
Did Lincoln would be there Obama
So we get an hour to sort of the intro the preamble to talk
Answer and Alex
Seems to think that
He's on this whole thing where is like Richard Spencer is a liberal
Really
Right
If he's bought into that
Framing a little bit
Richard Spencer
Easier to come on the show
You know most liberals and socialists will not come on the show
But
And he's really been angry at that.
So I think that's ludicrous for a number of reasons
But
Leaving those aside I want to give a real important caveat here and that some of the things that
But I'm going to end up saying
Sound
Positive
About Richard
Subway and they are not
Okay I think this guy's a pile of s***
Sucks is a liar and he's a dangerous person
Very much so
Across-the-board
I might end up saying some complimentary things about him
In the sense
That he's better at this than Alex
That is the only context in which
I am going to say positive things
And I do not want that to be missed
Construed by anybody
Also
Before we get into this interview
I'd like to play
A clip
I'm Spencer
That's recently
Leaked
You are this
Okay
So ask if Milo is involved in
Anyting I just skip over
No interest
These Charlottesville rally the unite the right rally Milo apparently recorded Richard Spencer
Having a little bit of a breakdown
About what happened
What is ranting
A little bit
And I guess
Whatever reason
Milo wanted to diss
And some cell from some of these communities
The end of last year he posted this audio
On YouTube
And
Just a little bit of a Content warning this language in here
It's pretty bad
So
Obviously this is coming from Bi-Lo who is they
A source of information you never like to take information
I'm from but you would be someone who is situated in
In such a way as to be able to record something like that so it lend some credibility to it
Come from inside
It's not like we're going to walk up and
Record Richard Spencer saying that
It sounds exactly like
Spencer's why so it's either him or
The Great
Rich Little Randy credico
Greater presidents of Arts
Further it sounds exactly like the messaging
It sounds in line with what Someone Like Richard Spencer dustbelief
So I
Of course
Reached for comment
Tons of publication
Richard Spencer has not commented on
He doesn't want to dignify the story but obviously
It's a deepfake
So I played it I play that because I think it's important to wreck
It's slick leazzy
He's going to try and come off
In this interview and as he does all the
Beneath that
F****** insane
Right
So Alex
Starts off this interview
And I think
He thinks
This is going to go very differently
Then it.
Give me your current video of President Trump
Why you're angry
Metropolis is not your
Your fuhrer anymore
Well he was never a a leader
I don't think I need to talk about
How Trump from a white nationalist respect
I think I could talk about Trump
American nationalist even conservative
To deliver
Convey
Keystone prom
Promises
His 2016 campaign
There is no law
Graichen restriction is not
Going to be in the cards
Policies on health
Healthcare admin the other things are absolutely income
Hear it
We have been
Getting
Domestically deep
Call Ryan agenda
Daenerys
And so on and we be getting the George W bush agenda
In the Middle East it's not quite as bad
Give Trump that
But yes very bad he is making war in the Middle East more likely
Play
What not just me but what hit the PIN
Ace of supporters voted
It is true that he said he's going to cut back
I could leave
Types of visas for skilled workers
And then he hasn't done that
That was Alex's first question
You can tell that
He might be realizing that he is in no way
Prepared to have this conversation
I was legitimately thinks he can just say what's wrong with drawn from a white nationalist perspective and think that
Anyway get Richard
F****** Spenser on his heels
Labeling the sky white nationalist is knocking
Tardis human anyway from the perspective of Alex's audience
Many of them probably think that white nationalist just means being a white person who's also a nationalist
And the rest of them don't say
I think that white nationalism is a bad thing
In the way Alex delivers his quest
100%
Trump isn't
Spencer's pure anymore
But that smugness
Can only really be the result of not realizing that Richards
Spencer is a pro
He's been doing this for years now
And every single interview he's had in that time it's been at least
On sublevel confrontation
It's the easiest thing in the world for him to deflect that week s*** and push forward with his own talking
Is a fewer Trump's never been a leader
What do you think of trump from white nationalist perspective
I don't need to speak from a white nationalist perspective
I can talk from the perspective of nationalism
Drop the bass
Sprite with just those two simple deflection
Spencer's completely neutralize these two accusations
But I would start at the interview with
Empty
Given himself
The High Ground in the conversation
Which
That's going to allow him to deliver these talking
Which Alex can't really disagree with
You can almost hear in
In Alex when Spencer stop stalking and there's a long pause
And all Alex
Can come up with is a comment about Hope Trump hasn't cut down visas for skilled workers like you
Upromise
Whatever Alex hope to get out of this conversation is already gone
He's failed right out of the gate because he had no idea who he was about to talk to
And he underestimated his gas
And again to be clear
It's not say the richest Bachelor some kind of
Superhuman think or debater
Is there someone is skill levels
Hi
High above Alex
That reminds me of when I was
First starting out in comedy I went to
A show
Featuring a friend of the show Marty.
And it was put on at a theater
And it was a regular comedy show put on in a 500-seat theater
And maybe 50 people show
And
It was
A disaster
The stage was too high and so on and so forth
What's a Marty
It is featuring set just jumps off the stage and starts wandering through the crowd and
Blew the place up
50 people made the theater huge
But then the headliner to follow up
He tried to stand on the stage
And you can't go by
Marty had changed the the Battleground in Thai
Right
The headliner wasn't equipped
That is what Richard Spencer just did
Alex. He was going to have a thought he was going to have a white nationalist conversation and all the sudden the criticism
Comes from
A completely different Battleground Alex is not
Able to
If you can't sort of predict
That is what's going
It happened that means
The year either
Terrible
At the job
View signed up for
Or maybe you're not super terrible but you just weren't prepared for the circumstances that you have allowed yourself
To get in this is why you don't do convey
Crustaceans like this
Unless
You are
Fully prepared
Unless you take it very seriously
Because
Like
Salt Lake I keep stressing Someone Like Richard Spencer Knows these things
He's fought through these
Countries
But do you like okay if someone asks
This question what's
The best way to proceed whether or not he's sat down and actually diagram these things have no f****** idea but intuitively
Experience in rap
Petition he understand
Okay here's wearing attack is going to come from
Here's what I do with that
Yeah it's very simple and he learned
The link it back the crowd work
Comedy club or kind of works the same way
But you know that there's only a certain number of
Types of things an audience member can yell at you
So if you come up with
Like standard
Kind of strategy to respond
Me and the things that said
Unintelligible thing that said
You'll be able to roll with it much better
Panthers able to roll with
These are blue
Frame
The conversation
The framing failed
It completely failed
And now it is up to
Spencer to just dictate
The terms of what they're going
Absolutely I'd now
He does that
Immediately after that
Takes me high
I overheard the tail end of your last Converse
Versation
And you were both saying well we don't fear h1tv
IH-10
Divisas
Smart Indians or someone well
The fact is we actually should care about issues like that
Immigration is not simply about illegals or very poor unskilled
People coming in
There are billions
The people who are highly
Highly-skilled have II
Can come into the United States and displace them
Middle class
Anyway read wipes
Then low-skill
Illegal immigrants
Doing construction or
Boy job
Very serious issue and you actually she idiot
A big unskilled
The underclass taking control
I think more smart people will build the country up not displaced a little blast
Dumb people that'll destroy us
We're dumb and migrants to Smart immigrants to be free
Heated smart immigrant or Glendale ocado
Jobs at University of North America Dell up once Europeans came here
So now that Spencer's realized you can take the upper hand in the conversation it begins immediately with bringing up things Alex said earlier and
And this case
How to desire for more high-skilled and intelligent Democrat
Alex is going to have a really hard time defending his position against someone who's willing to take the other side
Which Spencer is
So this is Rocky territory
And you can see how not great Alex is standing is when all I can come up with his smart immigrants made this country would Europe
Game over
Without any
Without any effort without any Force
Spencer is elicited a white nationalist idea from Alex
Bye
Not even cleverly hiding his own whiteness
Thought that was
That was brutal
And he has no real reason to hide it and he's not
Immediately after this
It's pretty clear in the context of that
Clip
I've just
Of course he doesn't mind a massive
Unskilled immigrant
Population
He wants to enslave
Right you know that's what he would like to
He doesn't want
Intelligent
Alex is going to have a tough time
Unskilled people are not until
That's bulshit
Alex is going to be tough time
Combining his talking points and worlds you with
Arguing against
What sponsor is bringing
He isn't he's in a kind of an unwinnable situation for himself
And that sucks
So
Expensive kind of
Brazil's a little bit of this
Whiteness being at the core of all of it in
I agree to a very large extent but the
The United States was in 1790
Ultimately a white Khan
Country with a white European country with an Anglo Protestant
Fortuitous
Brought in lots of other European
Was
So Alex is said that smart immigrants made America in Spencer
Completely dismisses that comment by claiming to partially agree with it then moving on to his talkingpoi
And he knows that Alex
Can't really disagree with it without count
Contradicting his own position
America was not a white country at its founding
Good God that's kind of a silly thing to say for a lot of reason
But the most important is
Because what we perceive as white today is not
The same is the 1700's definition of wife
In the late 1800s
Italian immigrants were absolutely not considered white whereas now you'll be hard-pressed
How to find someone who glued Italians from the category
Same goes for Irish polish in Greek
Throughout the country's history
Winship Benjamin Franklin called the German people living in Pennsylvania
Palatine board
You could make the argument that the country is Anglo-Saxon
In nature
At the beginning Maybe
But if you did that you're kind of implying with a goal should be for us to make it an Anglo-Saxon country now
Which is not a white one
Because those aren't the same thing
Current a white nationalist trying to wave this idea way because
Definition of white is not one that would be productive if you try and
Consult history
Their definition includes
People they feel they would want to be in a group with
Which conforms their underlying prejudices
The sleight-of-hand trick if they're doing is
Yeah it is it is
Part where they try to pretend that the definition of white has always been the same
And they're actually
They're just in line with the founders of the country at
They don't say that this country
You should be Anglo-Saxon as a country because that sounds.
Stupid
And almost all of them would be
Considered undesirable
Undermining the purity of the country
As they would have been in the 1700
Spencer says 1790 and that closed because that was the year that the United States passed the Naturalization
Which made all male white inhabitants of the country
Citizens
But again
What is white name
I guess that's an open question
Considering decades later they still definitely didn't think Italian
Games work
My point here is this is a stupid conversation and it doesn't really prove any
Even if somehow the founders of the country magically have the same arbitrary definition of white that Spencer does
And they wanted this to be white country so what
That's slaves and women couldn't vote
I'm going to say that whatever their understanding of the world was
It had room for improvement
But here's the thing
Spencer's talkingpoi
This is a white country
Is b*******
But Alex can't refute that
Without supporting some kind of Multicultural
Spencer kind of headlight has Alex over a barrel where you have to choose between
Supporting minorities are going along with explicit white nationalism
Really having a tough time with this interview and we're only like two men
I think what's interesting is
They are arguing
Flavors of white nationalism
Yeah but Alex can't say that his flavor is different
Because then you'd have to admit
He has a flavor of lightning
It's similar to the David Duke interview but I think worse
For Alex
Cuz
I don't I don't know exactly how to describe this Alex
I think you might have prepared a little better for the David Duke won
Or at least he's known of David Duke for a really long time
Or he was just more capable mentally back then
Sure
Irresponsible of me to
Guess exactly what the reason is but he was more prepared for this he's completely off his game.
You even see what
Could be considered
The two of them
Kind of making
Friends
A little bit
You're welcome
Step we hear coming out of the
Gratis way more racially-based
Whites are bad people don't trust them
Leaving because of the color they are
See that white people into aggressive
Race Pace individual cuz you're not going to have
Other choice
The Establishment organizes things to do erase base system that just like being in a prison
I wouldn't want to have to go get in the Aryan wing of the present but I did not be killed
I agree that there's a lot of Thai
Toxic nasty
Auntie White
Rhetoric and even anti-white discrimination policy
That are emerging from
The GOP does next to nothing to actually
We'll talk about
Moderate compared
The Democrat leadership Shane White
You're not saying no
Then you're like a little demon
Self
Then then then you are they very small evil
Thank you Alex
I'll take that
There's almost a dismissive like humoring that's going on
Spencer has so much more power in this conversation
And I think that's what Alex is doing okay I think he recognizes that like
Spencer is
Authority
And I need to bring us together a little bit
But also Alex realizes they like the whole premise of this interview you said it multiple times already on the show is that
He thinks that he's false opposition
So that is what needs to be dealt with your false opposition but you're not
Well
Here's the thing
If you're going to make that kind of an accusation or bring up that subject
I think you probably want to do it in a careful life
As opposed to just blurting it out
Alex.
But my big be forgiven first
Is that your synthetic and you're working for the global equipment
I'm not
Decker working to the globalist
What I was saying before was it
This whole episode Alex has been saying is going to confront Richard Spencer about how he thinks he's synthetic and working for the globalist
Alex is so on his heels in this conversation
And Spencer is maneuvering him so well that the only thing you could do is blurred think you work for the globalist comment
That's a joke man I've ever seen First 48 hours I've ever seen
Do you know when they do those
I like
Enter those tents interview scenes where the guy is like
They're interrogate
In the trying to figure out those always start with did you do it and then accepting whatever answer that right
Did you do it no okay cool get out of here
You can see how easily Spencer was able to take that as a sincere question
That's a no then move on
Spencer's in complete control of this conversation and Alex is completely wasted the only arrow we thought he had in his quiver
He thought he was going to ask about the white nationalist perspective on Trump was a
Spencer would say the Trump wasn't mean enough to the brown people and Alex could work with that
Or something
That didn't work out
Now he's forced to
Throw is supposed knockout
The globalist accusation
And Spencer doesn't even
Flinch
This is just sad this is like
It's ridiculously bad
The only reason people even enter
Pain that like all white people are bad bulshit is
Because of guys like
Alexandra
If I didn't know there were so many of these white Nashville
Close out there it would never occur to me to think that all white people are bad
Write other than our history
Wow
So Richard Spencer's starts talking about like there's an interesting thing with the the globalist
Accusation
And that is that Richard Spencer does recognize the global
Possession is a necessary part of the modern world
Ian so he talks about that a little bit and
Alex just can't handle this s***
There is a
Basis
Or identity politics
That isn't just a
Globalist
Or is it just some bad
Policy
The Democratic
We live in a globalized world
We don't live in a world where your
Eat your Consciousness is form
By your neighborhood or maybe you're nice small nation-state at most we actually live in a world where we
And the
Major fissures of this
Upcoming War are
Are going to be racial
Cultural
You are a white man whether you like
We're not your perceived
As a white person
Establishment
Supai Emigrant
Refugees and migrants and etcetera
Identity is
Upon Us in this time we need to plow everything not
Geology of freedom and Americana that unifies they want to make it
Racially-based
Erase base system
Have that warrant
Until I see you playing in as the other side of the left trying to make it right space
Eastbay
About those two models
I think it's okay to have that discussion
It's not good to bad
The left pushes erase space
You are correct about that I'm saying
You how did you come upon your ideas your system who you are and what you're pushing for
That's
That's so bad some good work right there
I don't I don't even know exactly what Alex
The same
No clue
No idea what he just said I don't know what he was trying to say
Richard Spencer is
Being a mess
But he's also giving concise points
That's a better artist for Alex to argue against
Yeah well you know
Avenue debate between these
The I'm having a debate between these two systems or whatever
Is that translates to
What do I do it's going on getting my ass beat
Yes
I do wish they would just play like Civilization instead of war game using the race war that's coming sure
Civilization it's fun
And the other problem to that I think is really intrinsic is that
I don't think that Alex can really argue with a lot of things
Spencer saying
Because some of the
Conclusions about like
We just got to have a all us weights together
Do you like it or not
You're white which means you got to fight with the whites
The upcoming War
Might agree with that but wouldn't want to say it
But a lot of the other stuff that he's talking
Talking about is right in line with Alex's rhetoric
The concept that the coming
War is going
Racial and cultural
Like that is that is
Infowars 101
Absolutely
So the fact
So much overlap exist
Steer it becomes very difficult for Alex to have any kind of a
Conversation that
Involves
Counterpoint's pushback
Follow-up questions
And that's why you see you like Alex
Rambles is nonsense but
Got rear-ended this stuff and then goes to where'd you get your ideas
What because he thinks that the global he thinks that the rates were is coming but it's because the globalist are drumming up
People from the other racist to hate on us
Play the race war is coming
And we all should buy together cuz white people.
Richard Spencer into making whites identify as absolute because
Spencer's work
Thing for the globalist
So
In order to
Make this even
Worse
I was hoping you would
Spencer man he is
He knows what he's doing
We need to be proud
Out of ourselves we need to
We need to be tough
Because one thing that I really like about you to spy
Criticism
That you are a bull
Gold top
Man's man and that's a
White racing stabile apologizing
We need to stop
Cena beating around the bush on issues
Add we need to be proud of who we are
In terms of how I
I came to these ideas
IComfort
From great.
Background idle wonderful childhood 51
Wonderful parents
I could have just gone in and become a warrior and
I made a lot of money
When we come by at because because the right rally were all former Democrats
I have no idea of Richard Spencer prepared for this interaction and new the
You can easily compromised Alex with flattery
Orbeez just intuitive enough to read the desperation and median
Listen Alex whatever the case
He comes in with the perfect compliment that Alex can't help everyone over by but not only
You like you said Galaxy's a tough guy but on top of that
Alex is what white men need to be like
That's really hitting Alex
Exactly where he lives
Yep and you can see the end of that clip as Alex is going out to break he's almost walking back his suspicions about Spencer being fake
He's capitulate
He's explaining why he was suspicious as if to show all these cards
What he's trying to apologize by laying out what made him suspicious which that almost looks like I'm sorry
Fuse because five of the six were former Democrat so that's why I thought you were controlled opposition
Now you have proven beyond a shadow of a doubt since you're not a lawyer
I know I look that's why I was a re-look
You're great I'm a big strong boy we're all having a great day
So I when I get back from break Alex explains
That reason for his suspicions
And
Like
It's
So lame
Okay so rubber tree Spencer's here weather
Talk to him himself near thing from his vows
Y'all got some of the background here
Classic in Ocala
Prove that
Then you guys have the unite the right rally
Flash
Out of that they blame Trump
And then up most of the leadership of it we're like
No I was supporting Obama but not an hour
Hillary two years ago now I agree with Richard Spencer and where
And it just looks like the left
Creating a group to identify with Trump
Deseo look he's a white nationalist
Out there saying that
And doing that
Dialectic
The problems and you Collide them together
Create the
Synthesis
What do you think is really going on here and then who are you really
First off
I did not organized
O'Reilly I was in
Invited to speak at at and I was at top
Build gas etcetera
It is a perfect example of why Alex needs to do his homework
His big conspiracy theory by Richard Spencer working for the globalist to create some white nationalist
So you know
Stop this big event to tarnish the Sterling reputation
Necropsy spiracy
Hinges on the idea that Spencer had something to do with the unite the right rally
If that's not the case
The whole thing falls out
Because Alex doesn't really know what he's talkin about who he's talking to he thinks Spencer was one of the organizers of the rally and he's decide
I did with no evidence
All the rally organizer
Like Jason Kessler
Our secret Club
His conspiracy Falls to pieces in 5 seconds
When Spencer points out that he wasn't involved in organising the rally he was just invited speaker
Every piece
Valic suspicions about Spencer is easily dismiss
And now it looks Ludacris
To the audience it looks like Alex doesn't know what he's talking about
And this sort of game would not be so easy to play with Alex or done any preparation
It's interesting because I've looked into it and I
Kind of think that Spencer's Li
I know for sure that Jason Kessler was the lead organizer of the rally and Spencer is sometimes credited in stories and places like
Like the hill is being an organizer
But it's tough to find exact
Confirmation
The splc doesn't list him as an organizer just as the headline speaker
Nnn article in the Associated Press from just
After the rally
They credit him as an attendee
Of the rally
That's said I find it pretty difficult to believe that he was
Did Subway involved in the organization
None of the event behind the scene
And thankfully I don't have to go off insta
Because right now Richard
Spencer is one of the people facing a lawsuit
Over the United right rally
Which goes to trial this October
In the course of the case proceeding a number Spencer's Tech
Text messages were turned over to the court here in a filing
The picture that's painted in these texts is one where Richard Spencer is far more than just a
The speaker at the event
In one text
Spencer's requesting speaker booking
Like he's saying hey what about this guy
Getting in touch
Jason Kessler
We should have this guy
In another Kessler's Consulting with Spencer about needing legal help for an insurance policy
C4 the rally
Do not text you to expect between an organizer in a headlining speaker
They imply relationship
Far more than
Add to that the fact that Richard Spencer held a torch Centric rally
In Charlottesville in May
About three months prior to the unite the right rally
It just kind of hard to accept that he was solely just a headlining speaker at the rally
But all of that will likely be sorted out later this year when
Skates goes to trial
Considering the legal implications of him saying that he was an organizer like if he said the Howard Stern Show makes total sense
Ultimately
Depicts
Point I want to make his
Whether or not Spencer was an organizer or just one of the main speakers
Is kind of secondary to the more important
And that is that Alex's conspiracy
The hinges on Spencer being an organizer of the event
And even Alex
Clearly doesn't know if that's
True
Spencer can dismiss that with a few Choice words and all of Alex's theories look like paranoia
And Alex is made to look like he doesn't know what he's talking about in front of his audience
This is really just a
Display of Alex being outclassed by a very slick
Very horrible person
He's being humiliated in front of his audience
08 you and your fellow organizers of the United right rally
About to the other ones are clearly Secret globalist
That's why I think that you are sick
Secret Club
Wow
What do you think about you
I love it
But white
She's only
Do they make cheddar and white
It's really sad
So
That being
Established
Now
Richard Spencer is free to talk about some of his political leanings
George Soros ending in people
My own personal
Background I never
Democrat
Voted for
John Kerry in 2000
Reasons that I might very well vote
For a Democrat again in 2020
He organizes this rally
Charlottesville
Have a lot of
Ideas
Rattling around in his head
I don't know if he knows who he is
Tobey Maguire
It's not terribly unusual for people
Particularly young people
Different directions
Bobby Lawson was running elihu City facility white supremacist compound
That's all Alex's Howard Howard
No all pretense of a of an adversarial interview
So he's coming Alex is trying to
Need to come up with like
You know hey Jason Kessler used to work that is like
I don't like
Yeah if you read the text
Text that are in that Court filing
There
Horrible to Kessler
They hate
Thank you. There is an exchange between Richard Spencer and this other dude where they are
Like talking about how
They've discovered that Kessler's grandma is Jewish
And they're going to blackmail him if they don't if he doesn't
Leave them alone after the rally
Say f****** hate this guy
I don't like the idea that
What is going to be like well
I'm going to bring up your buddy
Like no I don't like that
Richard Spencer's position
Politics makes more sense than Alex
Like this accusation they like some of these people voted for Democrats like
Yeah I voted for John Kerry because I'm against
I hated you
Didn't you hate towards consistently against
And I am willing to vote and backup that position now I'm sure I'm sure it felt great for you to run around and you
Yell about Ron Paul we all knew Ron Paul wasn't going to get elected in George W Bush's a f****** warmog
So
Yes I voted Democrat
That makes
More sense and the explanation
People particularly young people have you know they tend to go in different directions
That is it that is
Much closer to reality than the picture that I'll explain
And the reason why this is dangerous
Is because
Richard
Goddamn Spencer is making way more sense than Alex on Alex's own should absolutely
Because
There are defensive bars
Solo
Alex's accidentally allowing him a platform
That not only normalizes him
It makes it look better than that
Man
Are you I want to say I don't know if I want to say this but I don't know if this is
I don't either
I really don't know if this it cuz if I could have an accident on Alex's bar
But I don't know if it's an accident based on whoever book this morning
I think Alex wanted to come off better but I do think that the point
Was to
Platform
As well as I struggled as well as like
Grab attention for
I haven't got the balls to talk to a wire
I struggle with what I say
The motivation would be
And I think for me to actually say
What We Alright this is why he's doing this I think I'll be a responsible
Feels like that
King is the editorial
You know
Subway but I mean again like we talked about on the last episode you can have people on if you have a
Confrontational
Approached
At least pretending that's what he's doing
So you could easily say like well
He executed terribly that is intention was right
Back on the stupid the evil continue
That is
A possible
Like I was going back and forth with like what is
The reason for this happening
And I think a big reason for it is
They're both white identity guys
And
Richard Spencer's recently broken
With Trump
That is
Something with relevant to Alex
I think he wants
To bring him on
Humiliate him yet because Oye globalist would do
That motivation makes total
Similarly I think
That there might be a kernel of it that is
I want to bring on someone who's demonstrable a white nationalist white supremacist
I distance myself from them
Because everyone thinks that I'm that
If I'm publicly disagreeing with this guy
Then
Right
I think
I think that there's possibly a very complex
Motivation
Yeah I agree with you I'm not I'm not I don't think it is simple
Vienna
By any means
It's cuz there's so many different.
And having rich
Spencer on your show
It don't I could almost even see it being a setup
The booker was like
I'm a white nationalist and I want to get these views out and I know Alex doesn't have a shot against this guy
Yeah you know I'm losing my mind
All possible explanations for why this is happening as being
Possible but I don't
I think the psychology that Alex
Consistently expressive
Leaves me far more towards
Like he's going to eat wants to have him on to provide some
Some sort of a distance between them
Whatever energy have the Builder
Example address
Being pretty
Clearly that so it's more likely that that's
The situation
I think also that's not taking it
Into account the amount of differ
Prince there is
Spring 2015 Alex in 2020 absolutely
Lakeview
Even if his intention was
To do the same thing
I thought you was doing
The David Duke interview
The circumstances aren't
Same
Is bad
That we can agree
How did main criticism
Is that he thinks that he's false opposition music
Believe
We are I think I think their criticisms is just
Squasht
Position like that
Created
That is not who I am
I'm.
You and I might have similar origins in the sense that
Young Angelina
There was something wrong with the world
So at this point Alice has made his accusation
Spencer's
Responded to it in the negative
And Alex has accepted his claim that he's not false opposition
If you're paying attention
That means that Alex is just a deuced
He's talkin to a legit White
It should be the point of the interview where Alex takes issue with Spencer's white nationalism
But that is what I see
I see Alex and well
Who are you then it opens
He opens the door for Spencer to create Report with it by saying I bet we're a lot alike when we were starting
This is manipulation
And Alex
Completely unaware
Or totally fine with the fact that
But he's being played
Yeah did Spencer like
Call pechanec before this just being like give me give me some give me some Playbook here
Let me know what
Steps I need to take
And then I'll get him saying that he's a Nazi by the end of the
See I don't I don't think that's necessary like I think the
You know like the flattery
Stuff I think that would be something that someone who has some awareness of how people
Are communicating would pick up on and be like all right I'm going to flatter this guy and he's going to roll over
Mmm if you have any understanding of
Alex's talking
Pinpoints in his worldview
Sure you could Taylor whatever you're saying to be like
This is going to be in line with you
Or
You could just
Be a white nationalist and say what you believe and there's going to be a lot over
Just a natural thing that happened
Yeah that's true
Because they
At right after that after he says like
Probably very similar, got there was a problem with the world we identified
He starts talking
That problem is nonweiler
Right
Did you listen to this clip
Anybody who listen to Infowars
A lot of this stuff
Really familiar
I wanted to understand why my people
Pulling our civilization have been so demoralized
We are not able to stick up for
For ourselves and our
Are people
Our future why we
Stewie Richie unilaterally disarm
Why we have this black
Black cloud hanging over our heads whether it's
Slavery Woodhall
Holocaust or or so on
Venting us
Acting in our own interest
Being great
From golfing to the Stars
To put it
You can go by yourself
Guilt comp
Plaques
That is always weighing us down
This is so close
Do so much of the stuff Alex talks but he talked about going to the stars all the time
He's wanted understand why why people were made to
A few of his guilt
Alex's like
Primary emotional
Driver
Is this
Desire to
To not feel that guilt but he feels like
People are putting on him
There's so much here that if you are a
Committed Alex Jones follower you'll hear this guy and you'll be like
Man Richard Spencer's Macon
Good points
I thought he was a bigot
Right-of-way
Right
Now
Alex
Then
Spencer gets talked about Trump
A little bit
And
Somehow that's
More
I think this is where their paths diverged a little bit and I don't think they're able to
Define
Not really
But I
I think that their perspectives are fairly interesting because all Alex has is like soda
Surface-level talking
Pinpoint
And I think that Richard Spencer is
A little
Closer to Acura
In terms of what Trump was doing in his campaign
A little bit earlier when you showed that
Give me getting punched
IND
They were creating a dialectic
Donald Trump
Created
Dialect
Donald Trump
Calling upon race
Even if you wouldn't use that word specifically
He told
Directly particulate the RNC that
That I am your man I'm going to stick
America
American Dreams 2
Graichen is out of
Control
Maybe your guy
This was
Implicitly is it was explicitly Nationalist and let's
Break it was an imp
Illicitly racialist
Meraki has
A white country
Entire political
History that's what Donald Trump was about he was actually
Calling upon these Energies
In a way that no other Republican but he's calling for you and those that want to divide us
It's okay for America
To exist in
All of Alex Alex Alex
Well.
RNC with a rainbow flag
Abby also went and
Unifier but also stand up for human life
Mastiff
United States of 19th
50 could have been Unified
WYD in a kind of nationalist message we were to a very large degree
Cold War we are polarized
Polarize down racial lines to a very large degree
As opposed to the 1950s
Country is
Fragmenting into small communities
Olympic totally racist
It's wrong and needs to be decried
Autoimmune response
Aligning upon race
Just like a warden controls a prison through race that's all
We're going to have to accept this reality
We're not going to come up with some nice
Public and conservative leader who's going to unite
That is more ridiculous
Ito outlandish thing I've ever said minorities
What color they are
I'm sure you can
Find individuals like that
General Metals
Highest level
Just don't I just don't
Buying what you're saying I see the media trying it
I see you was playing the part on the other side if you don't know if we'll just come back longer segments
I'll try to give you the floor for at least 5 minutes and see what you have to say goodbye
I think because of Alex's incompetent
Flailing he's going to me to use the terminology of that the community
He's allowing his audience
Be kind of red pill down this road of of like
Yes Alex these are problems but sooner or later you're going to have
I have to accept the reality that
You're not going to get some guy in here is going to unite people
Explicitly what the conservative people are against
Height
And I think the
Whether or not Spencer is right
About what Trump was doing
He is accurately describing how a lot of people heard Trump
Message
And Alex refuses to accept
He refuses to accept that a lot of things that jump a thing
What specifically tailored to be heard a certain way by white nationalist in White Sulphur
Probably because of the influence of people like Stephen Miller
Alex
Is constantly said lovezinho
So it's an almost an Ouroboros oh yeah but I don't know
I was trying to think of the word while he was talking
I think it's I guess it's maybe lessig
Exhausting
To listen to this b******* just because he's saying the quiet part
Yeah you know like I don't have to work
At all and he's just like
Trump is a white nationalist that's why we voted for him and I'm like that
Andy singing Folsom City
And he doesn't jump around to all this like extraneous b******* like Alex does
I'm not tired speaking in Little Nugget
Of like a scattershot
It is almost
Meant to wear out your attention
Absolutely sure of Alexandra
Because he comes off
Smart
Right now
That might be boring
Let's suppose I don't know I don't fully know how people would experience it
But I do think it runs the risk certainly of being heard of that way by his listen
That's a real
That's a real danger that Alex has a responsibility to be aware of
Even if he pushes back a little bit defending Trump calling for Unity or whatever
Yeah that's not that's nobody's
Going to buy
Trump was calling for you today
It seems
Hard to swallow
Richard Spencer is
Far more attractive
Right
On this interview
So if you if you were deserted dominance deflected all of Alex's criticism
Is Big accusation
Look like s*** and now he's suffocating himself before him
With only this sort of
Surface-level talking point push back
Talking over Spencer whenever he's
We are trying to make his point
So in this next clip they get back
And Spencer starts talking about how he wants homogeneous
Is population
I'm sorry
The globalist want imagine
Populations of everybody
Intermix
Yeah and Spencer want slaves
Why is everybody confused
It's more accurately
I think we actually have to look
2fa
To understand what
Global US1
Cuz we see it everyday
Differentiated Mass
Of humanity
The Aulani
Planetary scale all eating McDonald's and shopping and charging things on credit
I hate you so much
Sacrament agree actually
It gets even worse
They want that version of globalism that is not what I want
You could call civilization ilysm or identitarianism or racialism
We have real vril unify
Cultures
How they that are part of an historical tradition
You can look
Forward to a future
That is connected to their path
Don't want to turn the planet into a giant shopping mall
Europeans to be European to pursue our path
Africans to be African I want Indians to be
Indian
ReDiscover themselves
That is what I am about
How can Alex argue with
What What In His
Serta rhetorical Arsenal
We have to be like
No country should
Just be one ethnicity
Yeah I know
Are other ways it's a Spencers frame in the beginning of that argument with like
This is what the globalist one
They want everybody to be cookie cutter all the same one world is a big shopping mall
Alex's gas and hang with him at the beginning
He can't
Then be like I disagree with your conclusion that I helped you arriving
But that's f******
I hate that
I hate that so much at such an inverted bulshit
Buick Reatta
What we live in the city
There are people from every f****** culture here we have parades for Puerto Rico's
We have gay pride parade we have food from everywhere we at we celebrate
All of these different cultures all of the same place
Both together and separate
But that's part of the joy of it and I and then he's talking about all these other places where it is
I grew up in a small town of homogenized with nothing but white people and everybody ate a f****** Wendy's and shopped at Walmart
That is what
He said that he's again
I f****** hate him
I hate him so much
Wow
So much
You're going to hate Alex more I think in this next
Did Mike down for this cuz I think it was
The Christian Western ethos was The White Man's Burden
Build a civilization to develop technology to go into all these countries and really not exploit people
Build them up give them science those population
Load
Then the modern Corporation technocrat
World
Christian ethos
And then bring the whole thing down
By The White Man's Christian quote burden
Anyways
Population
But now that's being used as a weapon against the West
Wow
Civilization to all these other countries
And then be demonized
For it
He could have just stopped
Bright when he finished the Kipling reference once he was there I was like
I got it
Yes you think colonialism is great and definitely not what that leads to is no it's a good thing
We actually did great
Bright
God I hate the worst
That's the worst
The help like
Push back at all again
The things that Spencer saying like that's not going to be a rebuttal
So
Yeah totally
Spencer saying that globalization
Is normal
Which is a very unfamiliar conversation on Alex's show
And it actually does eventually Force Alex
To express that globalization isn't bad
Global never heard him make on the show
Because
Spencer's
Clearly think there is a global community that is
Real
We got to get away kind of from
The Nationalist Globe Global it's divided
And move toward the synthesis of
Civilizational racial consciousness
That is how the world is
Breaking down
Are major figures in this economically globalized world
On the basis of civilization and race and culture in the deepest sense of the word
Now
Richard you know at the highest levels of the global system are actually very very race
You notice that
I'm starting to like these guys
All the scientist
Project
So they can just accelerate
Yoga challenge
Hegemonic
System of the
I think Spencer's is letting Alex talk
Honestly
Just rambling about the
Take all the good
Sucks
Search keep on going once you're done I'll get back to
The talkin smart
I'll get back to you at least use in sentence structure I will continue laundering white nationalism in
And calling I'm a racist
This Christ
So Alex and his next clip is
Complaining about the media and MSNBC in particular and he's like they're like
And
Rich's burgers do not talk about my fuhrer like
That it leads to an interesting Exchange
Need to understand ourselves
Europeans
Water
People
On this planet
Particular Destiny and a particular charge
Well there's no doubt that the closest thing to Hitler is MSNBC I mean that's just butt butt from the position that
That white people at
MSNBC
Has the purest Hitler message I've ever seen
It's just from the
Whites are bad instead of other groups are bad for my from an area north
Nordic perspective that
Socialist
It's Hitler but from the other
And surely I mean you say that
That what you're saying
It was just a man
It's Ray
Baa major
We need to understand why
God
Our
Consciousness and also our challenges can be varied if
Let's talk about Hitler
The real Hitler on the other side
That was me calling on answer
Possible got your question I can think of everything about Hitler bad
Do you like Hitler
No
I would go so far as to say I strongly dislike her latest guy
You start with he was just a guy that I know where you're coming from
Yeah
But you see this like this is
High-status Behavior
Yeah the way that Alex is like saying you're msnbc's close to Hitler and the he's just laughing off
Even after
Used to having something like that like having to defend a position that he just Rambles out
Yeah he's used to working with like
F******
Two-time losers who need Alex in order
Exist
Employees are potential employees are Barnes is going to flub a question like do you like Hitler
Associate grifters
Laura Loomer
ALEKS contabil
Yeah msnbc's I K like yeah you bet it is
They're all evil
Give a s*** about that
He has his own
Industry or whatever he doesn't need Alex
So either
What are you talkin about Alex's used to that
Alex has to explain himself
The answer is ridiculous
A Richard Spencer even after the exclamation
Yeah I get home to get what you're saying I think you're trying to say MSNBC is bad
And I don't like
You bringing my boy Hitler into it
God that
That should be this simple
God you're so
Easily called enough
You're nothing
If your answer to do you like Hitler is not know
Then you're not see I don't understand how that
A complicated question
It seems like it
So Alex at the end of the clip said they would get back from break
What's up with the real hair
We know what that means that means no not not specifically
Is he's no Steve yet
It is that Hitler was set up
Kind of narrative
So you Rambles for about a minute or two about his normal talking points.
The Rothschild which is
Weird
I guess that mean that's a big part of this couch clearly said that he's researched
Improving it
But you didn't bring that up he just talks about how like
You know Hitler was set up by the globalist
Add soy
If you listen to
How This Ends
I think it would be a fair description to say that Spencer is kind of amused by Alec
There's like an elevated like I look at you
Hitler was a creation
Then shut up
Destroyer up and then bring down that model but then bringing the scientific behind the scenes model
The IBM and others
Hitler
That you are controlled you just need to watch out
And I understand that you might be working
By the system by
How they promote you another thing because you're helping create
One part of that dialect
Class if they're wanting I mean if you ever
I thought about that
Diives
Jurors and roll I might play
Not in a bad way
Tell you very seriously I am for real
Passionate about these ideas I care
About our future
I'm My Own man
That's all I can say is I mean for better for worse I'm not
Globalist
We probably need a
Why Soros out there while we actually
Serious movement 4
Google change
From the stage of his
Sweetest one individual free
Freedom in concert
Tatoosh ilysm and so on
No
You're actually going to need major
Asterisk
We're going to need people
Behind the scenes
In order to accomplish this
You get serious about that
Add a realistic about it
So there's a meanie scoffing when I'm not paid by globalist
He's like oh ho ho you'll learn when you grow up
U-save-it MSNBC is
This is ridiculous couple times
And so Alex brings up
Soros is a Nazi collaborator constantly with people
It's almost a litmus test
Best of like are you going to go along with this everyone knows it's not true
Seeing
Universally
Everyone is on Alex's show goes along with
Richard Spencer
Hitler
That is not a smear Richard Spencer
Response
In a way that I've never heard any
Pulling back from that usually needed Soros
Nazi collaborator did help Roundup
Hello Jerry
On 60 Minutes
Funny that the guy
You say is the polar opposite I guess of what you're trying to do actually work for the Nazis
Looks it's a Taurus had a beastly it's strange life history
And in Soros also has it been
Complicated relationship with
Israel war
To be American
Policy stablish Mehndi opposed the Iraq War
It's a complicated
Story
The notion that George Soros is pro white or or racialist
Find some win some way is completely ridiculous agree with you for the dialect
The other side of what you
Okay
That is
Real loud
Yok
You can hear the eye roll
Yeah sure
Alright Alex whatever
That is
Funny because
Spencer is a white nationalist
Oh yeah so he doesn't
Don't need that
This yet
Hide behind George Soros
Pretend being an obstacle to
Alex
Come out here with me we love Hitler let's just say it
Come on buddy I hear you. Hold hands and walk
Underneath that rainbow
And burn the rainbow to the ground
At what this demonstrates I think it's some ways is the way in which these narratives like sores is not the
Collaborator and stuff like that those are the things that are used as a mask in order to hide behind
Yeah and once you're out now and people just know what you are and what you're about
You don't need that mask anymore makeup b******* about Soros
I love Hitler you can
You can just
Open Libby like a pretty complicated figure that
Is a lot of stuff in his politics in it in terms of his life that are
That are so complicated
And and
The Alex's will premises that Source was a Nazi collaborator and
It to imagine it has that politics is ridiculous
That's that's funny
Really
Many
Any I think your might
There may be few but I mean baby like Dina Del doctor Dean Adele
Maybe one of the only people who like really
That kind of
Smackdown looks down a little bit news a bit more Joyce
Yeah then that's where I've not heard many people especially lately
Come in and just be like
Almost
Patronizing
It is it is so Stark
In contrast to how simple
Simple how much more simple your life and explanation
Get when you're just telling the truth
About you believe instead of
Hiding behind 300
Complicated conspiracy theory lies and I would freeze you up
Sort of demonstrate
Whether or not you're calling people out straight the lying and the deceit
Someone who is hiding
Yeah and you can engage with reality in terms of Soros and be like that he's a complicated figure I can say the
Because
I hate him for Pikachu
They get to talk about what Spencers view the future is
Which is great
But if you listen to this pretty carefully I think you'll see a couple of inches
Senses where he's directly attacking
Some of Alex's core beliefs
And because of the way this interviews gone I don't
Big Alex has it in him
To stand up
I'm self the future and what you thinking on full
I think Maya media view of the future is
Basically more of the same
United States is suffering from a car
White death deaths of despair
People who are
Hooked on drugs
No sense of the future whatsoever and are are literally
Figuratively just
Doing themselves
I think there is going to be more of this in the future
But there will be a reaction to this here I guess
Kind of agree with you
There will be a point in which white people starve
Collaborating together working together as a team
Forging their own destiny that we start we stopped unilaterally disarming mice
I understand
There Is Power
Collective
The team is going to destroy
Individual Epona
Eventually White
Families are pro-life
Communism if they're racist
All that's kind of individualism at some level you know about saying we don't want the state power
You just want to be left
All that kind of stuff
We're never going to be left alone we should get
Get that out of our minds we probably won't leave other people alone
Meanie. No.
Rise to the challenge as opposed
Just saying oh just leave me alone I'll be okay
Give me my rights or things like
We need to start being the bad
Classes of History again
Right direction
We need to ride to that Chow
Why do people in general need to push a pro-human
Anti Human level of takeover debt that Beast
Admitting their own megalomania
. and I'm laying down the shield
And if you look at what you were just talking about
And then people committed suicide in the death of everywhere
It is because there is a racial attack on whites being directed
Bill Tanis come in Hollywood
Club was combine who are the enemies of all Humanity
So
Aces right there
So what you have is Spencer laying out his view is going to come and that is
Basically we need to have Collective
Action in order to take over apparatuses of state power and
Will be in charge
And ruin everything
With that
That world is you in employee
And what about you know that
Come down on you if you're into the Second Amendment
These are the most
Deeply held beliefs Alex as
Richard Spencer says they're weak
Yep those are weak we need to control the state apparatus we need to embrace
The state
The power of the state
We need to create an authoritarian
Yeah
System
And Alex
Everything
He
Professes to believe
That should be
The single worst insult anybody has ever said that every
F*** off my show
You person who you what you would love the government do you want a bigger federal government please
Yeah you should know that you think that you're going to get your
Cool White
Hey guys in there for the government but you know that it's just going to be used against you
Operation you can't allow them to do that it'll like that should be his
Pro-gas something
You need to prove that he is the exact Olay I'm just fight for produce
Chelation
Yes exactly has been
Banquet yep
By Richard Spencer
Richard Spencer because
Like
Like legitimately there is something Alex could have done
Like he could have argued
Summit
Will be difficult with his established position set really really
F****** hard
Retain your beliefs
And argue against Richard Spencer
But he could have prepared
You could have watched any interviews that Richard Spencer is done
Any of the streams that
Spencer's been on where they discuss some of these issues
You could have figured out some of the tricks that
Uses
You could have figured out what what's a week
What's a point
You could ask him about Hitler
DNA
Like that would even really work that
Do you see what the Yeah Yeah Yeahs
That's even like attack that he's had many times
So like you could have done more preparation and been able to handle yourself a lot better
But like I said I don't think
I think he was destined to lose
Because
Of the
Beliefs
That are compatible
With
And Alex isn't good
Nuance
Specific
He's explicitly again
Nuance
Spices
Which might be the only real way
To have this conversation and not come out looking stupid
Because I mean if you were to
Take some of these talking
Points that Spencer has
I am trying to differentiate them from your own
You really need to get into Theory you need to get into like a pretty deep
What's the
Distinction between your version of whites are under attack at mine
Well and then Alex would have to try and do some heavy lifting in order to
To try and rationalize why would he is expressing isn't white nationalism and what Spencer is
Saying is
And Alex just can't do that
Even with
A ton of prep I don't think you'd be able
To do that
Enough about being a white nationalist when you've already explicit
Dudley said there's a problem
It is it is
Again so f***** up
How easy how easily Richard Spencer is
Cuz the ideas that Alex and so many of these guys
Espouse
All logically end
With extermination or enslavement
Right always
And Richard Spencer is just out here saying we probably won't leave people alone which is like oh so you know that it
It's going to end it
Extermination or enslavement
And you're just out there this place
Or displacement but even then
Displaces people you think
But he's in his a world white Nation do you think they stopped at the border
Of course
Knock knock
It would end up being pretty a
Empire Orienta
That's the only way that they live he wants everybody to look at up at him with a
Is Bhutan there
He's f******
Crazy yep so here's where the interview ends and I think Alex complemented Richards
Well I got to say
I would have them back on I want people on the show it just
Play just turns into
Trying to like
But but I appreciate you coming on the show
And I are you going to be in Virginia
Next week I'm going to be there in a DC at the women's March
Well I might come
If you're there sure
Yard
Again
Yeah that's great
He's completely laundered this dude to his audience I mean
Jesus Alex do you want him to rub your belly now like what is going on here stop short of offering him a job
Yeah
He just want them to be on-air personalities that he can interview from time to time
I don't see I don't
I don't see that being like
Not possible I think Richard Spencer Mike show up on Alex's show more
Future I believe it
This is the worst
Yeah
Yeah it's disappointing it's a piano
But it's not surprising
The way that Alex has been operating
In present-day like
Michael Jones on
Steve pieczenik denying the Holocaust and Alex not batting an eyelash
Like that there's a real Trend that's happening
Richard Spencer being on the showing and basically just being presented as
An anti-racist compared to the last I can't I can't
Bedspreads
In the face that's very productive
But that's no it's right in line
It's right in line it's it's the same kind of hail that we've been going down but
God if you say that anywhere near me
So
Spencer's gone now and Alex starts talking about
Some of the stuff is much more able to stay on WIC
Perceives to be the message
When he's not
Talking to Richard
There's a movement to end Humanity as we know it
Opposed
And that's a little boys and little girls
Children
And
And it's absolutely true that whites are under attack and that the left is pushing it with a marxist-leninist agenda
But I believe were smart enough to expose
How's that and change that
We are
Submitting to their political agenda
So now that Spencer's laugh Alex feels more able to
Stick to the message which is still pretty race
Fairy races
Yeah it's a fairly consistent spiel about how the globalist are attacking everyone but let's focus on the white part of the equation
I think it highlights a point that
Pretty important
And that is what Alex is only differ
Richard Spencer in terms of how they see themselves
Spencer's pretty open
In about how he's just focused on wipe
Alex pretends to care about all people but weirdly every single thing he seems
Talk about
Pressing issues he covers
You have to do with white pants
Well that's because they're under attack I mean when the other when the other groups
And racial groups are
Are the main people under attack
I'm sure you'll come
Right course
Right it didn't see it seems like that's the
Fake
Call Vic
Between the minutes
It said it's only opt
So Alex starts talking about immigrants
And
He seems to express that he's fine with second generation
Immigrants
The majority of people being brought in right now
Are being totally made dependent and brainwash and used to drive down wages and Abby racially-based
People that have been here a generation or two now
What color they are
They get what's going on
Generation Z shows that
That is the least white generation
The American history
And all the poles of studies are the most conservative
See
How that work
Brown
It's because
They're living in this Clash
See that it's a load of crap
Now that doesn't mean you become a bleeding heart and run around apologizing
Because you're white
Swastika armbands on either in my view
What
Giant who invited you
Choose to run their flags that way they want
That'll be a group of non-whites that have decided to come at me because I'm white
I'll be all the other brown people that didn't choose to be with that pirate
What are you talkin about so so in this scenario
Did you try inviting
Are there any non-white people that you were down 42 wiper it out
Read order to keep everybody else out
Outside on
That is f***** up
I don't even want to address any of that stuff that's it
But yeah
Eastern white redoubt is
Right
He just talks about it anymore like soda
Abstract
In the future when it comes to it you'll do this
Spencer's like
We need to do this I mean obviously I'm going to join with the whites in the coming race war
But until then
Hey I love second
But in the past I found polls that show that there's some conservative identification among Generations
Z folks
But also that the age group is overwhelmingly in favor of very Progressive politics
When I look at this question in the past I've always come away thinking that there's a
Complexity in the younger set that pulling
Must not
At be able to
On the one hand you can find like a Forbes article citing a UK study found that 59% of gen Z responded
It said quote conservative or moderate views
On social issues
On the other hand Pew polling
From last year showed L Progressive leanings
About even self-identified Republican members
Generation Z
For instance they found that 52% of self-identified Republicans
Zere's
Said that the government should do more
To solve
Which is far higher than any other generation
Genze republican-leaning people are far more concerned about climate change
Are far more likely to believe that humans have a part in causing
Also just generally jenzie is overwhelmingly onboard recognizance systemic racism
Supporting people's pronoun
And a lot of stuff
True even among Republican
I'm leaving members of that group
What it looks like is this
There's some people under 24 who identify as conservative or Republican
But that doesn't mean anything close to what Alex thinks
Does
What are the likely outcomes you might expect from the sort of data is that these people will grow up and realize that their politics are not
Republican-leaning at all and they'll stop identifying themselves that way
Alternatively if there are enough among the generation to retain their
Book an identification
And they're fairly left-leaning ideas along with it
You could see a GOP being pushed to the left by that
I have no idea what to expect but I can say definitively
That laid the Generation Z is not the most conservative
Regeneration
And even if
It's not as liberal as some like to imagine
It's entirely possible that labels mean a
Nothing to gen Z then people like
Alex water realize
His brand of
Conservatism
Is not popular among anyone
Except maybe the silent generation who still alive
That's
I mean
And even out that cuz this is Bernie part of the cycle now I mean it's obvious
It regardless of
Party affiliation there's going to be a difference in perspective from
The baby boomer generation
Who knows they're going out real soon
And jenzie who knows that
When they're 50
They're going to be dying in a giant hellscape
That's going to change your opinion
Future policy
Alex talks a bit about the Democrat
Clinton broken
Coalition
Strategy
And it's interesting cuz he's had Larry Nichols on to yell about it a lot
Actually Larry doesn't yell much
Serta Rambo
I bet about it
But the way Alex is talking about this I don't really
I think you understand what that mean
I don't think he understands what the broken Coalition is
The left have something called a broken
Coalition strategy
Alone people
Then throw together
Right now they're using the attack
And all of white people and white sneaker reject
And getting the
I'm getting the face of the left
Christianity
Only getting a Trace
The racist left then talks
Talk to him
Worcestershire recommend the racist
Minority leaders we should get on but behind almost
All of them
White
PhD Ford Foundation
Weird
Okay well then don't
Then get the weird light
YouTube Foundation people
Right now they're not going to come on
Course not so I don't care about that
Stupid b*******
And his
Strike to save that rich
Spencer's on the left or whatever
Broken Coalition every time I've heard Larry Nichols talk about it this is a strategy that is specifically about prior
One of the things that every candidate would do is prioritize
Straight white
Christians
As the largest demographic block that you're vying for
The clintons
Realized
That you could fight for this demographic
Or you could understand that
There's a lot of people in the world
Who have different
So you could
Bring in the LG
G b t q community
You can bring in the African-American
Community breaking Hispanic voters
The psalm of those
Coalition that are disconnected
Apparently
Because of their individual
Create a larger voting Bloc
Then do you straight white Christian
Action blocked
That is how it's always been described
To me in the way I understand it
But Alex seems to think
It's
Broken people
People who are like individual Atlanta by one person over here one person over there
Not at all what the conversation is always
I think he doesn't understand the topics
She's talking about
I don't know
That's that stupid
Just a few years later
G.w. in the conservatives
Name it better and just call it the big
Tent
How do you get so confused at broken
Coalition
That's so stupid
Yep
So what insects with no wonder the conservatives had to dump it
Yeah
Alex talks about how you know his whole conception is that the globalist and they create two sides and then make
I can fight shirt
Right
But Alex
Prefers the Russian model
They create the two sides together
Fashion model
I know they been attacked I know they brought in all these other group state rochon
Russian suicides down Russian for the first time in decades are living longer and they're having more kids
They're coming back not out of a racist thing the Russians are bad
We like ourselves Who We Are
500 years and we're not going to go down
And we are proud of ourselves you want to work with us to be ready by the group that's right
What to do
We're going to throw your ass out that we're going to kill you
I'm at the poles are doing and that's what the hungarians and Romanians and the checks are doing because they've been in
When they hear again that white people are bad you better let the Muslims in a run your life
You know what
I'm going to run the whole show
I'm fighting to the death Heather winning
Willow
Okay lilacs prefers that model what just
Why is he even bothering to
Saying is I want a Evo
Homogeneous
Is population
All sharing my exact appearances
Values and all the stuff that I say and I want them to wipe out everybody who gets in the way
I don't understand what the problem here is why are people calling me erase
Right at it okay if people come in to the country and they are completely subservient
Jesus
It is just stop it it's an artificial distinct
Huey
You desire is to make
Yeah
Upsetting
I'm almost
What I what I care most about is the people who are getting hurt
Whenever we allow the races
Systemax
That's my issue
All we're doing is fighting all the time
Let's go to a homogeneous whites-only population without nothing bad ever happens when that goes on
Alex is interested in you
Samantha
So if there's one
Shining
Brightspot
That is true second
Is that
Analog time
But Sir Alex brought back one of the hits in this
But one of his greatest
Okay so me weed
Might have spent way too much time talking about in the past
I'm not a big partier but when I was getting divorced
I would go to Halloween parties and stuff
Women
White guy I say
Racist
You tell me I'm erasing
Arab men doing it and left us women I'll just laugh
Baby suck your boots
That's not going to happen either
So we get the Nazi Halloween hat story making a Resurgence in Hawaii
Really weird
I don't know maybe he's in the mood to deflect criticism that he is
So Alex talks about how like he gets
For a lot of stuff
Is talking about
How
Extra-dimensional aliens
Are attacking him
Bees on YouTube
Good point
Me when I say it's offworld
Manipulating Humanity, teaches how to destroy
Are you complaining that no one attacks you for that cuz we we do pretty regularly
Stupid also based on what we're learning more and more about the Project Camelot stuff
Interdimensional alien stuff because usually underneath that is a s*** ton erase
Yeah it does seem like there's a weird overlapping
Yeah and I also think that other people are mocking him
For this it might not be the most relevant thing
That like let's say
A publication like The Daily Beast cover
It kind of Fades into the background
When there's more pressing real-world issues extra-dimensional demons are causing races
Cement giving Global a secret
Space technology
Yeah that's not for right
Interdimensional right-wing
Right
It's a new one I'm starting welltok
We'll see what happens it's one of those things to the lake I could see you at like an editor just being like this is the least harmful
His beliefs
Pascal
We're in Erte mechoso we make fun of it quite a bit
Hey Weekend lyrics
Yeah so I was supposed to call
WhatsApp
Answer
Interesting thing that happens on this call
But I finally got through happy
New Year that new decade
Play roaring 2020s The Roaring 1920s don't be roaring 2020
Roaring 20 20
If you notice that caller wish Alex a happy new decade and Alex's
Very insistent that it is not
The beginning of
New decade is a globalist
Calendars
This caller
Does not get corrected I think this color is obviously a global it's because nobody would make a nickname
Longer than the Roaring Twenties
That was an already long nickname
The double Leroy
I don't know if this guy is a globalist or not
But somebody says in this next clip leads me to believe
Probably not
Impossibly
I'm guessing that I am your best customer info
About $19,000 last year on it
Underwrite the show so my friend God bless you
Real bad
How
Don't know
How do you lose money gambling with his product or something what happened Wonder that's just not true
I can't be
Seems very
19000 what is it everything
Yeah
Animated you bought like a like one of those water filtration
Devices that are like
Oh that's like yeah yeah some of the ones that Alex sells
Surfer like showers
Frozen stuff to water
I could see
I see you pee
Possible
I was sleeping on wise
Yeah I say that
I was
Shocked somebody spent $1,000 on candy crush you like
You can't even
You can't do that
Can you do that
You did
So when's this caller says he spent $19,000 last year at Alex's
Store
You kind of got to get like this guy's got a
You got to let him talk yeah
80s videos
I just want to start with some background
I believe
Based on my
Research over decades now album
World history in psychology
Rachel superjeenius
And I and the thing about him is it with the horrors they were political IQ test
It would be about a 300
I mean
And I've been saying that for years
He is clearly studied Machiavelli he's clearly study Bismarck
He's clearly study son
So he's clearly study Claudius and I can get one of those
Okay man
I mean maybe you should try reading more recent
How can you possibly believe
That I mean how can you spend $19,000 on it
Nevermind of course he believes that Trump is
The single digits by mohbad
Good call
And I'm not going to
So Alex is next with
I got kind of derailed man
Backstory that I had was supposed to be the main story today
But I ended up
Then I was a Nazi for a while anyways let's get back to mainstream Richard Spencer with my audience
I kind of forgot
Well I better yell about it
I probably won't get to the report even though it's our job story
Sunday I can read Friday covered Saturday is it so huge
I got you to the whole show tomorrow on it cuz you can't just
You know you'll be smelling something this big that had you inside the says
These are killing people
We've been covering it up and there's no actual testing and then she's on TV show
All the other topside is saying you don't want adjuvant
People are passed and the doctors don't believe it anymore vaccines are hurting everybody
Intercourse
It's in the Independent Media and okay if you wanted thousand views on my website the band video
Needs to be everywhere the only way it gets out as you but she
Wow that's stopping Public Health
Covering up for drug companies
Vaccines mandatory
Nazi just lied you a shot give it to you know how to give you a shot kills your 10 years later he's got to stop talking about going to come out of this
Violence
Are they keep trying to force vaccines and people get their kids hurt and they get hurt
Vaccine had any corporate head today big Tech heads are going to be fair game
Season
Whoa that's not good
That's not good open season on I guess doctors
The pharmaceutical people because of vaccine
By that
Same
Sort of logic
You could really see somebody making an argument that people who push anti-vaccination stuff should be killed
Like it hate there's open
Season on that because if you could
Create some sort of a causal
Inference between
People
Disseminating
Anti-vaccination information in various areas or let's say
Increased numbers of people getting vaccine waivers on exemptions
Is and then outbreaks of diseases happening
If you could do that
Then
It would track
Anti-vaccination is causing people to be hurt and killed
It's like I don't know that's not
That's not good
So
You just see the canvas sort of lying probably feels good for
For Alex to say
But realistically he's opening the door for people who are extreme on the other side
To justify violence
Against him it's all very stupid
And it doesn't take into account the reality of the situation
It's just blustery nonsense
Is only meant to escalate and make people not really understand the topics it'll be covered being covered
But feel intense
Yeah
And the violence doesn't then they're man
Alex starts talking about Fentanyl and
Now he wants to kill all the Chinese people
I'm not necessarily but a different group
Gwayne a fentanyl will kill you and their lacing everything with it and I just everybody I know as people dying
I am so pissed I must say that anybody in my family gets hurt my Fentanyl
Responsible
MPS
God
That's a law enforcement understands that didn't like cocaine or somebody let some of the slip through whatever
Anybody with fentanyl selling it needs to be executed or Singapore
Millions are getting killed by this crap
Millions
So here we find noted self
Describe libertarian Alex Jones expressing a desire for the state to enact lethal Force against people who are engaging in a market in
Interaction where they provided dangerous substance
The people can choose to take or not
Why doesn't Alex believe the people have individual rights
Why does Alex think that
The state has the right to initiate violence
He should be entirely against his
Basic
Political principles
At least it would be if he were actually a libertarian
But he's not
He's evolved
As many libertarian
Into into a full-on authoritarian
The legal system does already recognized
The selling drugs that result in injury or death require harsh
Four penalties like longer prison cell
Are you sure they don't require execution though positive
What Alex is calling for his execution of drug
And even in his calling for it he's cognizant that his position is in line with you
Horrible
Oppressive States
But he thinks are the big
Evil in the world
And what are the main problems you're going to run into if you try and act a policy like this is where is the line
Many of the people who are selling opiates with fentanyl in them has no idea there's fentanyl in
Should these people be killed too
How do you prove an established that a drug dealer had foreknowledge of exactly what was in the drugs they were the middleman
A selling
It's almost an impossible case to Macon I would assume that what you'd end up doing is
Probably just encouraging summary execution
And now we're at the level
You know what I remember based on
2 amendments
Constitution
Prohibition War
Well I mean they didn't
Just execute people with booze wasn't that what the Untouchables was about
Spider-Man Subway
Further I want to ask this question
What's so special about fentanyl that makes Alex want to kill people who sell it
Sure it's dangerous and it could be lethal but
Soak and tons of other drug
Overdose isn't that from an overdose
Regardless of what Subs
According to the CDC only 67.8% of drug overdose deaths in 2017 were even from
And that's not all fun
Approximately 20% of overdoses involve cocaine
So what did Ike
It would be important for Alex
Explain exactly what it is about fentanyl that may
Makes it okay to kill someone who sells that
But not okay to kill a cocaine dealer
This is over the real issue
Alex thinks he's making the nuance
Cogent point
Like this Sentinel is just so much more days
Sandusky have to kill people who sell it
This is
Exact same line of rhetoric at Auntie drug people abused forever
Yes objectively decided that fentanyl is so dangerous that it merits killing dealer
But using that same path of reason
Someone who's universally anti-drug
To the 20% of odds and 27
Gina Baldwin cocaine
It's a the cocaine is so dangerous that you just have to kill people who sell it
Plus the opiate crisis
This is not just about Fentanyl
Tons of people who are dying or dying
Taking prescription open
Which could be super dangerous when they're abused
Using Alex's line of reasoning it would be possible for someone to advance the position that we should kill pharmacist
Which kind of
I kind of hope this illustrates how absurd Alex
Disposition
This level of Baseline childish and violent positioning
Is really dead
Alex is mad about stuff so he's letting off some steam saying drug dealer should be killed
But the effect of this is normalizing positions that should be way far outside with
Acceptable
But then again
Alex has never really had a problem
So this is probably just some
He's been cool with for a while
You know kept Under Wraps
I hear I hear two things
Things going on
I can hear him
Like
Finally reacting angrily to
Rolling over and letting Richards
Spencer rub his belly
It seems like that probably is
You can't prove it it feels that way
And then tujhe
Just dislike
Because he was talking
To this out
Now whitening
His rhetoric
Is so much more violent
And so much more
Bass round extermination
I think you might be seeing Court like a coincidence that's entirely possible but he's not talking about like
We need to put people in prison this
Straight-up Exterminating you know
It's also still fairly in line with the escalation that you've been going on there for months
Schnauzer like
I can see you
Psychologically the way Alex operates
And how f*****-up he often is after an interview doesn't go the way he wants a Jeff
My sense from listening to it
Like the entire thing
It doesn't really track that way necessary
I think it's more just like this is
More what he's
Doing these yeah yeah
I mean these goats are curated in order
So obviously I don't have the folks
Text Aaron
It sounds like because
The ones immediately after he was fairly
Docent
Linda
Docile
Like
As we get further and further away from it is
You are like
I think it's more
The I think it's more reflection of
How it's
Extremely he's selling this un
Backstory
Cover it on the show
So you needs to make up for a little bit that leads him towards this violent right right it carries over into the the Fenton
I think that's probably but I'm glad you brought that up
Because I think
You could easily
Love you heard by our listeners as like that being the natural conclusion
And honestly
We can't know that might be
What he's going through
Orbynot
That's entirely possible
Yeah
Unfortunately that's how the worth
Takes one last call
Pure on the show
And
I think this caller might be in
Project Campbell
I have something I want really quickly the crew to just promise me to look up it didn't have to be the day for the next few days look up
Salvatore Pius
Before AAA vehicle that
U.s. Navy
Opryland enabled and
Salvatore pioske
Pais
The country music
Literally translates
Savior of our country
This is real
This is really really really real
46th and
So over the past few years Salvatore Pious is
Supplied for patents on behalf of the Navy for a number
Futuristic technology
Including machine that would create electromagnetic
Fields
A zero loss Electric electrical generator
And a compact nuclear fusion reactor
There's literally no reason to believe any of these things have been made there just patent application
Anyone can apply for patents for whatever they want
Not required that they pad
Something that actually exist
Set the time of application
Some people theorize
These patents are part of the misinformation
Can campaign to make other world leaders believe that the United States either has
Or is working on particular things
Which could have the effect
The redirecting
Some of the research
And lead them to wasting a bunch of money down rabbit hole
Seem like something that's within the realm of possibility but I have no idea what's going on
That that is just a theory that some people have advanced eight dimensional chest
And science has proven
That there are dimensions above
And below
All around us
And evil spirits are real
This stuff is being pushed
By people like David Wilcock
Fox TV
Exactly what this caller is saying
Yeah
People in the projects
Camelot side of the equation
Until there's any proof of any of this stuff up that application
You know once there is that I'll start to give a s*** but for now this is really ignorable
What does demonstrates very clearly though is that there's a
Basic lack of reality literacy
And people like this color
Into a certain
Next.
The caller doesn't realize that a patent
Doesn't mean the same thing
As an actual invention
So he's using
Completely irrelevant proved
To claim that the Navy has all this futuristic
Tech
Because Alex doesn't really know the difference either he can't explain it to the college he's making a reason
These two people have different deficiency
But they come
Found each other
The color is a basic misunderstanding would you presents to Alex who supposedly and Authority
In his capacity as that authority figure Alex
Completely abdicate
Any responsibility
Cossetta's call her straight about Patton
In doing so he allows his stamp of approval to tacitly attached to this
It's just bad work all over
Also there's a slight problem with the translation
Salvatore pias's
They are
Specifying what language
It translates
In
And then they know you think it's
Savior of the country
Salvatore does mean savior in Italian but
Highest is country in Spanish
There is a word
4 country hits
Close
In Italian
Spell different
It's not the same word
It's not the word that most Italians would probably use
In that context
Write this is more for like town so generally
So he's the savior of both Italy and Spain
Totally
Station is complicated and honestly it's
More fun to use this guy's
Name the building conspiracies
Yeah yeah
So
A little bit this is sort of how we we end up the show
I just have one question
And it determines whether or not I believe anything that he
What do you think about the Getty
Do you have a
Alex I mean
He's not
Doubling down on this guy the
Listcawler but he
He isn't also bring any reasoning or any rationality into
Because this is space horses this is the craftivist
Space force
Realize that
A lot of hidden technology they haven't rolled out yet and in front wants to do that
The innovators out of this
Out of this job bubble
I don't even bigger one the big juicy one
I will look into it yeah there it is that's an article I haven't
Daily Mail
So the headline of this article in the Daily Mail begins
U.s. Navy has been granted a patent on theoretical aircraft
Theoretical being the operative word there
The article literally says the representative from the Navy has said that the text
Described in these pants is not
Possible
Quote has corroborated by a letter defending the patent Pain by the chief technical officer of the Navy naval 8
Aviation Enterprise James Sheehy
The mode of movement is quote beyond the state of possible
Also for someone who's made a career selling gold in survival Goods warning that the globalist
They're going to collapse the economy
Seems weird that Alex would applaud Trump for escaping the current economic bubble by entering a big
Juicy or bubble
That's just a fundamental
Misunderstanding
The word bubble
It seems like if anything you should recognize that the end result of that bigger it's a bigger
Unless juicy crab
Use Alex's eyes put a Band-Aid on a resume or work
Yep
Do the OSHA
Center Heating
Put a lot of ice in
And that'll solve the problem for a
This seems like a weird episode
I think is really actually very salient
The problem that is going through
Throughout this episode
Largest speaking a lot of hours
Career
This caller is calling in with a complete
Bulshit
Siri
Easy art misunderstanding
Of housing
He believes that they've applied for this patented there for this machine exist
This would be pretty simple to set straight with Ignacio patents don't work that way
Look there's a bunch of time machines that have patents
Doesn't exist can't exist
Rights
That would be something
That Alex
Should
Instill in his audience
A greater understanding of how the world works
So they can be better critical
That's presumably with Alex's mission is
You want smart people out there Absol
Living in the Rio
That'll do it
But because Alex is Maine
Basic
Narratives
Everything that he talks about doesn't stand up
Any kind of critical scrutiny
He needs to have an audience that does believe the pat
It's mean a real spacecraft exists
He has to have that and so
He will never do any of the pushing back on
The callers
In order to help them
Reach
A more critical thinking
Oriented space
This
Nobody has
The byproduct
Of having
A group of people you've brought
Together to think
Uncritically
Exposed to people like Richard Spencer
Dancing circles around you
So when you have somebody like her
Spencer Ron
And you think I'll just because I'm so great and awesome and smart
I'm going to have him on here and he's going to Bow before me with my
Superior
Points I'm correct 97% of the time
After all
I do is interview
Mutual liars and collaborate
Basically people are
Has me so I have a very over it
Inflated sense
Of my ability to make arguments
And simultaneously
I'm surrounded by co-workers and employees who put up with me barging offset
Mike not being given
To me or some s***
I have outbursts all the time the people have to put up with a situation with my employees
Wolf course
I am going to be great at talking with this guy
Guy comes in
Completely dismantles all of CounterPoint
And the audience
It is trained to be
Basically just
You're sitting duck
I hit 1000 playing in my t-ball league
So naturally I can bat another thousand
Playing this minor league shitpost
Yeah yep cool they're sitting ducks
Bad actors
Who are introduced
Into Alex's face in
D Michael Jones and Richard Spencer are
Particular examples of it lately like
If you did any preparation you would know
What you were
Exposing your body
And
Alex
That that's why
It becomes very difficult and understand where you're coming
From where it's like there's a
The plan here
It becomes very difficult to deny that it appears that there is
When the behavior seems very consist
Refuse to be a pattern
Intuit
It's hard
For me to sit here and say like
Alex is just
You know he's just bad at this
Yeah he's inviting these people on like a guy who
Hates Jews very passionately
Dispensaries just inviting tomorrow and he's doing a bad job
It's hard for me to take that position
And I don't fully take that position
I only do so because I don't see any
Like actual hard evidence
Did this is
The plan
Even still
I can't
Deny that
This is kind of what you would do if you were attractive I think that's where we get right back to the
2013 investor
I don't
Functionally
It is the same
You know that's one way or the other I mean it's not my job to parse
How people feel or what they're thinking
I mean it's
My Java parts
That's the difference
Fair enough I will now advise it
I take your position entirely as well and in terms of like this function
Channel difference
Negligible
It's not really important
What the end result is is your presenting
Hardcore biggie
Do your audience under the
Auspices of
Pretending to push back against
Explore what they believe
The same time presenting them in the most positive light imaginable
The function of that is your Sitting Duck audience
Is going to
To think of them in a different way than they
They might have
If they were presented based on what they actually believe what they actually die
So yes I agree with you
My only quibble is at all like
From my perspective if he's doing it
Intentionally
It does change
What you should
You think about Allah
If your titties doing it acts
Accidentally and like because he
White supremacist
Magoo
Fumbling through
His existence
I mean
Still looking at me
Think is pretty bad
Temperature
It doesn't excuse his behavior know but I do think there's a different approach you would take in terms of looking at
Everything is relevant for me
And it is becoming harder and harder to
Allow plausible deniability
I don't I don't know
I don't know
I'm mixed
Yai
Roi feel like
It's it's similar a little bit to me to hearing that
Milo
Wreck recording of Richard
Dispenser
Like
I don't get I don't care
I mean
That is the end result of his white National
That's part of his white nationalist belief if you just even says I'm a white nationalist
I don't care if there's a
Gotcha tape
He's already revealed that the got your tape is is what he think right but got to take out
How to tape is implied
But at the same time it is
And you shouldn't need that like the New York Times should need that to know that you don't give this f***** a
Because they were doing that you know and you shouldn't need bread
Stevens most
To know that he's a f****** Nazi
Me too like you don't need all that stuff
Functional purpose
As opposed to I'm not going to say that I can prove that at
Tape like that exist
But functionally
It might as well have
Right right
You know
Hybrid
I think we have
Similar position
I'm slightly different
Places
Responsibility
Anyway this was a tragic
Episode
I think that
As we see
2020 developing
I wouldn't be surprised if Richard
Bouncer comes back
And I honestly wouldn't be surprised if Alex ends up talking
Irresponsibly with even more
As as things were all along
I'm actually going to disagree with you I think I would be surprised if Rich
Spencer came back
Not because of anything they talked about but be
Because
Alex either
Is going to recognize that he got his ass roundly handed to him I doubt that he is going to
I doubt that too
Entirely dependent on what kind of coverage
That's probably true
America gets a lot of new traffic I would assume he's going to keep going down that road
No I mean like you got
You gotta a trend
Growing not good so I don't look forward to
Where this goes
But we will be back Jordan
Yeah
We have a website and its knowledge
Girls on Twitter
Go to iTunes leave a review it said try to go to other
Castrol apps donate to the
Yes I will be back
Until next time I'm Neal I'm Leo I'm dzx Clark and the juiciest
Bubble
Alexandra first in color with huge fan I love your work