Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as if through the good guy
We are the bad guys
MoneyGram
Stripe.com
Everybody come down
And talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Is the new crew Spider-Man across the room and opened things up in the air.
What's up
I think this one's going to be what are your top three Fast and Furious films
And I will include Hobbs and shots should you so desire
I don't know it's really hard to rank the later ones but I'll tell you for sure that one isn't
In the top three
Yeah I have a soft spot in my heart
2 Fast 2 Furious because the name is hilarious and
My friend named their cat to cookie
YouTube Puscifer
Can cat after cookie butter went away
What is strong
Just the right age
Ludacris is in it is amazing that when he came around at
The hell out of that one I would say it's
It shouldn't be
The top four but I'm going to put 4
Okay in my top three
A four-for-four
For furious I don't know
For furious discounted the only reason that one gets in
Into the top is because I went to go see that with my buddies
Missouri
Dickhole friends we almost
Got kicked out of the theater cuz we were laughing so much
You funny
YouTube funny movie I me and my buddy Burger laughing real hard
Aggressively by people around us very high
Probably drunk
And took me at that experience was really fun like this
The movie is almost
The tertiary experience
Yeah
And then I don't know
All of them all of them
Always found fast5 to be a very funny
Yeah I have no idea what might have been Fast and Furious
I think that would work
Quite remember
Tokyo Drift was great to you love him
Guy one of the actors in it is from Missouri
I was really proud of that
Missouri
There's a lot of talk about that when the movie came out
And they drifted they did
They didn't dka
They also do you like so
You like to drive fast
Basketball
Anyone else I knew
I think
Yes I recall we saw that together
And they keep calling him
Dekay
And
Burger cuz I got
Make a dog talk
What I wear to the movies over call the doctor X
Anyway fond memories of seeing Fast and Furious movie
I know a bit about it but I refuse to strongly rank
But I do know a lot about Alex Jones and I'll ranked him as poor
Bottom three
Yeah dude to go over week
You cannot get out of present-day because everything keeps happening
Yeah so we must pay attention and see what's up
Episode today we're going to be going over January 5th
Through 17
Pictures Wednesday through Friday of last
And you know there's been
Currently
Right now
Ever recorded
This is Sunday
And into next week Alex Jones is out of Studio
He is making a trip to the East Coast
He is going to Virginia rally on Monday Richmond he is going to be in DC I don't know yelling at a
The building Trump is having his impeachment hearing
So he's he's on that
Trip.
Preamble to it
Is this three-day stretch
At the end of last week
And I think there's
Trouble
Pretty f****** hilarious things that happen
But also very responsible very horrible lies that Alex is putting out to the
Pretty bad consequences
Star All Things
Considered but also
Just be his normal standard fare where you lies and people just
Incorporate
Bad Boys
That's so I will get into bunch of this before
YouTube Paul Walker
And everybody who signed up to support the absolutely rest in Powerball
Damn great day and thank you so much
Juvenile policy walk
Text Tara or maybe talk not entirely sure but either way thank you very much
Thank you very much
Text John S
John F
Thank you so much
You're now probably want
I'm a policy wonk
Lee Leigh
Thank you so much you are now a policy wonk
Donated on an elevated level
I'm so first of all catcher thank you so much you are now it's
Democrat
Mr Kevin thank you so much you are now it's like
Money off that heroin
So good
Freakishly large
Catcher And mr. Kevin
We got a Sketcher if he's in
Stealing signs
Oh yeah it should be illegal
I don't have a position on baseball rules
I think it's silly that the infield fly rule
About it I do not know
If I'm making a sound argument I do not know anything about bass
The whole thing
I'd like to randomly be in a game where I'm in a position to hit a walk-off home run
Like I like Robert Redford in the neck
Sure
Whatever however I get there is it in God's plan
So I'm there I hit this walk off homerun
Immediately drop down
Crab walk the bases
Call man you don't know about the unwritten rules of baseball you'd be murdered I've been told that
Imagine a 97 mile an hour fastball at
D-des tells me that
Baseball has a cultural problem that needs to be
Who needs to be a Reformation
Anyway thank you so much Catcher And mr. Kevin
Enjoy the show
Website.com
Sports show
Baby lovey
I'm going to actually let's start with an out-of-context
Stone awake
Was awake
Rock place for that at
Anyway I want to save it
Dismiss something
Things that I think that everyone's probably in
Interesting take on
Which is that there's been some videos that have come out of Alex like at the women's March in DC he's like rolling around town in
When is dump tank
These are all just videos that Infowars
Put out and I'm
Not really seeing a ton of folks taking the bait
Amplifying it and I think that's positive
I'm not particularly interested in this frivolous and desperate attempt to get
Get free press
Give me side like seeing a child acting out
To get attention
If you're that kids parent you need to take that behavior serious
Otherwise
Just leave it alone and ignore it in Jordan
I'm not Alex's dad
So I'm not concerned with this Behavior look at me I got two
Call he's human resource
There are more pressing issues today
Namely
I took the look at Alex's Behavior prior for him leaving on this
East Coast trip
A lot of Alex's focus seems to be on the upcoming second amendment rally in
In Virginia
And his desire to preemptively declare that anything that might happen there that's bad that's going to be.
But there's a little more depth
In his bulshit then immediately meets the eye
And I think it's a wiser worthwhile
For our purposes
Take a look at it
But in order to start things off I feel like it'd be best to take a little moment
To discuss the lead-up to this Richmond rally
And how things got to the point where we are right now
As we've discussed a little bit in the past
Are there bensema messiness
Going on in Virginia
It's better than over-simplification to put it this way but
Pretty simple explanation
For what got us where we are right now is that the 2019 Virginia election
Untap it
And that election cycle all 140 of the seats in the Virginia Senate and House of Representatives were up for re-election
Democrats had a net gain of to see
Seats in the Senate
Which gave him a 20 1219 majority
In the house the Democrats 1855 245 majority
That's giving them control of both houses of the state legislature for the first time in 20
6 years
This naturally led to the right-wing becoming completely paranoid about what would come
In an article in the Virginia Mercury members from the new Democratic majority made it pretty clear that the largest focus of their agenda was
It's going to be reshaping voter access
Set laws
Taking on redistricting
Repealing voter ID laws
I'm passing notes
Excuse needed early voting for every
Currently in system it is now like you can early vote but you have to give total
It seems weird
However
There's another reality
According to polling
Conducted by everytown
4 gun safe
Quote
28% of Voters said that a candidate's position on gun issues was the most important
Issue to their vote
And they found it voters who listed gun issues as their number one issue
Democrats
That's coming from a gun safety group however so you might not find their polling to compelling
Certainly can find other resources that argue that what drove Democratic voters at the polls was healthcare-related policies and climb
A change concerns
I think in the end the picture becomes pretty clear that whatever you choose to focus on
The Democratic party just had a better policy
Please set that appeal to more people right now in Virginia
The reason gun issues were fronts
Center is because
In May 2019 the former city employee in Virginia Beach went on a shooting
Free killing 12 people and injuring four
That was just a few months before the election
But I'll see if you think about it
Virginia state with a long history
A really high-profile Gunn.
You had the shooting at the
Congressional baseball game
2017 the scalise situation
Get the Beltway snipers he had the case of Allison Parker
Who's the news anchor who was shot in the middle of interview
You had the Virginia Tech shooting in 2000
Every state has their own history of gun violence
Virginia's experience some of these really big high-profile cases
So it could make some sense that voters might want to State Legislature that
Lakeside issue head-on
Absolutely
According to w
Beauty VR3 gun-related bills and passed the Virginia Senate
So you know they just need to be signed putting
For sure
The first Senate Bill 35 quote authorizes any locality to prohibit The Possession
The firearm and ammunition in public spaces during permit
Or events that would otherwise
Require a perm
Do you mean they overreach their Authority and they are trying to take our guns away
Some might say
This is basically just saying that he having is that like an outdoor concert or a Saint Patrick's Day Parade you can say no guns
Republic space
You're going to grab them
From people and then go to their homes
You can grab them there
It's The Logical extension
The second sb69 makes it a misdemeanor for anyone
Child
This bill makes it a misdemeanor for anyone who is not a license
Firearm dealer
Buy more than one handgun within a thirty-day.
Even this bill has a
Exemptions
Like if you're buying
Personal Collection of someone's weapon
Estate sale you can you can do that
There's also a provision for
Specific license
You can apply for it to not be
The subject of this one-gun-a-month limit
If you have legit
Reason to need to purchase more than that say for a business
Independence
Security company
Course there's even exempt
Engines for like if your gun goes missing and you report it
You can replace that gun
Within that
Oh and also this totally doesn't apply to literally anyone who has a valid Virginia concealed handgun permit
It also doesn't apply to privates
This is not a very severe bill as there's a whole lot of groups
People who are exempt from
And even people who are not
Are only going to get charged with a misdemeanor if they run afoul of it
People who are in bigger trouble for not following the
30-day rule are licensed
Gun dealers
Who has heavier punishment
Under this new belt which may
Makes sense I guess
This last bill is sp70
Which requires background checks for all gun transfer
Except again
They're a bunch of exempt
Princeton
Gun transfers between family members are exempt
Hazard gun transfers at gun shows and gun ranges
The reason for exemptions for gun ranges in gun shows is because this is not about gun sales
This is what literally
Handing someone a gun
Big Bill is about transferring of
Possession of a gun
Gone to another person
It'll be kind of impossible to require that everyone at a shooting range
Do they have to go through background checks
Being able to shoot it
Target
Best build builds Indies exemptions
Which makes sense
Also makes the bills kind of weed
If the gun weirdo world is good at one thing it's
Getting around laws on tagging
How many calories
It seems like this is a friends they could
Exploit really either they would have any issue
Other than like
The Sovereign citizen to Wooden
Follow it anyway
Right
Cuz I don't follow the crowd in capital letters today
So anyway those are the three bills that have been passed
Appointed recording of Popeye the Virginia
And their way to being put into Act
There are other bills that the legislature has introduced including military-style rifle bands and red flag laws but it's
Seems like fairly middle-of-the-road
Stuff that is
What does what is actually gotten
Whatever the reality of the situation is begun weirdo Community is taking this as an all-out assault on the very basic
Right to have a gun
Part of this is because these dudes don't really have a reason to exist like the people who make a bunch of money off this stuff you know
Unless guns are always
Best interest
To create whatever controversy
Is the camp surrounded esorts
I wouldn't be too surprised if some of the more intelligent among the right-wing
Extremist communities
Also pretty scared about the Voting Rights issues at the Virginia legislature plans to take a condo
We make a great public
Blick case against expanding vote out loud
Tougher to get people on your side when you
Try to make an argument like that you know you can whip people into a frenzy easy
The timing here is what becomes particularly
A troubling though
Because just as these bills were making their way through the Ledger
Just later and if that was on the horizon that would be
Completely co-opted by the most
Xtreme fringes
Which brings us to Lobby.
So the group returned this year's Lobby day into a complete disaster
Is a group that Sedona as the Virginia citizens Defense League
A GroupMe is presumably
They're very similar to a lot of gun folks
We ended up and have
Encountered on the this show
Directions are less lobbying and More obstructionism in
Borderline Vira
Honestly the probably most notable prior to this year for two
Large-scale media-related gas
The first was when they tried to sue Katie
We correct for how she edited a documentary that you made called Under the Gunn
They felt that you defamed
And sued for 12 million dollars which is
Of course thrown out of court
Their other gas was when their president Philip Van Cleef got tricked by Sacha Baron Cohen and his show who is Amir
In the segment he was in Cohen's Mossad character got Vancleave
To promote kindergarten
An initiative to Arms
School children as young as
3 years old
It's legitimately embarrassing
Cleavage out there singing songs promoting guns
Plush animals on them to make them
Fun for kids
One of them is a rocket-propelled grenade launcher which is should be a dead giveaway
A gun that
Longer than a baby
In the hands of a baby
Please stick around for what he described as an hours-long interview
Was revealed to be a Sacha Baron Cohen
He claimed he only stuck around to gather Intel on who is behind the video to warn the rest of the Republicans
Undercover operative
Yeah you knew it was
The setup you Caesar
According to the Virginia Mercury it doesn't
Seemed like. Weirdos bought that excuse
Comment on the vcdl Facebook
I'm a vcdl number but Philip if you're so damn dumb to fall into this trap I think you need to find a new gig
Just how could you do more harm to the 2nd Amendment in Virginia gun rights
Another combat
How are we
Going to just be mad at the leftist media when our own guy walked into this
This is hilariously terrible
Step down
It's a surprise ideas still in charge of the B CDL
That's that
Crazy shouldn't be surprised
Is Oliver North going to take over for me
Consultant
Shouldn't be surprised that he still around
Littering that he also didn't
Step down after he made some if
Common sense
Did the Sandy Hook shooting
He's asked by The Washington Post why people like guns like the one used in that tragedy and he said they were quote son
This guy's a dick which is what I'm getting at
Yeah Vancleave in the vcdl lower part of the forces
Behind all these counties in Virginia passing these gun sanctuary resolute
With your kin are legally meaningless
If there's one person who's at the center of the escalation of things in Virginia I would say it's fair to say
Mostly Philip
Van Cleef
Because of his actions things have now
Inspirobot
We'd be out of can
Control whether rhetoric is amplifying
Things are asked
Escalating
Extreme group
Are being
Towards
Like a moth to the flame being drawn towards this
What could have been just a normal day we like guns
Kind of demonstration
Well if you are in Virginia
Where are you
Long enjoyed rampant
Overwhelming
Control to then
Lose an election
Thinking
Well we'll see lost because
Democracy
Allowed
Then of course you're going to try and base
Sickly intimidate your
Political
Listen to inactivity you met that's there
That's our main goal
So in addition to the legislature being Democrats also Governor Ralph Northam is a Democrat as well
I enjoy that makes him evil
According to
Folks like that
Seems like a real
Real Not Grey dude
He signed an executive order Banning
Guns and other weapons from the sight of this this rally
Anto
Because
Look at it
Really was becoming more or less
Completely unpredictable gun rally
So he put this ban in place effective
Friday the 17th through Tuesday the 20
This executive order was also Declaration of a state of emergency
Based on credible intelligence
What's the 10,000
People from out-of-state
We're planning to convert
And I quote
Available information suggests that a substantial amount
Substantial number
Of these.
Ozarks
Spectre to come from outside the Commonwealth
May be armed
And have is their purpose not peaceful assembly but violin
Rioting in insurrection
Yeah
It's hard to say exactly what his credible intelligence is or was
Since we aren't privy to the inner workings of Virginia law enforcement
But if you have to go off with publicly available
I think you should come to the conclusion the Northam
Decision was
More than just
For one thing you have Stewart Roads and The Oath Keepers make
The trip up to the rally
Plenty of all keepers have been arrested for things like having Napalm bombs or planning to take over small towns in the past
So their involvement in something like this
Is definitely a red flag
For months now
Talk about an impending Civil War
And even
Publicly on Alex Jones is Joe he's literally said that it's important
Start while Trump is in office
This is a man who's been very clear about his intent
I do think that
They're there a position to Red Flag laws is also personal
Most of these people
Building red flags
It may be they are covered in red
That could be
True
Leinster road is dangerous and scary
And him joining this Virginia business
He has is definitely not good
However
He's far from the top of the list in terms of these scary raspy
Vector what's going on
There are a ton of
Indicated
Interest in attending or intention to attend
But
In terms of
People who have no
Concrete information about
I would say the thing that is a most alarming
Is a group called The Base
In the last week 23 person
Some cells allegedly members of this group called the face
Square arrested amid plans to carry out violin
Three Men and George were planning to murder a married couple they believe their high-level aunt
Antifa
That would have been upsetting on its own
But what made it much more notable is that this was
The 2nd
Three-person group arrested within like a day
In Maryland another Trio is rest
This one including a former
Canadian Army member who have been exposed as having Association
With white supremacist groups and then disappearing
The FBI Advent
Had this cell under surveillance
I need to learn that one of them had made an assault rifle he described as a machine gun capable of firing more than one round
The time
These men have discussed attending a rally in Virginia
To a headline in slate
Quote
Neo-nazis allegedly discussed open
Opening fire at Virginia's pro-gun rally slated for Monday
Governor Northam had credible intelligence of threats
Violence at the rally
In this very well could have been what he was referring
Of course it could very well be that this
Just one of multiple
Instances of violent threats around of the event
Whatever the case when it comes to group like the bass
I think it's probably best not to just dismiss it as straight talk or like
Hey you guys talk
Okay so
From what I'm hearing I'm far less worried about Stewart Road seeing as how he has a public
And
I'm more than a little bit of a monetary interest in
Continuing with
The paranoia but not
All out
War where is this looks like
Three person terrorist cells that are loosely
Affiliated
It appears that way
Cool cool cool cool.
It is one of those things where it is true that
Kind of is the end of the road for the revenue stream
For someone like Stewart Road
Unless I guess you do know there is a civil war and he
Recreates like a fiefdom
For himself outside of his capabilities
Mistreater
I wouldn't say
That's fair
I would say it's best not to dismiss these people in these
These arrests that got made
And that's because the base
Is a group that explicitly and specifically about creating
The terrorist
They are not interested in the people posting stuff online or slick media dicks
Like Richard Spencer
They exist to help
Encourage and train white supremacists and neo-nazis to carry out in
Real-life attack
The return of white tiida
Started in 2018 by a man who goes by the Alias Norman's
Sphere the base operator
Encrypted online forums and message
Aspiring soldiers for whiteness
Connect with each other
And they get to learn about a wide array of topic
Cyclone wolf
Send chemical weapons
There's steadfastly acceleration
Extended signs that they want to commit Acts
Twitchell provoked a backlash
Which they believe will lead to the ultimate goal
To the gigantic War that'll give him the opportunity to overthrow the government which they feel is run by the
Do they not know what Charles Manson
Plan was
Come down
One thing that makes
It's the base different from your run-of-the-mill b g
They have an emphasis on United white identity and be or Nazi groups who otherwise have
Tactical or ideological differences
Their push
Is that there
Common interest is greater
Then what they disagree about
So they need to work together
This is heavily reminiscent of the Rocky Mountain Rendezvous meeting held an esta
Is Park Colorado in nice
We're militia dude klansman neo-nazis and Alex's body Larry Pratt got together to formulate a strategy after Ruby
Ruby Ridge
Belligerent
Right-wing extremist activity
It's hard to imagine that a big Summit among the major
Players didn't have some role in that right
Coincidentally Larry Pratt's going to Richmond
Is probably just
Yeah yeah
Not important
I ate a daffodil
Like this is so fake this is so
Like cost
Play e
But at the same time they're they're almost like
Civil War
Preenact
Like they're there
Play-acting the Civil War that they might accidentally start
It's really really
Really tough
Know how to talk about it responsible
Because there is
A feeling of
Not wanting
To buy into the hype
These are right-wing Fox of ours are engaging in
And at the same time not wanting
Not take things that seem like
Pretty serious f*****-up Bad actors seriously
What their regular MO is
Large
Outside threat that they have no intention of following up on
But when you start hearing about 3 person
Some terrorist cells
We're not talking about media blitz these guys are
Legitimately trying to stay under the radar in order to carry out the
It's that's what that that's what it seems like they're doing
But it also could seem like they're playacting at
This very terrorist cell thing that there
You know it's so wild
Very difficult
I know
I'm silly
But I would say
The most fortunate things about members of violent hate groups
Is it that usually hate
Distrust
Each other as much as they did
Distrust anyone else
Another planning illegal shitzo anyone there associating with could be effect
This paranoia Tennessee impede their ability to organize
Earnest attempt on the part of right-wing extremist
To put their differences aside and
Collaborate are a very bad sign
It's something that needs to be taken very seriously
I think Wendy
I can't pretend to have any kind of elevated understanding of what's going on or what will happen on Monday
In Virginia
Outside of information publicly available
I can say without reservation
Is that members of an accelerationist Neo-Nazi group would not be planning on bringing any legal self-described machine-gun to Monday
These rally to peacefully at lawfully open
Open carry to support gun
I doubt that is absurd
I don't believe that for a
Today it's
It's all about Recreation
You know it's at that's that that he made it
And that's what
This is what really highlights
The problem
People who are concerned about possible trouble at the rally
Are concerned about normal law-abiding
Citizens carrying
I would assume most of them would have no qualms of trump supporters open carrying as amendment rally
They were problems
Do people like these neo-nazis
You are being
Attracted to this
People like Alex hear the concern that there are violent wide identity groups planning to attend
And he spends it by saying that the
Concern is really just
They think all responsible gun only people in America are terrorists
What he's doing is absorbing people like these members of the base
Into his Collective identity
And then getting defensive about
It would be the easiest thing in the world for him to recognize that
These dangerous Fringe elements exist in you have an inch
Kristen separating yourself
But Alex doesn't want that
For whatever reason to possibly guess what that is
I went to the consistent trend of inclusion
When it comes to White identity extremist
Just either he's a real he wants to hear from both sides
Yeah I think that's it
He's balanced
What are the tragedies listening to Alex's show and understanding how he operates is that I know that even if 100 neo-nazis were
Arrested with explicit plans to attack minorities and liberals at this rally
And they all confessed
Alex would still say that he has proof that they're also
He arose contracts tan
Easy
He's built a world of information that's so insulated from reality that he could make the claim Danielle Don sense about eulogium
City for a while then pretend he's proven his point
Probably let him get away with it
All right-wing extremists are secretly globalist
All left-wing counter demonstrators are also secretly minions of the globalist
No one really exist
Picked up Alex
And everyone else is on
Some kind of control agent working for
Dialectic
Benton Alex's gunby
It's a completely nonsensical worldview and it's completely
I'm totally into
At least it is until you consider it
Through the prism of supporting right-wing extreme
Start to look at it in that light
Big things make a lot more sense
We're going to get into this episode at along the way Alex is going to go out of his way to preemptively declare that any violence that happens at Monday
Is Rally if any happens it's going to be a false
The globals to trying to start a civil war they want to kick it off
I've seen some Publications glibly pointing out that Alex is pushing that angle
But I really wish they would flash out
He's doing that
Alex knows that people like those members of the base have been arrested
Seemingly plotting to commit violent act at the rally
And I'm certain he doesn't naive enough
To think that they're the only
He's friends with f****** Stewart Roads and he's been an associate of Larry Pratt
For years now
He has to know that there's chatter
From his side of the aisle this is very much in line probably start here
He knows that
Guest on his show have said that
And if God forbid anything tragic happen
He needs an excuse
Implace
Ahead of time
To make sure that no-one blames his right-wing extremist
Is a very difficult situation to Assassin
Particulate from the outside
I don't want to buy into any right-wing hype that
There's going to be viola
Start because
I think they're taking them
Face value plays into their narrative
At the same time
I don't want to miss
I don't want to diminish
And failed to recognize that there are a lot of very extreme people who have attached themselves to this rally
And that they are not good
Personally I hope the calmer heads prevail and the day passes without him
As of right now as a recording
I've seen some indications of people
Gunn weirdo side they're encouraging people to stay home
As the chaos of the situation is way too
Unpredictable
Stay away from
As a recording I have no idea how things going to shake out but it's entirely clear that there's one side that's basically desperately pleading
For something awful to happen
So they can justify living out there Civil War
Fantasies
Stay-home
I think that dichotomy speaks volume
Sorry about that long rant
At b a
A seltzer
It was
There's a lot of context
Yeah the thing I see as most worrying
Or the thing that I'm most worried about
People who are play
Not those
Not that the Luna
Text butt
More like
Somebody just
Mentally fires
And that that
That seems far not a likely Thing by any stretch
But as far as scenarios go historically it would make
Far more sense for some idiot to
Accidentally
The safety off
And then everybody goes
Active and that's
That's the thing you know it's it's a very scary possibility I don't I don't want to go
Through like what is this
No not at all what I'm saying
It just
I don't want to pee I just don't engage
That
So we start on the 50
Just for clarification because
Easy to paint Alex
The news of those Neo-Nazi arrest
Doesn't happen until the sick
So on the 50
Alex doesn't know about that
Achy couldn't
So what are you doing
You breaking some big news
Use
Don't you say it
Like that
This is going to be a llama situation all over again
There's no law
Infowars
100% been the tip of the spear
Again I don't say that say oh look
What are the tip of the spear
Are we great
Jessie
Actually a great responsibility
In fact it was Paul Watson
About
4 years ago
That began to really fuzzy and she'll movement as being a mass shooter
Magnified at Infowars magnified
Blind dog story
And now the FBI and the Texas State Police have come out and said actually
Almost every Mass shooter has been a
Incel
Involuntarily celibate into the occult
Braided line
Population
Pictures of Whitman
So once again Alex is pretending he was ahead of the curve on something
We'll get into this Texas FBI report a little bit later but suffice it to say that literally none of it
Who sang read that report
This is absolutely constructed out of thin air
Actually
Thought out
Complete finnair
Alex has not read this report
He's only read an article about it that was posted on National file which again is website run by his employee Tom Papa
The article is
National file
It's basically I just about how the report warns about an incel Rebellion
Well completely ignoring everything else in the report
Spoiler alert that's because most of the report is about how the number one domestic terrorism issue in the country is people who believe the same thing
Exist
To distract
From the actual point of the record and make it a story that Alex can effortless
Mostly cover on his own show
And this among other stories recently really highlights our national files becoming a laundering house
Prefer a proper
They are Dara send it
Analysis World which is weird because he used to have Paul Joseph Watson Road right Olive
Yeah
I think Paul is
Not distancing himself but
Definitely
Keeping clear of a certain
Not sure I'm not sure 100% what it is cuz I want to still using him as a source for like blaming Muslims
Australian fires still linking to like Summit. News articles
Connect
It's a hedging
Got I got this guy coming in this dump a guy
You really post a lot of articles
I'm going to go with it I like
That's right I don't
Give a s*** about quality
No
I think it's more like a
Could also be the those depositions
Paul Joseph Watson was kind of like
Yeah I don't know I told Alex he f***** up not really Towing the company line
Stories that came out about it we're about how Paul threw him under the bus maybe Alex's
Derbyshire
In case he goes Rogue
I need top happer
Well I mean
Massive stepped out yeah that's not great
I mean there's there's something to be said for
Keeping certain
Subjects kind of
Separate from each other you know you got Tom pepper to laundry this stuff and you can call Joseph over here laundry
Ria in ended better
To have a diversity of controlled sources
Put all your eggs in one basket as you know we can get more information is that they are things that Paul
He wouldn't
Go along with Alex if he was going to try and pull another kind of Sandy Hook probably would
We go along with just about any
So Alex gets said to talk anymore about this
Report and
Man it's so funny how
Here it is he hasn't read
Magical crystal ball
This is well but
ATL still in control
Well now all that's been outside
Enforcement
It's antifa leftist incel needle-dick
Send the problem
Gotcha do you think this report talks about antifa leftist in cell needle dicks I would say that most
Reports I've read from a professional service have not added beat at any point
I wouldn't join
Probably too much
Talking about Izzy newly-released Texas domestic
Stick terrorism threat
It's not a long.
Only about forty nine pages
Some of them are blank
So there's really no excuse for Alex not to
Reddit
If he had
Maybe this wouldn't be such a gigantic embarrassment
So let's imagine that he has read the document
I know he has
Let's just imagine
I'm putting myself in this headspace
And here he is on air
Finally law enforcement is coming out of telling the truth
He's pretending that that true that they're telling is that all of these Mass Shooters are antifa leftist in selling needle-dick
But let me read to you from pain
3 in the report
Based on the prevalence of recently conducted attacks Nationwide white racially-motivated is currently the most violently
Act of domestic terrorism
Tom pepper remove that page before it got bad weather report
What other type of domestic terrorism threatening or forceful Behavior the loss of life from recent worm
White racially-motivated
Text elevates the nature of this specific bread
Seems like
Give Alex
Thinks that this report is law enforcement finally telling the truth and that truth is that white identity-related terrorism
The most serious problem in the domestic
I thought I was at this report was about all the shooters were antifa in cell needle-dick
Terrorism
White leftist
Needle dick
It's whatever
Exist what time
In this document and it's in the URL of a footnote
In the form of a link to New York Times article about the classes at Berkeley back in 2017
Literally nowhere in this document is there any indication that any of the shooters covered were inspired by auntie
Answer incels the report doesn't know that they are they are equipped emerging domestic terrorism
And that this group to be aware of in the future based on some past attack
Max and Chloe
Dreamly violent online rhetoric
Dissection weather report
Detailed instances of incel related violence includes five attack
From 2014
Into the present
And literally none of them are stories that I've ever heard Alex cover
Although he probably did Cover Elliot Rodger back in 2014
I haven't listened to those episodes but I imagine
His take on it was not good I think it would probably have been
Let me get let me check
Maybe didn't happen
Right love that guy guy Wasn't Man Enough
The fact that this report mentions in cells is really good for
Alex because he can use that to pretend that it isn't most
Play about people he agrees
Therefore instances listed of terrorism motivated by anti-abortion
Any recent history Alex Azar
Bryson leanings in favor
Violence against people who work at the abortion field
Airport list five in
Census of sovereign citizen related domestic terrorism
Definitely seeing Alex Express
Sovereign citizen
Slim-Fast
Probably not enough to suggest he's a full-on
But enough to make me think
He doesn't want to talk about their violence
Laws that I think he would go Sovereign citizen
Yeah I don't think
Yeah I don't think it goes.
Unlike
Well obviously deposition
Do you like do you like Lady Sovereign
No.
Awful
It's awful that he doesn't like lady soft
It's a bummer
But more importantly
Report highlights white racially-motivated domestic
Terrorism has the largest threat in the field
Specifically pointing
How a lot of it is driven by belief in the great replacement
Conspiracy
Which Alex is
Bullion board
Airport is an overview of different
Sorts of domestic Terror threats
That exists in the country
It's not really biased towards one particular viewpoint
You can say that they're singling out white people but there's also a section on black racially-motivated terrorism in there too
You can say that they're singling out right-wing anti-government people but there's also a section about Anarchist motivated violence
As well as environmental and Animal Rights Act
It's a broad analysis
But if you actually read the report it would be literally impossible to escape
The conclusion
Who spelled out at
At the beginning of the report
Namely that white racially-motivated domestic terrorism
The most violently active type in
In the country
Alex cannot allow that to be the
Conclusion People Come Away with so instead of engage
File article
I need direct people to that
So they can read that and pretend that they've also read the report
This is an act of running interference
Spur White
Racially-motivated domestic terrorist
If you're endorsing this report
In claiming that the conclusion is that all these shooters are
Antifa leftist in Selbyville
Your gaslighting your audience
And you're trying to cover up the reality that white man
Nationalism and white supremacy
It's a severe problem and it's getting worse
That's it this is this is where you get into that like
If you look at this through the prism of
Hoarding disorder
Do pigs like white racially-motivated extremism
Everything makes sense
I mean I guess the only frustrating thing about that
I'd say maybe there's only been one year and the in American history where
White racially motivated terrorism wasn't the most
Like we had 2001 and then ever like
From before and after it's always been
I'm not positive numbers but I
Willing to bet that there have been some years that's unlike single-a
Wish you motivated stuff might have been large
I mean I would say I'm not sure is my point like
Harvey be hard to find a year when
You know I did I take it you think I'm probably might be right
Not sure hundred percent
B
Closer to 100% than it is to
Is my guess
Yeah I can't think of it
A little bit of Comedy
Gloria
This report was produced by the Texas Fusion Center
Absolutely
Every single thing about it
2012 article by Kurt Nimmo on Infowars
Fusion centers not only violate the
Rights of Americans but also a colossal waste of taxpayer money
Anyone who listen to Infowars in the preacher a knows that
Very consistent aspect of their content was the fusion centers were hubs of evil
And they needed to be destroyed
A lot of that was based on how these centres were able to collaboratively collect
Intelligent
Pilot in to recognize Prince and might be missed by police
Work independently
You can make an argument that this pushback
They had started around
The miac report
Was really you know there's nothing quite so dangerous to the right-wing as people learning
I think that's probably the biggest
Fear that sharing information
Yeah they're not fans that
It can be tough
You know it's like
The church wasn't fans of the Gutenberg
Nothing but Alex ever say
Nothing that enforced puts out
Everything is made up and the principal
Leica I hate fusion centers
With all these principles they claim they're behind their action
It's all a facade
None of this means anything
So
This report is going to play a gigantic
And
All of it
Salt Lake
It it's going to be a through line
He hasn't read
Totally
It was really impressed rated by that I don't like that that's a
It's brazier
Possible
Somebody about this report and like
They're not
Like fully onboard with you
How do you get out of that
That's probably the best route
So anyway Alex claims that Virginia is going to call
In the UN
To take people's guns
And then we get some
Big breaking
Ginger would let the
I don't even think the democratically-controlled the housing
Never let the UN
Virginia
Now it's loaded.
But
Big
Canoes
Virginia governor guns
Talking about using the UN and using proofs
Who what
We all that crazy that we don't mean that
Heather just getting you in the back of hearing that term emergency
Begin to expand
Then we learn from The Bernie Sanders campaign
Burn down
Milwaukee
At the DNC
Rental Works
That's a strong plan for Bernie
If Sanders doesn't get the nomination in a truck
When's the Round Barn it there
The fires will spread
Summer of Rage Across the Nation the government
Will be under communist control
And I will then arrest males and put them in
Re-education camps
Or some will have to be kill
The police will have to be killed
Submit
Cool kind of makes me think this wasn't a quote from
The Sanders person cuz you said summer of Rage that kind of makes me think of you
Did he you know you'd Warren Post all her plans on medium did Bernie post that one on medium Tuesday
A lot of Milwaukee
Is B
He has an autumn
Overrated
So first part first that stuff at the beginning where Alex's talking about how Governor Northam was planning on using Roblox
Troops to seize guns also the Arkansas
. is all the roads
That's all
But here's the thing
Alex
Didn't make it
Alex is reading this headline from the story that Mike Adams posted on natural news
This article is really just about how he was on a radio show talking about the research he done into how the governor was going to shut all the
I listen to that interview and it
No point to these dudes prove anything
Literally all of it is a hey well I heard this from a highly credible high-level source
Short all that b*******
Yeah
The reason it's all vague nonsense about an ottoman sources
Is because Mike Adams have done any research
This is very often the case
He'd fallen for an internet hoax
That interview was posted on YouTube on December 9th
And just six days prior the white nationalist radio host Hal Turner
Be completely fabricated narrative the governor Northam it quote
Allegedly ordered a small Cadre of staffers to begin the
The process for determining how to cut off electricity telephone
Faxes
Cell phones as well as the internet
In areas where he plans to send Virginia National Guard troops
To forcibly seized gone
From the airbox Amplified the story on social media there's a bit of a
The game of telephone
Where the pieces got morphine
Embellished
Ultimately leading to Mike Adam
Presenting his ankle
Is it raining over the UN replacing the Virginia National Guard
I'm making up his own details about how to describe the martial law
Be enacted
I've seen this sort of thing from Infowars before
Play launder hoaxes
But they pick up on is the
Slightly changed some trivial details
So they can deny that it traces back to the clear hoax source
So anyway this is all bulshit
This is what Mike Adams as game is
It's very clear
Such a ding
So much
Pales in comparison
Didn't know that
Right we we should have known this all along he's evil
Commander after all that's a problem
You should have known in the debate
You got to trust them when they tell you that they said they would
Temper down his rhetoric
No you got to believe when I say
This is just Alex reporting on a new video
Project Veritas
Kiss band of idiots caught a Bernie staffer saying some f*****-up things on camera
I watched about as much of the videos I can tolerate but
I swear he's just talking into a camera or unbearable
I just cannot handle it
As best as I can tell a Sanders staffer whose position in the campaign is on
Clearlake what would live over there at
I said some stuff about being in favor of gulags
Send re-education camps
I don't particularly care about this because James O'Keefe has shown himself to be the biggest weasel in the game
Nothing puts out even deserves a second
Consideration
Present this stuff manipulative lie like he usually does
It's very easy
For me to say the stuff that staffer was saying is horrible and I don't I don't support it
I don't care we talked about project the last time we talked about project veritas
But the main thing is
I don't care
Anybody else reports on it maybe I'll listen but if it's coming from you
Cluck-U I even think that is Project Veritas put out something on Alec
A piece on him I wouldn't do it
I don't believe a thing that they've says reputation
Just to tarnish to God
Yeah I'm not going to entertain it for a sec
Right right
Could have Nancy Pelosi screaming awful things into his face if I was going to murder his family and I still did
He probably deceptively at sabotage.
Yeah
Even on face value it's
They talked to in the video was that politically involved
For instance at one point in the video he says that if Sanders doesn't win
We're going to make 1978 look like a f****** Girl Scout f***
Cookout
2 problems
The Girl Scouts are not particularly known for their cookout
There wasn't an election in 1978
He's picking up 68
Sky is a little bit of it was strange that he was the campaign manager for
Do you know what you going to do
Brinkley this could be from
F****** Rodger Stone
Acting like he's Bernice
A supporter for fucksake
The entire stick that O'Keefe is working with you is called a composition fallacy
He's found a low-level person in the Sanders campaign
Probably just someone involved in organising and knocking on doors in Iowa and he caught him at a bar saying some f*****-up stuff
The implication is
Just push that what this guy said is actually would everyone in the Sanders campaign believe
Probably Sanders himself
This is the entire bit and honestly more than anything else all this reveals to me that the big-money donors who fun project Veritas
Are becoming more worried about Bernie's numbers and they see him as an actual threat
Now oh yeah I supposed to just focus on
Yeah that's that's one of the things that everybody
Who is supposed to really really hate
Is it really tough
To paint him as like
Like that this guy who's a
The Sleeper Cell
After a 45-year career
I'm saying the exact same thing over and over again it's like
Really his plan lasted fifth
How long is planet supposed to last you just need to find other slippery ways to attack a minute
You'll see you'll see a good better than easier
Just playing a clip of bite you unless, you'd best go.
Care about James O'Keefe
If you had an actual story that wasn't based on manipulative practices or fudging details
He would do everything in his power to keep
Keep his name off it
I think that's a good life strategy to employ is anything that has a name project Veritas or James O'Keefe on it is apps
Blue balls
Until it's verified or vetted through another outlet that has standards
Is just like
Is to tarnish
And it's just like whenever one of Alex's employees goes out but doesn't
Have the Infowars
Microphone
Like yeah you can't be associate
With that if you
If you want to get anything
Speaking one of Alex's employees
Is it goes out
Alex
What's the throw it to a report
I'm going to go to some Kaitlin Bennett
Feature
So Kaitlin Bennett
Kind of embarrassed
Stupid lately
Some videos where she does not come off as
Talking about all that much
Albertsons
That's not what this video
Instead
Play another one
I think it's a
I want to be clear
Alex is setting this up like it is a very serious piece of
Like he said in that last this is what we're up
This is yellow straightening the vicious
Dangerousness of these
Willfully ignorant
Morons
Father asking both hands lyrics
I need to be clear
This is setting it up as a serious report this isn't a comedy
Here's what the
Premises
Bruno the laptop becomes foreign policy experts overnight we're here in Toledo Ohio at the
Trump rally to see if leftist can you do point to Iran on a map it's right here by the way
This is some
Media organization is desperate for contact when they pull out the
Can you find a Ron on a map card
If This Were a segment on a late night comedy show it be a little cheap and dumb but Alex is pretending he's doing the show that means something
And yet
You still think the segment like this is a good use of his time
There are just a central problems with a bit like
The first is that knowing where country is on a map is not an indication of knowledge or lack of knowledge about the current issues
Surrounding that country
You could be fairly well-read on the issues in the Middle East and not know exactly where countries are Geographic
I mean obviously you'll be better if you did
Vallarta
But it doesn't mean that you're not
Thredup
I'm not going to say
That's ignorant
Is
Berkeley fine however I do not think that knowing where Iran is on a map
Matters when it comes
Is it okay to Assassin
Out of moral basis yeah it's it's like a different question
I mean I guess it's okay to assassinate somebody because I don't know where they are
O'Reilly Auto
I'm concerned about a second problem is it that this will segment is based around the smugness the Kaitlin Bennett
She actually has some kind of a Higher Ground over these dumb leftist because she knows where Ron is on a map
A strong suspicion that she didn't
Know that before she prepped the sex
I have a very strong suspicion that this whole thing could have gone
I'm totally off the rails of someone after defined below
On that map
She likes to add jatate about refugees a lot so be interesting to see if she knows which countries are which in Central and South America
This is the sort of segment anyone can do to paint any group they wanted
It's the cheapest trick in the book
Invalidate one side's position on an issue without even engaging in it at all
Very stupid
But I wanted to point this out because
This is a level of s*** that Alex is running with and thickness worth is
Time
Honestly
I think it's meant to be comedy segment
Travis and presenting it that way
Kaitlin Bennett isn't funny
And because she's such a bochabela figure
These videos just constantly end up with her just being made fun of
Course it is video is no exception listen to this
Otters
People laughing
Glasses don't make you a reporter that is the first lesson in journalism School
Don't make sure they don't know much
Embarrassing
Yeah I don't think that idea
Cuz that's the premise of a Leto
Man on the street shirt
Exactly
But even then
Their idea of
Well I know something you don't know so I'm smarter than you and I can talk down to you
It's so
Because that means okay well now what if I know something you don't know
The tables are turned and you're just
To deal with it so you're going to cry like a little baby
We go for that very serious report
Very serious hard-hitting suffocate
Death to Alex of predicting that there's going to be a false flag
Then they stage a false flag or they provocateur an action
Jussie Smollett
Dial the time steroids
And then they say look
The gun owners are the evil 2rsr the white supremacist
And I run the same operation we saw the Democrat
Control State Police
A couple years ago in Charlottesville
Whoa what
It was a bunch of theater kids running around like a bunch of gay Theatre kids arousal and Nazis in Charlottesville
That's what he
His I mean it's resolved the tall black provocateur.
No don't sweat it
This is a prediction that he's making and he's you know doubles down on it
It's very consistent this is what he is saying they're going to do
Galaxy saying
Aren't you making a big deal out of it
Open with each state would back down but
More and more it becomes very clear then try to pull something
In Virginia
And it all starts
It's basically on the 20th
Going to try to
Krowd
They're going to try to Stage something
Begin gun confiscation and across the state
In an attempt to trigger a civil war
All this is just pre-emptive narrative building in case there is some sort of violent right-wing
Extremist all that was the provocateur that the global asset into the crowd that's all just it's just preemptive self-defense
At such
Disingenuous
Bulshit
Like he's cheating
So hard it makes
Right
Yeah I know
Still just disgraceful that like
Oh no you know I'm
Just trying to deescalate things it's
You spent the last three months being like what we got to do it now
Got to go hot
Haven't started talking about it
F*** you you don't get to
To say that now
No you certainly don't but he does
Feels
Awful because it's the present
And you know things are still yet to happen
Right
It's terrible but it is
It's exactly the same thing you see consistent
Only with Alex
Yeah
Course it is but it's such
Just like
Ever not be mad at somebody
Cheating lie
You know it's just
It's
The truck up
I should be past they the right or wrong
Still getting
Hung up every now and again you're going to get hung up like crazy on
Because Alex makes a very bizarre recommendation
And then tries to prove that the left
Launcher
Go out, Kate Gunn
As a nation we have to stand up to that
When Governors trying it
And people are like Mahatma Gandhi and turn them in
They won't be able to start the Civil War
But they'll just provocateur it maybe I was sniper shoot some anti-gunners
I mean this is their playbook
And it there
Failing on every other front they already sent to my
All the Patriot Republicans a baseball game
Other Republicans
Carlson's house
Now the FBI and State
Antifa
Incel
Plantera is a nationwide
Usher in a collapse
The government
Civil War
So firstly it's kind of weird
But I think people should comply with state level guns
I guess that
Interesting to hear
I don't think that you means
State-level bans guns in the left
Have guns
Is that why I could be like Gandhi and turn your gun in
State-level for governor is doing it and then he's feeling on it
Do that it'll cause a political backlash and then the state will turn red again
That's what he should use Allstate
It's right from Cheer
I guess I'm glad to hear that
I don't believe it
Not for a
But more importantly that list of incidents he's talking about with the last being violent is sad
Is Steve scalise shooting was in June 2017 and there's literally no evidence that anyone quote sent him
Shoot those guys
It seemed like his motivation was an intense hatred of Republican
More than anything else
And I was way out of line and plying me with some kind of an assassin
Consent by the globalist
If Alex got deposed about that allegation
He would 100% USA
He's talking about his feel
Feels like the shooter was
Kill The Patriot
Yeah
I have no idea what he's talking about people saying to kill Trump or it's
Let's go Alex
Let's do not specific
For me to work with
A small group of protesters went to Tucker Carlson's house in November 2018 and spent about 10 minutes chanting stuff
Tucker wasn't even
Tucker budzyn
Steven home
He claimed that the protesters were threatening to pipe bomb is house but according to people who were there this is a misrepresentation
Temptation of the protesters
Evoking the pipe bomb
Aberdeen Maga bomber
And the recent synagogue shooting
As a reason for why they were protesting
His particular brand of rhetoric
As they were leaving one straggler spray-painted an anarchist
Stay on his driveway with other protesters
Express their disapproval
The internet was completely brought up blown out of
Proportion by the right-wing media and again happened over a year ago
See what I listen to some of what they were
Screaming and they were actually saying that his pipes
Sorbonne
They really love his voice
Oh I thought you meant a collection of glass weigh
He's got a meerschaum pipe that's also go to hookah lounge
So that's what we talked about earlier
Dialysis
Compared to the list of very real and actually deadly right-wing attacks in the same span of time Alex discovery
Also all left us this is
Legitimately
Apathetic
It is
Especially since he could just list all of the right-wing terrorist
Yeah why is he listening
Needle dick
Yeah what is he listening
I don't know
That seems it seems like a slam-dunk to be like oh well it was this one it was this what it was this was Becky only remembers
Certain touchpoints Rida
Police all the time and
Pretty in Tucker Carlson
These days so
Bring them up
Little more about how he would turn his guns in
If
Texas band
Alright while
Texas
Close to it
They tried something like this and wanted to have a big Riot and wanted to blame it on President Trump
And I came to take my guns
This point
Would turn them in
Knowing they were wanting a civil war then that would trigger such a political movement
Go back red
You're an idiot
Try to fix this peacefully we're winning politically stable
Trigger a war law enforcement
Okay
Politically that's why she want to overthrow the chessboard
Yeah
I strongly suspected Alex's saying you would comply with state level gun ban because he knows that many of the folks on the writer
Very publicly talking about shooting cops who come to take their gun
This feels like an attempt at presenting a moderate public
Face knowing that the work has already been done in terms of radicalizing enough people to make the world super dangerous
Although I have heard in some like recent episode some people like
Pushing back on it
And for The Stance of like I would turn my guns into maybe you should
Cops
Call yousoldout yourself
You created this audio
Copy the face I don't know I have no idea why my audience feels like I would shoot
The cop in the face if they said to take my gun to other than the past
10 years where I've said that it's our constitutional duty to shoot a cop in the face if they come to try and take your gun if you come to drive
You literally said if you come for my guns
I will shoot you
1776.
Again did you think so
So Alex
Main point
Is there
They're trying to start a war out of this
That's sure
The whole like
The big thing
Cuz I don't do that
Do the Infowars
I'm not going to do
And show
We're winning politically
The left is self-destruct
Dislike
Who's going to win out of the
Baltimore face
Civil War
Bart Deering
That's it
Dial next week will be on the ground in d.c.
Just miles away in Northern Virginia
Revolutionary War
Well
Boston in the North End
Virginia the South
Quick fact check the
Heard round the world Richmond Virginia and Concord so
Damn time he screamed about The Oath Keepers rally at Lexington Green for like a week during the Boston bombing time.
Symbol with a revolutionary war started Asheville will talk more about this a little bit
Alex makes it even bigger claim that's nonsense
That these just way off
Boston in the northern Virginia
Stuff to make historical parallels
Because he desperately wants something horrible to happen in Virginia
You don't want to solve things with an infowar cuz he knows all his talking points aren't true
Trump is not super popular the impeachment is
Not super unpopular
The Texas threat assessment he's lying about
Clearly says it white racially motivated terrorism most violent type
Gen Z is not on this dumb Patriot Bowl
Most voters
Do favor some country
Control measures
He doesn't want to go with a sensible rational root because he loses that every single time
Everything is just b*******
Anyway
You heard there
They want to do this
Yes while Trump is in
Being impeached
In the trial in the Senate because
He'll be distracted
Wow so we won't be able to
Quizlet
That's not so much with okay alright
Alex Bell.
Conspiracy a little bit here and now apparently it's mostly about getting Trump out of office
But I thought they wanted to start
Do you know what
Let's just roll with it
And the governor
Is basically talking about going ahead and having gun confiscation don't hadn't having gun registration
When
Where is already declaring emergency at the idea of an emergency going
In your head
Can trigger
Some type of civil unrest
Civil War in the region
And martial law
President Trump used to blame
And then removing him while the shinning
In session
Next week with a trial
Bob the president all the planets
Aligning right now and our intel was the governor was planning this
Now you see it's beginning console
Pictures of jussie Smollett type false flag but a billion times bigger
I believe we're not going to be getting away with it
You notice
Also have
Das bombshell videos
With this operative for Sanders
The weathermen
Pan books
Are the main
Terrace rent and they track
The country it's been
Incels tearing out almost all of the mass shootings
Tied together
So In that clip you can kind of see the anatomy of this
Conspiracy cycle
And I think that Alex isn't
Like super comfortable with all of the
The pieces of it yet
And so that way you can kind of see his brain trying to jump
Connect them Gap
The end message Alex wants his audience to get is the last particularly antifa in cell Demon's are coming to put you in a fever
I suspected this is at least partially based on Alex realizing they yellow but Hillary is not going to sustain him this election cycle
Matt is best
Play is probably to really
A sphere of burning
Even though in 2016 you wouldn't
Stop talking about how unfairly Bernie was treated when he was trying to use that to attack Hillary
And in the past
You called Bernie the only good Senator on the left because he works with Ron Paul
Getting oversight for the Federal Reserve but who cares about any of that we got fear to self
Because he wanted to be unfair to Bernie
The Heat
So the goal is that sort of a conclusion
So you really need
Pieces that you know in place to support that can
Conclusion
Luckily this b******* artist James O'Keefe put out a thing related to Bernie and gulags that's a good start
Who this
Texas threat assessment came out mentioned in cells
Just pretend that the whole thing is about antifa in cells doing all the violence
That should help back up the fear
That the audience should feel based on this O'Keefe video
Now to make it all feel super immediately liked it
Imminent crisis
Let's mix in some of the stuff we ripped off from Hell Turner's hoax about Governor Northam declaring martial law to seize guns
A good measure just throwing some
I'm stuff but how this has to do with getting rid of trump getting him out of office
Pico de gallo
This is what's going on here these are the pieces of the narrative that
Meant to drive towards
The desired
Conclusion
It's it's
Seems like what he
What he thinks he's doing
Or maybe doesn't think
He's doing but what he's funk
Actually doing
Is trying to give people who otherwise would be against domestic
The
Safety of saying well
Because they're not domestic terrorism by side
And they're the ones on their side to make it look
Like my side is bad when the theoretical Civil War does stark
I'm fighting a defensive War
Not I'm part of America
The right-wing
Is the one who's doing and the rationalization for that largely has to do with
If we don't do this
Antifa
Put you and your family in a FEMA camp barely targeting us
Because yeah
None of these pieces of the puzzle are real
That he'll turn himself in
Completely made up by white supremacists trying to get people to
Freak out
Alex is just making stuff up about the
Texas threat assessment order to cover for white identity motivated Terror
Is James O'Keefe
There's nothing real
It's all bulshit but it's meant to make his audience scared
I'm feeling under threat
Because that's super profitable
And like you said it leads them to normalize and
Except
Because they might not otherwise and it gives them the ability to
To both say that they're against
Domestic terrorism while at the same time
Friday
Terrorist War I go
Epsom salt
You know what really
Jordan
The governor declared
Yes obviously
Means the guns are going to be take
I don't think that's how it works but okay
Emergency at the Capitol in the grounds
Because people coming with guns
Introducing the idea of a civil emergency
Why does the president trial will undoubtedly be taking place next weekend will be there covering both
That's my whole main cruise to be the rim
15 people there
Do your calls in one minute
I just want to say that it takes a lot of money to do this
We are expanding our backup Reserve to do
We are going to have a security team of quite a few people up there
Police officers from the locales I'll just leave it at that
Because this is a major threat area for everybody
I need to find her operation
Natural fjords salmon
Good
Natural at the artificial heart
They're Alex implying that he's in coordination with the local cops
Unheard-of regularly
You could be talkin
I have no idea
I think there's one thing they're the end that I think is kind of an interesting thing and that is that like
If Alex isn't lying about the
The Tight money situation
F****** terrible idea
He has to think that he's going to get so much price out of this
Justify whatever expenses
Star I have no idea
I think it could be an indication that maybe he's been
Overselling
How bad does
Financial situation
He really is just like
Desperate
Largely due to the point of the
It's easy for Alex to say the governor Northam declared an emergency
Because people were going to bring Gun
Monster rally
But that's not really being precise enough
Put your language
If people were just going to show up to peacefully assemble and carry guns there's no doubt that it would not have been an issue
This is technically about people bring gone
More specifically about these sorts of people were planning to bring those guns
Because of people like Alex we've been building up the
Turn the next civil war is about to start because Virginia
Considering
Mi gun
A lot of really extreme folks have been drawn into the picture
This entire thing to completely spiraled out of control to the point where I don't even think
The gun supporters even really know what
Expect now
You know you have this double talk
Meant to be
Kind of winking
Came all over the place
Yes people from the Pulaski
Tri-County Second Amendment Coalition putting out statement stressing
If you're going to do it legal s*** you need to stay home
And at the same time
You have Philip Van Cleave saying quote
It's ironic that this is a gun right
It's in the governor is trying to take away our ability to carry guns
How ironic is that he keeps poking the bear you know
Thesaurus super extreme but self-contradictory messaging is
It's a recipe for a chaotic situation
It's a real-life and way more volatile version of Alex rambling out pornographic leave Vivid description
Killing his enemies
And then existing is all about the information
It allows them to antagonize and wink at the extreme members of the audience
Well reassuring
Extreme listeners is really just about to begin
Seems sort of
Dynamic
Is being played by
Some of these people who are involved with that
The gun side of the rally
They're signaling to a
Stream folks
Wow
Playing the
About the infowar
Different
So
I don't know it's
It's not good I mean
Impossible for them to not know
That's
The threat is
Credible
The worst part about the perfect
One of the members of the fandom
Infiltrated the alt-right
Chat boards and and
Discordant message
More than all of that stuff
Fairly easily
I don't doubt that the
Cops
Can do the exact
They have the will
You know that's always been
More the issue then
Anything else
Yeah and I want it and it appears that they were
They were surveilling
Bass
South
Couldn't have been that hard
They're not great
Yeah I don't know I don't know I'm not a in intimately involved so I don't know maybe it's difficult maybe it's not but
Yeah I don't believe
Did people like Alex
People like Stuart roads
Are unaware
That element of
And that's why they need to present it as they're trying to demonize all gun owners as opposed to
Discussing the very real Fringe
Streamelements
Yeah being attractive
Because they
They don't have it
Answer that also don't want to denounce those people
Right if they like it
Because they're good
But
If there are
State-level laws go to turn in your guns
But if there's Federal
I just Jordan
No
You got to go to Walmart
Organized Federal
Starbucks we got to go to war
Okay and I'm not looking for that but I'll go to war
That's not our government that criminal it's on American
The fight against it
The Democrats are trying to start
I know our people.
Alex knows that which is interesting because recently Stewart Roads is giving a speech
Why do we listen to a little bit of
So just looking at down the road
Truck furniture
One better in time one gun
That's what we going to do
No
Butterfinger Butterfinger where you're at
That's why you
That's why you need
The Neighbors Bar
You're sure be behind you
The game says the audience member guys over 60 just shoot cops
Succumb to take gun
Will loosen old timers.
And Stewart Roads
A better answer is Sheriff but I agree with that sentiment
I think it's the mark of a courageous
Send perf
Victorian ization
Sacrifice be elderly in the altar of their War
Were there.
Alex is a close associate of Stuart Road
4 years and I have definitely heard collars on Alex's show Express
That exact same sentiment that guy the audio
This is the idea that Alex thinks that no one is
Going to shoot the good idea to shoot
Papa never happen
It's pretty regular occurrence
Yeah
So Alex
I don't I don't know how he's done this
Yes but I guess at this point he's confirmed that the globalist
The blinding of false
Wow
The police aren't our enemy the globalist want to make it that way they want source of War
I'm going to be there
How do we stop it what are they going to pull what are the policeman
Sodick
The Deep Statesboro you know they're planning this it's been confirmed
How you confirmed it
Yes really getting too specific
Empire
Didn't you see Pepper Road
Kind of
Post on a Facebook page
Confirm
Alex Costa calls
And he get the call allegedly
From Virginia car
And he asked
This guy
How how can I avoid
So I'm just asking how do we somehow
Not let this happen
I wish I had the answer for you Alex because everything I could possibly
Answer is something
Going to be a counter to
And
I just think at the end of the day there's going to be people there they're going to try to
Something I don't believe they're going to be involved
And the Patriots
I just think there's going to be
Passionate people
You been talking about
There's no doubt that they're so desperate because they're losing politically this is what they're going to try
So I apologize I believe there was a former Virginia Campos now in a different place
A couple of cop car okay
This is an insanely irresponsible kind of think we put it on there
The conclusions that these two people Alex in this guy if they breach
Before anything has happened days before the rally even happen
Some kind of horrible tragedy is going to happen they're into it won't be there side the Dozen
I probably talk about this too much
Watch but this is one of the ways that Alex make sure that no matter what happens
To prevent present himself as the winner and the hero in this
Situation
If God forbid something bad happens at the rally he's on record pretending he's proven
To his audience
At the globalist
They're going to false Flags he's been proven right
If nothing happened to get to pretend that
Unit Patriot Buddies
You're so strong
Intimidating look Global said call an audible
Decided not to false flag after all
Solutely no matter what
Autostraddle
And his ability to keep his audience
Convinced he knows what he's talking about remains intact
And he's able to move forward
This is a game time
It's really f***** up
Considering the stakes
He's doing
And if they do call inaudible and they don't do the false
Flag
That just means they're going to do it at
The different time so you always got to be ready for the false flag, always the end time preacher
Reginald X
I hate this I hate this Especial
Play Just Because
Nothing
Genevan
Think they know what a civil war would
Look like today like today have any
Clue
Like wouldn't it essentially based on everything they want when it just be like
Rural
Counties
Holding cities under
Siege I don't know
That's sad
Smart doors for sale you know notes it's just
Wild
Yeah so
Sort of Gorillaz Anthony
Access get this Virginia caller
Another guy
And I think Alex thinks he's gone
To be way more sensible than he
I'm not even positive this guy
All we have to go on is that
The caller says that there are caught I don't even know I think this guy's pretend exact is real too
Now we have Willard
State Police in Virginia
Amish objects
Thanks for calling
I control rats
Spell Alex
First of all
People shouldn't be voting and counties to
Sanctuary cities they ought to be arresting this guy
Program
Military
Thomas running this thing
Obama still running our government placed in the government
Ignore Trump or they'll indict them and
And the people just scared and
People just frustrated but I tell you this Alex if they go ahead and go on with this I'm all wrong with it
Because
American people are stupid for putting up with it
Punching jail
How's your right of the American people to put up with this text
Yeah BS
Why did Alex agree with them being like yeah, I'm going to take your guns if you didn't cuz you all are stupid
I have no idea
Are wild
Obama still running the government and I don't think that's what Alex wanted to hear because that's
Something
Before but that's not this season's content
Yeah
Derek that's what that's the kind of thing you want to bring up when there's like deep State entry kind of narratives going around
I'd like we need an easy
Today just explanation for why your hero Trump isn't doing any of this stuff you want them to
That's when you tried out the Obama still running the government stuff
This season right now
It Patriot masturbation season
Contact making
Excuses for things throwing blame on people who clearly not run
The government doesn't play that well
We are trying to get people whipped into a frenzy about standing up to the gun grabbers
Alex was looking for something more along the lines of I do 100 cops will kill their superiors before taking gun
That's what you wanted
It does seem like there is a
Kind of significant amount of cognitive dissonance nostalgia
These people like
I miss whenever my life was better under Obama and I was still allowed to do
Adam Wright
And now my life is worse
But I'm supposed to like this guy but
He sucks
I hate Obama still VA for fun yelling about Obama and Hillary
The guy who's clearly eBay
Yeah this is a bummer
This guy Rambles
Surprise
And he's voting machines are these voting machines are as what
Spilled all over this country
And it ready to jump on as soon as
If it doesn't
Always ready
Go ahead and
She's other states
Bunch of sleepers
And it's
And I hate to see it but like I said
If they pass away
I'm going to rescue
Animal do what they told me that I'm not going door-to-door
That's what the other people
Dictionary
And I don't want that
People need to wake up and do some
Don't have to be on the deuce
Let's expand on that
Domestic terrorism threat assessment
Report on the number one terrorist
The FBI came out said that the main threat
Is leftist
Antifa
Ladies and gentlemen
They are going out doing the majority of the mass shootings
Consciously
Define the Second Amendment
So again you have this Texas threat assessment being brought up completely deceptively
Is one of the only things that he's really trying to push
Super hard
Again I don't know why he's not addressing
Willard wants
To take his guns on the road
Anyway Willard says some stupid Earth
Another thing to email anymore
He's God
How many more
Giuliani's parallel dilbar
Call when billboard don't deliver by this election
Call Juliana
I think that might be a conflict of interest
Further than that Giuliani guilty of a lot of s***
I do believe that there was a time maybe then right when Trump was elected that maybe
Maybe Rudy Giuliani could have been the attorney general not a f******
I don't think I would do that to confirm attorney general nominees
And I have no face
The Giuliani could clear that hurdle
Dirk Nowitzki
It's so incredibly painted right now like he's been all over the media.
Weird interviews for the last year is big step in this Ukraine business we deeper than he has any reason to be occasionally
Devon interview
Don't get me wrong I think
Those would be some of the most amazing confirmation hearings imaginable
Like an entertainment standpoint but
In terms of it being a feasible plan there's no way that
That's never going to happen
Stop talking about Hillary's emails cuz he has them
You stop talking about them because he got what you wanted out of
Talkin about the
And bring them back up now doesn't do him any good
He's not running against
Hillary to bring up her emails be kind of a week
And even Trump knows.
Honestly this dude who Alex is presenting is a real wise Insider by virtue of them saying that he's a cop in Virginia
Really seems like a regular ass Alex Jones listener
Some dumb ideas he's presenting as the
The truth there's all these they're all about
To drop these bills and all these indictments and everything is right around the corner if this thing doesn't happen or
This thing does happen what's next
We're going to drop
AG Rudy Rudy is coming in
Putting them on their shoulder
Put me in coach
That caller was
Full of bad idea
Yes yes
Alex gets another collar it's actually kind of scares me
And I believe that
My number with you ear your peers there if you want to get back in touch with me
With me please
So I've got
I'm trying to keep my phone
Involved in Lotto
I've got a lot of guys here to Farmers Federal police
Military and things like that so what what I'll do is be in Virginia
We've also got some of the guys robbing the truck up there so I appreciate your call
That's not good
Wanna start something in Virginia
It sounds like
Most the FBI has
But they're not communist
They're not globolixo
What rap artist Lee I'm sure has FBI task force is down Virginia right now
On the ground surveillance the Left End of antifa
Still walking around and not in prison
Yesterday I was asking for that
The 2015 plan for martial law in Maryland
This color clearly wants to talk to Alex about stuff that may or may not be cool to talk about on air
That's awesome
He's clearly struggling to speak without saying the wrong things Alex's wise to cut him off
Before he went to far
Also Alex goes with that
Stack everything that antifa and Soros are terrorists
Suspiciously apps
Confirm that stacker news of the articles about the two groups of members of the base
Or arrested I'm just being a dick.
Reported
Until the day after it's out
It's just funny though that those stories are going to be coming out the next day
What else is working with is
Fake Soros and
Antifa contract is intern found on 4chan
That's what level of things
Things that are
I think Trump's 2020 campaign slogan is
It's just going to be I know you are but what am I
Neener neener
We're not terrorists
Is jet is a slogan
I'm just going to be
Yeah
So Alex gets another caller who's that what you know
Real dumb
Two days ago about ended past all those things about
All those are in the general assembly and white
That same date
Active shooter hoax
You can look it up try to share that and put it on screen but it was pretty much
Student called texting
He was an active shooter
Middle schools in Virginia
I'm not exactly sure what this collar strongest
Suggest about this active shooter hoax but I assume he thinks that this is what happened
The bubbles trying to push these bills through State Legislature that already
Absolutely has enough votes to pass them
They create a hoax active shooting at a middle school in Virginia to grease the wheels
So this color brings out the shooting hoax
Suspicious
This analysis responses
Convenia
Is it the condescendingly imply that of course the hoax in the bills are connect
Haha
Here's the problem
According to wtvr local news in Henrico County
The police received the alert about the shooting through their new text to 911 capabilities
Because people can just text things in there's often not inability to come
Confirm things are ask follow-up questions
Before you need to act
If someone texts
911 that there's an
Active shooting and you're the dispatcher
There's no chance in hell you're going to wait around and see if they replied your response text
Before sending out units
Way too serious a situation sorry my battery died
Respond to your 911
Right
So I guess the conspiracy has to be that the globalist sent the text
Problem
There
Where is that the police get the phone numbers
Upheaval sending the text
And they traced it to a twelve-year-old girl who goes to the schooling
So I guess then the conspiracy has to be that the
The globalist use this
12 year old girls phone number to text in the hoax
But the problem there is that the police geo-located
Phone is being inside a first for classroom
In the school when the text was sent
This girl's phone and used it to send the hoax
Message from the school without anyone noticing
Sing anything weird
Like a globalist in the classroom
Or the simpler X
Explanation of younger
The really stupid
Maybe seems more like it's really unusual to see
Ghetto Kids between the age of
12 in
17 doing
Stupid things that could get them in trouble
Never ever happened
That seems odd
Probably the globe
Got2b the globe between 12 and 17
Another problem is that this shooting scare happened on Monday January 3rd
By the evening of the 13th
It was clear that this was a situation where someone to text it in a roni esquer
It was all over the news that night that this wasn't a real Act
Shooting
The Virginia Senate didn't vote on these bills until Thursday the 6th
The motive makes no sense
The supposed process of how this would be some kind of an elaborate set-up make
Makes no sense
To disconnected events that are easily explained on their own and actually become pretty nonsensical when you try to connect
At least they are if you think
Even a little
They both
Kind of have to do with guns
These two things
Announces train these Dum Dums
In his audience to think that everything that happens is part of the
Conspiracy
That snapshot
Alex saying isn't that convenient
Perfectly captures would an idiot
He has no idea what this caller is talking
About there's no anything about this story
He's perfectly happy to reinforce this
Kind of think
The kind of thinking to just randomly connect independent things
Noted about conspiracy
Now I will positivist
Perhaps
The globalist
Have every twelve-year-old in the United States under their can
Maybe they had one Good Year where they just got everybody you know they swept up the whole twelve-year-old generator
Right there
What someone who's 12
Right now 2008
It was all about
That makes more sense in there
So Alex gets into some
Something now that I think is amazing I think is one of my favorite things and
The dog barks
There's a bee sting there's something that carries on when your feelings
There's somebody carries on through the rest of this episode
Surprised by but
Also
I should I should have
And they also contact gungrave since David Jones on
Get your podium in Virginia next
The leftist media We Built For This audience
It seems like
The gun organizations in Virginia even don't want a spare that must be heartbreaking for him to have them
Distance themselves from
But I put armor Alex
Hey you're too hot man I can do hot with his Daddy hugs.
Hope to have you but you're standing up
So sorry I heard that I was like wow that's a weird slip
Clearly indicating
That has projector they speaking
Diego
But I didn't expect it would come back up
But it does
Veterans
Personally
Barre method
Play this next court balance is talking
About how
Individual officers
In the military or in
The police
If they get an order that they think is unlawful
They should shoot their Superior know okay alright
Now baby that would be fine if we're talking Nazi
Baby
Even then I still think that
Whatever awfully right
When they graduate boot camp
Explaining
Wobble wobble
They need to not follow orders that are unlawful or heads up
Do that you turn to shoot him in the head
Goes from there from legal orders are you
Just a quick reminder the Trump is recently pardon war criminal
Before Trump
I guess I think that's what I would say I think it's a dangerous mentality to
Advance
Bet that did that you should be the sole arbiter
Kill your general should be at least one step between
Saying yes
And then murder
I would say there's to be like maybe mediation
Let me be clear
I think this applies across the board
I'm strongly in favor of workers right
Let's say that your boss breaks a labor law no
No
I mean well but the Nuremberg defense would apply
So
What you going to do are you going to do I was just following orders
So Alex saying is next clip says it
Manuel's
So Alex said it's like they're business just sort of vague
Just ordered it is so wait till they are
He's really encouraging that everybody's got to go to
I'm going to
Be there
And
We're doing it because
Delete everybody to understand that you need to be in Virginia
Bmdc
Bowser pick one
Take the kids out of school
Do whatever you got to
So he's are advocating this
Like civilians go into a chaotic
Situation where he's already said he
Expect the globalist are going to pull a false flag
That seems irresponsible okay if he believes what he's saying
You putting
People in the path of danger
Right and that is not good
Okay so the globalists are going to pull a false flag and blame gun owners
Hours for it where assumably
People are going to
So what I would like for all of my listener
To do is gather together in that space put more people in a smaller area of space
Keeping people from getting hurt correct I guess if you really believe this sort of thing is
Potentially dangerous
The thing you would say is
If you don't need to go
People should not
Come for no reason
It should be 88
You don't need to go
No just don't
Sing the exact opposite
Governor northam's calling cousin
You want the demon eyes
Now the only solution
It's something we know is how it's a solution to every problem
And that is him
Well
Exercise that rises to demystify
Emergency crisis
Materializing
But you're word-of-mouth with a chain-reaction about Bandai video infowars.com forward slash show those wings fly
Exponentially via text messaging word-of-mouth
But outside of the censored YouTube and Twitter and all that good to everybody which is starting to happen
We have a countervailing narrative of what really goes on
All those folks
Walmart
Kyle Texas
The cover-up
This is important
Alex does not give a
About the El Paso shooter except to the extent that it helps him create propaganda
He doesn't care about this guy's addictive
He doesn't care about the
Handicar
F*** man he doesn't even know his
The point Alex
Completely lying about what the Texas threat assessment says about Patra
Crusius
He's one of the examples listed in the section about white racially motivated terrorism
Here's what the report says about him
Quote
On August 3rd 2019 Patrick Wood crusius
Allegedly opened fire in El Paso Texas Walmart killing 22 people and injuring 25 others
Did the shooting croesus posted a Manifesto in a digital media platform in which he justified his actions
As a response to the perceived ethnic replacement of whites
By Hispanics
And vote a voice support for the
Christ
Church New Zealand shooter and his Manifesto
Crusius is awaiting trial on state charges including capital murder
Airport
Also points out that there have been at least two International attack
One on a synagogue in Germany
Injured in Norway
Where the shooters quote were inspired by his action
Or demonstrated similar tack
There's nothing in this report about an
Antifa
Nothing about any of
Alex Jones is a bald-faced liar
Pretending is This Racist Mass shooter wasn't motivated by the execs
Same s*** you talked about on his show all the time
I can't put it any simpler than this
Alex Jones is an intellectual coward
Top of the world
Story
Also the words
Satan doesn't appear anywhere in the report nor does the word devil
Nor does
Occult
The word Pagan shows up twice
The only in the context of white supremacists adopting
Pagan symbols
The point here is that Alex has talked about some
Something very serious
And it relates to people being killed
This is not a matter to take lightly
Because 22 people died at that Walmart
And countless lives were changed for the worse that day
To take that event and lie about it just a
Demonize your imaginary enemies in
Further radicalize your listeners towards
The conclusion that there's no such thing as white identity motivated terrorism
That's the octopus monster
And Alex doesn't not care
He doesn't even care enough to
Using read a report
You just said he read it and makes it up about
This is just disgusting
The worst
Yep
The end of my comments
He is a very violent guy in this world Alex's world revolves around
But you said
But it's important
Right now
You work hard in the Infowars
Give links to ban.
But
Things are going to go bad
Okay and he hasn't words
Need to do when that out
I believe you will dejected
What
So you get to decide who the globalist are you know
Decide when things
Kick-off definition
You don't get to have boat
I guess you don't need to be like let's cardioverted however
Your criteria for starting it and
All on your own
Jesus enjoy
So
Galaxy gets back from break
He starts talking about the Deep state is tried to
Turn Trump
I have some thoughts
Okay
They have the Deep state
And the entire corporate media rights
Thousands of articles
Cyberspace
To get Trump to come out against Infowars
Tina believe that is the president ever came out against Infowars
That would turn his face off against
And that would turn me against the present
I don't think anyone is Ever Wanted Trump to denounce Infowars because they want to alienate him from his face
I think it's generally more benefiting where it's completely unacceptable for the president of a country to think Alex Jones is anything other than a liar
The case of Erica Lafferty who's mother with
The principal of Sandy Hook Elementary
She's very offended when Trump was elected that he been on
With Alex
Not the same person who'd said on-air that her mother wasn't really killed
MP clear her mother died trying to save the
That's cool
Called her as well as Erica
Working for the global
Strength Jake is gone
You can kind of understand why she might be interested in the president of the country distance
Himself from someone like that
And then you just had your garden-variety reasons to want Trump away from Infowars
Namely that the information that Alex puts out he's bad
It's usually factually come
Wheatley wrong
And almost always has a kernel of Lights
Supremacy buried in it
It's just unacceptable for the head of state
Talk to someone deserving
Anything other than condemnation
You don't need a deep state
Motivate people to arrive at that
Conclusion
Policy director is
A white supremacist who does all the
Right who Alex loves
So
That's all
It's all stupid
But now let's enjoy
Does Alex starts talking more about how no one wants in a
Stuff that's what I'm looking for severe burn
I want his failure
We just called up some of the pro-gun groups in Virginia today won't you come on the show
We don't want to be associated with that
Weird narrate president-elect
Associated with the First Amendment
Not even getting the instinct
Who cares what the media says about you
What we are
Need to be
Love by the couple of organizers of a rally
Shut up there
If you that has the power of what your message is
How you let them
Amateur nature
Have a lot of political activist and they look at somebody's been very very successful
With our audience America
Always being led by a bunch of political novices
It might not be political novices and they must also not be worried about bad press they might
I hate you
Little bit of reverse
Little bit of a little bit of shade on there just like
Hey if you don't want to come on my show is cuz you are
Qpi f****** amateurs
The podium was ever spoken on a Podium before and had things happen for them Alex
So mad
The Democrats
Civil War
Get there at
Together
Meanwhile the main groups that have financed Trump
The biggest fundraisers for him
For six months of a trying to get me to go on event
A bunch of them Politico what a joke
Armored vehicle
Your phone
Man he's got such
Andromache
Pathetic
Child
Do you know what I didn't even want to look
Bigger people want me then you so I did
And it doesn't bother me at all
I don't even care if you
I suspect during that break but he just went out to
Someone maybe Rob do came over and was like hey Alex that was a bad look
You look like an a******
Bad. So you say
Go back live ladies and gentlemen I want to just say one more thing about what I talked about last second
About me
You understand
Yeah I understand
Sure about it about me otherwise yelling about how your amateurs are not wanted to hang out with me and, by jove
And I'll be there in no one looks at you cuz I'm the Great
Created this movement
But I created this movement
Single-handedly imaveriq
This is not
About
Absolutely anything from my history
Alex Jones in history
I don't make it about me notably humble always always always
Is Right 100% of the time if I wanted to brag I could because I would brag about how right I am 300%
So Alex ends this episode are on the 50
Where do we see in a bit of
In the reefs
Recent days
And it's getting it
Descending in
Locked up
Space about killing global
We're starting to get to a point that as a citizen who sworn an oath publicly
Defend my family your family in our honor
That
We need to be very peaceful and very focused and very active right now
And then we'd have to understand that we don't bust our ass
Face and Emily
Watching them
That job
Pichai calms the bubbles know they can sit this out there
Again
They are intended to start
And if the president would have arrested some of the deep state
Dotty's
What the chips fall where they may
They try to bring out some dirt on some of the Trump people
Nobody's going to care
As long as he American
Supporting
Enough talk
Sand
It's my pay grade is he what we should do about the president knows
Walmart
We're not in normal situation
The Democrats are a bunch of insane methods
Are minions
They're not insulated
I need to know they're not insulated
So the only reason I I highlighted it does seem like towards
At the end of his shows lately this these sorts of conversations are becoming
Armoire
Normal
Okay
I'm going to throw this out
What if
Instead of Democrats being insane meth head
Just people like you and I just disagree
What antifa
Incel
Neil dick they can't just be people who disagree
Antifa
You know what actually you convinced me with a simple chant
I understand now just getting into this
16th and I can understand some people having a sense of like
I just going to be a slog you know I promise
If you stick it out
By the end of this episode
You will get
Here Alex Jones
Try to interview a baby
Okay
I'm not saying that we do things regularly
But so far I would have opened the show with that cuz I'll be willing to go through a lot more of that early
Tough with a better attitude I regret to tell people literally about the 16th
Interview
Now but he starts
16th by just stressing and reinforce
Sing that the globalist are going to false-flag the rally in Richmond
That used to run false Flags
When they had
The presidency
Delta Force
Bombing of a federal building
Stage
99 events
In
Washington State
Seattle
I don't have the military they don't have
Those units that can carry out
False flags on presents or anymore
And by the way when Clinton ordered all that stuff it was the beginning of the end of the deep state
But if they're going to have their metal Foundation
Birds out there
Trying to pull some all trying to trick people into a mass shooting
They got milia windup toys drugged-up probably in comas right now they're going to turn back on if I roll out in d.c.
And
In Virginia
But everybody's got to be on maximum alert right now
In the next few weeks
So I mean this is just
Spaghetti at the wall kind of s***
But it all just isn't service loan
Tank why not
Oh they're all in comas that they're going to run on ice
It is all just still in service of the exact same thing which is preemptive Justice
Applications for a theories violence it appears to be origin
Originating in the right-wing Spears it wasn't real at all fake
It's and it's sloppy Foundation people now cuz I don't have Delta Force
Alex we can't be associated with you because you
Screamed about false-flag Amateur hour
I understand why you disagree with us however
You are screaming about false Flags right now as well so you see why we're headed
Attempt to join with you
On account of your ability to learn lesson
So Alex says something really into
Christine at the beginning of this episode
That has nothing to do with
Senior anything like
I love
Freebird
Skynyrd is going to come up later
Right now that's not that's okay
Is really fast
Watching their every move
And the police are there watching
Before I had deeper understanding
America is
For good and for evil we are both here because
Cuz we are
Destined to decide the destiny of the planet
We haven't voted bad coming together in the
So I think that's really interesting
I think it's a surface-level where that statement is f***** up but there's another level it's even more trouble
Insane on the surface this is Alex saying that America is more important than any other country in the world
We decide the destiny of the planet which is just stupid
If you would have asked some blowhard subject of the crown during any of the Fallen Empires and
In the course of human history
The exact same thing
It's a myopic view things in more over it's just childish
Kipling wrote a white man
I think we got
Buried in the statement seems to be that America is the only country where both good and evil exist
The implication being that you literally said quote
America is where the battle is fought
For good and evil we have both here because we're destined to decide the destiny of the
The planet
If we're destined to decide the destiny of the planet that's not something that can really be true of more than one
That's a unique cat
Tribute of America
According to this line of thinking
That's so destiny
Nice work
The structure of the Alexs state
Is saying that
Yeah because we are the country with this unique attribute
There's both Good and Evil
Which heavily implies it in his mind
Other countries are either solely good or solely evil
I don't think Alex consciously
But I definitely think it's
Subconscious believe he holds
And guess what
Easy to guess which countries are good which are evil I don't understand what would be the difference between
If you're majority like a very short
Visual thing just give me one quick thing so I don't have to think about it
What do you think the difference is between mouth
If your majority Muslim or not but there's one way you can convert your country
The overage being good
It turns out and that's
If you have a ruler who's friends with
Override
Clear geopolitical bias towards hating on white countries
So it turns out and I didn't know this
But it turns out that
God has
Created the United
Midstates
As a Hunger Games type Battleground
To see what
Whether good or
Evil wins in the end
If your Brazil's Trump Alex is cool with you
Absolutely
So I think Alex has red
About these
Yeah base
I think he has
That's because he's aren't real
The news broke before like an hour and a half before the show started, 6
I think
That he knows about the
But he doesn't
Bring it up
Todd County right now
There's no doubt
I'm telling you it's so damn perfect
Everybody's like well why this impeachments a joke they're not going to connect him instead
They need that symbol
What day is in Traeger next week
Churches getting shot up
You'll think it's in
Virginia
When it's going to be in
California
Texas Michigan
Illinois
Mississippi
I think Alex knows that
Based on
What
The reporting is on
Did the group
That there's a possibility that there are
Other trios of people in other places
Is there other small group
Attacking a black church or a gay bar
Things that are in line with
What sort of
Neo-Nazi escort these groups
Have to achieve
The way Alex is presenting this makes me think that it's in line with him knowing about it
But he won't say
He won't talk about that story
And he doesn't
At all
No like the whole show
That seems like a
Big story
Is that a lot of people would cover
Because the information there is that
There are
Maybe a lot
Of
Cells of terrorist cells at 3
Also that
Remind takes
And you could be in over
For sure for sure the point being
It's a big store
Yes it's a big story and if I was a news organization
I would probably
Well Alex's other
Talk about being cut off from God
Call dispatch
I forgot
Thought about God hates Tim Cook story
That's a big one cook when he goes to hell which is just a
Dementia
Subway
He's going to be in a jail cell for eternity with himself a jail cell
Is Bernie hatred for Humanity that he created
God
Create hell
One thing God didn't create
That question is
Eclipse stupid and has nothing to do with anything
But as I was listening to this episode I looked at the time on it and I realize that I had cut an eclipse in awhile
So I figured I'd just give you a little Tay
Taste of how the first half
Half hour of the show isn't a stupid everything is
Alex is preaching real hard but it's a real standard boring
I think it's all the b******* about our ancestors wanting us to go to the stars and how Alex it doesn't love his fancy cars
God that's important
Of course he's in a deep hole
And legitimate
Really the only thing close to real I've heard him touch on his him making
Can clear in that
Quick we just played
Caltrop
I think that it's clear these aware of those Nazi arrest
It won't directly cover the story
It's my sense that he's
You know he's building up
Tomatoes arrest
Part of his false flag narrative
Now that the globalist putting out stories about these rest
It's probably aren't real fish in the country for a rash of fascist
Racist violence
Just secretly just being carried out by antifa until needle dicks or whatever
Shameful
And it's really boring
Honestly it's
If you're looking
For a demented televangelist
It's kind of services
In the sense that at least he's clearly an idiot
And he's calling out real people like Tim Cook
Which is kind of fun
What is a half hour stretch of a show that's
Pretending to be a real serious new show
I find it at
Exhausting
Especially considering that he's mostly doing this to ramp up to running interference
Literal neo-Nazi
Peter sells
And seemingly
On the table
To talk
Yeah it it does seem like rather than deal with
Neo-Nazi Terror cell
He's rewriting a Chris
Miss Carol
And Tim Cook is going to
Forge the chains in life that he will wear in death
Also Tim Cook
He's creating his own
Prison
Ergonomic
The god ask people that are consciously evil and do bad guys don't destroy him
But people that know what's going on
Connection to God
That's like nerve endings that the God and God
He's just like
What you know this is wrong you don't like
Children
You don't like drinking their blood will they back for Mommy
Like inventing new Eagles but you don't do anything I am on a really turn you over yourself you.
Damn coward
I have no idea what Alex is saying is some reference to a Bible verse I can't remember half and he's misrepresent
He's making God into really a human figure this is s*** that you
I'm not saying that he should be forcibly institutional
But this is the type of ship
Did somebody who is institutionalized
It's been a long time since I've read the Bible
On whether or not God has a grudging respect for people who are willfully evil
Terminal leave that aside
But I do think it might be worth
Pointing out that on many occasions
Alex's talked about having a grudging respect for people like David Rockefeller
Who are the heads of
Evil globalist
Where is he just hates
The followers are no better in sign up with evil anyway
Basically what I'm saying is this
This is trying to
Personify God it seems like a lot of his own personality gets wrapped up in the presentation
It is where I did notice that God had a very kind of like
He kind of has a cowboy nature2 I didn't realize that God wondered from
Town to town
With a grudging respect
For the black hat they're only actual
Somebody called this blasphemy
But I was just call it a very predictable manifestation of his rampant nurses
So Alex Starks
You brambles by garden and that's understood for a long
Stretch any finally talks about
Close to real at least
And that is that the governor Northam had to Prescott
So
Hh8 he reminded you know when it's like when people talk about
They're describing their pets
Baby dog loves tacos
Yeah and it's fun because you're friends with your dog
A little bit about this Northam press conference but he doesn't talk about anything
Specific he never gets to covering it
And
I would say he faked
Scrying
It's enough
Transcript
Exact script
Following the exact
We already saw them pre-programming
We got to just sit here and wait for them to come at a bash and blame it on it
Play me
Play music
Arigato
We know they're doing it and we can
Take a class
Guy is such memory
Perfect
I have seen a High School production
F******
What's the name of it the Scottish play
I was going to kill me
So we get back to this idea if you touch down earlier and that was at the Revolutionary War started in Virginia
Expand
Here
Clip
This is weird
While the Senate trial the present start Tuesday will be there while covering up the devil
All of that is going on
Just south of their Virginia
For the Revolutionary War
Nope still didn't care Boston
Boston isn't in Virginia
Where the Civil War start
The Deep state
Is it
Guilt-free repeat it
History repeats
Repeat that
Batting
Table everything
Virginia and Charlottesville Square
So
Got You Under stand correctly the globalist
Don't have
Because of course
Of course
A side effect of this isn't there obsessed with history repeating
They need to be that such of the banking everything they have on this rally on Monday in Virginia which I was calling Charlottesville Square
The only thing that makes sense because they want to kick off another civil war and that's where the old Civil War started the Revolutionary War
True thing
Again the Revolutionary War started
Despite Alex's claimed is not the same place as Virginia
There wasn't even a battle in Virginia until the Battle of Great Bridge
Which was December 9th 90
17 seven
25 for 8 months
Concord at the spiritual beginning
It seems like Alex is actually the one obsessed with
Pretending history repeats when he's got history wrong
He's also completely wrong about the Civil War
Call Mainline historians recognize the beginning
Of the Civil War began when the Confederate Army open fire on Fort Sumter
Which is not virtue
But is actually in South Carolina
I mean there's that
That was an April 8th
1061 and it wasn't
Until month later that there were some smaller battles some off the coast of
The Virginian but those were
Nor were they pivotal moments in the Civil War
If I had to guess Alex might be thinking that the Civil War started in Virginia because that was where the
The first biggest land battle the battle of Bull Run 2
But that wasn't until July 1861
3 months into open hostilities
This was a big
Confederate victory
So maybe he thinks
That's where it all started but that doesn't really make sense
Fort Sumter that attack was an absolute Confederate Victor
I'm getting out of the Alex's view history is incoherent
And he's just trying to Bluff his way around pretending the to all the big Wars in US history started in Virginia
To lend credence
Who is b*******
About the globalist want
I can take off a civil war on Monday
This is really sad hard for history to repeat itself when it didn't happen in
In the first place
That would be a difficult thing for
Like why would the globalist want history to
Repeat itself
Inaccurate historical
I don't know
Patriot lure
Burn up Laura is a good way to
Headway valet
Timey wimey
So instead of talking about
Governor Northam
Press conference
And instead of touching on this story about these Neo-Nazi arrest
At all
Alex just starts rambling about Governor Northam
And talk about how he wants to kill her
The governor
Is running around
Peckerwood
Pathetic he is evil here
Can organs
It is
Tell you weren't invited
Tell me you're bad
You need to get here
I got it all set up or he's the victim channel for kids
The Killing
With that guy so we got to shift
And watching
Salivate and literally get an erection
While he's talking about boot
The man is an Abomination but here's the thing
They'll make it attempt on his life
I wanted a little long time to prison cell I wish no harm upon
Gavin Newsom
What is this is a new wrinkle that he got an erection
Action while talking about babies in abortion
I was right now I'm just wondering if Peckerwood A step above
Music
It's hard to say
It's hard to say there's no clear hierarchy
I remember the Bible verse though remove the
Wood from your pecker before trying to remove the needle from somebody else's dick
Slipping problem remember that way
I mean look dude this is all just Alex being like
Everything in my being wants to kill him but
Society
Okay
Micelles
My heart that it's right
To murder this bad up until now has done
Nothing to me in a negative fashion whatsoever
But societies like
Don't murder people who haven't bothered you
This just ends up with Alex rambling
About Northam
And then he gets into Michelle wolf
Complaining about her
This is
This episode is
F****** exhausted incoherent
So boring and stupid for this particular episode
You didn't know how to talk
When she talks about how she killed
This is Michelle wolf
Joke
At the metaphysical image of it's a piece
Piece of crap
Family shops in right around
Material world
You know who's going to be flushed down the galactic toys
To you lady
Michelle toilet
You're damned hell
Because you made help you build help there's a place for people like you ladies and you built it
The governor
Keep calm
Carpal tunnel
God will keep you will dump open you'll give you a free will. So you'll be cut off for me
Done
You Like Oxygen you like this plan
You like everything you got your mama took carrier
Northam
God is a really weird dude
We got do invoices
Cuz you're so damn dumb
Power
I love going to the mall and see in a packet
Basically
Great job man great you're really cool.
Blowing out their transmitters
With nanotech
NASA's that connect electrochemically
Wow
You're going to ask why yes
From God you're wrong
Okay
If you
Torn into pieces
But I wish you would have long healthy life like an exhibit
Museum of what
Piece of bullying
Filthy
Arrogant
Crashes
There's nobody dislikes plug
Do you like standing up
Wow
Oh my God I threw my back out from that transition that that was feel like a
Crash test dummy right now that I just went into the wall in the car
Exploded
Wow
Embarrassed
God sounds a lot like a middle-aged
Texan man with
6w
Sarah Braden should be
Sounds like Alex projector
Little bit
A little bit of a longer clip cuz I wanted you to
Feel it
Episode
Father why have you forsaken me
Jesus
Anyway we'll see you in a little bit I hate to plug
Nobody hate plug-in more than me
Nobody dislikes plug-in more than
So glad I told you that to Skynyrd
Going to come up and I here's the clip where that comes
Keisha Scott
Alex's describing
Alex's describing what God told
You got to take action
Control
Godson
Cuz that's all God wants
The song from
Direct line to God.
First of all what the f***
Kind of Southerner does Alex think he is
He can't remember the name of Simple Man
I reckon that where I come from
That's a brick
You show up at
Karaoke bars I used to frequent
Forget the name of the Skynyrd song you're going to get a bottle of Pace Picante sauce thrown out
New York City
Episode and Alex just cannot get himself to cover the story
He's vaguely reference Governor Northam giving a press conference
Literally been talkin about nothing friend
Our Behavior press conference about nothing
Outside of a couple of supremely weird things he says this whole episode has just been
Treading water
And it doesn't sound like he comes back into the second hour and what do you know
Still talking about the car dealership
Like that you'd use hydrogen
UPS latest photo
HBO teams with CNN's Brian stelter for documentary about the rise of fake news
Going to be starring in that
Carlton
Probably going to get a mansion
He's going to get
Laughing about how fast can stop talking about
So he does a long segment on Brian stelter
Of course Angela
Weirdly
Esoteric
In the middle of this
Complained about Brian stelter physical appearance
Amazon Lala looking shelter because I want to know what the devil look like
Army that's what generals look like
Slaves
Why does Batman
Tone-deaf
I need my telephone
He doesn't have anything he is literally
Other universe
He is the scum of the earth is
Absolutely destroyed solid piece of trash
Hold on a second
It might down for the rest of this club because Alex is going to I really don't know what he's talking about and I do need your help to park
I don't say that to me
Get away from it
Because the next level here in the find out what's really going on
And I'm telling you it's already erase
Almost
Detonated
Is it a weapon
God is good
Because we think I'm God is invincible and omnipresent and God is he we believe in God and stand up
Let me tell
The bomb
The bomb doesn't
I think it just destroys it carries out this
Fraction of children
.
If its primary mission
All it does is kill live
And I see children
The potential the future
That's why they're powerful
Because it's broke
It's not a soul
I don't I get it
I get it all you're looking get it all I'm very I decide totally got moving can I ask
If do you understand this because there's a piece of SyFy that you've read that I have
So you are familiar with
Okay
This
Is Peter Pan than this is
Exactly Peter Pan
God is a strong if we all believe in him out
God is Tinkerbell is killing all of the children that's the f******
Crocodile
It's all it all makes sense
He is completely confusing the plot to Peter Pan
I think
Got I think there's a possibility that you're right and made the Tinkerbell part of it
Is very if you believe it
Okay that's weird that's
Tinkerbell
Idea what he saying
The end that like
The
Like the demons are at
Computer program.
I mean I don't agree with him but I can't
I get what you're saying
I understand conceptually
And I think the other stuff
About like there's a bomb
It's been detonated
There's a bomb in the crocodile
True
I'm convinced I mean to express it like there is a timeline or there's a dead
There's a deadline we've got to get off
Planet by
The demon
Program has already been
So we're running away from the bombs
Detritus right because
Brian stelter looks
Yes that is correct that is that is what started it
DLR right
God began a half-hour into the second hour to snow now and you will not talk about anything
Means anything man
Dude I will say
He did give a long retelling of the story of The Prodigal Son
It seemed like she was kind of close to the actual story but I'm not positive the metaphor
So it was way too long
Take me to Cotton Club
For it but everyone should know
You getting closer
Children's bible stories
Still waiting for him
To give a critical breakdown
Don Quixote
Right on every single.
Those windmills
Those are the ones causing all the problems
Jesus
Protect us from windmill that's why the Jews put them on a windmill and spun around everybody knows
I was working
Pretty late
Getting all the all the stuff ready
Episode
At 2 in the morning
Maybe 1 or so but whatever the case
I lost my mind I would have been flagging long before
I'm amazed you made it this far
I quit made me lose my mind
Laughing
Dinos
It's not bragging
Infowars people
You're the best
You love God
We're not
We said it wouldn't recognize that
The elect
God love Justice and freedom are hypocrite
Start face
What's another show
That just made me lose my s***
God's elect
Alack
No no this isn't
We're just God's chosen people just so happen
All the good people in the universe are the people believe my outrageous bulshit
What's even crazier is that all the good people in the universe
Love me
Love me specifically
Perhaps
Maybe the only thing that
Actually unites all of these good people
Is there love for me
And I'm not saying no
I'm not boast
So at this point Alex
Finally gets to the neo-Nazi
I'm lying
He doesn't
Football games
Talking about
Get on your knees
And decide you want to be a Brian stelter
I got up this morning I saw this infowars.com article that I wouldn't saw this.
Dental assistant
Animal training
Dental assistant fired
Expressing support
Pro Trump on Facebook
So Alex is gearing up here to interview is conservative victim of the week
Yeah this time it's a Milwaukee woman named Robin Pollock who claims choose fired from a dental assistant job because you posted
Make America great again on Facebook
Unfortunately this doesn't really seem to be totally true
Apparently someone left a bad review on her employers Facebook page
Claiming that her social media was offensive and racist
And that might have a lead to determination but it doesn't seem like
Supporting Trump was the offensive or racist
Nothing
CBS 58 out of Milwaukee fountain for Facebook post where she had posted things like
Suggesting that President Obama was the leader of Isis
All right well that one
That one's trouble it's possible that someone saw that post founded offenses racist to eat hunted made the
Complain to her employer
I have no idea what the reality is here because she says that she was fired for supporting Trump which is
Exactly what she should do
In the circumstance
So she finds herself
Victimhood narratives are like
Catnip
Conservative media so she's going to get a lot of play out
And plenty of opportunities to promote let's say a GoFundMe
Like the one she's already launched
Called quotes
Wrongfully fired for saying Maga
Good for her
Her employer says grift
Employer says they didn't fire her for supporting Trump and the labor attorney that CBS spoke to even if they
Did that wouldn't be illegal
Political opinions are not protected
From an employment
Perspective
Alex tells her to Sue or former employee
And that she is a slam-dunk case
But I sincerely hope that used to paying attention to Alex's legal situation
Knows better than to think he's a good
Source of the law
This gets a big old who cares from
I generally are on the side of Labor
So I would say that the employer probably shouldn't
Issue just posting
Dumb memes online or whatever
But also accept there might be a whole lot more post
But I'm not aware of it and I can't possibly be bothered to look for
And honestly the solution to this problem isn't going on Alex is showing
Complaining about
Dumfries Peach
Fighting for stronger protections her employees
Yeah you would think that strike you can't now you can't have Union
You need protections for employees
And employers me to just
Willingly give those out as we all know they they were always
Protecting their
Western Christian
Ethos make these employers
Whatever possibly can't care about Alex making a big deal out of someone possibly being fired for supporting Trump when he didn't give a
S*** about people were actually fired
Specific
Because they supported Obama
In November 2012 The Huffington Post cover the case of a man who owned an aviation Service Company in Georgia
Fire two employees
Specifically because they voted for Obama
Is part of his backlash for Obamacare
But I'm sure Alex
Cry about that on air
Strange you're plenty of other cases like that
People fired
Transporting Obama
But pointing out apocracy is meaningless
I only bring up this point
At all
To help explain
That what's going on here is not Alex being offended that someone would be fired for their political beliefs
It's a play
He's putting on to amplify feelings of
The political Vic
Anyway Alex interviews her about how she likes Trump
Because
He can't
Handle covering this news
About these Neo-Nazi arrest
It doesn't seem like he wants to get to it doesn't seem like he's not interested in terms of like he just doesn't cover the story
Wildly incredibly interested in not talking about
Seems like he's
Desperately trying to fling himself in the other direction
And he also says that this interview was set up on short notice
Seems like all of this good Feller this is red
See what I don't
Is
If it were me and I'm pulling this s***
I would have I would have brought up that the professor who got fired over saying you should
If you want some targets hear some cultural
That guy got fired
Right and sure you disagree with
Here's a cheap White
Nobody cares
About hypocrisy
Nobody gives a s*** you just point that out and be like see look I'm
I don't care I'm all about free speech
Imply
Anyway
Coming to this and I thought well this'll be skippable
Skip about now cuz in the middle of the interview this dental assistant baby
Comes over
Alex decides it would be a good idea to interview
He gets a little bit esoteric
And
This is one of the creepy or things
That I've heard on his show
Because you said I was your baby bring your baby
He wants to see if he heard your voice
Hey what's your name Buddy
That's awesome you love your mommy
You love God
Yeah you know God loves you
You look just like your mommy
What do you
What do you want to do when you grow up
Spider-Man
You know a Spider-Man semi-auto is Ono
Comes great responsibility you know you have a lot of power
Diseases
Are you watching years from now
Boy
Knowing the web
To this three-year-old
Is the web
Yeah I mean for Alex like all of his talk
All the time about like globalist wanting to take children his interaction with a child is
Unnerving
3 p.m.
Man you know what
Here's the worst part
I think Alex really does love Spider-Man
Baby and I think you really did hate Spider-Man into the into the spider-verse probably because there was a because mph
Elsa Spider-Man
And he was notoriously non-white
And yet
That's the best Spider-Man movie
This is why racism is bad you don't even get to enjoy the best Spider-Man movie
But yes there are other reasons for a little bit longer
Upset how did it go
And ask her baby out on
Eventually you be mother
Sit down
They just talked about her jobs great news you should have been fired
Whatever
B
They get to
A commercial break
And Alex
Gives up again
I'm trying to find an attorney that
Perfect for the situation and I've had a few people contact me
It's a very very fine line because Wisconsin is that state where they can fire
Are you for anything or do it because
Political news
I'm here
You see that the mask for concern for the law Slips Away
Now it's revealed what this is really about
He feels
Attacks by proxy because this woman is saying she was fired
Because she supports Trump and all he wants
Is Payback
He knows damn well that you can be fired for political beliefs
For no reason at all
Wisconsin's an at-will employment
And political belief is not up
Protected category of speech in unemployment
Setting
He's been pretending that it is
Energy
But here at the end he acknowledges that
It's not about that
Who cares what the lawyers say this company needs to
Be punished
He doesn't want to punish them for breaking the law
He wants to punish because they've done something he sees as being against
The world of truck
This isn't about anything other than Venge
Anyone who's against the leader be punished
This is a super f*****-up especially as a way to sort of wrap up this interview there was about other people firing her Worth or Terry
Whatever
I was noses audience won't even notice who gives
It's always so fresh
Frustrating to me
When when we're being
Like
When people on the left are being demonized
Where the evil ones were trying to destroy everybody
And then you hear this interview and you like lady
The stuff I believe
Would have protected you too
Even though I just
Disagree with you more likely
Even though you disagree with me what I'm going for would benefit the both of
And what you want then if it
Not even you
Doesn't seem like it
Late I thought that was going to be the end of the interview
Well it turns out when they come back
Be engaged
Some pretty
Bucked up Behavior
This person really like
You need to put him on blast
Completely Mia
Listen to Rivers which is Lake Norris
Someone creeping around making sure women lose their job for the president
He's a real person
Belize women I'm surprised
I understand how this woman probably feels like it's no big deal to say this guy's name on Alex's show
And point out that he's the reason she got fired but Alex would really have learned his license
He's currently being sued for his pardoning
It's getting of harassment experienced by the Sandy Hook families and now here he is essentially dachshund this dude
And saying that he likes
Tabouli women
Alex's audience is probably not nearly as potentially dangerous as it once was but this is so f****** your response
Possible no matter what
Alex can't do this order
Putting Targets on private sitting
Whether or not he feels like they deserve it
I just don't think he cares
What happens because he wants people who he feels of wrong Trump supporters to be punished
Hopefully this doesn't lead to another lawsuit for him
This is
This very night
Shefit
She just has no idea
Has no idea she's
She's talking to him I don't know
Oh yeah he's this guy like
He's lives up in there that she doesn't realize
Maybe see if
Maybe I can't believe
I don't know I mean they talk some more about needing to go after
Okay well then nevermind f*** her
Is being cited as a lot about the dental office and stuff
Precision Dental
And Blasting all them same time they should be blasting this guy if he never made
That post a review I still be at work
Be at work right now
So you're saying you're saying
Why do I burn Precision Dental when we should go
This
All American
This wannabe slave master
I think that we should go out there both it's a big deal you know I was wrongfully fired because of his Rubio
Maybe she's talking about suing him or engaging in illegal process but she's in
Is not not the sort of thing
Anybody should being gay
These people are so stupid
Yeah so they have this interview is pointless and
That's a pretty close after this
And immediately gets to his neck
Right we're not going to talk about this gas and I'm going to
Explain why after this clip
But this
Really worried
Cuz Alex started talking
About his lies about this Texas assessment report
Auntie was trying to describe his own narrative
I kind of got the sense
Is it
This is really troubling
We got our nice guy
I just want to get the shop
State Police Department report
Wikipedia portal years ago
Incels
People that are in the posthumanist movement environmental movement
Involuntary
Celibacy
Almost every Mass shooter
That clip makes me pretty concerned that Alex doesn't know what an incel
Like if you were to ask me my first response wouldn't be someone who's into posthumanist moved
Environmental movement
Some satanism
I
Without a doubt
Say that they are people who are into involuntary celibate
That's kind of right there in the word in a voluntary bit of an oxymoron
There's a
Baseline issue year that Alex is absolutely lying about this Texas threat assessment
Report that he definitely hasn't read
Eclipse like this really make me deeply worried
But he doesn't even have a conceptual grasp
On the stuff
You say
If he doesn't know what an incel is
How can you possibly have any understanding of what he's talking about
Really scary the level of irresponsibility seems to be approaching his job
Gazette
That's f***** up yeah for somebody who even in his in his own f*****-up worldview is
Obsessed with
Chivalry
I would
Also
So I can't talk about this
Next gas
He's a guy he's the guy
Who disrupted the mass shooter at the church in Sutherland
I'm not going to cover this interview primarily because I don't want to appear to be judging
In the sky too harshly
I read an article about him in Texas monthly and he seems like a decent guy what a life-changing
Experience
And since he's been cast as the archetype of a good guy with a gun
I'll read you a little bit here from the article
You didn't ask to be a citation in someone else's debate
Is experiences more than a datapoint
Those seven minutes ravaged
This guy and I do not
See eye-to-eye on politic
At all
But you seem earnest
Is that like he's anti-abortion
He also says in the interview that some of the stuff Alex is saying sounds like a
Conspiracy he doesn't want to engage with it
Any intro to the interview Alex makes it clear that this guy had no idea who Alex was before agreeing to come on the show so I'm
I'm going to give him a pass
Answered not beat him up
Making
The bad choice
Show to go on
Yeah it doesn't
Seymour
Anyone's time
But
Because this guy is on
He didn't know who Al
But his wife had told him
That he
Lied about Sandy Hook
So
In the intro to the interview
Alex start rationalizing
His behavior
About Sandy Hook
Aunt
Accidentally
Admits exactly what he's a goddamn
What an idiot this is this is
Basically
Confession
Everything's out here. There's nothing nothing sacred are none of it
And I used to follow Abby internet.
You know cuz that's like we don't believe this happened with bloggers this anomaly
I found out well I think that did happen.
The minute though
I went and said I stopped
If you you said nobody. You lied about that you do that
To make it my identity when I hardly ever talked about it so I want my identity back
And I understand it's not about me
It's about
How they change the subject
In that clip Alex just basically admitted to what he's being accused of in this lawsuit
What are you saying is that back in the day you just believe whatever he read on dumb
Conspiracy sites online
Let's be honest that's not a back-in-the-day thing that's basically his business
Two back in the day I was seeing all these anomalies online about the Sandy Hook shooting and he was convinced of them
Mantelli was
And then when he said that he thought the shooting
Did happen that's when people pounced and accused him of lying
This demonstrates
A fundamental misunderstanding about why what he did was bad
It's not so much a matter of him lying about it
It said he took these conspiracy completely baseless and fraudulent claims that he read online
Almost all of which came from Jim Fetzer and Wolfgang halbig
And you reported them
As fact on his show
You didn't report them as
The internet has a question about this thing
Whether or not it's actually strange
He just repeated bulshit from the internet and pretended that it came from real sources
Honestly I
I think that clip is about to occur
Fashion
Announcing go f*** himself cuz I want my identity back bowls
Yeah I know
Now you don't you
You earned
Yeah that is your identity
Yep you got to own it
And you don't want to know
Alex has Matt Bracken hosting the 4th hour
16th and it is worthwhile.
To know that
Matt Bracken also recently made an appearance on Red Ice Radio
Supremacist Neo-Nazi adjacent show that
He was on there to talk about the
Situation. I assume he was against
No
It was used against the way they got
He is against
The globalist
Trying to set up
He was up to no good
He comes on
Alex said does a little segments
The 4th hour
And the audio is a little bit different on this
I'm not entirely sure why
But
Because I have a little bit of fun
On the way out here
That sucks it was all just leading to a false flag
Sing all along
Also I think the Dave Mustaine probably was like I used to write my album haha
Imagine he's not here
Very derivatives Galaxy's angling to write his own Metal Opera
Ubv like a
Shatner
Talking weirdly over
And everybody knows that when the alien
They will find us
Subway
So
How to use in 4th hour like his mood
At the end
And
I have I have a slightly different thought
About his behavior than
How he described
Virginia
About 1 a.m.
Alex has absolutely not been in a good mood
So he's been very weird and yelling about the devil
I guess he's not in as bad a mood as one might expect
Considering the
And I think the reason for that is not that he's been feeling
Spirit
It's been he's been that
Textbook definition of Escapist
On this show
There's real news cover but instead of talking about any of the stuff you supposed to know about
You rambled about abortion
Michelle wolf
But now Brian stelter is ugly than interview dental assisting
Alex is a
Because there's a story that he needed to add
And he couldn't even bring himself to talk about it at all
Two cells of suspected white supremacist terrorist
At least one of them having plans to attend the rally and Rich
And all Alex
Can do is make vague pronouncements by false Flags
And why is ass off about the Texas Reddit
This is a week
Weak man
The news about the first three men arrested in broke
Going in the hill by 11:41 Eastern Time
64 an hour and a half before he went on air Austin time
There's no excuse for
The rally is an event he's been building up his
The sight of a globalist false-flag that
It will start the next civil war
And he's attending the event
This is a major major news story that
Very relevant to his coverage and honestly
You have a responsibility to address
Even if it's just to say that they're false-flag globalist neo-nazis
Is there something
But he's too chickenshit
Steven Steakhouse flag there yeah that's
It is
It could not be more glaring in it
It could not be more an admission of guilt
I think I mean enough for a guilty
I feel like if I had to guess
It is probably as a
Situation where he's like
I don't want to alienate I don't want to say that I don't
This is the infuriating kind of Alex Jones
He's right here he's an embodiment of a very serious problem
I would summon up like the
Most people would not have a problem with normal law-abiding citizens carrying guns at a second amendment rally
It's kind of what you would expect
The problem lies in the extremist album
They've been drawn to this rally with the constant over-the-top the next to the Lord's going to start
Does a false-flag plan to Global it's going to do it
Without the propaganda machine that Hypes up these sorts of events this rally would not be taken on the sort of character that it is
And Alex and his ilk
Have played a role in causing that
And Alex don't give a s***
Even if there is a shooting at the rally he won't be there
He's pretending he's going to this rally but he barely doesn't he basically doesn't even these events outside of his armor
Tank anymore
I'm certainly not going to let that get close to where the people are
This is a marketing offered
Tunity for Ally
His brand is the Second Amendment guy in 1776
I'm going to start again guy
Do you go to Virginia like you Xanax are going to La for Pilots
He's going for
Exposure all the wild
The people of rich
Men have to deal with
Like this
Is just disgusting
I can't stress enough like
He had to talk about
Yeah he had to
And he didn't
Yep
That's
You can't
You just can't
Yeah like that's not a thing that
Can be done that's not an acceptable thing to do
It is simply
I don't even and you'd I don't even know where to begin with policing that kind of concept all I know is that
From any any reasonable standpoint
Him doing
Nothing but
Bugging
God is saying this and Brian Seltzer's a demon
After is
Insanely inflammatory rhetoric
Helped to lead to the situation that we are currently in
Not that I'm giving him any kind of direct blame for these
But it is f******
Imperative
That he say
Bad or
Horsefly
But even then he's staying
He's at least saying that committing a terrorist Act
Is out bad thing
But even from
Early part of the show where Alex says
They're going to try and kill Trump this week
Like I sent
Becky's aware of that new
I don't think
The he's unaware
No he can't
And that's one of the parts of it that makes it really difficult for me to swallow this entire show
It is just Escapist
It is just a rambling about abortion in North America
Michelle wolf
Stelter
And the devil
And interviewing a dental assistant in the guy with the
Disrupted the shooting
Glen Springs
Almost like
Anything not to cover
You need to it is simply a
Possible for him
Do not know about
If if we get a if I get a
Tweet whenever like 5 minutes after I kaitlinbennett things go goes viral
He got a f******
Text
2 seconds
After that he'll Atwood
6 hours before that thing
Somebody we know is going down
Also to that point
National Treasure
World
Squirrel
Basically not
Samantha post
But
Before he does
Alex
Teach other and kill each other all day ever what color we are
And they're manipulating as the
Supposed savior saying oh we're going to take your rights and Liberties way to stop the racism
It's disgusting
We don't need white guilt and we don't need
We don't need to be
Frankie lights
I don't go down here almost every weekend eat at the local
Soul food places black people on it
That'll just get back to you with what you stand for you produce that Talia measure thing
Jimi Hendrix
Credible
Well that settles it
He's not racist
They're planning something big in Virginia by knows it imma be on the ground there
A lot of money to go to Virginia
Different to a plug
You did a pre-recorded thing about I shouldn't have white guilt and everybody's great my love soul food Jimi Hendrix music is great I'm out of races today
Go to Virginia alright alright Alex I know you're not going to be in studio tomorrow so we just got we just got to record
We just need you to plug this so we can cover some of these cost
I know it seems crazy okay so we're just going to start with
We have a lot of great products go ahead and start there
No okay no you're doing a lot of weird right now
Okay no I think that's great I think that's great let's just start from the top
Okay that's still not even like
Directly addressing the situation
But it's all still like there's a big plant they're going to do all those applying something big
And that constant drumbeat of like
This is going to be a false flag there going to be a false flag
It's all just super irresponsible
I detest it I find this
Tubi
Like a
It is
Life is real
And
This sort of s***
Trickling into the real world
Is just
Where is
So much
Right-wing media is simply not held accountable for in
In terms of
Joking this
Constant paranoia in order to take it
Advantage of these people
In terms of money invo
Yep that is that is what
The conservative media sphere is
Is doing and has done
And we'll never be loyal to count of
Go for it I guess
I guess that's just not something that I have
It doesn't seem like it's a high priority
Nope
Anyway
We come to the end of this
All I can really say is I hope that
Calmer heads prevail and everything is alright
And the things go off without any incidents but I have no ideas
The recording is on Sunday like I said
Enza
I mean this is this episode sucks and it's mostly just extended Alex being
I douche
And
Trying to play preamp to groundwork for
Narrative
No matter what
Yeah now
That is all stupid
But
We did get to hear Alex interview babe
Now here's the other thing though that
Include him in interview
Every manager
To be shameful in
Every single possible aspect
Of running a broadcast
True I mean is he didn't miss
Anything
It's not even going so far.
Even going so far.
He's never added a baby to this before that's a fair point
So he's got it from every Lucky Star to bring an animal
And everybody will be at the bottom of the checklist
But until then
Also on Twitter
Please go to iTunes
Yeah tell next time I'm near I'm dzx Clark
I am the juiciest ice
Alex