Alexandra Thurston color
We're couple dudes like to sit around
Drink red wine talk about Alex Jones
Then wait for death
There's been a change this week
Probably the best way to put in water and waiting for death
Time
Boy boy
Build a bunker
Too like I got to go to Infowars store.com
Radiation
Vinh phuc yea we're at but it might finally we discovered that there's one good thing like
Alex Jones
The entire human race think what he has
Anyway to the shows that I know so much better
I'm at is where we find our Middle Ground
We might know a little bit
Might be closer to buy we educate and inform in the meantime
Hopefully
We entertain you know what you know what
I was because I'm impossible to listen to
It's
Damn folks
Probably some Jordan photo
Probably some kind of annoying
And vice versa
Yeah
Sublimate
Sound off on Twitter
Destroy both of our self-esteem
For a safe space
I'm a policy wonk for you Bryan Burger thank you very much
Donating to the show
Play some music Brian
Donators
You also
You can or we have and if we have any Alex Jones listeners that's the real problem
He's an old friend of mine on the night before his wedding
Almost beat me up over a sink
He's a good man
Before
How did the wedding go
What it was fine I got too drunk at the reception though it might've
No ice
Ikaraoke Strokin
And didn't realize that there were still children present at the reception
It was a it was a Knight of Cups on my part
I get to what are episodes
I told you before we started
Unlike a lot of episodes we've ever done in the past
First I want to start with an out-of-context drop
I have nothing to do
With what we talked about on today though
Baby shots
As well
I don't like any of what's going on out there
That was
A long
Time for them to do that
Little round table about
That was some of their deep analysis
It went way off the rails
They just showed that some indication of like how the show has been the last
Few days
It's been a disaster
Okay
There goes another one another baby dies
Liberal veterans hierarchy
Most of it
You can imagine what he's doing they're doing a little
Next episode
Go to be about
Really hard couple time travel episodes we're going to end up doing
Okay in the near future I want to do one of my
The day of the Boston bomb
Cuz I was really curious cuz I remember listening to him a little bit back then
Here's the thing I don't know Forever cover the episode itself because
Much like the 9/11
Episode it's really not that interests
Okay but
The news of the Boston bombing is breaking
He's in the middle of an interview with Richard Belzer
Richard Belzer
The Richard Belzer sidecars
His coverage of the Busta
Over Skype
It's amazing
So he is still on Skype with Richard Belzer
Well this news break
And Richard Belzer is not allowed to go
No and he's thrilled to be there
Wildly
Target Patriots
Belzer's just straight-up signing off on Olive and Order and everything
You think he's like you know he has a lot of ideas about JFK but
Richard Belzer Bells Hells Bells
And he's just there
I told Richard Belzer
So it's digging around as trying to find a
Something for us to cover because like I said
No man's land
Where was no good
I was really struggling
And then
I realize realize
On Monday
Alex Jones didn't interview with Jack
Dystopian
Yes we brought him up a couple times and
And today
It is finally time
For us to do
Do something
Call one of our 30 days
Are going to become more and more essential
That week
Clearly delineate these f****** characters are
Exist in the periphery
Okay Alex Jones interview with
Because
He is one of the main forces
Is behind the neck Ron Lee
So I found a
A New Yorker article
The contradict
His story
About what happened
Okay Yorker story
That actually
Uses
An interview with Jack
Sobiech
It sort of foundation
From this New Yorker
I reach pasovic by phone on Saturday
The previous day he told me he had flown from Washington
Is Miami to attend a party hosted by the far-right
Self-promoter
Milo yiannopoulos
Asobi expect much of Friday night monitoring for Chancellor
Pole
Before 10 message
Which has recently become a breeding ground
Four nationalist trolls
Both in the US and abroad
There's a quote from Passover
People were claiming something big was coming so I just kept hitting refresh you told
Shortly before 3 p.m.
3 p.m.
4chan user posted 9 GB of information
Reportedly hacked emails photographs
And internal documents
From the campaign of Emmanuel macron
Bia could not know whether all the information was authentic
He didn't even have time to glam
Through most of the thousands of pages
But he considered his journalistic duty to let his followers know about the leak
Quote
Massive dock jumpit Pole
He tweeted he included a link to
4chan posts
Along with the hashtag bicron week
Got involved
According to him
It was
And that's why everybody was mad at
Wikileaks or something
And yet they weren't the ones who
Leaked the information to wear hats
They just had it
Yeah they really got with it and really stiff
Hacked by somebody
He goes to this party
And people start retweeting it
And it starts
The catch Steam
So like at about midnight
He realizes
Milo yiannopoulos
Does party
Penny realizes that a bunch of other
Started to pick up on this
Play some of these Bots Farm started
First Contact
It's been demonstrated has been done in
So on the phone video on periscope
She called a quote
The first few minutes consisted of
He has not read or looked
He's going to a party at the
The first episode and his girlfriend
By Migos
Wapa sobiech occasionally made the okay hand gesture all right
Just f******
Just let me enjoy that
Yeah sure that
Mental image of monsters
Journalism bulshit
Yeah
You're dancing to Migos
He took some harsh criticism and his response was
I just find interesting things and post them to my Twitter feed
Look journalists have gotten so bad that they see someone like me doing real work actually digging through documents
And distributing them to people they assume there must be some sort of
Conspiracy behind it
Anything this could be a learning experience for the New York Times and lamon
And the rest
Understand how real journalism words
He would do his own admission in this article
So that should give you some food
F*** that guy is
Yeah I'm not right
Hate him I read I read something about him
Describe
Journalism
Garrett
And I believe his quote was
I'll go to a trump rally and start spinning anti-clinton stuff
Such a dick that's not being a journalist of any kind of directly relate
To what we talked about in the 2050
Peanut
Where Mark Dice went out
And ask people to be supported
In Fort Worth without a video about it
Drudge Report
Alex Jones starts reporting The Drudge Report
Is reporting
This thing
ABS cycle
Yeah
Itsnotjakefuller sobiech goes and starts a fight
Anti-trump rally
He becomes the story many reports on the story
Yvette
Okay
Now I have only taken
Journalism
But
I have read
Journalism
Temperature
I feel like that's wrong
Aren't you supposed to like by the definition of Journal aren't you supposed to record these things
NFL
Even
We're going to talk quite a bit about the Soviet today
At the end
I guarantee you
He going to be bought
But
We have to start
With why he was on the show on Monday
So he was tweeting about the macron wife
Right and now he's coming on to Infowars on Monday
Because
The Narrative is
Is that macron himself
Is suing Jack Purcell
So I will let I will let Alex Jones start the narrative
The Shelby actor
The whistleblowers the Lakes
I don't know if he's doing
He's doing is they're starting an investigation into
They are
Simply legal
To investigate
Leasehackr
The one
You got hacked illegal
Especially because
This hack is different
Then the podesta
Another hacks in
In the past
Flippantly
Has tons of pictures
Apparently macron put his own fiction
Mark
Super smart
Didn't know he was going to be hacked
Still
I mean if you're half you know you're going to
Intelligence agencies in the last
Today's have confirmed that they told
Guys
We can monitor them we're seeing them happening
You are being
Digitally attack
So
You should guess
Like if you're going up against the Nationals candidate
Anywhere
You better believe you're gonna get high
Just do a better job of hiding
It's becoming the tool of the present and the future of life
This one is undeniable
Like this was
With Italy
We're trying to influence
The selection there were sirens
And the only reason is to help the national
The other hack
Helping Nationals candidate
With title
To Putin
Yeah it is
It is now on
Evidence
Coincidence I will kill mice
It's like it's like this stuff happening
Sally gate at Valley gate
Clapper's testimony the other day
Call me being fired
Today ever recording this
All of it is cheap
Too much I don't know how to handle this
Let's not talk about that let's talk about Jack put Soviet
It's easier some person who deserves to be
He's going to talk about
Stuff that's being found in these documents
I hope it's pink what really happened what's unfolding why they're suing you either so upsetting
Escorts the drugs and what's going on
Try Channel
Funding antifa
Let's be clear
There is not
Of those Bank
But he's talking about
There is absolutely no evidence of it because it's been proven they do not exist
Images
Are all not what they say they are insurance
During the pain for defamation because that
Literally what she's doing
Not noticed he's not a French I don't know
But they're not
Here's the thing
Will probably
The kind of behavior that's being expressed
Pierre is the kind of thing
Sure hope they do now because now he's he's introducing this idea of like
They were paying people to secops
And then it's going to get worse
May 1st
Designer drugs
Mmc30 sophisticated
Sexual cult
She was involved in pedophilia himself
No
Search for mmc3
Everything that comes up
Is about an inn
Nintendo controller
Kobe memory-management controller
This is that
Deep stuff
I mean his wife is a lot older than him
The age of consent
Francis
So
I don't know I don't know if you want to call that pedophilia but like actually
Yeah specifically about
Child abuse
Unfounded
It's just weird
Who was his high school
Relationship
Weird and unusual and
I know at least two people who ended up dating teachers one of them got married but they did not
Start their
While they were
Peter and Stewie
They've been around that likes
Team17 no man
It's f***** up but
Mary Kay Letourneau s***
I don't know I'm not here to go to bat for macron
Bangarang
But I also am not here to call it pedophilia
I think that that is
Be great if you explicit
Like at the very beginning of the
The episode you like
Personal investment of this whatsoever
Yeah
I do think it matters though culturally that the
Is 15
It's not illegal
Gross and you should be held
Anyway I Eagles on UE says even worse stuff
About
Macron and his wife
But even then it's he made it implies it
He wasn't
That he was involved in Petal
It was like he was in
The victim of pedophilia
All around
It was part of that world and therefore he will always be part of that work
A complete skipped over the part where he said that he's on a gay sex
Colt email
Is totally believable
Email is what kind of gay sex called as an email that's a shity called
It's time to send email blast for a next game
Hey guys I'm going to
Send you an Evite
How's Saturday morning around 11
He goes on a little more and this is the stuff that I've actually seen
People tweeting about
Like this this part of this comment
Haven't had enough
Things to translate
Hopefully people
Handle ever
Truth based investigation
Secondarily brought up Rebel very important
A piece of this puzzle that is going
Going to be increasingly dangerous
Future
Designer drugs
Doubt the story is Amy's admitted with him and his older wife that there's a lot of weird stuff going on
High school students
Relationship
Something is going on
And they found this guy very very young and they were using that too
Controlling president
Around the world
Great journalism
Mind control
Hooray
Yes all of them
Celebrities
Yep
Therapy whatever Kim Kardashian
Yep he's groomed
Because he said that nothing started until he was of legal age
Sister's going on
Sure
If somebody asked
Do that question all the time and then you answer
Truthfully
And then of course
Mind control with the designer drug right yeah they take this really young guy and you drug him up real good now he's
Your puppet
Now he's the youngest
President France ever literally
Someone who just beat the
Ants off of Maria Lopez
Crazy like
The idea
What the age of
Consensus in France
That means he's not doing any work
Just Milo's party
Mancino's really good at all
Right and then he comes into the hours Jerry's like
He's probably being
Drugged up
It is just a puppet
Like you
If your turtle toucan
Gypsy that
You don't have anything to back that all wildly about mind-control drugs and whether or not they are being used to
Populate the leader
As well as music
For phone
The number one musician being mine
Uncontrolled right now
Migos
This data most of the substance
What are you talkin about
He also is asked at one point about how he found out he's being sued
And his f****** answer is
Solveig nonsensical
Like I tried to Google it I tried to find like
You know
The Soviet being
Sued by macron
There's nothing
He said the documents Republic
But there is nothing
There's nothing
He's not being sued by
Anyway
We're going to get back to Jack the sobiech in a second
But I want to get the taste out of our mouths
With our old friend out
Do we need some Alex Jones on this
Yes we do is going to be a lot of
So let's
Joy Alex while we can
Discussing how evolve
What you want
Is Beto
When macron
Pyramid you came out in front of the
The pyramid
Satanist
Gesture
Now
Some might argue it's one of the biggest landmarks
But
Alex brings up
I need
I need you to let
Like I want you to hear every word of this
Alex Jones
Because he starts reading for once in his life
So here we go
And sure enough
Obscura
Duluth
And you can read where
Impairment Rays totenberg cats following the publication of an official brochure
It was claimed
They figure it wasn't quickly quoted on Denver's his diapers and became a widespread
Do they have
The gnosis that blue pyramid 666 painted in fact
False
Himself
Why is there at the end he tried to undersell how what he was reading
Says the opposite of what he wanted to say
You think that like these 666 tile thing it was
Sigelei proven to be a hoax
And he
Drops off the word hoax
Andrew
Getaround
Babe's on the beach Brock Lesnar
Because the loop
Came out
Right and all of this stuff is
Just based I mean if you listen
All just based on
Looking around you
Airbrush
Who doesn't
Hey bro
Isadora fraules
French for a little while
So
Technophobia
Just come in here
He's made his claim
About my screen
Johnell
It's time to
A little trip
Time to the last time
The jackpot sobiech was on Infowars
Okay baby the last time
What is the most important
Is when
Was breaking the story about pizza
So what we're going
Is f****** monstrosity
Story that's still
Goddamn
Died because
No one else should have to
Watch the entire video
Objective sobiech going
And isolated clip
Now we're going to work video
What we're going to do
Is work going to listen
Do his interview with Owen Shroyer on Infowars
And then whenever he says something about what he did
Comet Ping Pong
I will play the actual audio I just proved in real-time what else
Just put those back-to-back for the rest of the episode will call it will call it good afternoon
So like
Does serve a purpose
I like company
This is the beginning of the interview we did with Owen Shroyer
Totally
We are joined by Jack Purcell
He was giving me great until on Election night ended up coming inside of
Comet Pizza and ping pong
So we should just stop there for a second and really make clear that he is
Is not a journalist
The functionary
Yes he is a political off
Never been
Journalism
Yeah you know how Fox News
Basically it already
Not too sure
Anyway biggest Trends on Twitter has been the whole piece
There's a lot of weird activity going on here
Yahoo actually went to Comet Ping Pong
On the ground temporarily
Research
Just towards the end of the campaign as Citizens for Trump we're working very hard to get
So I haven't really paid much attention to it
So he is already laid out
Gear his groundwork he was
Actively working
To get a particular candidate
Like a journalist
What's this
Controversy
It's sprung out of
The illegal leaks
The opposite
Gmail
Brett journalist and really didn't really pay much attention to
There's also not true
He goes on
They
In this next clip
Discusses
A little bit about
Decision
To go
City have in it
Inner battle
Who's a hero story
Okay
Hero's journey concert Tampa.
Can I pull the sword
He doesn't know
Sit down
Order dinner
And see what happens
Kind of a strange reaction
I mean humans have a 6S there's a reason why certain environment make
Hair stand up on the back of our necks there's a reason why we get butterflies I feel
You would kind of sent it you sent the weirdness of the place
When you walked in and then
No I can feel some
It just got a little bit colder
That game is not your journey
Can feel pedophile
Energy
Pizzagate
I remember
Amber
Walter Cronkite would get on TV
I got to be honest I got no facts but this story
Good evening
Edward arm
Want to let you know that
McCarthy
Give me some bad by
Every time I get near
The hair raises on the back of my neck
Prosecute a lot of people illegally for actually have
Let's black
Hollywood
Lucas music
How kind of the staff are treated you
CarMax
So big
That's just my name and
Super Bowl 55
Who is there
This is your table this is going to be
Characterizing
You welcome
Pedophile
And I know all
That's what gives us so I want to be clear I have not cut out
Anyting
From the time that
Cookies in Comet Ping Pong
He doesn't thrown out him and his friend
Standing outside talking about how they might
We're going to be the next victim
There they might be high
They might be f****** Stone
Yeah so here is
Him going
Inside,
If it sounds like it matches up at all
With us
The food
See if it is
Here we got scientific rate
How do you even get in this place
Menu
What's on the menu
We work in DC if we want we want pizza
Does that here for
Sounds like Jungle Book
Ono Ono
American Pawn or not
Are the sickness into the back now
Play more sleepy
In history and
He does one of the first things that tip
Them off I'm certain that he's not on the level
And that is narrating their walking us to the back
Spigen walking into a flower he has his dances periscoping
Phone in his shirt pocket walking around with it
Nothing creepy
Tons of families
Signs of people eating dinner
It's a cool looking
Being like restaurant bar
There's nothing
He claims that like all we got footage of all these
Creepy pictures
Nothing anyway
They were not
Any would you like
Near the peak
The first dance
Pictures of him
Incredibly mischaracterizing
I am human
Mario Pizza
I would like to
So he goes on in his interview
With our man
Owen Shroyer
To talk a little bit about the various games that they have
We are going into the back room
In the Navy end
So here
You spend the goalie
3 *
So that's
Characterization
What happened with the foosball
Now I have the all the audio of that
Here is what happened with the foosball
I know I don't know
I don't know
It's crazy
Close attention to the end of it
Cuz the lady very clearly explained
Why she was a little bit
Anime
Is it foosball to do we have to
Footballguys
Football football
So you got that there
I don't know
Server but at the same time she doesn't know
And her reason for not knowing is she
He just started
I don't know
Suspicious if you don't know what
I don't think it is
You guys got bumper pool
You guys are pretty.
Again Emco
Wheatley taking out contacts
What happened
But the Foosball fun
It's not done
We have two more clips about foosball
How
Because be this much about
Because it really illustrates how weird
Like he's not acting like a normal customer
Listen to this
Pacing and leading
Do you say that out loud
Basically
We're just normal guys who want to play foosball
Looks like an idiot
Go to work
Eventually the person
Resume
Doppler radar
In the video
But someone comes over and bring him
Ball
And it also has berries
Suspicious
I thought you said he was just normal things
So that's how you know
Immediately is not interested
Foosball wants the ball shows up
I see you've come
Confirmed my suspicions
Okay great
Case proven
So he goes on
Centerview
See what else he's got with him
Is hurting people going back and forth
Oh no no no
Door opens
Play Sam I in right now and unique
Bathroom door
Evil says that there's like a backroom
No no no come over here to use the bathroom
That's where the f****** bathroom is
Right but he also
Come over here to behind the bar
To use the bathroom
We have a
Before that he was saying if there's kids
Stanford
This curtained area and zip
In the area
It's not in
This is
There is a backroom
There is because every
F****** business as a backroom
Every single one there's a kitchen there might be
So what's your cleaning supplies
What's fun about what you see in the Periscope is that he shows the back
Door
The ventricles of the backroom Minis
Stafford
Don't say anything you can't really see if it's too far away
There are not kids scampering around
Why
Creepiness of it
But there's also
No one back there playing ping pong
It's all empty
No one tells him not to go back there
Thursday
The end of the last Clipper blade
Here's the bathroom
Underground brother a little creepy
Got a little creepy
Adore cool bar
Of course you'd want to have something
Interesting and unique in your bar
So beat goes on to
To tell the the rest
Little bit more of his
To Owen Shroyer
His time
Narrated for you
To Washington d.c.
And says you need to leave The Establishment I am denying you service
So before we get any further
I want
To play this
I think it's important
This
Confirm
Projector sobiech did in fact order at
The hottie with the pepperoni and jalapeno
So he did
Thank you
As far as I can tell everything else is alive
Did order I got
I like to be more fair than not fair and in this case
Brightright on
Right on with that order
So he tells the story when he's on
I think that
I mean
Obvious
He ordered the garlic
He's part of
Code
Absolutely
Garlic Knot
Thinking at this point like what do you think
You heard
Describe what
What's the story
Well we do know that he
That's true
Have to give him the benefit of the doubt
Yeah
Bob Barker
Give me $1
So
Is sitting at a table with his friend
And he start you started
He's starting to crack under the Spy pressure
He's on the phone
The guy was talking to you before
Tobacco please
Bulshit little child
It's a good one
This is it
It's actually in the army
Yeah
Apparently
Apparently our armies
I am not a confident of every type of support this really f***** up is like these kind of
Louis beastars
I have been incredibly effect
In terms of making him a celebrity
Important
In the alt right
He is a prominent figure in alt-right Media
Women
Already 14in right now or not at a pizza place freaking out that we've been burned
Okay that's true
We have not been burned yet
Jackie
Decided that he's burnt
You know I love I love that he's like we've been burned and then immediately
Normal order psycho
Shall we only have Pepsi
She probably heard him say we've been burned
At this point they've already behaved
Super weird
Misplace
Like to the point where I used to manage a movie
If someone was acting like this in my theater
I would
Either ignore them
Or I would throw them the f***
Yeah it depends on the circle
From stances
Let's say in a movie theater that was
Center of
Spurious roofers
Satanic
Pedophilic murder
Periscope and narrating
Yeah I picked at the reasonable thing to do
More obviously have negative intent than if they were like
Two kids
Standing on top of each other
Fake 2-Step
Decided decided I don't know what is
Friends
Call Mater
He's been burned
By of nothing
I got that out
The manager and two DC cops
Say I am denying you service
No thank you
So this is getting an in-depth Pizza recommendation after we've been burned with a barn
The guy comes over there the waiter comes over and he's like even goats
My favorite use of spinach
Yeah really popular pizza
Yeah it's really not my favorite Yusuf
I want a special report
Favorite uses
That's the waiters
Is discussing the pizza that's very popular
Anyway
The waiters
Doing his job
Is being very friendly and helpful
There's a lot of
Is that like
Really in-depth
You get what are you like
Land
Alright that's 10 evil
So far
Yeah
Breathe
Ben
Shown
Through his Twitter account
If you go look through jacket so big
Interested Russia
Seems to have a lot of interest in reporting Russian Embassy news
There's been a number of times
That's because
Recorded things
Things that are not very important
Russian Embassy
He has reported from
They're just
I'm not saying everything
I'm just saying
I do know what you say
It's weird
And if you want to get worse vibes
Here
Again
Haven't been kicked out yet
Human friends get a drink
And this is how they cheers
Unusual
I've said it
I have actually thought my company you haven't cuz I would have called you a goddamn red
God dammit McCarthy
It's not it's
Nothing in this whole thing is it's nothing but in the context
It's interesting
Chase Bank
Yeah I agree with that
But I leave it in really more to illustrate the fact that
Pizza recommendation
They've ordered a garlic knife
They've all gotten drink and are choosing each other having a drink
And they're also I should say
He's picking up the
The camera and like
Moving it around
Clearly brought
Anybody who was watching him would know what he
He's doing he's not being discreet the camera is out of his pocket
If either sitting on the table with a light
So he can be seen
Darken, on him
It's
So then
Here he is turned off
The
Is a very bad
Totally
Please turn off the recording
And then it comes back on
With that
It starts up really quick so pay attention
I turned it off
Understand
But considering that I myself and my staff receive death threats
Not anything I can't control what somebody post
Funny internet internet UPS
Calculator
Because you're you are okay you're eating a dangerous desire
Hi diet turn it off
Alright we're going to find out what's going on also
Can I get that car laptop to go
Did you want to talk to me okay
So
I mean I want to take them out
It's not a bad thing to say.
Thrown out the manager
Me and my staff
Have been getting death threats
Do the game
Play Denver
But that's what the manager comes back with his
Are you reading the things that people are saying online
You're feeding into it
And your childish game of
The members not having any of that b******* because you are
That's the little brother like
Grow the f******
Is version of Journey
He gets kicked out and his buddy go out in the sky
I cut all this s*** out.
Cuz it's all just like
Oh my God
At this point
It's clear
More f***** up
Then he was
Yeah like I don't
I don't know what was going on but
Some sort of substance
I think it was probably
But anyway
We've never heard
Is really poor
Yeah the entirety of his time in common
Talk to himself
And narrate his time there
We've heard him make a big
Deal out of the Foosball table and then wrecked someone brings him the ball
Completely
We've Illustrated
By having a bright light on himself
Filming around the place
While he waits for food
He's giving a Russian
Here's what you don't think it's a big deal but I'm going to
Hang my hat on
Interview with
Made them want to deny you service
Absolutely
Streaming from inside here
He didn't
Aggravating
Yeah.
Dinner at Thomas Pizza
I didn't say you know.
Pizza
Lots of people take pictures and put it on Snapchat Instagram that sorta thing
And there's a lot of people around me with smartphones but for some reason
What type of weird pictures
Up just final question on your experience there before I move on to the next topic
Did you see any of that weird artwork
You see this weird sort of demonic artwork on the van just to the inside of the front door
Cross between a zombie
Recently
So there's a possibility they may have actually taken some of those
What
Pizzagate it has been trending on Twitter certainly some weird stuff there we'll see if that Trend continued
The weirdness that are reporting on and breaking on social media
The most
Suspicious
Pizzagate
He's taking pictures down
If
Picture elf
Episode Vehicles any kind of reporter he would have looked on the ground next to where the Pixar should have been
Preparation of the Rapaport group portal
#brother portal
I remember when I was a kid right around Christmas
Watch out for that Rapport Elf on the Shelf right there you got to leave your wooden shoes out yet
Like okay
Be careful you'll get a lump
We got nothing
Because nothing but you does feel go on Infowars and do this interview
In order to cast aspersions
And insinuate all this stuff
Truly
F******
Propaganda
Surely like he's not know that they're lying
And the fact that
Owen charges goes along with
Of course
Percent know they're lying
They don't care
I don't think first of all I don't think Owen
Redeem
The periscope
Is long and boring
Adidas
Just going along with it and like assuming the
So big is a reliable source
Maybe Sylvia Kenosha
He's lying he knows
But he lucked into
This outright Fame
Who gives a s***
Reality is malleable it's like
Milo used to always argue where to post fact
World
Doesn't matter
Yeah but that's
Real bad
White
Seems like
Is Justin
AMC in your narrative
But seeing people believe your narrative
I think there's a trolling aspect of it they would never Cop 2
Addiction
Because I think
Whenever you get a like
Quran Twitter
Same kind of dope
Influx
All of this attention maybe they are just really gay
Getting off on
Did yeah they're just doing whatever they can to get more
More like sand
To get more
More people giving them this dope
Could be like a propaganda version of like this new
Internet addiction
We've experienced
The possible
Series as good as anything
There's no possible reason
Send that
Cuz I can't
Believe it
Denny's dark moments he knows he's a liar
There's no doubt
Tons of videos of him
Like dozen
Really give a s*** that his whole existence is kind of based on
I don't really care he doesn't really care that he's a liar he's making money
Washington
The rebel media
I don't know if this is
He has White House credentials
Okay I don't know what you have
Supposed to get in there
You could you can get day credential
You have like
Across-the-board credential
Mike cernovich was there for a day
My point is
But people like this we have no regard for the
Just one
Insinuating
You can't prove you don't know
It doesn't matter he's never going to
To GameStop
It just makes him more
In the White House
He goes to the White
I don't not anymore
I want to pee on some
I do too
Meaningless
The Congress if it was worth a s*** it would have already
Everything
Investigate all this s***
The investigation
Every pop
Possible turn
What is tax.
Why won't
I think it's actually cheaper than that
You heard it here first
Bingo
Why are balls off and that way wouldn't even f****** matter
Yeah
Standard when the world is
Because what does it benefit a man to gain the world if he loses it
Sole Jordan
And everyone we talked about
Except
Encapsulate that last
But he had with Owen
That last
Legitimately
All the stuff you like everyone was creepy there
I saw the Periscope we heard them they were just
Free People
They didn't know what foosball was
The girls started three days ago
I don't care that she didn't know what foosball is
Very belief
That's not it that's nothing at all
They treated you weird
Exactly
Asian kid scampering around behind curtains
So
Where we come to at the end is the only thing that is maybe defense
And you can't tell from the periscope
Cuz it's shot terribly
And it's dark
But there's a possibility that there's weird art
Right
Like a lot of cool places right now I want to say first
Who gives a s***
What's second
If that's the only way
Real thing in your argument
You are the most
PC fukka
Pile of s***
In the world
If your argument that you can hang your hat on
Against this pizza place
Okay
This weirdo okay
Oh really I mean that that is really what's going on Ark
Definition of weird art
Satanic
Play Store
Kiss with seitan
Satanic
Let me know
I feel personally
All you really need to know about Jackie
Yeah pretty much
In the middle of the pizzagate
Controversy
Quotes
He went
That's two,
Pong made a very misleading
Periscope video about it
Parlayed it into an interview on
Infowars
Work he lied about it since a tional e
In order to make it appear that
Really creepy things happen there wasn't when they didn't
His own source material doesn't backup his reporting
Either shity journalist
Is propaganda
Why we need to be afraid of
Character that comes up at again
Because because like I said he's going to come up again
He clearly has some sort of
Connection
The
The Nationalist
Movement that's going on otherwise he would not have had pre Advanced knowledge
Bleach
His own video
Complete opposition to what it is easier
Bother
Did you hide your tracks
Why are we losing you know why
You know why it's because it's what we keep coming back to the battle of the second step
And they always will win
No one looks into
The shorter episode today
Du-du-du price
Well yeah I mean
I can't I couldn't
I couldn't get it together
But will be back
If I was going to take
Automation
It would be that
There is
Absolutely
Like they
They just
Complete and utter
They have no they don't care who they
They don't care about anything but
Themselves
They don't care about each other they just want to get as much as
That's fake
Even in that Alex Jones profile whenever they're talking about
The interviews from other
It's just a
Medium to sell pimple
Article about Alex Jones
Talk about the service Financial
In his
His business
It's really interesting because basically they're just laying out s*** that we laid out in one of our first episode
We scooped the New York Magazine buy like four months
Really interesting because
Beer batter
Well they aren't they on cupboard that it doesn't cost anything for people to
Play Alex
Does Travis pacificator show
Like I told uncovering.
Your number one Alex Jones information source
Knowledge
We are just the real uncut
We should get
We should get energy
Being a lot more
Totally
Hit us up New York mag
Anyway
Guys if you want to email us
New York Magazine
Look at gmail.com
If you want to follow us on Twitter
Or if you want to send me a DM
Hit me up if you want to download the podcast
Can do that
Yep you can share it on all kinds of different social media platform
Would like to become a donate button on a website
Support
You become a policy wonk
Or request
Time travel episode
Which
Alex continues to be
Disoriented and
Frankly
I think you described
Boring right now
Keep doing somebody
Episode
Oh yeah
Also my mom just emailed me an article from the Austin State
Austin Chronicle and apparently
His ex-wife
Alex Jones ex-wife
As I press conference said I will come on your show and talk about our
What on Alex Jones a joke
No way
Yeah
Please
You know how the people around you you can't
Really around them right
Secure cuz they know
That was underneath
Rite Aid him in his intimate
Right knows who he is he can't pull that character
Her s*** on him
Should be able to call it out there's no way
The show
Michelle
F****** come on our show will absolutely
You're on a nymph
Yeah well you're an honorary policy wonk
I'm sorry that the world is the way it is
Survival
Get a bunch of water and canned food people it's time
See the world
Can still see the world
Easter Island
If you donate $1000000 or more for our papers
Sorry
We will move to Easter Island in
Continue doing this bike
From the relative safety of giant
Old Lady Who Lived in a Shoe
Alright
Yes
Absolutely
For everybody has donated
Your policy one
Because we
Couple of policy
Alex