Damn important sweat it
I have great respect for knowledge by now I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Stripe.com
Everybody looking technology
Jordan damn you're doing that like the finally those Rock
Podcast
Little bit of a
Subtle Jab
You know what a lot of people say to me Jordan
You don't scream enough
Consistently that's the review I guess
Dear. Have you ever been
Sure of what
Somebody looked
Just by their voice
And then saw them in real life and when
No idea.
No clue that that could possibly be
Yeah I mean like I think the standard one is like radio people
Loving
I talk radio and when I was much younger thee like y107
Personalities are like the morning show
It's like we had it
Liquor in
Turning thing
Dang it my junior high or middle school
You go when you find someplace and you do a day of turning and I love radio so I wanted to go to the
And so I went
And not only did I learn
Nothing like what I thought their voices look like
And not in a terrible
Most of them were way more attractive
Then I imagine
Yeah I don't know that was the image of head of my head but I thought they hide behind a bike because it's something
You never see pictures of a lot of these right people I like plastered all up all over the Play Store
On the radio aren't too big celebrities butts
And the other thing that I learned was that like
There were at least
A couple of them
That were multiple differ
Different people on different radio shows
Oh yeah
Like
I don't even remember what their names to be but they're like I'm icon The Morning Show and then they do an afternoon shell
Voice in a slightly different
I'd like my world shattered
No
That's a look behind the curtain moment there
Cuz I remember like my parents had to pick
Pick me up but like
I remember them telling me
As a guy who really loved radio and wanted to
Don't do this
All the sudden their real voices they just like
Today got a kill you I'll eat you up alive
Like this is
The future of what
I think
Those before allotted the
Play Jack FM
Type stuff works ship those
Things are coming Grandpa
In the field you probably
Had some
The sense that this is what was going to call the evolving Market of radio disappearing and then also
It doesn't pay well it kind of sucks
I don't imagine many more hours to work in the
Newspaper in this
History that's it's probably not good advice these
I don't know it any hours
You know if you got to be up real early
For newspaper a like morning shows
You don't want it going to be up at 3
Fu comedian 2
Babe do the morning radio thing
I wake up at
3 every morning in your leg you should
Stop that's not a bad schedule if you can get used to it and if your life allows it but I find it very
Very difficult to adjust to it
Either you stay up
I got to learn more about Gary Allan
Like this do I
Overnight
Radio show about
Weirdo Communists nonsense
Love you guys because Robert Evans friend finally saw a picture of him
You put that picture up of a owen Shroyer
Yeah and I have never I've never seen Owen Shroyer
No more I never looked him up I did the whole point of the show is don't look at it
That's really weird cuz you talk to Adam for a long time
Completely different than what I expected
He's a weirdo
Yeah baby
What is a guy with a
Beard
Nonexistent
Or trim down mustache
Disgusted look for a little while
I'm not proud I wouldn't go back to
But now
I think I will but hey I have been denied
Heritage
They felt like I was honoring it through my
Shaving the mustache
Of course I'm also part lumberjack
Backside the chop stash in a little while done it all
In the facial hair games Lumberjack meeting you worked as a lumberjack part-time I assume
No I just have a beer
Alterations by Caspar I know a bit about learning that people on the radio look different than you think
About what you do
Expecting
Something episode that I'm going to call
Grab bag mini soap
We do not have a full episode
Here but we're going to do is we're going to put out of this sort of scattered
There's a there's a couple of interesting things that are worth touching on
And then on Friday will be back with a full regular episode
Covering one
And it's going to be interesting to figure out what that will be because Alex is still on the East Coast
He went to the rally in Virginia on Monday in Richmond
And then now he's in DC because the impeachment hearing it started
Like I can't do it without him
Well I thought that he was going to be doing his show from DC that would make
Have to do he's not in the hearings right
Just be live doing his show in a hotel room in d.c.
Jerome corsi was supposed to be setting something up there I think you took the right to not workout
There is no Bureau in in d.c.
He could easily be doing
Something Wild
Abdul is up there with him he could be watching the impeachment hearings anything that's important you can come in
Scribbled on a piece of paper like easy we figured out our issues so much harder than the
Very simple
It's been hosting because he had a heart attack
No flying is out of the question
Travel
He's a steady hand to Alex's got him in studio
Jhonni Blaze
If it if it comes down to it then like
You get there won't be an episode with Alex
Really except for butting into do like little
Truth is rising
I halfway expect him to start to try to false-flag some
This is that if you guys won't do it I'll do it myself god dad
I'm really bored
Yes I do I don't know what to Friday's episode of B but we will get back with
I'm so anyway
I have I have a few things to go over here today
I have to miss
Free things
I have
A little bit of it before and after of the Virginia
Icon second mammogram
Make sure I also have a weird ass
Did Alex
Put out
I love it
Vets really upset
On a number of levels
Before we do Jordan got to take Mama to say thank you
Pittsburgh Zoo signed up and
For the show love it
So first Mason thank you so much you are now a policy wonk wonk
Timothy thank you so much
Journal policy wonk
Text Makayla thank you so much you and I'll probably walk
Next time Eric
Thank you so much you are now a policy wonk
Thank you I'm Eric are you the one
Text Jessie with an i
You by Jesse with just one eye and no email without the eyes
Sir Geoffrey thank you so much
Next Chad
Journal policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Tony Hawk 2
No I did not play with roller skater Chad Muska
I don't think that this
Lame yeah I know I know I know
Get a rap album
Supporting this line of Sean had a rat album
But I know
Conscience
Always got a whole flight of stairs
Like Rune glifberg that's not even name
No it's not
Phillipsburg
Glitzburgh
Prune like a Nordic rune and hieroglyphic
Anger is a speedo
Alright
Andrew Reynolds
Triple kickflip
Play too much alike that alright
Anyway thank you Chad
Signed up on an elevated level appreciate that very much so Steven thank you so much
You are now a technocrat
Thank you so much
You and I will check
We got to go
What's the business
Heroin
Freakishly large
Thank you so much
Yes figure
Website.com
The sports show we would appreciate it be very helpful
So where we're going to start here today Jordan is we are going to be looking at the before and after of the Virginia
Second
An amendment rally
We're on the other side of it recording is on Tuesday we know that the Civil War
Did not start
Alex's
I don't know what you would call infirm that with an outside media source
Eventually but
So on the 8th
18th of January over the week
Alex put out a little bit of a emergency message
It's this is before the Wrath
This is the sort of Tanner
But Alex is really bringing
And I know that we talked a bit about his coverage on
The show already on a Monday episode but I think it's still worthwhile to check
A little bit about this
Because I think there's something that's really important
You can see
In the aftermath
In the responses
Cuz of how people behave so here is the beginning of this from January 18th
We have cracked the code we understand the glove was false flag operation plan for next week
Y'all wonder why did Pelosi
Rush impeachment then hold it back for almost a month
They were liable under that Martin Luther King Day
Yearly gun marches happen for 20 years
In Virginia at the Kappa
They're planning stage mass shootings bombing or false Flags
The American people against gun owners and President Trump
The pre-programming is a
Thousand percent clear
It is
Absolutely imperative it everyone understands that the globalist
Are losing their fight against America The Awakening is huge and they are betting everything on planning from
Supporters are white supremacist pro-gun and who are going to come kill law enforcement
Pretty clear I mean if you have a situation where Alex is
Predicting that there's going to be bombings and mass shootings
And
Dupree scripting is 1,000
Preside clear
And it turns out that
His predictions are not true
It has to make you
Bring into your mind the possibility that hey maybe you don't know how to read
Espree scripting s***
Or maybe you're just making that stuff up
That's possible I mean some people do you know when they're shooting movie some people
Do you have same-day rewrite
You know they did better
The script on the scene
Comics to come in to do punch up
Although I like it
I don't know if that's what they're doing
But
So Alex has this very clear this is the prediction that is what is going
Any tells people Hitman
Brinkoetter
If you want
Brent Gunn
The rally hate but
That's not the most important
Bring your gun
I'm totally for the Second Amendment I've done open carry marches all over the United States
We really need
If people with cameras watching the leftist
Antifa in that weirdo that they've gotten drugged up at some Hotel like a Southern Poverty Law Center has done before
Who they're going to use as their passing
Because this is one that dictates going to make their move
The planets have aligned
The trial starts the day after this in Virginia
And on every channel they say the right-wing Terror attacks are coming the cops are all going to get killed
Because they always pre-program before
They stayed something
All over the news they weren't saying that that's what Alex
Turd
Because he thinks
He can read secret messages
In the news in the same way Steve
Mechanic thinks the newspaper is communicating directly to him
That is how these
Folks like Alex and Steve work out there like all this
What's going on
I know the secret codes of the universe entirely acceptable thing for people with a massive flat
Form to act as though the T
TV and the newspapers are
Talking directly to them right that makes perfect sense and interpreting secret messages that are directed towards them
That is behavior that we encourage in all
Now it's interesting that's like
They can take some different shapes
Like this
With Steve he literally does think of the newspaper is sending him message
I think he doesn't even leave that the security Community is speaking directly to him and that's how he stays in
In contact with the security Community he has implied
Things
Is very very close to that prosticks that he thinks he's getting from the
Six or word search okay. The jumbled is like oh my God call swag coming
I'm not sure exactly
At the mechanics
Sudoku I'm going to blame that he's been pretty clear that what he believes is that there is like direct messages to him
Through whether it's
Like specific Riders
Newspapers or
Or whatever
Alex
On the other hand seems to think
That the band The globalist yes
Need to get these coded
Messages after all of their people
Right and what have you and he's able to read their language
And that's why he's able to deduce all of the stuff there
And that's just ludicrous
Very much
Also like
He's clearly saying that
According to him what he believed
Is it there he's already someone drugged up in a hotel room
Morris Dees
Individually keeping under house arrest ready to launch out
I'm in same day you got a book that trip in advance they had to get a good hotel rate
The globalists are Thrift
See if anything else
Right right program they've got rewards points that they're using to false
Hey. My My Name a little wrong there
Yeah I I just I think this is
I mean the word of the day for that is
Is Justin Sation
It's ludicrous
And now the narrative has
Become
But this is all I mean
But the owner lifesteps
On his
Is on Broadway
Vance
Largely to do with Trump
Impeachment
Like all of this
Of course they want to race war
That's really also about
The mostly about getting Trump
What what you can't do two things at the same time
Blazing gentlemen
They're going to make their moves I've been saying for months during the Trump Trauma Center I told you
They have no evidence
Because they don't want Trump to take it serious my gut is always right
They want them to take it as a
The jokes and be ready for one defense
Abuse of power by the president
Blocking Congress of trucks
Congress
But what they're really going to be doing is using the trial as a way to have him under judgment
While they cause race riots Federal Building
The reason Alex has been saying that Vermont
Is that I think he has a key
Keen sense
The Trump being impeached
Might
Triggered
Some sort of a right-wing reaction
Manifest itself
Extremist violence
Any of those I mean he had all sorts of people from across the right-wing talking about there will be War
You see it across
Cancel wide spectrum of right-wing sources it's not unique
Alex the show but its rhetoric that certainly has been on his show
So it serves his interests
In terms of this pre-emptive narrative building
To associate
Like this is after this clip is after arrest for
Prior to that he's saying that this is going
Virginia rally is where things are going to pop off
But it's also about the truck that they put
Evening pietschmann
Impeached him right in order to have him there
In the state of judgement
Yes so then they
Could set off all of these race Wars and bombing Federal Building sure make Trump look naughty
That's what that's their goal
Alright I think that's I think that's
Counterproductive stupid
Any of these words work
If you look at it through the correct prism of how he
He operates from a propaganda rhetoric standpoint
What he's doing is
Creating a just
Suffocation preemptively
In case as the impeachment does go along
Let's say somebody blows something up yeah
Now you're like of course of course they're just doing that 12
All I told you I told you
Right absolute
All
It works this way
Court how he operates
So
You know we got already suggestion that
There's a guy
In hotel room
Course of the globalists and the splc and
Morris Dees
Alright
Are you getting ready
Say which hotel
Did they put them up in a nice place a really good letter
I would
He's drugged up though so you don't hear nobody knows
This is not spelled out bios
But he does talk a little more about
Besoros funded by the crate that class to say that one poor woman dying was Trump's fault
Babe.
Make this move
Screw the pooch with the attack
With what happened with Pelosi with other making sense unless they've got something big
I'm saying they're going to wash everything they've got in the next 3 or 4 days and
People need to be aware of it. Fueled up in my view message
Mentally ill white supremacy in hotel rooms right now they're telling me it's the second coming of Jesus you are the Lord
Have some more drugs and go out and kill a bunch of cops and that's why everybody said it's got to be on a swivel
So what Alex is doing their is making it so even if
Character is
Sickly and according to all available information
Someone who does
Commit one of these terrorist attacks
Look according to
To everything available
Dead to rights
There a right-wing meth head white supremacist
They were being coached by the
Now admittedly all of them
That stuff that he described them as being coached to say is stuff that he himself has said multiple
Right
Something people do then say
It's okay to kill cops if they try to take your gun
This is the way you will knock your late your audience from believing
Any of this stuff is real even if
All available evidence
Indicates that it is real
If somebody he's running
Very clear explicit interference for right-wing
Domestic terrorism
Answer you have been
Particularly with his discussion of the the Texas
Domestic terrorism threat assessment
That's
That's the that's the name of the game
And it's very clear
If anybody asks on what I said clearly
Verilife
And they were coached by the globalist
Because wouldn't that be perfect
If I were them it's telling you to do that
What so this was recorded and put out on the 18th
So you said they're going to do it within the three or four days is not the evening of the 21st
Recording
Have a gun
No are you sure I get that confirmed
Deadline isn't going
To be up until you know this episode will be out so I guess we'll have to wait until Friday will everyone know for sure
So far prediction not looking good
Pirelli
Not great
He's got he's always 100% right though
Bright
Because he breeds
The Prieto
Victorville
Television talking to it
I can't imagine him actually knowing how to read in the first place
Let alone a secondary level of reading that goes
I think that the secondary level is required because the primary wanted
As week
I suspect that that's how he
He gets by
So in this last clip
From his
Emergency warning
Alex
Gives himself
A way out
Will they be able to pull it off I pray and hope not
They're not fully right now
They're badly organized
Are you talking about you
But the false flag
Governor Northam has already launched a civil war or white supremacist when he's the one wearing KKK outfits
And they're going to make their move their the media's going to make their move there
The day before the trial begins to make it all about that pressure on the Senate to remove the
President so I mean you can just kind of threw out that three to four days prediction he said it's going to happen
$100
That was always right
But the globalist also might
Be too weak to pull this off you never know but I just said that
Infinite is a organization that has existed since the dawn of human history of
Apparently they're very poorly
Still working at
Governor Northam didn't say this is going to be a civil war
Are white supremacists terrorists
Already
Initiate the false flag
No
So as we're on the other side of this recording
What's on the 21st we know that there was not
Civil war that broke out
Call Alex
It's very queer like in that warning message that like that they're going to make their move
He's very he's repeatedly talkin about
Them having a drugged-up of meth head or whatever Jean people
And it's extreme
It's it's
Nonsensical
Sensationalism so now on the other side
Let's go check out Paul Joseph Watson Twitter
What's this tweet here from the 20th
Other media fear-mongering about the Virginia rally as that just
Did four weeks before the Joker came out
Same result nothing happened it was all alarms to stereo
No history on this
Dang that's a bummer
I seriously believe that some people in the media and on the left are disappointed the Virginia rally went off peacefully
Strongly disagree yeah I'm going to go with
What's this
Paul Joseph Watson article from
The 20th
The same day is this
Here's a headline for you quote
Conservative activist
Queens antifa is planning to Stage violence in Virginia and blame it on procon protester rights right so the fee
Fear-mongering in the media.
Include health
Conservative author and activist Tom DeWeese
Claims he has received credible information suggesting antifa members of planning stage violin
Virginia later today
On pro gun
One protester
Those media figures stoking a fear monger
Yeah that's awful
Ryan based on a tweet here
Tom DeWeese
I'm in Richmond and I've just received information from a very reliable source concerning Monday's rally against the legislators gun grab
Antifa rented seven buses to bring in their Thugs and cause trouble
The report says they will be wearing Maga hat swearing-in are agar
They'll pretend to be pro-gun people
Meanwhile others posing as Democrats holding anti-gun signs will stand on the side
The antifa thugs pretend
I need to be pro-gun will attack the sign holders okay making it look like a pro-gun people have started violence
This is the plan okay
You know when you're making a
Complete and total bullsh
Do you like the use of the number 7
I think that's a great number that grabs your attention
7 bus
Bright
So I mean
You know you see the game here
Anyway Alex gets back into Studio
Actually doesn't
You just recorded something and it
Advance
Play at the beginning of the show on the 21st
And he seems to be taking
Credit for the fact that the Civil War
Is the fact that won the publishers
We just saw in Virginia
People
Stopped
Stampede
Your prayers have eyes action
But yeah
It shows we got to have action on the ground
There's a strange phenomenon the more viewers and more traffic we have the Infowars
Video
Money we have coming in out of a bunch of big sales just ended
We have crippling low amounts of money coming in right now
We need to keep him for supper for just the next year that we're delivering
Square.com
American
That translates to I think I've probably milked my dedicated audio
Some lucky loser are checking in to see what the f*** I'm yelling about
Is not a sustainable way
Just go I do like the cash crunch don't bring your whole team to Washington DC for a week
Like weird attempted a public spectacle
That is my advice don't behave that way if that's
The truth as a an immature financial advisor
Right
So Alex's you know his angle on it is this a you know a we stopped a false-flag when we all come out and
Moraware
This is how he's able to have it coming and going you can see if Bo demonstration of how this goes
Wait people into a frenzy
Something bad happened
You predicted it
Nothing bad happens we we
And that is I do like him not only taking credit
For stopping
Any violent but also using that as a sales pitch
Like totally
How are we going to stop
More violent unless
You buy stuff from Infowars
Soda
So that is kind of a tale of the tape
There and I think
I know that we covered a lot of that on Monday earliest the like sort of the lead-up
And how he was behaving
Before the rally
But I think it's
I think it is worthwhile to take a look at like this is me before and after that
The Bread is made this is how this whole
World of bulshit operate
And it'll
Ensures itself
Non invalidation with the eyes of people who have bought in
So
I want to take us now to this ad
Did I write that I found
John the 17th
Alex
Pre-recorded
Is that message we played on the last episode about how you don't need to feel white gillibrand then
Jimi Hendrix are not races weird please buy stuff weird weird pre-recorded at
Ben Paul Joseph Watson
Took over and saw lighter
Turned off
It turns out that there was another ad
Another pre-recorded thing
In the second hour
That
I thought it was
Super Bazaar
We're going to listen to a little bit of that here
It starts with Alex disorder
You know cuz he's still before the rally at this point
He's talking about the how it's going to be a false flag
We're going to be there all next week
Bring It live
The federal holiday
Ruby
And Virginia
Thirtysomething
Virginia
For the laugh
Is openly trying to
Cause martial law and tried to
But all this insane garbage
This is America
Reply
The football game where bicep going to head in the third quarter one
I made it.
Easier
Addison the football game versus the Hulk
Humanity
Being fought out in America
Weather right now
The future of humanity
Rest
Like the difference
Between good and bad is
Alex
Stopping
False flag
Obvious
I don't understand why you play games like this like when you rent relief
How do you escalate
Like where do you go next
Future of the world right
Alex save the world on Monday I mean you got to go galaxy neck
I think that's the only way to go he's actually going to be a man in Black
I could go talk to Carrie he's agent Jerry
Sure
I don't know anyway that's not the main point of this little piece
This we get to that here
Navigate to Ramona
Let me just do this up front again
Tenda plug
At the end of things and do it like
Apologizing
This dog
Doesn't he
This dog doesn't win
Unless you buy the
Like seeing some old boreas
Happier
Been a pig
You know what
When I take
X 2 x 3
When I take the
Confusion
I can't wait
3 months now
I can't work for me
Organic
What
Attached
ABS again
You know their test
$10 stuff
Find something
That's just about how a couple years back BuzzFeed did a piece worth
Egyptian God stop saying that always happen
Indicates to me is that like he's working with bad suppliers or
There's something because it shouldn't take you a quarter of a year
To actually get something to pass a test
This product
The everyone loves has been sold out for
Quarter
Yeah a full quarter unfortunately
Yeah I was going to say the only way that
Show me why they can take 4 months
To test something is if it takes
Three-and-a-half months
23 and a half months filled with failed that
I assume that has to be what it is the restock
I mean I think that might be more likely
I don't know what it is I don't know what the reality is behind it but
Like what he's Express
Can't possibly be okay
You can't have
If it was so hard to pass these standard how is anything organic
Just called Gwyneth Paltrow to use the same s*** borrow some of hers
I don't
This is just bad business whatever it is
I once I once did
A couple of sample ad reads when I was trying to get some voice-over action for a little bit
The great Hustle
I remember reading so many like a husband-and-wife little conversations or like
I don't know where to get my tires done like that kind of stuff I would rather have read one of these address
Incoherent rambling that starts with a
The world are out of stock for four months of his intestines hard
By other things
Christianbook
Voiceover ads included
Sorry you can't buy this
Hey I got bad news
If you want living defense
That's one of Alex's Providence
You also can't buy that
Defense
Fremont
Three months
Are you mad
It two days ago
And I said listen
Supposed to take 12 weeks for this
The order and they said yes
But we
Continue
Adjust
It's not
Everybody else just
Slap the label on thing
This doesn't pass.
Eastandard
A billion
The air
But they like California
Toxic waste Ridin to the water calling at fluoride
There's a waiver for that
Alright buddy
Joan
So
Inelastic comes down to
I don't understand what is going on
What does Alex think that his business would be crippled if there was a warning label on the bottle that says B has laid in it
It would really counter all of his this is the best most
Perfect stuff
That you could ever put inside your body if it
It comes with a warning label say
Not in California
I got yeah I mean I guess if your business model is based on this being the best
To keep up the appearances and keep warning labels off
I meant I think that's
Maybe a limitation of the business model
Again this isn't that this is a voiceover ad read I want like
This is like
Hey get all of your auto needs taken care of at AutoZone except for headlights we can
Get headlight out of a don't work
So Alex is that you sold out on a lot of stuff and they're not doing a good job
Weird
He's also defensive
About
Some of his water filtration
Enter comments
The people have made
About
I am selling water
Yeah member David Hogg said we're bad we tell you the water
Poisonous
But the water tables
Poison
Body that's a revolution some other things and they got more poison into it
I realized after WWII the water was so toxic
Did they put
Fluoride
But that b hundreds of Kim
The mining Industries
Phosphate Industries in
From aluminum industry
So you want regulations
In the water and fat
Was the waiver
Poison in the cover-up
Poison that was already in the war
Huge plugger rant here
You didn't yeah that doesn't make sense
Butts
I should point out the David Hogg
Beto's comments
2 years ago
Yeah yeah
Are cigarettes for two years two years isn't that long
I'd like to remind Ally
Exit his buddy Mike Adams started website called
Hogwash right about attacking a high-schooler survive the school shooting
And David Hawk doesn't seem to
Complain about Mike Adams
All the time
Hulk made a comment
About Alex selling water filters yes still angry about
Is a snowflake
Vines about
And also the problem is not so much that Alex sells water filters
It's that it
Peers
That's some of his behaviors
Inspired by the things he sells
Yeah you know like how he would always yell about others going to be a financial crisis it's going to be the summer of Rage
Buy gold hey that was really that was
Just coincidental it was just so
Helpful you know you're surprised
Is whenever something
Whatever things match so well right
Accident
It's a situation where
Thinking person would have
Grounds
Disrespect
Maybe some of
Your content is
Being led by the things that you sell all right now possible
That there is a connection between
Teen Vogue is heated what are you going to hold him to a higher standard standard
I'm going to hold him to whatever is too I don't know what other
People do I
Show me another people all say it's bad to
I don't know
Teen Vogue had that
Quote sponsored content that had no
Byline that was basically a
Really
Everybody roundly and rightly said fuc
I just listened Alex Jones all the time I can comment on his business
19 pho
So
Alex
This is where we get to like some real high high weirdness okay
He starts talking about how he goes down to seven
Understand
Just don't like the devil in Georgia I want the best right
He starts talking about how big is fish oil pills
We go out to the
Very best
The best
You've ever made
Mega yacht
The product
Private label for a ride
Like no excuse me
You understand
I
Wanted
WeatherTech
He's a great negotiator
Text somebody took my also
Official
When I open one
Eating
Real quick
The way he's
Phrases things is so weird that like where's my bottle official out the one I was eating eating is a strange
I don't like the word needed their what is this special look like
It's a it's like someone who doesn't understand idiom
Everything is a chewable of urim and and these are not chewable
And he finds a new bottle and then pours them out onto the table
Fox Terrier
Please deliver
Is anybody ever seen
Horse pills that big a maybe that's not a good sales tax
Horse pills
They go down okay with some water.
Have you recorded
Have you ever taken fish oil
Subway
Now they're always big
Yeah they are very big capsules
General
All fish oil pills
Cancel
But he seems
Really singularly focused on how big is horse pills are
You can do a sec
This is perfect
Biggest horse pills
They go down okay with some water.
I'll tell you
Clinton's
Oh my God
Classic Sonic
Roll a die.
Horrendous
Look at these baby
Those are big
Here it is
Tallywacker
Family Show
Come on down to AutoZone unfortunately we don't have any headlights obviously we can't get them to pass California
But that reminds me a lot of Bill Clinton getting a blowie
So how about that look how big that piston is over there
Wouldn't be that big dick
What
Apparently AutoZone
This is
Pre-recorded add read
With the Monica Lewinsky joking
I think it's unwise also for Alex to be making Monica Lewinsky jokes
Context of like
Hey there's an impeachment going there is that there is that it kind of calls to mind how trivial the last one was
That might not be in your best interest
I like
You know you want to make fun of Bill Clinton or go ahead all you want
I feel like a specially now
In the present day 2020
It's really shity to still be making Lewinsky joke out of
Whatever
Attack you want to make on the clintons
They took her it took her what
20 years to reclaim her
Reality
You something like that
Look at what he's looking at the pills
These are big
He says
Monica Lewinsky could handle
Lakes at the beginning of it is not attacking Bill relief
A joke about her that is
I bet
Well it's cheap and it's just
I think it's lame
Also these pills aren't that big
I can't
Recipe
Pics of special about these pills is
Not unique
It is
An attribute of every
Single fish oil pill I've ever seen in my life
We are look I'm sorry we're out of the life
Fence that's that's really tough
However take these fish oil pills that I call Lil clintons
Based on a Monica Lewinsky joke that is incredibly
Time Lake again this is a pre-recorded ad
Pre-record
It seems like every point in time they could have been like just stop
It seems like
Has to be because
He's going
To d.c.
And like he's supposed to be there like in a couple hours
Unless he's taking like a helicopter from the Infowars roof
I still don't think you could make it already
It has to be pre-recorded but you also understand
He's not a to take kind of guy
That's true I don't think he's got to get to to the east
That's fair as all these things take got to keep it in
It's like the movie 1917 it's all one big pig
Sure
So it starts complaining
About to drag queen story time
Story Hour
And who cares we don't need to listen to a lot of this but I think he said something
That is absolutely not true
Pedophile drag queen Story Time like 5 years ago
And people is not that big a deal
It's my library
What the hell parachuting in fat dudes
Clown outfit
Okay
So do you think it's fair that Alex has been on this beat 45 years
Probably not
No drag queen Story Time 1 hour
I did the starting 2015 but we've listened
20 20 20 15
Almost all of it
Yeah and I can confidently say
Do not come up
Route and I don't think I remember him being on the beach
I also don't
Think that they are remaking Operation Dumbo Drop with fat
Certainly I don't think that's
No
Nope
Operation it MacLeod
Alex
You know he's rambling a bit it doesn't seem like
It seems like he's lost the
The thread a little bit anyway
Pre-recorded but it gets back to
What not everybody looks like rice.
Most of our
Okay imma stop you know I am I am
The energy level
Planets really up right now
Governor's right now
Cuz you're not there
Is tell you that
I need funding
It's like a missile eats fuel
And I will
Hippie anime
But
You got to have the best hunting dog around like I said stop
But you did
You don't feed it
You don't get more
And you don't need
Flea
Asia's got
He's going to roll over
One more
Quite frankly I'm not
Hot dogs in really great shape
Is that he's getting a little bit too in better shape I think it's largely because he stopped drinking
If you know what hey take that dog that you're talking about and I get it drunk for years
Then take away the booze I bet it'll look better be it'll be better if I just have one
Thing to say which is
Where's knock
How many
Dead dog references going to get on this show that won't even slip by me a little bit
Yeah I don't know
I just seen others just desperation
Like you need to
You need to give money at
Anyway this this next with Alex is going out to break the ends up doing it
At least two segments by kind of lost my
My patience for
It is a Searchlight
What do you eat are you goes out to break
And he's yelling about how the globalist
They really hate
You
Absolutely
You you and Alex
Around the same wavelength if you like freedom
And that's why they're attacking Alex cuz that's the way of attacking you and to take
Freedom
And then
I don't you just is very tough
Energy levels take they just don't
What is a sounding board
If somebody say what
And saying what you're already
Wanting
Good morning the same
Spirit
Liberty
Wood Brothers
Could you be Monica Lewinsky
That's why I'm not going to be Hypocrites I want to make a stupid joke about Bill Clinton I'm going to make it because I'm not a hypocrite
Okay
All right all these ranchers telling you not to make Bill Clinton
That I have been hearing that
From So Many religious
Just figures
Or at the past
Sierra tire light
Non-Stop
My childhood Pastor sent me an email out of the blue. He just said it was Jordan This Is It
Email blast
To whom it may concern I've been noticing a problem in society and that is everyone's making
But too many bill collector joke
That's why the United
Church broke up that's why the United Nations exists.
Alex is so defensive
Look I'm not going to be hip
I'm going to make my Bill Clinton
Credible to me that
By making a Bill Clinton joke he is
Being hypocritical
I don't know if he's being hypocritical and like by issue with it isn't like
Sing he shouldn't
I'm saying that it's lame
Michael
Complaint is more like
This is lame also.
Technically it doesn't seem like it's a great
Joke to make your face tanvi impeachment parallels that may be brought to mind
Buy it but
You're not going to win me over by reminding me of a road hack that I worked with
With two years ago making Monica Lewinsky
That's a very specific memories about I'm not sure many of the people things.
We're going to be at one-nighter
So like I said Alex does a couple seconds
And this he comes back from break
And he is trying to cover
That un video about vaccines
That he's been
Which
Who traces back to Del bigtree in this anti-vax Lobby
We're finally going to get
He Rambles about that a bit and that would starts
Weaving into like him talking about
All of the nurses that he's talked to have told him that they give
Babies shots and then they die and all this
It's all very non-specific I've heard of Dude Ranch about this
All the time over and over again through the years
But I've never heard of this
I think Alex might reveal a source of information
I would say doesn't make him look
Good
Little Willie Nelson
I'm making this stuff up
Willie Nelson concerts in
Dump Chatterbox
Beers down
Female doctor
After about five beers
Well they start singing
I already know all that
Do you understand what I do as a great journalist is I go to a Willie Nelson concert with a
The doctor get her drunk
And then she said stuff that I repeat on air
Probably embellishing it
That's not great journalistic
That's not bad
Best practice
I mean
I
5 Shiner box down a female doctors throat
To get information
But I already know all of it all man
That's bananas makes him look like a real freak
Creepy photos
Great man
And I assume he made a Cosby joke immediately following that
So that's why we're lost my pay
Very boring
It didn't
Didn't add anything to the the conversation
So that that's the end of this 17
It's all good it's all good
He had there
This is like I don't know who this is
Quite enough
For an episode
Started dipping around
I was looking at stuff and I watch some of the videos of Alex at the rally
I mean do you really lot of its kind of visual
You know like Alex
Clearly uncomfortable when someone ask him a question while he's just standing around on the street
Or
Alex poking his little head out of the truck and yelling 1776.
I don't know it it's not it's not all that
So I started also like considering some Project Camelot stuff for this episode and
I didn't find anything that it was
Worth talking about
Sunny went to banned. Video
Alex's website
Is Big video site
And I can report that it's still all just enforce people talk about providing a platform for all the band people
Has a really panned out
Not seem to materialize
I was looking over the channels a lot of them
Very enact
A lot of them
Black people are not posting
Stuff on there
Glass videos like 3 months ago
Make any videos videos have been passed out
So I was
I don't know man
Who's like a lot of John bowne reports on here that I've never heard
And then I was like what
This
Alex's son has his own channel
Yeah
Oh no recently Alex's son Rex
That started his own show
Now the name of the show is
I'm not bragging
Which is interesting because the name of his show
It seems to be making fun of something his dad says all the time it does seem to be
Cloud
Know if I would like it if by child named their shows something that I said when I'm acting like a dick
I do remember that
You know we should have named I do remember pitching the name of the show is my dad is a big dumb dumb
I did that one
That wooden mustard
Possibly a bad
Strategy
For the longest time I've had a very hands-off
Approached
Durex
Am I still kind of do
Good idea
Recover this show regularly
But the fact is
He has his own show on this at the Infowars Channel now
So I decided I'm going to dip in
And check out what it's all about what you going to do
Now it's his first episode
Is first guess
It's someone we are aware of
And it is not somebody that
Someone of his age and
Persuasion the Vezina like an impressionable young man should be talkin to
I'll bet he is
Mike Jones for this business a real ride
I should tell you just for a little bit of clarification Rex
Has a birthmark
On the side of his hat
So there's a reference to that
At the beginning of this
That's probably
That bud
Well
We're here
Debbie Dennis
Starting off with a bang
Yeah what's up man
Say hi like a headache
I'd 130 walk
Like a Walmart
She saw me and my dad walking out
Beating me up
GPS when I was about
8 years old
I come home from the t-ball game
Walking out taking Gatorade
And physically try to pull me away
Twitter bird
I hear it looks like the Dublin logo
That's what my except
Without for men
Tattoo of it
Like a tattoo
On the other side
Anything remotely we
Get the girls like you
I totally agree
But yeah that's my type
If you like something
Makes you different
Plastic surgery
We should talk about sex
Seahorse
I don't get recognized
Pizza tits where there's absolutely nothing no with no meat in there at all
Someone stole it
That's a deal-breaker
And then going bald as a
But cankles
Acne scars
Laugh lines no boobs
Loser weight
You big
Like a little
Gap in the teeth
You know what I would like those little bit wandering eye
That's unique
Superhot
Obviously
I heard
I heard it I heard a saying
You can get 10
Small boobs in a nice ass
Great Moves In
That's a tough one
Asians off of
No ass
I don't think I've ever seen
That Asian booty
That's like
But that's
Tik-Tok
This is my man
Just like what is this show
What is happening
Baby eighteen-year-old son of Alex Jones talking to a gang leader
That's child abuse
Wow
It's it's absurdly
I can't tell if
The intention is to be funny
Like I really can't cuz neither of them are laughing at the end there were Devin says this should be your child
They're laughing at the idea that they're talking about this at the end
But when you saying like
Pizza tits
Yeah yeah
Sex isn't laughing
Gavin's not laughing now they're very deadly serious
No tits or if you're bald
Hey bad news for you ladies with cancer out there
Amanda this is Rob this is repulsive
Mean
It's really making me rethink my next show which was going to be me saying misogynist
I just
Now I'm starting to think it's a bad idea
And then my other my other idea was saying racist eight-year-old and that's even worse that'll be the next episode
Later in the interview and I just turned it off
Is this how it started
From the jump
First first thing that Gavin wanted to get off of his chest
To a child
Pizza
Man I don't even like him saying that that makes me feel really uncomfortable
I'm still not entirely sure what he's made it up
He might be
F****** cry
Pre poo
I thought gross thing to say I found that to be pretty surreal and also just like I can't I know I've already said this
And I can't stress
I just needed one sharp okay
To see this
I understand the wrecks
Is the Sun
Why is this on the network
We're going to fight we're going to fight the globalist by talking about what is and is not acceptable in a women if they want
To be attractive
David Duke said that s*** to me as a thirty-two-year-old man I'd immediately be like
Hey stop it that's f******
Gross you're a gross
Girl who was raised by Alex may not know better
18 year old
Who's raised
So we have one last clip.
I think it's another little piece of a grab bag here and I mentioned that I went
Can I listen to some Project Camelot episodes in a Pursuit
And there was nothing to be found
I'm but I also listen to
Bill Cooper
Okay I randomly shot around
To a couple episodes that looked in
Interesting
I found some interesting stuff but it's tough little take a little bit longer to develop into like a fuller epi
Episode
But one that really caught my eye
Was episode 150
Of his an hour of the time
It was called
Proof of the New World Order plans or whatever
Pizza Pit
This episode was not proof
The New World Order
I will tell you that right now
The proof that he gives is basically just op-eds the written in newspapers in the 40s
Not really
Even compelling
To deconstruct
And explain why it means nothing
Otherwise we would
Might have just done that isn't episode of his proof was actually even interested
There's something in this episode that I thought like well this
Is
Very much important
Actually Abdul important
I got this episode this clip here is going to start with Bill Cooper
Doing an ad
For the gold
Company that sponsors his show
Great
Tell me it's not today
It's not okay
Is the different gold
This is something that I want to also always wanted to stress and I think I've done this a little bit but I think it always is
Deserves more
That is that
All of these people have gold companies by
So many of these conspiracy
CER
Operation
Are have there either their own
Little cottage industry or they're funded by Gold's
Right because
It works really well you make people really afraid of societal collapse
Been paranoid and all that stuff
To offer them the solution of gold
What is a Sound Investment that even if that happens you'll be a king
That's a
Wonder who the first person to figure that who the first gold company was to
To figure that out cuz it had to it has to go back
Acting like the 80
But yeah I'm in some form or another
And then
Secondarily
There's another
Very big
I'm here
I was kind of
Taken aback by
I'm in reminder
This episode
This is two years before Alex got on air
Time for every one of you who have not called
What you need to know in order to survive
Call now 1-800 289
894 courses required time because I'm going to play some music
While you're
On the phone
Hell yeah you are
For all your life
As much time as you think
Don't procrastinate
Wake your ass up
At work
Years of hardship
Retrieve all face
Are we going
Water New World Order
The One World Government
And dope
Don't believe for one moment
Connectrn jiron you'll find out for the true
I don't believe that this is not going to happen
Has been in the works for me
Can anybody to take any time off
To do the necessary research
Camping permit
Anjappar very short
Courier-Journal 1-800 289
Corphish Pokemon 896
4 pics
Call
PDX
Cherry picking
Charcoal
Call Matt 1 800
2 pics 4 pics
Tuesday
Forfeit
Quadratic
The hour of the time
Clutter
On crocheting
Your future
Call 1-800
Toothpicks
By protecting
Yorkie
Radio broadcast
A quart
Freedom
For the world 100
1 800
Supersport.com time
Poke
Everything
I told you that Bill Cooper uses theme Attic music
Throughout his episodes
In order to sort of height
And raise the mood
He's talking about
In this episode It's called proof of the New World Order Plan
Just definitely an episode that Alex
Would have probably list
Listen to anybody been one of the main
Episodes that he would be drawn to
Bill Cooper
In trying to create the mood of
This evil group
That he is talking about their nefarious plans we need to buy gold in order to make sure they
You were able to survive he plays the f****** Imperial March by Alex plays on every one of the damn show
That was the
Crucial mistake that so many people on Tatooine made they didn't put their money into
That's why they're drinking all that weird milk
Man that's the whole situation that was in one of the novel
Yeah that was discussed
Yeah so obviously
It's impossible to say absolutely
That Alex listen to this episode and I was like wow that's really good
But it also see
Very Potter
Literally everything in that clip is something that Alex
Up to and including claiming that if you don't buy the stuff
Then the world will collapse with that
Order to protect
Your family and the world you need to buy gold
From me from the person that I'm director
It's not going to happen it's going to have less time than you collapse is coming
Play this song though so you have plenty of time.
The full involvement of bike that is Alex's operation let it sit it Scribd
Immediately
Weird that is
Exactly how Alex Stowell
F****** everything
It does seem that way
Yeah
We all should have listened to the Jedi they told us to buy gold Ben Kenobi he made the mistake
Farmer Derek exactly there we go
Are we go
So anyway we don't do that of this and you know it's a bit of a shorter episode but hey
It's a grab bag
I don't know
I don't know we walk away from this with other than
Galaxy
McGinnis is a
Reality
To the thief
Lewinsky jokes are dumb in 2020 still going
And I think
You know this looking
The overs
Sensationalizing
And hyping up
Of stuff in advance of this event
In Virginia
And then pretending like all the other side did that
Afterward
And the way in which is rhetoric works too no matter what happens
Beyond aside that he can move forward from pretending he was right
I think whenever those
Events happening
It's good to
Direct knives like this
Is the trick this is
Is the cheap move that he's playing
People in pocket
Paul there should be some sort of car
For Paul Joseph Watson
Listen to
Pull that s*** in the same day
But there's just not going to be with but here's the thing he's already suffered
Those consequences
No one takes him seriously
Without consequences because your life is a
Rye Rye
You are where you are is the consequence
But you you are seen as a liar
A fraud in a propagandist by anybody who
You know isn't
With you and
That's the consequence you can just do this stuff
If you're already
I don't know I don't know a good metaphor but the one I was thinking of is like
Is there already blind you can dump acid in your eyes
Doesn't work
That one's not going to go up in the pantheon like people in glass houses shouldn't throw stones but I think it's not terrible sure
So anyway back on Friday with
Episode
But until then
REI website
Dot-com
Yep we're also on Facebook
We are on Facebook and if you would like to download the show please go to iTunes rate leave a review its
Centra Etc we love it
So we'll be back but until then I'm Neo I'm Leo
I'm dzx Clark
I'm a big old horse
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work