Damn important
I have great respect for Tenaya Lodge like I'm sick of them posing as if through the good guy
Stripe.com
Everybody
Novelty Beverages and talk a little bit about Allie
Alex Jones
What was the last
Live
TV event
Something that you felt like I got to watch this
Live impeachment hearings on like not I don't have a TV to watch it on a S3 considerate
Is that
I don't know
But I ain't going to cuz you don't watch sports not really never do that live
Though
I meant something more like what you wanted to say
Some people are like it's Monday I got to watch the f******
Something like wrestling pay-per-views in the past
Is a lot of listeners may assume based on
Knowing things about it
But
This weekend's the Royal Rumble I'm excited about
I can never not get excited about a Royal Rumble
You know trouble is what you you live and die for
It's great
You got 30 dudes that end up having to be fighting with each other again thrown over the top rope before this thing can a
The whole thing and the way it's structured actually I should say now there's also a women's Rumble
Both lose 30 women also in a in a match
The way the matching structured is
The first person comes out and then the second person comes out
Supposedly two minutes later someone else
Although that time frame is
Is very variable
Random
But the excitement of the
The countdown is like
You don't know who's coming out alright music hits
And they just give you that at
Like that to dopamine Rush
30 *
It's very exciting
New people from the past that come back on
Oh God I watched a few Rebels there was a couple of
Comedian friends
Used to do a like a fantasy football game with it and trying to guess like surprise entry
Yeah yeah everybody
Money put on it is fantastic
Is Greg Lovett
Even if take even the wrestling
Respect out of it just
Random people showing up
You somewhere
It'll procession
Really taking up a noon
Alright
One ring
But
2 rings
In the back so there's a ring there's one whole thing and then only one ring divided
It sounds like two rings
Smash together one wall
On either side there's the women's Royal Rumble and then the men's Royal Rumble
Stack of every staggering every minute somebody news coming out
And you can
Throw a woman or a man over those Central Buckle men's or women's Royal Rumble WWE
He is very much
Not super into inter-gender wrestling
At this point
Of men hitting women are super into that they sell a lot
Lot of toys
Sprayer
I think their sponsors are not
Not interested in them
What about drawing women out of a
Call me if it's other women doing other women wrestlers
Specs
This weekend so that'll be the next time I probably watched
Something live Lovett
I know it is because I don't know too much about live TV entertainment but I do know a lot about Alex Jones
That's not appointment
I'm so Jordan we're back today cuz we have a little bit of that minisode on when
Wednesday wanted to have a full-on normal app we're actually have to look into things
We had a mini set the length of other pot
Podcast Regular Show
Most of it was just sort of Alex's
Add
Is weird ad
There's not really anything to look into that I have
There's no way I can find a database of his stock
It is Warehouse
That's probably true that we're out of work for it
January 22nd
I'm Dan this
Alright alright
Do January 22 2020
Yep
I think this is an interesting things with one of the things that we can do is really keeping us in the present day is the fact that the Trump impeachment is
Beginning
There's these flare-ups that keep happening like Alex
Declaring a Civil War was going to break out on Monday
So there's beat these are the things with the impeachment hearing
Then the trial is really what
I would figure
Is going is the most
Compelling most
Thing thing
Alex
Should have an angle on it
So that's what I was mostly looking for here
In this episode and I didn't really get it
Punjab not surprising my guess
We're talking all about
Beezus
This phone no bees on this phone does not come up
I know but we have another overarching
Narrative that is
Awesomely stupid
And we'll get to that here and Mama
Some folks
The show
Very exciting list
Two fun names
Spell believe
Alright first
Mbsr
Next tinker's damn thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you tinker's damn if that's a real name and you you leaned into it like I was fake that guy gets it all the
Nextleaf
Thank you so much
Relationship
Bren
You are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk Brenda build
Next Sparks
Thank you so much
Journal about Willy Wonka
Xbox Xbox
Damn thank you so much
Juvenile policy wonk
The tinker's Dam and Sparks probably are there fairly fizza 50/50 call for me
Spell different
It smelled just like Leafly
But anyway you're closer if it's a real name
Sparks I apologize for apologize
But I've assumed that this is
Is an alias and quit lying to us measure real name dammit
And I finally like to say thank you to a couple people donated on an elevated level appreciate it very much so
Thank you so much you are now a technocrat
And Patrick
Thank you so much you are now
Technocrat
What's the business
Heroin
Freakishly large
Thank you so much I Lee and Patrick
If you're at the listening everything hey I enjoy this showed like spoke with these gents do you do that
Website
The button that says for the show we would appreciate it absolutely
Thank you know Jordan we have an out-of-context drop to get to that is very off-color and very not a family
Text drops
Rex no
But before we get to that I want to talk about this
Don't forget remember
Michelle I think the audience
Might enjoy this
So I
I have some trouble sleeping cuz of noise in this house speaker
In order to play like always greater volume
Can on my phone
The phone speaker isn't it it doesn't work
It does work a bit better but
I downloaded an app
That has a bunch of different sounds
And you can play them
Together or you can make your own blend of sound
Amazon employee listening to you
Pacifica got one that has no internet capability
No I got it has all these these noises
That's cool
I think there's some promise
In terms of being able to block out the troubling noises
So that's good that is a plus
However
There's also one option where you can get the
The sound of a cat
No
It's just a cat going
I started to think about it really bummed me out cuz I who would want
Someone who's cat reason
We died
I was thinking somebody who is trying to drive another person in
Insane
There's a cat in there wall it's either prank like that or someone who's
Grieving the loss of a pet wants the comfort of the illusion of that pet still being there
Cuz otherwise it's very distracting
And that is a bummer
That is a bummer
What focus group was that
Idea flood at this very second
Could you put a cat sound on they feel like that
Like a person who would want that
I'm going to suit the sounds like
Celine
I got my cat
Immediately
I went crazy in a way that I've never seen before I started stalking around the house like trying to hunt
For this other cat is in the house okay
So I started using that the f*** with her
Wheeling third possibility
It was like
I never seen her go into like real hunt mode before it was it was fascinating
Anyway that is the saline up
Gotcha now let's go
Get to this out of color
Rust color out of context drop that is not
This is not a family drop
But you know why
He had a good side job
Okay
If you're out there if your dad
You look down at your son and you like
Wow
Even though you're a full-grown adult misses a weird thing to be doing
I know why
Little bit that's the chemical that Alex has based his the tap water is a freaking
Can gay bomb ran out of time the frogs gay stuff on development
To talk about
Before we get to that that'll be a little bit later
Alex said some other business
Take care of it out of the first
He starts the show doodle
Talking about how great it was that he took over the women's March in DC
They took over the Virginia rally
Every report
And the security people had just done a 100-percent job
Everything fell into place
Everything we did was wildly successful and game-changing and national news
Taking over deep state
Narratives that gun owners were going to cause a giant murderous Bloodbath
Turned it around on them educated the folks by the governor was trying to cause a false flag
Accounting for people John's
Same thing I'm with the women's March how it's run by Soros how it's been to divide the family we totally took
And not the majority of the car
Highbridge
Billion buxoro spent on that. Mitch
We took it
Boom boom
Soros admits it
This is George Bush putting up a mission
Accomplished
You didn't do a goddamn thing
You're an
I think this offers us a really interesting
Interesting window in
Into seeing how Alex
Excuse the world
Like in his mind globalist
You're saying that all gun owners are evil and what he did was
Hijacked that narrative and show the world that isn't
True
But in reality no one really was saying the gun owners are all evil they were saying
But The Sensational way that's certain
Extreme is good weirdos were building up that rally in Virginia
Was having the effect of attract
Like unstable and very dangerous people
And that could be a recipe for trouble
The thing though
Is that Alex isn't really responsible for demonstrating that the globalist positions are wrong
Because he was responding to a strong
However he was partially responsible for The Sensational coverage of the rally and how is going to be the side of a globalist false Flags
Is the kickoff a new race
Slash Civil War
He was part of creating that app
Atmosphere where extremists like the members of the base
Felt the rally was prime target
To create an event that would Advance their acceleration
Mister genda
Alex is part of the problem in the real world
In his head
He's created an imaginary problem
Witchy is the solution
This is how the rhetoric work
He's a f****** loser
Well yes
But I don't say that cuz it kind of marginalizes people who
No that's
I think what's interesting about the rally is
Statistics and everything that they put up
It makes you realize that responsible gun owners are by and large
Very responsible
Liking a what was it like 80% of gun owners supported every single one of the
Gun control measures passed
And the only problem are these
Plugging thousand Gunn weirdos who are absolutely out there looking
Infor
Danger
I do I don't think most
People are particularly that
Concerned
About
Only being able to buy one-gun-a-month
Doesn't seem like it I don't know but it's the rhetoric that surrounds it that involves like okay yeah they want you to
You're only be able to buy one-gun-a-month
Unless
You have the concealed carry permit cuz it
Concealed carry permit is the way they can track you to come and take your gun registration is
God wear world
Yeah that's the way you make it so there's never any progress
So the issue that Alex has is it this is a lot of victory
How you going to make people scared because all these Victory time to roll out
Fear
Ball is the stock market
The other big car ball is this Coronavirus
That did you know there it is
Just
A month
Days ago
Got
Certified with a vaccine
And blow and behold the exact same virus pops up
Start spreading
That's just amazing I wasn't insinuating voice of his again like he did with the
Caller who's talking about the the shooting hoax
Around the time of the Virginia Bells
This is a pathetic man
Pick a day
Weird weird a bit of an interesting situation
Concurrently as a relates to what's being called the Wuhan
Coronavirus
This novel strain of coronavirus just come out of China
At the point where recording us a lot of the basics regarding
The spread in scope of the virus are not entirely clear but it's definitely some
The merits attention in to be taken serious
Most of the people who come down with the virus or believed to have caught it when they were in Wuhan
Hey I travel Hub in China
We thought they were exposed to fish and seafood market
The Danimals
At this stage
It doesn't seem sorry it does seem like there has been some human-to-human transmission of the virus
But passing it along still would require transmission of bodily fluids
So according to available information
It's not like something where we need an extreme Panic surrounding this like it's an Airborne
Everyone's going to get it right
No no plague masks just yet
Perhaps not
I'd really like to say more about this but honestly according to the information I can find from the CDC and other official sources
We most likely won't know the extent of this outbreak for a little while at least
It's being said that
To be a serious concern among the elderly babies and people with compromised immune systems but
It seems like for most people
You might just end up even if you get it with a bad cold
Yeah yeah so I assume that
The Chinese are trying to slightly lower our productivity I don't know if Alex is the Chinese on this one
Ambiguity and the uncertainty that surrounded the situation right now is
It should lead people to approach it with
Some caution with their reporting
And then forward
They Come Out Swinging with
Sensationalism in
Dearborn the likes of which I haven't seen since the last time I was yelling about Obama trying to sneak Ebola
Normal Outlets like CNN or quick
The point out that even though there have been deaths from this strain that the rate is lower than stars or Mercy
Two similar viruses that have come up
In the past
In the recent past
Infowars
Article about how Imperial College of London Professor Neil Ferguson
Was quoted as saying that this cold start this could
Have a similar death rate to the 1918 Spanish flu outbreak
MMA editorialize that could mean that 100
85 million people could die from
Sad is that might be a bit of a
At least in the early going
What Infowars fails to point out of the rest
Ferguson's commentary
He was talking about
The current rate of death among known cases of the virus
But according to CNN quote
Ferguson believes the fatality rate is likely
Play to be lower due to an iceberg of milder cases we're yet to find
Once there's more information a lot of this
To probably end up looking a lot less
Drastic and severe that it does immediate
Okay so you're saying that some media Outlets
Took noted expert entire phrasing and and wording and answering questions where
Basically he
Canceled everybody to be cautious about
Making this a ripped
Diculous sensationalize thing
And the media Outlet grabbed the one
Hypothetical where is like
Well it could be
I think you Ferguson
Comments could be better characterized as not saying like
Worry about it seriously
Amanta a reality of these the surface
Situations is that
Oftentimes what you see is it looks really bad
And then when you find that there are I don't know
Additional people who had the virus
You realize I
Okay it's not as deadly as it
It appears immediate
That's the gist that I got from
From Ferguson
There were mysterious
Incubus in their absence
From the invoice article
Not as bright
I can't tell you what's going to happen with this this this virus
But I do think it's repugnant for Alex to behave the way you
No matter the scale of the eventual outcome this is a public health
Issue and people should be given the information they need the best equip themselves
Keep themselves in
The family safe
A situation like this there's no place for
Sensationalism
But honestly Alex doesn't have any other games
To play
All he has is
Insinuation
In a position that is
Equally knee-jerk as it is uninformed
That this virus is a globalist attack
As opposed to just a reality of life in the modern world
Every virus in
Condition is unknown until it's
Not people who work on this stuff understand that Dynamic perfectly well
But Alex
He has a piece of information that blows this whole thing wide open
A month
Four days ago this virus was
Was patented
Vaccine or whatever
Which definitely prove
Set this is a global
I can find no evidence of what he's saying
This would be December 8th
Keep 2019 that he's talking about there's no and no indication that I can find it
He's not just making this up
On December 20th 2019 mark
Announced they've gotten FDA approval for an Ebola vaccine
You called
This is huge news but has nothing
You do with the Wuhan situation
As best as I can tell there's a
Conspiracy running around there was a patent put on this vaccine virus tumor
Make a vaccine prior to the outbreak being reported to the World Health
But I've reviewed the arguments of basically it all boils down to these online Dum Dums not realizing
That the word coronavirus is not unique
To this outbreak
It's an umbrella under which there's tons of
Specific viruses including SARS and MERS
I can find
Conspiracy theorist talking about it
Prior
Coronavirus patent
Suspicious
I can't find anything about December 18th
That s*** that Alec
What is talking about
Infowars opposed to time two articles but I need to be very afraid
But none of them have anything about this
Mysterious Pat
I have searched
Natural news as well and I couldn't find any information on
I have no idea
At this point what Alex is talking
But maybe a little bit later in the episode
Alex will reveal
And we can figure out whether or not he's making s*** up
I wouldn't be surprised if he was like
They make you put a lime in the in this
Alright
Coronavirus
It's a it's a
Very heavily featured in the fast
The Furious movies
That's all Ludacris tricks
So Alex
This is going to get back to this and
It'll be very hilarious when he does
Just because the roots
To this are very
And very soon
Before he does he's got to ramble that's another issue
Medical free press that I find
Very stupid
Text to be talkin about
The breakdown
Brazil is going after
Atlanta
Ion
The leader of Brazil and on
But he's not nothing
I don't know why Alex is surprised
Why what's happening with Glenn Greenwald in Brazil
What is a dashiki
Did he think the jilber sinaro wasn't going to attack Nebraska
We'll get to that here in a second because like
Alex's just like
Back way out of
Out-of-left-field on the
And again
I have my own going
Theory that Alex does not know bolsonaro's name
Play the leader of Brazil becomes much
Stronger every time Alex toxic
Modern communication is Facebook his YouTube is Twitter
Altona
Play myself
Don't even
Pick the phone up you just sent a text message
You send voice message
Communication is down
We're looking into Banning Jones off of
Text messages
For Nissan
If using Whatsapp
He doesn't
Baby tries to use private messenger without the wheel bearing in there
And now Brazil
Facebook is using at the block people there that support balsara
Journalism
Dangerous situation
Yeah it certainly is
This is
Hellboy
Talking about there with is like
Give me to not be able to
The text or whatever isn't Facebook there was a conversation
I think on Sienna and maybe
Some sort of adjust
Casual conversation with a reporter who owns WhatsApp
Is he kicked off that too I don't know
Yeah I don't know this whole thing is baseball
More of a hey you're kicked off Facebook does that apply to
The other business is a Facebook on
Yeah yeah
How does
Roll that ball down the hill
Now ever want to know what apps I'm on
Yeah that is that is like
You're not allowed to watch Disney movies
Did you like okay
But also all the
Things that Disney owns
That's like 40% of all entertainment Star Wars
I'm a 1/2
And I'm glad that I was supposed to have Glenn Greenwald
What is being treated by boss
Brazil
On the other hand I have no idea why you surprised by what's happening
Alex has absolutely supported Boosie too
Up to this point
Supported bolsonaro up to this point when literally everyone who knows anything
Think it's been shouted warning
About is repression of the press and his authoritarian leanings
Alex knows enough
Think about the country
He doesn't even know the name
It was never important
He was just Brazil's
Trump and that was good enough
That's all you need to know
In his campaign bolsonaro called the media trash
Reporters Without Borders sounded a very serious alarm noting
That after the first round of Elections
You'd said he
You plan to quote put a final stop to all forms of
Activism in Brazil
Which is the sort of thing only
Dictator would probably say papa
Well I mean that in like praising previous dictator
Only dictators
Is it probably do that
Did that did he
I don't know
Yep
He later qualified his position that the media was trash tweeting quote
When they cover the fact
Without political activism in partiality the media fulfill a valuable role of informal
The rest of this is in all caps
Quote we are against any type of social control of the media and internet yes pictures
Maybe political activism and partiality is only a problem when it
It's not in agreement with you
Innocence it seems like yeah
You could be called the
Brazil drop
I mean you know he hasn't murdered a journalist on his birthday
Drew
That's a good start
Reuters reported during the campaign that quote the Brazilian Association
Investigative journalism is identified more than 60 in
Listen to the physical violence or it's imminent threat against journalist
Stirring the camp
Champagne
This probably explains why bolsonaro tweeted in Ark
Really attacked over stressed these attacks
Start the natural result of his rhetoric
What we're seeing now with the targeting of Glenn Greenwald is terrible but none of it should be surprising
In the campaign Brazilian journalist Miriam Nieto was aggressively targeted and threatened by bolsonaro
Supporters for an article
But they wrote about the threat
Did he pose to
Reporters Without Borders
Cover the female journalist who cannot be named for
Security reasons
Who work for any 10 News
She was hit in the chin and arm by bolsonaro supporters who threatened
Draper and said quote when the commander is President the whole press will be killed
Bolsonaro himself attacked and threatened to remove any government advertising from Full hot Due South Paulo
The newspaper
When a closer examination reveals is probably just mad that they ran critical coverage of him
And Brandon story affirming that he had threatened
Did you kill his ex-wife
Is constant and aggressive attacks on the media created a very hostile and very non-free
Environment
For the price of the country and it's exactly what everyone who cares at all
All that time Alex is not given a single s***
He supported bolsonaro
Because nothing matters to Alex other than opt
This guy was being called Brazil Trump
And he was acting a lot like Trump
He was friendly with drop use the same words like
Like fake news
How the f*** are you supposed to
To criticize him without it being very clear that you're fine with
The same thing from Trump
Alex has now entered
Is the place of
The. We're criticism about Trump for not free Julian Assange that's become normalized
So now he can feign some kind of concerned about Greenwald situation
Without jeopardizing losing
When is audience
Dumb dumb
This is all just very sad and
Clear demonstration
How's little Alex cares about any of this s***
We Care
You know bolsonaro's name
If he cared
He would have noticed the very clear pattern of attacking
The press in Brazil for a long time already
If he cared he would take a look in the mirror and realized that he would absolutely lockup Brian stelter
If you had the power to do so
What I'm getting at
Is it if I were Paul Joseph Watson
I probably accuse Alex of virtue signalling hear about caring about the Press
Probably what I would do
Yeah if you're surprised
Is that bolsonaro went after Glenn Greenwald
The guy who revealed operation Carwash was AJ corrupt bullshits
The guy who revealed that today illegally ousted
Silver in order to or not silver
They all stood her in order to install to Mayor even though that was illegal and he wasn't even allowed to f****** run and then because
Lula was in prison at the time again it legally for no reason
Visa political
He wasn't allowed to run even though it would have won by a f******
Miles said bolsonaro is in with a f******
Absolute Stranglehold on power
I don't know why
They would go after
Glenn Greenwald
Only thing that's surprising is it took this long
Yeah exactly I was kind of surprised
But my point is I course this is
I'm glad that I was bringing attention to it to his audience
But at the same time it's
It's indicative that the issue isn't he
He presented to be cuz if it was
You should have heard These Warnings long ago
End. Just been blindly and stupidly
Supporting
Gennaro the rest of the world said
Lookout
I think that very simply the he's lighting the entire Amazon on
On fire would have been a good warning sign for he's probably going after
Regardless how much does a care about that that's been to release more carbon
Now that's right plan for God tonight then I forgot about that sometimes you say stuff like that
You got to make sure you do that to look like that and it just think man
This guy does not pay attention
Just an idiot
So stupid
So
Alex is is dumb on that count
And he starts talking a little bit about the impeachment but instead of talking about the excellent
Trial he wants
To distract with
Boutique right-wing victimhood narrative
And this is before him that it
For today
What they don't want is
People tuning in
See the impeachment feed
Or nymphowars or right side
A Judicial Watch
In the Modern Age
A couple hundred bucks
C-SPAN
Congress and they'll just give me the feed
I can carry
And CNN is always behind us and you know
It was
Oliver Darcy one of those guys called up
YouTube
They got the contact the top of it what are you doing
So the story is the Judicial Watch and right side broadcasting streaming the impeachment hearing
YouTube shut down the street
Alex is completely making up
B e n n and Oliver Darcy were in any way involved
In the story that he
He's talking about
He has nothing to base that on other than his imagination
I'm making this up
It feels to me like CNN and Oliver Darcy probably did that you are discounting his
Deduce
Information rather than
I'm not disc
Accounting pad
IMDb
I'm putting it on trial
Matt Silva
I find the story hard to care about too much
Right side broadcasting is an extreme right-wing organization that is employed Nick Fuentes @joeysalads in
In the past right
Mayweather streaming capabilities taken away by YouTube previously due to a breach
Community standards
It seems believable to me
That they were in violation
In the game here and Heather's
Suspended again
I don't care
As we're Judicial Watch their ridiculous right-wing propaganda Outlet who received YouTube strikes recently for things like
Revealing the alleged Ukraine whistleblowers name
It seems very believable again that they were not just providing
Some kind of commentary on the impeachment operating
Single bed Outside YouTube the rules
This is specifically a YouTube thing
Judicial watches stream the impeachment
Continued on their own website
Is just something about their stream was not appropriate for you to
I've been doing this show long enough
Not to care about Judicial Watch and I cannot possibly believe anything the right side broadcasting says
We will remain
Forever
Who cares
Yeah yeah
If you can watch
Throughout a bunch of Edward they'll be like
Go to eBay.
Whatever it is they had it
Yeah I don't know what the issue is precisely here but
Actors
This is Alex isn't telling the whole truth
The story and I don't
Really cared
Nope
Care to look into
The judicial watch this
So
Another thing is like I can't be distracted
Drive to buy this
There's bigger issues at the coronavirus was Patton
A bump in 4 days ago
I just get really
Excited when I hear Alex
Get to it, stop
Confirm
Belmont report
We're going to break it
Bodily harm
Coronavirus
It was patented certified for
Authorizes a vaccine
And magically that's right after that happens if
I'm saying
Yes you are
What do sometimes equals 4
Water
Marshall and Skye
That's an upside down
Lana's real loud
Today no one died today
At the doctor last month
This is very serious situation were to be laying it all out
And breaking it all down
Here today
Please remember that
Without you this dog doesn't
With your elbow supported does and right now we need financial
4 +
Products you really need regardless
So if you're listening or paying attention what is just happened to yours Alex said that
This coronavirus was patented for a vaccine a month and 4 days ago and then there was an outbreak
Hey isn't that suspicious I'm not saying that the globalist
To doing this but sometimes bananas are yellow bats hang upside down two plus two is four
That they are attacking us
The world with this bio-weapon on Coronavirus
I need some
Yeah yeah
For the products that will almost certainly
Text you from this
Oh I don't know
He doesn't go that far as to imply that his products are going to help you with this situation
Commercial that he plays is that one about like
Hey knock on wood
I don't get sick often I take my products and I don't get
Who is still the understanding among his audience that he sells product that will help you not be
I take iodine and colloidal silver I won't catch anything
So I don't know what if you what if the only thing
It stops Coronavirus
This Is The Life
Then word
Serious drop me another quarter that's going to be no good me another quarter before that gets passed the standards
So
He's just teasing though he doesn't get any specifics on this there's not much I can do is no information
Based on this bit is
Is readily available
And so I just need
You know I'm like a rock climber
I need something to eat I need a whole
Yeah I need a hold beyond the pole
Myself
We just got to see what happens
So he starts talking more about the impeachment
Trial
Complained about this they think is very dumb
Savannah Hernandez
And Owen adjoining us coming up in the second our here today and again live reports from
DC
With the second day of the Trump profit all it is is the Democrats
Grandstanding and
Again telling us over. We're going out guilty
Trump is trying to game the system
Game
The house
He's complaining that it's just the Democrats grandstanding it's the
Democrats
The opening statement.
Yeah like what the fuc
Why are you
Just Democrat stalking
That's how
They agreed for the structure of the hearing to be the f*** are you talkin about
Great doesn't matter
Lawyer for the Republican said none of them were allowed to look at the stuff
Even though everybody sucks everybody was everybody knew you was fine and you can just lie in there
Because it doesn't f****** matter could you imagine like during the period where it's the you know the Republicans
Opening
A couple days can you imagine like a serious
Left-wing commentator trying to pull that kind of s*** like
Is grandstanding up here same props innocent you telling me that they're just going to talk for 3
3 days
What kind of ridiculous pop party would talk for 3 days
Exploitative of his audiences
Lack of grasp of the specific things
And how they work
That is what is going on in the trial right now
You may be annoyed by
But it's part of the agreed-upon format
So
Shut the f****** just because I agree
To do this doesn't mean I can't still Moline you while you're doing
Stupid
Sonic says the ONN Savannah Hernandez are going to be in
We're not going to hear anything
From Savannah because they're Skype doesn't really work out now it's like f******
Alright
He does have Owen Shroyer come in and
Before he does
He plays a video of Owen going and like
Roofing
Reprove
Good protesters on the left
Any pro impeachment protesters
They don't even know why the mm
Impeachment
You got to listen to a little bit of
The impeachtrump Rousseau and
I'll go ahead and school I'm on the issues
You don't know the reason you don't know the reason
Do you get ready
We're going there for a second because clearly this person who's trying to talk to has said I'm not here to talk
Even
If I know that a lot of people on the
Let you know what's a people who work for The Daily Show
Big only talk
Two people at Trump rallies like
Make fun of
If he had a video where one of them said I don't want to talk to you
And then he kept antagonizing them
I would say that that is f****** b*******
Even though I agree with the idea of making these people at Trump rallies look stupid
I agree that good funny.
I'm not sure if
But it's fine you know it's entertaining
If one of them
Open the group
That I don't care much for said I'm not here to talk
And then Jordan clever's like
Dominate this person
Then I would say that this is not cool
You are now harassing people
Pretty sure you still have
The signed releases on broadcast
Stevie apparently
Just be like this person for a while
Give explicable thinking that he's going to dominate anybody in Onarga
Go dominator
Claiming that trumps impeachment is for Ukrainian quid pro quo the only problem is
Nancy Pelosi
How can the impeachment
Look for something he did as president
My cameraman please
You can see the strategy there is
Let's get ongoing gay
Let's argue let's fight
That is all they have that that is all this and really they should stop putting out videos that include those
Worship yeah
Because it's
To clear that these people were like I don't want to talk to you
Not block
Us or whatever
There's a clear disinterested engaging and then he poking
Antagonizing
You need to cut that out in only leave in the part where they're yelling at you later
This really hurts the optic
It does if it doesn't
But if your intended no I mean
And it does for for us who are like there are standards and things
You should do an
Maybe just
Birra polite person that reveals too much of that
The goal is
The album
The goal is eliciting the outburst and they don't care the people
May say
I don't want to talk to
Owning the libs
Is
Not about
Arguments
Norwin
Or being correct it is about making lives
Right
So when is that going to be on the show and talk
The Alex about his
His plates
And how difficult it is
He says that he is
Like a second
Can class citizen there's a two-tiered justice system against
People like him I would like to put him down to 3rd can we put him down to a third-class citizens are you think he is a just fine so
He's doing all right
Put them down first
Anyway Alex
Some thoughts
Was just stupid
You know what Infowars tells you something's bombshell news we're not hyping it
The future of Humanity on this planet and Beyond
Beyond Buzz Lightyear lights
But I just got a call or the producer did Daria
2 minutes ago
Dinocore
It's bomb shelters are trying to put him in jail
In there at the kickoff of impeachment saying
Is the Democrats and the Deep state
We can't find cases for the Democrats
Sometimes
They've actually been indicted
But when will the Democrats take over Live Events
They might get arrested but they're throwing the book
You can find tons of left-wing protesters and activists who are nonviolent do been arrested for demonstrating
And face
Consequences have to go to trial
How to completely making up the idea that none are in order
Exaggerating
A few of the right-wing victimhood that animates his business
Turning on Troy into some kind of a martyr
Although I do think this is really interests
Think because this is
News
On the 22nd
End of January
Owen Shroyer disrupted that impeachment Hearing in early too
December he's just had to go to a court date
This makes me realize why he's still in DC covering the impeachment
Because he left
So he
DC providing coverage
Joe argue about a ticket
I appreciate that
DC anyways might as well block a few hours I'm laughing because it's funny
Not because it's not why
Alex has been teasing this coronavirus thing and it really was me hitting my head against the wall trying to figure out what the fuc
Talking about I have no
Is really absurd
Then finally
Here
At this point
Alex uses a specific
And I'm able to run with
There is a
Eyebright Instituto pronouncing that right
The shadowy William secretive group
Twerking
On
Trying to create
Vaccine for this
They've patented
Over the years
Mutations
The virus
Until I just find it very very interesting that
Magically there's a vaccine for this now and
Well there you go
This coronavirus grasping at straws this is pathetic
Talking liar answer isn't there isn't
Cream for that there's one in the works
Probably won't be ready for a while
Literally never heard Alex bring up
The hybrite Institute on his show before and he's obviously unfamiliar with them
Being as he isn't sure how to pronounce their name and he pronounces it
Is reporting on them as a shadowy organization that's up to no good
He's making insinuations about them as if they're a long time bad guy on the show but this is all new s***
Also point of order he's completely making up if they're funded by Bill
It's entirely possible that some
Funding for that Foundation does
Exist from Bill Gates but Alex is absolutely just guessing and making that up
He is no reason to suggest that other than to make the hibriten
Look Evil by connecting them to an established bad guy in his cinematic
Now that is some information I can get to the bottom of
Edit this clips
Aesthetic rambling didn't already tell you this
This is complete b*******
There is no article on Infowars
Nord newswars
North summit news
Nor natural news
Does that include the words
Hibriten
Ever know
There is a headline quotes
Secretive Institute patent
Did coronavirus vaccine recently
But that article on Infowars is just a video this episode that we are listening to it right now
There's legitimate
No proof of any of this ship
I won of things it's the most difficult is that there are a number of ways you could spell hybrite hybridlight
H i h i g h
Who knows
Thankfully
I'm an old salt
If this game
And I know the odds are that Alex flash something up on screen that could help me out here
So it turns out I went
Consulted the video
And turns out when he says hi bright
It's actually.
Cirb HD
So he meant
So he said
Fire bright
No he said hybrid he said hi right
Pure bright
Alex appears to be getting this information
About the purebright insta
Two and how they got a vaccine patented in December from Jordan sather
Noted qanon weirdo on Twitter
And a guy who recommends people drink bleach
For healthcare
After tweeted about this
Conspiracy back on January 21st
The day before the episode we listening to now
And it spread a bit from
If I had to guess I would say that Alex saw this but would absolutely never admit that this
Who's this source
Unfortunately
The Panthers owned by the pier Brighton
If it's related to the Coronavirus
Is not
For human use the one that Jordan sather was tweeting about the one that's Central to all the
The conspiracies
The group from there
From the patent
Although live attenuated vaccines and inactivated vaccines are universally used in the control of ivv
Desired condition is related to a Coronavirus
They're protected game by use of vaccine
Be lost either due to vaccine breakdown or to the introduction
Of a new ibv stereotype
0 type that is not related to the vaccine use
Posing a risk to the poultry
Further there's a need in the
The industry to develop vaccines
Are suitable for use in OVO
In order to improve the efficient
And cost-effectiveness of vaccine program
Jordan pits for birds
If it's given
Chickens is the VMAs
Fervor
Yes all right
Isn't it a little bit convenient that this vaccine is for an oval chick
What do we eat
Chicken
That's how we're going to get the vaccine virus
This is the problem with people not reading
If you read over this patent you find a dead giveaway when they're talking about clinical indications from the vaccine and the
The main side effect they're talking about and are concerned with is Snicker
Which is a respiratory condition
Chickens
There's no conversation in this padded all about human used because it's a vaccine for f******
Chicken
That's an issue
There's only one sliver of plausibility here
And I need to stress
But this story Alex is talking about
Propulsion
Bluebird observable reality is
That's a pride Institute does study animal diseases that have a
Potential possibly spread to
Like in the case of the Coronavirus
Some chicken
But that's not all that they do
They're primarily an Animal Health Organization
As one might learn from looking in
Maybe some of their other
Search like they're recent breakthrough related to foot
Mouth disease
Which only affect hoofed animals
Which humans are not
The body Galaxy's foot-in-mouth
Cuz he's all right how we doing
The bottom line here is that this vaccine for chickens
Is not even the same strain of coronavirus it's currently showing up out of Wuhan
Physical play Leon related padding for an animal medicine that Alex is reporting is being related to the Wuhan outbreak
As best as I can tell
These sources be Twitter account of a dude who tells
Followers to drink
Which
This is bad work
Yeah that's
Probably not what I would say was going to get you a Pulitzer
I don't think he's going to win on this one
TV
The Great
Somebody patented of vaccine for chickens and that's why we're all going to die a story of 2020
Probably isn't going to
I'm going to win anyting now I doubt it
So that's a big guy that's the big scoop out
Jordan sather tweeted out a f****** patent
For a chicken vaccine representing as being the same thing
Is this Wuhan coronavirus outbreak
It's proof that the globalists are attacking everybody
People need to go to school
I'm going to say this quite a bit
Just go to school
You really need to go to school a little bit critical
That's what I'm
What's the problem isn't like people not knowing
How to read
It's blind trust in people like Alex
Jordan sather
Those types of people who
Don't do any work too
Throat spaghetti against the wall
Presentational effect
People just need to not trust them
And go and read these things
The people who is like tricked by a lot of this stuff they know how to
They just don't
Do it and don't
Confirm these things
Like with Alex
If any of his listeners went and actually red
The Texas
Domestic terrorism threat assessment
It would puncture the entire world
Recreating
Why would they
Why would I
How to say this is all about themselves it's
Very clearly about white racially motivated terrorism
Cause that
Depressed in these figures is what
To be eroded
Because they're bad Act
They don't they don't present the information
Accurately
Alex is presenting his f****** dumb s*** about a chicken vaccine
Has presented the information
That you're if you're presenting information you should have
To present the information for you should be
To and receptive to calls
Address the information you're putting out
If you're wrong about something you should be
You know you should be open
Open to that as opposed to Alex and now he's going
Like this is going to be established as a
Piece of his rhetoric moving forward
That the globalist
Planned
Muffin
Four days in advance with this vac
Dean Patton
Everyone will just internalized it as a real talking point as opposed to it being based
On a f****** chicken fix
Vaccine for chicken
Correct correct
Now
And there's some point soon about a nickens
What he say
Is that
Lapeer pregnancy
Dude
Patented a vaccine for the coronavirus that is now being treated
Wuhan as a possible issue
But it's Fortune
None of this is real
But this is the kind of dangerous news that Alex covers
And that's why they need him to be taken off the air at Banana yellow
But not when it's brown
They want us also here because
Broadcast
Government
Buy from the government
The hundred bucks last time we did it
Oliver Darcy Oliver Darcy calls up and says that's his job
YouTube
That's in the news right here at some level they don't want us on there they don't want us being able to cover any of it they are the
Are the controllers
So now it's become Alex is implying that it's in the news that Oliver Darcy in CNN
We're behind getting right side broadcasting in Judicial Watch
Is dreams on YouTube take a Daddy has nothing
Nothing to base that on he just made it up earlier in the show
And now he's repeating it as if it's
He even added something to Oliver Darcy's LinkedIn page
Apparently he's in
In charge of getting people
Kicked off YouTube as well
So this is how this is
Again how's this
Mutates over the course of just Alex's rambling
I'm completely unhinged
Ungrounded
Show like
Just him talk
King s*** that Condition Nothing spiral out of
Controller
Things become
Substantiated
Things become concrete
Without any real confirmation of anything
It's just I said it it felt good to know it's the truth
And he can't remember long enough because
This memory is very similar to that of a chicken
Bright and so he just assumes that if I said earlier that means it was
Confirmed what I said it do we
Yeah
So Alex now gets back to complaining about Owen Shroyer is victimhood
Call little bit of a remote thing
Anti He-Man
You know this is just all bulshit
He didn't disrupt our receipt he injected one little bit of Citizen truth into it
And he's been arrested
Go to pay for a lawyer
Stock price
Again
Yes I did
Unequal
Weights and measures its selective
Enforcement
Push our they're trying to bamboozle and they're trying
To Shanghai and they're trying to Buffalo him
Infowars
All of that why when you buy the coffee
That's why when you buy your good thing for my
So I mean this is what this all is
You see the transmutation hereof
The victim of the exaggeration the lies about like
There's no complete selective enforcement
He's Democrat to just rub don't ever have to deal with any consequences but people like me and Owen
The Deep state
I'm so brave to do this bike week
Alright acted pleased by my
Did he tell it how the victimhood
Gets translated to a call to action for sale
Captain mind activist
Feds
The Government tried to put
In prison for the rest of his life for leaving water out
I don't know and I don't think he knows
The left never gets any consequences for that offer the government trying to put you in jail for the rest of your life for keeping
Well look dude
Who cares about that stuff cuz I want troyer's getting Bamboozled and buffalo
Man also Shanghai
So I kind of hope it gets Wuhan
Alexandra
They're convinced
That Jerry Nadler himself is behind Owens persecution
They talked about this a little bit
And Alex gets a little weird
Play Protest
Come out here that I've no idea what the impeachment hearing about but oh my gosh
If you're one lowly peon
If you're one tiny little and one little citizen
DARE stand up for your ride
DARE stand up to the Halo
But he is one hot man
You know what I'm not attracted to Umpa Lumpa is Alex so I'm not going to comment on that
Great riff
Glamourtress
Yeah Marvin Gaye's great good comedy
Alex is like I'm not I'm not gay but
That Jerry Nadler is real hot
Does dead Arrow ingest
Not not a yes and Guy
That starting point for the
The bet
First of all and then Towing
Just really
No butted him
Not great
So they're stupid and not worth even really talking about
Alex Goes to break and he comes back
I don't know what happened during the break
But Alex's
Really mad
You know this happened she can hear poner and Anderson total transparency
Why does lighter on the 4th hour around a play at now
So important and
We got so many incredible clips
Rapidan Virginia
That during
Tried to decide again which ones were going to play
They're also powerful
And then other people come in the room and ask why do this problem
Open Newsroom in here
People doing too much I'm not complaining
Then I get angry
Instead of getting angry
Just say hey I'm going to pick what I think was most important report I just play
So this is a devel
This is furious but he's keeping it
Together enough
To throw it to an ad
So he does that he's plays for the rest of this entire segment a video of Millie Weaver
At the Virginia rally
And I mean I guess it's
Probably less abusive especially if it and like weird to your audio
It's that just scream and storm outside
Just off air
This is really really bad
Seems like
Somebody just pointed out to him that he's abused his staff on are maybe a little too much
It's bad luck
Yeah you can just
Throw it to a segment maybe one of his producers came up and was like hey Alex that
Cool thing about the Coronavirus
Stupid
Like that you said dumb s***. About it
So he's got to throw to Emily Weaver report
Now there's something interesting
When he comes back
His coverage takes a real ship
And it becomes
Very anti-islam
It seems to me that there's a possibility that when Alex gets really mad
The only way he can really out
Allow it
To get out
Is googol about Islam
Complained
So he starts doing that a little bit here and there
Well it's Now official French government admits there are hundreds and hundreds of no-go zones
In which French cannot go to be black YouTube eyuboglu Young if you're not a mug
Get your ass attacked American rapper
Your ass up
The President Trump get you out of jail short
Islam has come up
White guys fight back
The Americans
And they go to jail
How Europe has rolled out the red carpet Islamic
Generally speaking I try not to pay too much attention to things like celebrities getting into fights
Particularly when there's a
Play some ambiguity to it
I don't care about celebrities and I'm not impressed by fight so it's
It's just not really a
With the ASAP Rocky
Situation I have no idea what happened
But it's literally nothing like what Alex
Describing
There's a video of
The fight and it's not a bunch of black guys walking down the street only to be attacked by little Islamic
Is Alex is Alex puts it
This is gas-lighting because whatever the reality of what started that fight is
Documented reality is not what Alex's describe
The nineteen-year-old who ended up getting beaten up didn't get charged by the Swedish government because it was determined in court that he only acted in
In self-defense
Also even if Trump did push to get Rocky out of prison
It's hilarious how stupid is attempt
Decoding article in Reuters
Nervous about it quote
Trump had said he would personally vouch for Rocky's bail
Sweden does not have a bail system that's an issue
Ultimately Trump
Didn't get ASAP Rocky release
On August
August 14th 2019 he did he had an appearance
Before the Stockholm District Court
Where he was found guilty
But the court decided not to give him a sentence
Demon time served be sufficient
As well as an order to
Pay for his victims medical card
Trump really didn't do s*** in that case other than act publicly pretty embarrassing
I don't
It's the story of his birth
Do it do it nothing just being loud
An embarrassing
I don't think that Alex is right
To claim that the French government is admitting that there are no go zones a hundreds and hundreds of them but I think I understand where this story is
He's reporting on a Breitbart story that uses
The story in a French paper Lowe's
As its source
There's a little bit of a slippery translation
In here I think the story is saying that a classified document allegedly says that 150 districts in France are how
Held by Islam
Islamists
This document is reference
Expect the article in the journal dude tomorrow's also says that a quote has not been disclosed
So it's not clear even what this document says
But the article does go on to discuss polling numbers animal bears
Mobile
Magoo's
Where do you
Where the union of French Muslim Democrats got a 40% approval
Interpol
So it seems to me like there's a d
Decent chance
This is about is that there's a Muslim political party
It's popular in communities where there are more Muslim
And this is being translated in reported as no-go Zone
I think that there's a possibility that that's what this is about right
So I looked into the union of French Muslim Democrats a little bit it seems like Alex and his ilk should really be
In favor of them
Also to be clear just so you know off the top like that party has fielded
Candidates for office that are not Muslim
It's naughty
Uniquely strictly Muslim
Party
Anti certainly not
According to an article in Deutsch
Well
From 2050
The UFM
Dee is an attempt
Combat islamophobia
B A by encouraging young Muslims
To get engaged
With a
Go process
The article spoke to a 28 year-old woman who's involved in the party who stressed that getting involved
In this sort of activity is
Important impart
It's an important part of quote
Showing that we are not like them
Referencing ice
In the article sociology
Just named Pietra
Reflect on the party and notes that there is
Is little chance
The making real strides and Regional election
But
Quote the fact they Embrace their attached
Secularism
And the French
Republic
Can help Indy demonizing Muslim
As their people
Appear in the media and get better now they'll be seen in a
Way
I don't know how much of this article proves that the government is
Admitting that there's hundreds and hundreds
The no-go Zone
But it definitely doesn't appear that that is the thrust
Does the article
I feels like this might just be the spin that's put on it by Breitbart
And then exaggerated by Alex
And in reality
I think that there's probably
Blade
Bigotry finest
So this article is referencing a document that hasn't been read
By anybody
That has alleged contents
And then
The article itself immediately goes
What's the polling
Suggesting that
In reality this is just where Muslims are
And
I'm not I'm not certain I mean like I don't know what this Secret
Classified document says
What is the article when talking about these
Areas that are quote-unquote held by islamist
It then immediately talks about this Union of French Muslim Democrats
So it seems to me that there might be some sort of
The connection between the definition of
Held by islamist
The USMD pulls well in this play
Play connection from the text
I'm not entirely sure I don't trust Breitbart or Alex
To spend on these sorts of issues
So whatever
I think this is just islamophobe
Yeah that sounds just
Be because
From here Alex just descended
Complete nonsense about Muslim
And I had Muslims repeatedly come up
When I was in d.c.
Listen
We're going to conquer you just lie
Like we talked her parents
On our way to start a conversation
Add
And
I guess this later but
Story
But I got a group of Muslim covertly messing with my wife
When I took round trip
What
Mess with me
I would mess with her
Crazy
But I was a really and that I caught one of them doing it and hotel
Doing what happened gaslighting
It's just incredible that I know how to not go frontal up against the man they mess with your woman
And it's really just it's disgusting for us
I don't believe a single part of the story and here's why
41 Alex seems to be trying to come up with a story
Here in his brain isn't so fat
Lastly just randomly cobbling together some b*******
Second he has no video of this yet his team was surrounding him with cameras the whole time he was in
DC
Third he says that Muslims are messing with his wife because they know not to go frontal and mess with the man but not 10 seconds
Prior you just said that Muslims repeatedly threatened
The Conqueror it while he was in
DC
What is it
Are they so bold that they openly threatened
To conquer the big strong Alex
Or are they so slow
Ricky that they dare not confront big strong Alex
But instead mess with his wife
This is so incoherent
But it makes total sense
If you look at it as just random bulshit Alex's making up to
To demonize Muslims
Cuz he
Whatever it is they're doing it
So I'm going to say they're doing this in this bad not say they're doing that and
Bad and it's all bad Dan
Reissue though is that
Like Islam is intolerant
Brave Christianity really don't think that's where we're going
This clip is really stupid
We need
Christianity
Are the answer unified Humanity together
Appreciate
Islam is not
By making it the world religion everyone
Globalism shows
The future
A weird globalist
Secular system
Is
Islam
It will be able to persecute whoever it wants
And the Beast the same time
Everything was Satan is a fraud and a contradiction
As you can see the whole thing
Clearly clearly interview
Really
The Beast of the horror rides
That's why the vatican's converted to Islam in
Remove
The Catholics are rejecting
Is a longer Catholicism that is in Rome
Idiots 100%
Satanic religion
Captured by the devil
Is a big get for Islam woowcool poker
Is like a baby priest
Good f****** he's like well it turns out you're a line with his love now realize that the Vatican and converted to Islam
That's that is a
The big guy
Tom Cruise and Scientology level get right there so dumb
So dumb
I mean all Alex is really expressing his basically he wants his weird version of Christianity to theocracy
Globally
So great what we need to unite humanity is my weirdo Christian today because that's so taller
That it will absolutely
Crush Islam if I didn't cut
Intolerant
One person who
Subscribe to Alex's religion and that's a lie
There's one word I would use to describe him
Taller taller
Just one of them like a
Beacon Thunder standings
And unity and Oneness
It's at
So amazing to me how intolerant everybody is and thank goodness for Alex
Pointed out to us in a very vicious and racist play total
It's amazing how intolerant everybody is get rid of them and smash them
Kaitlyn from the Earth
Cuz they're so intolerant
So he's descended into like a pretty stupid
Islamophobic
Chunk of his show right after he came back from break saying that you
Super angry
And
Are you saying those two things may be related
Feels like it
Okay I said I'll get to all the sudden I have
I'm just angry right now
Absolutely angry
Coveranything
Stop it
Just seem like
If you save this
Often enough
If you say often enough associate
Then you should buy now
Have a strategy to
I often feel like there's too much going on in the world and it's kind of overwhelming
I kind of deal with that especially someone who has a show and put out a product
Is that I just have to make peace
With the fact that we
Can't cover everything that's important right sucks
Because there is a lot of stuff that's going on in the world that does deserve attention sure that I feel like other shows are probably
Far more capable of doing that
Can I take a narrow Focus
And I really only cover the stuff that Alex brings up
And that allows me
To actually cover thing alright so you said supposed to be
Deeply deeply overwhelmed by
The stories that are going on in the world
All I can do is really like well Alex brought this up so here we go
Oh hey
Is there a patent for this
Coronavirus thing
I know this is a dumb qanon weirdo tweeted about this and it's a chicken vaccine
We're able to cover it
I would imagine what I showed be if you just open it up top with just
Alex said just too much for us to cover today
He just said too much for us to cover so let's bulshit for the first half hour 45 minutes
Maybe we'll get to something you said I have
7000 clip stacked up in my iTunes
Next hour in the next hour I'm going to go to 10 Clips or 10 clips
But
You got to fight you got to fight back against a dude
Do something
Can I drink
Part of that is because he knows how flimsy all of the
The thousand of new news stories that he needs to cover all that
Like you can't get in any greater depth
On that vaccine story because he knows that is soon as he does
It becomes clear the visit
He can't get in any greater depth about his
Complaints about the impeachment because it
If he does
He then has to address the fact that this is the Democrats opening
His lawyer is grandstanding whenever he says is he taking in any greater depth about how
Owen is being singularly persecuted because if he does it opens up
The possibility of recognizing when people do get
For this sort of thing
You can't get into a greater depth about the no-go zones in
In France because
He does this primary source that is
We're going back
Doesn't
Necessarily prove what he's talkin
You can't
He has to get overwhelmed by the amount of news
Because all he can deal with his this surf
Doll that it and that is overwhelming and I feel bad for him
I don't
I mean what he could really do is
Instead of having too much
He could take a few subjects
And really make up some good b*******
You're not you would have done that
15 years ago probably but he's old
He's tired and he's not good at this I guess I guess he's just trying to
To kill a little bit
Time is
Because you wait enough time
And you get to do stuff like this
So you come here legally and then you're producing
Immigration
Play John
I don't break
Didn't plug wants to shower we're not bringing in really any money right now we got
Two big sales running
I really need you to support us and get products you already needed to tell them when to just take action if you see him forward busting our butt
Killsometime get to a pimp
Get
So ever that's what I'm asking for some money discussion of like
Illegal undocumented
So Alex's wrestling when he gets back for
From commercial about Heather
Maybe said he was going to take
Calls or talk about news but he hasn't done any of it
Make calls today but I forgot mine on the news here
Water breaking news
Also the latest on the virus their hyping up he's really this Mega deadly threat
Eby
These dump
Could be a threat but there's more information that's needed to assess like the realities of it and all that stuff
Just if you can't you can't behave
Any issues of like
Serious Public Health
It's just
It's bad
The Trump and Greta stuff like who cares
It's like this is just
This is nonsense
Looks like Alex is only point is that like
She's not
Complaining about China
And the issue is that with her app
Perkasie you'd like through the UN filing
Complaint on the behalf of the children of
The number of countries
She can't
Complain about China they're not signed onto that treaty
RockAuto
That kind of
Falls apart
They complained of likewise itchy
Singling out China as opposed to
These countries that she has listed
There is no mechanism in place
Daytona has a sign that read
Very simple
Why am I not calling out China
Because they're not listen
I'm talkin
To you
So I'm not going
To talk to you about China
Anybody any f****** good
It's
It's everyday
Just so you know it's all China's fault I'm so mad at China so of course you guys
Should do everything
So Alex
He has
To address something
Because
It's something that Tucker Carlson talked about on his show
Otherwise I would probably just f****** ignore because you didn't want any part of
Brought it to the
The mainstream
Consciousness
And that is the fact that Trump
And his Environmental
Turn agency
Are rolling back restrictions and regulations
Shinzon atrazine
Write reports is the chemical that is turning the freaking frogs gay
Right
There have been in place
Restrictions on
An oversight regulation regulator
Testing of water pipelines in order
To have hard limits
It's on what
Come Out of Africa
In any
I drinking water
Right
But Trump is loosening those regulations will have the effect
Of leading to more
Prove that I am sure that private entities as always our will
Going to regulate themselves and
Keep problem that's not Alex's angle
Because Tucker Carlson is docked
About this and Tucker and Alex have a very
It's a Venn diagram that's a circle
Although Alex the circle as much
Smaller
Butts
V he has to address
You can't just
Sweep this under the carpet short and so he has to
Rationalize
But yeah there's no perfect way to stop this we just got to take action
A lot of chemicals
They don't even the same class as bad as atrazine
Crump has
Lucian.
Restrictions on
Bazine when they've been Crackdown on
He just saw everything the Democrats will restrict
Week
So like I said addressing the chemical it's behind the moment that most
People probably know Alex for the turning the freaking frogs gay rant
Obviously Alex doesn't understand the science behind the effects of atrazine pollution but we've gotten into that in the past
More important
Thing here is that you know after seeing is not a chemical that
Good for people
Go to be exposed to in large quantity
Not going to turn people gay like Alex mites
Suggesting all the available evidence seems to suggest that he's over blowing the dangers of it
But I feel like no pollution is good pollution so what are
All agree that we should regulate the hell out of these
Pesticides and herbicides
So they're only use the proper
Alex
Agree with that
You shouldn't
Is no way to put
This chemical is a gigantic part of Alex
His career
And now he's gyro King Trump
That is presiding over an EPA that wants to loosen regulations that experts say could increase
Atrazine
Contamination in water wave by up to 50
Percent
Another interesting move on the EPA part is that they adjusted the amount of
The chemical that's
Considered safe for human
To make easier for pollution
Contigo en punta
The amount they decided on is taken straight from the primary Factory manufacturer of atrazine
Syngenta
The company that makes it
Made a suggestion EPS followed that suggestion
As the EPA just finally admitted to changing its name to
To be Environmental
Destruction age
Environmental
This is
Same much like bolsonaro attacking depressed surprise for any
Of course would thought Trump would sell out the safety and protections enjoyed by all the little p
People in the country to benefit a large busy
That's what he's into
He's made it super
Everclear
Alex can't ignore this one
Tucker Carlson talked about it
And after seeing is Alex's /
A hero to be doing the opposite of fighting
Against a well that's a problem
Trump not further restricting atrazine
Further implying to Alex's.
He doesn't know or doesn't care about the
Does chemical
Which I guess is the angle Alex is going with
That seems like a really sad spin
The best Alex can do is say that you have the Democrats are pushing regulations on ton of stuff so Trump
Didn't even look into the thing
They were regulating and just said about on doing all of this
That's what a child
Alex's describing
An idiot
Being in charge of the country
And not for nothing
Alex is also being very clear that the Democrats were the ones who were doing what he wanted
Which is to limit atrazine use
This is true
Going back to the food quality protection Act of 1996
Which Bill Clinton signed into law
That was about creating safety standards or pesticide
Particularly aimed at protecting
Children's Health
Here we have a chemical that Alex believes is a part of a giant globalist
Attack on the public and it feminizing the Benz of the can of Western Civilization or whatever and what we find
We find Alex
Does big enemy Bill Clinton signing legislation to restrict
It is hero Trump
Pushing to rollback these regulation
Expose more people to it
And the best Alex can come up with his Dad
The drop is just
Now he's exposing everyone two dangerous chemicals because the Democrats didn't want him
Who's pathetic
Even at the propagandas this is just the weakest s*** ever yeah
This
The the Trump years and
The last
Aubameyang
Really
Changed
For too long during Obama's years
I was I defend
You know like with why did he close down Guantanamo Bay
Well these are the political realities of the time and he's got to spend his Capital this way
And this
This whole thing with Trump and looking
Can Alex turning into this f******
Weak Toady b*******
I just realized it now there's no defending the president
F*** him if he's if the president is doing some b*******
Then it doesn't matter what
Team Iran
F****** get on it
I'd still on the president
I think that there I think that there are different
I think that there's a difference
Tween recognizing
Political realities and making excuses
It's sometimes a gray
Think I think I think that there is sometimes a little bit of
661 half dozen of the other
You know I understand that but
I don't disagree with the point that you're making
But I also think
That
Take him to the
Extreme that argument is
An untenable wave
Lead to a
Sweetly
Piranha like infection
Throwing bricks
F*** you
I just read that it is a smart idea for us to have a
Baseline adversarial relationship with our government regardless of whether or not it is the
We have voted in
They need to be held to the
Fire at
All f****** type single moment that adversarial nature needs
To be tempered with
A collaborative
Spiritual
It has to be otherwise
Otherwise
It's incredibly out of
Cancel course
But yeah
Point point well-taken
I still think
Even whatever your
Describing about your path in the time where you were
Making excuses for Obama has nothing
In relationship with Alex is like
Really just escaped that
Concept in Thai
Is the same that you know it
It's revealing how silly it is to go
To make it
Excuses
At all
Do you know I'm saying this is where you f******
With his rambling about how it's okay that he's putting this chemical that I'm spent my entire
Bakery railing ago
Into the water it's not okay
But the reason he's doing it is B
Because he's just a post
Everything the Democrats
So he's
That's even worse
That implies
Did Trump's decision making process
Sweetly reactionary and it's completely
F****** what they want
And that to me is like
You're describing then a bad thinking pass
That leads to decision
That may be right or maybe wrong
Process
And therefore everything is
Yeah yeah end ended
It's good that it bad
Is borne out by
It does seem like literally everything that Obama did is
Is exactly what Trump is trying to untie
Seems Seems like as a pattern
But it's important to recognize that address
It's shrinking dick
There's just no way around
The last 70 years or so that was in the water
The genitals this is a
Uterine
Development of the
Where males slowly are having their genitals waste away until soon
Men are going to have genitals the size of a woman's clitoris
In about two generations
If you like your son's not having a car
Then you're going to love
Trump is getting rid of American Cox and then we got a chicken vaccine and a cop killer
This is
Is the family show if you like your children having dick
Or whatever boys are weird
I looked into a little bit and there are
Some instances
Is of like genital malformation they can be attributed
To potentially attributed atrazine exposure
But what I think Alex has been
Mistaken because it's not a giant issue that is noted
From mattress
I think he's mixing up
Congenital
And genital I think he's mixing up that with the word congenital and thinking it means
Askew
That does not
Right
This is all it takes to wipe out dicks on to the play
That's surprising
So we're in a serious situation
Alex
Besides
Time
Send a message
Trump director the show
Talk about this
As well
Because really it's a message the light off
I got the White House reach out through a lot of people
Save-A-Lot
Legacy auto parts
Because all the phones are tapped
Location of myself is down
The Russian as well
BFDI but it is edipi
Juan Capistrano
They obviously know I'm not a Russian understand what's happening
Don't want I don't need
Call me
I don't need Trump dead
Have other journals contact me to the present wanted to thank you and
We appreciate you and appreciate what you're doing
Don't need to be pat on the head like a
Donald Trump when he calls me
I need action from the president
Bolt action
We need to get on the offensive
We need to indict the Deep state
We need to indict
Deptford
Racketeering
Surprise
And that ended ever
We have
The authoritarians are the danger
President Trump
What do we want them
2 Generations
Pomp and Circumstance
What about the song
That's all I'm asking for
And I know you're giving this action on so many fronts
I'm just simply telling you
What people want
What's right
But we need to see happen
Who can take action
The fusion of the Republic 1776 and real Christianity
Not fake
In-your-face Pharisees a holier-than-thou stuff is I love God
Take action and I know you do too let's do it together
Buying products infowarsstore.com and sign up for auto-ship learning support
Now
This raises a really interesting question and that is was that add pivot part of the message to the White House I'm pretty sure it
Cuz if you do it in the same way that like when you're praying it doesn't end until you say Amen
He didn't even put
You like it that still seems like a
Message to the White House
You need to get our great products
While you're wearing a diaper nothing keeps you from getting your pants
That's quite like lights
How many distillate also does raise the question of like why isn't Trump giving them a bunch of money
But he clearly has no
Has never
Ever
Ever given anyone money right but to the to the
Like the viewers who believe in everything Alex is saying
Obviously Trump is corrupt
The shed
He would not have any problem with like R8 Alex and you two million dollars in your job
You get the Ukraine military
Through some sort of busy
Hiding money
I did
And I think that actually is kind of like
The way that activity structured it really does kind of draw tents
To the fact that I
Yeah
Wait
I'm not a right-wing billionaires give
Tons of money
Why would you ever have problems
Money-wise
Billionaires are notorious for their loyalty
Billionaires are noted for when you stop being used
Spell for them
For them taken care of you for the work that you
They may be much maybe
Sometime around
Don't know
So earlier Alex was talking about about the deck
And receive
Trump is getting rid of America
Alex Jones says
Trump is shrinking American Dick's put that on right wing watch
Now
But I was talked a little bit more about this afternoon situation I think you can really see like the mechanic
Behind what he's doing
In this clip
Apologize to Corn farmers and tell him that
You noticed it for
Farmers Mills areas have a lot of cancers lot of problems and
Your daughter can't have children
Anderson
Can't have sex if they don't have genitals
Lightly the detachable Donuts
Get reported
But you know what
Wonder why
He had a good side job
Concorso scary bunny
Don't do this
Still not good for your liver
Bioaccumulate
In the corn
The water table and it stays there
4 years
The same time
You got well water 11 anywhere near farming
You are
Insane
If you don't use
Gravity
That takes out
All the bad chemicals in the highest rated
Filtration system to find out there
This is a perfect example
Situation
The reason for this is that he doesn't appear to be saying
Accurate thing
In order to make his farmer listeners scared of their water
Then offering them a solution
For a price
All the stuff Alex seems to be getting
About Dick shrinking like I said I think
I had to gansett to not understanding what congenital mean
Yeah that sounds
Think that's
I think that's what's going on you want your kid to have a dick well then you better get this
Walking water filter I think you just as misunderstanding words in the rain
Anything about them
From the data I've seen from like the NIH there are some very small indications of possible genital deformations can I
Make a diet Racine exposure but it's near the top
Concern related issues for example are far more common
The big giveaway that I was just talking
Come sit here is that he says that after seeing bioaccumulate
This is not true
According to the age
Toxic Subs
Disease registry
3A division of the Department of Health and Human Services
If Youmans taken atrazine it is quote primarily excreted in the urine
And quote
Some atrazine and its metabolites might enter the organs or fat tissue but they do not buy with cumulate or buildup
Or remain in the cube
Body so not only do they not
Call man
Not even like a little bit
So that's within the human
Body though
What about
The corn that Alex is talking about
From the same report by the 80s
HDR in their section about atrazine in the environment
Quote
Atrazine does not tend to buy a week
Another report
Put up by the 80s.
Doesn't buy to accumulate in fish
End quote little
Food chain accumulation of atrazine has been observed
It does not tend to bioaccumulate
A 2014 paper put out by the Journal of environmental science and pollution research
Compromise
Of identifying a person
Circular green microalgae
They have the trait of actually accumulating atrazine it and then biodegrading it
Within itself
This is interesting
Does most plants don't behave that way and this would be a way of
Cleaning up
Places that have
Atrazine pollution
Atrazine is a chemical with a fairly short half-life
Between 14 and 109 days in the
When it says the human body is only detectable for approximately Forty-Eight Hours
It's flushed out really quick
None of this is to say that it's perfectly safe for doesn't still pose a risk for
Particularly
In utero Shrek the story that Alex is telling us specifically not true
Atrazine is a chemical that researchers have found is not prone
Bioaccumulation
He's saying that it is
Or as I call
Lion
Because it creates a
Problem for his list
These listeners
Well then have a reaction
I'm getting scared of their water
It's going to make their sons have no text
And there is Alex
The perfect solution
This giant water filter
City sells
Alex talks all the time about the globalist using the hegelian dialectic
Where they create a problem
To cause a reaction in the public so they could be there with
The solution to the problem
They themselves have created
It turns out
It is also a very apt way to describe Alex's own
Miss Molly
Well I mean if they're doing it
I don't know if they are
All the time now
Yes in the context of Alex's own sales
Those practices it seems like all liquor
Anyway
Sew-ins next clip
Alex says talking about having a breakthrough
I'm quick when
Right this is filter even filter out
The chemical table
You think so
Probably won't I think that I looked into it quite a while back but it seems like the filters
Play really good
It's a third party that makes me feel better
I know Alex isn't f****** backs basket weaving
Everything to about this is like these are
Big f****** purchase
If he's talking about a farmer getting one of these
Like these water filters
Swinging for the fences in terms of like
Big Ticket items to get big ticket items up
The Shelf
Imagine they take up a lot of space in the warehouse
These are so I can't get anymore
Please art on the Shelf is it as he gets a cut for any sales that the filter bli
So Alex gets talking about the impeachment
Brighten air brakes are about why the impeached
It's happening
If you listen carefully
You might miss it
If you're not paying attention
Little subtle plug for his coffee
Something really hit me
During the break I was
Back there in the coffee room I've been busier than that little bit more today cuz I do mostly positive town I'm exhausted
You just have maybe two cups by now my life
Number for this wave America Coffee
Libertarian I was so delicious
Everybody
Very subtle
Watching Adam Schiff
Bed bug
Obstacle course
The grass is green next
All the reasons they keep nice impeachment going and the fake investigations going all of it is
To change the subject
For what losers they are in other cities are collapsing and how corrupt they are now able they are
All the time and energy to be the center of attention
Is there racing to dig up more fake dirt
Okay
But the length of the trial is already
Right
I guess that means we're done
I don't care
I don't I don't
But like these aren't even do thoughts
He's talking about this is a breakthrough these pigs out all the time
Fourth cup
That's almost as much as I drink
So this is our last clip and it's Alex talking about the impeached
Spencer Moore
I really
Thought when I
Came in on this episode
I really thought there was a
A good likelihood that
This was going
To be a real break
Like a real freak out his hero is actually having the trial in the Senate
For impeachment
Right but then
When he said this I realize like
Course he's not going he's not even going to talk about it at the most part
Oxygen out of the room
The impeachment very much with the trial
Chapter
I will cover that
So I'll just go
Can I cover the Republicans
Pretend all the others
Advance
To know that there are going to be
Very
Very biased coverage of my show
Village of Andy Daly podcast pilot project whatever is left
Whatever he's doing the
Character it is just like
The prosecution should be allowed to say anything here's how the trial works I get
Get my defense you guys say I didn't do it and then we go home what do you mean the prosecution prosecution
Miscarriage of Justice even have the prosecution
Why they allowed to talk
Yeah
Yep yep
I thought work so anyway I don't expect it to be very fertile pastures for us
What's 2
Cover Alex is coverage of the
The impeachment so
That might be a might free up some time and
Make it much less of a priority
Talk about the present day
Also on the other hand it makes
It would be
It's almost even more damning just to listen to the Republican debate
Just because of what could they
Possibly have other than
It's a deep state conspiracy
It's the cover basically all I hear is him just advocating any kind of
Responsibility to address points that are brought up by non
Nunez
Trump's lawyers Jim Jordan
Pipes
Doesn't want it doesn't want to address any kind of thing that's
It's not already
Implicitly and intrinsically on his side
So great
Enjoy
What's the definition of being in a bubble
Socrate Alex have fun with
That it's a good thing
The most
Important thing here is that I enjoyed
Is the
The Narrative about this
Institute with the chicken vaccine
I can't that it turned out to be a chicken vaccine
And it's just
I can't stress enough like these
Did Alex present
As narratives
Almost always
Without fail you just look into them a little bit more
And you end up finding that he knows nothing about what he's talkin about it's all just b*******
Like this and the Texas said domestic terrorism threat
Not like they're just to prime example
Of
Him trying to make hay out of b*******
Laughable this is just sad s***
The how anybody
Confused them or ever
Confuse them with a
Actual journalist
Mind-boggling because they're fun
Does on people
I mean
It will ya
Get you in with the yelling about gay frogs or laughing before you know I do like
Maybe wrong about everything it's literally not possible to be wrong about everything I do
Right it turns out it is
Is literally possible to be wrong about every
Does he know why
The backyard on Monday but until then we website
Facebook we are on Twitter
Please go to iTunes download leave a review.
Until then I'm Bo score, chicken vaccine