Important
I have great respect for knowledge by now I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Sit around drink novelty Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones Jordan
Have you ever gone on a bed
Diets
Did you ever do one of those like all-meat things or only protein geyser
Caveman not so much I had some
Inclination
Towards the keto diet a while back
Yeah I read
Some stuff about it and I thought it
Seemed interesting
What's a keto diet
Do you like have carbs way down my body goes into key
Ketosis
The theory behind it
I don't know I don't honestly don't know enough about it
Cuz I didn't really go full-on with
I thought about it
I went
Dabbled towards it by way of like restricting carbs a bad thing
I had a buddy who lives in LA but used to
You come to here in Chicago who lost
Dwayne got really healthy and he swore by
Okay it's sort of made me
Me feel like that maybe there's something
More to this but I never went full-on with it
But that that did
That was a really effective
Strategy not so much going
Olan
Limiting carb
Intake
Was something that I found some
Some success with I don't know I mean I guess that's with a k
Cans diet is right
Anything about it
To be a fad but I do know that I had
Pretty decent success
We're not cutting out all carbs but limiting it
Exercising a bed
More water
That's
I saw a lot of problems a little bit
I thought I still had a lot of problems though because I am
Really not a diet
Petition
And so my obsession with
Like alright well we're go
Is low calories as possible I didn't know where the lick
Nutrient
How much of a
XYZ
So it didn't
It didn't ultimately end up being a good diet I did have
It was effective in losing some weight
Might be very on
The way I operate whenever I went on the I'm only going to eat one frozen pizza a day
Diet witch
Baby
Alright
And I've actually been giving some consideration to like needing to
Tweaks app to my
That my eating
Currently but
I think based on my experience with the last time I realized I'm very stupid
So I'm considering it
By will see what happen
No fat diet
Don't know much about diets or food
Or how to be healthy
But I do know that
And I don't know much about
Correct
Jordan
Today we are still in the present
Okay we are
Nothing
What's going on
Today we are going over January 24th 2020
To give you some sense of where this episode is going to go
I have to play this out of concerts drop before we even think we will find out no where
Things are calling
It's over for Humanity
It will only be lone survivors
Mike Adams is.
Declaring it
Over that is a
That's the straw
That's a strong Proclamation and trust me I know that clip is out of context but I didn't cut
About him saying it would be stupid for me to sit before he declares humanity is gone
Example of something that somebody
Is humanity is wildly irresponsible Proclamation
For a pretend elf expert
Would be to say that snow he is
He is declaring it
Dog
Humanity
Great time we had we we
Anyway we'll get there but before we do you take a moment to say thank you
Who signed up and supporting the show
Appreciate it even though
Broadway Matthew thank you so much you are now policy walk
I'm a policy wonk I'd rather you sorry about the bad news
What's next Christian thank you so much you're now about to walk
Next SOL SOL
Like the sun you're going to explode
Text Nick thank you so much you and I hope all is well
I'm sorry to
Do all of your loved one
Steven thank you so much you're now policy want
Thank you Steven
Giving up on it
Alright
Jimothy
Timothy with a j
And finally likes a thank you took of people who donated on elevated level appreciate that very much so
Timothy with
But he's not a j
Like jimothy but with a t
Thank you so much you are now a technocrat and Christopher with a K thank you so much you are now a technocrat
Heroin
Freakishly large
Timothy M Crist
Hey Humanity's done
But I like this show and I like smoothies dance to
Appreciate it
You can't take it with you
So you might as well just donate a little I just realize that every single time I say
You can you click that button
Just work the show Aida pantomime at all
Completely subconscious did not even realize I was doing that
Anyway Today's Show is very weird
If you didn't get that from
They're in a good head space
Man
No one's doing good today this is good this is such a weird show
Mike Adams is way out of line
Alakazam
And then we get the return of someone who is missing
And presumed
Dad I don't know we have not heard from in a very long time
Open house phone
I don't want to ruin
Surprise I have bad news.
Is still dead
I'm no but the Alex starts the show off
With the Special Report
It's like what the f*** is going on
It's like 10 minutes into the show
Still do special reports
The first
20 minutes of the show
Special Report
Alex finally get some
Studio he's playing
Couldn't do the show
Reading all the news all the information
This is probably one of the first
First time
I just fed
Physically could not go on air at start the broadcast
It really just comes a time when
The world just going to have to be judge
And
Tell you what I really think about things as because I respect
But
We're not going to get away
Boarding Williams babies
And not doubting him alive
And watching China the model of where people don't value human life
And watch that
Become the global
Standard
Multinational corporations who are Beyond solace
And not pass
The lab some feta
And so that's where all this is going
So we have tomorrow and pauses and they're only got Alex a real f*****-up Moody goodnight do is reading articles about Dumbo
Bulshit right and apparently
Like
This is not doomsday preaching this is the Doomsday is here
You know I ever
I went to a psychiatrist when I was depressed
I did feel like the world is ending dead but I didn't broadcast those feelings to 100.
I should tell you Alex
Does get a form of therapy on the 10th
Prediction Doomsday
Hey stop this is like we're in it
Where in it has to do with the Wuhan Coronavirus
Be able to assume we're already like
We've got a bunch of confirmed cases
Up to this point I believe her over a couple of thousand
You know we're getting
Rightsure now
Means that the world is that Humanity's done
Absolutely it's got a long way to go before it
All of us that's all
Innn
You know it it's
It's fun to joke around and make fun of Alex
But at the same time I do think that you know the outbreak is not a laughing matter it's something that should be taken
Pretty serious by the people who are experiencing
Another people in in China
Are going through some
I'm not I'm not chastising you for laughing
What I'm saying is like
It's a delicate balance to walk
Of like making fun of Al
Alex while respecting the situation
And
I apologize in advance if we walk that line
Alex's red
Some
Not about the impeachment apparently not about any of that stuff yet
I don't know his thoughts on that
Has really come up about it
Dems are talking about going with their proof
So Alex has
Seen some videos on Twitter I believe
Might be the exception
Is a fake is a bird
All that might be the extent of his
And now there
Driving around in China with a giant
Fumigator
Popping out chemicals
Hoping to kill
The virus
The government is using it
For a police state authoritarian
Enforcement drill
You know really the big takeaway from this year's
Infowars
Not the ticket
Help absolutely with Phil
Articles in Gadsden
PowerPoint presentations
Thousands of times the tailed exactly what you see beginning unfold
In
With the Coronavirus
Melinda Gates
Few months ago about a big drill
For something similar to this weekend
65 million people starting in China
So first things first I want to reiterate
Stress that
I'm going to say is to apply this is not a serious health issue
Did you be a high priority
All I can do is go on the word of experts
And this does not
This does seem like a situation where there's a potential for things to go
Pretty badly
But even with that said it's so wrong for Alex be doing this doomsday preacher
I understand that that's his bread and butter it and without pay
He doesn't really make money
But this is the sort of subject or coverage like this could really get people hurt
Whether it's from discouraging people from taking appropriate
Health steps
Or from feeding into a generalized panic
The director-general of the World Health Organization gave a press conference
According to them quote
This is an emergency in China
But it is not yet become a global Health Emergency
It may yet become one
I feel it's important
Good perspective
And express our concern for the people of China and demand action to protect them as best
As possible
While taking steps
To keep the odds low that the virus does
Become a global Health Emergency
Another thing that's important to point out is that at the
The time of Alex's episode the death toll from the Coronavirus
Was it 70
And the World Health Organization is commented the most of those deaths quote occurred in patients
Pre-existing health conditions
This isn't to say that it's no big
Big deal but it is to say that there's a lot of uncertainty
Right now
And using out-of-context numbers can be really irresponsible thing to do
Especially when you're driving people towards
Conclusions like what Alex
Yeah it's a struggle to
Listen to him because what he's talkin
Think about is
Fictional
So when we laugh at that we're we're laughing in his fictionalized Universe of what's going on you know we're not laughing
The reality of
The circumstance
That is correct interpretation
Like a line of respectful or
Respectful but
When do we get into making fun of reality versus
Important to point that out a little bit I
Because because I think could be easily misinterpreted as
Sick dark
Humorous
Of course
Do in response to the outbreak China put the city of Wuhan
On where the virus is believed originated on lock
That city alone is home to 11 million people in this lockdown was later extended to
Surrounding areas
And at the time of the writing
King of the disciples
The preparation
Is covering an area of about 56 million people
The World Health Organization and representatives is like Human Rights Watch has been some comments about this not being a great thing to do
We've discussed in the past that makes
Intuitive
They quarantined would be what you do
But most experts will tell you that it's an ineffective way to deal with Public Health
Piccalilli when you're dealing with large Geographic areas or large groups of people
It turns out that it's nearly impossible to quarantine quarantine on a large
Scale effect
That being said there isn't a whole lot of the World Health Organization can do
If that's the strategy the China has chosen
Pursuit
So there's
There's differences of opinion
Yeah you can advise them but
Remember there.
Another thing to keep in mind is that in recent days the number of reported cases has jumped
Considerably
We're just cause some people to lean towards panic
However to cook the Associated Press
The rapid increase in reported deaths and illnesses does not necessarily mean the crisis
This is getting worse
It could instead reflect a better monitoring and Reporting
King of this newly discovered virus
Also China's not the most trustworthy player in the
So it does make sense to maintain a position to Skeptics
Given their government
The cover-up of the
Beginning of the 2,000
To SARS outbreak
But it's important
Keep that as a position of skepticism
Not a blind confirmation of the worst-case scenario pasa
What I'm trying to get out as there's a lot of like
Real
Complicated element
Let's do this
It in terms of like yes there's a lot more cases of it but that
Could not be a bad sign be a neutral
Sign
China could be
Giving
False numbers
They might not be
Right but they could be in advance
That's the case what does that mean
You don't know what that
Alex doesn't know what that means
Even people commenting on it who have
Backgrounds in this
Don't necessarily know exactly the conclusion
To drop right
Whatever you want to do if you want to approach this with a with a like
China they're bunch of liars got to be worse than this
It's
You can have that
Concerned are you can have that suspicion
But
It doesn't Merit leap into whatever conclusion of like
We're all going to die
No and and that
Conclusion is actively harmful
Yes now so many people are going to experience any kind of sim
And they're going to go and they're going to fill up a
As many hospitals
What is possible possible
That's impossible
Happens whenever you stoke this
It's kind of panic and there are plenty of hospitals now where it's
It's like I literally would they literally have to scream everybody
There are in that area so
It's a yeah it's a lot a lot of work
That's going to
I
Maybe not even Venus
Yeah but there was a video that made the rounds on Twitter of a vehicle driving on the street supposedly in Shanghai
Hi friend quotes
Confector
I have real difficulty with this
Because I can find that video on Twitter but I have no idea when it was shot if it was actually Shanghai who shot the video
It's very difficult to tell at all what's going on
The Washington examiner mentions this video
He may have to say that it quote
Purports to show workers spraying sidewalks in parks
With an unidentified
Disinfectant
I'm really not sure what to do with that video but I definitely understand how the Optics of it or right in Alex's wheelhouse
I'm not surprised
See him making a huge deal out of it and
Instead of reporting
Responsibly
Initially I had no idea what I was talking about with
The Bill and Melinda Gates
Extral
I have to assume that it's just
Kind of made up
Cuz at least I did
The first cuz I couldn't find anything about it anywhere like I looked through the Infowars website I didn't find that you search for Bill Gates
Nothing nothing comes up
Yeah there is an inch
Interesting reality behind
Okay
On my pass through this though I should point out that it's fun to go through some of the headlines Alex's posted about Bill Gates over the
Here's one from 2016 quotes
Did Bill Gates create the zika virus
Horror from 2017 quote Bill Gates
Retton's world with biological weapon Menace
Seems like Alex kind of just done for after he created
Zika virus
Alex Cottages does this whenever there's public health related story it's always Bill Gates
Weather weapons he's a super villain write the whole thing
It took me awhile to get to the bottom of this but it turns out that this is something that Alex found on a Blog written by a guy named Michael Snyder
There's also an article written by Kellin mcbreen on Alex's side about this week
Create was pretty difficult to find
Cuz his sight is unnavigable
That website that article by Kevin mcbreen is basically just a copy and paste job from
Snyder's article
It came out the day after the
Schneider blog post about it
The name of his blog is the economic collapse
And I should tell you that Michael Schneider is a bit of a nut
He used to be a frequent guest on Infowars but now you can more commonly find him on the Jim Bakker Show
In fact he has even hosted his own show on Jim Baker's Network
It should give you the first clue uni
Need to deduce that Michael Snyder is a doodoo super into ranting about the end time
That sounds right
His website the economic collapse
Collapse blog
Include the set of Link
The tell you everything you need to know about this a******
In addition to the standard survival food sales companies and gold and silver sales
Chicks website
Where you can buy all of the chicks
Attract
Which IBEW don't know her little cartoon books little comic books that are designed to terrorize children into fundamentalist Christian
If you to hell
Anyone
To Jack Chick
Is a f****** a******
With no reservation whatsoever
He's earned that reputation
Snyder's got a list of failed predictions way too long
How to get into right now but suffice it to say he's a guy who's really leaned into pretending he hasn't been wrong a million
And so is Alex
Despite this dude constant doomsday shift failing
To come through
Alex still considers him a worthwhile source
Which is not surprising at all because Alex has no
Standards
Soap
This story here out of Michael Snyder's website has the headline quote
A high-level exercise conducted
Three months ago showed that the coronavirus pandemic could kill 65 million people
Before I get into what's actually discussed in the article it's important to point out that the article also
Contains this paragraph
I find it
Quite interesting that the Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation was involved
Because they're also Financial backers of The Institute that was granted a US patent for an attenuated coronavirus in November
Number 28 chickens
This article is using the Hulk story about the
The pier Brighton
In terms of building up their article
Which is indicative of what
Quality in the work he
It's really just indicative of an operation to void of Standards just trying to push the
Propaganda cause panic
To be clear that paragraph did contain a hyperlink
So at least there's no providing a citation
I followed that through and found the exact same patent the qanon weirdo Jordan sather was tweeting out
Analysis reporting on our last episode
It's all just a chicken vaccine
Steamship
As for the actual meat of the article
It's about an alleged event
That's called event
Okay events 2015 /
Okay it took place on October 18th and simulated it Coronavirus
And it said was meant to explore various
Responses
Alex said that their simulation involved virus starting in China
But according to Michael Snyder
Who is absolutely his source
The virus in the simulation
Started in Brazil
This is trademark Allen
He can't stop himself replying
He can't stop himself from massaging details to make things fit his narratives more clothes
It's not enough that this drill just happen
Pendant simulated a Coronavirus
Outbreak
It has to have started in the same place as the coronavirus originated in the real world
If the simulation matches the real world
It strengthens
Perception that the simulation was the
Plan for the real world
Which is why he lies like
So disappointed
Because it's so
It's even better if
You tell the truth if it does simulation
Was tried in Brazil and it didn't go the way they wanted it to
You can you can turn that into even better propaganda
He's so lazy
So honestly beyond that I don't think there's anything suspicious
About this event 201
It was a get-together people with different egg
Expertise has
Which was hosted by the Johns Hopkins
Center for Health
Security
These experts basically at a symposium where they discuss their reactions to hypothetical pandemic event
Like I said that they had set up
They represented people for business field governmental organizations and ngos the latter of which
Is why there was representative from the Bill and Melinda Gates Oregon
Who was involved
You can go to the website for the Center for Health safety and watch the Inn
Entire thing
I watched most of it last night
Really good people talk about the implications of a developing emerge
And how their field to be
Inclined to respond
I watch a bunch of it and I got to say I like
This stuff
It's like if you take away the fact that there is a real-world how crisis going on right now
This would be fun
Basically yeah there was
Casa the Columbia Aeronautics and Space
Association of Realtors
I think was part of my
Gifted program or whatever we had
Like they we went and did a space shuttle launch simulation
That would that was such a fun day I'm 35 and I still remember it
Naked in this thing that they did with the Johns Hopkins
They even like they hired actors
The film news reports to play throughout Parks and Recreation at all of the people
Except for like the ones were involved in
Like the actual order
Malaysian I had no idea what
What do you like to do
We're going to be in there to roll with it
God dammit
It's a live-action role-playing
Basically I am also
Should point out
A lot of these people are not really into role-playing or anything so you can see the clear discomfort in them trying to put
Tampa situation
Ability to act
Mexico
American State Bank
Alright expert will still responded in a situation like this
Past
Anyway if you go to their YouTube page you can find videos their past exercises like this
Like in May 2018 when they did this
Exact same exercise with a slightly different hypothetical disease
You can also find plenty of other videos of confer
Prince's wear these sorts of issues are disgusting
Slightly different prison
Temptation just like speakers giving
A lot of it comes down to discussing questions that may not come up in your normal thought process
What would
If your role playing an outbreak with a bunch of experts
Different field
Like you bounce things off I call I hadn't considered
What the business
Response
Your field has thoughts and concerns that mine doesn't
We can better help a coordinated approach
If we get together and pretend
Yeah it just makes that they should have had a representative from right-wing weirdos Woo's
We set the southern border on fire the whole thing it's just a 20 ft tall Flame
From one side of the country to the other
So how are we going to get people okay so now we got to help break and arson
Is it suspicious Jordan that they use the coronavirus as the hypothetical Out Boy
Break and now there's a coronavirus cuz we've had coronavirus outbreaks in the past so it would make sense to mod
In the past 18 years there been two major outbreaks of Coronavirus
With SARS in 2002 in Mercer in 2012
The host of the event when
She's giving a speech setting everything up even points out they wanted
How to create a scenario for the expert
The disgust that was realistic
If that's your goal coronavirus is a great candidate to base your hypothetical disease on
And honestly from the perspective of the
Conspiracy theorist
That detail doesn't even really matter of fact that it's Coronavirus
It's a Tuesday bolos that hypothetical disease
Alexander's Elkwood
Just be advancing the same narratives about the medical plan meeting for a pandemic
Get cold if it was a virus and they just do it the
The same
It probably sounds like I'm doing a bit of hand-waving here like I who cares but honestly this doesn't rise anywhere close
To being above like
The level of
For me
This is a public health organization that was holding a panel discussion
It's centered around a hypothetical pandemic
That's what they do
The hypothetical pandemic they chose the Coronavirus
Which makes sense as a candidate for them to use
According to discussion in their EX
Exercise the World Health Organization
Deals with approximately 200 outbreaks
Every year
Many of them small and localized to the point where we never even
I hear about them
They're able to do that work
Effectively and save people's lives
Lives because they train
Because they do things like this exercise
Disaster preparedness for larger more dangerous situation
All that is is just
I mean
I know this sounds like
I don't know
A cop-out but
This is just timing
Yeah this is just a coincidence
Sense of timing
Training was in October
Yeah
Okay that makes perfect
I mean
Imagine that they would do something like this at least twice a year so
You would never be more than 6 months away if I do not think that they do any year
Maybe maybe I don't I don't deserve
I don't think it's that frequent
But from what I'm
Understand it's not a hole
Leon comment
Nothing
For them
How to do a far enough away from a training of
Meant for it to matter though
No Indiana considered
Is one in a line of training event that goes probably many that we don't know about the car
Much more localized smaller like
The coordinating state and city responses as opposed
To government and international business
Sci-fi typing
You could do
You could make this argument oh they had a meeting about this
You know they had a
Play an exercise you can probably make that anytime
You'd just be a matter of digging
To find
The example
I find
Nothing suspicious
For Alex
Proof
That's so f****** annoying that
There are so many out
Breaks that are
Handled because these people are incredibly competent
Then you do here about 1 and
These
Lunatics go out
They're like these people have no idea what they're doing and
Or they're actively trying to kill us all even though it's like we have
Mountains upon mountains of evidence
What's that
It's
Good chewing
A good job it's a sincere bomber
So Alex talked a little more about this
Exercise
Have you like
The bench will be used
Melinda Gates
Foundation Zone
To bring in world government
So the Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation didn't say they're planning was to bring it world government
The conclusion of the exercise wasn't even that there should be world government
Kevin mcbreen article Alex's reading doesn't even say that
The conclusions reached by the exercise were largely around government and international business recognising the need to work together to avert crisis
I know Alex thinks that any kind of international collaboration that doesn't involve Trump doing something weird counts as world government
But this is just weak
Oh also
One of the goals they recognized as being important in the exercise is quote
Governments and private sector should assign a great greater priority
To developing methods
Combat Miss and disinformation prior to the next pandemic response say that would probably be a smart idea
Are the Galaxy's basically making their case for surround Alex Jones
Right right
Halex darts like getting into like
But you can tell he didn't do the first half hour of the show he's coming in weird
He's talking doomsday is here type shyt going to be on later and say that humanity is done
Like we're in
A f*****-up Place yeah I can only assume that the lawsuit is going well
I think we're going to go with it that baby
That might be coloring some of this perception
But
Because he's in the state news like what pandemic here
Humanity is going to die
You know cuz we're cuz of cuz of abortion
Inspiron minutes divine retribution
Instead of being like
Everyone go to the hills or exactly what you're
Normal person
Please respond to this would be
Just wait to die Alex's response
What is
I called it
And you know I
Long time ago
Time sure flies
I guess
13 years ago
This is the time to reminisce
World that big at all
Call Dan game
For Global enslavement
And
They want you dead
Who wrote
Explain everything
3 Hour film
Too long
Add
It's all a couple
Are David copies of it
About for free
I'll go video
I got over 50
A million views on there before Google
Got rid of it already
Cool
About 10 million views with platforms on YouTube
Proud of you
Is it if you watch this
13 year olds
It lays out are they what you was contrived bio
Does it damn for anyone who's interested we have a 5 episode series Breaking Down Alex's film endgame that you can find
Very easily by look for it
Don't listen to the last episode I lost my
I spent a lot of time with that pile of s*** film and I can tell you conclude
We did not only did Alex not prove a damn thing at that movie
But it also the bioweapons were almost not mentioned at all
There's a lot of talk about depopulation
That was mostly in the context of him misusing quotes
It's for people like Bertrand Russell and Margaret Sanger
To attack vaccines and abortion
He did talk about race specific bioweapons very briefly citing the project for a New American Century documents
Is proof The Cheney wanted to use
Far be it for me to defend Dick Cheney but that pinac document mentioned
The use of bioweapons
Stay out of that variety
Is 1 in a list of hypothetical threat
The country could face
As a justification for rebuilding America's defenses
Which coincidentally is the actual name of that document
It's not called the p
Document
Alex's calls if that's what started a fight
That sounds right beyond that the documentary and heavy
Is a bunch of bulshit
It's just fake quotes
A lot of people yelling about a road
It's a horribly shity documentary and it honestly is embarrassing to look back
The idea that Alex is sitting here and pretending
It somehow Devin
Castrated approved
The globalist music by wepa
To bring in a one world government
It's just sad
Just sad
And I was wondering why is he getting reminiscent about
That's cuz it doesn't really make sense
Isn't really about bile
Not even a little bit
No it I mean I would I would say the road is there's a large that was a far larger part of it
Family about a road
Yeah
It was a road
It was fake quotes
Thomas Jefferson got beat to death in that movie
No Thomas Jefferson
Fake Hitler quotes in Rockefeller quote it was all just a load of horseshit
And then just citation needed
Y'all over-the-top remember bibliography look like
Like swiss cheese there is quite a few references to just
Microsoft
Encarta
Might not even like
Topic Justin
Just screwing around with her for a while
My favorite part of his bibliography was
In the section where he was providing a citation for
It's claimed that the Rothschilds
Funded both sides of all major Wars
It just said insert Rothschild funding both sides
Set the timer
Would like the movie really wasn't about bioweapons
Alex is in a situation where you have this coronavirus outbreak he's been building up The Narrative of
You know using this chicken vaccine patent
And then nowthis
Center for Health safety
Exercise is being all evidence
Since this is a
Globalist
Thing I greet your good to go
Because
Z's liquor
And it's the greatest documentary that anybody has ever seen
So you know ormeno
I got a lot of calls on it cuz it's in the physical paper
PSI
And it says
Video
Gives amateur
How to conspiracy theories
Questionable film can't have a book or film is questionable
In the marketplace just not allowed somebody up there says no
Amazon
Down The Alex Jones film Game
For violating Community standards
Watching game
All they're worth
They're playing
They're smart cities are controlled rats
Novato
Bigger
The last
Now they say they'll use it for
Couple of things
This was not a big article
The real thing
How much is a little off on the
Details though
He says that the films
You're taking off Amazon Prime for violating Community standards but that's not what the article says
It says he violated quote
Company policy
And it goes on to say quote
The company
Amazon their content policy focuses on issues pertaining to sexually explicit content violence
Send copyright infringement
It gives Amazon leeway to disallow anything it deems inappropriate
Prime is Amazon streaming service and apparently their rules are that you can upload your own stuff if you want to but they also can
Take down anything they want to
Seems like this when exactly is it should have
Alex lit under the radar for a while and made some revenue from Amazon
Then Avengers endgame came out and a bunch of people accidentally watched his documentary got
Confused and complain
At which point Amazon Turkish it down probably cuz they didn't realize it was there to begin with
Also Alex seems to forget how bad and game was
Or what it's even about
What do you think
The film is just
The globalist downwards
I can think of at least two
Completely fabricated quotes
City used in that film
Antonio
Sometimes use quotes
Sweetly autocon
Making the meme different things
Then what they asked
Even when he specifically said he was using their words
Right with not using their word
I refuse to do this all again
So if you want to learn about how full of s*** and game is we have 9 hours
You can listen to take care of that
It was mostly about a road
It was a big bro
It had of God
That stuff I was just
Like because it kept talking but I started remembering little things that I forgot
I forgot about Daniel estulin
And that his book
That was one of my favorite things
Which book was that his book about the Bilderberg Group that had like one of his inside sources was a guy who believes that
Goodies from like
It sounds stupid s***
Anyway this is why Alex is talking about endgame B cuz they just took it off Amazon Prime
And he's really pissed off about it
Empty can use
Is it to weave into like his his narrative that like
Oh yeah
They're taking it down because they're doing
Bio weapon released
Is too real for that course it is
So it all works
People are never going to know about this f****** road and less
What what do you want to watch
Tony Stark go back in time
Time b*******
You got to hear about this f****** road
Terrifying I'd like to congratulate Alex on taking these pieces and building exactly what he should have out of it
Granted it's all bulshit but it's
Probably exactly what you would do if you were
A crass
Liar
Pretty simple
So I was just sort of
Talkingshit
When I was suggesting that Avengers
Endgame came out
And it caused a bit of confusion
Turns out Alex has some thoughts
About Avengers
Why is this so important
Why was it taken down
A lot of reasons but you see
This film inspired
The Avengers
Genocide
You make me feel that
And then
Down for a thought
Who could forget that subplot in Adventure Time game where Hawkeyes trying to build a road
He's just running down that buck and run
All right I do,
Was it when the giant spaceship fell onto the door
I'm trying to think of a good road
Situation in a Avengers endgame
Big Daddy Stone Alex Alex would not approve of wakanda
I'm going to tell you that right now he's talked about not if not like
So Alex gets to talk in
In about how use experts on
To talk about Daddy's health issue
Little face in the world
Is list
Is not good
We've been reporting that since last week
We've been having a
Experts online
Mike Adams and many others and playing in historical clips
Publico inventor
Aussie
Polio vaccine
Admitting that they knew it had
340 in it that causes cancer
Keep that clip of the co-inventor of the polio
The back your head cuz we'll get to it later I was very
Confused by that I didn't know what to do until Alex
You talked about it again later
I do not think it's fair to call Mike Adams an expert on any
We had experts like Mike Adams on
Look okay
So one time you say you should put a Bola in your blood and then drink it and now all the sudden you're not an expert
That may come back up later
Second when Alex says that they put
Sbirs v40 and polio vaccine
He's lying
Between 1955 and 1963
Approximately 10 to 30% of polio vaccine
Were contaminated
With what's known as sv40
Or Simian virus 40
The reason for this was that at the
What time do irises I'm sorry that exceeds were made using monkey
Kidney cell culture
And unbeknownst to the vaccine makers some of the vaccines were contaminated
Obviously that's not good
However according
To the CDC quote
There has been some concern that the virus could cause cancer in humans
However most studies looking at the relationship
Gene sv40 and Cancers are reassuring
Finding no causal association between the receipt
Of sv40 contaminated polio vaccine
And the development
Animal testing shown that it can cause tumors and hamsters
But the test for people have been done inconclusa
So Alex can't even prove that basic piece of his argument which is what he's getting
For sure
In the history of Medicine
Which one were you can find a ton of whoops
Moment
And if you don't really want to concern yourself with.
And you just
Attack the medical
Maybe because you make all your money selling time supplement
It's really easy to pretend that all of these moments were actually secret attacks on the
Republic
But Alex can't prove any of this
Is it just
Is Felix yeah
It's it's like l.ron Hubbard trying to prove it all psychiatrists
Sure
Evereve everything is been the Psychiatry industry search
Yeah
Experts on like Mike Adams
And played clips
But we'll get you a little bit down the road
Co-inventor
I don't like experts telling me that the world is already over
I don't like experts telling me that humanity is already punch I can pick I can reassure you like Adams
He is a douche what about the whole above look like
The bat workout
So
The whole point is that sv40 was put in the vaccine for polio in order to give people
Search sure so Alex talked a little bit about this cancer thing
Did you know chickens come from eggs
You're paralyzed
Yep how do you fax
Raindrops come from
You betcha
Sort of you know that
Almost all cancer comes from
In the scientific
Curology
80 years
Okay
Sorry
I just I just enjoy a childlike sense of wonderment at their universe and that's very
Did you know that almost
All cancers
Army
Virus
According to the paper in the Yale Journal of biology and Medicine
From December to
2006 quote
An estimated 15% of all human cancers worldwide may be attributed to viruses
A 2016 released from the national toxicology program from the national
Institutes of Health
Put the number lower
Saying quote about 12% of cancers worldwide or like
Viruses
A 2013 article from the American
Society for microbiology carried the headline quote
Percentage of cancers linked to viruses potentially overestimate
This was specifically about some research
2011 out of the karolinska institute in Sweden
If you rise that 40
Percent of cancer is like
Viruses
At which points are scientists began to test that theory and found it was not good
And if the number was much lower closer
10% which is right in line with at 12
15 is in the bulb
Is kind of within the scientific consensus
Alvin's a
He's almost all of them that was wildly
Overestimating the number
Still didn't make it all the way Tom boats
No let alone
Almost no
What is assertive s*** that you end up saying when you think Mike Adams
Is an expert in the field of
You understand stupid
Anyway
You jump off
Coffey Medical
For a little bit
Because
There's some legal
And it's not Alex's legal issue
It is boy
Coinsurance
Owen Shroyer is Ben arrest
Hearing is in about 20 minutes she was on time and DC
David guess the next hour will have more bad as my lawyer that start with him
And Owen on the broadcast arrest
Came across his mouth inside
That's not what I meant any of those Senate building
Somebody else was allowed to hold up signs and do stuff
He can't because Riley babe ordered the police to write him and they fall
How is that is that what's going on
The only got himself in trouble at the Capitol because he was specifically advertising Infowars
Advertising is not allowed at the Capitol even in the foyer
If you watch the video it's actually really funny
I want to
Begging the cops arrested
They're clearly telling him that the problem is his sign
Which clearly says quote learn more it banned. Video
Direct advert
It's so sad
He's got this tape on his mouth with the word sensor please still talking to the cops
Great great it's just a bad cell boy at one point a cop goes to put them in
Cops in the Kapaa Owens been talking to says no he gets a warning
To which Owen replies quote
No arrest be in front of all these people so they can see the censorship in this country
It's ridiculous
The whole game here is that the
Pro-impeachment protesters didn't get arrested but Owen
The goal is to reinforce the right-wing victimhood narrative the drives this entire world
Crucial to this game is didn't never recognize what you were actually doing
Why it's wrong
And what you got arrested
For which was the advertiser
Back in March of last year someone who works with the artist Robin Bell was arrested
Super similar thing
When they projected the words discrimination is wrong
On the capital bill
The issue there I think it may have been that the projection also included
Hashtag
Which could be deemed at 4
Okay speaking to WaMu Bell even said quote
The main thing is as long as it's not an advertisement we were pretty much told that it looked like we were able to do this
So even their advertisement
It's really hard to say whether Owen and Infowars knew that they were advertising in the Capitol building
They be arrested and they could make it look
Like they were being oppressed
Or if they're just too dumb to even check out relevant laws
Before doing there dumb s***
I'm going to go with
Door number two dad
I'm honestly not sure but either way I just
Do not care about Owens
Stupid publicity
Anyway you by the end of this episode
Norm pattis
Could show up
In-and-outs that
The charges have been dropped in Ellen's released
Call who care nobody cares
Steven gum up the DC law system with
If I was a judge and I saw Owen Shroyer walking to the car and register like
Jesus
Price go away whatever you need to go away
Goats
So Alex
Get back to that to clip
He played of the co-inventor of
The
The vaccine for polio vaccine
There's a co-inventor right we know that Jonas Salk
Created
Given to believe that he was a hero for creating Apollo vaccine and then refusing to profit
Prophet
There's there's some complications with a lot of that history
Documentary that Alex misdirected
Me towards
Vex
Holy Rosary is very fast at 1
I'm not going to get into it too much go ahead
Look at do-it-yourself you want it's just not relevant
Anyway Alex is saying that this guy
Who you never know
Right was work
Working with Jonas Salk
If you are the coordinates are the folio vaccine
I think you should I think people should know your
Oh I do I know who he's talking to
And we'll get into it
Says
To the scientist interview
CBS in Boston that's what we are
Yes I can
He said well
This is terrible
Is it while we're not going to stop
Vaccine
Obfuscation
Too many Rockets
What
Weekend
Alex keeps talking about how the people who made the polio vaccine do that there was sv40 and if they didn't care they wanted to give people can
A number of times he says
This guy who worked at Jonas Salk
It said as much
Kind of implying that he had the guy on the show which just isn't possible
And that clip it became clear that he's talking about how he played at
Clip of something out of context
Where someone talks about the sv40 virus being in the polio
I found the full 10-minute piece that this game from which apparently originated years ago unlike atoms website
And you can tell from the context that it's a doctor discussing the discovery
Avast v40
Which one presented in a certain way makes
It look a little bit more nefarious than it actually is
This is a clip of dr. Maurice hilleman
Who is one of the leading virologist
Destiny USA
Lucky you invented so much s***
The interview that Alex plays out of context
Is Helaman discussing how he discovered at 3:40
Not that he discovered it in the vaccine
He literally discovered
When you found it some polio vaccine weekend
Contaminated
With it in night
It was previously unknown
Jonas Salk developed
The first polio vaccine
But he had a bit of arrival in
In the field
This was Albert Sabin
The two kind of had a bit of a disagreement about method
Sock wanted to take a faster approach using dead polio is the vaccine
Where is Sabin believe that the only way to go about it was to use live virus
Switch takes long
Sock wanted to rush
The market cuz this is a crisis yearbook
Cuz really not into dealing with this
Crisis any longer
And ultimately stock strategy won the day and he was successful in making
This sad that the polio vaccine
Later
Albert Sabin would produce his own oral vaccine for polio
Can be very effective
His vaccine was being tested between 1955 and 1961 during which time
Hilaman identify the sv40 vaccine virus
And theorize that it could have a negative effect on people
And ultimately found it in the vaccine
Because they were using
Monkey Kid
Nice outfits
The clip alexplayz of hilum
Man includes and talk about how he and Saban
Joke about how the Russians would have a worse shot at the Olympics due to having a bunch
Tumors
But since I said that was
Where the primary test
Sabin's vaccine was being dumb
Gotcha
I kind of a chalk this up to dark humor
On the part of Helaman and I think it
It's pretty clear from
Yeah yeah
Morning Pointe
What also be
Because Subs
Tests have shown that there isn't
Are you strong causal connection
They can be drawn between sv40 and human
The
They're obviously they don't know that
Yeah yeah
Stuff that happened in the late fifties
These conversations the right they were joking around about
They didn't know
Right so to assume that he knew that this was going to cause
Cancer is
Is absolutely
Absurd
So the idea is this guy discover
A virus that has heretofore been unknown
In the vaccine
Did not know what its results or effects would be
Simply you catalogued it and then
As a
Better dark humor that I imagine a virologist would have
Stew Leonard's
If you're dealing with
Papa potential
Millions of lives being in in your hands
Yeah then he just goes
I hope
The Russians toolkit
Essentially
And more to the point with Alex's just driving is not accurate even to that edited piece
He played on his show
The joke is about to Russian
She's not doing well in the Olympic
Not that there are too many Russian
No one says but we killed Americans too and Helaman doesn't do that gross laugh that Alex's
Claiming like he's just creating a supervillain out of this isn't even fair to the fake source
Fake Source material but devoid of
Text Source material
Also Jonas Salk has nothing to do with hillerman's comment
This was all about Albert Sabin
And Alex doesn't even know that
He literally has no idea of the surrounding context of these topics he's covering when he tries to pass himself off as an egg
Expert in Tavares
But he's saying that
This guy who he can't even remember him
Men's name
This doctor guy was talking to Jonas Salk it wasn't suck it was saving
Like you don't even know anything
Why should I trust you Alex
On the grand parts of it right you don't understand the basic
Right well
I mean
Bright
Interesting Lee this video
Self does not ultimately traced back to Mike Adams
This is clear enough if you actually watch this video cuz a man comes on at the end did Shane's doctor hilliman
Is like Bad Medicine okay
This man is a dude named
Leonard Horowitz
And he is a real career dumb
Horwitz is a dude I've started building episodes about and repeat
Heatedly lost
Centrist in the middle
A couple
It's something that I've been meaning to do and then
Give us
He's been on Project Camelot he's Bono
Alex's show and he has like a real lunatic pedigree
But he's also pretty boy
His big claim to fame is his theory that the Rockefellers forced musical artists to use the 440 Hertz
Frequency to make music
Which makes people depressed and spreads evil
Horwitz promotes 528 Hertz music
Which is healing and
His link to the Divine creation
Horwitz claims the John Lennon started to make music using
Show me 528 Hertz
Model into the New World Order had him murdered since we'll be too powerful and who ruined their playing
I don't like you
That shouldn't be a claim to fame
That's it. You don't get to
That shouldn't be that should make you famous let alone
Allow you to claim that it may
Because horrific because I'm not insane because I'm not sure if we're ever going to
Actually do an episode about him I should tell you that in preparation for doing an episode I decided to only
528 Hertz
Frequency for a week how did it go
You didn't get healed
No discernible effect
I will say that that was alright annoying anyway that's the guy who edited together this Lobby piece
About dr. Helaman devoid of all this context that was funneled through natural news and Mike Adams
And now Alex's further abolished
Sitting and lying about
In order to
Perpetuate the idea that
They knew there was sv40
Put it in there
Right order to give people cancer
The back end of the human centipede of b*******
It's just just utter garbage
Begin the garbage
Yes now Mike Adams shows up right
That pile of f****** human garb
Amanda's
She's get really severe
He is just like
We're dead why is he in a bad mood
He's a millionaire with nothing to do go f****** home because the
I'll just lay it out for you the reason he's in a bad mood is that
There are like
People on Facebook people on
Like other platforms
That are taking
Misinformation
Surrounding this coronavirus outbreak
Pretty seriously
The pushback
Are might have people
Writing letters to the people who host
Two servers
So he might be in a bit of like
A pickle about the fact that he
He's putting out
And has
As a career
Put a dangerous misinformation about health issue
These guys have no idea what
Consequences
No no clue but I've never had to deal with
Well yeah
And if they don't take well no no
Without ever facing
Negative consequence for your ex
Right
Yeah and of course
Because it's
Finally catching up and people are taking what you do seriously doubt he would tend to feel like well this is the big one
I don't know anyway
Bioweapon
Personally I've been studying the situation so I've got a lot for you here let me just get right into it
Number one realize that the globalists
They know that the most
Wyclef
Fatalities in their simulations of 65 million people dead
Will be liberals in cities
So the globalist are willing to Mass
Massacre
Their own left at switch
By the way it's consistent
With that project Veritas video documenting that Bernie Sanders supporters who said they want a mask
To understand anytime you release a bioweapon and engineered virus
Like this
It's going to impact the cities
This probably doesn't come up enough but this clip is a nice reminder of how the word globalist dozen
Mean anything
Or more accurately just means
People we don't like
Mike Adams is saying that the globalist released this Coronavirus
The bioweapon
Which is not something he can in any way pray
And the result is going to be that a ton of liberals
Cities are going to die
That's the global Esther willing
Going to kill their own people
So liberals and cities of the global its own people
I thought the globalist or an evil cabal that were like multinational business heads bent on world government
I thought they were the CFR and the trilateral commission
Not a pro-choice activists in Port
They have to understand how the sleight-of-hand trick work
You start by doing some over-the-top demonization of your shadowy vague bad guy
And then once that's in place you can
Reply that demonization however you want
Where has Alex used to pretend that he was above left-right Paradigm you can pretty clearly see now that that mask is dropped
It's clear that the Infowars line
Is that liberal and urban living
Equals globalist
There's not a distinction anymore it's just a pejorative term that could be applied to anyone they disagree with as a way of
Attaching them do the big bad guy demon that they've built up for years
Childish it
F*** you
You don't get to care about me
That's you you there is literally said that we should just murder left
Who's in the street you don't get to Suddenlink care that I'm going to get killed by my own
People
So sad I feel bad for you don't get to judge the globalist for something that you want to do anyway so sad the globalist
What this bioweapon before we can have our civil war
Are they want to murder you with disease
I wanted to shoot you like a good human being right
It's pretty
Pretty stupid
So bide Adams has some more dumb things
Things to say but
Before
That he gets down to business cuz Alex what he ends up doing is just like Mike take over
The show
I'm going to go get a drink
But I don't know what
He's doing but
Eat before he lets Mike take over
He gets real f****** weird and
I got to say the only thing I hear
When I hear this clip
Is I hear Alex saying
I'm pretty sure a bad story is about to come out about
I have been the subject
Of deep state
Attack
Their next level
And
I was a spy
BFDI
And
Vote for the Central Intelligence Agency
At this point to not get into this on here
Action sobotka
Obviously talked about years ago that against your group
On the phone with me during racing join us
Will Dartmouth Goodyear going to be part of the elite you're already LOL
Yeah man you know that the Pentagon people doing it over the phone I mean
You want to see it behind the scenes
But
They basically told me used
And this isn't just like a death threat over the telephone
Oh that's the best thing for your family this is what it is
You're going to see
Cannibalize the media about me the next few days
You're going to spend
Family Guy
Albino.
But it is about our show
I'm just a canary down in this coal mine
It is about
It is entirely about you I don't know I don't even know if any story is going to come out but I hear Alex worried that something
He has some indication that like
Oh
This reminds me so he was reached for comment about something so you could read someone's working on it
S***
I don't know this could be the Megyn Kelly situation all over
Until the Megyn Kelly interview is like
They might publish all the s*** that I said they're going could be and every bad they are only doing this to prepare
Prayer for my dad
It's a
You can you can start to read
Through the the
The intention there at that stupid like
Alright guys f***
Some bad stuff about me that's just
Nancy is really bad
You are going to hear some s*** about me that you
You do boy is it bad and I did all of it
And the CIA is
Canary in the coal mine though
This is
This is kind of an interesting Club cuz I look starts ruminating
On canaries in Colma
And didn't
To do that I don't
No
I think he loses track of the metaphor
It's very complicated but
Liberty with
Mary's blood no no but
Alex does get around to being like weird
Already
So he's right there with Mike
But they have canaries so in the methane goes up certain I could Aries.
Terry can handle any any any gas
Cherry Falls over matters
Okay
Well
The canaries are dead
Right now
Weave
Bond through Moesha run
Analogies
Already dead already know you're not saving the day already
Nobody else can handle this week notice what time and we built for it
Louisiana lunchbox
Weird that already okay
They're doing all of this right now
And the coronavirus obviously is as prepared simulant
Recover Brothers.
Cuz they always having something else is really doing and they got the virus
You can see all the stuff
It means we are now game time
The balls been
New World Order Donatello Humanity
So he hands it off to Mike bitlife
The thing that I hear there
Please like
Shades of Project Camelot
You know with these like they have this virus but it's just cover for something else
I hear that Kerry Cassidy saying yeah there's these wildfires but they're not really happening it's just because aliens are
Coming through the portal
Course it's it's it's the same
Sort of
Thinking well I mean obviously everybody knows that spider leadership only a text through Corona
Making their move bingo
Bingo
These people in denial isn't like 80
I'm not going to be overwhelming and favors anymore we are but
All of us disappear into the nothingness Canary
And the abyss is all of us
But at the same time you got it you got to reflect like
That's some of the language that he's using
Is really f***** up
Yeah
And in his
World
We've heard many times
Scholar's asking when does this kickoff
When is the time
You know it and for him to not be aware that this is
Language
That has a meaning
Specific to his audience
It's at best
Super irresponsible
We've discovered that the virus is Airborne everybody should leave their homes and fire their weapons wildly into the sky
Might get it all Mike does get close to the
Jesus
So anyway he comes back
Mike does
After the
Alexandra talk to him
And just mad he is
Spitting wisdom
What's the
This Coronavirus
Situation
This is just the first wave folks
The second wave of the pandemic begins when the Coronavirus
Vaccine
Begins being administered
And we will come to learn
Maxine
Contain contain
Live virus
It would be live virus in the coronavirus vaccine
Edible
Will set off a fire
Firestorm of the second wave
This is already been fly already engineered
We know the Playbook
No you don't lie
Why would they do that that's a terrible plan
Waffle plant
Be representing me and they're not even doing a good job of killing me in the cities that they're trying to
Mike is is making this s*** up ain't what is the effect of this language in
This rhetoric is is to make people less
Trustworthy and less
Willing
To engage the public health
People
That in that will make it much more difficult
For them to help
You contain
And treat
This emerging public
Lookout situation
These feel like
I understand that this probably very little effect
The Infowars has
Anymore
Worst case scenario this has
They are the only outcome of this
Is either
Neutral
Or people get hurt there is no positive outcome other than Mike selling more s***
More of his supplement
It does make me think about how
You know like I were wired wrong for for this type of s***
Are you I would find it
Hard to believe that we would have the same level of
Distressed of Public Health
If our coverage of Public Health was more like
The World Health Organization once again quashes outbreak before it becomes Global issue
World Health Organization once again claims up all this stuff
You and once again brings massive amounts of age all of these people
Instead of only mentioning them yeah then they f***
It's it's hard to imagine it's just our wired like there were not going to
Clickbait is never going to be
Positive
You just can't win
Yeah it's unfortunate
Because that is lettuce
To the point where
I mean it's over
It is through this troubled nightmarish it's so
It's so horrific
Such a nightmare
Can we do
Are the human race
Medical
Calendar for Humanity
It will only be lone survivors
The strategy must
You can be a Survivor we can help you survive
The information here Infowars
And what I do
Can help you survive I'll give you some practical things in the next segment
Maybe maybe it's an ass
Massaging statement to hear from me the health Ranger but
It's over
The masses will be slaughtered
Wow
Wow it is over for Humanity as a whole
Only you can prevent forest fires but it's too f****** late man we're all dead
We're all goddamn dead I'm smoking
Caleb are bringing you this message ride to get out of your home you see the trick there to even eat
The best-case scenarios Soul Survivors
What do you know I work for a company that sells
Survival food and bug out everybody else is lying to you I'm the only one you can trust at
And it just so happens that the problem I am warning you about
It's something that I myself have been preparing for
And hey how about you scare somebody
And it will be 149/99 every month until you don't win student that is weird
But I got to say
How to say he keeps repeating that most of humanity is dead
And I got to say you starting to swing me
I believe it's over for Humanity
I think that you marry
It is being Target with so many factors of Destruction that
The bulk of the human race will not
Survive this
Now there can be lone survivors or small groups of survivors
The strategy we have to get
Now
And it just the fact that you are tuning into this broadcast means that you are Survivor you have a Survivor mindset
Really
Are the sheeple class
I just walked off a cliff
Because everybody else is doing it in for
This is salesman tactics
That's
Let it ruin you learned when you go and try and get a job like with Cutco the nice sale people
I was a Salesman for 10 years
Me is to make the person seem like they're smart because
You know you're not wanted people who wouldn't listen to this sales manager
You're already here
Listening that means you're smart you need to survive hey when I was working with the hearing aids
Sonos two people it was just like hey
You know what
Just by coming in and getting your hearing tested you've already
Take your already way advance
You don't even know what you'll be whenever you get to
I think there's degree
Hearing aid like I was it was weird I was I was using sales tactics that are normally used to
To get people to waste their money on
What what
What he's doing is creating this sense of like
In group
But the in-group is based on like
Hirabayashi
It's it's
So manipulate
It's very deceitful like it really undercuts
Did my ability to believe that he believed
What do you say
And it's so over-the-top
Don't like
The mass of humanity is done we're all rich Society civilization
Yeah
You know.
You know we've only got 10 days before everybody's cannibal
Close to Dad
That's the next step
Can you imagine
I demanded of Cormac my
McCarthy wrote the road but the only lone survivors were f****** infowar Adams
God never mind he did write that book is called Blood Meridian
So
Did you know
In the past
Infowars has been very prone to call
Different
Health Gracie is false flag
This one's not this one's real
Okay one way that I believe that you know that this is a real pandemic is because the who
Is trying to downplay it
Who
Whatever the Whow
If the opposite of reality
When the bird flu virus was a non pandemic
They declared it a stage 6 pandemic
So the floor here in Mike's thinking is that he seems to believe that outbreaks are predicted
When they very much are not
You could have a plan in place and executed quite well and then some random variable can make an outbreak still occur
You can prepare do your best to mitigate the Damage Done by natural phenomena but
The idea seems to have about the
Level control these groups he hates have his
Is absurd
Mike is also playing fast and loose
What's the classification of outbreaks used by the World Health
He wants the audience
To think that the higher the
Number of the stage the worst
Things are but that's not entirely accurate
The whou the six phase scale to describe the stage of which
We currently find ourselves with a particular disease
From a public health stamp
Phase one is that there is no animal-to-human transmission
Phase two is when there's a virus that's a known to have affected human circulating an animal population
Phase three is when there's small clusters people who have been infected by animals
But human-to-human transmission
Is Unser
Things could have been more serious in Phase 4
Where's sustained human-to-human transmission
Taking place
Faze5
Is when confirm human-to-human transmission has caused
The condition to read
At least two countries in one region of the globe
Basic
Is characterized by community-level outbreak
At least one other country from where it originated
The avian flu situation met the criteria of Phase 6
The World Health Organization didn't Class B that way too scared
It was just an accurate classification
After this phase
You enter the post
Pica.
Where activity of transmission
Decrease
Health Organization
Keep an eye out for second waves
When things return to normal levels
The post-pandemic. Begin
Monitoring
Continues in the evaluation of the
Response the organization
Add commands
It's right so far of a cycle
Explaining the f***
Water cycle
Interested
Not like
Phasix means 10 billion people have died
Oswego
And honestly like from all of my understanding
About this
That where we're at
Currently with the
This coronavirus may not reach
That level
And the reason the World Health Organization would be cautious to give
Their classification
Lessons learned from past circumstances
I don't find anything
Suspicious about
Also I think Mike is mixing up
The bird flu and the swine flu
In June 2009 the World Health Organization
Declared a public health emergency
Fancy International about the H1 N1
Epidemic
And through focused efforts and use of antivirals
We reach the post Peak
Pandemic phases by November
So then a few months
This was something that was right
To call a pandemic at its peak since it did Kill over 40
Teen thousand people in 2009
And the transmission of the virus was fitting fa6 qualifications
Currently the Wuhan Cora coronavirus does not appear to meet all the criteria though if the confirm fact
About the outbreak do end up meeting them in the future I'm certain that the World Health Organization
Class fight
More importantly this opposite oppositional position towards public health organizations is very stupid
But in very
It's one thing to be skeptical and recognize that no human organization is infallible
So it's best
Be cautious
It's an entirely different thing to say that whatever said organization says
The opposite is true
Particularly when you run a business selling dump supplemented
Beatley
Dangerous
It goes back to the
Got Instinct feel about
Anti-vaxxers where it's like
You know what f****** fine
Get polio
Go for it
If you're not going to be and it's
You just can't operate like that so please people so often
You feel like you're dragging them Kicking and Screaming into
Continue to go
Yeah but something we all have to be like f******
Get just
Just come with us I know you're stupid but
Citgo
Good afternoon
Temp of people who are
Entranced by these narratives let's say or they were there behold into them
The recognized that the people who are disseminated these narratives to them are liars
They're trying to sell them
Something right
And hopefully
You know people can be shaking into an understanding of
The world
Through recognizing like
I want am I listening to the house yeah yeah
That kind of thing you hope
And that's my hoe
Anyway
Not only was this
Past
Pandemic
Fake
So was zika
When does zika virus
Was a made-up
Virus I mean it was a made-up
Pandemic
Doing it didn't exist
We were told that was huge we were told I mean do you remember
Couple of years ago
Babies were going to be born with shrunken heads
Across Florida
And Louisiana Mississippi
Regions of the southeast United
Babies were going to be born with shrunken heads
You remember those no stories that was all over the media
Because of the zika virus
We all better run out and
Get zika vaccine
Emergency zika vaccine research insurance
Congress
Remember correctly
They approve
I think it was 2 billion dollars for zika
Vaccine research
There were no babies born with shrunken head
In Florida there's an epidemic of truck and headed babies
In Florida
Never happen
It was all made up
The reason there were concerns about babies being born with shrunken heads in the South was that in areas where there where is he
The outbreaks particularly of Brazil
They were accompanied by highly increased rates of microcephaly
The reason estate sealift might have been discussed is because he has transmitted by me
Mosquitoes and those states of climates that are far more hospitable to
Mosquitoes
And therefore
It would be a higher
Risk
Pregnant women being bit by the mosquitoes
Anyway
The issue for the u.s.
Zico it was that it wasn't his huge
Threat for us
But it was
4 people around the world
We have the public health infrastructure to deal with it better
Insomuch as we have prevalent air conditioner
Screen Windows
Which cut down drastically on the ability of mosquito carry diseases
Spread
It was proposed
That Congress allocate 1.9 billion dollars does
Zika but they ended up actually just found a 1.1 billion
And a lot of it was aimed at funding local and state agencies futmas
Mosquito control initiatives into place
Not all Direct
Did towards of Acts
And the big picture here is
Zika was
Not a made-up
Virus
This is a representation of how Mike Adams doesn't believe the people in developing
Countries around the world deserve help
The concerns that people had about how zika could possibly affect the United States
Did not come to pass
But other countries absolutely suffer dire consequences
Consequences from the virus
It in that sense the World Health Organization was absolutely correct
Call it an emerging
He does not give a
F*** now it's
It's a weird solipsistic
Nationalism
And where it's like if it doesn't happen
It's like if I don't get zika then they just
Made it up
I didn't get zika my kids have a normal sized head there.
Push it also there was one woman in Hawaii
Who had been in Brazil at the beginning of her pregnancy
See who did end up giving
Bring birth to a child with microcephaly
So his
His claim that there aren't any American
Florida so technically you could buy him a technicality
It doesn't matter the Warriors are nonsense
It's all stupid right
So
He's just talking a lot of s*** trying to like
Moline
Past
Disease outbreak in order to make this one real didn't happen cuz
You got to move that survival food creator of the polio vaccine was the creator of the
The poliovirus right name it
So he gets to talk anymore about
Does Emma like look dude this is all just an a
Infomercial for the food
Food Supplies
And this is a critical issue for all of us to get
Supplies
Wipeout
In the city
People
If you are not
Yet prepared with a backup food supply
In the United
And you live in any major city or near a major city
Then you're crazy
This is a crass and disgusting sales pitch
Pure and simple
Mike is claiming that the food is running out in Wuhan because he wants the listener to to buy his and Alex's survival food
That's the game they're playing
I can find no evidence
There's a food crisis in Wuhan
Obviously there's going to be some sentiment of
Concern for people under a quarantine
About food
But all the articles I can find about this
Are about how the government understands that this is an issue
Inner stepping up their deliveries
The food to the city
According to the South China Morning
Post shipments
The various food items
Coming in from neighboring provinces regularly
And that there's a stockpile of 11 million lb of rice
+ 10000
Tons of pork and beef
At the ready
Addition to the
Regular deliveries
Good food
The same article discusses how some residents are stockpiling food
And that does make some sense as a human
Behavior
There's also doesn't demonstrate that there's a food crisis
Just did
People behave that way sometime
This is Sensational ISM aimed at Mike's domestic audience
He doesn't care at all the people around the world are going through it mean
It's clear from this talk about zika
You just do it he knows that this isn't
Opportunity to heighten his doomsday narratives to sell these food.
That is like literally
The underlying
Of his
Sensationalism
Humanity is done
All this dude going to be lone survivors
Get your food.
It's just like
It's that kind of person that is so stupid
And so incompetent
That stay assumed that everybody else is
Is more stupid and more income
And in order to make themselves
Feel smarter
So that idea of like
We're all going to starve to death
Is like nobody could
Possibly think I had for this nobody but
Me could ever realize that in this circumstance
There might be food worries
So obviously all of these people have no idea what they're doing and we're all going to
Right
Know if I mean people look it sucks but people know
If you want to look at it from the
Perspective of how stupid is Mike
I mean we could talk about that yeah I think we could for a while
Ebola virus
Great surfaces with bleach
Like a bleach water mixture
And put it in a spray bottle
You can spray down the surfaces
And it killed Ebola virus
And then what happened back then
The media
And the government
They said that
So don't talk about natural cures for Ebola
I think Mike Adams is trying to pretend that he didn't post any Bola cure on his website natural news
Sample of live Ebola and some booze
Into a bottle and mixing it up real good
Well
To Mike's credit he did take that article down from his website that's no I don't give him credit for that but it's
Volume City ever published its beginner credit for taking that down
Right
It's not a secret that disinfecting with bleach
Can kill Ebola
That's pretty readily available information in literally no one would criticize Mike for saying
They would however criticize him
Heavily promoting a cure that would almost certainly infect
Anyone who attempts
22 use at with Ebola
In Zoe's trying to Reaper
Purpose that criticism than glad
Descendants 2 / 2 use bleach
Go fuc yourself live Dylan Morin in Black Books whenever
Loses mind
He just grabbed some oven cleaner while he's sick and he's like if you can clean it up and you can clean me any drinks
Mike's got this real f*****-up View
What's going on in the world what's going to happen
Who you should trust
Alright
So World Health
Officials were trying
Their best
Games
But I think he does recognize that like
The climate that were living
Now with people taking propaganda
And this is Bad actors more seriously it's going to lead to some backlash
Right answer
Frames that preemptively as sensor
When this pandemic
They will be take down orders and censorship orders
To take offline
Headband any account
Of anybody who talks about a natural
Cure
What Coronavirus
Why is that
Why would that be happening
Because they can't have people chewing themselves
They can't allow people
To survive
The onslaught
They
The globalist Who engineer that's who
Who ran the laboratory
They want to kill
As many people Spa
Can't prove any of that s*** and you posted a f******
Can you Bola cure
On your website to get the f*** out of here
Like its
It's an issue of
You're going to get people killed
If you behave in the ways that like let's say you did surrounding Ebola
Like let's say there is a possibility that someone could have gotten their hands on
Survive Ebola
To prepare the Cure that Mike posted on his website
That would almost certainly
Spread Ebola
So I
Okay I understand there's a there's issues with the
Free speech
And what have you but I also recognize that
People who are
I don't know acting in ways that are
Specifically going to further a Public Health crisis
I might be fine with let's say Facebook deciding we don't want this on the platform
They don't want people healing themselves naturally like whenever I say that the
The cure for this Coronavirus
Is finding an Airborne sample of smallpox
And injecting it directly into your blood
Dream and then spitting and sneezing on everyone around you
They're going to take that down Dan
And it's my right as an American to say that the government doing it I think opens up like another box I have no evidence
The government is doing it
No I don't even care to have that conversation
Maybe a little bit different but if he's platforms are just like go f*** yourself you're pretty people at risk
Then I think they're well with
The right to do that and I sport there
So anyway this is it all
Just about killing
People with this Coronavirus
It's also about training
We know that part of the agenda here is indoctrination training and also
The quarantine training so
Whether or not this is the big kill virus
Or some other future virus is still unknown this
Rate of fatality rate from this virus has not yet High Enough
To kill a billion people but it could kill tens of millions as projected in the software but
It will most certainly provide
The president
Total police
State lockdown
The United State
In every major city
In America
Say whatever you want about China's responded to the outbreak
It's kind of irrelevant to the point Mike is make
You can say that their lockdown of Wuhan is shocking and
Police state
Going to argue with you it's also
Mike is making the argument that the US will use this outbreak to set the
The stage to enact martial law
But this raises the question
Why didn't they do this after other outbreak
In the mid-1980s there's a giant measles outbreak that didn't lead to Marshall Lodge that it led to Greater Public Health
Practices
The polio crisis of the early 1900's didn't lead to martial law
Diphtheria
Like around 50
Thousand people in the US
31921 and 9025 Neptune lead to martial law
Some estimates claimed that as many as 57 billion Americans got swine flu in 2009
That didn't lead to martial law
There are over 5,000
Confirmed us cases of zika in 20
16 Legend League martial law
They are a decade behind
They wanted to do it for do you receive
2009 they were a decade behind they wanted to use it to do martial law
Oh great
I hate is walking back ass
Cowardly
Well I mean I know I said that all of humanity is over but
Might not kill billions
They're going to do this in practice for the next one
The public health system do we have in place or very competent and do exercise like like the one carried out by the center of
Call safety Johns Hopkins
We consider complicated response variables to better enable them to react
To changing situations
Fluidly
Editorial position of enforces that everything is
The ultimate end goal of everything is to get to martial law
Because that has to be the endpoint of their theories they often have to say completely stupid s*** like this in order to work in that direction
Honestly the only thing that makes me at all worried that there could be some elements of marshmallow pop up and respond to this outbreak is that
Trump is president
Yeah they fully
Support Trump
He's the sort of president who doesn't trust science or expert
To be easy to imagine I'm overreacting
Quarantine in u.s. City
But to be totally clear I do not even think that
Is a likely series of events
Nope he can block travel because of religion and race but
Not disease
That would be crazy
Also my good little weasel trip
Break their
He said that the software projection save this could kill tens of Millions
He's referring to the center of Health Center for Health
Safety
The exercise which was not simulating the situation
It's currently unfolding
It was just using a hypothetical coronavirus outbreak
The context for the discussion
The actual variables are very different
From the specific characteristics of the virus to the context of its origin
Where is wild
But you're responsible to pretend that the simulation has any predictive value in the real world
Situation
Mike is pretending that this is
Is the case because you want the audience to believe that the simulation was exactly like the
This actual situation
Because the globalist planned it all out
Matt is deception
He is deceiving
What an a******
Right
He's the worst
So
These terrible
Get to a refreshing guest
A little bit later after we get through the bog of it is Mike Adams he's done
Server hosting on his own now and Alex shows back up
He wants to stress
Victor
We don't make things up
Chicken vaccine have a call with somebody who's like you get stuck
Again it's like they're aliens on a sabotage human develop
They poison everything they kill the Earth
Supported
Sabotage all clean human development
I can pack of Gremlins whatever they are
Superbad
Coordination
Cuz they're getting a transmission Mike
I just scientifically look at
What
Bill this is anti
You call them
They call themselves
But they're not they're the opposite
What are these equations
All I heard was
Things up and then he goes on to talk about equations that he's made up
Looking at made-up equation right
Right so they don't even know if the standard models true Dan all equations are made of
At the quantum level Alex is right all the time
So Alex is like
These people are bad news
Manthey Volvo
Big news
So he's he's talking about how like a man you know they're planning what they're going to do is they're going to wait this out and there were.
They're armored without sure but he has bad news for
Every person I talk to
Everybody else says
Who
Elin
Kauai Hawaii
And Tasmania
They believed would like a year-long
Global war they want to stop
Stop news.
Go in
The new bases in Pakistan everywhere
They're going to eliminate everybody
Stabilized
Scott
But the fact is the minute
All these people are in Severn
Billy me a combat robot there and then drones watching of course I forgot have a combat robot
The minute just like my a soldier or officer gives order to kill
Eminem children
Soldiers Turner Gunn the default
Human resistance
Computer
Now the military guy nuts element
Realizes they're being replaced
And the default
All the global at the minute they kick this off
We're going to have a 90%
Capitation
Within days of employment off my
So yeah
I mean
True this contacts
Ripe
Should
Shadowy group of elite
Have engineered the end of the human race huh
And have built ridout's combat robot robot robot
I
Thoroughly support 90% decapitation unfortunately I don't think that's true
What should these exact Circle
Has arrived
I'm disappointed that we're not at 104
Right
Fahrenheit
Baloch sides does a wrestling promo
How you talk to all the same people
The military everybody get
The sky is real but its incremental
It didn't happen like it was
Oh you're even named checking sky.
Ever try
This plan
They're All Dead
Okay
On one level Alex is a
Child living in a bizarre fantasy world full of Espionage and ins-and-outs
And to that extent this is the sort of rhetoric you should just ignore and move along
More than anything else it's just another example of his big boy violence
Fantasies
Whoever there's a real danger to this kind of
Thing particularly in times of elevated anxieties like you might find at the beginning of uncertain
Stages of a virus outbreak
The reality is that this out
Outbreak
It's inescapable in the modern world
However Alexander's capable in the modern world true
Brunei living in the
Ancient world
Discuss that
However Alex is painted this coronavirus a bioweapon attack by the global
They're hoping
They can wait out their armored without
But if they try this
The human spirit is activated in the good guys are going to kill them all
Right so then we just all
Here's why this is Dan
The coronavirus is not a bioweapon being
Deployed by the club
However there is a possibility that things will get worse before they get better
As tensions rise and
Alex and Mike with the audience into a frenzy saying s*** like it's over for Humanity
The odds of one of his listeners taking him seriously
My Tribe
The definition of who is a globalist is completely arbitrary
Prairie at this point
But you have the major figures out
Axios about all the time ranging from the Clint
Thesaurus to Brian stelter
As the natural progression of the coronavirus plays out
Alex runs a very serious risk of his rhetoric being understood by the more unhinged in his audience
Hugo and Kilby please label does the enemies of humanity
Alex's said a condition for when these people are to be killed which is supervised
He says when they try to kick this off
But what the f*** does that mean
They're already tons of cases of coronavirus in a number of countries
And Alex's. We literally said earlier the same episode that the
The ball have been
Kicked off
So that seems to imply that the
What time is already come
This game Alex is playing
Profoundly dangerous
It very well may be that his audience is too small and disengage that this point where it now there isn't anyone listening will take him up on
What is advocating
What you mean that the secondary point
He's more or less riling up his audience
Used to kill his imagine.
The way I hear this is just Alex being
Clear that he's on his last
Flags
He isn't bringing anybody
Anyone
Like it was getting radicalized into
Conspiracy theory ship
There's way too many free options of the same kind of content he's
Providing there's no real Prospect of him growing
In the future
He's hitched his wagon to a present to do
Impeach the new just loose
Restrictions on the
The chemical Alex
About for a decade's that's gone
Kind of embarrassing
He's only
His once remarkable conspiracy kingdom is dust
Is anger and resentment about it is being expressed
Bayou Sharpay
Increase in the violent rhetoric towards is imagined enemies
In blood conversations about their murder
Which is not
Surprising
But is really dangerous
Chris as it as a trend I think people should be
You know I think
I think it's worth
Take me at least a little seriously it is kind of dangerous when people who've spent their entire life
A pug and Isaac
Projections of
Basically themselves onto imagine
Figures
When they start
Projecting
The end of the world because
Their own careers aren't going so well
Soul
Loosely
Tied to Alex's World being a revocable
Probably
Anyway Mike's got one last thing to say before he shuffles on down the road to tend to his llamas or over the
The f*** he does not anything to do with health issues
But man like listen to this b*******
Last thing to mention you know this big
Explosion in Houston
This chemical
Exploded entire neighborhoods have been destroyed the police are telling people
Look for body parts up to a mile away okay
What we talked about
Sleeper cells being activated I don't know if
Could be payback for the soleimani
Play strike this could be
Extremis sleeper cells activating we need to we need to see if that's the case
But Houston was one of the key targets
What may be happening we need to research further
Well there's no doubt that that's a Target and we should cover that alright
What the f***
Insane person
That is crazy has
No that crazy insane this was Friday that explosion happen
And on Friday
He has
No reason why is involved
Payback for soleimani for sleeper cells
There is no reason
Suspect that
He has nothing to go on this is
Purely his imagination
Keep this up as something like a possibility
Did you say we go to research this further
What I hear that all I hear is like hey I was what do you think about this narrative
A good because
At that point to say anything
Sandy Hook with sleeper
Versailles by Iran
Preemptively
Fighting us back for sulemani
That's terrible
We got to guess
Was that now that Mike Adams is gone
We have a guest
Do we have not heard
Hide nor hair up
Leo zagami
He's been on
More recently than this guy
I'll tell you a couple things about it
You like to hide in bushes
Well joining us down if we could him holding this week
Genre
Portray patriots.com
Rob Ford still living
I will be goddamn
I'm not sure if you still following us on Twitter but so I can set up
The picture is no longer sitting there but I don't know if it's
Hanging up it's a
Angle might be different room than alright okay
I'm so it says I'm clear
Outlook
We know that there's some
Knowledge of us
But the only thing that I want to come of that
Is just for John rap
Forward to finally hang up that f****** b****
He might have
And he announces a torso
Says something Auto Show guy that would get me so much joy it's been a very long time since we've seen John Ray
Rapoport
I know also known as Batman
He is
F******
Like insane
Just Medical
Denial
So when there is a pandemic
Type mood
When there's a there's an outbreak situation of course you go call up
No more fake lews.com
There's two things that are in
The first thing is the John Skype I don't know what's going on it doesn't seem to be working
But the second thing is that does not surprise me interview is very not
Much about
The virus of course
Of course
It takes on
School lunches
Nope
It's about Alex needing Jon rappoport to reassure him
I have had a theory for quite a while and I've brought this up on the show then I think that John Rappaport has hypnotized out
Neuro-linguistic
Programming
And has Alex
Exynos like some sort of a weird state where whenever he
He comes on Alex
Guy gets into
F***** up mood
Halex darts
What did real emotional
It starts talking about like
Let's talk about the spiritual Dimension John Rappaport
This guy is
All this b******* about to fake science yet
Spiritual
But from the beginning
It does not work out
Because his
Like I said
Rapport Skype is working
And so
You'll hear this clip Alex tries to ask him
A question it doesn't work
And then wrapped Porter starts van
The Gestalt
Prime computation
Are we right now what are the globalist
Alex I can't hear you
Well we're doing some
More training today I'm not sure why
Where we are as a culture in a space station RAV4
Are we talking
Try to push you into doing some
Something that you would know
That is not an answer to the question that was asked
I think that is
Clearly John RAV4 being like well I better just talk
About something I like it
I like Jon rappoport his willingness to just jump in there can you imagine how many other
I had that exact.
Like Rapport nose like well I better just start saying something
He starts rambling a bit and this leads into a conversation about how the globalist
Do they do is they
Trick you into
The thinking that all good is evil and all evil is good
They're so good
We're going to show you the opposite of everything
The way it actually is
Convince you that this is so
Show everything you saw
Good actually
Turns out to be evil
And everything you saw
Receival actually
Turns out to be good
What do you know about that
This is now the Brave New World and isn't it wonderful
This is college dorm level s***
Arab Sports out here trying to blow people's mind saying the globalist tell you everything good is bad
Denver things
Everything you've been told the true it is true but the reverse
Wake up right
Right so it's kind of like if
You
Spent all of your time
Screaming about this chemical and how it's
Destroy you
And the government then says
No actually it's good for more of
Is that is that everything evil is bad maybe
I kind of just whenever I hear this
Sort of mentality I always think like it's not a loser's game
Because if you
Trying to get you on my team right
Like a man
Freak out
Everything you've been told
Is not true
Everything everything
Literally every
Holy
Now if I were to
Try picture this to you and you
Take it in like
Know what things are
I have been lied to
Wouldn't that make you more
Prone to
Question me
We going to like what
Well, I think my next question would be
Okay
So everything is inverted
Everything bad is good okay
Okay so how about murder is that good
Well the problem
Okay so okay then how about
How about the taste of oranges are those still sour or those sweet know you got to take those the tastebud LSD
Okay
Jersey the truth
That's god dammit
I bet
That's the other thing
2 is like obviously it's not a blanket everything
What you're doing is you're trying to use this as a rhetorical device
People out of their Slumber and what you have to do then is really quickly
Them to like take your worldview
Because the longer that they stay in that
Questioning state
The more likely it is to like look at what you're doing to be like wait that's bulshit
So it's okay that you're telling me divorce been a massive conspiracy that has lied to me my entire life and everything that I believe is
Actually the inverse
And you are telling me this
Why would I believe you
It's a means by which
Like you could maybe
Create an opening the
You can get people in with
But it's not a
Not accurate and you got any but you got to do to me but I believe you
Because I don't have I have your best
Well they say that they have my messenger
Yeah but you can believe me because better than you have to Jerk Hut in
So in the middle of his interview with rapapara
Alex gets update from Norm pattice about Owen Shroyer is legal situation
And I don't keep this in because it end
Itsfunneh
Everyone
Litigation
What event
To find out who gave the order for his arrest
Means now that no one will ever before
To answer that
Questions
To bring civil litigation
False arrest
You know what else would have come out in that trial is that he was arrest
Stayed because he was advertising on Capitol grounds
Have to decide whether that's worth doing is
Tell me this
Infowars audience
Was more important than Alex Jones are on Troy
Synergy credit
You bankroll. I can sit atop lawyer bankroll. So I can put on there
Money did all this to understand that for store.com I want that
Money for War I want that money to fight time
Give me your money and I swear I'll wait at
Lemoore weather
Give me your money and I will pull off
Embarrassing and impotent public
Spectacle
To advertise my s***
To begin with I would like a better return on
Yeah it's not great
So we get back to Rapaport
Alex
And there's that you know there's a little bit of talk about medical stuff but it's really just like
Anti-vax
Nonsense of course
Your run-of-the-mill and Evac stuff either goodnight weirdo
They're going to kill you they're going to turn you into a
Can you record our satanic
Is the struggle all about
Vaccines
Abortion vaccinations sent destroying the health
For the body
Side group
You must let us
Something in you
When we already have all our ancestors and what we are together
What
What are you saying
Human race is all about
It's about survival
Shabazz about missing women
Choosing each other
I got to get some company that's gross
And we're just supposed to trust him
It's Satanism to get shots I guess
Is a family
Is Alex one of these guys who thinks all medicine is evil then is that what he said it has to be it cuz they're just some
Some things that like
You don't have the antibodies
To fight you don't
Then if
You don't have those
They can kill you
Is that what he say I guess so cuz that's
Messed up I mean it isn't that kind of it anytime somebody's like the the story of the human race their history is survive
That's somebody who's signaling
The people who didn't survive deserve.
Can I bring clear that they don't believe in like survival of the fittest evolution
No no absolutely no I don't know what they're saying even survival of the fittest so long as it does
Doesn't involve Evolution they just want the bad one
Out I guess you should have been dead anyway it's very weird only the genetically perfect
Survive they're saying they're all humans are
If that's fair
It's very weird this perspective is
It's strange
It'll be hard to defend in a PhD kind
Setting
I started to think about like
Why
Is this the mentality that they have and then Rappaport starts talkin and I realize that might be why
You have been a Pioneer in warning about exit
Is that a thing you can be
For me in college
Actually
19 6
Mission College
Sing came down the pipeline called
Slough one winter
I had no idea what they were
We talked about
Everybody's got to get a vaccine
Otherwise she
When you get sick
And I thought to myself
I'm not getting
I'm not going
To get sick are they crazy
Talking about I mean I don't know why I react
Did that way
I didn't get sets not good enough
Got sick
And I started
Develop this stealing
Feces
People are doing some
Violin
Strain
Perversion
They're trying to make us normal as
And it's completely cover
You are very weird John Rappaport why I could realize too that if he was in college in 1950s
7 he's 80 years old
He's a very idea
That is true he still has some salt and pepper there that's why
Mostly grape
I have a very hard time gauging people's ages
I just generally speaking and
Good good on you
Yeah anyway what's on that
Picture
Maybe a picture of Jon rappoport
Tell you that the end of the flu of 1957
Talk about the Asian flu between one and two million people worldwide
It's a very serious situation
By the summer of 1957 and it reached the United States and in March 1958
An estimated 69800
People have been killed by it in America
Rapoport decided not to get a vaccine and he got lucky that he didn't catch that flu but his it
Exactly zero importance
In terms of sine
This is his backstory that he's presented when he's called
Leader in the field of denying vaccines
He was a dumb dumb in college you didn't want to get a vaccine
He didn't catch the flu and other people did
That's not how science works
That's a really bad style of thinking to hear
Someone pretending to be involved in the field of science
There's a dumb dumb undergraduate who thinks they're already a genius.
Not somebody who study the actual
All of these guys
Alex Rappaport Mike Adams
You scratch beneath the surface on them just a little bit
One time I uncle got
Wheatley unwarranted and unearned oppositional
Defiance
For no reason Rapaport didn't want to get a vaccine
It worked out for him and now everything the man says is opposite
It's all opposite
Mike Adams is out there telling everyone that
The opposite of what the World Health Organization says
The truth is true all the time
These aren't experts breakdown secret wisdom
Their children who haven't yet grown out of throwing 10
Yeah that's what this is
This is very clear
You can't
That's
That's the fun is not a fundamental misunderstanding
They have abs
Addendum and the
The like
No it's science is all about skepticism and all that stuff and it's like yeah but it
It's not about skepticism
Because you know a guy
One thing happened to one time
Or because you personally didn't get a vaccine one time and turned out fine
That's not
Skepticism isn't confirming the opposite it's not just automatically
Assuming
Whatever is said to you is a lie
That's
That's equally Steel
Unreal
That somebody would say that out loud
And not bother to lie
You got to have something better than port
Sometime I didn't get
Spell obviously all vaccines are lies
Stay in the damn bushes Rapaport
So now at this point
Things get weird
I don't have a board no more thing news.com is here with us in defiance of their thing
John Let's Get metaphysical termination segment
What is spiritually happening let's go down the rabbit hole from your deep research your great investigative journalist for decades
Your investigative
Yeah Allen Rover
A Woodward
I know you did some great investigative journalism but I want to talk to you about spirituality
So Roberts not complaining about Hollywood
Scoresby of course this clip is so funny
It's just in complaining about Hollywood
Response
Is so f****** stupid
What company coward
There are in Hollywood
Appear on the screen
To be the greatest
Superheroes in the world and so on
It's acting
And you say what do you think
Think about this
Don't you realize that she holding that yeah but I
I can't say any why can't you saying
I'm going to lose my position
Work in this town again
Who is he talking to in Hollywood
Noah
Show what
Who is Robert Downey jr. talking to you of course I have no answer for that but the answer is
Drugs
Lowering their own Consciousness protest
Standing there somebody else
Their job coming robots
Becoming robots
People who are robots
X
You have
For example
I don't know a million people
Independent country or its territory
The circle
In the circle it just keeps
Sean going
We're all together
Because
I'm looking at you and you're looking at
And we both know that we're complicit
It could be gigantic
It could be
100 million
Ellen Show on
It could be more
Oreo cookies
Jean-Claude told her this is what it's all about
Somebody like Bob Dylan
Really
You're going to join a call we advised that there are called to join
What
And just rails off also rebuttal
No you don't you got to join a cult
Nope nope
Americana Patriot called
Nope
You look at these guys on the screen and they're they're superheroes
Throwing hammers all over the place
And then you talk
Chris Hemsworth in real life and he doesn't want to say s*** about
Guard Amendment Hammer right
Yeah
Okay
You're very smart this is the high spiritual plateau
You see so many people in Hollywood they don't even
Robots.txt
Robot
Rapoport we have reached
Rarefied
This plateau of wisdom this
It's all about Rappaport
I don't understand loyalty
This is so weird
Why would you
We have this conversation at your medical iron
Anyway they start talking about the
Of this is a secret with all of my being
The devil.
System tells you you could be powerful you can be amazing you that I'm all these dreams
I put a mirror in front of your face
For your entire potential in forward
Shore show you your soul it says I will give you your soul
Follow me
That great vision is giving you is the potential
You already have that if you give it to Satan you lose your already made in the image
You're already Divine in God's will you already have all this potential
Taking you to give it power
To control you
Because you believe
That it's
Giving you that
Power
When God made you that way
Didn't give it to you made you
But your Freewill your maid
You're a Madman you're a Madwoman and they're trying to steal
That's the most frustrating thing
Watching people sign away their Birthright
Never they've got to these these midget Gremlins
Older
Then eyes and they're they're in placing themselves
In front of our vision
Exactly
He kind of it you got to be trained real well to listen to that
You got to have that
Plug-in loaded in your back pocket Rapaport study that
I don't know what research is
Medical Science a is doing to
You did come down on
Double mirror strategy I'm always amazed
At
Just how
The devil and God both to be both seem to be egg
Exactly as stupid as one Alex
They never seem to be Beyond his
Intelligent
It's strange it is to be like an ethical and unknowable on account of
Nope creating University of Texas
You okay
There's a trend that I see throughout a lot of Jon rappoport appearances and I've talked about this in the past
And that is that Alex
Often seems to have
Breakdowns whenever rap Horton
Therapy from Rapaport
Can't get himself to go talk
Talk to somebody needs help
And somehow Rapoport is like
The outlet for it I think it has to do with I mean
It's funny to call it in
Be the reason that Alex looks like a wizard
Obviously this guy looks like f****** Gandalf right and he's doing some kind of a mind-meld on it
Galax feel better whatever he talks to RAV4 it
This clip
Just feel like this is like an excerpt from therapy
God
These free will show how do you
Open yourself up to God
But not the bad stuff and just say cousin people open yourself to God you and jacket insulated
Connect to it
Iron do it but the point is
The David
How did people begin that Journey
Charged you do that
Either you recognize that
Your
You're an individual
You're not
Existing by virtue of the fact
Your
Two other things and people and so forth that's not the
The source of your exact
Facebook Goldman Sachs
You need you
If you start there
You're going to go on
On the path
See what's going on in Alex comes in with this weird question about like how do you let God in without letting all this
Southern stuffing
Rapoport takes that question and refocus
This is a tour
It being about individualism
Love you need you
And Alex
Take something from me
And then
Rapoport reaffirms
This is very similar to how like a conversation with a therapist
This reminds me that weird bulshit
Putting it in terms that are like almost usable almost
And then feeling like yes Alex
It reminds me more of hearing about somebody else's therapy like-like Rapoport is giving Alex
Advise that his therapist just gave him a little bit ago
With Entertainer
Who been through the f******
Crisis Millie well you know
I just I just realized I need to refocus on me
But I don't know
It's not annoying but
Well it's annoying to me as well to be certainly
Not a show
Interview
Supposed to be a medical
Expert
About what
The devil's mirror
Right right
Right I made it over
I forgot about that
I forgot that were passed
We're both Ubud how old is just completely Reckless
One last clip
And it's just like
I just feel like this is addictive like some sort of a brain control the report has on Alex
John report you got to come on more than once every 6 months please come back on next week we love you
Walmart.com your beautiful soul we love you John beloved on report thank you so much
I've never heard him be so like a few Civ with
Praise that love you
We love you Jaan I love you
John
I love you so
God dammit
Are you alive
Drift
SeaWorld never heard Alex
Say goodbye to a
Guest like that sort of
Chuck Rappaport that is like
It's otherworldly
John sometimes I just don't want to be one of the lone survivors vanities over but I'd
Just I just don't maybe I should die with it to Alex's individualist
You know you're right there is only one in Lone Survivor on my God I love your job
Weird
I'm on here it's nice to see you again
Positive
It's it's really weird because I remember that being something that I'd sort of
Ayodhya theorized that there is connection between these two and their interviews
Sometimes
Tend to Veer towards like Alex
Needing help Rapport being there to help her
And I also think
But
Just
There is
It's so weird
This episode
She's so weird there's more lies hoaxes mouth
The Coronavirus
There's Mike Adams
Declaring the end of humanity
John goddamn replicating weird
F***** up I think John has become the emotional Center of Infowars that I'm just going to go out
Mike Adams is to apocalypse
Alex that you obsessed with God and put in there for the individual is
The monologue yeah but also it makes sense that he's the heart
Cancel of invoice it is much as
He's f****** absent
Is there once every 6 months
So anyway we will be back
Another episode but until then
We have website that its knowledge
We also are on
We are at understand I'll just go fight not go to bed Jordan
We are on Facebook do you like to download iTunes labor video it said try to donate you know the whole thing please
You know I try
And I normally on this
With these aliases
I feel like an honor
Of Alex's love
We should probably end this by saying
Go f*** yourself Joshua