Air Jordan
I have great respect for its knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
We're couple dudes exit around technology Beverages and talk a little bit about
Alex Jones Jordan
Big event happened last night
What was last night's Sunday night
I don't know what day it is it's Tuesday while recording it for me Sunday night
That was rough
That's okay
Anyways
Is running around going
Rights to get into how is the Royal Rumble it was
Sunday
Glad you're at
Have some thoughts
It was fun it was really interesting the Royal Rumble Sundown and the 30 people enter the ring and then
Libro now Court
Be at the way they did it this year the it was a really interesting
Structure to it that I actually really didn't like
In the moment but I like
In hindsight
Sportsbook
Paradox of Brock Lesnar is the chair
YouTube Monster of a man
Paella beef everybody
I thought he was the champ and he decided he was going to enter the Royal Rumble and put himself in the
First he was number one
You're the number one entries heat up a flight through everybody but of course
What is a cocky
It seems like a bit of a car
Kaki bukit
It's so he enters first and of course he just beats up everybody who comes out come out
Get their ass kicked
Grown-ups the first guy was thrown out a media
Who is Elias
Whose character is this guy who has a guitar and he sings sarcastic
I forgot I watch wrestling a long time
So he comes out and he starts freaking the song insulting Brock Lesnar and so Brock runs out of the ring grabbed him and I
The way they give you like little moments of Hope like maybe a couple p
People be able to work
The Gathering take him out
Hey so it gets to like halfway through and all hope his likes would have been diminished right and then finally this big sky
Scottish guy named Drew McIntyre comes in and Ricochet kicks Brock Lesnar in the balls
McIntyre
Perfect perfect
And what you realize exerted in hindsight is like I had to do all this stuff
Kind of unsatisfying in a little bit like
Disappointing
In order to get you to enjoy
When McIntyre
Does yeah
I kind of enjoyed that and then the rest of the
The people who came out like
I know it is what it is for the rest of the rumble Championship they had a guy
Who's the wrestler who's around back in the Attitude Era and like back when I was watching way back
Yeah it was rated R superstar
And he had like a really
Really traumatizing neck injury about 10 years ago and he had to retire
It was just like this horrible thing where you know he has his emotional retirement tonight
Ldb loves being in that he had somebody
Craziest moments
From like back when I remember
Watching wrestling
And Christian these two guys were tag team
And they had these insane matches with The Hardy Boys
The Tables Ladders & Chairs match with irritation
Mystery
Antonio here to retire and it never
Seems like he was ever gone
Comeback
And he came out
In the 21
Out of control people freaking out
But what I found really amazing about it was
I gave you
Like watching the moment when he comes
Through the fog
The smoke machine that he has
He looks
Almost like he's going to cry
Like just this moment is that I am back
Doing this thing
There's a
Put wrestling aside
There's just such a human moment you can
Seeing his face
I would like a stadium full of people getting to
View of that moment
Begin
This is what I was
I was meant to do I never thought I'd be able to do it again
It's just so Universal and it just like it is amazing
Remember Lou Gehrig did that Ten Years After he retired
Take all of the
Bulshit people not liking wrestling or or whatever it
Whatever
Take all of that out of it
That moment
I think makes up for like
Any kind of
Negative
Review you might have like this match
Boring or whatever that makes a night
When putting on a 30-person Royal Rumble
Creating it
Life created that moment facilitated Andre
This much as it is like this emotional thing for for Edge it's also for the people who
Lovin and then missed
You know like as a performer
So that's those
Anyway I have a lot of feelings about
Save-A-Lot feelings about non-wrestling aspects
The wrestling
Very side-by-side got bar to your other stuff
Anyway that's up I guess right now I've been about that
Right
Date 2020
20 episode of The Alex Jones Show
I swear to God
Swear to God I wanted to not do a present-day episode because we've done a couple in a row
And I think we all kind of get the sense that Alex
It's just going to be talking about
The Coronavirus
And really exaggerating and being irresponsible about in it
A lot of chickens are going to get sick if they don't get that back
Feels like almost like you're just
Beating the same drum
And it's annoying
And so I wanted to try and do something else but man I went down a lot of avenues
And none of them
We're good
I listen to two episodes of Project Camelot where Kerry Cassidy interviews magician
And neither
We're any good now I feel like I have to go listen to them
Confirm for you I never I never listen but how can Carrie Cassidy f****** talking
Hugo 142 Italy
Are you got the time go watch him I don't give it to you
Alright
Only Project Camelot
See if I give a s***
Actually honestly pretty glad that I ended up being sort of backed into a corner with a bunch of like
This isn't this is not a good thing
To cover this isn't going to work
And having to reach
Treat back to the January
28th 2020
I think there are some things
Things that are are worthwhile in this
Some having to do with coronavirus some having to do with other stuff
And with all that in the moment
Before we do got to give a thank you to people who have signed up and are supporting
Ashok
Sarah thank you so much you are now a policy wonk
Is appropriate for the Royal Rumble
Samoa Joe you are now if I was Ewok
I guess emoji
Nope wall block
Next
Thank you so much Morgan you're now about
Brandon thank you so much you are now apology
But Kitty Unpretty thank you so much you and I'll probably walk
Maybe there's a big fan of TLC that's possible
Next Juiceman number 32 man thank you so much you and I will probably want
Bagaduce man number 32 man thank you very much
Say thank you to a couple people signed up on an elevated level appreciate that very much so first of all Mason
Thank you so much you are now a technocrat
David
Thank you so much too and I have a technocrat and Anthony thank you so much
You are now attacking
How's your 401k doing brother
Business
Money off that heroin
So good
Mason David and Anthony
Pizza
That sounds like a Dave Anthony from
Really into Mesa
If you are amazing inducted into the Scottish Rite and you would like to
The sport the show that we do here that you can do that like all your website now that's right. We would appreciate
Alright so we get down to business
Although then again I don't think our
Show should be funded primarily by
Outside the auspices of their Masonic Nessa
It looks like they say all money spends
Or whatever
I don't know
We start at the show and to Alex had some suspicions
Isn't it interesting that the coronavirus has been heavily study by the Chinese communist government
Foundation
Pay stub Foundation that bill and his father fun
Patented the Coronavirus
4u Shanna vaccine
They may be able to rush it
Into production to protect
And your family aren't we just blessed and lucky
We are
Conspiracy theory
Their sites out there saying that there's a government vaccine development this has been staged
Push
Vaccines on the public
But now
Nbcnews J&J scientific officer pretty confident they can pray
Coronavirus vaccine is outbreak widened because
Patented viruses of it
I've been patented for use in a backstage we just mix it all up and
Goodall is
You just mix it all
It's not
Suspicious that scientist to work not a vaccine for a novel strain of coronavirus that just appeared
What you'd expect
The entire history of every situation that ever happened like this
You can see here how Alex is incorporated that chicken vaccine patent into his narrative and laundered it so now it's just
Just accepted fact
This is often how Alex works and it's one of the things that honestly is most frustrating about doing this kind of work
If you aren't listening when the narrative launch
It's often compared
Wheatley impossible to track down what he's talking about because you just speaks in vague
Buzzwords
It evokes something to his audience
But like any of the details you need to
Confirm what he's
Saint
If you didn't know that he's lying about the
The pure bright Institute having a patent for a vaccine
For poultry
It'd be really hard to
The details of what he said in that last clip
Hey tray sit down and be able to learn more about what he's talking about
And that isn't intentional strategy
He's now turned this into a talk
The media didn't say that it was a
The Conspiracy Theory the people were working on a vaccine
Many of the articles that I've read and
Preparing for these episodes of mentioned that work was underway but that it would take a while if it was even really pause
Possible at all
Coronavirus Hazard notoriously hard
Great vaccines for in generally doctors tend to take the approach of
Just managing simple
Which are often the most dangerous part of the virus
For instance in the case of SARS
It was often that how it led
To pneumonia that was the biggest
Concern for medical
The catch-all for
Something done f***** up
But now there's water in your
Haha
So Alex is making up all that stuff about them having patents on the Coronavirus
Which is a lot in allowing scientist
To do their work
There's an article in the New England Journal of Medicine from January 24th which discusses AC DC investigation and research team
Examples
From which they were able to
Identify the viral genome sequence of this strain
All the information is perfectly available but I would rather yell about the gates family funding animal disease research
Get them help them build panic
He's business model largely relies on his audience being scared
In events like this are basically sweeps
Like a Superbowl for him
It's legitimately
Disgusting
That article that Alex is referencing is about Johnson & Johnson
Or J & J
And how their Chief scientific officer said he's confident that they could make a vaccine
Alex didn't read this article
Calling them J&J
Is reading the headline
There's nothing in that article that talks about them having patented viruses and just mixing them all up
In fact the article explicitly says quote
Stoffels who's the John Cena John
Chief scientific officer
Said that the pharmaceutical company needed to start from scratch
On this vaccine
Giant kind of runs counter
Pair to the narrative italic
But you know when you when you bake
Scratch you have all the ingredients and you just mix them up so that can still
I'll still give him that
Okay I'm not because
Really
All this is is trying to heighten the mood heightened your height in the panic
And then funnel it somewhere
Yeah it's very clear where that
Infomercial is going
On this episode
We have had
Sources
Play the big food industry
I'm your Chevrolet
Suppliers that institutional groups
Food prices raw food prices
AR
That indeed is now happening in your now seeing that the news today
Selling out
Suppliers are already sold out
Relational doubt the big institutional group
My Patriot that pumps out Infowars select
A sticker on it
Still has food
Still able to guarantee delivery within 7
Days
They can do that I can tell you
But
That could change any time that means if you get your order in now
You will get it within seven
29-0 my God there's a crisis going on and it's causing food prices to go up really
Say hi but hey call my bakery supplies Celtic area
All these other places they don't they don't even have any food
You want to buy food but you can't get it anywhere else
Interesting Lee the US Department of Agriculture
Just put out their food price Outlook report for
For 2020
And what are you doing
It's the exact opposite of what Alex
The thing
Rumor report
The 2020 consumer price index forecast indicates a continuation of low inflation at grocery stores
Answer for Mark
In 2020 food at home prices are expected to increase in the range of between .5 and 1.5
Percent as potentially the fifth year in a row with
Deflating or lower-than-average inflating retail food price
Sweet there's a 20-year historical average
2% rise in
Send food prices
So this is well within
Then or even below that ever
Gap
Given overall inflation factors
This could be a maintaining or even
Decreasing of point-of-purchase
Price for consumers within the United States
This is true the United
States where Alex's primary Market of listeners is Loki
However it's not uniformly true in the world
Princeton Cindy is currently seeing food prices
Is Jump considerably with most experts point
Oil price
Instability is being a major
You're factor in the country's retail Market
Inflation
Another major driver is the supply chain
To quote an article from Court
Quote
Prices of vegetables and fruits were driven High because
Crop damage
It's caused by excessive an unseasonal rain
Supplies
I can't imagine that many of these people in India that are affected by this or the target market of Alex's
Food buckets
So I don't know how this
I think there's a
Maybe
I don't think you don't go for dialysis
So there's also a recent article in the BBC about how brexit will likely lead to higher food prices in the of the UK
And the people there would probably Disney
Need to adjust to that
But Alex is in favor of brexit
So doesn't seem like you would want to bring that up
As a potential consequence
Avari adjust my
Yeah it does seem like brexit is going poorly when
After everybody's already agreed
To brexit
Oh yeah your food prices are going to go up this is going to go out this week
Going to go up I don't know if you guys do this
It was a battle
So there's also been reports and writers about Rising food prices in Wuhan
I'm turning the corner
And I think that's a problem
I've not seen any numbers are hard information but the exact
Kind of rising prices so it's
Kind of difficult
For me to assess
But this is the kind of thing you see in most
Emergencies
Situations
Unfortunately
People get gas prices when they have the ability to do so
I just last week you saw Uber and Lyft
Charging people insanely elevated rates after the shooting in downtown Seattle
There was increased demand it so the price for the available Supply Rose
Like in that case if it was the result of
Like automated algorithm
It's not like a militia
It's from a human standpoint
But it's just mirroring what happens with
You know a lot of
Exactly what they desire the freemark
There are laws in place in the United States that forbid price gouging
Situation
Is when a state of emergency has been declared but that law doesn't apply
The other countries
And honestly you can find a lot of people here in the United States
To take a position
Like if
You're in the position to sell someone
Something they need to survive you should be able to charge them whatever the f***
You want
These people are often libertarian
Which Alex pretend
Going to be so I don't know what
Philosophical position
He comes from where he's a
Supposed to price guide
Whatever is happening on the day
Rights for against
And that is the
Right anyway my point here is that the rising
Food prices in Wuhan Arkansas
And it's something that the Chinese government has made clear that they are aware
And we will see
See what happens from there
The larger Point here is that Alex is selling these food buckets
Not to people in Wuhan
He's selling them to people in the United States
He's trying to use the Optics of that City in quarantine too pushy
Cheese product
Inches disgust
Yeah and the underlying messages
This is going to happen to you
Even if it's not happening now here
You can already know because the globalists are using this to take a worldwide and kill
6 billion Peter
And that the may not be an underlying message a little bit later the trip
Yeah might be an explicit
It does seem odd that you'd be selling food buckets if previously we've already
Confirm that the world is already
Done and the human races
Oh yeah
For Humanity
There will only be lone survivors
So I mean
You want to be one of the lungs it's all still makes
Mark Wahlberg
So Alec
He's talking about these Rising food prices
Citizen his food bucket
It's being the solute
Listen to it so it's kind of funny that he ends
Is plug like that
My Patriot
Bring your distributors
Square.com that we were way lower than all of them but they
I'm at the lowest price for my Patriot Supply
Comedy or just goes to them every
According to the UN Zone definition the Coronavirus
Okay obviously
Obviously
Sure obviously
How could you not know that
I love her Alex's blood for the food buckets is based on the idea that food prices are going up so this is the solution to that and ended up saying that the
Prices of a suit pocket
Are going out loud
Seafood prices are gone
Give me the Department of Agriculture and said the food prices are not projected to go off it seems like some of the narrative he's do
This might be a rationalization for him Verizon
Prices so you can
Make a little money
Woody's been clear he's not been doing lately I could be home money is coming in
You are looking at your sales and you're going like who the
The food is down
If we got a virus
Guess who can't eat food now
If you're not making money
At the current
Rate of sale or whatever one of the strategies you could employ is rising margin
This might be a rationalization to
Raise margins to make money without having to say that's what you're doing
Seems
Maybe like a
I'm not sure
Also I'm not sure that the UN has a formal definition of pandemic that's really meaningful
Alex may have wanted to see the World Health Organization but he's just rif
I think so he's mine just plugged in the um
I think
There's a lot of controversy with the World Health Organization and their definition
The pandemic
Menu at the World Health Organization say they don't really have a definition but they have description
What constitutes
The pandemic
And they all over
On the Border
That is true
Generally the guideline the people go by is that
That none of the six phase model that we discussed
Some last episode
Basics and a pandemic
Wisely pandemic face
An outbreak has characterized by a quote
Virus causing community-level outbreaks in at least two World Health Organization region
According to that definition de coronavirus outbreak does not constitute a pandemic
At this point
There is a community-level outbreak in China but we do not have evidence that is
Is the case in any other region where there have
Ben cases confer
So
Eva is Alex
Wants to talk about the World Health organization's definition
It doesn't apply but it's
Turns out
And he's not talking about the UN definition he's not even talking about the World Health Organization definition
Here's what he's talkin to
The definition of a pandemic
Merriam-Webster
Alright
Sites
Current traffic
Unaffected
Exponentially High
Proportion
Populations exponential mean
Go to Merriam Webster
She'll help you out
Elgin
Now don't do this
Exponentially
Stop it no this is not going to go well
Dublin
Time
And spread
People use the word exponentially to just mean something is growing rapidly like in the
Kukla colloquial sense but it does have an actual meaning that Alex
Definitely doesn't know
It means that growth is characterized by
I think this mulch
Lakeisha not like double
At the first interval it's just the base growth
At the second
It's not rape
Squared at the third it's Patrick cubed
And so on
Typically in the early stages of viruses
Spreading they do sometimes 10 show exponential growth
Until there's a countervailing force against it
Like a vaccine or
Some sort of intervention meth
This is not really all that controversial
But it's a little strange to recognize that Alex doesn't know what the word exponential mean
Also the Merriam-Webster definition of pandemic has literally no bearing on what the World Health Organization or you and Mike declared
To be a panther
Alex can't use this dictionary to post
Some kind of a gotcha
On this one doesn't work I don't know
I'm pretty sure he mailed it also get this
Definition of pandemic
The point about exponential design
Call raging pandemic
Merriam-Webster
Definition
Rodger rabbit area
Affecting a
Lehigh
Abortion
Population
Alex just added the word exponentially because he wanted to
By the textbook definition
Change the definition
I just
The mind boggles at how bad you can really be
Like you can be so bad at it
Still get millions of dollars yeah
Infuriated what's fascinating about how bad he is at it is he's bad at hiding the Badness
It's somehow just like
Yeah it's fine if I just admit I'm just throwing random words.
The change definition
So did
You know he's creating fear about this
Outbreak
Certainly
But one of the other things that he's doing
When is Easter
Now at the stage
In his coverage where it's important
The pivot the sphere
Into what's going
Going to come
Because he knows that eventually this what we won't be able to make money on this forever
And so he does that
Rundown
People
A lot of pollution
Hours of break out there then
Terrible thing
B a response to it
Got no wings
Article share where they're saying
Google and Facebook are blocking Liars explaining this was made in a lab
Vaccine for it as part of a larger plan
The long histories
Publix
Vaccines of the things I
Call Dad
Spock admitting they put cancer
Play PBS
Interviews if you want to see him
Helaman in an interview
Saban
He can play the PBS clips and in it it does say salt does say source of many people and
Doctor says there's too many people anyway in the clip that he plays
Has played in
Example
It's
Not
Salt
Sock is not involved
Albert Sabin
Get your information right Alex
And I'm like dude
Yes of course
I I think the
These places like Facebook
The platforms
It's a certain amount of responsibility
To everything is at a noun
Delete
People being hurt
I I think that it is
It's totally fine
When Alex says why would
You speculate about this stuff
It's one thing to be specular
It's another tab
Be a liar who's trying to sell food bucket and weird pills
It's
It's not
It's not the same
Facebook isn't
Oak Washington Post
On Facebook where it's like
Suspicious of the government
They are questioning malicious actors like Alex.
Misinformation
Front then
What is AK
You know we should be cautious
This about
Informed opinions are different than
Haha the Chinese are released in order to
It's different informed opinions are usually better than
We're all going to die
Bye-bye food
I think this next trip is actually really clearly Devon
Dude why Alex is not just being
Suspicious and speculating
Yes is viruses deadly
It's not like SARS and things that were just a hype up and scare people why not
This is already killed thousands and thousands
What
Comprehend
It does have a high kill rate
18%
According to a BBC report from January 28th
The day of this app
Episode The confirmed death toll is currently
Conversely tsar's killed 778 people but another important aspect of that is that there were deaths
Different countries from SARS
As opposed to the current situation which is been entirely in China
A death is a death that is true
But from the perspective is like
Gauging the spread of a virus
It matters a lot where the Death Star have
If they're in a bunch of different countries
It it demonstrates a difference
Situation
Alex is completely outside the accepted reality with his claim that thousand
Thousand
Who died from this outbreak
I suspect that he's getting this information from noted Muslim hater
Pamela Geller's website
Where she posted a breaking story about there being 10
10000 dead
According to factcheck.com this story was sourced from a blog post on a website that's largely about gold
Quote which has a disclaimer that says
Vouch for the accuracy orca
Completeness of its information
Now that is a big disclaimer
Quite
I think we might be lying is a huge disclaimer
This website
JS mine
Mine set.com it published in
Email an anonymous person sent them who is relating
A phone call he had with a friend
And spoken to a Chinese friend who had information for
Family in Wuhan
If you're keeping track
At bat
This is for panda information at the point of this blog post
The alleged family in Wuhan is first
The Chinese friend a second
The friend on the phone is 3rd
The anonymous email her is 4th
Then Pamela Geller using the site as a source
Sleep and information on her site
No one who operates a legitimate news or information out that wood
Ever accept this kind of work
It's just gossip
Basically she will be testifying in the impeachment hearings
Chosen only her to test it will not be spread
Alex is misusing the information also in that Lancet article that he's talking to
In the actual article researchers examined 59 cases of people who'd been admitted to Chinese hospital with pneumonia
Symptoms
Which they've been whittled down to 41
Who also tested positive for the novel Coronavirus
All of them had pneumonia which indicates that these are all
The most severe sort of cases
Among the larger population of people who come down with the virus
Just on Viscount
This is not a fair study to extrapolate to the entire population or even the entire population of people who come
I'm down with a Coronavirus
No no viral
No virologist would be like 41 that's enough of it
Yeah and none would take
That information
That is provided in this paper and then say that if
Whatever you all the time for all
The report says there's a 15
18% incidence of patients
In that 41
Sample size
Which is 6
However
28 individuals or
3% recover
Edward discharged from the hospital but Alex says one point that out
Also it's hard to say if there's any direct parallels here but
Of the same
Set that they had
15% of the patient
And also had pre-existing
Existing hypertension
And 15% had a history of cardiovascular
Based on the information available in the report I can't say if those are all the same 50
I'll but it it's just a illustrate that there are cold
Mingling variables
But Alex isn't
Considering
And
Make this a
I don't think anybody thinks
Step most
I'm at maybe I'm
Way off base
Since we're dealing with Alex
People believe any
But
In most viral cases
Nobody is saying that the most healthy members of society are going to
You instantly died
If they get this coronavirus it's generally
The Alden children
Generally
Most
Regular people are saying
Yeah
Looks like nobody believes that nevermind
I want to sing straight up 15% of the 18% of people who get the
They're going to die
10% of everyone
Also the report even says quote with the limited number of cases
It's difficult to assess host risk factors
For disease severity and mortality with multivariable adjusted method
This is a modest-sized
Case series of patients admitted to
Collection of standardized data for the larger cohorts
Would help to further Define
The clinical presentation natural history and risks
To put that more succinctly what they're saying is
This is a small group that we looked at and we need more information
Don't know if any of this could be
Explained by other variables
About the specific people that we looked at
Whatever impact that might have had
On the results
I see this is where we getting
Into trouble again
Yes I understand what you were saying
And I indeed understand your interpretation of what he was saying
But ultimately let's boil it down still further
We don't know yet we still got a little work to do
Sure
Via interesting Lee
Even this study doesn't say there's death rate of 80
10%
This again is another example of Alex being unable to stop himself from exaggerated
From lying to make his narratives more severe
He strips literally all contacts from this Lancet report
Exaggerated its conclusion
While simultaneously blindly reporting as gospel some dumb fifth hand bulshit
Pamela Geller post on her blog
This is just embarrassing a dangerous work here and you should be ashamed of himself
I don't even like. I don't even like the use of a percentage
Whenever you're dealing with sex
Just small stamp
I would prefer a fraction
Because 15% people go like
Oh well 15 out of 100
Not six out of
No it's those things where
It's like
We do
It doesn't it's not
I don't know how you're feeling for me update
Hey when we get
Get to 100 you can use percentages until then
It's fractions all the way
Fair enough that when you're in charge
That's it
So Alex has a pretty severe news about the United States
And this by
And
I don't think
Because I don't know how to make it but if you go to infowars.com you see the live feed headline
It's official this is now a global pandemic
Coronavirus
Us
Officials believe
But the virus has already
Broken out of containment on the way
Ghost
What
When was hitting containment on the bus
I believe it
Really what they said that they said something else
We Believe
With Johnny students that came in
A massive emergency
How to figure out how to
Announce to the public
I can find literally no evidence for anything Alex is saying here other than his own words
As of this recording there are five cases confirmed the virus in the United
States and all of them have been people who had been to Wuhan
There's no evidence
Has there been any person to person
Some Transmission in the United States
I have a particular disrespect for Alex and that he doesn't want to pay
Literally everything he's been doing is
TaylorMade to cause a certain amount of panic
In a certain type of
But panicking people
When he said that he doesn't want a panicky means he doesn't want people to lose their s*** in
Start looting
He doesn't want that kind of
He wants a controlled Panic he can profit off of
He wants to stoke just enough fear in his audience that he can get them to buy all this food
But not enough that they start killing people
He is a calculated monster
That's why he throws in things like I don't want to cause a panic
Yes sir to try and reel it back in a tiny bit
But at the same time make
Get super sensational
Cuz we know if we have 10 days of panic when people are going to start eating you true
Cannibalism I want to put that on
Gravestone
That's not what they
They said they actually
You can't you can't even do that.
That punching me in the face and telling me you did
That's just an example of him being bad at this bad thing
So this is just grow
Last week to say 47,000.
So this whole thing is out of control we be praying about it
How about a vaccine personally
Have been
Vitamin D3 vitamin
Great great
Great stuff
I'm you can just see it's like
It's clear if you if you without him awful if you listen to a show with a
Any sort of a critical eye
Orire
All you see is like oh all of this is really getting ramped up
And then you funnel it some
Really fun
All these hundreds of thousands
The people they do know it's all everyone's lying about this what you need to do
All day food prices are skyrocketing everywhere it's going to be a disaster no one can find food get my bucket
All its 8
Clear formula even used
Car salesman looked out no used car salesman is going to go out there and be like
Hey man looters are going to light your car on fire you better go to backup
Get a backup right now your car will be lit on fire tomorrow and if not tomorrow
So it's the season of health and that means that the health Ranger is on everyday now
Time stops in for a little visit
Isn't that it is a situation where you sort of blew the officer the finale a little bit early
You wait till the end of the week
Interview situation now we're like
Alex should be like all right we got like Adams on the show is reporting live from a bunker deep underground where you stocked up
We got back out of here who put his f****** money where his mouth is undisclosed location
Coronavirus
As we all know it only takes me 5 days to Aid go cannibal so
Let's see what happens
Yeah I mean
It's all very stupid but
Yes
They're just beer bong
I guess it's really
Absurd
Global pandemic
No
Media in America
Is now complicit
Cover up
Cost millions of
Will get people
Killed
The same media that pushes transgenderism or they going to do next
Trans vitalism
Identify is a person who doesn't have the virus
Hospitals in California
That's how you know they're not taking
Any of this that is the most
Teddy bears joke
Ain't that the Matt elfring character
So what person listening knows what you're talking about
Yeah I mean that's just like
This s***
I mean you're just taking opportunities to get your weird social pun
Launch is in
Evian
Transgender what's next
Trim virus
Everybody
Nobody
Good stuff
Alright I'm going to need another beer
Here's where Alex
Gets down to like
I think this is what he thinks
The conspiracy is
If this is
You been hard I am so alive for more than 3 weeks
This could be a bioweapon released to bring down the global economy is a way to counter nationalism
Global to shed bad economy for Nationals
So everything is about them
If they can't they're incapable of
Understanding a larger world that isn't about themselves
I don't understand something like this virus
Brake is not
Just a natural phenomenon the people need to come together and
Try and
Mitigate the damage has helped each other as best as possible
No it's an attack on Trump and nationalism
This virus was released by the club
In order to spread
A panic whatever
Crash the stock market which
You know the Domino's you keep seeing which one Falls Boom at the end
Trump and nationalism earlier attack
It's so
I don't even know a cynical doesn't even seem like the right word
Damn it's such a disgusting
I m Norse is he is speaking for the Sheridan
Experience of humanity most of us
Live in Austin
In a mansion and make millions of dollars scamming people with with pills
That's a normal thing that's a human behavior that we all share
Right
Oh well then
He's a narcissist
So Alex gets back to trying to sell food bucket okay because I really
I can't stress
Isn't it comes up over and over and over and over again
It is just like
A very
Consistent like marketing
Give him a call
Yes yes
They just know well enough
To know like this
Is good opportunity
I have sources an industry that have talked to all the big storable food company had
Institutional buyers started
Who are the
Lineup
Then it exploded
Friday basically everybody was sold out
Suppliers that are
The biggest Supply
Literally
Horrible food
Third-party sold out
My Patriot is boxing and they needed
Fast as I can
You got to drink for sure.
Vonda Smith exact same assembly line
Star Sticker
More select never done before if we can
Plug year
Talking to the folks there
Tires
I just stopped by the post office
But it's
Let me guess the West Coast Mission yeah course West Coast
And I said
Obviously that's the first
Playsets
Obvious Chinese cities in United States
Seattle
What's going on
This is so ridiculous
Alex is trying to spend a conspiracy that the coronavirus is going to explode in the west coast and Seattle due to the high Chinese population
Canon Seattle
We're apparently it's traditional buyers of food or storing up tons
The stops we need to act now by survival
Food buckets
That sounds right there a few problems with this Theory
What are
Seattle has the ninth-highest chinese-american population of major US cities with approximately 30,000 Chinese
Those are the ones you know
Compare that to the 562 thousand Chinese Americans in New York
You should get a scale between
First and night nobody's going to
Send a virus out to New York you start with
Seattle there that's close to
To Portland and all get-out it's all over for the lips
Alex did say the Westco
So I'm going to take New York out of the equation
Let's consider there are 180,000 Chinese Americans in San Francisco 77,000
Los Angeles 75000 San Jose
43000 in Oakland
Thirty-four thousand in Irvine California all higher
In Seattle
College students is nonsense to
The biggest school in Seattle is the University of Washington Seattle and they've a smaller Asian student body than UT
Also
The case of the personhood coronavirus in
Washing
In state
He wasn't a college student
Any wasn't in Seattle
Who's the man in his 30s who lived in Everett Washington
Honestly all this he doing going to Wuhan a businessman do I want to know the what's going on with this guy
Online Jordan
Dachshund bad idea
That sort of speculation makes more sense than what Alex is doing
Guy was doing in China is
Amor sensible conspiracy
Then this
Comes down to make it trying to make Chinese Americans
Scary to Alex's audience
It's Ellie's food
Yeah that's never gone wrong we've never treated an entire Asian population negatively in this time
This is all just
S*** this is an infomercial for the food
Also of course
Looming in the background
The pals
Are you getting the food you might have
Might as well
Mix it up
So there's more
Conspiracies a fuk
Can a smart guy even Main Line news in Shanghai
Stolen by Tchaikovsky
The same people were involved it turns out and weird stuff for the bowling weird stuff
This sounds like a movie script
Parmalee
What are you doing on here
Interesting
Three or four or five
My days ago that was immediately called fake
Mainstream media now they are reporting and confirm
So
We weren't
News we were ahead of their news
I just replied to here's what Mike Adams was saying a couple days ago
It's over for Humanity
Lone survivors
Okay he's really not bring it on this
Joke season it's not going well
So that story Alex is talking about beating mainstream news it's not
It's b*******
This all started with a guy on Twitter named Kyle bass posting a CBC news story from last July adding the caption
Husband and wife Chinese spy team were recently removed
From a level four
Infectious disease facility in Canada
For sending pathogens to the Wuhan facility
This tweet was retweeted thousands of times in the story began to take traction
Conspiracy community
The only problem is
Is the article that he linked to didn't say any of that stuff
That's not what they
They said they said some
Well
Alex Trebek
The two people who were taken out of the national microbiology lab in Winnipeg were suspected of making an administrative violate
And every organization that's involved in this matter as well as the CBC reporter
I'm stressed that nothing surrounding this case
Involves any kind of public danger or anything close
To what this
Tweet is electric
Zerohedge started taking taking this as a launching Point start speculating the China stole the virus as a bioweapon is it
Caught fire in the dumb dumb world's people who don't read
These people are out
For sensationalism and trap
In the prospect
Two Chinese spies sending the very same virus that ends up causing an outbreak is a really good way to get eyeballs on your s***
But it's not supported by actual facts
Reporting
To the point where someone
Like CBC is reporting
Fitbit going to do reporting a couple of Chinese scientist to remove
Fermilab in July that's fair game
Does did happen
It's supported by available evidence
In order to come up with the rest of the
The stuff that people like Alex are saying about this door you can make up a whole lot of details
And simultaneously you have
Insist that everyone who commented on this story is lying
Did you shity stuff
That's that's
There is no conspiracy he won't latch onto
Who is
Terrible just such bad work
They will
Lee Papa
Any desperate thing
Just one tweet the right-wing machine will find it and they'll turn it in
If it works million illegal
Said f*** off
Right
So you might ask at this point you know like
Hey
Why isn't Trump
Doing any
I don't know why you would ask if
It's broken
Containment and right now at all right
Why isn't he stopping flights
It's from China what is doing anything
Wow no
Turns out
Mike Scott Mike knows
Why isn't Trump
Sorry no Chinese coming into the United States
You always see how bad this is for sale week or so
Exactly
My criticism of the
The president on this issue
Tractors here number one
Is he's a very successful
Intelligent person
Not have experience in epidemiology of virology or Laboratory
Expert
You are no doubt lying to him
Exactly right
He doesn't know how to ask
They are making this up
Sounds like
Trump is going to need a 20-point I do Health Ranger
That's all just made up there's there's nothing behind that
Obviously you know that
The health Ranger who have deemed Humanity over driving what's up
It does seem like he he's he's planning for a future that doesn't seem to be also part of his plan
For the future
So that's the one vector
That Mike has to criticize drunk on Expert friends
I got share advisors are like them
Here's the second Vector which is
So much worse
He's very much
Concern that any loss of faith
Could
Taxes reelection chances
Bubble Market depends on irrational exuberance
Irrational exuberance is fear
Fear of the unknown
Causes people to sell stocks
None of the stuff that Alex in my car saying is connected to reality at all but I think this clip is really in
You have Mike basically saying the Trump isn't
Taking the
Coronavirus outbreak seriously because he doesn't want to hurt the stock market it does hurt his chances for re-election
Mike Adams
Trump will let Millions die to get re-elected
Even in their fantasy world where they're bending over backwards to
Defend an indefensible present
They still have to fall back on excuses like
Trump would act
Protect the health of American citizens but his personal interested re-election is more important to him that he is going to stand
End up for honest
Everyday Americans by letting a large number of them die in order to facilitate Israel
This would just make me think that these people have
No idea what they're even saying
But they're openly expressing support for a leader who would risk the lives of the entire country if it means holding onto power
And yet somehow they point the finger at the last
Does being obsessed with
Guy holding onto power at all costs
Victor fake SeaWorld doesn't even make sense
It's absurd
Mike Adams
Obvious
Like
Explanation of how to
Exploit the bubble economy is very fresh
That's all that should be illegal
It depends on irrational exuberance and means no rational person would think it's a good idea
So
Money
Mike
He's just making so much s*** up like this is all made up
One stress that before we even listen to this clip
There is nothing to back this up
It is Mike's
Ideas
Fantasies
Yesterday in the show Alice I believe that they were working on this strand
Yet ready to release it
Why
Needed a few more tweaks
Before they were ready to release it
They would have released in China on purpose
Africa
Hampton Inn North America or Mexico City
I get the blame of this
What
They're just making this up none of that means anything
That's just like hey this is what I feel isn't even more interesting if we talked about it like
Like this it was a bioweapon that they plan to release somewhere else but it got out of the lab too early by accident
Yeah it does seem like they're more
Spitballing script ideas
More like they're they're tossing ideas
Doesn't
He's my cat he put a bullet in his own bloodstream
Which is worse
So Alex
If you ever if you need any indication that he's an opportunist
Easy crafts
Piece of s***
Just trying to sell stuff
This is
Maybe is good as yours
Because of what's happening I said I couldn't get 50% off anymore because
Doesn't give us the margins to find herself
Going to then
We have an emergency like this
Raise prices on the Protestants
Lower them
That couple days it's snowing out right now okay
By the way
Products super silver toothpaste 50
Got to have big sales now because it got to strike while the Iron's hot there's a situation that I can exploit to cause
Panic
That leads people towards maybe wanting to buy the
The things that I have given better
What is the move all this product
I mean I use Visa
Lost leaders and hopefully the profit margins on the food buckets that I have pushing
Real heart
Maybe it'll all work out
It's it's soy
Yeah
Places are bad grift yeah
Yeah it's really pretty disgusting
Now we're done with
But
Alex has another guy
This guy
Is a holocaust
He is someone who
I think we can just leave Holocaust denier is assume
It's at least
Lurking in the background is too many of his gas
He's a guy who is a made-up resume
And his name is dr. Steve pieczenik
Ads
Alex Alex
But yeah
It's not the right
To also declare the end of humanity no
He's on to talk about John Bolton
And I'm alright is
Alex
It's clearly doesn't that any of his gaster nose really well because
The spoiler alert Steve ends up completely contradicting Alex's virus narrative
Great booking
Like I said he's on to talk about Bolton
And here is Alex
Steve pieczenik on
Casinos
Bolton
Neocon ways and the time
What the hell you doing
I have no idea Steve actually knows John Bolton although I can save it
The last time Steve was definitely in the state department was
Prior to Bolton interpublic entering public service
At that time John Bolton was a lawyer at the firm of Covington
Berlin
Also steep did Wornall
Alex about John Bolton
Trump can't allow him to be in the White House
And Alex didn't listen to him
Because Rodger told him that Bolton was
Cool
You can try
I don't want to I'm not going to give
Steve-O
Hatred of all things
Things neocon whatever
Anyway Steve immediately
A pretty quickly gets to saying they're like a man what they're doing with
Virus outbreak
Totally cool
Transit and she appreciated with Trump have said
Transparency in China
Seclusion
Different areas and
Because of the flu
Oops
Steve's eyes Cecil point of the matter is there two other handling this appropriately
I don't need to worry about appreciate them they it's mutual appreciation
Humanity is going to last
Thousand more years working to get to the stars that populate the entire gal
So a lot of these appearances just yelling dumb nonsense about how like the state is pointless and what-have-you
Elizabethtown of that but there are some points that are kind of Interest
Sing like this
What's really happening at
Point is the absurdity
A representatives and how little they really do it
Time of need right now we have a world
Is it going to
CBS maybe no
Surgeon General appointed
Service office has been appointed
House of Representatives job
Steve does make a great point though like he hasn't seen that there be a surgeon
Now Yasin
I wonder why Dan
I wonder why
It seems like somebody
Somebody has the ability to appoint a surgeon-general I wonder
I mean Steve doesn't
Think the House of Representatives is really failing us on this one
I don't know
So Steve has this weird thing
Where he thinks that the newspapers talked to him
Eddie thinks
Back to powerful people
When he comes on Alex's show remixes YouTube videos
And I would generally are on the side of thing
Thinking it's like just sort of a flourish of language
Or something
But it's soaking
Consistent
Again in this next copii
He really seems to think like
He's sending a message
Nancy Pelosi
Through Alex
Idiot savant
We had
That we are a republic
Not a democracy so she went
I can read all about
He's really to be expressing their
Rue Alex's show they have taught Nancy Pelosi about the nature of a republic and she's gone and done
Some research on it
This is this is seriously Disturbed Behavior
That doesn't sound like any kind of rhetorical flourish say that seems like he is remembering fundly a time when
You taught Nancy Pelosi
The rules
The Republic I don't think that haven't either
So Alex is having a good time talking to Steve
But
You know all good things
Must be interrupted
Did when you need to make sales
I am not an opportunist
My goal is to promote the lifestyle and
Up against the Tyranny that the globalist promote
Because I believe you're going to want to buy in
To having a free open
Truly
Constitutional Renaissance BAE Systems
Show The Americans
Tricom system or the EU
Return of modern nobility models are
Steve pieczenik
Notice
The last few months I'm saying hey
Vitamin D3
And very strong
Hide your phone
In the winter
It's getting son that
Boost your immunity
Deficiencies
Knock on wood I have
Had a fever in over 4 years and it's because I
Fish oil everyday
Are the best sources of natural
Vitamin D3 vitamin K
1% off you know it's very close to selling out
Set within a minute easy start saying by saying I'm not an opportunist and then he's using this
Outbreak as an opportunity
It is the most
Infuriating verbal Tikki has
Of starting every sentence
With saying I'm not
And then does exact right
I'm not bragging
Right
I'm not an opportunist
Take opportunity opportunity
As a reference
The edge
Anyway bring me the Cowboys
It sings Alex talks a little bit
He's not a cowboy
He was a Drifter but he's not a cowboy
Continues this plug
And honestly I think I only kept this in cuz you said something I did
A bad mood
Radio show
Do I bring a bottle of wine and drink 4 cups of coffee
It doesn't work for me
Big old juicy
Gross
No good
Makes you sleep better
Your body is really amazing
First of all
Juicy Fishel Elitch's that ridiculous
Yeah
Cool Google
So
This might sound
What drug is this Steve comes back in
He has something to say about this
Coronavirus
And
This
Clip
Is r
Okay
This is a masterstroke of Steve pieczenik
Using language
This could be an Agatha Christie okay alright alright
We have a cronut coronavirus coming in
Be safe
The reason I can
90s because I treated a patient
First cases
Coronavirus before was ever reported
Chinese individual
Pneumonia
And was treated with high doses of antibiotics
I'm saying to the Public Health Service
Attorney General
Together
Steve pieczenik is patient zero Coronavirus
Oh you're f******
Raising
Treated yourself for the first case of this coronavirus everything that's in Port
Every
Relevant world event
Steve is at the center of not only the first person
Takeout Coronavirus
He also cured himself
I just
I just can't hang with that I can
That was bananas
That needs a
Commitment
Just like
Yeah man you're amazing
So anyway Steve Took issue earlier with the fact that there is no Surgeon General
And what do you know Alex starts
Repeating that client
I agree he should have them
Something is really bad
Man I mean it is a really interesting point that now like Steve is brought up if there's no Surgeon General and Alec
Good because I like because Steve is that he's repeating it as like that's a real criticism
Surgeon General is named Jerome Adams
He was confirmed by the United States yes it was confirmed by the Senate on August 3rd 2017
If you want to make a point that he's not doing a good job go ahead
Do it
The bureaucracy is making sure there is no Surgeon General
Both of these dudes don't even know that there is a surgeon-general you don't even know that he's a real person
Have you seen him in person
Pictures
Where is now mister
Big picture guy let me tell you something
Fake dude
Steve pieczenik within those pictures and they took him
I'm out Steve is coming in and making an argument I haven't seen that there's a Surgeon General right
And now Alex is like
Doubling down on it and either these dudes even know anything
Anything about what they're talkin
F****** surgeon-general you dumbasses
Was the first place
Don't know how you can listen
You too man say
Confidently
Just so proudly
Bracelet
I was the first man with this Global pandemic
What month before it became an outbreak it's even better than China better than that
Because like I can't stress enough how
Great the storytelling of that clip was
The eye treated
The first patient very well because
Level a pageant
Straight to it that I appreciate
Yeah
That person is
Steve Hunter said I was the first person who got Coronavirus
You wouldn't Bora Bora this is a master at work
Oh you treated him personally tell me more about that
City with you this is a twist
Said I could not have been coming every night you
Gorgeous.
Alex has been
Reading Merriam-Webster's Dictionary and adding words to definitions in order to prove that this is
Pandemic
How many is Steve pieczenik who is
According to Alex on all things
And
Let let me ensure your audience in the American audience
Where would not condemn it
We have to
This will be
Control
Want everybody
Panicking
Oops
Shut him up right now
You can let him say that you wouldn't want anybody
Lying about having
You were the owner addicting at the pandemic that's hybrid
That's brutal
Steve recognizes that maybe
He's contradict
Doing some of the narratives that Alex is using
To try and drive sales
And so he decides I'm going to go ahead and also help
Do you sell pelts
That you're saying is correct
K2 vitamin D
Fish oil
Stay healthy
And you're less likely
Pneumonia
Getting pneumonia sore coronavirus is the immunity system so as long as your immunity system
Even if you're 60 70s
But you're young
She's not going to be leaf
Number one
We don't have a Surgeon General and a public
How service is disturbing we do have a surge
General
This whole thing is based on a faulty premise
I guess we don't have to worry about it
I guess
Steve
Yeah
Man
He is done every
Really seems to have
Every single thing that has happened since like the mid-70s
Steve is Hattiesburg
Fingering
He was also the first person to get HIV
Hear that
Absolutely did
Have
Play in another route
The recent
Of course
This one
Boy this is
This is a big swing
Years ago when we had the Ebola epidemic
Have to sit down with a former friend of mine and asked this individual was the
Pharmacist and Surgeon General
Of the United States
Do we have a Surgeon General the answer was no
Do we have a service that can stop
Got the Ebola from coming in
You have a problem
If I ordered
Descend / 3
Ordered General Dempsey
Answer was no
Dempsey who was
I mean our military officers who created situation
Really coming into the United States and they read
Buyracon
Understand
Steve that old friend was Dan
Steve told the chi
Staff deployed
Ordered the general
Right
This dude is
It's f****** while
Crazy
He's very high-functioning within this
Weber
Bulshit that he's spinning
So it makes it much more
Difficult to
For Alex
Text to pinpoint like where there's a
This is a clear break from reality or just a
Malicious lies and Alex's isn't equipped to deal with it
You know I actually ordered Tom Brady to lose in the playoffs him to do that in order to get
Get him the Wuhan virus
Then he dropped it
In what
Which is ironic because we had already named it that
Way before it right
Well I mean
I guess without Steve we would have Ebola everywhere so that's great I'm glad
But he stopped Ebola
I really
Sometimes have a hard time keeping that information in my mind what Steve says something
Things like that and then you repeat it back to me mere moments later
I'm like he couldn't
Possibly upset.
Anyway Steve has a
Prescription for what we need to do
My point is simple
Do not panic we have everything in control now President Trump get
Assign somebody in this as a Surgeon General
And create a public
Service
Military
To mobilize military so that we have a
Convenient weight
Control
So I guess who's his his angle is you got to either get a surgeon-general which we have
Deploy the military to police the Border
That's not good
Can you imagine
What these morons would say if they did to play the military
Oh yeah that's
I'm sorry this is all stupid
Steve's whole thing is very dumb
And but he has a third possibility
Either
Surgeon General military the Border
And actually it's not a third option
It's actually like what we also need
And at the same time without
Go to the nearest universities and assist
How many Chinese Oriental students we have
Just simply to know what's going on
Oh yeah it seems like a real
Good thing to do
Cataloguing every member of a certain race has
Never worked out poorly I don't want names and addresses of everyone of a certain
Erase I think that's bad that's probably bad
And certainly I don't
Trust that sort of thing coming out of the mouth of somebody who calls them orientals
To me I was really struggling with that one
Yeah
At Sunoco
Steve titles
When is Miss Saigon we need to make sure she's taken care of all of my information about the east
Comes from
Musical
It's a it's weird
Holocaust denier
Antiquated racing
Divas match
Brush with the other Coronavirus
Jesus anyway he's a he's done
It isn't nonsense about
Bi there like
John Bolton
The pathological liar and not really care
I don't care to hear his perspective on that absolutely it is what it is
I want to I want him to be
Set down in a deposition Style
And just ask
Just peppered questions about historical event
Just to see where he think
I bet you would know a lot of like details about a lot of stuff like a lot of
Claimed to have done it
That's what I want
Enough
To get him committed for the rest of
Good life
So Steve is done
This point
I do like I should reveal like one of the things that I really wanted to do this episode 4 is B
Because on the 27th
News broke that Wolfgang halbig got arrest
Yes
The guy who Alex had on many times and was the basis for a lot of
Alex is reporting about Sandy Hook I'm sure Alex had a lot to
To say about it and how big got arrested because
He had gotten letter Posner
Personal information his ID and his social security number and was sending it out
Yeah that's that if that wasn't a crime I'll be real mad
Now it's an interesting Theory
That I
I think it's possible but I have no idea this is the case
Auto recent episode Alec
Mike said get ready for bad news about me
Need to come out
Even building this up
And I
Think it
Within the realm of possible that Alex was one of the people that
Wolfgang might have sent
Information to I don't know if that's true
Speculation on my part
Possibility
That Alex
Might have known
That's a positive I'm sorry that Wolfgang B
Be getting arrested
I think it's
You've connected to a lot of
Even if he wasn't one of the people who woke and contacted
Possible
Rocaine contacted somebody else who knows Alex and pulled out
Ha there is a possibility that he was aware of this and he knew
When Wolfgang halbig gets arrested his name is going to be brought into it
So I
Kind of thought that maybe Alex
To touch on this
He doesn't he doesn't mention it at all
On the 28th there's no mansion
Or discussion of it at all
So we'll have to wait and see if it
Pizza Everett
Enters the
The Infowars
But for now we can
Steve's Don
Alex
Finishes up the show
And
Erie is being a dumbass hole
Helicopter little while do a live feed of us and be back in studio later
Punjab powerful broadcasted a great job crew
Great job group
Weather
F***** you doing he goes out on a f******
Kobe
Yeah he's going to go in the film rights or report where he's at
Hey look you know there's a lot of you know a lot of people
With positions on Kobe
Without getting into any of that
What I would say is
The voice that really we need to hear
And the voice that no one is bringing to the table is
The person whose defensive about helicopter safety
I got is a real angles that f***** up
When I was reading
The coverage of this
What I should have been reading about what
Is whether or not people were more afraid of
Write that
Hey if there's one thing
Thing I know about this Kobe so
Situation
It is that people are clamoring out
Forte
On helicopter safety day I need such a bizarre thing for him to
It it's super bizarre but it is sort of a way for him to skirt any kind of
Like
Overtly
Distasteful
Kind of things about like Kobe's passing
Yeah and at the same time he can
Get attention
Yeah give me like a really
Cowardly way to still try and capitalize up celebrities
It is something
I think that should have been shot down at
Search meeting very quickly
No way
What's our take on this whole Kobe
Put you up in a helicopter
Stop at work
Love it
So I think that should
Be Illustrated with the sort of work that he's doing
Will you see
Throughout this episode
Very consistently is
Trying to raise the temperature of people's feelings surrounding the coronavirus and that
Transmute that into
2 sails
Largely about food
The food buckets are like
Primary
On this episode
But also the pills
You see that you sure
You see that
This is empty emptier than
Then
At least it was
A long time ago
Yeah this is
Really really
It's it's it's
It's G but I I think they like
I might have
Not really even been super interested in doing this episode
Except for the fact of wolf
Getting help it got arrested in Alex Camp bring himself
Even talk about
And then Steve
And he's crazy.
Yeah he was the first person
Yeah
I still can't believe
He said that out loud at that I have a hard time believing that
Genuinely
Like on a very visceral level
Resisting believing that a human being
Said that that sort of thing is absolutely worth it
In the same way that edges return makes makes it all worthwhile
Pay-per-view worthwhile
Rusty's declaration
Obsessed
I'll bet I'll tell you who had the first outbreaker
I thought you knew that was
It was me then and I directed the military to stop Ebola great
They're all in one great Steve Grace
Will be back
But until then Jordan we have website
Containers at knowledge underscore fight
A nap go to bed Jordan we are on Facebook
If you would like to listen to Sugar activity podcast ABS room rate leave a review donate to the whole thing
I could be great
Until then I'm meiaum Leo I'm dzx Clark
I am the juiciest fish oil
Holding
Alex
Person coloring