Air Jordan 5 sweat it
I have great respect for its knowledge B I'm sick of them
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Everybody
Joan Jordan Jordan
Let me ask you a quick question
Super Bowl Sunday Super Bowl Sunday
Super Bowl Sunday what was the last Super Bowl party
31 American holidays
What happy holidays around Superbowl time because of right before we started recording I informed
Jordan that I woke up this morning and realized
I had no idea that today as we recorded
Is the day of the Super Bowl
Two
Okay
Alright Obama just want election he was inaugurated a couple of it was the one the super
Eli Manning
Was the car quarterback
It all over the door stopper that was that was probably the last time
I don't know I might have been with a friend at a bar watching it or something at some point during the the
Comedy
Chicago
I don't know I don't I don't care
I'm happy for everyone does though
Enjoy it
Have a great time I wish you
The best with
Answer this year you know I'm from Missouri so the Chiefs
Reality of the team
F*** you
I'm using both faces
Bi when I was growing up in the
The big thing was like Kurt Warner in
Team17 around people really into
Into these Ram
Missouri head
We're still
Keep Skype
Chiefs right
Wu-Tang Clan
Live
It's at the Blue Note Columbia Missouri
Came out one at a time
And then at the end
Yeah and that's it man was the last to come out by himself
They got on stage
In a Rams jersey
I was like how many old people on your love the Rams and he just shook his head at the audience
Tore off the Rams jersey
There's a Chiefs jersey
It's f******.
Man knows what he's f****** do it man
Did that big man got into like Rockwilder
Play sweat bucket, clever
I still remember to this day
Showman people of the Chiefs
And I wish them the best
Roland ever that the Rams were going to move to l.a.
Put that timer
I'm so angry Jordan is back has run a lot about method
Man's feelings on Missouri football team
The present day
Because I just can't not I can't not
I can't do anything you just can't quit the the present
Things just keep happening
Keep liquor events happen
We're in the middle of
Absolute chaos
Things that are geopolitical irrelevant
We're going over January 31st
2020 Undead this is 20/20
A house
In the surrounding
Context of this
A day will be one of the the Senate votes on whether or not to have Whitney
Israel
You've got that's the day of brexit
Right
Have the coronavirus situation still looming in the minds of
Propagandist
A etheric
And we're going to talk about Wolfgang halbig
Just a couple episodes but I have not heard
Even come up
Not been mentioned in the time that I've been listening
Timer things
Anza
Happy we got the Iowa caucuses on Monday
Everything is
In play
And are coming military dictator
Is going to be great
So I've been like
You know listening to other things trying to find episodes that might be
Interesting to go over but I
I just feel like if we don't
Stick around in the present
We run the risk of
Missing
Something
So I I've just
Committed myself to the fact that like we've got to be in the present for
A while probably
And I'm going to do my best to make it fun as we go along
In much the same way we got to hear Alex Jones interview a baby
On a recent show
This episode does include
Jones doing one of my favorites big Bragg's
He's ever done
Something a little little brag about his past
That I cannot
Believe is true in any way and it makes me it makes me giggle
A dog's life
So
Who signed up and are supposed to show
So first of all Malcolm Forbes
The no not that one thank you so much
PicMonkey
Borgir thank you so much you are now
Text Kirk
Krrp
Thank you so much
Next
All one word
Big athletic
Are we the biggest
Except
Text John p1212 thank you so much
Text
Thank you next
Tom Brady
Football
Appreciate that very much
Episode
Matthew thank you so much you are now technocrat and Becca Emma thank you so much
Heroin
Is freakishly large
Thank you so much and Natalie Matthew and Becca and thank you very much
Brother listening
For these Gents
Let's do an
Football I do not support
Football football football whatsoever
What do you like to start the show
Sports that we would appreciate it
Sojourn
Today we start off as Alex
Starts off
You still on the Coronavirus
And here's where he's at
On this January 31st
Well the United Nations is working with the globalist client state of China to stand
Size worldwide martial-law policies
I've never seen
Descale
Commitment
Oh oh
Mike response at this level
In terms of all of the
All of the different
Tremendous support
According to Wuhan and who by
Highly organized emergency management structure
Challenges with the response
Husband
The Chinese government deserves huge credit
Transparent sandwich
Pictures of infection
Working with Germany to investigate
Is it was
The lab in China
Contact
To tell them that they had to return
Not only helping
To manage
Cases and its own country but it is
And it just goes on
Alexplayz B
I don't know
He's playing the clip to demonstrate like it's something nefarious but it's nothing close
I recognize the voice he's playing because I happened to watch that conference
He's playing a clip
I want to sing that the UN is working with
The Chinese government but this is actually World Health org
Is a Chicano
And In fairness to WHIO is a branch of the UN with the
It still feels a little bit sloppy
Shrimp
Also of course the World Health Organization is working with China on this outbreak
Why is that
What is Alex expect I'm just to be like I will wing it
F*** it
The part that Alex plays there
Is This World Health Organization representative talking about how quickly
The Chinese government record
Recognize the virus
Identified it found its genome
And share the genome with the rest of the world so people could
Identify it if it
Pops up in there
Region
Of all the things in this whole story I don't know how information-sharing
Alex is taking issue with that seems to be the lead
One degree of separation away from standardizing Global martial law tan
Everybody knows that it's wild that that's like the angle that he's starting this this whole thing off on
Cuz it's week
One thing that everybody is kind of universally praising China for in order to demonize
Yeah it's strange that's a little bit
This is just a little bit of like a little nibble on a moose Bouche
At the beginning of the show
Complaining about the virus
Outbreak
Marshall
Alex gets distracted cuz one of his
Interns play the little prank on it I think
That's what I was telling folks about
Coming in here and seeing this incredibly
When during the show
So what's happened is one of the triggering image somebody is put up on his big-screen a picture of Adam Schiff
Haha
Cannot stand the sight of Adam Schiff
So he is sort of losing it a little bit any Italy
You heard right there he's like the break we're just going to
Start the show
That's what I was telling folks about
Coming in here and seeing this incredibly
When do the show next segment
Never even existed
Aw of that problem is I get into your last-minute right before
So I got here
About 30 seconds late to apologize the crew on that
Reset here not just blow up and turn this freaking table over man because
Stop going on this world
Like I said
That son-of-a-b****
We off
I probably shouldn't have that up there
What the hell is wrong with that
I really like you just freaking he can't handle
The sight of this guy
That seems excessive Alex Jones
For three years
Lowe's
I can handle seeing a picture of him
The president is one of the most
Evil people I've ever encountered in my entire life in the present
A picture of
It's very weird pics
F****** worked up about
Sing this picture
Who I am
This is the people do they see a picture of Adam Schiff
And that they
I really have to go over the top doing the performance
It's Abby really Furious
I'm not positive
Performance
Some sort of like Rio on
Regulated emotion
But he has yeah when he sees people that he doesn't like just this
Is overarching
Uncontrollable rage
Seems like he could have used a trigger warning
Has railed against but it seems like somebody should have said that
Don't put up images that trigger made does chi sound like
Uncle freak out
Have to restart the show which isn't the thing that can be done with live broadcast
Okay just everybody hates it's like when you're
When they introduced evidence that the judges liked disregard Stephanie
Right so he eat this again
Be clear this is not part of
Absolutely
This is this is
Stricken from the record
Look like a pedophile
He is one of the democratic
All the tea in China
The dad guy is a
Pedophile
I will take that bathroom someone is pedophile
In a movie there's only one person that
And the Popstar is pedophile Young
Shelter or Schiff
Because when you really get down to it really feel like this is illegal
Make your skin crawl pieces
What are children
I told you I'm going to come back this is not
Arsenal screw-ups
Boy
Play
What a baby
We're really getting to the point where it's like somebody needs to confine this may
I really think you can't do that
No because I think he's using such
Vicky's walking the line
In terms of defamation gangrape of the country
That's not actionable
It's like a pedophile is a judge
That's not something
Laboratory
But also
Brian stelter he has cold he did directly call him
You did say he's a pedophile
He said he wouldn't be surprised
You did also call him
Yeah it's not good I don't I don't know what you'd have to do
Publix
Be difficult
Briarwood be difficult I still feel like
You can't directly go on the radio and say
Certainly
That Adam Schiff is a pedophile
That was not part
Hello.
I don't know if I ever heard it episode where Alex is like doing right now
What you just heard
Not really taking a mulligan on this Earth
I love it also if you're casting a movie
I would say the Brian stelter and Adam Schiff are both not in the in the running
I think they would be perfectly cast Boaz both Brian stelter and Adam Schiff
In a movie who needs somebody play Brian stelter
I recommend
Sorry your brain filter right away Doug test
Navigate to be actual show cuz I wasn't
Alex
Comes in
And apparently
CNN
The problem with
White people
Trying to stop the Coronavirus
Article with their tweets
White people are trying to stop the coronavirus spreading
White people's fault
So the article an Infowars unsurprisingly was Paul Joseph Watson
Found a CNN tweet to complain about
Between is about how the pictures that Trump
Tweeted out where he was being briefed about the coronavirus situation by a panel of experts was legitimately all white men
With one white woman appearing to be at the meeting in the background
The CNN tweet links to an opinion
He's on CNN about how striking this image
How commonplace it's become in Trump's Administration
Ministration to only see why people in positions of authority
Or even close to power or official.
What
No one else did anybody see that coming no one is mad that they were trying to work on the virus situation it's just a notch
It's pointing out how Trump tweeted this picture along with
The caption calling them quote the world's best
Best the best
Expert anywhere in the world
As the article expresses quote
The recent photos of the best
Experts Telegraph the kinds of people the administration Deeds worthy of holding power
Or even being in close proximity
Somebody to it
The article ends
Quote the visuals that have come to
To find the Trump Administration say something else
They signal which people in a multiracial half female country
Trump values the opinions of
Mostly white men who are mirror images of the president
Himself
Paul takes his pretty short op-ed on CNN
And which mirrors points of people that made pretty consistently about Trump's Administration going all the way back
Today 1
And this is how he comments on it
This is from the article
According to CNN
The real concern about the coronavirus is not the
Potential for a global
Pandemic
The fact there are too many white people trying to stop it
Does not accurate at all but that isn't the point
Intention I think that might be a little off I don't think his analysis is correct
He says later in his Beast quote
Apparently wanting to
To not a racist
This is more important
Stopping the rapidly spreading global
Pandemic has not reached at least 23 country
This is yet another example of how diversity means less white p
At the heart of This flagrantly Racist premise that people should not be
Be judged on the content of their character but on the color of their skin and the people with white skin should be discriminated against
Paraphrasing Martin Luther King jr.
At the end of the sentence when you say that diversity just being blessed
Is a
Carmen
Neo-Nazi white supremacist talking toy
Sort of point
I think his point was Martin Luther King
King jr. would have loved
Neo-Nazi
Like legitimately that diversity being the last white people is
A
Gigantic
Foundational talking
Employment for whites
Supremacist group
That is
Bike
When you hear stuff like that flying around from people they're really showing card
Anyway that's Paulette's in Paul's article
Article
He quotes Martin Luther King
Junior which is I think you get
Five points for that in the right-wing quote
Paraphrase
He's also using the or not to talk
In order to drive home this point the people weren't having this kind of b******* like with CNN's throwing around Paul posted some response to
Tweets from the
The people you don't like to have people normal response it's alright
Call Neo.
Course.
He had three response beats a black one is carpe donktum another I've no idea who they were
Dad sad
If you don't know is mostly notable for being a freak
The feminist
Sjw bashing
Gaston joke
Podcast
Who got super pissed off
What do you wasn't included in that Barry Weiss
Peace about the intellectual dark web
That's
BoBoiBoy
Horrible people that are Paul's including response yet
General
Great
The peasantry
People
I think you get
You get an idea of where this angle is coming from
Good good good. Coverage
So Alex is really
Concerned about
Take the situations happening in China in
And apply it emotion
E2 America listener
Yes
You trying to do that
What'll happen if there's something like that here
Shelter in place
No one's there to help you and you can't have any food
Looting and burning would begin with an H we all know that
It would look like Devils would Detroit
Great author researcher former Navy SEAL
Long time
Breakouts
Talk to him we come back
So we got Alexandra like if there was a situation where there was a coroner
It states
He's also having these weird qualifiers what they like tall so you can't have food
Well I mean if they said
Is going to happen you're going to need to
Usher
Societal breakdown that's going to happen immediately
Anything like this happen
Now as an expert on the topic
To bring in noted weirdo Matt Bracken
Who's been yelling about a race war and gave collapse of civilization 4 years
Is a gas pedal down like Red Ice
Lunatic
Weirdo
So of course we'll get here man to talk about this
Public Health
Situation
I read an article from
Research
Who is
Describing the work he did on
Basically like what
What happened
Small-size catastrophes and everybody who is
Poor essentially
Bands together works
Together respect everybody around them
It's the rich people who are like
If we don't control these poor people they're going to start food
Burning and looting everything
And they called Italy
Panic
And that was
That was basically
Put that towards so many different
Catastrophe
I've been like see this is how they f*****
Because they you are so separate
From the rest of humanity they just think we're
We're all Subspace
Kind of an interesting
Perspective
I mean like
People whose primary
Primary function
Survive
Often would view it as
Collaborative exact like you and I we were in an
Let's say we don't know each
Probably could do better surviving
Together then
If we fought each other for whatever
We need to survive
That's literally how we got to this point
But people who have
You know much more.
They aren't so interested in the survival they're interested in the maintaining of whatever they have
And if that means hundreds of
The people die in their Phi
They Don't Really Care
As long as they don't have to kill themselves
I don't know I haven't read those things of your arrest
Printing but it seems to make some intuitive
Sense based on
Some of the stuff
Yeah the term used was Elite Panic it's it's really interest
Make sense
So Alex gets
I mean he doesn't mention the Iowa caucuses
But I mean you know like
He doesn't have a horse in the race really so he's not
He's not as interested
In that
Is it worth
Avengers cha cha
Democratic primary Chinese
Really interesting perspective that I think it is
Self
Contradictory
Sanders surges
Why do plateaus that's why they're getting ready to go after Sanders already stole the nomination from a few years ago
Dollar Bank
The duet
Authoritarian so that's all
Coming up
Here's where Alex is going to run into trouble with
His entire prayer
Sanders is also supposed to be a leftist authoritarian universe
So now you have the left
Just a Thor attarian Nancy democratic
Establishment
For some reason
He now has two
Explain why that's the
The case between the left
Authority
Set the case that the Democratic establishment
Which is really just the globalist to her trying to push socialism in order to lead to Communism in that authoritarianism
And then rounding up Alex and his friend
If that is their gold why would they screw over a democratic social
Who's running
President
It doesn't make sense why would they if they're trying to assure in a socialist dystopia this is their only shot
I would they go after the only social system fuking right
Who happens to be incredibly Papi
Why they can heat heat
It doesn't make
Sense and he doesn't really spend any time trying to
Break it down
Because he's established in the past this
Anti DNC
Anti-democratic establishment
Talking points memo
Did they screwed over Sanders in 20s
It's already
In the Infowars Canon terms
The talking points purple things the audience
Believes and accept
And so
Because of that
You trying to go back
To the well for that right not Ricky
Makes no sense
It is real never
I have to explain it is interesting to me
That's the right has kind of accidentally made
Sanders the only candidate
That the hard-right would fine
Palatable
On the left also you baby I accidentally yesterday in the last election
They can't then like you because you can always
Weather like
He's told they were stealing it because he has good ideas and all that's right
And it's like everything to Mastery outright anti-hillary stuff they were perpetuating by praising
Sanders
In the 2016 primary
And that would
Optically comebacks
To hurt them but
It doesn't matter by Chris
It doesn't matter who's back
I didn't mean that
Who cares I'm just saying that as a general as a general sense of priming people
Right everybody was Prime to hate Hillary Clinton and they accidentally primed them
To be far more apathetic to sander
On the right
It's an interesting
I don't know if it
True rapper
I'm not sure either so anyway Alex is selling stuff that'll help you with
Emergency like the one that he is yelling about
In Coronavirus
And you know he
You got his his items
He's also got
He's also got mad
To help you
Antiviral mask
We left XL price
Sold out in one day last week
We got him
Made them cost you ten times more that
Amazon selling single mask
$3
Because I'm an opportunist
From everything I could tell Amazon is not price gouging surgical mask
I just checked and there's one I can get a 50 pack for 1799
There's another brand with a 125 pack for 89-75
No idea what Alex is talking about but I assume he's just imagine
Amazon jacked up their prices
The couch people
And that he's been Noble hero
Because he didn't do the thing that Amazon also didn't
I imagine it's possible that some resellers on Amazon might have gouge prices but I see no evidence
To that when I was looking over
Thanks
Would try and buy
One individual methadone
Foxy
Interesting though is that even if they did do that
The structure of Amazon almost guarantees that they're gouging
Strategy wouldn't work
The only way gouging works as if there's a scarcity of Ops
You need to be selling something that people can't easily get
From someone else
Amazon Marketplace works
Usher's that they're almost always be someone else selling the thing you're trying to go to the price of
Would likely lead to No One buying your price inflated shitzu
To begin with
It almost has a built-in
You from that
It doesn't always work
But it is this
It's fairly effective
Amazon was criticised after Hurricane Irma
In 2017 when things like bottled water riposte
It was very high price
They were clear
Census of price gouging
This was not Amazon's doing
It was the work of third-party vendors who use Amazon Seller item
In response to this Amazon took action to be more proactive
Against vendors who engage in these sorts of practices
But honestly given
Alex is Legend
Political philosophy
He should not have a problem with price gouging
Specifically on Amazon
For him to be against price gouging on Amazon here's what he
He has to believe
You have a business that sells a product
They want to have access to more potential buyers
So they use a platform like Amazon to cast a wide net
It's basically like an advertising
For Alex to believe that price gouging is wrong
He has to believe that it's appropriate for the platform Amazon
To be able to dictate
Priced it which this business is able to sell its own Prada
That's nowhere near a free market position
The libertarian position generally speaking is very
Troweprice
Give you some idea of their take on it
Leave me since
Attitude published
2017 right after titled
There's nothing moral about opposing price gouging
With price gouging in quotes
As if to imply it's silly to think it's a real thing
There was definitely more than one article published by Denise Institute defended price gouging in September 2017
Which I think is
Really awesome
I was done with Libertarians after I heard their argument for why blackmail is fine
Great
You have a choice you can choose to be blackmailed or not like oh okay
Well then we're done
This article argues that
Gouging rules disrupt the natural processes
Supply and demand and it's actually it moral
To Levy fines or jail time on someone for quotes
Selling their own property at whatever price they walk
Horrible
Alex Jones 4 years
Pretended to be a liberal
Any fetishizes the imaginary free market
We fail to understand
But even the basic aspects of this belief system he claims to have
I think that's probably a wise decision
Because if
He actually believed the city pretend
He'd have to openly denounced the Civil Rights Act
Back support child labor
And if he follows them
School
You have to believe that quote
Parent does not have the right to aggress against his
Trials
But also that
The parents should not have a legal obligation to feed clothes or educate his children writes that such applications
Until positive
First upon the parent
Private be right
The parrot of his right
The pair therefore may not murder or mutilated child
But the law properly Outlaws
But the parents should have the legal right
Tunak
Feed the child allowed to die
Directly from
Institutes write-up on
Shelter been right
I think I think that's a
Babies get rid of libertarian and say their fascist but weird
Like they're not they're not the mainstream Fashions they're just
Weird fashion fashion
Alex took on the label of libertarian never really can
Considering the
Completely f***** up things are entailed by
Applying it
Primary beliefs
The real world situation
He's never really been a liver
Battalion
He's been a Libertarian in the same way that that guy you knew in college you like weed too much to be on the right but was a little too right
Places to swing with the left was
That's the wrong Paul libertarian
Maybe
Alex is not interested in first principles or actual philosophy of belief
He's interested in selling
Primary motivation runs in that direction its position
Alienating discussed most right-thinking people
Like in a disaster it's your right to pray Scout even if you're watching people die Who
You could have say right there
My point here is that most Libertarian beliefs are insane and very
Unpopular with most of
To the public and even out
I would almost admiring if you got on aretys like it's crisis time I have what you're
Need the prices go the f******
Wallet the same time saying he would never price coach
Libertarian stance
Like free-market s*** that you pretend to believe that it is be like
I have what you need
Pay up suckers
Like that would be at least in line with his beliefs but you know the reason
They can't do that
Is because he's also artificially
Trying to create
Adam Ant
He has the
The hard work
Of trying
To create this
Panicking is already a year
Inflation of demand
She'll be like
I have the supply suck it kind of hurt his ability to
To do that
Might it might
Honesty does not work in free market capital
It's not the best
So
Alex said that Matt Bracken was going to be coming in to talk about this year disaster
And before he gets to it might break and gives a little bit of a shout-out
To group
He's
I guess fans of
Just for a moment
If you can indulge me I want to give a shout out to the the Appalachian battalion
The mossy oak militia
And do
This is our secret
One of our secret ritual
Recognition so enjoy haircut
Give me a picture of that
Not because the mossy oak militia anyway
Have to be wearing this today so
Anyways Carter inside joke Among Us
People like to shoot in the woods
Anyway
What a f****** dork
So the mossy oak militia is a name that pops up a bit in Forums on like AR-15
Keen.com until I'm not sure it's a real
It seems like a name that's thrown around to denote someone who seeks to embody the vibe of a guy wearing camo
In one post
Discussing the upcoming at that point Virginia gun rally
From January 20th
The poster discusses Howard be a coming together of quote businessman / profession
The local boy in blue jeans and a t-shirt
The Fudd in his coveralls in a straw hat
The mossy oak militia and the tactical gear guy
It seems to me that this is just sort of a designation for right-wing cosplayers who put on
Fatigues rally
I might be wrong in the Bracken is actually talking about a real group and if so that's even more f***** up
Sometimes means that Alex's allowed
Guest on the show to shout-out a private
Militia
That's
Probably not the case I think this is just a dumb old man
Yeah
He's just a dork
Do you mean by soul
Matt Bracken
Is a guy
I mean luck here's all we need to really know about
Mustache
Via
B b b b guns
Sure
He's not a doctor he has no public health or anything
Sing like that nothing less Alex wants his expert opinion on this Coronavirus
Research
Do you think it's man-made you think it escaped from a lab
Why is it being hyped up a gut-level what do you think this virus is
I think it
Huge pandemic like this today you know it almost is a moot point whether it's natural or men
Handmade because
I don't understand why that's all really know the truth there's never going to be a record that comes out that everybody believes
What cop out
It's a whole chicken
Point hop out get the f*** out of here into the Coronavirus
Is completely meaningless
You recording to his own self-written bio there's literally no reason to take anything he says about biology or health
According to his bio he has an undergraduate degree in Russian study
What you got back in 1979
Any was a Navy SEAL for a while then in 1993 he built
About Russian studies there's the northern lights in Russia
Corona boom Coronavirus
There's nothing in his background that really makes him qualified to speak on whether or not I coronavirus is man-made
Makes him the perfect guest for Alex to ask that question to
They aren't interested in reality or analysis there
Didn't extreme weirdos saying
Sensational things to drive sale
That's always going
I went to a wedding
Inn in Maine
And it was held at the
It's like summer camp place where
Religious kids would go
And I remember
This incredibly strike
Kingseed where the woman who work
Is
Making of
She works there
She makes fires
Every night
Every summer for her entire tenure there
And she's trying to make this fire and
Four different dudes are walking in there in like
Hey how about you try using some newspaper and s*** like that and it's like that that aggressive white dude
To use in
Nothing
The confidence to be like
And I know how to solve the Coronavirus
You made a boat
You've got more boats than me so Alex asked me this man made real naturally-occurring it's a
Point because no one will ever agree on Bracken elaborates on that'll
There's always going to be theories that are that are competing
So I would say you know sure it could be snake to bat to man
Canadian biome
Research lab to Wuhan bio lab
Research lab
And then it gets out somebody in the lab and
They go home and it gets out that way
Don't think we'll ever know definitively
There aren't competing theories
There's science and then there's a load of b******* Alex and Braken 30 round spreads
This is a really dishonest framing device that Matt Bracken
Confusing there's an insistence that dumb completely baseless stuff it's
Discuss. In Fort Worth is exactly the same as the work researchers at the CDC or doing
There's literally no
Points to them
The head of the World Health Organization at John
F****** Rappaport
Write this is ridiculous they are competing theories one is a theory okay on the others bulshit
Alright well I think we need to teach
The controversy
Controversy
Nobody believe nobody will ever know whether evolution is a thing that happens
It's impossible to have a
That is the like
Black just
Put on
Lele Universal scale what do you say
Like yes
There are people who are taking this very seriously
I saw meme
Right
We are the same okay
We are the same so this guy is worked in this sort of I don't know virologia field for his entire life he's got
Got several phds
I think you've got something to say my brother
Awesome
Stop
Doug talking about like
Hey riddle riddle issue your man why isn't Trump stop
Travel from China
The UN has had some emergency but doesn't want travel restricted but most countries are incredible
Done that yet answer that question as best we can on the other side it's Friday we're live
We've discussed this in the past but suffice it to say that experts do not agree with Alex and his assertion
The shutting down travels the best way to practice
Containment of an opera
It's pretty well understood in the academic Community which is why when you hear people who are insisting the travel should be shut down
It's a pretty fair assumption to make it there either not very informed
Or they just want travel shut down for other reason
And this is a good
Excuses
Variegated
Interesting Lee Trump is
Not stopped all travel to and from China probably because the experts know this would
Would not have the
Desired result
Screaming in person
Cedars of the way to go and you can't
Practice appropriate
Screening of Travelers shutdown
And that scenario all the people who come in and out of the country are unaccounted for and completely unknown variable
When you leave travel open your able to monitor people coming in the country and track people or suspect
I'm having condition
And you can even isolate them if you need to
You give up literally all of that possibility
If you shutdown travel you in no way guarantee the people
Art still going to be
Be coming across borders
So it it's
It's something that's only one of the factors that
Sitter like how much it would disrupt
Economics
If Trump stopped
All travel from Sun
MBA gigantic
I'll just use this as an excuse to add more
Non-white countries to the travel
I'm not sure that the I don't know if I heard it framed as like the coronavirus has anything
To do with him adding those countries
He's using it as an excuse to do that buddy
You sure seems to be
Fine with stopping some travel sure
It's not actually travel that that is inaccurate countries can still
They can still apply for like
Visitor
Immigration
Stop from
Nigeria or Eritrea Kyrgyzstan in Myanmar
And the people from Sudan in Tanzania will not be allowed to apply for lottery
Right
Do you still
Creeping towards this
Sing yep yep
Yep
But not that I'm not interested in
Could not handle
Adding a travel ban
Fury to the the whole survey
Little bit about the impeachment stuff and he's pretty convinced that they're going to vote
To acquit
That Eve
Friday evening
31st
That's pretty standard of its position
You're the really have much to add to the the entire thing but he does try to rewrite his own history
Why the hell did
Trump
Right now as they try to get Witnesses which will be Bolton
So Alex is trying to say that
He warned Trump not to hire boat
Steve pieczenik
Did Alex argue to Steve pieczenik
V Moody and apparatchiks
And he would do Trump's bidding
He knew his way around the swamp and so he would be a really useful tool because
That's what Rodger Stone have told Alex
Presumably
Is it true but disgust on it for the Rodger Stone
Play poker together
It talk
But Rodger was like 90 John Bolton School Alex went that way
Steve pieczenik was the dissenting voice
Who is that Alex is trying to protect
You rationalized
Whether they play poker or not we all know stone is ratfuck his way up to V
Sooner or later so
They
Definitely know each other
So it matches anyway the news
Couldn't handle Incorporated
Eating this this
Immigration
Crackdown
Something
In that new cycle
Dogs can't handle his own
Show either
Is this breaking news
Lago gatecrashed shots fired
Shots fired
Palm Beach
Checkpoint near the property
Bible getaway
It's still out there
Ridgid somebody offer medication
Jesus
Or is it a psycho
Kill the president or trying to attack him
I physically of Happy
You can tell by the way Alex is reporting this it's a story that he wants to be about someone attack
Donald Trump
You can tell because there is no information available to him at this point but he's
Trying to decide how to portray editorial choice in the direction we take this
But people have been attacking me here you know
In reality this is a case of an impaired driver driving very erratically and dangerously near me
All the shots were fired were fired at
The driver and there's no reason to think the
Did she was trying to even get in tomorrow Olga
According to ABC News
2 checkpoint
But did not enter Mar-A-Lago
The sheriff
Alex's favorite kind of Lawman
Even said quote
This is not a terrorist
It all began with officers were called to the scene where a woman was reported as quoted
Several miles away
Tomorrow logout
When the cops came she fled and the cops follow
Coincidentally heading towards Mar-A-Lago
Bike Windsor
She was driving on the wrong side of the road and flew through checkpoint so I guess the police
Decided to open fire on her
Her car
She managed to get away and
Fletcher Motel the police have been following and they arrested her there
Honestly this is a story that in another time
Alex will be covering
Clear evidence of
Horrible police station
2009 in this woman is a nice white Ron Paul support just want to have a good time dancing on her car
You can see how this entire story would be played
Sweetly differently
But now every story is told through the prism of nationalist
Turn Alex's weirdo Community being under a
A story that has literally no.
Details on it is being told
Speculation that it's in
Attack on truck
Because that is what you wanted
If this is an attack on Trump you can yell about it for the next
Gear
Police shooting
He can use it as evidence that the left is violent to drink
Dakil Auction Service
But it's not
It was a drunk lady driving erratically and
The cops decided
Yeah I'm going to
I'm going to go with every
Part of this story should be blamed on the cob
Yeah
She was just dancing man
I think that you probably
I don't know all the details
Run from the details I was able to clean it doesn't seem like she handled the situation very well
4:00
It really really really doesn't she made some bad choices the police made it seems of work
Mar-A-Lago
Anyway later in the show Alex gets
An update on this
I ate some more the details
Really still feels like he wants to push
This as a trump letter attack
Could have just been somebody that was going the wrong way and I'll pay attention that could have been drinking
And then you didn't you do that the security like that you're going to get shot at
That's that's sad but
There's going to be glad in a
Climate weather saying
Trump is literally Hitler
Having a nation is Hitler
The only person with an e
Election Hitler we see
Is George Soros literally was a Nazi collaborator
Financial Networks
What is Hitler
You kind of get the sense there that like the narrative he's more interested in telling is the one where
This is an example of blowback from Soros funding and Hitler
So I mean you get it at least we have some more
Maybe
The Jordan I got some
I told you
My favorite one of my favorite big brag
Is going to be on this episode no coming up
Text Clara then we got something
Been really fun
Then we got something really stupid
Okay so that's
The syllabus for the next
Little Liars
So get excited
What I'm saying is have some fun while you can
Here is Alex Jones's big brag
I'm not bragging but I was actually on the road to being like a top voice over guy that was voicing
Major trailers seprafilm TV ad
Insurance company commercials
But if Obama
When Obama got in
1 year $890,000
Scott built on voiceover mine
Happened as soon as I criticize Obama
The Jabs wings
According to ZipRecruiter the national average salary annually for working voice-over artist is 6
$5,000
Only 7% of working video people make over $198,000
And these will be your big names in the field
The idea that Alex Jones made $890,000 in a year doing voiceover work is laughable
None of the stories about him discussing his early years in public access or local Austin radio
None of them mention his ridiculously explosive voiceover career
There are credits to his name from that. You can find which would be the case if you done any work in film
Azhar TV
Keep records for that
Sure they don't just stop
By the time Obama was elected Alex was already yours into being a pretty widely known Luna
He put out his Bohemian Grove film in 2000
After 9/11 cemented in his images of 9/11
Conspiracy theory
I don't want the image to be that he criticized Obama and lost
About a million dollars a year and its side Hustle
Because the only real currency and right-wing media is victimhood
He needs you to think that he's been
Depressed political positions
Unfortunately
He's making all of the
Sup
The figures that he comes up with the sound
Comical
If Alex made $800,000 in a year doing voice-overs
He would have legitimately been one of the top
People in the field
Stress this enough there would have been so many pieces about him in trade magazine
Give me the Talk of the Town
Voiceover is is
Primarily funded by a video game
And I was like you're not making 108 $90,000
Pre
You might you might if you were like got big ad
I made
Yeah I mean like a John DiMaggio isn't making
$800,000 a year and he's one of the best
I bet he
I bet I bet here
Nobody's making even more
I genuinely do I think
I have a little bit lucky drama DVDs are going as hot as they used to
Spell
Is that deal
I'm not saying that Alex doesn't have some
Skills with voiceover Jeff
The only places I believe he's practiced this art in his own film
And enforce
Because there's a little trade secret that I know from my time trying to get into voice overs
Dude with voices like mine and Alex's are not in high demand
It is super competitive area of the market cuz there's already a ton of very established voice actors with
Deepest graph of voices
So even if Alex did have a decent voice no one would care
Hebe guy number 5000
Who fits that mold
In order to get me work
He'd need a really good voice over agent
And you have to be working on it full-time
Sending out like sample Edition
Tapes
Four Scripts
It would be
Such an intense process for him to break in
With a voice
But he has no yeah
The picture that Alex's paint
Depict a reality that does not exist
He was a number-one voice-over talent in the world
Criticized Obama
But had it all taken away from
Such horseshoe
Also it's pretty funny to imagine that someone with the political beliefs that Alex has whatever join the f****** Screen Actors Guild
There's plenty of non-union working getting voiceovers
So that wouldn't even be a necessary thing for him to do
South bulshit
Just complete s*** yeah I don't remember him in any early 2000
The anime which is
I bet
That he did do some like local
Oh yeah I wouldn't have especially because he was working in Public Access Radio I know from my time when I enter data
The radio station a lot of the radio
Commercials the voice-overs word on B
Is everything got kicked a couple bucks
Yeah they worked all morning and then recorded a couple of probos after after their show and then they went
Doing a little bit of that $890,000 in
Year
The fuc
Out of here
Show me
Tax return
Credit
Yeah that would be fun
Some sort of proof of that cuz if so
That's crazy story
I'm trying to latch onto whatever conspiracies are floating around about the coronavirus outside
Chicken
Some of them a real stupid
None of them have been like
Real laughable
Stupid busy texting is pretty laughable soup
It is once you get down to like what that patent was
This one
Right in front
Oh my God
This is bad
There was an article on show laughing
Real operation and
Not a huge Resident Evil fan I am a fan of that to Easter p.m. check whatever 90s
Eagle Corporation
Google
Got it
Because the oldest operating intelligence agency Kentucky
Ever been right
This is like the Umbrella Corporation and then my buddy change Connors me this this year
Image and it says umbrella
Corporation Bradshaw Tamika W awesome thing
The actual research laboratory where they had the exact same symbol but it's
Red
Engrave engrave
That's got to be a joke
Translate
Oh my God
I don't want to get too deep into the Laura Resident Evil
The games on the movies diverts a little bit and honestly I can't keep should straighten my head
Amanda
Later on she becomes
Clone fighting the lights White
Look what's in Port
Your other than Alex being attracted to Milla Jovovich
Is there's a meme
Where's the city of the logo similar to the Umbrella Corporation
Slogo
And that is convince some dumb dumb
Let it must mean that this
Roblox
Is created by a weapon
Much like the Umbrella Corporation did with the t-virus
In
Yeah I mean I can't
I can't find any flaws in that theory 121 leads to be
Hammers at home it's Corona translates to Raccoon
The man that went around with flaming at this place with the Resident Evil style logo was the Wuhan Institute of virology
But it clearly says
If you look at the uncropped image
Shanghai on the front of the building
That's because
Actually a biotech lab in Shanghai would you like 500 miles away from
Also Snopes looked into it and it doesn't even appear that this biotech lab in Shanghai is even open
Seems like it's going out of business
Geek culture the website posted an article about this lab having a logo similar to the Umbrella Corporation in
In June of last year
And in the same article that discuss a skin care clinic in Vietnam having an identical logo to Umbrella even down to the color
There's actually even another article about that
Skincare company in Vietnam
2017 about it
Are there at the end
Alex is misunderstanding another me
When he says that you translate Corona
Raccoon
In reality
The meme is Vic
Corona is an anagram of raccoon which is the name of the city
The outbreak in Resident Evil raccoon city all right
Major problem with this theory is that if you look at the word you might notice the raccoon has to season it where is Corona does not
I don't know just kind of makes this a dumb anagram
H-E-B clear the spelling with 2 C's a raccoon is cannon in resin
But that is how it spelled
This is super super stupid
But it also it's really important to point out things like
Alex is taking the time to cover the dump meme s*** as if it means
This is the level of analysis and insight he brings to his work and it's so sad
He said idiots like Mike Adams
I'm coming on to say things like this
It's over for Humanity
Only be Lone Survivor
Because of the outbreak
Humanity is over
Desperate to blame is Imagine enemies for this that he sings to his level of shitheadra
Pretending dumb hoax
Beam some idiot posted online or worth anyone's time
This is the best work Alex can do because he's not even trying Eddie
He doesn't do any research he doesn't prepare anything outside of the show just shows up and gets mad at a picture of Adam Schiff
Yep pretends it's not the show
All this information comes with dumb beans and headlines series on websites run by him
0 editorial standards
The tentative make s*** up
And so
This is what you get for the show
Dumb memes presented his research
Alex yelling about his feelings
Did anyone doesn't
Like people
I don't care his audiences 20,000
Some people the idea that there is
Anybody
Who doesn't see through this
Very sad
I remember
Plan
Collaborative storytelling games online
When I was like
Angelfire website
What if we had banded.
From using it
It was just it was our little secret Club adults were like I don't understand this this internet culture we just get rid of them
No memes like that
I don't think that would work
So this is dumb
Yes
This is very
Super
Raccoon
Corona
Translate
Logo
Proof
Not good I thought Coronavirus
Crown but
I got it I was way off
Alex
Why would they use
At logo
Why in the hell does it look like they have that symbol
I got to look it up I spent like 10 minutes this morning and couldn't find
When they got that logo
But it appears the company in the logo comes
Resident Evil
Why would you pick the Resident Evil symbol of evil Global Corporation
Famous ocean
This is babe
It's not
Girl hundred possible reason to that lab to use that symbol similar to the Resident Evil 1
Off the top my head
The owner think the owner doesn't know about Resident Evil just think it looks cool or the owner one
Wanted to troll idiots like Alex
There a lot of possibilities
But it's
There's one thing that I'm confident about its that this is not you
Analysis
Not about to crack this case
Also
Does Alex think the people shouldn't be able to use certain logos cuz they're associated with fictitious villain
Real free-speech hero over here when was the last time you saw anybody use a golden gun that's been
Retired does he want the state to be able to
Exert control over a business owners First Amendment rights to use whatever iconography they want
Also does this extended countless products are marketed with.
Pictures of the Christian devil
Why would they
Tell me give me one good reason so how did the square with Alex
Constantly playing the in
Imperial March from Star Wars which is the anthem of the bad guy
Himself house
The Hello Kitty show over with the Star Wars theme music
How could catch on Williams
That's what that
Yeah that really how come
How y
Why would they use
How did f****** Resident Evil come up with the logo it's the same way
Logos are hard to come up with
You just start drawing
Eventually you're like I like
Why is he speaking today
Cuz raccoon translates to Corona death
Alex is operating off the
Not true
Piece of information that this logo is on a lab that is the Wuhan virology
Connecting a bunch
To stuff together here
This is just sloppy
Where this came from a lot of experts believe in shadowy group Todd in the US Military
Steps in Canada of a committee actually genome
Renee
He is now
Being tracked back to this company
Coronavirus is before stars of the Coronavirus
Play Chinese Labs you better not ask question
Conspiracy
Talking about it yesterday
Claimed
Almost two months until earlier this week
Originated in a seafood market in Wuhan
Animals inside batsuit
Or snakes
That is not the case
The published Study last weekend
Demonstrating
Set of the original 40 14 of them had no contact
Capital Seafood Market including patient zero
Hematologist at that
Into the seafood market
We still don't know where it originated
Seafood market
Food Processing Company
China Wuhan also has China's only
Safety level
Super Laboratory
The world's most deadly pathogens to include
Coronavirus
Call Trish Redden on all flights the US
Has landed saying
The 15% death rate which I don't believe
What
Said it was 18% yesterday
Flights from China
Clippers of bottled massive b******* got to disentangle a little bit
Episode
Doesn't say with
The Coronavirus
Is a 15% mortality rate
Just among the 41-page
Since I work in their sample set came from
People who had pneumonia and tester
Two positive for the virus
They had 250
Mortality rate
That's not applicable to the general population in anyway
It's good that Alex doesn't believe that there's a 15% mortality rate but it's super dishonest acclaimed Atlanta to sing
Second Alex is saying that this lab with Resident Evil logo is the lab
Tom Cotton is mentioning in
It's not
There's a lie being spread to make the
Suspicious
The source of the out
Alex is acting like it's weird the Derby a big bio lab in Wuhan
Come on
It's a city of 11 million people
It's not like it's some kind of a rural spot would be weird
It makes total sense
But it's there
And no matter how many times he implies it
That lab is not the same one as the one in Shanghai which probably doesn't even have
Third coronavirus was not stolen from a lab in Winnipeg in Canada and Central
This is a light went around a right-wing media based on a CBC report
It did not say
Even close to that
She hears all this getting muddled up in mixed together to form some kind of a unified
Conspiracy
It's not true
The scientist Coronavirus
And
It's not true that this lab with the Resident Evil logo is in Wuhan
When you combine them
It's now true that a Canadian scientist that coronavirus to the Umbrella Corporation
Can't you see how that works it's pretty quick
Combine form unified theory
Also I said
That he thinks
When he said he doesn't think that it's 50
10%
Think he means that it's
I don't I don't think so
Lower
W interpretation
Much like the Bible
As for what Tom Cotton was saying In that clip it's fair to say that it's
Still unclear
Exactly where the coronavirus came from
Initially there seems to be a trend that a lot of patients had exposure to that seafood market so to quote Lancet quote
Exposure history to the Hunan Hunan
Seafood market wholesale Market
Served as an important clue is at
The early stages
Yeah its value has
Decreased as more secondary and tertiary cases have
Have a
Nose means what
Wanted to me
He's playing this clip to imply that
The seafood market was a red herring it was.
Deployed and that the lab must be the source of the out
But nonetheless
Substantiated outside of Alex's gas
Implication
Kittens that are not
Stop believing people for competence
That's what they
We're like oh well we saw a bunch of people go to this market so our first thought was let's look into the mar
And then we found out that it wasn't the market so now our thought is let's find the other thing
That's called doing your due diligence
It is
Add stop
Thinking that
Trails
The people go down that don't turn out to be correct are a cover-up
Stop
Thinking of memes meaning
You can see the opposites
Trying to hear they're trying to keep
From interviewing people
And seeing though and maybe going down the ramp
Yeah yeah yeah
So
The voice-over was the big brag
The Umbrella Corporation ship was the kind of fun goofy stupid
Right now let's get now we get to the annoying
Alex's mother Gaston
On the show
If you see something
No don't
Last night with all the stuff going on
Coffee get a shower
When walked around
Local golf courses next door
What am I 5 a.m. and sat down
Dad
10 of a cup of coffee and I
Infowars.com and sauce but I like yet last night
I don't have 45 minutes to wash
I watched it
Add
Because what an illustration
Everybody
I'm going to take on the impeachment trial
The virus first in this segment
Comeback
But I mean
Describe how these
Senior
Campbell Federal police now attach another Federal group
Veteran
World mounties in their suits
Like something out of a movie about the old Soviet Union or Nazi Germany I mean
Anderson
I watch this
I'm coming like 6:30 I'm making breakfast
Everyone see who it is
So it looks like as a revamped
It's going to be a much more frequent
Presents on Alex's show
Stick together
Guitar
Remember Ezra Levant is the guy runs Rebel media which
Employed
Of the
Real dickholes Lauren Southern Katie Hopkins Tommy Robinson
Gavin McInnes
Salty's real
Cool
People also Alex that Golf Course
Private
You should walking
There's a lot that's interesting about this clip and I'd probably explain what the conscious
Texted think it's most important takeaway
I think is it Alex.
Caught up
Spending hours reading YouTube,
He's a forty-five-year-old man who pretends he does real research it somehow
Feels like YouTube comments or in any way a barometer of Truth or public opinion
That would legit be like me saying like
Something Trump did was bad
Sing that I read a bunch of Twitter responses as proof of it
Still trying to maintain that I was at all a serious person
This is f****** sad
Also super important point we don't bring up enough
Alex gets up in the morning and checks out the news on his own website
He's getting the news from people he pays to come up with b*******
This is the very definition of a vicious cycle
Idiots post dumb s*** on Alex's site then he reads it
And gets mad about
It's just such a lame way to live
And no amount of walking around a golf course
Justifies that kind of
That doesn't make up for it it's still very
Kelly was fighting to keep Infowars awake
I imagine we should get a John Kelly to keep Infowars away from Alex
Is that a tribute
As for Ezra I don't really care about his situation
It's very clear what's going on
And all this
What it is it has all the making
Kings of a perfect right-wing victimhood
But it's just based on nothing
So the situation is this
Ever released
The book called
Toronto
LeBron
It's like liberal by like with
Sopranos at the portmanteau
Lubrano's liberanos
Anyway it's about Justice
Trudeau being corrupt
New releases book bacon
September 2019
You barely call this thing a book
It's 124 page
So in the world of political expose
Prettymuchit
Ronan Farrow didn't
Consult on this one did not I'm surprised regardless this was a problem
Because according to the Canadian elections
What he did may have been a violation of elect
According to the letter that Ezra posted on his website
30 God
The commissioner of Canadian election sent a letter saying quote the allegations are there Rebel news
Contravene.
By 1
Failing to include the required information on third party election advertised
N2
Having incurred over $500 in election advertising expenses
To register as a third party in the general election
To break it down the allegation is
Date at the buck
And the
The marketing of
The Bucs amounted to political advertising
Against a candidate
In order to publish such materials in Canada you have to register as a third-party election
Advertise a manta ray
That's that's
Smart and kind of keeps
Should hold him from doing stuff like that right
When it comes to the publication of the book
Chicken Lily relevant whether or not the book
Plan to be published
Whether or not there was an election
That's the central question
And the answer is
And this seems to be one of the central questions of why this letter was sent
Informal event that an investigation was being open
Something it's probably not working in lavance favor is that there is a clip of him that's referenced in his interview
View with these investigators
Where you specifically said that he wanted to get the book out for the
The election
That makes it kind of clear that he was trying to do election advertising with the book
Right
Regardless this is a polite letter it informs him that
Operate or not
And if you'd like he's invited to schedule an interview with the
Anyway
That letter was sent on December 9th
2019 apparently Levant just had that interview
Because he snuck a hidden camera in and recorded himself no badgering the interviewer
Jack is a really sad look
But it's exactly the performance you need to really get that conservative victim of juice flowing and I can see why
* it would be like practice
I watch the whole video
It's annoying
Another one that comes off like a scam artist baby
But also he seems to be editing
Obscure an element
Into the case
It seems like the interviews
Viewers are less interested in the publishing of the book
And more interested in the advertising of
If you write a book about your well-being
Then advertise it with a
A ton of signs and posters everywhere
With Trudeau stylized as The Sopranos DVD cover
It's going to be indistinguishable from a flyer posted by a
Political party
That seems to be where their interests lie
In how the fact
That you wanted to
Get the book out before the election
And that is advertising
Materials were basically political average
That's the vibe that I get from their question
Position
Trying to defend
Himself because
Based on the way they act as written
It's pretty clear that he's gone forever
The bottom line is that there is a law that Levante is very likely in violation
It's a law that sound weird to American years perhaps
What is part of the Canadian election law
And he has every reason
To know that
All you really need to know if you want to understand this is to watch the first two minutes
The video that you put out and now it's wash
It's kind of a Sizzle reel of him sassing the interviewer
Then
You get Levant talk
Control camera and he tells people that if they want to read the letter
The elections board
They have to go to save Rebel news.com
This website is just a
The fundraising
The top link is for people to send him Bitcoin
It's all just
Trudeau is trying
Take me down and then
There's no way I could pay our Free Speech legal fees without
The help of you and thousands of other supporters like you
So if you use the form below you can chip in whether it's $10 a hundred dollars or even more
Man I can't imagine somebody
Sending him Bitcoin that's like one Bitcoin is like
3 Grant still
Exactly
This entire website
Built around a video Alex's promoted
Irrelevant being a baby in
It's specifically about raising money for some imaginary free-speech standees taken against Justin Trudeau
This is Tex
Book free speech grifting if there's ever been
Open a case
It looks like he's guilty of violating election
You've been warned that there might be a penalty for his actions
So instead of trying to start a movement to change this law
He's fundraising about his
Quite
Overturning that law seems like a really dumb idea because I
Any billionaire
Going to get around to like election regulations
Just put out a half cooked
124-page book to use it as an
Excuse
Ton of unregulated election materials masquerading as bookcase
How bad it's
Seems like regulation is really a good thing in the sea
Isn't it
We've seen in America what
The consequences are
Loosening up fees
Little titty baby
Zero interest in his self agreement
It is 1:35 about this interview that he had with the
Since people yes for money
At least six times
It's very clear he's treating this like a publicity
Restart ultimately going to get hit with a nominal fine probably I would guess based on the assessment I can
Can see you the situation
He's going to raise so much more money
Based on riling up conservative persecution
And feelings that's the entire play that's being done
Can't we just
Campaign
Take that
Take the money that he raises
As the fight
Stop just all of it just hears your fine however much money you raised from this dumb website I wonder because
Is 50 Bitcoin
I wonder what the case is because
I think
Probably some of his actions might
Yeah they're hurting his case
At least Big D definitely into
Malicious intent
Absolutely I don't know how those things
Kingswood implicate
The actual case
I mean
I think based on just the information that's available from
He is edited video
The investigators have
Evidence that he's indicated he wanted to get the book
And that makes it so
This is political advertising which is against
The Canada election
Pretty open
I know but as we know now.
Just because you go on TV and admit that you committed a crime doesn't mean that you can be punished for that
That crime or even
Except responsibility for it at all it's upsetting
The idea that he would be able to just walk
Through this with no consequences
You very well by
Well it is Canada though so they might give him
You say it's Canada
Alex says it's America
Text Flip
Is talking about Ezra Levant flight
Any accidentally says that this is America
You watch they're going to charge and you can smell it they say you're guilty
You want to walk that back if you're guilty of writing a book during an election
Lawyer
You're going to jail
This is America
Block somebody
Play smoking weed
It's believed that American sovereignty extends to White right wing assholes
Another country
If you're if you're a white right-wing a****** you are a citizen of Alex's United States I guess so
Also that letter that has received from the election
Commissioner was very explicit that this is not a criminal matter
From the letter
The fact that the Commissioners decided to proceed by way of an administrative invest
Can indicate that he is of the view that this is a matter best dealt with
Administrative leave rather than by way of a criminal
There's no intention to charge Ezra Levant with cryamore
Charge him
Burlington prison
There's only an intention to sort out whether or not the advertised
The campaign surrounding his book
Was against Alexa
I look I get y as what Levant would make a big deal out of this and it's because he looks really guilty
And he's a big old baby
And he's also really
Administrative staff for you
The law enforcement just does not know how to deal with these guys
They always get this tiny little well people
Crime by speaking into a federal building
They could have done jail time
Which is what we need to do with these militia
Just actors if there is any way to punish them in the law to the extent
That is who should be punished
Introduces
Difficult Quest
About
How you deal with
Like people that you can
Very intuitively and
Llano empirical observe our s*******
People are marijuana f*** these guys
Play Pure against that to you can't use that as a justification
Difficult
It's a really hard question like
And I think I keep coming back to
I think just
Widespread awareness of these peoples
Patterns of Deceit
And it had a real
I think it's probably the only thing
That is
Really
Powerful against
Because otherwise wielding the mechanisms of the state
Become really difficult because then they get
Pretend they're victims of the
Pretending he's a victim of the state just as he got kicked off YouTube
True you know like they're going to pretend to be victims of the state no matter what
I would say the I would say deplatforming does
Does it help it does yeah
Yeah I mean as far as
Steps to take that
That's pretty big
I don't have a prescription for the solution
I would say that locking people up marijuana compressor
This guy
Pendleton store
I'm with you for the first half if he himself
So Azria get to talkin about how he thinks he's innocent
I don't
Know if his defense
Is very good
Canada election law disaster
Exemption
Promotional book
I've written an almost pembrokeshire
Camera best sellers
Where are we
Under
Brought me in
Ezra doesn't seem to understand the issue which that's me being glib
He fully understands the issue but he's pretending not to
Because if he reveals that he does understand the issue we have to admit that he probably broke
Action laws Alex I've been advised by my lawyers
Actually actually great work
To lie directly to your face and your audience
That exemption are you talkin about that exist for books and advertising the books
It only exists
If the book was going to be released whether or not an election was happen
If the book is specifically released for in the election
Is Ezra said is true of his own book it is no longer eligible for that Exempted because it easy an Essence and
Election advertisement
The aunt that would all be totally fine for him to do that
Can do all these advertisement
He would just have to register as a third-party political advertising is confiscation
How to do that either because if he did
He would then be subject to other election laws about misleading advertisements
Puts out with me then subject to a bunch
Higher level of scrutiny
Then it would be otherwise
McDonald's I just want to lie to you
Why is everybody making this so hard
This dumb dumb knows the game he's playing
You can't register the third-party Advertiser without getting hit with a ton of fine for deceptive election advertising
He can't pretend that you would
Have to put the book out whether or not you know those are wasn't because he said he wanted to get it out for the
And so he's left with the only Refuge there is Con men like him
Insisting the law says something different than what it says
There's a particularly difficult peel
For me to swallow send Edward used to be a practicing lawyer
You know damn well that accept exemption works
Good work
Investigation going as good as action strongly implied that he wasn't eligible for
For the exemption he's claiming he's covered by
Alright okay sure you have me on tape murdering that guy but I didn't work
The statute clearly says
There's any special exemption for murdering this guy
What's interesting is that Alex is like trying to defend him when he starts
Rambling real hard
And in his Rambo
He's clearly saying
California election
Yeah so this is
This is really strange
This is real Taryn
Have you sold your horse if you're just some citizen or of the group you can publish a book anyway you want
But if you're a political group and it's a political publication by the party or by third-party is an action group
Tell him to say yes
An opt-in
You're guilty buddy you admit you did no crap Sherlock
Of course I don't like this piece of garbage and I'm doing this it's my speech alright
Canada
Common law
The standard isn't if you're a political action group as I understand from reading the statute these things out
Like if you're a web
Website primarily
It's size
It's size of website that has the factor if you need to read
Register for this third party
Political advertising designation
And in this case
I believe it was
The threshold is like
3 million hit
If you're in English
Language
Website which they are above
Okay well thank your own website
Dunn Bros song
Got it isolved
Yeah just be less successful at that you can play all these bullshittin
Open
Who's your playing was b******* games
Because you want to make money off that you are
The problem I think might come from
Spending your entire life lying about
Topman
Anyway ever-lovin baby and I do not care
To listen to any more of him
Because this
This whole thing
Coughing
Is just a right-wing aggrievement fantasy
Play doubt
Perpetuated in order to direct money to Ezra Levant
And it's
It's pretty obvious the great grips of our time
It maybe is the best graph
Lying to white people and telling them that they're always under attack and then they give you money
Stenograph
Stronger it's not hard
Another guest coming up that actually leads to one of the
The funny or moments
That we've heard in a long time
But not because of the gas state
You'll get it later but
Alex
Sell it
It's amazing
I know you got to go we got to go to
Congressman Bob Barr
Couldn't do better on a day like
The president
We don't know yet we're tagging shots
That's the lifeblood
Daddy
Aspirate
First of all like I haven't read a book need to sell it
Hey we got Bob bar coming on he started Clinton impeachment what a great things shots fired at Mar-A-Lago
Argo
Speaking of fun day forecast
So Alex talking about how like you had a realization
About the global
Okay
Many years in
This is not a real
This is basically just Alex
Killin Time
Blown Away by how evil the Deep state is and how sick they are and how filthy they are and how wide
These people have been waiting for a long time
They have been
Absolutely dominating us and so
That makes me feel
Like a wimp
Allison I can lay down and again I'm in a lot of guys and kick my ass okay
But I remember being at like a little kid
And getting off the bus in like sixth grade
Fifth grade and beat me up.
Until that moment when
You looked at me weird cuz he said he missed 3 years older older
Thatskannada that is Infowars 10 years older
Toddler he just can't speak you met older
That moment when
Technically almost killed a guy
They don't have the Killer Instinct folks we do
We got it
What voltage we need God will give it to us
God will allow me to use this rock to put your eye I'll kill you
Because God gives me that's true
Like the later stages of this episode there is more of him just get
Getting lost in thought
I'm stealing time at nothing because he doesn't really even bring up
I know who rented takes effect in the
The day
It's going to happen
Forever
Broad got what he wanted and now he is
Is God
What do you get Tommy Robinson on
Countdown
Thank you Lord thank you Luis busy
She doesn't have time for a small show like Infowars because I don't I don't know well it's good from the UK any
Anymore
But I still
Think the dankila is not
I'm going to need you to back up your your,
But
Alex
I don't know anyway
Bob Barr is coming on
Do you come home later
King of the elephants
Rollie with any clubs in cuz it's just yelling about the Deep state
But
It turns out
Alex did not mean to book Bob
It was an accidental bucket
A lot of calls today we got Bob bar
Actually initiated impeachment against Bill Clinton
I couldn't think of a better
Gaston this whole constellation of news only
Robert Barnes back on as well
Marble CO
You should have thought of that we should get them on each
Got punished weather
Barnes is so busy now and coincidence
For you we got real busy is really wild busy shows the specific time to get very busy
Why would I do my show it's always
That used to be on
All the f****** time when I was in
Employing him
He had no intention of winning any of those lawsuits and he was just charging me a lot for the hour
Exposure
I think that might be
I might have been
F******
Nigerian scammed Again by
Not going to come back on the show
Not being paid
No he's not going to do it
What is
If we give Bob bars pretend we miss murder
Let's put that of all the names to miss here
Very very
So I said I don't care about Bob bars
It's it's meaningless
By Alex
Get back to
Talking about the
The coronavirus situation
He wants you to know
That's a very good product
I'm sure
For this
And
I think he's a dancing
Real close you can't say that there preventative
Right
I'm not sure it's this virus
But
You have our bases covered
Damaris
I said I would talk about this person such big knows I'm going to break them up with gas, do it right now
Because it's important decision for all you out there to think about
And it is going to do
Tell you something that I've been authorized
It's just I can Congress
This is 13 years ago
And this is the company
I got this information for my days ago I said
Listen
Are you sure you want me to do this because you got Department defense contracts yellow others
Did I mess with him I don't know where the owners we would be like what you're doing we got a partial you would want people to know
Department of Defense
A congressional report say that
This product nanosilver
Confounded knockout Stars
Well no crap no
No
Nobody selling 16 oz of nanosilver
Ridiculous names
Medical name you can you can drink it all
My dad is an oral surgeon a dentist named it so
Call Garland
Start he's dancing around this
Silver has been found
Kill bacteria in water
Nano silver has not been found to kills it's not entirely
Fair
But the point is that these this ad could be a problem for Alex even if the claims that he's making about nanosilver r
Substantiated
Not like it doesn't really matter
From the limited amount of scientific research
I'm able to do it does seem like there have been some studies that have shown some indications that Nano metals have potential with Viber
Viruses and bacteria
But that isn't the part to be concerned
It's a fact that he's selling the nanosilver product in the way he is
Bike directly linking it
And that click and later you going to with Coronavirus
In 2014 Dr Rima laibow former Alex Jones Gaston wife
General stubblebine
Received a letter from the FDA and the Department of Health and Human Services warning her that the way that she was selling her nanosilver
The problem
She was promoting the silver in a way that was understood to be
Bee quote for using the Cure medication treatment or prevention of disease
And because of that she was no longer selling ass up
She was selling a drug
And as it turns out there are different rules
About how you can sell drugs
Particularly as it relates to Interstate
Commerce
When you do
This letter was sent to her during the time when Ebola
Hot virus on the scene
The medical scammers
So she was pitching it as any Bowlarama
Enter sales pitches you mentioned that very similar sounding release from the Department of Defense though she says it was from 2009
The timeline
To make sure that 13 years ago. 7
It's important to recognize that it's immaterial if Alex thinks his claims that he's making are backed by a study
This is an issue of what he's
Required to do
If you sell it
The drug
He has to get FDA approval for the sale of the products easy
If he's engaging in this sort of
In addition to FDA approval if Alex is selling a drug he's required to label his bottle
With known side effects
Contraindication
Thanks for the drug drug
Directions Etc
I went to the Infowars store and looked at Alex's labeling
For his immune gargle they had Ella
And it doesn't
Include any of those things
In fact it has a warning
The claims he makes have not been evaluated by the FDA
But you can't do this is a drug
It's weird
Because if you look at the label for his super silver wound gel
There is a statement that it's been evaluated and is effective
Can staph infection
E-coli Bursa and a few other
Weird that he would label that one correctly as a drug and is nanosilver mouth gargle
As the standard supplement labeling
He's selling it as if it
The drug
Consider the fact that there are some dissenting voices
The matter of nanotechnology
Vegan supplements
Review from narcos
However nanotechnology carries risks
The primary one being long damn
Studies have shown that the
Most nanoparticles migrate to the lungs
Other organs are susceptible to damage as well
Scientist who found that sometimes
An activity of this destruction process leads to cell.
Metal silver made damaged mitochondria which leads to
The DNA bear
Until further Evidence
Concludes nanoparticles
To use what is true and tested for several decades
And consider colloidal silver without
Nanoparticles
That was an article from Infowars
From December 23rd 2014
Silver
Fake medicine Community nanosilver was all the rage
Rema labor was selling it as an ebola cure and people were excited about the
His new breakthrough
But since Alex didn't have a stake in the market is messaging was that it
Was dangerous and you just use colloidal cell
We can go back to 2008
Find out the posting an article titled
Scientists care does nanotechnology and nanoparticles become common in consumer
In Articles all about Heather dangerous side effects to nanosilver
Like pollution The Kills aquatic ecosystem
The article says quote
Ionic silver is
Is
The humans at very high
High levels
The toxicity of nanoparticles silver said westerhoff
Has yet to be determined
At that point Alex was not selling nanosilver
That is the important
Stick with colloidal silver
Because I'm not selling Thanos
Right now I'm telling nanosilver
It's actually a
Cure for a virus that literally we don't know a ton about
Skillsource
The important thing that we're going to get you a little bit later is
Medical Claims can be made about the
Topical silver gel
Because that has been
Evaluated by the FDA and it can be sold as a drug and there are warnings on
That that
That is not true of his other nanosilver product
He's trying to play fast
With which product is which
You can make claims
About the gel
Show me a picture
About these other nanosilver products
And you eat playing a little shell game
That's such that like the supplement industry is a
Billions Dollar in
Industry mainly because they can figure out a way to live in that
Agraria
That's the situation outside I don't know exactly at 1
The FDA would care or take action
Intel
Seems like he's very close
I'm testing the waters as to what
You can get away with yeah
Which is really f*****
That's
That's God
That should be I don't know how to police that but
Supplement huckster like Alex should not also be able to have enough.
Approved drug
Like it should be you're either an FDA-approved
Drug salesman
Or I I don't know
You can't that's so f***** up that you have similarly-named products
Explicitly for topical use
To be ingested who be very difficult for anyone who did any kind of
Looking into it to get them
I'm confused
Okay well
Give some indication that the audience
Don't eat the bun shop
Because LA's is opening
A statement on every show.
Some sort of letter here
Not he's not reading
Really like
Important
I don't know what's going on here but
This is what he's using
Sort of imply
That his products are useful again
That's the Coronavirus
Army Headquarters United States Special Operations Command
Tampa Point Boulevard
And receive on Edinburg
Attraction
They go on to say that with antibiotic-resistant smaller Iced Out
We have found that this particular type of nanosilver
Effective against each other
Then it goes on here
The Texas A&M system
Health Science Center
Because
Stuff out for a lot of reasons
Says Dear secretary Ridge
And I go on to see the office of Homeland Security
John B Connelly building
Vacuum dining for an old secret project for the government
In our trials secret trials
Secret
American biotech labs
Was very upset
This report is that the Coronavirus
Without the data
Our product to kill
Security
The secretary.
Carrollton
Internal Air Force brilliant man came up with the model
Hospital system of autism
Don't receive a copy of it because our testimony
Before Congress
And it was included in the addendum
Richard heaven.
None of this matters in terms of what Alex
Does doing
If the testing really is there that's cool
I've no idea what he's talking about because it's
Apparently secrets
Secret testing
You can find a medical journals that indicate there's some promise for Nano cell
Alex Fields emboldened by these secret study
Clearly hasn't read
Honestly I'd be surprised if even read that letter prior to getting on are based on the way he's jumping around
Whatever is highlighted
Because he feels emboldened he's drifting super close to selling this silver is a cure for the Coronavirus
And if he's doing that he's entered akam
Completely different game
And he's at the great risk
The FDA getting involved
At which point
I mean that's the last
Thing that he wants yeah
I really don't
I think you want can't handle another
Now
The Heathman can't handle the fronts that he's on right now let alone adding BF
VA into
He's been teasing that he's going to you know reveal the name
Silver
Supplier
He doesn't this
Next B2 he also revealed that is a dad
His dad is behind all the supplement
Which I wasn't clear on but I also don't care
What's the Lakers are going to say that I need you to come in and manage Shuffle much we need to put on the wrong side of the bed
You've brought the fee doesn't reach her sinuses well this thing
Get it
He brought us the folks that are the Super Silver
Which is the top company
I know just who we are
American biotech Labs LLC that's the big one
The only ones that have approved
The counter
American biotech Labs is a legitimate company they focus on large part of their business
This is medical application
Silver
They have an FDA approval for the wound dressing
But
Use of nanosilver is top
And it's not
Same nanosilver that isn't Alex's products that are taken internally
He cannot take the approach
5908 disapproval is here for the gel
And then just apply to other products because they're both silver made by the same company
That is not cool
You cannot do that
Also interesting Lee American biotech Labs uses silver salt
Nano silver
Guess what that is exactly the same nanosilver that was used in Reema lebos products which earned her a warning from the FDA and
2014 gray forgetting too far down the road Alex is starting to go down
The more details Alex gives out the more it looks like he's heading that same direction
Which would be great for
Cuz I need to pretend that he doesn't understand rules and play the victim of government oppression tried to wipe out my supplement business
Also
Now that I know where Alex is getting his silver wound gel from I can compare price
If you buy it from Alex
You're going to pay 50% off 10
Your P30 995 for a 4oz
What's bottle
Currently mark down to 2397
If you buy it from a website like
Vitacost
Without the Infowars labeling
Just the American biotech labs
Product
It cost 2799 for a 4oz bottle currently markdown
Rye Rye
You can get everything that he sells cheaper without the Infowars labeling
If you just go to
This is a really dumb idea
Take all the products from there
Put on new labels
Anybody was in his audience
I guess it still is just for funding the Infowars
But you're paying way more
I guess that's
I got nothing
That's a mean that's standard like
Say the MSRP is this
Deflated and you still have your profit by
But I'm not at all
Angry about people who do markups in order to allow their business
I am again
People who make their entire presentation
Hey we don't bark anything up we're not playing a game here and then all the prices are higher
Then other places you can find the exact same product with a different label
If he starts a
With a clause
Then the following Clause will prove that he was lying about the
Sure
I just take issue with that
I think that I would
Close
Like
Badwater
I am not positive that he's
Fully in violation
NFPA guideline
But I think he's
Really f****** clothes
And the way he's trying to sort of Muddy the water with the the gel and the gargle
Is just like
It's it's a bit of a cup game cuz the implication and the message of the audience is supposed to get
Is that the gargle
Will have the same effect
Kill the Coronavirus
Where is that is not an FDA approved
Because he's not
Illicitly saying that just dancing around it I don't know if it's at
The intention is there and it's bad
He does sound resentful toward his dad
The immune Target
Terrible name the technical name you can drink
Note 10
Show biz
Clip is a little long
But I think it's one of these things
It's
Kind of against
Throughout this
You will hear
At least four instances where you're like
He's about to do an ad page
Okay about to do an ad pivot
And it never come now that's f***** up if you can't do that to me now it's important
I've ruined it but it's important to show every now and again
Exact same behavior and then just never hits the dismount
It's rare
It doesn't happen very often but I think this is an
Intense
Example of it
The reason the president have more support as they threatened everyone around him
We're talkin sex operatives infiltration grab their bank accounts
The kids I mean it's it's it's it's beyond any movie you ever see again
We just saw Canadian Royal Mounted Police saying we're going to put you in prison
Wilke Road against Trudeau I mean
These people are Unchained
I have no chivalrous
Chivalry
Is what
Powerful people do because
They want some rules on themselves
Want to get registered at 1
Start going down that line they're going to reap the Whirlwind
I got to tell you something from bottom of my heart
Obviously
Incredible historic hives and I just
Wedgewood golf
Thank you so much what you're doing
They can put a gun to my head I would stop doing this she understand that because this is like getting oxygen
Huge Skin Diver butt
About 80 feet.
Compressor your blood sodium or oxygenation but
It go back up you got to watch out for
So here here is where I thought I just meant to get to plug and he got
Just distracted by talking about skin diving
The plug is going to come after the skin.
Everything's so bright
I start using tolls
Analogy
But
Products
Services
I know I was using an allergy
Good McDonald talking points here but the.
This is like
Stop in there
Slippers
I just want to get that are
So here I'm thinking like okay he's found it he's now going to use like
You giving me money exactly that I need to continue to fight for the only reason
Blood pressure
Well you don't have Aaron did
Show me fighting tyranny is knots on the road ever
And the air in our lungs
Is
Money
It's not like something really thing to
Love your children or somebody walks up punches you in the face and kick their ass that's not it rolling
Giving us money as hero
Thing about fighting
You don't want to get if I was something I certify with you
But you know soon as they take a swing or soon as I can
You know what I'm going to beat your ass
Satisfying
Really hard and then rallies again knocking down again of that all the sudden
White Sternos
I'm telling you
Thank me for this b**** is
Pigeon the animated contest of Liberty
This is what it's all about
And here's where you think he's going to jump it right there if
Are you support me I can continue the acklay absolutely
Absolutely
Anywhere else if it weren't for you
I'm not going to put on some fake
Bible thumper BS up here
Jesus
You just made me
I love God and whatever God does through me it happens
Now here's where I thought he was going to get sacrilegious
It's been minute
The clock to get to the commercials
Absolutely I have no idea what
Trying to say skin diving
Kick somebody's teeth out I don't want to be like that
Jesus loves me I guess
So I thought like okay he's accidentally started talkin about Jesus
He's going to have to use that somehow to launch into his ass and I think honestly maybe because he started talking so much
Jesus here at the end
Maybe that precluded
I'm probably realize like
There's not a really good
Swingpoynt nothing
Jesus loves more than naked capitalism used and it exploded as manager
God didn't want me to stand up there and tell me what app is I am all day
I read the Bible And I memorized this and I'm
God wants me to get up
Take on the New World Order
God
8 Scouts
That's not true
No one knows who originally said that was true
God
Literally the meek shall inherit the earth you dumbass
You are default position to not have fear
Is it God's will
Flashes in perfect the process
A plane
Have you got to be put through the fire
Play the Metal it's all about
Are you guys out to commercial agent
That's the weirdest thing
It's so weird I do so many points that are like
This is a classic
I'm mad because I was trying to sell his product
Here we go
Call Mansell machete
We have proven that Alex Jones
I've never read the Bible or has
Has no idea what the con
No Genesis 1:1
The beginning God hates
Gacha my bad I don't know who said that wasn't God admittedly or in the Bible
God really likes people
Default position of no fear
Loves it loves that no fear clothing line
God wears nothing but
Three wolf Moon tee shot is basically a dog with a t-shirt
Anyway
I think one of the reasons that Alex could have
Afford to not
Duo
Pivot there
4ad
Is that he's hosting the fourth h o u show
And it's entirely
About survival food
Alex
Super defensive
About selling the survival
Before this next guest joins
I'm just going to talk about this right now
Start selling
Storable food to the audience
Monster 6 months ago or a year ago
Horrible food
I've been doing that
For 20-plus years
Cuz it makes sense to me that insurance you can eat during any crisis and we hope Trump and America wins we hope
Globalist get defeated
But in a war like this there isn't any arming
The Winds of War
Politically or militarily
It doesn't have food
True
We're talkin about here to polian
When in the Russia Iran a fool you fell
T-Fal
Are these examples of people you wish had more food
Absolute
This is a big problem with Hitler was he
By my phone this is bad Freeman
Yo what Hitler but he didn't have no food
Real tragedy
Just didn't have enough food
Already off to a weird start
If pulpot had enough food man he would have been able to kill way more p
So Alex
Is like
Before we get to this next gas
In the next gas station
The guy who runs my Patriots
Survival
This is a big old info
Marshall
Loyal
You love's
My Patriot
Supply
But the thing is the reason
He's been being reached out to
Dubai other survival food company
And the way you trying to get more money out of this. I don't think it's a shake that
What it is
Convoluted as hell the way you presenting this
Obviously I just straight shoot blisters it's all I can do it's my superpower is that I just
Tell the truth what's going on
Coronavirus is obviously out of control and I said
Promoting
Water filtration is horrible Foods
And the best oral surgeon the best water filtration
Not going to sit here like
Freak out this point
But then we saw the sales
This weekend just Skyrocket
And then I got some calls not just
From
Water my Patriot Supply
But I got called
From all over the country
Different
Companies
Trying to get me
Product becomes sponsor suddenly
Right and here's why
You're good at that
You are good at scaring people are dedicated audience
Are moving products
Because you create
Pandemonium fears and like
Relate everything
Every kind of
Fear or anxiety people can have
You take
Amplify
And direct them
Whatever
Product you want to buy
If I were running a survival food company and I was a little bit should be
You better believe I'd be calling an absolute
Play hit your wagon to that bucket sales are skyrocketing
Because
We are skyrocketing have people like Mike f****** Adam saying things like this
It's over for Humanity
Only be lone survivors
I'm never going to stop playing.
Ebola cure
Anyway
Like we have that kind of rhetoric being pushed
On the show you have at least
A certain amount of people who believe
Entrust Alex it's going to drive sale
Sales have been way off these other people want to get in
The game 2
Makes total sense
It's not just such that that like
This is the psychopathy of capital
Entirely like these guys are like
I'm definitely going to hit
My wagon to this f****** lying huckster salesman
Because I'm going to get a few more food buckets out
For the next couple of months
I think there's a I think there's a way the business
Mrs. can do these
Existing these faces ethically not with Alex
No
Certainly not
I have some thoughts on it there will come a little bit later
About like
I don't there's nothing intrinsically wrong
About selling survival food
You do it so I would be I would be
Prone to say like
Yes
The
The pursuit of profit
Does tend to make people
The Haven weighs like
Getting Alex to sell yours
If it works
Dusseldorf
And that's bad
That is bad
Do agree with you that
Thank you
So
Alex's
It's really strange
Because he's clearly feeling an infomercial
He has the guy from my Patriot Supply on
But he doesn't really want to it
Middleton infomercial absolutely trying to live in this world
Clean space
It just ends up not
Stop making sense
I am saying
So it is
The equation
Appreciate you
Yes I'm patching you food right now
He just said you weren't
The fact that
12 years they began
The philosophy of high-quality food
Low prices
Reason I got a Moniz
Why
From other food supplier saying we've sold out
Big institutional buyers
Call up
Believe your letter to try to buy our product I sold you have it on hand well
Not sure how fast it will get there
These other food companies that are calling him and trying to get him to sell their food
What is going on I'm not a look at this isn't the pitch but I'm going to try and picture food yeah
I'm saying I'm not pitching but I am going to 8 might as well
What is this I don't know
Pizza Hut
Bananas this is double speed I don't believe
Any of what he has a course not
What what
Stupid Survival company would be like okay we're going to call Alex now and we'll have food for them in 2 months
When this entire thing has blown up
No food
But we need more customer to go
Salesforce get on it
Call Alex
F****** Joan
Alex's is trying to like maintain that illusion
My Patriot Supply is on
Not to sell any
But I mean they are
Today is not even to sell you food they're selling out faster than get it
It's a breakdown the fact that
Call
Few days ago and I said
I'm getting calls at the food selling out
They're gearing up for some big emergency do you know about this
You tell me if there's been big governmental buyers coming to United listen
It's a secret
We've had the general
Services Administration
Coming.
Find a vibe
Everything we've got
Because all the other major Food Distributors are either sold out
The closest selling out
So if you understand the Dynamics
It's going on here
Supply is not on to self
Panic that there is no food
I don't know why he's not just leaning into this Narrative of like if the institutional buyers are buying up all the
The food we're selling it to you
Keep them from getting it
So people get their food and not the Institute Patriot Supply does
Make that point
But that's what you lean into you don't do this
Wishi-washi I'm not going to put you on this food I'm putting you on the food but I'm not
But I am I'm a straight shooter who's lying to you as we speak right I think it's because Alex is getting good
Done some pushback
About that I saw certainly posted on Twitter
What people like in crisis
She's like this
Scam artists
Are opportunistic and they this is where they try and make it there
Their bread and their logo I really need a header image
Johnny was Alex and bike that horse
So like
I know that he knows if people are like
And he knows that he's doing it
Right
Same Dynamic with Ezra Levant
Do you got these
Personal buyers
Buying up food
If that's
The case I would assume that it's
It's the same thing that happened
With like
The the emergency
Lima
Like of course they buy a lot of food
Which I don't know if it is
Please be supply chain because there are emergency
A lot of times you and small-scale emergencies that we don't know about
They have to respond to
You know it's not always hurricane
There are smaller scale earthquakes
Soror
Droughts or floods
And they need food to be
Be able to
Keep people alive
Right so it wouldn't
Surprising to me if
They did
Some people
Here's why I don't mind buying up
All the food
I do not
I don't buy this
Nothing at all mainly be
Because Alex just said that
They
Texted him
Looking to buy up all his food
If they had contacted him looking to buy up all this food
It would be sold
The moment they said I'm look
Looking to buy all hearing like
Give near me
They're only
Selling to the Patriot Alex
Would absolutely sell out his entire Warehouse of food if somebody called saying they want to buy your house
Food warehouse warehouse with all of his other shipment
Spell his website
Directly sends the orders to my Patriot Supply
He's very clear
He has no interaction with the food
In the past it's just been an Infowars sticker that's on there
And now it's even apparently not that cuz they don't to pay for stickers
His intellect
But the food is the $4 bill
Is the $4 extra that you pay for it
No ability
You to sell to these instead
Do snow tires
Contact him he's just speaking
Precisely they contacted my Patriot Supply
Gotcha and my Patriot Supply told Alex about the
This contact they
Now they talk about that a little bit more specifically it in this next clip
And I mean
If you want to point a finger you know where to point it
Just started in November
I started getting
Females
Phone calls from different people
From government basically
Trying to get into the system
Where you can get Jesse contracts to work with
Registration is confiscation
We will never do that will not sell to the government my Patriots
If this happened in November it's having sense November guess what
F****** call your boy Trump
This is all Trump Administration stuff if it is some sort of a nefarious plan
So hey
Talk to your boy
Stop complaining on the radio cuz the only function of this is to try and sell these goddamn food yeah that's that's
It's weird this whole thing is made up now
Right
So basically the government
They get really defensive
Pensive about this idea that like it is a good idea to have
So I'm emergency rations on hand
And I have a thought about this on the other side of the
Last week going
Episode I'm ordering gas mask
I should be promoting this my audience
We shouldn't be ashamed of that
We should be proud that we are warning Americans
Hurricane right
What American State win any hurricanes approaching
And so young people running for parents stories days in advance
Here
Come to pass it may not come to pass and always
I'm not cooked
Teaching my Patriot Supply guy nearly as much as I am Alex
This conversation about like yeah if you're in let's say the middle of Missouri
It is wise to have some canned food in your basement
In case there's a tornado or something like that
It is wise to have
Spare tire in your car
Put a nice put ice in the freezer put water put water bottles in the freezer and then yeah you're cool
These sorts of things are
Not
Wise things
What's to do if a blanket in your car
Mel
If you are in the middle of Missouri
And you are trying to sell somebody something by screaming at them about tornadoes
You are being a dick
Maybe yes
If you provide or offer
Survival food for somebody and recognize that in the case of an emergency
You might need this
Great
By all means
Sell your product in good health
If you were selling it by escalating
Annex surrounding a situation
Especially the way Alex is completely
Lying about f****** memes
About to Coronavirus
What you were doing is your
You're engaging a dishonest business
Absolutely
Thing to do which is prepare
In some way for a
Potential
Emergency and what you're doing
And that's
That's that's taking something rational
Turning in tomorrow
I hate
Yep
F****** hate I
And that's Bass
Musically like
This whole thing
It's all just
By the food
It's just a food
There's just no other way to put it then
You're scamming
That's that's it you're uploading
That's like
That's like it to carry your analogy still further
Like if your
Screaming at a man in the middle of Missouri about
F****** volcanoes
And saying that that's what you're going to need the food for her because the government of volcanic activity
Yeah yeah or hurricanes there's that there's going to be a massive
Missouri hurricane hurricane
So Alex
Problem is
These institutional buyers are buying up all the food
What makes this clip a little weird
Literally like 15 contacting me I just said okay
What's your background you got a big Supply there like watching don't you guys do is why I chose you many years ago
To get a good
Respond so they treat me like I want to be treated so let's come back and talk about kind of them
Play that started in and how it build up to where it is now you guys are buying up all the food around the Sun
Convoys of 18-wheelers
Alright whatever
Anyway
What are these big things
Flex uses
You don't hear anyone else
Ever use that is
Redoubt
We talked about people
Another globalist have their armored redoubts
Scores in New Zealand and I all over the place
Somewhere in Hawaii
Interesting
Graphic novel about the
Call Lazarus
Surprise you to learn that Alex has his own
Would be surprised to learn
Father
Being charged for the future
You know I'm outside
In 45 Acres with a
Done saving food
Because
Living in fear I'm living empowered
He has an armored he has an armored word out a little bit outside of Austin
With guns
And food
Okay
Alright
Thanks Ali
Where is it you want to give us the address makes
Because if I'm going to become a cannibal in 10 days after the end I'm going to your f****** house
This is this is where it all just like every single thing that he talks about the globalist
Doing it seems like you just wait around long enough and he talked about doing it himself
LeVar Burton
It is very much like he thinks that
The way he thinks is the way they thing
So of course he's doing what they're doing
Is he thinking that
Take it a step back
Night Like This is whole idea about these glove us having our bird out just like they can
Can wait out the consequence
This is the things they've done
If you take a
The broader Alex
I don't know
He's really trying to sell this food in doing so he ends up in points
Pretty
Ridiculous
Things like
Idea of
During the Great Depression
In 1929 to about 1938 + 39
Major Universe win
That is a
Figure I cannot find anywhere we we had a greater famine than chair
Chairman Mao in China
I can that what we're talkin about
I can't find it
Toronto articles about how
Because of social welfare programs
Actually a lot of people received
From starvation
Galax probably doesn't want to consider
17 million is an outrage
Just figured absolutely
Figures like that
Is to make people like hey you know I don't want to be one of those 17 million
Better by the survival food
All TaylorMade
Direct people towards
So anyway the other thing Tuesday
The Alex is
It's pretty clear
It is time they need to buy this food to the virus
It does creep me out that I didn't think about this until I called you guys
Opera
3 days
You never liked promote that's because
Maybe a month or dummy
So you been a little bit concerned about what's going on it is kind of scared me a little bit
So when we saw it last week and moving into full motion saying hey this is
Everyday
So there is there is a
Italian of the
The situation with the virus
We need to buy food
Now you have
Essentially
Like a fool
Sensationalism
You have
Calls to action
Weird vague
Idea that the government's buying up all the food I'm surprised they didn't put a clock on like a special
You know
They are not going to do that well
Not exactly but that is exactly the last element
That you need to make this a full infomercial
It's not the same as like on QVC
8:20
Love the fact
During regular time
Great food water filtration United
Hyderabad times they get it that scares me though you're saying 23 weeks
That is scary
Thank you so much and go to infowarsstore.com the fun. She's all dropped at the same day
I mean you have the eye
Did the presentation that there is
You've only got two or three weeks now but you're running out of time
It's just a just a name
Your wife
By the book
Sort of infomercial for this food
That brings us to the end of this January 31st
Episode
Wolf
I don't
Think he did a
Great job
Is that right
Interesting review I think it's performance left something to be desired
The God hates cowards thing that's a standout
Not the voice actor in claims and the Resident Evil references
Not vs Levante crying like a baby
I I couldn't pay attention through the I was talk
That was tough
I was listening to that
The episode and I had to
I had to stop
A couple times
Like Knock-Knock is how long they can get
An hour or so
Capping like
Cannot do this
I'm so bored
This is such a
Transparent thing
Unappealing
But I mean you see the directions
The show is going at
That accelerating
Full steam ahead on trying
Create Panic surrounding this Coronavirus
It's full steam ahead
Monetizing it whether it be through
Real JC headed areas with the silver
And just
Overt
Barry Shameless
Foods
Sales
Play I predict that's the
This is the one time that I will say that they are not Shameless
It does seem like they
Little
Shameless
Is begin in the yard
I expected this
Discontinued
But I also think that on Wednesday or episode is going to be
Why the f*** do I make
I don't know by then
Brexit will have actually happen
Is this
The earlier in the day Arabia left
I'm feeling is that right right also
The Iowa caucus will happen
And no matter who ends up winning that thing
I think I was going to have some feelings
Mouth
I have something to say
Did our next episode is going to be a lot about the Iowa caucuses
And you know what
Who gives a s*** we're going to show up and do the episode
It's going to be about be really might
Possible
Government is hiding their murder of all the bees using this Coronavirus
Who knows probably so we'll see but will be back until then we have a website
Yeah it's knowledge.com
We all are so on Facebook
KB
You guys are great until then I'm Neo
I'm Leo
I'm dzx Clark
I am
Leon
I can't remember a character's name
Navigate me home
Alex