Damn important I sweat it
I have great respect for snowledge b b
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
What's fight.com
Everybody a little bit about
Indeed we are. That's my new intro
Saturday
Dan 2020
Have you ever really f***** up at work
Lego
Really f***** up
Yeah I'm in the ton ton tons of time
I've been a terrible employee a lot of Japan fired
Lot in my younger days
I remember the car wash there's a there's a lot of
I know you were fired at about rehired as a man
Manager was fired as a projection
I'm not sure I think I quit when I was a projection
I came back
Beginning managers fired at the time was just like an usher
Box office
I was hired and fired and quit they are a lot of times over the years
You look like a bad relationship
I don't know I did screw up there a bit
Nothing too terrible a lot of the times the script
Your kind of manageable
In a popcorn popper
You have this big
Cabinet thing
The kettle that hangs down from the canal
Yeah and that pops the popcorn into the display thing when I go see the popcorn ready
Mi Lottery
Right
Underneath it in
The cabinet is a giant
Sing full of oil
But it has a little feed pump that goes up smoothie
Press a button
You've got to refill that oil bucket needs peanut oil in their whatever TV
And one time I don't remember if I was responsible for this
Somebody else was
But the bucket got knocked over and there was oil all over
There's an oil all over the place is everyone sleeping around trying to get candy and drinks for people
Does vodka have screwed up a lot at work
And I know
Alex Jones
Planning it working I don't know anybody
Today we got it I guess maybe this is
Zumiez grown up at work
We got another sort of what I'm going to call another mini so
We we set out
For like there's so much going on in the world recovering the
This present day stuff
My plan
This on
Tuesday in my plan was to
To cover Tuesdays episode
Like what
Today's episode of
For Wednesday
There was something that happened on Monday night I don't know if you noticed
Spell was the Iowa caucus
You know there's a lot going on in the world needs figure Alex Jones has
Probably
Even if the Iowa caucus went off without incident or any kind of trouble Alex would have some sort of
Bulshit to spend about it and it's relevant
Eat that and then you have the situation as it did on folder there are a lot of questions
Spiraling around about
Eisenhower
No one's really sure who won even as we work or
The most apropos thing that could
Could possibly happen in 2020 to the Democratic party
It's literally like I was hearing that happening as I
Oh yeah that makes sense
It was now that it was not a oh my God how could
He was like yeah
That's that's
There was a sense of like last night watching the coverage of it.
Hoo-boy
Come on
Come on guys
Guys
So I figured it was watching it last night
Alex is going to have a field day with this
This is going to be
Outrage
But then I turned into the episode today in order to prepare episode and Mike Adams and Owen Shroyer
Alex is gone
Total abdication of responsibility on that one is
Staggering
Just so it's clear like you know we're recording this on Tuesday and so it's last night was the Iowa
Caucuses in 20
20 +
We're not going to talk too much about
That
And we will probably on a future episode but the reality is that this is a podcast where we talk about Alex Jones is
Claims about things
That sounds Jones doesn't have any claims that we can address about that caucus
It seems like I don't I don't want to just do I want to be a news show where we get into everything that's going on
I need Alex to bounce off of
We can dress them but for now it might be disappointing but
There's no hot takes
About the present day
Necessarily coming from me
Be the obvious take is holyshit
Dum Dums
What
Don't
Hot to take don't do that
The scorching
DNC
So I guess I don't know
We'll get there when we
Right
So I thought like
Okay Super Bowl was Sunday Alex probably could be mad about Shakira on Monday
Podos Watson toasting on Monday
I don't care
No
Certainly not
It's so like I'm not covering Paul Joseph Watson doing his a boutique culture
Concerned he'll do
And we go to Sunday
Cuz I listen to a bit of Sunday
We'll talk a little bit about Sunday but then I decided I'm just going to go far afield
And find something to talk about and see what that's why today is a little bit of a grab
A little bit of Sunday
I'm a little
Pump up before we get down to that particular moment Jordan say thank you
Books of signed up
First of all Alicia thank you so much
Thank you Alicia Alicia
Sorry
Next Natalie thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Natalie Imbruglia
Next Matthew thank you so much.
Thank you very much Matthew Broderick
Did he
Julie thank you so much
Thank you very much Julie
Andrews
From The Sound of Music
Xavier thank you so much
You're now call if you want
I'm a policy wonk
Javier Bardem No Country for Old Men
It's a really really monotone song in that movie
Text Jamie thank you so much
Thank you very much Jamie from
What was the thing
There's Jamie
The Jimmy is a the famous pop star
Something
Now I can pick up his Jamie the shity
Okay
His alter-ego
Alright
Isn't good enough for you
What's the Sanskrit
We all remember West
All those great song
Donated on an elevated level
Jeff thank you so much you and I were technocrat
And
Elephant engineer thank you so much you are now a technocrat
Heroin
Freakishly large
K engineer never heard of
Those are great
Not that open
Thank you so much
Shug Isaiah if you're right there listening
Noteflight.com
Maybe very lovely
Start off on doing this little bit
From February 2nd this last Sunday I had tuned in and one of the things that
The first lady of note is it Alex's recording not from Studio
He's sitting at a desk
Somewhere maybe a hotel room
And the sound is a
Atrocious
And he gets into the show and immediately just like
I have no time for this
I've no
I'm getting very sick
Vista ladies and gentlemen
Thank you for joining us on this live
Sunday broadcast I am on the road
And we
Just have incredible break
He knows that just went live that is
Global explosion
Conjunction with natural news.com
With my cat
Raquel Houston
Coming up 2nd hour
Myself and
Pampered
To the main house I wanted to be able to
I'll get to all this new evidence
Emergent is Coronavirus
Bio weapon
Might have been
Experiment gone wrong
Genes contain
MP shuttle
SMS
Proving laboratory origin
Now why is
So important
Well I came out
Arrowhead
Reported on India newspaper
Aegis scientific
Research Center
Buy used computers
Regine at it
Clearly had
Another virus
Is welded in
Including the original HIV
Got to control corporate media come out and
Say oh well
Lexus
Read the paper
They said zerohedge made up
Okay
Zerohedge
Outage.
The doctors by
An NFL quarterback
That's how they
I took the second call anything harassment
Big Jack
So you know right away there's
This paper
Prestigious
It's prestigious you know it I've always thought that
There are two famous types
Two people there's NFL quarterback research scientist
Comparison
So sick and tired of us doing these episodes that have
Too much about this coronavirus stop
Don't very desperate on Alex's
Is Bart you can just see
Like how badly he wants this to be like a narrative that blossoms for him and
It's just not how I'm very tired of it it's not
But In that clip Alex does bring up two things that I think deserve it
The first is that scientific paper that he mentioned and the second is 0 hat
So on January 31st 2020
Researchers at the Indian
Betutu technology in New Delhi published a paper on a website called biorxiv titled
Uncanny similarity of unique inserts in the 2019 novel coronavirus Spike
Protein
To hiv-1
Gp120 and gag
One thing that's important to point out which Alex and Mike Adams seem to not want to discuss
Is what this website Bart biorxiv actually is
It's a preprint server
We're researchers and scientists compose papers that have not been vetted in
In any way
The issues the peer-review ain't can be a long process
That's where reputable Journal is unwilling to publish something without really going over
Make sure the weather
Their standards
That's weird
Preprint servers can come in handy
From biorxiv website
Quote
Because this process can be lengthy
Authors use the biorxiv service to make their manuscripts available as pre pre
Before completing peer-review
Inconsequence service
Application by a journal
This allows other scientist to see discuss and comment on the findings of media
Readers should therefore be aware that articles on biorxiv I have not been finalized by authors
May contain errors
And Reporting
Information that has not been yet
Accepted
In any way by scientific or medical
This paper that Alex is citing his prestigious was in no way verified and even according to its source
Should not be taken as a finalized version of anything
Also
If you try to find this paper now you find this message
Quote
This paper has been withdrawn by its author
They intend to revise it in response to comments
Receive from the research community on their technical approach
And their interpretation of results
They retracted their paper on Sunday
The same day that Alex is on air talk about it being a Smoking Gun
Diprove
This virus is a bioweapon
So to sum it up Oz primary service here is a paper that was
Attracted by its own authors after being
Published on Enon. View preprint server
Put it simply
This is not strong enough to support any of
The claims that he's trying to make
They should not allow
Non-scientist anywhere near that
Like you journalists should be allowed to go near it
Alex should be nowhere
Alex didn't even know it existed and if he does look at it
They should be like an Emmy
Menin black like neuralyzer that
Wiped his memory I don't disagree that it is the sort of thing they could easily and you can see the exact
Instance of a kitties alili
Lead to trouble but what years
Suggesting would be just as bad there's a cover-up
That's not the point is they can't have
They when they have this information they're just
They're just awful with
Ignore the caveat in the astric of like this is not in any way substantiated
Something's it's these research
Searchers are putting up
For discussion within the medical and scientific research
Community
It's just
You can't run with it like
Alex is trying to run
Server is we're putting up
Stuff for other scientists
To look at
Cuz we're fairly certain
That there's going to be something that we can make
Make better
Never
Particularly the danger is this game too is that because there was a lot of backlash
From the scientific and medical community about the way they were framing things IV results that they were claiming
To have received
Voluntarily withdrew their own paper because of this
Critique and comments that the guy from the the community
Now Alex can claim that they took it down because it's a cover-up
It's
It is all just
Disgraceful shell game
Instead of the scientific Community doing
Job and self-policing to a very high quality standards
Instead it's a conspiracy
Cover up
Bingo
As for the situation with zerohedge and as nothing
To do with
This paper from India
Alex is trying to conflate
The two because
The BuzzFeed article about zerohedge getting kicked off Twitter
Which is what everyone
Alex is mad about you
That article mentioned
That zerohedge should work with an Indian
Theory website called greatgameindia
Push narratives about the coronavirus being stolen from a Canadian lab in Winnipeg
That's the only connection to India but it
It's enough for Alex
To pretend that these are related
It's stories
So what happened is that zerohedge
Published an article accusing of virologist in Wuhan of creating the virus
Andy posted his name email address and phone
And your dog
Also said
Quote if anyone wants to find out what really caused the coronavirus pandemic
Infected thousands of people in China and around the globe they should probably pay him a visit
No no no you say if anybody wants
To find out that information
Stop check Outback
Do
Look at this time
That's just completely unacceptable Behavior has no evidence of this guy created the coronavirus and yet they're making
That accusation into
Suggesting people should go pay
Pay him a visit
You can't do stuff like that and if I were Twitter I would have kicked them off the platform for that too
Granted I probably would have done it a long time ago but let's not split hairs NFL quarterback there
Are public figures
Researchers literally no one has ever heard of before
Posting a paper the
Public figure
So I got into that and I'm like I'm not doing another episode
Alex and Mike
Trying to sell food buckets and weird silver with fears about this virus
Alex's
Glitchy audio
Yeah I just can't do it
I was not in for it I
Prime to myself for some sort of a political thing is like
I'm not in the mood I feel like the audio
Probably getting
I'm sick and tired of Alex's lies about the virus
So I
What can I do what
Can we do
Iowa caucus
I think it to myself
One of Alex's finest MoMA
Involves the Iowa caucus
Okay cuz back in 2012 Ron Paul was running
Pretty well
In the Iowa caucus
He had came in third and votes yeah but he ended up getting
22 out of
The 20s
8 delegates
Oh that's right because Iowa should be removed from democracy
I'm not I'm not
Yeah you got 22 out of the 28.
I'm not sure if I agree with you that I was should be removed from
Democracy but
The the
Caucus system involves
Places where manipulation
Can can be done by I think it might be
An undemocratic way of calling about
Rick Santorum won the Iowa caucuses in 2012
If you want the votes
Of the people who showed up at the Iowa caucuses
And I got
Pizza
Probably going to be something kind of
So I went back to the day of the Iowa caucus
Switches January 3rd
And what'd you find
Wow
You find Alex being very insistent the Ron Paul is going to win but
Is also going to be screwed over
And
An interview
With Wayne Paul
Senators passed the Fed
So we got a little bit of episode and then an interview with Wayne
Call
I don't know
This episode by be completely pointless
But hey it's Iowa caucus time
Go ahead and listen to Alex's Iowa caucus
In 2012 when he had a feeling
The Ron Paul probably had a chance
It winning
The nomination should be president
Obama's ass everybody was going to choose Ron Paul over Obama totally so here we go
We start off with Alex
Extolling the virtues
And
Did you know what is you
If you don't like Ron Paul Alex has some words
You don't like Ron Paul
You don't like
What America is
Imran Paula myself are
Vipers
Republic
Anywhere signed onto the New World Order
.
Putting it pretty strongly
If you like America you better like Ron Paul
So let's see some like us
Vipers
Nationally Ron Paul with polling
Between 8 and 12% of Broadway Providence roughly 90% of the United
I'd say it was 100%
Globalist
Snake Viper
Agree
I did I don't have a ton of like the rest of this episode cuz they
Who gives a s***
But Alex says take some calls
Amy gets a call from a guy was nothing
The Iowa caucus
Yes but I found this
Be very interest
Thank you welcome
Are you there
Okay
Find your listener
I'm calling cuz I need your help I'm I'm in the process of declaring myself a free man
On the land
I would have the Social Security
System
Number
If you accept that number to your name that's what ties you legally
They said they don't even follow their own rules just like
Gotten rid of due process and say they'll secretly arrest you and blow your head off
Darrell Wallace Criminal
But just because you say I'm a sovereign you pull out of it
Unless you're an illegal alien they won't leave you alone about the law because they're here to drive down wages
Sure see you thought this was going to be a thing where Alex reveals he believes sovereign
Turns out also
Swerves at the end to race
I think it's funny that he
He's gone he's he's against Sovereign citizens doing their bulshit
From the other side like a garlic pickle
Absolutely everything
True but it doesn't matter if they're going to find you anywhere there's a practical aspect
As opposed to the magical thinking of
What's my social security number I'm a free man on the follow the law
Of course you could
Would just be a man on the lamp
So Alex's pretty Sovereign citizen
Of course
That's true sir
That was that's a weird response that kind of call
School
So if you get around to the Dwayne Paul interview and here's Alex giving him a little bit of an
Intro witch
Like you can really tell their seams
To be a talk
Talking point that Alex really seems to be pushing back on
You think you'll be able to tell what it is
He's a CPA
He just a chip off the same block Tron Paul came from the same tree
And I wanted to get him on today
To talk a little bit about his brother who is Brother really yes
Volunteer for free
Cherry hospital
The pre-market you're supposed to have people to dedicate the wrong time
Willingly
To help those that are in need the Bible teaches
I don't know that Ron Paul Regina
German campaign from others
Volunteer in the minority of black
Areas mainly in
Hero
If you want to wow it because it's painful
Because he knows he's doing his duty
There's a little bit of a concern about Ron Paul's
Rapunzel racing
I was coming up for president
People that
People that say APA research people dig into your newsletters
Really racist
Find associations with your no
Nazis and white supremacist
From the past
Did you find
What's up with this David Duke really loves you what's going on
I know certain things
Dialects
I feel like you're one of the things that he really wants to drive home is like Ron Paul when he was a doctor love to give free help
Healthcare to black people clubs in but that's why he was giving free healthcare to Black
It comes up multiple times
Yeah in this this interview
Searchers are used to like
Digging for Stuff
And with rampal they were they put their shovel down put the foot on there when click
We didn't even have to go.
Not too deep
So I'm not positive what Alex is talking about when he says that Wayne Paul fought the IRS in court but
EPA
He actually has seen that on some
Particular
But
I did find a little gem
About a lawsuit and the IRS
I'm going to go to the Lost
But it wasn't Court
That involve Dwayne Paul
So in 2009 when Paul was called as a
The defense witness in the trial of a man named Robert who was accused of skirting
Tax laws
So it seems that the situation was that he was paying his employees with gold and silver clef
And people who had like contract to it. He was only reporting their pay as buffets
Ace value of the coin
For instance he might pay someone with a gold dollar coin that was valued at $200
But he was claiming it as $1
Text Mom
That might sound like a small thing
And it probably would be if you're just doing it with one coin
Was super rich
Apparently he was doing it a lot
Ultimately found guilty
Use facing a possible sign of
14 million dollars
Would you give you some kind of scope
Of what kind of money you was hiding from the IRS with this key
Soca reggae would ultimately end up being sentenced to 190 months in prison
Love it
HP Pavilion
In restitution for the
First time I've heard the criminal justice system working right
I think it did take awhile though it was a drawn-out process
One of his advisors
Alexander lolkhalia was also sentenced
26 months in prison
Because this involved
A bit of a conspiracy
That'll have
That'll happen so you bring in Wayne Paul as your defense
Interesting Lee log Leah was also a tease guy who is part of Bill Cooper's
Taji organization citizens Agency for joint intelligence
Bill Cooper sale multiple times
What are these
Defense witness in that case which did not go well for the dude that he was
Supporting
Iavarone Paulding like I said volunteering as a doctorate that's great
But I don't know how much I believe that you super concerned with minority
He's getting a proper
The stupid was published
Newsletter was written
BabyFirst
Person who had I it was
Personal opinion of politicians
We'll go straight there books
Sure
Cherry dick
So when Paul comes in
Am I handsome
Concerns about the transparency issues
You know like
I think it's a legitimate concern
And
When Paul has a solution
What is first
On your radar screen here today my friend
How do we know we're going at
Are bananas
Long time
Website
Transparent
Dotnet
Precinct 1
Put it up and you
A picture of it
With your iPhone and
Transparent
This guy sounds
Transparent boat.net
Shaky voice
Old camera photo
It doesn't seem like the worst baby on the world although I think that the photos that people are sending in should be vetted
Before they accepted as being real
Like I I think that the process could become free
Pretty complicated I don't know if the people who are running that website have the infrastructure or ability to handle that sort of thing
It's the same thing that I thought when I was listening to people call into shows last night as we're going his last night during
Iowa coverage
From this year
Are people calling in with Tally's
From caucuses
I don't have any reason to distrust them necessarily
I also have no idea what they're saying is a cure
Just a person on a phone in the same way this is just a picture you could make that picture and the possibilities
Need verification
Stop
Baseline idea behind this person with this website
Liverwurst ideas
Anyway I don't think this website took off
The earliest snapshot of it in the way-back machine
Gina's from early 2030
So that after this
Did not stick around for very long
Affair and by that point in early 2013
It already become a landing page with Spam in Japanese
Promoting a shop
In Japan the text that you will find on transparent
There's a sex shop that you always visit when you come to Osaka
The sex shop does not offer any special services
Especially notable
And not even
Thrilling business
It's a very ordinary sex shop with the image of
General sex shop
Especially Osaka this is special
There is no complaint to sing
However I'm worried and I go every time I come to Osaka
It's such a mysterious shop
It's not that I'm messing around rather praise
I'm going to praise it like this
I think it is just you want to visit
However why is it so attractive
I don't know well
And as I said
Go to Osaka again this weekend
Even so
I guess I would go to that site
I guess that is simple and cute girl smiles
The goes to the store
It says have you come I'm glad
Okay is this sex shop is synecdoche for the United States electoral system is that what's going on
Cuz I can see a little bit of it there
There's another page
Not just the landing homepage
Another page titled quote
Mentu
Which begin
Quote
This was also taught at the sex shop in Osaka
But man also squirt
Okay
All right interesting okay tomorrow I looked into the pages on this website the more it became clear that this was largely about a sex
Shopping Osaka not focus on prostate orgasm
There's a page titled quote I liked it! At the Goodwood quote
Yes yes
The prostate is something only we have
It seems to be about 5
The hole in the ass
What's happening here are these are these reviews communicating with each other it is said that if you stimulate if you will get pleasure
Almost forever
Almost
Bottom line is I guess that this transparent voting initiative didn't take off the way Wayne Paul helped my feet
Because I wanted to try and sort out what this website was like I was hoping to find some sort of
Japanese anus
Sex shop
So thanks for that
Sometimes you set up the website that you think you want
But you find out you get the website
Paul was really that's what he need
Yeah so that's a baby that has nothing to do with
Anything
Relevant at all but it's what you like you would look at the Wayback machine
Transparent
I did not.
So one of the things I found really interesting about listening
Into this interview with Wayne
Saint Paul on the day of the Iowa caucus
Lexus 2012
Firstly is it always does seem to be subtly pushing back on the idea that Ron Paul is racist
I'm on the second thing is
How much does
Directly mirrors
So much of his language about
Imagine your brother really for 40 years but prominently for three decades
Traveling the country writing books of Congress
Battling for basic
Americana Liberty
Constitution
And now here he is right is everything he warned of and you and I and many others and a griffin
Why does it all happening Justice League
Sad
There is Ron Paul and that's God giving us a chance she'll God if you study the Bible
A way out a chance
This is so similar to
So how he like really
Tried to characterize the
The 2016
The god giving us a
Free like Nineveh
Constantly
Absolutely
This it's startling to me almost to look back and see
What in in
View contacts
Could seem as a little bit more rational
I mean for all Ron Paul's faulted
At least he's a
Politician
Who's been elected to office Multan
We'll try and who seems to believe what he says
Sure
As good or bad as those things exactly have
Like
Not just f****** around
Do you see the same
Sorta framing
In the same
It just it was very jarring
Yeah I don't know I don't know if anyone else so
Have a similar response
Seen that language
Biso
Vigorously applied to the truck
Situation
A man looking back
It's exactly the same way here
You tried to frame the 2012 like
Really just makes everything seem
Wait cheaper
Like it makes
The 2012
Stop saying cheaper and it makes the 20s
16 things to seem like this is what he does
Yeah yeah
I mean
But he didn't do that obviously for Romney or the bushes
So
Probably
It seems to me like 2016 with something that is ruining 2012
Just doesn't have any other way of will cuz he had a candidate that made it out of the primary
And one that you like
Yeah apposite
Yeah
Flower f*****
That's weird
There's also the same thing with Trump I mean I guess like
You could get that even from that last like we're getting
God gives us
Icu2 I like it needs to be now
We live in the most
Starting times
Because if we never have enough
Like this in my lifetime
We here
I think it's
Fighting tickets
It is
Going to be
Something bad
Surprise everybody because the time is now
Okay
Do not do this I don't know why that happened
I don't know whatever Wayne Paul says The Time Is Now John Cena's theme song that starts playing
I didn't do that are you anything you had
No it's just something that really absolutely
Of course I had admitted
But it's important whenever anybody says the time is now you need
Okay
That's how much
I told little you could find today
Go to the actual episode
You would have threw the f*** out with
Open me like I did it's a representation of how little I
Respect I have for Whitehall
Probably
We are living in a
Exciting times because
Fake teeth
Well I mean beer again
You have you know we're living in the most exciting time and it's
There's just so much a ring
What would end up being exactly the way that Alex
I talks about Trump
So
An interesting thing is here
You got
Alex Jones
Who does Adam Schiff
And you have him supporting a candidate
Who has
A fair shot of coming in the top
End of the field
And
The first caucus of the primary Clinic
So it's so bizarre that Percival he chooses to have
As a guest
That candidates brother
No there's no,
Flick of interest there
First of all there is
Play Penis music
Second of all it just seems like
I don't know what
What you hoped
To get out of this other than maybe pay
You know like I know I can't imagine
If you have a
Like I wouldn't
You'll be bizarre to me for like
I don't know
Madout2 have Hillary Clinton's Brother on
Or something like that and think it's like
Hard-hitting
Yeah yeah Iowa caucus
It just seems like
I don't get it
I don't get I get to choice
Right but it's not a serious
No choice
Well I mean there's a reason that I don't remember making all the interview rounds on Nash
No TV I don't think Grandpa would like you went on Rush
Bring me John Fox News you're my surrogate for this interview we got to get Wayne out front
But it seems really weird and in because
When Paul doesn't really have much
By way of
Being a surrogate
Haven't much relevancy to Ron Paul's campaign
It ends up drifting
Into Alex trying to talk about their childhood
Where's the puppy
Would you like
Growing up with Ron Paul
You guys have a large family growing up
How would you characterize him in the family
And then he forgot his life what type of person is Ron Paul
What do you make of all of these yeah and I'm taking out of tens of thousands of newsletters
I taking an option lines or something
Conflating them with other things
And then attacking your brother
So there's two things that are going on here one again you see this interest in pushing back again
Against the racist narrative cuz that's what he's talking about
The newsletters
I meant secondarily I
This strategy is I don't even know if it's
Conscious strategy
Just how someone like
Opera
This is about endearing
Ron Paul further
By way of story
Like because
Broadleaf
Going to get into the nitty-gritty of policy
Or anything like that
The way you're going to end up doing is making stories surrounding
His Canada
That is the most important
Elements too appealing to this
Those right-wing base
Yeah you need an emotion
P0land that's going
Going to do a lot of work
Problem is everybody was listening to our to show already loves Ron Paul so I don't know who you are
Hoping to swing
Bye-bye way of like what was it like growing up with Lompoc give us
Character that we can all relate to in
Attach ourselves to
You're selling a sold car
That's what you're doing it just
Now about those newsletter
The racist and Ron Paul's newsletter is were absolutely not taken out of context and it's not just a
Couple line 12 lines in your conflating them with false information
What kind of
Idiot
Take only a few lines out of context and then conflate them with
Play different things that would be insane
There's a great
He's about this in the new Republic by James Croce
Check the gets into some of the more frog
Example
A Ron Paul being a gigantic raises
Princeton
1992 article about the w
Order was only restored in La when it came time for the blacks to pick up their welfare check okay
The piece also applauded the Korean store owners who are quote the only
People to act like real America
Mainly because they have not yet been assimilated into our rotten liberal culture which admonishes White
Face by raging blacks to lie back in
Think of England
Now that one is going to be tough to
Explain away
Yeah I think that one is pretty comprehensive in being racist
For there was the 1989 article that predicted racial violence will fill our cities because quote
Mostly black welfare recipients
Will feel justified in stealing from the most
Ugly white Ave
All car all right there's a June 1991 article about racial tension in a DC neighborhood titled quote
Animals take over the DC zoo
Okay
Nope nope
There's a singular fixation in his newsletters about the coming race war and a trend
Calling non-whites animals
In an article from 1990 to the newsletter says quote
Everyone in my family to know how to use a gun in self-defense
For the animals are coming
There was one for 1996 that opine
Find the quote opinion polls consistently show that only
Only 5% of blacks have sensible political
The newsletters called the end of Apartheid in South Africa a quote
Destruction of civilization
I quote the most tragic event to ever occur on that continent
At least below the sea
Sahara
Why is it
So many of these right-wing figures
Steam to take
The exact same view of the world
Charles Mann
Why is there so much overlap between
Manson breach
I don't know
Or who could forget about all the positive coverage of the newsletters gave to David Duke
Back in 1991 saying quote
Duke lost the election but he scared the blazes out of the established
All this makes sense I mean after all Duke didn't endorse Ron Paul for president
Is it pretty much all of the white supremacist
Community in the country that has any interest in electoral politics
Unless they're trying to become men of the
Plato care about electoral politics
This is very serious and very consistent
What type of ship
It goes on even getting into the gay bashing a
Completely nonsensical revisionist
History and
Anti-communist
Conspiracy s*** in those news
Ron Paul is not a folksy weirdo hates Banks and Lauren loves we
He's either of violently racist person who had no problem expressing
Brett Sanders views
Is it is newsletter incompetent
Allowed someone else
To write violently racist articles in his newsletter in the first-person and somehow we didn't notice until he was asked
About it when he ran for
Such b*******
This is this is sad
And like yeah go ahead ask Wayne Paul
About it
Ask his
Brother
Buddhist like growing up with Ron Paul
You do
Racist another Children of the
Wait wait doesn't even respond to the newsletter
Stop
Assertive waxes
Nostalgic about a bygone time
Alex tries to read
Dot-dot-dot
Alex tries to refocus him on like how would you
Scribe Ron
How would you describe
Ron Paul
What drives your brother
High School
Store
Making
Keep in mind
Ron Paul was born in 90
He's currently 84 years old
He was a child during World War II
This quaint picture that Wayne is painting sounds like
I-24 into modern years maybe
But it's super common
Among people who were born in the 30
Oh yeah
Why would they how would they
They even get jobs
Do you know how hard the job market is
Now I assume it's exactly the same whenever most of
The male population
Is going in fighting a war over
He talks about like paying his own way through college
It's like yeah
College constantly
Hundred dollars
Station.
I used to I paid for my college off for years and when I walked out I didn't have any debt
How much did you pay for Colin
$2,000 is a nice day
Do you know how much
So
It's not really a dress
So much
You know Alex keeps bringing up the like thing
Better serve
Geared towards the like everyone saying Ron's erases
But it's not really addressed all that much
It's just like
Pushed back on without really
Without Really dealing with what the
The complaints are
Consistently false claims
I know that you know your brother well
Well
EBay
American money
I made an agreement to get paid
Never
Medicare
Anytime
Being a duck
That's right never took it and many cases
Or just give people free healthcare
What
I mean most doctors would just turn you away right there
Oh really your brother
Understands the issues and that's why the system so scared of him
Because they know
He can't be bought
And there's no skeletons in his closet
Same thing that Alex says about Trump
Ikea's you can't be bought
There's no skeletons in the closet
Massive amounts of skeleton good both of their closet
Skeleton
There specific specifically closet built for Scarlett
Yeah yeah they hang them up very nicely
Full of sky
And also there's a big difference between with Alex's presenting like you gave people free healthcare and
What Wayne is
Describing which is like
You work under the table we work out a deal where you can pay me so I don't have to go through the administrative bulshit
Medicare whatever select different
So how about you give me a
A gold coin worth $200 and we'll call it 1.
That's
Whatever whatever Wayne is describing is
Quaint and I don't know the legality of
I don't know the thing
The details of half
If you can or can't do that or you should or shouldn't
What are the ramifications of it
But that's not giving people free healthcare
Whatever's going on is f***** up
The quote minority
I'm back on this thing it would buy by using this as a way of being like he can't be right
He gave Healthcare to Maita quote
Minority
Leah VI
DIA
Beds
Other places
Would turn away
Black patient
But Ron Paul
Hero
Of the minority community
Is the only one who will
I think you wouldn't be a f***
In fairness I think what he was talking about Maurice
Specifically was people who couldn't
You know it
Nmd
Alex was saying it was largely in quote
Minority Turning Away people at hospitals
Not paying.
Alex is
Combining those two
To make Ron Paul appear more virtue
Exactly
So while at the same time demonizing
Black people for always be
Well I mean it's
He's read the newsletter
Alex has a well-read man so
So
Paul is going into the Iowa
And Wayne
As unconcerned
I'm at is the
Certainly I mean that is a concern
There's dirty
Perhaps going on behind the scene
It does show The Awakening is huge that despite the
The line Decepticon media telling everybody
Ron Paul can't win
The front-runner
And they're in full panic mode
What are some of the dirty tricks are expecting them to peulwane
The Caucus meeting tonight in Iowa
Because
Big people in the
In the individual
The Grassroots
Serious-minded
Individual
Any one of the Canada
They're normally
Fairies
Dedicated hard-working
Moving along way
Quicker
I believe
Precinct
Numbers
Will be honest
In every way shape of
Michael
Would be what happened
One day go to 8
Secret place
Transparency
So it's
It's it's fun
This
Concerned
As you with that these sorts of issues
Primaries in Cox
Does butt
It's interesting that he's talking
Going about this
Is dirty trick
But they're going to be going on at the Iowa caucus
Because there were dirty
But
There's something really interesting about the what happened with the Iowa caucus
In 2012 and that was
Mitt Romney
Was
Everybody kind of thought God's Own favorite if somebody was going to take the Republican nomination
People in the race like Gingrich had a little bit of Santorum
Wasn't appealing candidate
He's made of
If you added November
That Outsider Fringe
Sting that the libertarian vibe
There was a lot of there's a lot of things going on
But Mitt Romney was seeing his up by most as being like the odds-on guy
Mitt Romney was 2012
He announced
Prior to the caucus
Even as far back as late-2011
Mitt Romney announce he wasn't going to participate
The Iowa straw poll
And he seemed like he was taking pretty low into
Identity approach
The Iowa
This is a whole lot of people like Ron Paul a big open
To really hit the ground hard
Try and get people out to the car
So despite a fairly
Meek attempted woman Iowa
Initially declared the winner
Of the Iowa caucus
Do you report what
Was that
He beat Rick Santorum by 8 votes
I was just kind of irrelevant because total supporters don't necessarily Translate
The number of delegates
Cockatrice
Stupid
I don't know if they're stupid but they're weird
After the talleys recertify
It turned out the Rick Santorum it actually beat Romney
By 34
But all those kind of mood
Has Ron Paul won almost
All of the states delegate
Even though he was thirty-eight hundred votes behind either Ronnie or Santorum
And he won how many of their delegates
22 out of 28 okay
And so that is nothing
For what risk
Who campaign was able to achieve this by manipulating the rules of how delegates work in caucus
Okay delegates are elected but they're not bound to vote for the person who wins
The state
In this case santora
Because of this little quirk
Post-campaign works
Get his supporters in positions where they would be elected as delegate that came with every right to vote for whoever they want
Due to this political maneuvering Ron Paul was
Easily able to win 22 out of 28 elections up for grabs even though he came in service
Milk people in there
I don't know what Larry how much
Like subterfuge went on and I was entirely sure like how much of it was
Actual like
Nefarious
Stop
Based on deterrent like the United that's not okay. Okay for the guy in third ticket
What 80% or 70%
As I look
That
I think
That's not really cheating
Backroom Bud Knox
Comparing two kind of shady there's a there's a certain part of me that finds that a little bit Charming
I'm not going to lie
I mean yeah
I don't I have I have mixed feelings about it cuz on the one hand it does mean that whoever was
Doing that
That was definitely super motivated
They were very into the
The process they knew the rules
Well but on the other
It is subverting Will of people a little bit
I mean there is
So I don't know
Waiting to be less concerned about the
Strategy that appears Ron was using every time these guys say you better watch out for voter fraud
On the other side it's because we're about to do some voter fraud on our I don't know how much rain is even aware of that
Because quite frankly
I don't know
Yeah so
We get back in this next clip to just like
Echoes
Of
And the way Alex souldrop like
If you take the name wrong Paul out of here I think
Probably sounds very similar to how Alex
Talk about drama
Once people convert to Liberty and put
Together
Understand how things work
Ologies
He's getting people to ReDiscover history ReDiscover common-sense ReDiscover
The horrible stuff were being sold by the establishment
It's the establishment
It's got something to hide it's the establishment
Discredited in cookies
Not Ron Paul
And every month
We exponentially grow
And that's why the system scared
Alex says everything
Thing is exponential
Sammy even said make her cook Freight
You know
I agree with that that to me
Is f***** up
Because
That can't be a coincidence
It's not his idea
No they didn't get it
Fact that ends up being
Trump
Rallying slogan
It's how he's talking about Ron Paul in 2012 it's just it's just weird there's so much
I think it makes
Based on what were
Experiencing right now
Now with Alex
It's B
This is the same problem that he's having
On the truck
He only has one way to sell a
Right you got a million ways to try and tear down again
He's only got one weight
To sell
So when Trump comes along it doesn't matter if it's true or not
Selling Trump so he sells them like so if it's wrong
It is it is
One of the shortcomings
Douglas Park
So far
And like in terms of what we've list
Listen to
Is that there hasn't been a ton of
Our coverage of
How he promoted Ron Paul during those years
Make me wonder if just this little glimpse of him talking
Dwayne it makes me wonder how much like we could go back
To the Ron Paul time
And you're almost
Direct parallels
Of how Alex
Promoted
Yeah I would be surprised if there was a way heavier overlap
Then why
You would assume that well I would be interested now and just like going through each of the candidates since like
Like 2,000
And finding
If you pick
Different ones at that time and told him the same way but that's all
In 2016 it would have been Ron Paul but in
Instead it was ran
Don't know
Did Ron Paul run in 2004
You might
I don't know I don't remember
12 where his big
Big rotten
Yeah yeah
Yeah I don't I don't know
I don't know I think
I think it's a surprise
His big runs came against a black
Weird it's almost like
Certain people or more in
You read the news
So I
There's another source
Parallel here and that you hear that
They've been able to control
Inspect
Somewhere
Beer with him
But those times are changed
Day is it changes
I am Groot
Beer
Life for he and his family
You're right on the same page together
So you have that same also that parallel look like Alex's
Pitching the
Crisis
If Trump is like he's too popular at your death killer
He can't be controlled and he knows they're going to kill him anyways but he
Still doing it because he just believe so hard he's willing
To divert
I mean it
It's almost shocking really to look
Get this would be like
Wow
I guess that's what he does
Yeah it's almost
Copy and paste yeah it really is
Very strange
So again
Wayne Paul is not like
The guy who is Rollo
Brilliant accounting
I wasn't asking about account
Seems like that would be his his best interview
Do his best shot is to ask
What about when you work
But get back more into this
Started waking up to this whole new world order collectivist
A slave system was it tell you was another brother was at Ron give us that more
Well I think
When was waiting for baby
Read Austrian economics
So he went all the way back
Indiana Street
Economics
Which is free enterprise
Private prep
Liberty to do what you want
You learned and understood
Daughter last episode we talked about how the me since
Institute believes you have the right to allow your child to die
Because because forcing you to feed them as an infringement on your rights
They are
Ron Paul was there at the beginning
Got it from the store
He read all of this Ludwig von mises s***
And he went
Buckwild
While he was waiting for
Baby I imagine he's standing there next to the woman just got his watch out and lost Rihanna
This book I'm not obligated to help you give birth
Forcing me
To help you
In your pregnancy is a
Positive responsibility and an infringement on my right
Wouldn't he be allowed to
First ask for payment before he gives her the baby
Probably I don't know
I think so but we talked about that issue with the me since
Institute on last episode but today I want to tell you about how they celebrated Chris
Smith's 1998
And that was by post
An article defending Ebenezer Scrooge
Alright guys we got this one
So from the article
The fact is
Skills were worth more to anyone than the fifteen Shillings screwed pay is it weekly
There would be someone glad to offer it to him
Since no one has
Denton scratches
Profit-maximizing boss is hardly a man to pay for nothing
Cratchit must
Be worth
Exactly his present wages
Sprite I don't think they got the
The point of the story is I'm starting to think that there
Their quibble isn't with dickon
No scratch it needs
I e w
More to support his family and to care for Tiny Tim food but Scrooge did not
For scratcher to father children he's having difficulty supporting children
Afford them he
Not Scrooge is responsible for their plate
There you go
The math checks out
You got to take responsibility for your actions homies Institute also take same
Right at the ghost
The Christmas Past what about
What's the conditions at the time
Definitely leading to Tiny Tim's series of ailment
That wasn't his
Joyce did he have a choice
The live in London
So but about to go ghost
Christmas Past
Scrooge's first employee are good old fezziwig was a bit
Free or with the guinea
He throws his employees a Christmas
Miss party
What the what the Ghost of Christmas Past does not explain is how physically
Weather for today
Did he attempt
To pass the added costs on to his customers
Or did Young Scrooge pay for it Anyway by working for marginal he's up or wages
Guys are having fun to hang out with
Clearly they f****** love everything's recruit
Get me a beer your friendship is not valuable enough for one full beer I will get you 1/2
About Scrooge it is at a closed
The article
There can be no arguing with Ditka
Wish to show the spiritual advantages of love
But there was no need to make the object of his lesson and entrepreneur whose ideas and practices
Is benefit his employees at Large
Adam cell
Won't anybody think of the oligarchs than what anybody think of how very much
Real death
These guys are real
That's almost
That Elvis has to be delivered trolling and I would believe that if they didn't believe everything that they're saying
Stuff that I've read from that my do not believe this
Stroller
I think it's probably written with a little bit of a win
But the wing
Is like
I'm f****** with you it's like
Look at this I'm I'm taking how I read this book better than you you dumb dumb
That's the way
Yats The Comedy of it
Sheetz
I just
I just admire
That kind of certain like oh I'm going after this
1 cherished
Immortal story from everybody
Easily gets the moral of
Flip it on its head baby
You guys don't have
Still like a central problem
With philosophies that put
Private property as
View top
Yeah the thing
The highest priority
I'm in secondarily
Libertarianism is a real problem
Wet because the non-aggression
Principal the two Central to libertarian thought
Is incoherent
And so trying to apply those
Two things
Like at and apply them to all sorts of Life situation
You just end up with
Nonsensical s*** like
Scrooge was the real victim
And you should be able to let your kids starve
Great
Let's let's follow our beliefs to their logical conclusion and all of our children
Starve to death okay
I think we might be on
Ron Paul read all that stuff decided here's a career that's what I got
40 f****** years
One lady had to wait he she was in labor for like 3 days you read all of the books and now he's sick of being a doctor
So we know one thing
A lot about Wayne Paul
Like
Defining
I mean it's what you said as soon as you heard his name and that is what he believes that three people voted
Federal Reserve
Cuz he said that in Alex's.
Documentary
And then it turns out he says it on the show
You really does believe that he does
Habitat for every person in the United
Its face
Spider-Man
App for route
November
1913 Federal Reserve
Free People
Saturdays
We turn around and Roosevelt
Bankrupt
Yep
Yep yep
I mean that's just lunacy
There's no other way to put it is it like
So easy
To show that that is not
True
You're being deliberately out
To see if you continue to believe
I don't know I don't know I think he's just
Like
Maybe old
And
Dumb
That could be all
I worry about the Paul family you think so I don't know I don't know their other sibling
But the two of them are not a good example of
I like really well-thought-out
Position
Like if I were wrong
I would be like Wayne
Don't go on Infowars
Don't say that three people voted in the Federal Reserve
That looks bad
Just because I also believe it's true doesn't mean you want to say it in front of the normies
It's very strange
So is life clip we have it's Alex F
Looking for closing
Closing comments in the two minutes we got left her
For the opportunity
Be on the radio again want to reiterate we live in the most
Exciting
Kind of my life
United
It's going to change
Environment
Change it
And I think
Every citizen of the United
To an unbelievable
Prosperity in this country
If we turn around and understand what's going on and we fight for our Liberty
It didn't
I like the idea that he's saying that he's living in the most
Exciting time of his life like he lived
Through the
Civil Rights era
Vietnam
It wasn't that good
Holyshit
The stuff that he lived through
I wasn't paying attention I guess it would be really exciting on a subjective level for your brother to run for president again
Yeah
But
I don't know
I don't know I don't know if I would consider the 2012 election
To be the most
Exciting time of the last 70 plus years
But we've had in a long time
But I do remember being very big
No no
Especially after the hole
47% thing where is
Romney
Is Wayne still alive
I have no idea
Well it cuz I was going to say
If he's on the Grand Prix
Man 2020
The end of the world has already been declared by another guest on Infowars
Over for Humanity
I'm always at the ready for my lunch
That's the most
Exciting times really
Yeah I don't know what Wayne Paul's up to is too easy a name to like a tube, Nate
Angie's to low profile to really be relevant
Also I don't care
I agree with you
It's a it's a really really
Sing to me and I think that
There's there is an interesting
Element in that you have the anti-establishment
Candidate
In 2012 in the person
Ron Paul
Coming into Iowa caucuses
Which has a slight
Mirror to the present day
With the Democratic primary
I think there's slight parallels but far more differences to make them analogous should I think that there is that that's really in
Interesting and then further
I think
I'm
Overwhelmed
By how similar this
East Alex
Speaking of Ron Paul to a bespoke
About Donald Trump particularly in the lead-up
That I was not expect
Define
And it makes me
Kind of want to dig more
That right Road the Ron Paul run
The more I think about that that's the thing that makes the most sense
Because I didn't consider but you're right
The with the libertarian
Nonsense people there's such a narrow view of what even a candidate they
Could support
Right you know so if you're trying to sell them any bud
You have to sell them the same way that you sell rampal
Lesbian you know and Trump
Can fit some of those Bales but
Why not just throw them all on there anyway
Selam to Libertarians as Ron Paul
Even if he's not
I just never really considered it for a number
Wonder
So
Ron Paul a.
Yes
And then second like Alex was already
Trying to do those characterizations with Rand Paul
Before he decided to flip
So I never really Confederate point
I never really considered how much like it just might be
Bees
Boilerplate
Way I Define
Good candidate
Yeah
It's it's
It's interesting how like
Even I
Knowing what I know about Alex
Give him
Way too much credit for like
Some kind of dab
To what he's doing
I got really I really need to probably get rid of some of
It is it is
Hard to
Because
We listen to the lead-up though
And hearing all of his b*******
You just assumed that he
Created
You know
You assume that there was some sort of creative Alamo
Do it because you would have to create drunk
With you with drama but then you're like why would I assume that the least
Creative man
Who does no research and does
Acknowledge
Creative
Yeah it's it seems like the most likely thing is
I've done this I did this with Ron couple times
Dial all my ramps
It's all muscle memory
It seems like it it's possible I don't know it in order to really be more certain of that it needs to go back and listen to a lot of two
House made in 2012
Which I may do maybe something for the future but for now it's
Take this little glimpse
Do Alex's
Iowa caucus date
In order to have something to talk about
Our new research are our new research project is just going through every election to find out whether or not Alex
Support
The candidate
Describes it will not be there but you know
It doesn't there's a little mini episode cuz Alex is
Add some sort of mysterious vacation where he's gone for a couple days I've no idea what he's doing
Aubrey came out of nowhere
But if he's out of Studio on Wednesday and Thursday then
I don't know what the fuc
So we will see what happens
Until you see we see you again
I will website
Underscore fight not go to bed
Jordan iTunes leave a review download
We love it
Amnio
I'm Leo and dzx Clark
I'm one of the three people who voted in the Federal Reserve in 1913
Alexandra Thurston color