I have great respect but knowledge by knowledge
Dot-com
Technology Beverages and a little bit about Alex
Indeed we are.
I've never asked you this and I am very
Have you
Everwatch
Foreign
Yeah
What is
Oh that's a second question
I would never
I've seen a ton of foreign language
Yeah
I'm probably probably is for sure
That's where
Just like when's the last one because I know you're not a big movie
Just wondering in an adult
I don't know a place called ragtag that was like the sort of indie film house
In town there was a smaller Run movies would go right
Films
Does Dallas
After-hours ragtag
They would run a lot of movies and end up seeing
It really tough for me to bring any
T22 mindray
A ton of them
Right okay that my
I was figuring if you worked at a small-town movie theater it's not like they're playing ball they've cartoon Tiger Hidden Dragon
For sure that's cool I'll believe
Play at the theater I worked
But it was
Gigante
Check when I was of just the Right Aid
I don't remember how old I was when it came out but
I was maybe emotionally 16 I remember
Without repentance
Yeah so I don't know if that movie Allah
Along with the United started French
Mission high school and so I have felt like a pretty
Particular kinship with limahl francophone
Yeah that's the one that's
6 up
I don't have a better answer
Okay
Fellini
Alright okay you big Birdman
Or A Series of Unfortunate Events or whatever live long
My mom loved that movie
Love the books
I don't know whatever anyway you guys broadcast write a lot about foreign language movies
Though not specific
And I know a lot about Alex the first time I know more about
Today we are not coming at the folks with a
Half surprised Friday episode for them because
You know I feel a commitment to put out two episodes a week
And I don't feel like our Wednesday episode was
A full
It was over an hour long
Episode we must right that wrong we got it on Friday
So
The problem was that in the present-day Alex's been out of Studio
And I don't know why
What will learn on this episode
I didn't know why and you look it is all this big stuff is happening in the world like Trump is like voted for the
Little India
Iowa caucus
Where is
Alex
I just hosting in 280
It's an absurd
Nightmare
Answer finally on Thursday
February 6th
Alex comes back
Actor Studio
You know I mean
I hate to call it a breath of fresh air because it still sucks
Compare Lisa's not Coronavirus
Woohoo
Okay
There is
Of course they're going to
Play some Coronavirus
We'll do a little bit of that
On a certain level I apologized
The audience about like you know
Betty
Keeps coming up but
I do feel like we're in the middle
Of Alex doing
A large-scale
Like a conspiracy
Pageant surrounding the coronavirus narratives and all of that
Tracking it in real time I think there is a utility to it even if it does
At some points feel a little bit like
This again
Trust me whatever is being on the podcast or show
Is 110
The whole thing
It's like a it's like a cross dog show
I think it's disgusting and I don't like it but you know you got to keep an eye on it just to see what's going on
Fair enough
So we're going
Recovering February 6th
Is it
And a little bit of February 5th
Cuz Alex today intro to that episode
It's a tiny bit and then February 6th
What's a thank you
Sophie
Thank you so much you are now apology walk director Kevin Smith
I don't think
Thank you very much Adam star Adam Scott
Story Adam Driver
Text Anastasia thank you so much
Very much as Deja obviously the star of Anastasia Mustang
Next Austin thank you
Macho
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much occupied Austin
Angela
Thank you very much
I got you yeah you prefer white actors that's next Korean
Thank you very much Kareem is it Korean
Corinth
I got nothing for that Alexa thank you to a couple people
The first Amani thank you so much
You are now at
Remember this name
Oingo Boingo whoopsie knickers
Technocrat
Heroin
So good
Is freakishly large
Thank you so much Amani and thank you so much
Boingo Boingo
Knickers
Thank you. I see that name I imagine it's a reference to something
Stop thinking of it just being like someone who's
And they accidentally poo in there
Yeah that lives that sounds right
What sounds right
The image that comes to my mind
Indie band
Starting in Barberton
Sheriff
Do Jordan like I said
Not today on February 5th
And that it's just a little piece that Alex's recording and then
Going to take over the shower
And I hope the rest of it
So this is the beginning
There's a lot going on even on the 5th
There's a lot that happened Alex should be like
Leading the show with
But of course
Look at this Newsweek article
Top story
On
Google
Has decided
The Run
All the huge news
The State of the Union
Control
Coronavirus
Not happening
Infowars YouTube videos uploaded by proxy
I was abused
Totally banned everywhere
Such an interesting tactic that he's deploying of this like
They are making it the number one story which is just sort of a wave covering that he wants to make
Should not surprise me
To know that with all his
Is it will look at all this big news around
I am going to talk about me
Knights that makes perfect
Because I have to cuz they've made it the number one story such a weird
Deflect like just the application
Responsibility
He's published millions of stories
Interesting Lee in this
Lacerta complaining about everybody
Writing all these major stories about him that are inaccurate
I think he
References Wolfgang how big's arrest
For the good idea I've heard him
Not Direct
Haha he doesn't talk about it it doesn't get into it
This is the only sort of oblique reference that I've heard to it so far
You'll see these headlines every few days
Alex Jones employees
Arrested for stalking family
Talk about it
Obviously about Wolfgang
Sure those are
Descriptions to make
But yeah
It's just so
Yeah such a week
Thing to do tonight even cover the story
Bring it up if your
Committed to not talking about it
Because he has to create a strawman of it cuz
Is the big enough story that people might Heroes
Strawman of they're saying that he's an employee
That way you could sort of
Argue against the story without dealing with the merits of intellect
I did Elevate this guy and
He did send out a Sandy Hook
Parents social security number
That's a bunch of people
So like
I don't know it's just it's just
Yeah it's a lack of personal responsibility
So we have one more clip I believe yet
A skier from February 5th
And it's
Alex talking about an interview that Owens going to do later
Which I want to talk about
But I also don't want to talk about the interview because
Doing
Coming up
In
2nd hour today
Francis Boyle
Will be joining Owen Shroyer live
So that's interesting okay
Owens interview missguided
So like I said I've no real interest in the interview itself
Which is a shame because the way Alex is promoting this interview and setting it up it sounds like a really serious legitimate
The message that the Coronavirus
Is a bio-weapon in the World Health Organization knows about Anna covering it out
So this guest has a man named Francis Boyle and on paper
If you just read his bio you would get the impression that he is someone whose opinion you really need to take Serious
He is a professor of international law at the University of Illinois
And has a resume full of things like being on the board of Amnesty International
And various intersections with the US government
For instance he did draft legislation that would become the biological weapons anti-terrorism Act of 1989
We just signed into law by George
H.w. bush
Do he did work on his draft it was really just the US version of the pre-existing you and biological weapons
Convention of nineteen
35 so it's not like he created rules about biological weapons out of thin air defined
Did replace
Coming
The guy would probably be insulting
Cuz I'm sure there were some
Things to flush out College of course
At the same time yes there was a previous
System framework I just needed to be put onto a u.s. level at the international
I can find no evidence that anything to do with the drafting of the UN convention
And that also seems unlikely thing as boil would have been 22 when it was drafted
Any would have still been in
College
Precocious that's like that's like
Look whatever
Tentacles in College Hill
You'd already assassinated somebody
I just killed Aldo Moro
Still in grade schools has been killing people across the world
Call Church
Despite his legal interaction with the subject of biological weapons people like Alex in these days
These folks they have a little bit of an Impulse to ascribe some kind of experience to him in the field of the science of biological age
Which would be a
Someone that's important
To consider when you have someone with what appears to be a legitimate
List of credentials making outrageous arguments on Alex's show
Is there hiss
And Francis Boyle has a bit of a hist
What you might call a
A pattern
Calling literally everything a bioweapon
In 2014 Francis Boyle made the rounds alleging that the
The Ebola outbreak in Zaire
Liberia Sierra Leone and guinea came from a US bioweapons released
Either due to testing containment
And I assumed he was.
Incorrect snow
And all the articles I can find about this I don't see him providing
Any evidence of this outside of vagin simulations and his own son
Suggestion
Interesting Lee what you
Camp fine though is how his theories were used by the North Korean State media Outlet
Like Pyongyang daily
2tact
The United States
Which is a really fun byproduct of rhetoric and work it
He puts out you put out anti us propaganda by yourself and all of a sudden other countries are doing
Authoritarian countries around the world
It just wasn't also his only dip into the
The pool
In January 2016 Francis Boyle appeared on Infowars
The tell Alex that the zika virus
Iris was a u.s. created by
Got that right
I watched a bit of that interview my favorite part is
Is the first word
Out of boils mouth
Quote I have no inside information
All right I heard that and that I stop listening
Come on
Daddy's push similar theories about the swine flu and probably every other public health issue you can
Can think of
This is the kind of role that Francis Boyle plays on Infowars
Whenever there's a health-related story he's the seemingly credible voice
Alex can call to say that the outbreak was a
Planned by weapon design
Depopulate the world
When the outbreak is handled in the Publix
Attention moves on
He disappears from the show so he doesn't have to explain why this
Attempted depopulation doesn't what I didn't work
Mary pops up whenever the next one come
If he still teach
I find I have a hard time getting
To the bottom of that entirely sure
When someone is 10 years
Really talk
Yeah that's true really tough situation
What
Oh no he doesn't have tender tender
He was fired and gotten rid of but he was there for a long time right
I think your good name wrong
How do you look how is the yogurt
How do you guys do your guy I'm talking about dr. Yamamoto
Yes but how
He had to go for a walk
Took the foundation
His theory seems to be that the US conducting research about things like in a bowl of Acts
Maxine or zika vaccine
That's actually cover for the US conducting research
To the how to use these things of the weather
Honestly that kind of thinking is just impossible to contend with
Because it frame something
Entirely reasonable
Namely
Researching things that are medically very
Proof of international crime
What would someone with this position prefer
Would it be better to not research an Ebola vaccine
It seems to me that that would be painted as a nefarious
Conspiracy of negligence
It's leaving the population is sitting ducks
In the off chance that I have outbreak did happen
At this position and it's a little bit exploded above the
Reality that
I mean the government has done
Terrible I'll prove it
Maybe if they hadn't done it it would be harder for it to portray them as doing
I will I will
Like
There is a level of
Reasonable distrust
Of the government
With control over viruses the operative word has to be reasonable or they said
Main remain healthy
When you're going on Infowars health is no longer a concern
Even if you're a ranger yeah I mean if you are if you are somebody
Who's going on
Infowars
You have reasonable is gone
It was like if you were this guy in like let's say that you are really into
City bio-weapon related issues
The first 50
Tea minutes of your interview should be like alright Alex
We need to talk about all of these bad position
8 Hour going to be on your platform my bus
Definition of terms Alex
I'm kicked off already okay 50 weight phone issues
Bottom line here is that although Boyle has some legitimate
It's sounding aspects to his resume from the 90
These is more recent career has been marked by some pretty incredible claim
Generally made on Outlets like Infowars
I can find literally no reason
Take what he saying seriously
Where I'm sitting he's based
Squee just the member of the Infowars cast
It gives the appearance
Credibility to outbreak fears that Alex is using to sell his s*** when Mike Adams
Kind of ruined his effect
Fitness by being overeager
It's over
Over for Humanity
There will only be
Lone Survivor
It's tough to go from there and retain your credibility do not just you not playback living just keep moving like
That's why I mean it's tough
Do you know shot that shot
Where do you where is there left to go
I wonder
So here's my problem with him
Boilermaker
I don't know
I don't I don't entirely know what his probably take me too long
Get to the bottom of a Bayside character
Utility as it relates to
Infowars absolutely off
Like it might just be a situation where he has
Lost his objectivity
See that's it that's my thing if you're going to be this guy you might as well be
The Griffin at this
Same time if you're this guy and you're not getting paid for it you're you're crazy sometimes that stuff's pretty tough though
Grist going is a full-time job
And if you're
Large
So we get to February 6th
The mouth
And I was thinking like guys probably all just going to be more Corona to coronavirus talk is going to be no
No good but Jordan
Remember
How Alex said on recent episode
He was going to get a homeless person in studio
He doesn't do that on their show
I just want to remind people that Alex said he was going to do that
Wheatley drop
Dear God dammit
You have spent so many years building up my truck
It's on porch
That like
It's so easy to forget though
Yeah and I don't do a good enough job of remind
Kicker going of like
Days since Alex announced you talked to do surgery
Give me the talk about the microchipping narrative
Yeah it's so hard to remember anything remember when we bombed in assassinated Iran we're all like it's going to be World War 3
3 an hour just whatever that
That was 2 weeks ago
Yeah I guess so
It's quick
Yeah so Alex is back in studio on the six
Man
Welcome back
We are live ladies and gentlemen
Thursday February 6th 2020 transmission any minute president Leon States
Walk through those doors
He is going to address the people of the United States people of world about the attempted
Take down for the 3rd
Current time
President-trump
Fighting
Harder now because they're pop
Globalist
Evangelist
That
Go to do this because it further divides and hurts the nation and it's very athletic
Sure
Absolutely
Public presidency
Last 30 years
They don't know what to do now they've got not just a present that spray
President that understands the New World Order
Last minutes
American Century setting
The New American Century
Has begun
So
Boilerplate pretty standard stuff but most part Alex coming into Studio kind of uninspired
A little bit
I wanted to
There's some phrasing in there that I think of
Really into
This thing I want to talk about it
A little bit
It's really weird that I
Alex is using the term New American Century
Primarily because that's what the last three letters in the
Pinac document Stan
Amps for
The term New American Century in the world of Infowars is a one-to-one identifier
With the dick
Cheney project for a New American Century documents
Rebuilding America's defenses
Main title was switch Alex
Constantly using
Incorrectly to assert
Cheney wanted to use race-specific bioweapons and use the diprove a Dick Cheney Paul wolfowitz did 9/11
This is weird
And probably means nothing
But I think it's worthwhile discuss this for a moment
Because there's a
Important
Sing buried within this the people might not immediately
Alex is obviously not signaling that he's been a neocon all along that he loves Dick Cheney now
He's just a fan of A Century Of America
Domination of the world
Preferably a new one
Something that you would describe as a new American Century
This is a very sensible way to express this idea and I understand why you would phrase it
That way
This is the same thing as George h.w. Bush using the words New World Order in a speech
Abdul that point there had been a world order
Where the United States and the Soviet Union have been soap
Preoccupied with each other
But they failed in their opportunity to be leaders in a global order
With the season of hostility between the two superpowers and
The end of the Cold War there was a possibility for the world world order it was different from the old one
A new world order if you will
People like Alex insist that Bush saying the words New World Order is proof that he was signaling to an evil cabal bent on world domination
Nation in the world
Without understanding how these words
Actually accurately describe
The ideal Bush was discussing
Alex is currently doing the exact same thing
Using an expression that means something very specific in one context
The context of his show
But also accurately describes
Nothing he's talking
Because I'm not a dumb dumb I understand that
And I don't feel
Compelled to yell about Alex's secretly work
Paul wolfowitz
Dick Cheney
Because he says he wants a new American Century
Anyway I bring all this up because it's
Teachable
But how sad
The thinking patterns are that underlies so many of the foundation
Alex's conspiracy
Theory
He knows that it does
Doesn't mean anything for Bush to refuse the words New World Order
Because he does the exact same thing
Just all bulshit
I think this is a very serious
Situation that requires
You musty oh no
That's a bit
His comeback after that
Exactly
I was very startled to see that
You think that there is there's something important
Pointing out little things like
What is being done
Is this
The same behavior
Alex if you confronted him about it and was like hey you said New American Century
Code for the
Pinac document
You know that's not what I intended as I know that I just it's just that I was talking about
America
He would have bought himself that sort of leeway and excuse that he would never afford anybody else.
It is just so it is
It's a
Whatever
Advantageous
You just go ahead and use that the rules are for you not
So
Couches out of Studio like I said we get
Reason for why
Studio
Bandits lackluster
Getting my now is so intense that
Have had a vacation in over a year Mikey Highlander my wife said dammit we're going to have one
And someone had took one but I
I was working the whole time
I got on a plane early and came back
Because Wild Horses couldn't drag me away
He just wanted to vacation
That's not fair
You later that I totally am of the mind that like if you want to Vacation you can
Conduit
If you're out Jones and you're talking about how like yep you have like Adam coming on saying it's over for Humanity
The death battle with the global is right the quickening
Is upon us Shore and you not like I understand
It was a little bit up in the air about Wendy and
Impeachment vote was going to actually happen maybe we would have witnesses baby now
Obvious that the answer was no
But there was a possibility you didn't know the exact date in advance show
Iowa caucus
State-of-the-union window side
Pre-plan
Around like
First of all
We have this
Pageant going on about the coronavirus really big event
Are happening
Look how do you support labor rights and you should be allowed to there isn't labor rights that all over
14 days paid vacation per year he's he owns the company
Labor rights become murky when the employer is the owner
Sure go ahead and take a vacation I just think it's
It said something about you when you are this guy who presents yourself one way and then gigantic news events are happy
Inside and outside of the world
Think about nurses
Like fuk it
I'm going on
Since that's also
I think
A very smart move
Just because
It goes bad
Back to the discussion earlier
Nobody's going to remember into we
Like it's just how fast shipping
And this way he doesn't have to say something incredibly stupid
Yes no one remembers that Alex wasn't there the day that the Pope
No one remembers
Exactly Matt Leo zagami and now they've got a bunch of ideas
Regardless of when you say that the world is ending and that you need to fight every single moment
You still got to take a vacation
Yeah sure the world is ending of course
Maybe maybe I should
Should take a cue from
Vacation
Alex gets into talking about some new other Coronavirus
Conspiracy UK and
I think that there is a
Type of thinking that's demonstrated in this clip
It's so bad
Coronavirus situation in Mali
Stop biological weapons expert
And a top scientist scanning the virus and saying it's man-made
Don't get ahead of this if you notice
8000 confirm I walked in here few minutes ago with 24000
The internal Chinese numbers that leaked
Publish in China by the people daily
4000 dead
Yesterday
The number of dead is a number of
Think about that
So Alex is suggesting
That the number of people infected
Is actually the Dead
Right
That's just based on what he's
Is feeling well yeah I mean it feels like that makes more sense
For him to believe but he's saying also that this is
Is based on
Official Chinese government numbers that leaked in the
The people's daily
I can't find the source
I can't find the source that Alex is talking about
From the people's daily
Because
Not
But I did find an article on Infowars about this it was written by Paul Joseph
According to his story Paul Source was website called Taiwan news
Switch is actually a actual news out
Propensity
Tweets as sources
Might lead one to be
Be suspicious but it's an actual Outlet right I'll deal with Taiwan news
This article is covering how tencent
Dance website
Their website called
Epidemic situation tracker
He did briefly show numbers of fatalities and infect
And that are way higher than the official numbers that are being reported
The infection
Count was 10 times higher and the death toll was 20 4508
As opposed to the official figure of around 300
These numbers were up briefly then we're chained
Change to reflect
The official statistic
This article does not prove that the numbers that
Tencent had posted briefly our Act
It's just suggestive
With lines like
Some are speculating that a codon problem could be causing the real quote in
Internal data to accidentally appear
Others believe that someone behind the
I'm seeing just trying to leak the real number
I don't know what the situation with this is
What it seems entirely plausible that some kind of a glitch go to been responsible for the error
The theory that someone is trying to leak real numbers is baseless
And there's nothing
Supporting that terms of proof
It's just something that is suggested like well maybe that's what this is
The speculation that a codon problem
What's causing real numbers real numbers to show up
Even boring
Sense if your epidemic tracker is built
To be a propaganda front
The trick people that the outbreak isn't as bad as you say
It seems like you wouldn't
Connect that to the
Real numbers at all why would that be something
If you're yeah
Nobody's nobody at a Chinese Outlet
For a second
Is going to
Leak that
Without knowing
Itsy I'm about to be
Seems unlikely
Basically
Quite frankly
It seems like an error like that idea that the code is
Pulling in the real quote about real numbers
That seems like an error that could
Happen in the setup that they're presenting is what this website is
I have no idea
Why they keep to Google spreadsheets
Spider-Man accidentally clicked over that
Alex is making
Tons of money right now amping up any indication that the Coronavirus
This is bad as it possibly can be and that everyone is lying
You accept whatever piece of information helps
Push that narrative regardless
Substantiated it is
Which I think is bad
Also we see here again another
Instant of him Miss citing his sources
Because he either doesn't know anything about the story he's covering
Or he wants to make it more difficult for his listeners to find the underlying information
But he's using to push his narrative
The people's daily it's not the people's daily it's Taiwan news
Is the
Pretty basic stuff that he is
F****** up either
Because of incompetence
Or trying to cover the tree
I'm not entirely sure what it is
Probably about
So
Add turns out
He was infected with Coronavirus
I'ma say something else
Fever
Knock on wood
8/4 years
Get on the airplanes today all the rest of it knocking on wood telling you that
Got a fever
Flying back
Got something
Gone now
I feel great
Can our body else I know has pretty much been sick with whatever this respiratory stuff is
Probably coronavirus about coronavirus update
Down some you gargle
Beltmann
Chanel
At that point he does take a little pull off a bottle of gargle
Turtle is a word
You know
You out like a mouthwash
Yeah he's just yay
Like it's that dude at the Hershey syrup rather a picture that went around
Drinking Pepto-Bismol straight from the thing every 10 minutes
Just like weird it's it's a bad
It's like Shania
Not take his own products on the show goes well
Vermillion nanosilver
Michael Sheehan recognizes safe for you to ingest
And
If you got none
Big Mouth M membrane in the throat
Go down the stomach and thighs
Thanks
Incredible things
So we're launching off here into a
Pitch
Alex's discuss
I'm getting a fever that is product
Killing a fever
Even though he knows specifically a person who has already cured
The Coronavirus
Why isn't Alex going to him
Galaxy Vanos that's bulshit cuz he's not having
Around
Steve you can't be doing that
You dumbass sometimes people like
Alternative medicine
Sometimes people like
Granny's
Skewers
Townhome fewer ya-ya-ya rabbits
Put your bedroom door in the morning you wake up and you're healed that way everything
Every time I've ever had a few deceptive frog in high school
Do black people like a lot of different things
It turns out Alex has a little bit of a down-home
Remedy for how he cured himself of his fever
So I got home last night
My wife said you're hot
Thermometer mouth
At about 100
Temperature
Steinbeck 157
Super Bowl
Got my coil silver silver bullet
Some of that
Took a couple Advil climbed into bed and slept from 7
Until
7 a.m. this morning and the fever was gone
Put on double shirt
Two pairs of sweatpants
That my ass up
Laika
And got up this morning and
Yes
Something about
When you
The Romans noticed
Sayings about it
What are we doing here
Things that would happen to either have another what are we doing
Clockwork everybody knows a long time to get sick
It's like 12 but I just
Commercial about how are you superstitious about getting sick
My God you can't
Save for 2 years I haven't been sick in 2 years and then be like
Ohshit see what happens when you say you haven't been sick in a long time
Also there's a lot of silver in that story
How you might have broken
My fever
The Advil in 12 hours
Sleep dad cook himself like a turkey
Maybe they're a lot of
A lot of things that could have helped one of my strategies in terms of fevers that I have had some
Success with over the years as I take really hot baths
Like You Raised
The temperature even I don't even know if that works
Something that I've always
It seems like
Exactly what I was
What is mirroring
But I could just say that I took silver
Over beforehand to and
Then save the silver help really bad with hell
I just
I'm just like okay well eventually this will go away and then go to work
You like my dad
Just wait it out it'll go away my body is healed itself
Before I'll die
Hi this is how life Works sure
You're not get some silver you're not like Alex
You get on an airplane how I finally got it for
Ray's going to pull that on Saturday
As soon as I got out of the airport.
We have a lot of that but
Jailbreak
Last week
Homeland Security
You cheating cheating bastard
Forest
The only thing found at a star's family which is the Coronavirus
From them private label
Original
Leonardo's Red Hill
Supermoon 2Cellos depending on gas
And by the military operations
On their hands and face
Something
Abrasions like a swamp
Directions Bass Lake
They said
The word they used to watch all those documents today
It was
The point is is that
It's chilling out
Yeah it doesn't
Are we past illegal yet
Man I think we're getting there cuz there's a notable increase in recent nanosilver and
Nano silver
As a way to protect yourself from the Coronavirus
This might be okay in the case of
The super silver wound gel
Santa's we discussed on recent episode that product
Has been tested by the FDA
And it's technically a drug not a supplement
Lately Alex has been using claims about the
The super silver wound gel and applying those same claims could be made about
The super blue toothpaste
Immune gargle which book
Contain nanosilver
His reasoning seems to be that if the FDA has approved the marketing of the wound gel
And it has nanosilver in
It must be cool tomorrow
Any product containing that nanosilver in a similar fashion
Tracks
This is very much not allowed by the law
There are Myriad of reasons why this is not acceptable as a business practice
This but probably the easiest to explain is that these products are not even
I'm close to the same
The one the FDA has approved as a topical ointment
The other ones are weird things
Things to be taken in
Currently which makes them
Wheatley in Carver
What really easy way to look at this
Is it the wound gel has 24 parts-per-million nanosilver
Where's the court
Infowars store website
Immune gargle has 15
In parts per million
It makes a big difference
When considering the products and what they may
My dude
Paperwhite Alex constantly tells his audience
It's not to eat the wounds out
Because it would probably kill
You would think that the fact that one product is potentially
Toxic and the other one is
Is not really Devon
I'm straight how
You can't make a dental claims about them
Especially when we're talking
Sing about 9
Parts per million separating
It's a big difference
You probably
Fatal that would make you feel good you might get a fever might have to take some other silver
According to the dietary supplement health and Education Act of 1994
Paragraph six
Discover statements made about nutritionals
Support
Claims can be made about supplements to the extent
But Studies have shown
The claims to be
True like you can say that melatonin helps
Set sleep patterns and stuff like that
The paragraph and quote
A statement under the
Sub paragraph may not claim to diagnose mitigate tree
Cure or prevent
Specific disease or class of diseases
If the manufacturer of a dietary supplement propose
To make a statement
Described in the first time
Paragraph
Any idea in the labeling
Of a dietary
The manufacturer shall notify the secretary of the FDA
No later than 30 days after the first marketing
Of the dietary supplement with such a statement
That's such a statement
Is being made
This is to say that even if you provide a disclaimer
That the product is not meant to diagnose treat cure prevent any condition
If you make a claim to that effect
Your required
Inform the FDA within 30
The FDA is not interested in health claims unless they
Call to ask
A substance
And it does
Disease or health-related
Condition you need to have both of these things
Before you risk getting in trouble
Princeton
If you want to say that fruit is good for your health
The FDA considers that healthy
The guidance
Which they don't regulate
Health claims on the other hand they do
And those occur when there is a
And a condition
Alex is very clearly
His immune gargle and toothpaste to being helpful and
The prevention of the Coronavirus
Which constitutes
A health claim
I'm not certain how concrete you have to be with your claim
For the FDA would
Take action because
You being so vague and suggest
Did with his picture
Is there is there well maybe they like
Yeah you couldn't make
Take the case of court
He's making unfounded health
For the purposes of
Podcast
I'm comfortable saying
That is exactly what he's doing
And the basis that he's using
Is the FDA approval of the wound gel which is erroneous
Replying to the other nanosilver products
It's just disgusting Behavior
And anyone who wasn't trying to profit off of Public Health
Is literally the
The fingerprint of a Shameless opportunist
I think he
Thinks that by
Claiming it
The Pentagon and not like
That's his that's where he's going to be like oh see I'm not claiming that a doctor better than
I'm just saying that the
The Pentagon
Which hey the Pentagon does all kinds of weird health check
The Pentagon thinks that LSD can control
Mine it doesn't matter what the Pentagon thinks I'm just saying if it comes down to it that's not
Week
Think that's what he's
England for these
Narratives these ways of pitching these products are emerging at at
The time when there is
A public health issue that Alex
He's really building in and making a major Focus
Using all these memes and dumb unsubstantiated things
To build
Panic surrounding the Coronavirus
And then being like
Oh hey by the way this nanosilver that I sell
There's secret studies that have been done yet
It's just f****** a response
An awful and we know it's not going to stop because
Apparently it's working
Very well
This is the first time in a long time he's been happy about
No totally
I think we're going to hear this go
Going for a long time it's not only the
Open sales
It's also the food
Of course
In the conference room in Africa
And he gave us a call this morning
And he said well we are
But now it's 3:50.
And everybody else is totally sold out anybody else telling you the reference is lying to you or it's crap they got high quality
Twenty-four hours a day
It may go up to two or three weeks by next weekend
They may be sold out they have the flu right now to take your order again. To you
Infowarsstore.com
You better get it now
Terry I think we're going to have to
To put a clock on
What you better get ago
Too fast alright we're going to put
Hour on the put an hour on the clock right now okay I got this
I don't even know if it's going to last the full hour but we got we got to put the hour I got this 100
From the food people and it's going to be longer now you know why
Inflated demand that Alex is creating with these
Didn't like his entire hour-long infomercial
In all of the content
Terrify people
About to
Virus situation in order to drive
You've got
The my Patriot Supply and by the way
There's a people who Supply a ton of other be
People who sell survival food
Diversified in terms of I believe Ben Shapiro food people are them too
Shapiro has food survival food
The f*** is wrong alot of these people do okay
Jim Bakker
Use auguston Farms
Is there something different
Okay good friends apparently they don't have any food
What was no help so he's going to be like we would love to tell you survive
Apple food
I almost guarantee the baker's page is no one else has food
Not just that but God wants you to buy his behavior
Manipulative sales
This is all it does is funnel people to buy the survival
Now there's an
Increased artificially inflated demand
Just pushing back
The delivery times that they compromise
And that appears to be a run on food maybe they don't have enough to
Fulfill
It it all it does is
Exacerbate Bank
Yeah
It is
It's like that's one of those things where it's like
They are not
Bummed
You know like
My Patriot Supply is in like
Alex we need to we need to stick by FDA rules that you can't
Say these things
They're like
You keep talking
My Patriot Supply
Nothing to do with the silver
Okay then
I don't know
I don't know if Alex could get them in trouble
I think that they're not responsible for the way Alex
Sell stuff
I'm not sure that's an interesting question
My Patriot Supply
East is
I guess
Making false claims about a disease is that acts
Anyway
What do you mean like
Like saying that the Coronavirus
This is going to kill you and your family tomorrow I don't think the coronavirus could take you to court
Irene has a as it like I
Criminal
Situation there can you know inciting a panic or anything like that I don't know in what way
It would be
So we'll get back to there's more obviously there's more of virus stuff
Coming up
Weirdly we get a
Reprieve from
Because Trump is giving
Don't be giving a speech is
Victory speech
Yeah by beating this impeachment trial and so Alex comes in and starts talking over
For the Applause
Has given Trump
The Big Dipper
Thank you
You better start defending his supporters of hundred dollars
So they're going to make a move physically on tropical house the impeachment
Is Trump has got on Facebook
We're all going to die
So deposit
Long
Gives Alex a lot of
Opportunity to talk over
I love you so much
There's a lot of like
If it's weird that that's a quote that he uses cuz I want to I know you know that
But there's not a lot of subtlety
Star Wars I don't understand
There's no like moral ambiguity about it at all there
Evil the Rebellion is good
Legitimately it's one of the most clear-cut examples of
Black and white heroes and villains
Any movie that I can
Can pick up
Alex
Identify with the bad guy
These bad guys are close
The line he's quoting while waiting for Trump
To come out and give his impeachment acquittal speech
Is a line that Darth Vader says after Obi-Wan is
Been killed in the death star's heading to wipe out the Rebellion right
The words of an absolute villain
On the cusp of wiping
Now the only helper
Freedom from tyranny that's the last of the universe
This could be seen as Alex being stupid and just
Is the dork
But I have a
Strong suspicion that it's really more of a tell about what type of person Alex Jones actually is
He's a fan of the empire
What he sees Trump is hero
About to give a triumphant
It brings to mind Darth Vader on the
The cusp of solidifying universal rule
I think I think that that's why that triggers it is
How can you not like a apple
Come on
He's an authoritarian
Tater he-he's maneuvered his way by a political machination
To destroy the entire flashlight
Absolutely
He's in control of rebellion at the same time that I was creating the Clone Stormtrooper
I mean this guy knows how to play the game also
Shoot lightning from his fingertips can you do that's not to like
Super silver fingernail like
So Trump gets to talkin
And he has a little bit of a verbal dip
My Kindle in a number of his speeches that he
He's been giving me seems to like lose
Track of words
I think part of that is probably just like he's
No teleprompter Ringgit reading stuff in
Turtle bike
Start saying the word
Getrag Stuck in the Middle
Gets bored cuz he doesn't have an attention span and
A super old
There's a lot of people who speculated about like
Neurologic
Nicole events
And stuff like that know that that's
McKay's
Bit irresponsible for us
Suggest that
I think it would be
Dumb
Forgot
But there are instances where you just clearly doesn't know what he's
Eddie starts
Yeah this is not one of those occasions I would never talk about any of that stuff at all
Because of trump in WhatsApp
Is talkin
In his speech and he gives a little bit of what I would describe as a verbal dip
And Alex
Takes the opportunity and he just needs to portray it in the way he wants his audience
Develop friendships and relationships when you're in battle and War
Much more so than Jesus have a normal
Situation
With all that we've gone through we've done I think more than any president
And administration
Almost crying but that really
And Republic
You just said situation kind of
A video there's no emotion.
I don't believe for a sec
About to cry
What would it take to make him cry of it maybe somebody removing his
Is named from a building
I would assume that would be an emotional moment that's about it
Space
The reason that I brought up those
Things of like the media covering like these
Is weird
Start of hiccups
In some of his rallies
Is because I think Alex is aware of that
And I think the key that
Kind of being
Close enough to that but yeah
But that is what's going on there
It paints Trump is like an
McMahon but he still has feelings
It's expressed on days when troops died or days when you've just defeated you
Your greatest sin
So
Did the speeches
Deandre
Ed's long
Interest in most of it because there's one thing
Love's
We first went through
Russia Russia Russia
It was all
Bulshit
We then went through the weather report
Don't delay that you are my presents
Can children are way so it just children Alex
Love's
Of course he loves
The Trump said b******* taking it even more to the lives with his
So Alex gets like really defensive about like no we're not going
Edit that out
And you know what I mean
Broadcast
The president
We can say that word
Nothing and nobody the FCC that Trump runs going to get anybody in trouble
True
It's the first time cussing
So first
Tyranny
Alex's pretending this is the first time Trump is sworn in a speech indicates that he has literally no ma'am
Memory for things that Trump is a complete fraud no
Interest
Anything you saying being true
Who can forget the time back in September 2017
When Trump was in front of a rally in Alabama talking about Colin Kaepernick
He said quote
You loved
See one of these NFL owners when somebody disrespects the flag
Get that son-of-a-b**** off the field right now out he's fired he's fired
Or what about the time on the campaign Trail
Trump discuss how he would deal with ice
Quote I would bomb the s*** out of him
Or in February 20th
16 when Trump was holding a campaign rally in Manchester New Hampshire where he calls Ted Cruz a p****
While pretending he was with repeating something someone in the audience headset
That's debatable that one's debate which is vulgarity a disease
Absolutely
After his speech at
C-pack you said that people were going to start attacking him with b*******
Like legitimately
Trump cannot stop swearing
Speeches
It's the polar opposite of notable when he said b******* in this speech the Galaxy's
It's such a common thing
Urban tons of Articles written about it
Like one headlined the profanity president
From May 2019 in the New York time
Or one headlines Donald Trump keeps person
Here's why it might help them
17 time
Or from the washing
Can post how Trump took swearing mainstream
Or from November twenty
MyTeam in the week
The cursing president
Angle on this is legitimately unhinged
God Trump's we're so goddamn much that it's the
Topic of a conversation about whether or not it's an intentional
Strategies used
He swears more than any other president
On the subject of people getting away with things
No other president ever would have gotten away with
Be consistent barrage of b*******
He doesn't his rallies in speeches Ono might want to come down at that horseshit conservative victim would talk
If Barack had said this is all bulshit when he was talking about Fox News Fox News it'll be like
Look at our powerful president look at how he's unafraid of the lives and he's willing to
Where did he call Kanye West
The jackass it was a new cycle for a week
I don't know what Alex's take all that was IP address
Probably worried about it later
Appethai probably didn't even notice
God it's so funny that William Randolph Hearst would have turned this into a reason to end a present
Then say like one b******* and it would be like
And there went
He said bulshit now he's gone
Honestly I think it indicates a certain amount of lack of
Control like it it's
Unbecoming
I know that's a conversation that maybe
Antiquated and pasta
But I don't
Enjoy it like
I don't I don't appreciate seeing president saying bulshit
Well it's a little bit like
Seeing it's a little bit like
Like seeing your parents wear for the first time
Like because you think
These are Edina when you're like 10 or 11 you think OSHA.
Together they are the authority
30 figures I know I can trust
Ask them and then they swear you like all bets are f****** off I don't know what the
The f*** is going to happen here
Yeah there's a difference
It's two between like the queen
Parents
So Alex is really insistent that this means
Like he's really pretending that he's never seen
We paused it we went to break when he
Came out at 12
It was all
Bulshit
Use cuss words on air
Really
I'm sick as hell on broadcast
Do it on The View
They do it on Good Morning America
They do it comes at night they do it during the family
Say doodle all over CNN
If we do it
MSNBC
Cut it out as well
Because the president did that
Know how serious things are
Sure like all the other times you sworn
You know they'll they'll swear on those liberal shows like whatever build miyares
Tim Allen is swearing on Last Man Standing that's that's exactly
Their sitcoms are everything to Tim Allen's now.
Definition of the globalist it, absolutely everything
Home Improvement man
Never going to get better
There's a weird trend of Alex like sort of listening to the speech and rejoicing throughout it like
Psychic
Cagoule
Like a Villain who's just won
Like I can't
Sounds like an evil person
Has failed severely the Liberty Patriot movement is taking over the Republican Party
The Republic
Quiet
Tenafly
That's
Wow
Wow man I eat I guess
We have to I guess in their perfect world we rewrite
All of the Bond films
Where the billionaires are the bad guy and it's just like
They're the heroes
I didn't have a thorny to use those gadgets he wasn't in his own sovereign
Haitian Dan how is it what are you doing going from Russia
Even if you're carrying love
Stroop
True Blood was a bad guy
I think an argument could be made
From the left
The bond was a bad guy 2
Play me every one of those movies were Back From Russia with Love
But it opens
He's
Having this lovely pic
About to go on a nice little boat ride
All sitting there you get to call and the woman's like
No put it down you don't need any just
Waxer you just hit there another like
Holyshit I'm not seen this movie in a long time
What the f***
Surprise me knowing what I know about you
Sean Connery
Not many of those movies that was not Jean Russia that appealed to
Watch
As a younger man
Maybe
Seen one or two Bond movies
I think I'm meeting Sean Connery's ever been that type of movie Azhar does
Homer
Fair enough
I find the
Type of movie that
It's like Bond
Tubi
Laborious
Exhausted
Okay
But
Primary goal on this February 6th
Show is to
Talk about Trump speech
And then go to call
That's basically all he want
What's to do
So he talked about that how we're going to get
It's called
Coronavirus
Giant developments on
It is deadly to some and it is spreading
That is engineer
Call donnisha Jackson
That's not confirmed confirmed by who are the confirmation is that self retracted study
Ivetta Alex saw the udon
It is now but it's become a part of Alex's rhetoric and a touchstone and a talking point
So it shall never be never
Never check in on any that's the confirmation that Alex has
And now in the
Canon of Infowars information
True Vine
So is the word I would use
So this episode also was very heavy on food sales like he's pushing
S*** hard
Cuz I think he recognizes that it's work
Yeah there's a chance
I've got the statement here for my favorite Supply when you're in Fort Worth
Camuy bar the money offender operation
It shipped out the very same time they're going our computer system
Decade
Now it's 10 to 14
High-dollar it 7-0
Orders are so high and everything's going so crazy
Today
10 to 14 days or so high Alex is recognizing I believe
Energy is working
Increase
In the orders that are coming in for the food based on what
Able to
Salad always able to sell it
It is ironic
How much he Israel dagg
That in some ways
China is now saving
Business nap that is a cruel cruel University 11
So when a man like a
You know he works
With my Patriot
Supply and what are you doing
The only good food
Is it weird that is that's what
B design
Great
That deliver when they say
It's about industry
Sad episode of luscious the truth
Is it breaks his heart to have to say that his
Competitors are not good breaks his heart
He what
Genuine competition Daddy
Each business
It's too tight
That otherwise they would never it's like those before the free-market Djokovic and Federer
I work for all three of them they wouldn't have read
The heights that they have reserved salute
I have bad news tennis is a bad business
Goddamnit
You like Rafa only good time to plant
Who is just
It is strange
Strange
So he wants to get the calls but he doesn't
Because he
Wants to do more
Is really use these narratives that he's built up
How to sell things
You really going hard to sales cuz of course
That's why
But it hurt that he went on vacation I wiped out on a plane to come back and sooner
Strike while the iron
1000% 101
Towing trucks
Leave him
Heather selling out of food what is Coronavirus and the 20/20 at all the craziness
Pop stock market
They are going to be very very serious
Portal Chell.
I think that is a perfect
Very distilled down example
Tudor drive people towards
The sales that he wants to
I mean there's a large chunk there he's talking about the
Can I get back to
To the silver and I think we're entering into like
Really Mia out application
Super unethical
And I do think that he is at great
Yeah I think
I would love to talk to somebody from like the FDA
I'm feel like a
It's though
That's true I have lived my life via the no snitching rule difficult to go against the grain
No yeah it feels like it would be an interface like I feel like it would also be interfering with Alex's world to an extent that I'm on
Regular I were to put in motion something that ends up getting
$1000000
I feel like that would be interfering with his world and then me covering
Him dealing with the consequences
Are you mean the apotheosis of your career
I can't bring myself to
Get to that point where is the line is
Well it's
Terrible that we don't have any lawyers who listen
Supplement regulation lawyers
But I don't know
The big bottle of immune gargle
It has been patented
Nano silver in it
Show me just saying
Go to l.a. confidential
From the commissioner of Food and Drug Administration
You've also got the head of Homeland Security in here
Confidential documents
Do we have in Super Silver
Silver whitening toothpaste
We are original products
Company
Ladies and gentlemen
When Alex
Splashed up on the screen the document that he's talking about if you look at it's just about the silver
Is just about the wound
So whatever he's trying
To use to apply to
These other products
Does not apply
It might as well be a receipt
From Bed Bath &
He has a responsibility to not act
Because these even these Secret
Whatever
But he's reporting
To be the basis
Is this
Claims
These reasons anyway she
Somebody's making
Arnot
About the gargle and not about the tooth
Directly about the dajjal
And I don't know I have a hunch that this is not
I'm I'm always amazed when people buy
Toothpaste
That are
Infused with something odd like that used to sell like radiated toothpaste it'll be like
It makes your teeth glow-in-the-dark and I'd like
No I don't want any of that
Basic toothpaste
What are you up to on a stick then
Used to do it
So Alex gets back to listening to Trump speech
It still going on
And
I think he starts
A little bit
Because it's not his
Aggressive and violent as he wants
Said to be
EXO he makes
A really big declaration
The Democrats work for foreign multinational government
Their party has to end
Republican party has to break into
European model of 10 different party
Party cuz
Buy out the other parties
Body system is the best that's not perfect
So it's worth noting that one of those Jake
Atlantic Hallmarks of authoritarians or Shoring up their powers outlawing their opposition
Compari's
This is a it's not a shocking
Think that's okay
Consistent
So when you see people suggesting that the political party that they're against needs to be destroyed or outlawed
The fuk up that they're in the beginning or middle stages of supporting
Democratic
Authoritarian form of government
Which I was absolutely is and that's why he identifies with Darth Vader in the Empire
It's a huge thing also too
Blame your enemies
Word for word for ship that you are
Word for word guilt
Maybe
Also how stupid is is playing
He sang the GOP should split in
The two-party and then that will be the new two-party system because the Democrats are all
Evil global
Butterfly
This plan is that a lie
Also thinks that a lot of Republicans namely the ones who don't worship Trump
Are evil global
Well it makes sense
Because what you do then is now that you've
Split into the two party system once more you have the hard right and then you have the middle right
And guess what
The middle right
Neocons also work for foreign governments are also corrupt it's at
We got to get rid of that party to split our Hardware
Play into the two party system
Thanks
The split would end up being Trump fetish community on one side and then on Trump lovers on the other
I'm just like you said we're exactly back where we started
Without accusing the side that he's not on of being the globalist
Racket that needs to be destroyed
There's no polite political disagreement that's really possible in Alex's world because
He believes his enemies are
Literal demon
Arizona
No matter how many parties there are how big
He created all the ones he's not in will need
Need to be destroyed
Alex wants loyal symbolic opposition
He wants his Trump dictatorship
Control like 85% of the
Then a different Republican Party
Need to be the other
10%
Completely incapable of doing anything
Providing the appearance of some kind of democracy
That's more or less what he's expressed Crazy Eights
Blake the first time we've ever seen any
Anything like this
The really unusual thing for a chakra
To do you would think a student of History like Alex Jones be aware of the kind of things that he's advancing as he's ideal
You welcome does seem like this has happened before and since he has red
So much history you know he would know about
Certainly not a book a bad with the Nazis to political party
Great well you think
I think the Nazis of the bad guy and then you realized
The Stormtroopers are based on the Nazis which means emperor
Team is based on Hitler and all the sudden you love Hitler
So
Interesting
Alex it like it's not a stray thought
This becomes a theme
For the rest of the episode
So talked about
Need to outlaw the Democratic Party
Applicants party
Party's poll numbers end
Donald Trump's poll numbers are the highest I've ever had that
Because from my family standpoint
It's been very unfair
Organization
He's calling for Trump
To Outlaw the Democratic Party
This
There has been a series of red flags
What Alex Jones wants
There could not be a larger
Easy buzzard
The reddest of flags
Alex wants a dictatorship here Alex Watson authoritarian regime
Surrounding his incompetent Weird Al
I do feel a little bit like a mundane That Tune
Edward two words into it and I hit the buzzer in like autocratic rule
Autocratic rule
This is really easy
How long your political opposition
I mean even like Trump coming to power with you lock her up in the idea of jailing your political opposition
That's the nation
Form of the weasel around with like I sincerely believe that Hillary Clinton has committed all these crime
Absolutely that's sort of like a
Hey you sound a bit
Like an authoritarian trying to shore up our
Are you can
Trying to get around
Outlawing
Your only viable political opponent party
I think I think you've gone way past
Radical state
What's the definition of radical state
From a legal basis when Trump leaves office
Switch
50/50 shot at this point
He should go to jail
Like there's no other
Whether or not
You care about party affiliation
Committed the crime
Necessary
Anita's alone
Pattern of committing the crime
And he's going to continue to commit the crimes even after
You know as long as
So it's not a political
Statement to say he needs to go in
It was like probably what
If Trump were to
To be any trouble after leaving office who would be something
To be Beyond
The scale of our Justice
The UN
Image of Justified
The Hague is going to be in real trouble
Situation
Trump starts rambling telling stories about Steve scalise playing baseball
Not what I wanted
I wanted to fire and brimstone
Speech for Trump is going to come out and say the globalist are fuc
Right I beat this impeachment right you guys are going to pay
He said bulshit man starts talking about Steve scalise playing baseball
And the first picture you sent is second base and the guy is really in bad shape
This is terrible
Round ball shot
I think too much
Well it's going toward him
Stop that
Constable
He's now laying down
What is the most incredible thing I've never seen
Not this demonized creature thus the strawman
I think Alex is partially right when he says the Trump U Van Nuys
People who need to be more
By standing next to them they are more human than Trump
Noises really bad yeah it does seem like
Like like what are you going to say Alexandria ocasio-cortez
Sure will give you that one Rashida tlaib
It will give you a good statements whenever
Previous how many civil rights leaders
Is a diabetic
Oh my God yeah
It says that humanizes people 8
Things like this are Steve scalise Who Sold himself as David Duke without the baggage
Yeah this guy
There's good people on both sides at Charlottesville through unite the right rally
Humanizing people who are
Not great Among Us hasn't wanted a commitment actually by ass crack
I should be clear I don't mean wipe
People as a whole I mean people who have
Some way
Some people who are not
Good
I will say that he probably wouldn't
Try and human eyes
He would I think he would probably leave that white person
Not a dude call you
So anyway Trump gets to talk about how he thinks that's
Elise is awesome
Steven he is fantastic
You are fantastic
You and Liz
I don't know who this is
Is wife is named Jennifer
His kids are named
I have no idea what he's talking about
Like I looked into it because there was a
Female
Secure a capitol police officer was also injured
She's not
To talk I don't know
Vicky forgot Steve scalise
His wife's name is.
That's what I
I'm suspicious
Yeah when we're talking about conspiracy theories let's go with Trump
Read
So Alex is hearing all this talk about scalise
I think he's getting
Sick of these
Nice words
Like he's really starting to
Pissed off
Seymour tax
Said some of that
So I just too much nice talk
I want
Him too
Gocube
I want him to release these sealed indictments I want to do a tack
But I will prosecute bulshit
Yeah yeah now that he's free of all of this s***
It's time for him to
Consolidate his power base
Disband the entire Democratic Party
I assume
Very least hang your Nancy Pelosi in effigy
And White House
Nap so I made for that it then that is exactly what he is he's on he's hyperfixated
Eliminating Democratic Party
I don't want him.
Hey big bring the country together
F*** no
Shouldn't be together half the country should be
Gone
And
The people who vote for democrats should be forced to vote for
Other Republican
They should be forced to vote for republicans
B words
They should have their political party outlawed
You know what we need we need a new Republican party and I know just who should lead it Pete buttegeig
Wine I mean
What's the Democratic party of course of course
Now how do we do that
The country shouldn't exist
Enemy operation
So he's just really on this tip like I don't know where it's
Coming from
Call him going on these ramps so consistently this
Hitting this point so hard
It's weird not a good sign
I really do think we're getting
We're getting
The point where he's
What is
Destroying the Democratic really passed the point where he was
Exploiting this
Autocratic
Kind of b*******
Thinking
Okay well yeah I know Trump's mobbed-up
I see now he's got all the
White aggrievement yet
This is perfect for my bass
We're going to ride this out
And then he just forgot that he was
Lying
It's possible it's hard to know what goes on within the hearts of man
William Shakespeare
Alex Goes To Break
And he comes back
Anybody heard like a voice
Owen Shroyer is now in Studio City
And being ineffectual
But it's not The Highwayman
You're not allowed
You're not allowed to even hear giant James Brown
I got it
Got to move tells me what to do or do not
He thinks the songs about the Holy Spirit
Also James Brown
Get on the scene like a sex machine also about the Holy Spirit
James Brown funky drummer
That's it because all jumpers
All drummers have the Holy
Lest you think of that
Sing along with I got soul Superbad if you think I put him in a good mood
No
It did not
Complaining about the Democratic party and how they got to go
Feeling nice about the people Democrats so long
Where you put up with this so long
In the Democrats
Like
What about
Wasn't it just a few years ago the Alex was above the political George W bush
Really should have just dispatched of the democratic party that makes sense he's Goin ideologically
For so long it's been about like a the whole left right Paradigm is all an illusion
They're all the same
But now you see me put up with this for so long
The Democrats
The saint you were secretly Republican all along cuz that's what everyone said I'm like
Where were we
Because we figured this out a long time
Time I go pee
His Paradigm is not the left
A paradigm
I mean that's where we're that's where we're at
It's the
Classes of
Person
He is
Against
The other
Yep it's cuz
Christian is so important
Mail
Cisgender
All of these
Heterosexual all of these identifiers
That's what's so important
Not the
Necessarily the Democrat or Republican
But now he's ready
Recognize that his coat on coat Patriot
Folk the Liberty
Folk have taken over the Republican Party
So now it is
Well it's not
Because there should be two or five
Sure
God he's so stupid does he not even
When you say
Get rid of my political enemies
And then let's take my political friends and split them in
Dwayne based on whether or not they worship Trump
Ball sack
And then guess what
They're the new f****** global
We just do it over and over and over again based on instead of
Oh oh evangelicos now it so you're not my type of Evangelical you're a megachurch
Guess what you're out of the Republican Party
Like it's f******
An obvious this is the mentality
Alex is
Just a part of I get it always ends up this way
Some more division
So Alex and his next start taking some
Calls and you get to caller who is
He's trying to
Give alok
It's proof that a major coins
Dean of the United States is about to happen
And the proof that he provides
I think he's been
Big prepper incoming outbreak repeat what you were saying that they have
You're watching this around the country. It's not a hoe
What
Directions back
In the Bay Area and
Doing a emergency
Job fair
Drivers
Normally you wouldn't think anything of that
Because of what's going on with the Coronavirus
Virus
You know they know what
This is what
Or maybe not
I don't know
That's not proof of anything normally you wouldn't think that's
Suspicious
And I will go.
This weekend there were multiple job fairs
Preferred CDL for specific Fields some of them are in the healthcare field subwoofer
School bus drivers
I mean is it
Nonsense
You know he jumps off from this and tries to justify why he believes that this outbreak is the real deal
As opposed to in the past
When it was all
Even though in the past you said it was like
Yeah Rio but the globalist
Doing it
I don't know it's weird
Is nonspecific
Terms that he uses around like what's real and what's fake
It's also
Indecipherable
To the point of not mattering
Real and very bad
Well it will be eventually
Normal because they're not hyping it but the real ground-level a
Phineas
Prices
Not hyping it but I'd like to see the world
What is that
Coming out showing all sorts of people at checkpoint
Piles of dead bodies in body bags
Where was this is much bigger
Like I said Alex is no precise definition of what he means by the globalist
Was typing something
That's such a nonspecific idea that you can just throw it around however you like
Even if the World Health Organization and the media are covering this outbreak you can say that they're not hyping it enough cuz they're not saying
Things like
It's over for Humanity
Only be Lone Survivor
They're not there you know they're not hyping it if they hired Flavor Flav then we're golden there then there's no
Complained about height
They're not hyping it be like my friend the health Ranger
Does he was the same time treating it like it's a very big deal
Lourdes manipulation tax
To justify the
Conclusion
But Alex is already operating
And that conclusion is that this is a civilization level threat which is actually a bioweapon deployed by the globalist
You should be very scared of it
And the only solution is buying all of the products of Alex cell
That's legitimately the entire game
So the stories that he's talking about that woman being shot at a checkpoint is based on an uncanny
Confirm video someone tweeted
I have no idea if
It's real or not and that it's not even a video of her being shot
Just someone on the ground who appears to have
Benshot
I have no idea if it's real and the last few times coronavirus season of Alex's show
I've seen things being
Posted that are very old videos
The people are recirculating
Claiming to be current
I don't know what that's
The case here and neither does Alec
He doesn't care to know because assuming it's real and current helps
Sell the fear that
Casella's Prada
Someone being told
Stay in their home if they're sick isn't really a bizarre story so I don't really know how that's being presented as some kind of
Yeah not sure what the angle is
Yeah if Alex points to a video of
Getting shot and
Current I want to f****** newspaper
For in that video otherwise I assumed it was from
12 years ago and it
It's whatever is good
I agree just saying that that the applicability
Stuff about that like crematoriums in body bags all stuff Alex's reporting
Michael Snyder's economic collapse blog
Which was I recently pushing
Can the chicken vaccine patent narrative
Along with other memebase outbreak conspiracy
All the stuff that's on this site is a site
It's based on the same sort of Evan
Alleged photos in
Possibly out of context
Quotes from people like in the
The epoch times
None of this Rises to the level of solid reporting
Best as I can tell
It's really hard to get solid information about this situation but that's not an excuse.
The traffic in here say in speculation
The main reason why you're seeing this type of reporting out of all of these right-wing blogs and website
Is because they have very low standard
It's for what they accept as proven
And they cultivated audiences that don't care if they're caught
Clear on this point also there also
Food apparel
Probably a lot of them are
A lot of them are
So I don't know Alex
Say all this stuff about like it's obviously way worse
Because I've seen all these things
Some of them are memes and some of them are absolutely
Old videos being recirculated and being repurposed as about
The Coronavirus
Some of them are stories like the chicken vaccine patent that Alex still
Thinks is real
And there are things that are in
Anecdotal
Like if you see a
Picture of
Someplace that has
Two body bags in it
You in your mind assume
It must be a lot more
Where is it could just be two people died in this Hospital
Get run on anecdotal stuff
In terms of assessing the scale or scope of them
And Alex
Does cut 215
Years from now
We would like to welcome our new director of the World Health org
Carpe donktum
Better choice
So Alex starts
Can hear about how
Tuttle-Click earlier Alex was ranting about how when Trump
Call Tim
She doesn't
I don't need recognition I don't need you to Pat me on the head I just want you to do
Globalization
Mirrors that
I'm here
What does the average person just wants recognition
Metal or at least that's what Trump thinks that's not why they really did it
Embarrassing to get those models
Three of these people because I know they're evil
Play my soul in my will and I'm fighting against that
I think that's about Rush
I think about Rush Limbaugh
I I didn't get a medal Rush got a medal all he did was get
Answer I can get cancer
I think
I'm not motivated by that
Even though farison for most people
Battles after we after we listen to the Piers Morgan
Follow up
Put the Gun Shop
Where is like
Hey how are you we had
Yeah I went there and I confronted him
I don't know
F*** off
Talking about how like you really it is all just about
Defeating the globalist
For him
Consistent about
That it was though some people have
All the presidents
Cuz I'm like you cannot trust
The people you brought in
Conversations all the time
Like what
Talk bad about John Bolton you know I've had a lot of drinks with him and play poker with a man
That's definitely Rodger Stone
Absolutely Rodger Stone
I said listen
He's against everybody stopped
Thinking that later is approved
President of all these enemies around know you did
No you did not not even a little believer hydrostone 100%
Every single word rogerstone whispered in your ear
Rat f******
Can you like a monster
A******
So they're sitting along
Not contributing too much
But
According to his ability
Sherp Alex I want some
Culture issues at Hammond
Owens got an interesting
Take on why culture
Was better
In the past your eyes
What is this nobody likes this
Course nobody likes it
What you want
About
Groening that in
Children's mind
Growing up seeing the Clint Eastwood's or not growing
Elvis
Bradley's not growing up seeing the John Wayne
They're growing up saying Nas in a
Female Cowboy outfit
He's not talk about.
What are those
3 old-time Role Models have in common they were all dead before Owen Shroyer with ever born
Rhizome identifying
Are there careers where at least some identifying characteristics
So you got
Clint Eastwood
We've got Elvis Presley Elvis Presley
John Wayne John Wayne
Well
One of them was gay
The other ones still allows music from black people and then Clint Eastwood
Talk to a chair I think we're good alright
Something something tonight
I'm not sure what it is
Alex sells the silver war
Since the last time we talked about this
I got blasted we talk on this episode
Male couple episodes Bancos mention
Weird about this
It's evolving
Only authorized to do this week and a half ago
Damn this
Texas A&M University Health System
This is
Again confidential
Security
That they're looking at this US Department of army
Operations Command
The address
And others
I found
That
The American biotech
Labs LLC
Nano silver has been founded
Bashar's
Saturday night at times 2007
The coronavirus is in the hole
SARS
The antecedent of the Cumberland progenitor
Know how that works
Stop stuff we shall bring to you
Michelle Burcham our research pal.
This is your what
Stop you're going to fight
Infowars store
I think he might be flying too close to the Sun
That was pretty blatant because
The documents
It was not them saying
The nano silver has been proven
Product
The gel had been
You can't
Supply claims just because they have the same ingredients
In it
Because the ingredients at different levels
It's formulated different
It's taking up in different parts of the body
Might not
Be according to the FDA according to trial
Clinical trials it might not be internally effective it might only be topically effective
Can't play this game
It's a game Alex is playing
Very clear
I don't know we'll see what happens
If you can
The
Nano silver
Just
Just start
Eaton silver dollars that's not 100% silver probably won't
Hell yeah you might pass
Some date knowledge fight does not stand behind these medical plans
So one of the phenomena that I see a lot is Alex
Start going down some Road and then you'll see his callers mirror
Often times it takes a couple of days
When he starts doing some
Something weird
A college be like that you know what I like
Who's case
2 seconds
It's pretty quick
Like any self-respecting
Game on
So you see callers
Calling in
Sing
I mean obviously he's using a metaphor he's not saying that something the Democrats
Step on their throats and fire into their
You should finish the job he's mirroring Alex's desire to see the elimination and
Outlawing in banishing of the Democratic Party
So
Ucihs very it's very fast Alex's pushing
Pretty hard on this episode
Hear it and get it
Now it's okay
He's also has Owen Shroyer sitting in studio and he's got to guess
I feel a little weird about that
Tell Deanna Lorraine
Awesome
Bose that monster is just a moment
So this candidate is running against Nancy Pelosi apparently as
Is pretty much guarantee that she's
He's not going to win
Infowars
This is not a good tactic
Decision on her part
What's a good way to get some attention
In specific
The community
I don't know much about
Deanna Lorraine
But I do know the people have been gunning for the female Congress members in California for quite awhile namely dance
Lowe's Yuma
Maxine Waters
What are people who is doing so is Omar Navarro who used to come on in for the bucks
Talk about how he was going to be
Beat Maxine Waters
Which you never succeeded in doing
And he's never going to
Because Omar Navarro is currently in custody facing multiple charges for stalking his ex-girlfriend
Who put out restraining order
His ex-girlfriend is Diana Lorraine
Obviously I am I a thighs with her for what she had to do endure the abuse that was subjected to her by
Navarro
None of that is her fault
Now it's just
Interesting to see her going the exact same route that Navarro did
Politically
She's running
Sweetly Doom campaign against a long time
Congressperson in California
And promoting
Herself on Infowars
Which seems weird
You can't possibly expect to win
For the best I can tell it's got to be
Some sort of
Publicity stunt
It might be a cash grab
Maybe she learned that from Omar Navarro
Talking about Navarro to The Daily Beast
Lorraine said quote
I think a lot of this power has gotten to his
He has a lot of money now from campaign
I think there's a
The entire possibility that
You recognize you run a doom campaign where you trying
Yeah you try and get a little bit of mud
Thrown on
The arrivals of big political donors on the right we're going to fund you even though you know
Didn't know you're going to lose
It's
Get a lot of money that way and the only way you get indicted for campaign finances of uses if
If you make too much money or you ask
Accidentally win
Like I that dumb assholes Vaped
Vapor
I don't know it's really complicated for me because I obviously don't think
That any of the negative
Aspects
Association with Omar Navarro are her fault
Point the finger at her for that
Jesus said assholes
I just think it's fascinating that
Both sides that equation are running against
California
Democratic Congress people
And they both choose to promote themselves
You get a grip you find the Griff
And you keep it going
That's the simple that's
Simple tactic
It's very strong
I don't really know how to handle it
Honestly
I've start running against
Candidates
Warren Nancy Pelosi
So Alex has Lorraine on and they talk
A bit about how she's going to be
Nancy Pelosi
She's not
Not a chance
Nope
I'm not saying it's someone
Couldn't but it's not a Republican
No it's not her
I8
Ic0
So they talked about that a little bit
It's blustery.
But they end up taking
Calls and just caller calls in and she is saying that she had a health situation
In the past
But you recovered from
But now she
She thinks that it might have been the Wuhan Coronavirus
And that a lot of people
Baby
Just maybe
Have been getting that if I coronavirus for a long time
And recovering a week
Didn't know it was here
It's a long-term game
And this
Maybe the virus
Been here already
Operation
Quarantine
It's a bunch of weird
My family Securus ago in 2 weeks
Tell me I'm pretty
Well and got really sick
I don't know about the
Precise details of Alex's family members
Or anything like that
I would just say that
There's
Some examples of people
Leprechaun
Things
Alex is talking about
And all of them are opposed to vaccine
It's interesting
Cross-section of like Alex's family
And Owen Shroyer to works
Aggressive anti-vaccination
Community
If you die of a disease that you could have been back
Vaccinated against
That's God
Will
You're not taking those globalist vaccines to live
Past when God said that you should die
Yeah ulcers were caused by Beck
Bacteria
Did so basically Buy
Ingesting a s*** ton of bacteria and then Keurig
I challenged her to infect herself
Coronavirus
You mean this call absolutely I don't know if we'll be able to track her down to make this challenge
Are you dumb
So
I wasn't all that interested
Deanna Lorraine
And her appearance on the show
I almost would have just ignored it entirely probably I wouldn't even brought up the fact that
Restraining orders against Omar Navarro
All that I probably would have
Just left it all alone
Cuz she's someone who is running
Against Nancy Pelosi as a republican in California
It does not seem like it
It's going to work
I would have just been like
But then she says a bunch of
Stopping at my
Nap got to talk about her
Because she thinks
Does Coronavirus
Miz Lorraine please comment on the Coronavirus
Absolutely
Was it manufactured
You know I mean
And it happens to influence these areas
Fractured
Rarely
Be conclusive
I can tell you
Delivery system
Fractured
Biological weapon tree author comes out and says it
Always said that
This is something this is something else
So he's saying that this is Defenders based on this study of it's retracted
An inconclusive not peer-reviewed
Can't really use this as
Proof of anything
And Francis Boyle
The guy who says this all the fun
F****** time on your show
No no
So I don't know
Like all this it's definitive it's
It's concrete it is not none of the stuff you song about means
It is interesting
I think this might hurt Laura
I bet you won't make it out of the primary
No
You can be a red wave that gets rid of Nancy Pelosi
Pelosi is ripe for
Certainly
The fuckout there's a lot of things that certainly from the last name from the right people have a number of
Complaints about her and
That's tearing up the speech
At the end
End of the State of the Union
I think I think
Send a message
I hate
Paper
So
I think there's a lot of comply
Some of them valid
Some of them from Alex not so valid
Here's one of those
Bitter Pelosi claims Trump was drugged
Oh how young we were when Alex and Rodger Stone were saying the Trump was
Speaking weird at speeches and rallies because the globalist
Slow-acting sedatives in his diet coke
Oh how how innocent was expensive it is for Pelosi you suggest
Yesterday
USANA Center
Arc save the thing that we said
What are we doing
What's the weather
So I feel like you want to leave
And if that's the case
You and Owen Shroyer have something in common
Cuz he doesn't want to be doing this later
And Alex
Not let him leave
By the way you were trying to go
Alice won't let me go on the war room for three hours from 3 to 6 at Alex's like
Gastro
Baroness James sensolo
Again Alex
Cannot frame what he's doing
There's no
Why wouldn't you be g.i. Joe
You know who my favorite people
In the show cap
Planetware
Pollution
F****** who had their goddamn Rings or that guy he's blue get him out of here what more Global is proved
Do you need that
Looks like the globe
The foot
Was actually the good guy
Ninja Turtle
Like Alex
Just being being
And identifying
Difference between antihero and the most evil person that could be
Is Cobra is getting like that's another one of those like
There's no ambiguity here this is a very cool
You are a United States loving f****** Patriot you anything
G.i. Joe would be your hero right now it's a small Factory
I think
This one
I mean maybe even if
The case with the Star Wars 12 just like
Is only a few Impressions Alex can do
So
Maybe it doesn't I don't know you were really good Willy Wonka he be a nice man
Yeah
Just the impression
Let him down this dark
What if it is
Scales I have Vicodin body these
Or I go
Tragic tragic
Only told me someone would have taught him
Obi-Wan Kenobi
That would a man
You really start to think about calvinist
Whatever
Are predetermination and at what time
Abilities to do impression
So Alex more calls after Owen leaves
And I think this call is really interesting because I think it
Alien bodies
I'll call her
Who is so close
To understanding the
The Trump is stringing people along to get reelected
It's so close
I love
Is one hair away
We're all like five
Old white non-key
Christmas for these guys
Say is I I just
He's waiting till
He knows if he did so
How
He's holding out
There's too many people on the fans
I totally agree
So he's so close to understanding that like
There is
Waiting until he gets re-elected to do anything
That's neat.
The classic things I get out of course I'll do that
I think I'm going to do
Political Capital until my second terabrite
Cheese's
Tragic
To me though
The way in which that's like
You almost get it
Does delude yourself into thinking
Yeah this
Time for real
It'll be whenever he gets back
Back in
All going down
Admit they got
It is it reminds me of that like
If you are okay
When will you get
To the line
If every step you take
Is halfway there
You know it'll just never
Going to get there
It's just never going to happen
And
Turns out
Deanna
Is
Also on this tip
Of like
Trump probably in the next turn
You probably going to do it
Specific things
What you want
Two happened to Trump's enemies
And if you're aware of the larger
Conspiracy ecosystem
What you wants to happen
It was you about what she believed
I really hope
And just as far as
She's a cute one.
Release
Release those sealed
Stan there's 23,000 have we moved up yet
The did he not write anymore sealed indictments saying they need to be sent to get MO
How is a educator is the indicator of
Adam Schiff in the crystal
Stalker whatever all these people are going to be
Mueller they're all going to get mode
Obama
They're all going to Guantanamo and that's you know that's why I trumpstock closing Guantanamo to also
I think you even knows how many cells there are in
Plenty
Probably
I really don't think so
Flanigan's
When she says things like that it's just a queer ad
Accused
Play one last caller
And I think
It's interesting
The way this caller phrases
He wants Trump to do
What do you want to see
When Trump gets re-elected
Unleash the kraken
Yes
I've heard that before
Tampa.
I think so
Andy is out
Weird
Thank you for reelect
If I understand correctly
Dan vedonde
Is the solution to the global
I didn't know that but now it makes
So much so
Alex talks about this a little more and like it's so funny to me
That is the way
He talked about Dan batondy
David Ortiz nickname was the cracker
Alex
Response to this guy is called without any
Any awareness
The fact that he's being sued right now
Release the Kraken but that is not an employee of it
That's exactly what I was
The trumpet has release the Kraken once he's re-elected
Close the present
So when you're calling
Destruction On Eagle's Wings
No like Newtown
Let's go have a crack in the Kraken is it cold unfeeling monster that tears
Bart everything
Right
So Alex saying that he's heard this in the second
Can term is now him.
Just feeding into the exact same wish-fulfillment narratives that
That other color was very close to recognizing is
Is is characteristic of what's going on
It's just very sad
It's a it's a sad day it's sad day
Such a thing that there
Primed for an infant
So long I think I did more than just Trump supporters are to it
But I mean especially Infowars listeners just on the just on account of how many years have we have we been waiting for this
Summer of Rage
Summer of rage, right it's coming here okay well it didn't this time but next time it's coming there still
You planning it there 10 years line
Expressing the price of gold forever and yet
Among other things
It's so characteristic
Hairstyle
Absolutely you're sitting ducks
He's going to actually do something about the bankers he's going to actually do something about the buzz going to close
Gitana Mobay
Everything that we were just talking
I think
Think you could get wrapped up in that I think a lot of people did but
And I'm sure they're parts of the right that you just never hear from the respond similarly
Mulatto
The left
That I'm
More
Familiar with and
There was more of a hoe
But that was what was going to happen this is definite
Like you used that time certain there are some Republican
Publicans who are the same
These things
Like
I don't know
Medicare goes away
Social Security when I'm older
Vets Trump will accomplish those things
But they don't look at it in the same way of life
If you get through
Re-elected he'll release the crack
All I'm saying Dan is that I am on a fixed income and I would very much like my president to take it away from
Usher
So anyway we get to the end of this episode
I think it's
I think there's no
There's a interesting thing that's going.
Something is
Certainly
Continuing out there coronavirus death
And the
What's a consistent
Thread of it all being soft
10 weeks
That's not that interesting
My charge
To keep keep tracking it as it goes along
Also very sad that there wasn't the in studio surge
Sorry that I got your hopes up.
You really did
I trusted you
For that one moment
3 year prayer
And the other thing
The continuing of the
The food sales
Clearly
And the escalating
I would say dangerous way he's selling the silver
Not necessarily dangerous to
People
Cuz I don't know if it really would harm them
To take it
Maybe they're not the money to buy it and he's hurting the that way
Possible yet
It's not so much
Did he's jeopardizing People's Health
By promoting the suffix
Opportunity cost
And maybe that would be bad your last five bucks to a pro
Prosperity God
F*** you you are an evil person
It's dangerous not the person giving the five.
It's dangerous on that front
Engaging in salesman
Is dangerous to his own interests
I do see that
Trend continuing and maybe even getting worse I'm interested to see how bad it
The camp
Stick around this point for a while
I think I don't know if she'll go in
Further
I don't know if you would like I don't even know if there would be any consequences if he did
That's a good question I think the fact that he's so
Public in such a high-profile person
He might get in
In trouble but I was reading some articles from like 2013
Where a guy who is
His name but he was a guy who's in the FDA and he was
Business Insider
Maybe the week
Are you saying it like
70% of
Supplement
Manufacturers
Product
Inappropriately
There's a decent chance to so much of this
Doesn't ever get anybody in any trouble
I was going to say I was like
How many cases in the past year has the FDA brought
Probably time that you did never hurt me
They also have a lot of issues
Used to deal with that might not be the highest priority for them
Right I don't know and so there's a decent chance that's another reason why I don't want to snitch
Matter
And yeah you want to still have some faith in the system work
That's what I'm interested to see where that goes like even in the next like
While
It's entirely possible he could get worse on that or
Stay in same place
And then this trend
The Democratic party has got to go
Is
Very disheartened
Turn
Most terrifying about it is
This
Propensity that we've seen for the right-wing news media to recycle
Ir-2 like
Take these
Horrifying things from the hard right now I just kind of like Smooth M into rounded edges so
People in the people in the in the middle
The road Republican and somehow Tucker managed
To use language in
In such a way that they're like
Well you know I used to think that the two party system required the den
Democrats but now he's making
In a good argument
You know what I don't like those hard right guy
Some of those guys are Nazis I think I'm the Democrat now as long as we get rid of
All the Democrats
Yeah yeah
I mean there are other flaws to the two-party system that I let you know I have
Other issues
I think are important
Right
Yeah I mean
It's a it is a it is worried
I'm not entirely sure if this
This is something that would trick
Because it's
So f****** over
It's so out of line is that I think there is a valid way that you
Can't Behave this way and not be authoritarian
Like let's say
We need to just
Destroy this party by winning all of the election Ray we need to supercharge
Organizing it right
Looking down ballot
To get to a point
Where we make them irrelevant right
Democracy are better than theirs are
There is a way to
Talk about destroying your opposition
Without
Saying Trump should outlaw
It's not like the country was born with only Democrats and Republicans
Political parties
They know nothing cuz although they were
More like a
We've been here before
It's not so much
Clarify
The idea of getting
Rid of
This part
That is the problem
It's the means by which to do it yeah
Markedly and specifically authoritarian
What was the know-nothings used to beat the s*** out of their political above
Sure there's that
It's not surprising
Likes but it is troubling
And I worry about where at
Cuz it'll be seeing for like at least
Last couple months
Has been like
Everything is down
Everything
Thing is down
And I wonder
I'm spit ball
I'm wondering
If all of these sale
Like that
He's getting by way of
The Coronavirus
Sensationalism
All the food buckets that he's moving
Presume
Increase silver sales
I'm wondering
If the thing that was driving
Sing him towards being so much more
Extreme was the desperation of running out of money and his numbers are looking better
Will that trend
Knockin
I'm seeing the answer is no
Clearly Office episode
And now you saying Outlaw democratic
Know what I mean
I was going to I was going to say that earlier is
One reason that I think the the
S*** about the viruses so weak
Cuz the sales are
So good
Even if
He's peddling
I'd like
Laziness
Why would why would you even bother doing anymore
You can just say coronavirus coming to kill you and
I've got the
By silver like it's so easy
It does seem that way
It's upsetting
I'm bummed out
But
Even ask
Much of a bummer is that is like it's still
I hate to
Go through all of this to do another episode
Fast turnaround time
Is Thursday's episode
Stole big relief that Alex is back in studio
Cuz then I know he's in Austin for what
In our world for what
A to all these other people so f******
Even as terrible as
He has he's still
So much better at this
Then the rest of the story
Studio
You got a fever
Your silver did not cure
I hope that VA doesn't come after you
We aren't
Bealls on Facebook
Tunes or wherever podcast
So download
Skyrim review donate to the whole thing
Until next time I'm near I'm Leo
Dzx Clark
I think Trump swearing is important
Holding
Alex