Important
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Knowledge
Collegeboard.com
Alex Jones
Dan Jordan
Quick question
Ensure
Have you ever been submerged in a body of water fully clothed
On purpose or by being pushed of war the
Probably I know that it like really stick out to me in terms of like if I was pushed
2 something right I mean like it would be
Some bullying in
Center something had a party in all of you all of your and your friends jumped into the river
That is an uncommon thing about life
Specific things but like swimming in clothes
Missouri
The reason I'm having a tough time with your question
Is because it's like he has this weird
Oh yeah it's places that we had that we would go
Has booze smokes weed
Jump in the water
But
Guess one
So
Time is like a little
Creek
View in a lake
It's not like
It was not alike
Charmed
Too far away from my house and become winter we would go out
Play on the ice such as I did
Fallen
Through the ice nightmare
Not a gigantic
Pond
Really deep
It wasn't a situation like
And I can't find the hole
I don't know where to go
Felon into freezing water I'm going to get hypothermia
I was able to get out of the water
But it was terrifying
What time the really sticks out of being in water in my clothes
You just like well I'm going to lose my my toes now
Yeah I don't think it's weird being bodies of water
Zagg liberal City Elite
The out-of-doors
Scared of the dark, but I do know a lot about Alex Jones
Sing episode to go over we are sticking in the
7th 2020
Friday's episode and then we're also going over
A special episode that Alex put out
On Saturday
Very uncommon
Okay for him but I usually only has shows Monday through Friday right
This week you decided
VR hands
Got to do a Saturday episode
You bet
So there'll be a bit of Coronavirus
I believe that this is
It's still worth talking about
Because there is an evolution
I think
Viruses evolve
A mutation or what's his coverage of the Wuhan Coronavirus
Situation
Is
Changing
Coronavirus
And it takes a very
Severe step on Friday's episode Orlando
Towns in this version of
It's it's not good but he's doing is not good much like the movie evolution
Start the recovery in Orlando
Business on this
So first thank you so much
Mason
Frank Mason
Text Devin
Thank you so much
Wyatt thank you so much
Chernow ballsy Wang
I'm a policy wonk even say why it without wanting to say
Text Christine
Text Liam
Thank you so much you're now apology want
I'm a policy wonk
You are now apology
Mike
Thank you so much you are now
Mike like Bray Wyatt
So Jordans
Like I said
February 7th 2020
Here's an out-of-context
Very few people Tabata pull of us her baby
Fair enough
Hey I'm going to need some hard numbers on that
He does not every starting I will learn
Real thing that he sucks
Early's most reasonable to assume
Harris J
So we started on the 7th and Alex has an announcement and I got pretty
Excited about this
Ladies and gentlemen we are broadcasting worldwide on this Friday
Transmission
And we have a very special
Yes
Joining us but I'm going to rebroadcast for a little while
I got to work on
And then I'm going to come back with all this breaking news information today
Crater the bioweapons access biological warfare weapon
In depth
Intel that's breaking the no one else has you know this
Type of person
That's a lot of big contacts
The United Nations and worldwide
He was also slow them Elijah B lawyer
What
Connected to
No no no
Who is Slobodan milosevic his lawyer
Airport Point hear that Alex really should clarify is Vic Francis Boyle was not Slobodan milosevic
That would be a f****** weird credential for a bio weapons expert
The Hague for violating the Geneva
Budget
Rodger stone with his lawyer
It sure would be strange for Alex be bragging about one of his guests for Naturals by saying you defended the first sitting
World leader
To ever be charged with war crimes
Oil was that not milosevic doesn't care about the
In reality boil he did file charges to the international court of justice
That's accusing Serbia under milosevic
Of committing genocide again
Against the Bosnian Muslim
Some population
Well it's not up for discussion whether or not a genocide took place in the Bosnian War they did not been decided in a court IFS
Serbia and Below Savage head directly or indirectly been responsible for those crimes
That trial resulted in the determination that Serbia was not directly or indirectly involved
In the genocide
But that they were responsible for not doing
Responsible in the sense that they didn't do what they needed to have done
To prevent
Whatever you're feeling about that result of the trial
Francis Boyle was not a lawyer make
He was just a person who drafted
It led to the open
Meaning of that case
Alex saying that Francis Boyle was Slobodan milosevic his lawyer is a deeply troubling slip-up
Knowledge base
Not only does Alex not realize that boil
Was involved in trying to get milosevic
Charged with genocide
He doesn't seem to know that saying someone was milosevic his lawyer would not be a great thing
For them to have on the resume everyone deserves a fair defense stand that's in the Constitution
Unpacking milosevic
He does not get affairs
Alex wasn't aware that Slobodan milosevic she's one of the modern era is big villain
And that seems to me to be a little worse
So Francis Boyle has been a lawyer representing a few groups
However
Alex could have brought those thing
Like for instance
Visor for the
For years
Metallica
Possibly bring up
Probably wouldn't want to do that since it involves people who don't think America is so great and don't want to be part of it
I don't think he wants me to have
It doesn't seem like he wants more Hawaii
Or Alex
To bring up the fact that boil is Bennett advisor
Therefore the Palestinian Authority
But you probably wouldn't want to do that
Palestinian
And then just being fully Clear Eyes for Palestinian rights
But I don't think I necessarily agree with boils position
Which seems to be in favor of the
The destruction of Israel and he is also called it juist and
Off of what I agree with
See that's what that's where you get to that full-circle situation where it's like somebody so anti-semitic their accidentally doing something
B helpful
I'm not entirely sure exactly what his
There are a lot of people who have some questions so I'll say that if you look into it
Well Melissa B couldn't even afford him
So he knows
In January 2018 Fox 55 out of Champaign Illinois for the 10th
St Patrick's Day Celebrations cancelled
Because of
Concerned the kids are going to get drunk
He wanted bars and liquor stores to be banned from offering drink
Specials or advertise
For the event
Which seems like Alex whatever chilling effect on Free Speech
Yeah he also outlawed dancing in champagne glass
People getting drunk something back
As recently as a month ago boy was making a
Appearances on podcast
Trump needs to be in
Primarily for his complicity with Saudi Arabia and their atrocities Indiana
Probably didn't want to bring that up but
To be fair also boil is called for every president since at least Clinton to be a
So that I don't think is that wrong
This that's one of the ones where I get in
Boil is a bit of a complicated figure from a political
Perspective
He definitely has some real entries in his resume mostly ending about 15 years ago
You have some positions that I think I can get down with like a y in Independence
But he also seems to really disproportionately hate Israel
Expresses his opposition there are more than political in nature
Think I can get on board
I want Hawaiian Independence so the Jews can't get it God damn it no
Whatever the case
About his
Agreement
Things like Hawaiian independent Palestinian rights
I do not know what you was up to and I would just as soon not
Consider him an ally
Too confusing and whatever the case
He was not melosa
Alex has no idea what he's talking
Pretty much ever
I'm glad that Alex is back on the show now and he has Francis Boyle
She has
As opposed to the last time he was on
Cuz I went interview
So we will get to hear
What Francis Boyle brings to the table in terms of you bio-weapon on do not excite
No you shouldn't be
It's very disappointing
So
Alex
Has a new Theory
About the
Wuhan
Novel Coronavirus
Right
It's not good
I'll give you that I'll give you that up front
Here is a
Surveillance fleshing it out a little bit
Is this a cover for the back of the Chinese economy was imploding
Major civil
Uprising
Definitely not
Okay
This Coronavirus
Is conclusively from the tsar's family
The Communist Chinese have been caught
4 * releasing another labs
Doesn't sound like accidents to me
So the implication is now becoming the China release this on itself intention
They've released
Did four times before
Okay
So first of all it's really important to recognize that Alex operates very consistently in the realm of speculation
He's introduced this whole segment basically as him spitballing
So there's no real need for him to come through
Conclusion and even if he does eventually make definitive statements
That's really just been looking at all the angles or some s***
So he's speculating the China was a shame that they lost the
Is trade War
With job which I'm not sure is accurate at all
Face they've launched
The bioweapon attack all themselves that's disrupting their economy at definitely not helping on that front
Right on its face this makes no sense even without analysis this Theory should be dis
How did the dumbest s*** it's not just throwing the baby out with the bathwater it's never having taken a bath and just
Killing your WhatsApp
I have to Alex saying the China release ours for time
I would call him to prove that
There was a the mainland SARS outbreak that occurred between 2002-2003 but since I was dealt with
There have been reappearance is of SARS
Is not the same thing as saying China released it four times
So let's take a look
It's some of those reappearance has
Spider-Man 1
Spider-Man 2 Spider-Man how many Spider-Mans has there been at least
It's it's pretty good programming
So on January 4th 2004 man in southern China came down with stars but all indications
Experts to believe that he was insect
Through human-animal Khan
Which makes
In 2017 the guardian reported on Chinese researchers who would finally traced down the origin of SARS
Do colony of bats
It was initially believed that the source was Civic
But further research found that those cats were actually just an intermediate step between the bats
Humans
The same article discusses how another SARS outbreak is very possible given the absence of a SARS vaccine
And the fact that animal human transmission could very well happen again
This is very much likely what happened
With this guy into
Sounds right
The rest of them
Are the
A product of Lab Rats
In 2003 in August of virology grad student in Singapore was
Exposed to SARS in a lab that he worked at
Anyone else Sonos
That was one
Reappear
December 2003
Researcher wasn't
All the people he had been in contact with we're quarantine
None of them came down with SARS
Investigation found that he'd been working with hazardous materials and improper settings
Improper settings
He wasn't using proper protocol and didn't have a
The correct uniform
Like gloves and a mask
She had are behaved in ways that were
Baby high-risk he wandered in with shorts and a Hawaiian shirt
Maybe not literally true
But spiritually
Proper protocol in this lab where he was researching SARS
I like the I like the balls on a guy was like most dangerous viruses that
You can get me just like
Having closer a lot to put on today you know that's not Saturn of releasing
Have to be one of the instances.
Savannah April 2004 the Chinese Ministry of Health
Reported three cases
Pictures of SARS
One of them leading to a death
This was the result of a laboratory researcher at
The Institute of virology
Which did research SARS although this person
Didn't actually directly
Research
Clearly this is where
Virus
This researcher that infected the nurse was attending to her as well as her mother who was there at the hospital
Her mother tragic
We passed away
But the virus didn't spread further than that
The details of these additional SARS cases outside of the initial outbreak it really seems hard for me to see
Any proof of
China intentionally release in SARS
Any of them
One seems like an opening
Shut natural case
Largely be attributed to poor procedural
Controls in lab settings
The guy in December 2000
Three seems to be the product of his own negligence
The guy with the white shirt is you
Not some kind of state attempted bye-bye
I imagine he's played by Pauly Shore in this
Chinese specific in East Asia and general law state
Horn of money during the SARS outbreak
An article in Reuters cites a research paper
Total at a loss of
15 billion dollars in
GDP just from that out
Is there some kind of motive that I was trying to say
Suggest that involves
Economy is argument is Ludacris
No country would ever release a bioweapon on themselves
To save face
Or Shore up their economy
Yes just
Yeah
15 billion in GDP of China 20 years ago
5 to 10% of their entire GDP wiped away entirely sure what exactly it is but it's
It's not
It's a it's a relevant
Yeah so
The trash bin
So Alex is like
Trying to
Think about like
Expo
Experts
Boil coming up
What about people who know things about China has one guy
I forget his name
Famous human rights activists
China open us adoptions
Were the CIA we got in my lives in Canada
He's really smart
What is it name and I can't remember guys get him back on immediately
What money camera while talking about
Call Vitaly
We don't need to wait till the colors I remember who that it's cheap
We talked about him but the past
He's the guy who runs that operation called pink Pagoda which he claims is helping arrange adoptions of Chinese children
He was the one who
Claimed that he was stealing and human trafficking children and he was doing it probably
I mean
Yes if he's not making it all up
Researchers who tried to corroborate anything he says about his adoption operations of come up
Completely update
And when they've tried to ask him for any kind of evidence
It's to prove his claims reducto for
Safety of people I will not prove anything thousands of children that you have taken
Getting from China
Thousands of children that you have claimed
It seems like the more likely thing is the
Keys
Scamming
Yeah
He was arrested in 2014 for having
Illegal gun which he claimed wasn't his
He cure currently now like
He has a bunch of profiles up
Promoting himself
Acting gigs
So I assumed that if Alex calls he'll be showing back up
Interesting Lee Jim's acting bios
Like saving everybody in China in China
Do they
No also his bio.
Do Dimension the time that the Obama tried to kill him or the claim that he was in the CIA for 45 years right
Would be some good
Experience to put on your acting
Explain the experience CIA guy all day
Having metal the way my life in various settings I've come to the conclusion that enjoy all that is brought to you
Part of growing up
As a foreigner coming in from Scotland I was open to the new world and all of its experiences
I did some degrees became a teacher principal College president
Teacher's College principal
Inside myself in China
Opening schools in Brick
Students back to North America
Then I did a small commercial for a resort in China
In love the experience
I refuse to adapt and I refuse to accept that take that down
I want to see some desist.
Jim Carrey Rosa complete
Someone Alex looks as a credible Source debases positions on
Pathetic level of knobs
Honestly I hope Alex does have him back on because based on his past record Jim Garrow is
The sort of hard swinging crazy dude
But I need to find love for the game again
Yeah
It's it's
Between the helmet and you know if sagami weren't such a heavyweight
In the field
At least number two
Like it was Leo.
Don't even know much about China.
Straight 911
The pantheon right
Stroop
Unfortunately Alex is actually thinking of a different
But describing
Pieces of Jim Gyros resume to him
Excavator comes up with this dude's name is Steven Mosher
We've talked about him a bit in the past 2
He was a guy who was an anthropological research student in 1979 when he went to China to do a cultural
Study
He published an article describing the Chinese
The practice of course of women to get abortions
Which ultimately led to her
Him getting expelled from his Ph.D program at Stanford
People like Alex would likely say that you was
Spell because you dare criticize China
But the reality is
Published photos and identifying information about the women who were his
Which is a clear breach of ethics
Fix the put these women's lives
Is it risk
I want to put this
Too bluntly but
It's a very serious decision when a school kicks out of
That's not the same thing as getting
Kicked out of your undergrad program for
For plagiarism or party
Too hard
Like universities make a
Great investment
In the people they choose to accept
For PhD consideration
And I know from conversations
Doctoral advisors at
High-profile colleges
Read my dad
Typically schools do whatever they can to not kick out the HD channel
In the case of vulture
The board voted
Expel him 11 20
Bowser try to appeal his
Expulsion but Stanford stood firm and explain some of the reasons they were uploaded
Is dismissal
One of them
Was regarding a tape his ex-wife had given
Where he brags about lying about having
Top secret clearance
In order to pretend to be a courier to get a free flight
From California to Japan
Why do people put everybody
Always recording
He's a fraud guy quiet
The school also had hired a private
Detectives determined at least one sale
Brother to get purchased for his work
Which is
Suspicious
At Stanford Zen President Donald Kennedy described it
You seem to have a pattern of behavior
Towards those
The school was right to expel him you just can't take the risk
To being associated with someone who would operate that way
Multiple
Instances of life
Rio this
Disingenuous
You just like
This puts your work
You can't
You can't do that
Yeah yeah yeah
Since then he's basically written a bunch of books about how evil China is
Along the way in 1996 he founded the population Research Institute
Which portrays itself as a group trying to
Overpopulation
But it's actually just
The pro-life
Legacy group
The Institute really is just a
The Catholic anti-contraception anti-abortion
Front that Moser took over in 1996
When Paul Mark
A Catholic priest who was an early leader of the pro-life
Movement
Stepped down
In the ensuing years the present-day they branched off into the predictable hard right talking points
Like denying climate change
AcuRite scores
They're very transparent about where their funding comes from because
Of course they are
But it's known that between 1999 and 2002 they received at least 130
$3,000 from the Linden
This is without a doubt a small chunk of the right-wing billionaire body
Coming into that insta
Attitude
Them to push their nonsense
Alex was absolutely thinking of Jim Carrey
Bass all the details
Garrow pretends he was in the CIA he pretend he was involved in Chinese adopt
Andy lives in Canada
None of these things apply to Mosher
Alex legitimately can't keep any of his guests nonsense backstories
Because they're all bulshit
They're all just
Fabricated
Eaton
To the point where I bet if you
Gave
Moccias credits is that motion would be like
Oh s*** did I make those flies God am I
Yeah I totally did all that stuff out
Canada
Alex
To get around so you heard at the beginning of the show Alex was saying like
I got to go off there for a little bit to get my note
Special rapporteur to
Know if he actually got anything right but he's weird
The beginning of the episode
It would help yeah
Insane what what's Jones doing right now
He said everything's nice because all over the map
I am brainstorming right now on air
Not good
Have a pre-show meeting
What happens if I get set
Play my wife
It's my fault I can easily destroy
The show
And then I got to reset
So let me just do that
Best I can here right now all that is
Yeah that's a hockey
Because I'm
Trying to wing it
I am
Easily confused
So Alex is
Big take
The China situation is
So far we've seen
Most likely
And one of the reasons you think
This is because he's never seen
Such a
Chin
2 an hour
Expresses that gear
It's just so stupid
We can talk all day about
How bad is it going to be what are they covering up why the giant respond
Comedian singing Feldick
Unified Global Response
What you never seen before least I have it
Am I wrong with a case example
Okay so what Alex is saying is completely insane and means nothing
Is it really suggesting that there hasn't been instances of outbreaks being there with International cooperation before
Really dumb things to say station solve their problems by themselves
Do you want the case example okay SARS MERS
Ebola
Zika
What does it mean by unified Global Response
Use the rosaries rooting for Stars this time around event steak city audit claims
Broadcast
Chili was all-in for SARS
Chili was rooting for SARS the whole time s2b
Frisbee different
This is the first time they world is united in saying viruses are bad
Going to tell you a little bit about the 2002-2003
3 SARS outbreak
You think this is
Unified Global Response
On November 16th 2002 China reports the first case of atypical pneumonia
More cases pop up and then by March 2003 the World Health Organization
Issues a global alert
Put into motion
And international respond
Within two days the cdc's
Established
An emergency operation
United States
And 3 days after that
An international network of 11 labs
Start working in conjunction
Determine the cause of the outbreak and figure out
Gino
By July 5th
The World Health Organization declares the outbreak
With no local Transmissions within the viruses incubation
.
A piece of the bulletin of the World Health Organization
Discusses the lessons
That we learned in the alpha
The director of the division
For combating communicable diseases
For the World Health organization's regional office of the Western Plus
Here is one of his main takeaways
Quote
What was gratifying was the during the SARS outbreak
2003's there was unprecedented collaboration among scientists
And Laboratories around the world to work together to identify the causative agent
Map its genome and develop reliable
Even in the face of
The Chili's resist
There was openness and willingness
Mr. share critical scientific information
As a result
The virus was identified within weeks of the Opera
The scientific world was shown at its
It sounds to me like a unified Global Response being discussed
That article in the bulletin literally ends with a
This line quote
No man is an island and no
Country can fight a global Public Health threat alone
Every single case of a public health emergency will ultimately require unified Global Response
Putting it bluntly Alex's is talking
You just making
Stuff up
Doesn't mean anything
Look
Government
Do so much evil ship
Why can't for once we all root for the International Coalition of people stopping viruses this is the one thing
Where can we all be like f*** yeah the CDC in the WHL work
Kick in the ass
Why can't we just do that for one thing why does Alex have to be a dick about every
I'm not entirely sure if I could pinpoint it to one reason but I think I might have the constellation of thing
And what
Play you this clip
So Alex has decided because the false flag
Attack the China did on them
Right now it evolves even
Even further
Alex
Is suggesting now that it's a race specific bioweapon
Meant to just
Attack the Chinese
That the Chinese are doing to themselves
And
Nevermind start there
B
Reveal himself to be a bit of a race
Rachel Science Guy
But it's serious
And they're covering up what's really going on and it's a
Just incredible to me
That is so obviously a bioweapon
Obviously race-specific
Chinese
Men
I mean it's so specific the Chinese genome is so
Close
Weathergroup maybe is white related
What
They're just what
Tailor-made for a racist
Don't want to use one
Racism
Kills
A mongrel wishing it was a bad term it's a good term in a genetically being able to fend off against things
Pure breeds
You get diseases
So look at British royalty and people that very sickly they're very mentally ill
Is it real smart
I guess my first response to that clip would be okay hey got a citation on any of that
I refuse to engage with that
Down for it because it's not based on anything
It's deeply race
Even if you ignore the part where he's talking about mongrels and how Chinese people are inbred
What underlies Alex's position here is their belief that there's something
Genetically distinct about people of different races
Which is to say that there's some gene or allele that makes it a Chinese person Chinese
And I guess he's somehow you know you somehow proven that this Coronavirus
Genetically engineered
Specifically Target people with vet Chinese G
This is completely f***** up
Swear I'm just going to say I reject
Travis and I'm not even going to take
Dignify this
With any sort of
Discussion like it's just unreal
Many many many Studies have been done about in-group out-group
Genetic diversity
Ethically in common with people who are not part of
Your ancestral lineage then
People who are within your
We understand as a racial group
It's this is really
F****** messed-up stuff
Yeah if he keeps talking like that he's going to be
Congressman from
That's what you get whenever you get that racist I think you get that
So Alex Goes further down this road
This is bad stuff
That road you can go further down
But we've reached the end of that road
Call God
Bio weapon because you can kill them off
And not hurt your own people
What does he mean by saying that they're asking for it
So the Chinese government is releasing a race specific bioweapon
That targets only Chinese men
Damn do you know what one thing most
The Chinese government has in common with itself
Alex is kind of wishy-washy
Whether or not like China did this
To themselves is a false flag
Now leaving pretty hard into this being a race specific bioweapon Chinese people are so slow
Similar to
Which they chose to do
I don't even know man
Chose to have a massive geographical location with
Many different subgroups cultures within and yet
But still be genetically similar like does that clip Alex says that the Chinese are perfect with the biome
Because you can kill them off with
People
And I think what's important
Recognize here
Is that Alex thinks very racially
He thinks very much in terms of people of different ethnic groups not being quote
He's people
Can I find that mentality to be racist and it's
It score
Also in this scenario who is it that's deploying this bioweapon
I thought you said you sing the Chinese did because they want to lower the population or save face in the
Or whatever but now it's about eliminating the Chinese without risking any non-chinese losses
Because incompatible with the previous.
Yeah that's incoherent
I'm guessing you
And I'm saying it's the globalist
Globalstar in bed with China and want to take over the world
Nothing you say makes any sense it's complete
Trash
Is a framework of a very
Very racist
Incredibly racist
A line of thought
To even
Entertain
Now I mean
Here's it cuz here's the other underlying truth there
Is that you don't think
That means he must think that
Skin color means complete
Genetic
Bricks
White people are completely genetically separate
From black people from Chinese people from all of those defense that's what I was trying
Yeah that is what
Bonkers
That's it cuz that's
Cuz that's when you
That's when
F****** he's he's into this like
Chimpanzees are 97% of the same genetic material as
Tell me where there are literal
Some people are Homo sapiens and then some people
Chinese
In his mind
It's tough to figure out exactly what he believes
Because he's not really Express
The little hints that he gives in a little indications lead you to hang out
Oh no
That's
That is
The if not
Out-and-out
The building block of a race superiority genetic superiority argument
Problem I think comes down with
I mean
But problem what problem is
Releasing a biological weapons
These days
War crimes are within the eye of the poor person getting murdered it's important to nail down
Who's doing right because
Crime
Turns out in summer
Situations
Maybe it's
Not a crime
Perfectly made
For Chinese and it doesn't do that
If you were morally going to hit a group that was attacking you
Morally
You would only hit them with something that goes after military age men
Young
Men
No
Wiping out
Specific
Perfectly targeted
So specifically made
Now do you think that just fell
First I need to get this taken care of
Right off the bat
Under no circumstances is it ethical to deploy a bioweapon against the civilian population
Regardless
If it attacks you
This is very clear in international law
Just possessing something they could be a biological weapon
And if not explicitly for legitimate research purposes
Could get you charged with a war cry
What Alex's suggested
Is it
You think this is
Ethical
Massive International scandal
Pictures of super super f*****-up thing that he seems to
Be okay with
I think it kind of sounds like a nut
Not even not even like
You start about something
Even deeper than that ethical country song about morals like
God
Gives you the right
So long as you only kill military-aged men
To murder people who aren't even come back
I mean this is insane argument
Unacceptable on any level
Also I have no idea where
Getting this information that is mostly military age men who are dying from the Coronavirus
Diseases according to a report in the guardian for February 1st they had reviewed demographic
Information that have been released about people who have died and naturally you'd expect most of them to be people who are elderly or have pretty
Additions
They mostly were
But they were five outlaw
People aged
36 50/50
355 + 50
That is far as I can tell is not this thing mostly hitting
Military
Man
I don't know what Alex is talking about beside to sources which you won't do because he doesn't
1:30
Just trying to find ways to feel good about
The concept of Chinese
People dying
The New York Times published an article with updated information on February 7th
Discussing details about 138 cases that they had review
One of these cases I'm sorry of these cases the median age
The person who got the virus was 50
The median age of someone who got it and needed intensive care with 60
They found
54% of the cases in their sample were men
Do they did point out that other reports of different cases claim to higher percentage of men
Princeton
Lancet published a report about 13 patients in Beijing
Median age of 30
And 77% of them were men
Both pretty outside the expected range of a broader disc
Fusion but considering it's a sample of 30
People it's not necessarily meant to be interpreted as representative of the wider population
See that's where we get back to that 77% thing where you're like your full by 77%
Well at the very least that means 77 out of 100
Instead it
8 dudes
It's
These things are really important for people to understand like you have to get contacts
Explorer
7 / 70
It's so easy people in Beijing
Specifically like not a representative sample
And in that situation if it's only 13 young men in in Beijing
That means that they're almost certainly people who travel around a lot
Making them
Far more likely to be
Exposed to this all of them
The median age
So that means there were more younger people represent
You would expect
But also none of those patients died or had severe complication
It wouldn't be too surprising if there were a lot of people
Lacrosse
To get the virus
Much like people of all ages are susceptible to catching the flu
It's a matter of it being far more serious for older people
Existing health condition
The bottom line is that I think all this up because he's fantasy role-playing
But there's something deeply disturbing. This new wrinkle to his language
Who does he think
China was at
Who does he
You suggesting that someone has the moral right to use a bioweapon against
Chinese military age
Men because of
Something
I guess what does he do it
That's the these guys are so scared that's why wouldn't you
Here or when you read about all of the
The times where
Trump has just been like
Right that's the thinking that these people have that idea that Total War makes sense
Like I stopped reading about military strategy whenever the
They read that some people burned crop
And that's how they won the war and they were like yeah let's start the poor
F***** up Heather Alex making rationalizations for the concept of
Biological
Like even in a hypothetical scenario
Anything acceptable
Alex talks a little bit
Suggesting the possibility that
We dat
The United
States did this
As an attack on Chinese military age
Because China is somehow attacking
That has taken a turn
I told you that I told you
Jurassic evolution
Now do you think that just fell
No in the scientist look at it
The Indian topside is everybody else's
That's why the US and China and others who have the genome
The RNA sequence
The virus will not send it out
Why would you say that we can identify
Because when you get it you know my God
This is a 57 Chevy
Made now the big question is did the United States watches against China has a reaction in the war
Your son has been secretly attacking a bunch of stuff
I think I have the answer on the other side
So we don't get to know if Alex thinks it was us who did this cuz of the secret War
Wow
Be critical masses bulshit yeah that one
I want to straight up suggesting there's a possibility that
Bus bread the coronavirus as a bioweapon
Does China has been attacking us
Just after saying it would be ethically right
To do that
Obviously the United States didn't do that but Alex is pretending that we might of
Justifying
I know that this is a bit of a stretch
But Alex hates Somalia
So let's say one day Trump decides it's Somali is our enemy and they've been attacking us
So he uses the biological weapon against
According to what Alex is saying right now it seems like he would have to be okay with it
He's normalizing the idea of using bio weapons on civilians
Peacetime
All you have to do is pretend their country is attacking you
This is so deeply Disturbed
He needs to get off air
Like I can't I can't
Ya know whenever you're saying that
When you're saying both
China and the United States
I have probably also released this
At the same time baby to kill people that
Either you would
He's very unspecific about what he's highly suggesting but
Underneath it used on normalization of
The concept of using biological agents
Against
That is a point at wittlake to which the Overton window
Cannot you cannot
Alex's
Good
Normal the Deep state
Yeah right this is really bad for
Normalizing this kind of conversation
He's trying to make acceptable to talk about now
Is
Porosity
I am and not not just that but another thing underlying it is that
There is no such thing as
Everyone is always secretly but already
He's always been if not opened
Then secretly at work so it doesn't matter if we declare war or not
We've already been at work
Yeah I mean it like this
He's been doing where he's been trying to make
Infomercials out of Public Health
Health Emergency
That's bad
But it's kind of what you
Back from the school of con man he comes from
This is something else altogether
Just the other day you sang the Trump should Outlaw the Democratic Party
Is warming up to the idea of using race
Pacific bio-weapon
Punjab Sevilla
I really don't know if he knows what he
He's saying anymore but I also really don't care
He doesn't get better from
This is how
The path downward that were on
That I couldn't even predicted this kind of thing
Call Ben
You know I was thinking the other day I was literally thinking
So many people who like well
When you hit bottom there's nowhere to go but up
And I was like
Or there's no bottom
And I was thinking I've been thinking others just no bottom it's just always
She's going to keep going
And even this damn surprised me that you can go this low
I've been telling myself there's no bottom I didn't even know this was available on the bottom
Also the Indian scientist who wrote the Yunnan.
Feedback from fellow scientist was not a tops
Alex is just making that up
To make that retractable
Percy more credible with
Which is not
No one else except for a week
Conspiracy blogs are saying the same thing that scientists said
I guess Mike Adams is but his website is an extremely right-wing conspiracy blogs he doesn't get to count his other sign
Factcheck.org actually did talk to other scientist
It's about that paper
Christian Anderson the director of insects
Disease genomics at the script
Research Transit translational Institute
Told them that the analyses in the paperwork completely wrong
Anderson said there was a quote
Misunderstanding of how to perform these type of analysis and said that they were just
Cherry-picking data
Timothy Sheehan the virologist the University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill
Golden Deli
Do you know if there are zero signs of human tampering
He said that
Because despite with Alec Steele
Keep saying on his show
Not like no one has the Genome of his if they did say
You can't trust him he's only 250 in North Carolina
Another person who study the virus Trevor Bedford computational biology
Just to be Fred Hutch
Cancer Research Center in Seattle actually recreated with a retracted study was attempting to analyze
They were claiming to be inserts in the are Nara
Actually just mistakes and interpretation made by the Indian research
What was claimed to be
TRNA work
Clearly segments of material that are present
Closely-related sars-like virus
He tweeted out all of his materials to so if Alex is so that's
Where to get his hands on it
It's been there on Twitter for at least a week
I was probably
Who's been kicked off Twitter
You know he's not really walk
Walking around in info spheres that include information
So
All this is b*******
Secret war with
Vagina and
Flushes that out a little bit
I'm not going to give the US government to pass
And say for sure that somebody in the Deep state
On
The American team in best
Enough fentanyl being shipped
Every couple months to kill the entire world population
You're like that's what shift in the USPS
Not the kill the whole world
That means a lot of it's not even getting delivered to the drug addicts they're just so much of it
One shipment they caught coming in from Mexico with kill
10.6 billion people
Newspapers at 11 billion
It was made of mosquito
11 million people
Took an overdose
Why you see homeless everywhere laying out
Asleep during the day and sleep at night they're not asleep
They're passed out on fitting
So is this how
The United States says
We told you to stop that
Is there a specific weapon that kills military age men
You want to kill
Teenagers boys girls white people black people in Spanish Asians old young
Will just hit you
Where they
Race specific bioweapon
I told you that towards the future
I don't think
Trump would do that
Whew for the relief
He doesn't stick
Trump would do that
Well fucken now I do
I think Alex would do it
Yeah
I don't I don't cut into this
I don't say I don't appreciate
Man
That's such a terrifying thing to hear
Alex
Stinks that
Sentinel coming into the country
Response might be to release a race specific bioweapon on civilian
Yes that is a
Important question
Questions to ask in the middle
This horrific s*** that Alex is spewing
Specific bioweapon
Real know the answer is
And it doesn't seem likely that they will be even in the near future
The basic reason this is the case
Is that the illegals Jean-Luc
What we call Race
It's not just one gene
They're a f*** ton of jeans at sequences that make up each person
Individual genome
And there's a whole lot of overlap
Between different groups
There isn't just a one-to-one relationship between genes and race
So the view I've seen throwing around is that you could probably make some kind of an agent that's slightly if
Back to certain group more than
Another you pronounce
Difference in the measure of a cup
Couple percentage
And it wouldn't be
It wouldn't be effective
Another reason why most evil villains probably would never decide to deploy these hypothetical race specific bioweapons is
A common feature of viruses is that once they begin to be passed around
Mutate
Predictive erase specific
Miss of a weapon you create would even last one
Cycle in The Wider population
It's just not a good plan even from all evil legit
No okay
So if there's one thing I know
Every biologist
It's that as long as you have a sample of say
1 or 2,000 people you can correctly assume what biological circumstances will arise for
From 7 billion people
That's just true
Humans are so similar
That you never see wild and massive variation
Zucker
For no reason
Alex has zero evidence erased
Pacific bioweapons Eva
Even exist
Wendy's press to the wall and has to say proof of their existence
Since the two things you brings up ID project for a new American
Century document
And that 1997 speech
The Secretary of Defense William Cohen
In both of these ants
Altus primary sources are people trying to justify great
Spending from the US government
And race specific bioweapons are
Hypothetical
Gofrette bring up to illustrate the kinds of dangers we may be protecting ourselves from one day
Neither of these sources prove the existence of these sort of weapon nor does anything else Alex can point to
They are examples of
People trying to get more money into the defense
Budget
If it weren't a British o I would say he watch
Utopia
Which is
Basically it's a
TV show about
Erase
Specific
Maybe he did I don't know
It's likely these people find a graphic novel that
Reveals a massive maybe spiracy to release a race specific bioweapon
To depopulate the
Almost word-for-word
So I don't think Alex is good on
Ciara
I didn't consider
The KKK seven-years-old - song
My grandfather going
Walnut Avenue Clearwater
But that the other Chinese dict
Formaldehyde
He wants us to do, because I want to get rid of their populations as wife
World governments can reduce the population
Please erase specific
And all and I told these stories before on-air years ago
Visionary man my my mom's dad was smart
I'd like to apologize I didn't know that Alex
His grandpa yelled at him when he was 7
I didn't know that he has that kind of high-level Source about how
Call the government
Is
Desiring of a nuclear war and that eventually they will release a race-based by
A weapon
You know it's true
I didn't realize I I do all this like looking into Alex
The sources I didn't realize he was 7
Did you not did you not
Email his grandfather for comment identities basic journalistic ethic
So
The end of our series
It's just revealing.
In a good
B here
You know like really
Insinuated he doesn't think Trump would do
The race
Specific
It is on the table
Thankfully he doubles down on that doesn't
Think that the US
Is behind this
Good
That looks like something the US would launch going to be military and you're being hit with
Channel. It will you head
We're not going to operate like that
Can you make a phone call
Ukraine saying yeah
Get a phone call
Corruption of the money they got to redo that
Truck is completely paralyzed other than promoting America
Get some B policies
Trump would never
Name one of them have that over his head
No way
I don't believe so
We have stuff on the Shelf like this you better damn well believe it
Stole it out of that Canadian lamp
I do not like that Alex's defense
Seems to be the Trump would do this because he can't get away with me
Love to do it
In a heartbeat
People watching him dance
To get people to do his bidding without interference
Be more of a logistic
Six issues na
That would be a gigantic
Maybe Alex is thrilled at the idea of his
I guess being Slobodan milosevic is a lawyer
Everybody knows
The God hates coward
That's the rule
It's in the Genesis 1:1
So
I mean sensational
This isn't saying this
The level of stereo
He's trying to build up surroundings
Virus
Aldi's new layers of it's a race specific bioweapon maybe a false flag
China's pulling on itself
Anyhow he of course he does a lot of sales
For his products
And we get to adopt
On Suffolk that is
What are described as
The opposite of a shark
Tell you what I'm personally doing 45 Miami and system
It's right here it's called
50 Park
Vermilion silver but it's not regular silver
Hire parts per million for the same price
This is what you guys the best and safest
It's immune
This is what the Pentagon is we showed you in the documents
Secretly
Text thing again
Family
I'm just saying it's nanosilver it's high-quality and its ingestible
Not just in Garland spit it out
It's what I do
And I love it
It's sold out
Before the show
Show ended it was sold out
Oh I wonder I wonder why I wonder wonder why it sold out
Because you're lying Apopka
Product
He's take
These things that are
Possibly true about the gel
He's directly applying those claims to the immune gargle in this in that clip
Way Beyond
The acceptable and of course your product
You're on bearings
Embarrassing yourself with this
This is Terry
Hysterical
You're engaging in really does he really does make more sense it like
He is an apocalyptic
Creature
Holding wearing one of those box signs on the corner
Scream about how everybody going to die in hell
Mixed with the f****** ShamWow guy
Events
It's Philly
Billy know he was the OxiClean guy
So Alex agos break and you take
It comes back and takes
Calls by this point he's kind of landed on the idea that it's a race specific bioweapon and China
Released it on themselves as a Volkswagen
Probably could have done it if they wanted to Absolute
I'm so he takes calls
He doesn't like Alex's
Very much
We got loaded phone lines here
Victory in Europe first he says the US release bioweapon on China
Bioweapon it is man-made. Confirmed
Specific
That is not
Why is it such a crazy response to would want this to happen it would be behind it what do you think Victor
So you see the way he is
Framing the parameters of what's up for discussion
It's not up for discussion that this is a man-made race-specific Iowa
Now did the u.s. do it
That's a good question
The phone line
Alex
False flag
This college is not agree
Do you understand that they can inflict a wound on themselves
To then get out
How does a factor losing the trade War
Embarrassed
And use that is why the Crackdown
Had the police tape measure to that make sense to you
It's not the most likely scenario.
13 years old
Is it
China and other Global it would launch bio attacks on themselves
Nautical and social
Hey Medical
I'm just saying what's today
Are you saying select possible scenario
See Alex's defensive about this guy pushing back on his idea of the China false-flag themselves
Aspirus
30 buckets to me that he's not so much
Exploring all the angles as he is visit the position I'm going to put forth
Pushing back on it I'm going to Tucanos
Petty and
I don't like the way you said that my idea that I came up with literally 10 minutes ago is not the most likely
A scenario I thought of it
10 minutes ago that means
Right so he gets another caller who thinks that this is a Chinese government psyops show of some sort and maybe it's not
Not even actually have not even happened
It's active it's a bingo I got a bingo.
This could be a Chinese
Communist
People out scripting it you're absolutely right
AstroTurf
Firms are online that are thousands
He pointed out and they sue us for saying it
When they advertise in hired
Not able to get the
Have the Clash
Mostly white supremacist
Tired
And again nothing against gay people but you know why
Acting job
The bunch of little pot-bellied you know out there for the real Nazi
Seashell Dauphin
I hear what you're saying God bless you Maria
All right when I come back I'm taking 5
It doesn't
Weird that he didn't bring it at Syria but you seems to consistently believe whenever you just rambling Richardson
Gay actors that got hired
Did Spencer space that Richard Spencer you are a f****** liar and all you did was hire a bunch of
Potbelly
Quotes
Gays
Grapes
This is a
Dumps
This isn't just offensive this is like
Give him give him out
How to get him the f*** out
So Alex
He doesn't take five calls
Backing
It's not good at taking calls
At all ever
That's not just today
Ever
He gets ready cuz he's got Francis Boyle coming up
You got this guy
Legislation back in the late 80s
And now is here
Comes on out to show all the
The time every time there's a public health issue to say
It is a bioweapon
And Alex said something really stupid
You trust people that have been around long time
Are there on record with integrity
Figure the truth out of data mean they're perfect
Doesn't mean I'm right all the time but we're riding 97% on your pillow.
Francis Boyle creator of the US by WeatherBug
U-joint us coming up
You've been right all the time
All vanilla bioweapons all of them bioweapons releases
Almost makes you think we don't even have actual diseases we just have biome
Weapons created by people
True I'd really is kind of what they think the other day I stubbed my toe
Oh s***
Oh no that wasn't that one was actually Stephen Miller
Could have been
So Alex
Gets into reading some
Pump up for
France
Does boil and he gets a little out of line
With his his bio
And this is one of the leading experts in the world. It's on the medical side of the genome and then that are and a side but also
The UN forces neon nose
This is a bio-weapon
Alex is presenting this interview is it
Explicitly dishonor
There's literally no excuse for him to present Francis Boyle as a leading expert on the medical side of things
Because he has zero background in science
This is one of the many many ants
Instances of Alex being unable to stop himself from embellishing things
Make its narrative less questionable to impressionable
It's not enough represent is gaster
Did the guy who was involved in drafting that us statute on buy weapons back in the late 80s
And here's why
The claim that Alex is having boil on to make are not at all relevant to that
He's coming on.
Discuss how the coronavirus is a bio-weapon
Which has nothing to do with his actual field of x
Namely
Law
The content of the conversation
His credentials to discuss
It's pretty important to make up things
Things to add to his resume like
You leaving
Expert on the medical side of bioweapons
When he's not at all
In the world of gambling
Is it called a tell
The fact that I was creating the
Disputatious aspect of Boyle's knowledge base
Gives him credibility
He has no involvement
And that tells you that Alex is creating an illusion
As opposed to reporting
We're doing this since your interview
No journalists operating in good faith and according to ethical standards would ever do this
Cuz it sets up the interview that's coming up on Ally
Which calls into question literally everything that's said in that interview
You would think
Yeah and it makes it tarnishes
Francis Boyle from
The jump because he
He doesn't correct
I'm waiting for Alex to be like the amino acid
Fly names
Time in India
At the 4th
Interesting glimpse
It's a fact that Alex recognizes
I'm probably have pretty much all along that Trump
I was having a Thor attarian strike
That's bad
Strong person in the Constitution. A strong man
Nothing you say means I need
That is a nonsense
Just
Bye-bye bye-bye bye-bye
He comes back from break and gets down to business and Francis Boyle
And
I'm here to tell you this Francis Boyle interviewees
Dragon
I was hoping for gold but apparently it's not
Pizza is not good if there is no information that really comes out of this
Yes there is
Nothing's it Francis Boyle has to say
It is groundbreaking
There is nothing
Vicki knows
And
He just seems like a guy who likes Infowars
Cool
So here is his main point
I think
That is outside of the stuff that
Alex's talked about
And it's trouble
These bsl-4 facilities
I have no legitimate
Scientific for
Medical purposes
They have one purpose and that is to research
Develop
Test
Used stock
Offensive
Truly offensive
They tried to justify
We're developing vaccines
Be true Alex
Bsl-4 is biosecurity level 4
And his main argument here seems to be set up like this
He believes that the coronavirus as a bioweapon that was released
From the Wuhan bio lab
Because he believes that all biosecurity level for labs exist to do is create offensive bioweapons
Although he admits in that very Clips they also do research relaxing
They claim that
That's why it's a girl baby true owl
The levels of biosecurity lab is subject to is related to the relative danger of the things that are study
Level one is four things that generally don't hurt people who are in good how
Level two
Four agents that have a little more dangerous side to them and they require slightly heightened precautions
Hepatitis or HIV
Level three is four things that could be
Contracted much
Easier and can often be transmitted in the air like SARS or yellow fever
Level four is the highest level because
The things that would be worked with their
Are specifically things
Is the containment as easily as level 3
They're also potentially deadly
Enter things for which we have no known treatments are vaccines
Past this would have included things like smallpox and Ebola
Level 4 labs are the levels they are because of the security protocols that are required to work with those age
It has to do with like the airflow in the lab and how that's
Controlled how waste is handled
Protective clothing and gear required by the research
That's what this designation mean
These things not like a ranking of loud like
People who work at bsl-4 is aren't like
Relationship
A scientist studying
Smallpox
So these
They're studying and working within level for labs whether you like it or not
Francis
Are things that could be a gigantic tri-tip
In the 20th century over 300 billion people died from
Smallpox
Is Dawning the conditions of level 4 biosecurity lab
It's unlikely that it would now be eradicated
Does boil can suggest all you want without proof
These biolabs exist only to create offensive bio biological weapons
But doesn't mean anything
They clearly
Servin end of import
Function
And without them
It would basically be impossible to do the sort of work that's required to come up with treatment and prevention
Diseases that could be
Plague
Agates
I just
What do you say doesn't make
It is it's
It's like it's like we don't have any ability to transfer
It's certain fears General generationally
You know like that
There's a generation
Who was so ravaged by smallpox
They would do
Anything and everything
Sing 2
Help get rid of that
And then once the disease is
Successfully at the very least mitigated
The next generation is like
You know smallpox
Fox isn't a big deal it's all bulshit that they're throwing out as we don't need to worry about this stuff
And everything they tell you about now it's back
Seems that are doing it and all that
One generation was all it took to rid the entire world of the fear of the reasonable fear
It's unfortunate
Also fun fact
Come back to earth from space
From places that are thought to have ever possibly had habitable environment
They have to be handled by a security level for labs
But I guess it's probably just
Because they're trying to make a space bio-weapon because the labs are perfect
Of the Earth's atmosphere would completely foreign things
That could be dangerous
They serve a number of birth
Being spotted
No real good standing
I don't really have any reason
But he might not have any reason to do anything
It's very unlikely that he has inside information
I'm passing I have no insight
But Alex has a sore
Unisource
Seems contradictory to all the things Alex has been saying already
Tell me we can have it whenever planning for us or others
Developing a vaccine but themselves
But somehow and they thought it was
So it would be
Continue editor Albert work and then it somehow mutated
They don't know
They can't believe it was an offensive weapon
They were developing a vaccine for that that's an accurate
But he believes that this is a false flag
Race specific bioweapon the
Government told on themselves to save face because
Heather being humiliated in the trade war in so they could do populated country
Aldi's various thoughts
Now Alex is saying that he's fake Pentagon sources told him this is a bioweapon that was being developed to be used
Us
The Chinese lab was creating a vaccine for that accidentally got out
This is a direct contradiction
Literally everything else you said on this episode
If the Chinese are making this bioweapon to use against
Us that kind of contradicts the race
Specific bioweapons.
Is that created the vaccine that kind of contradict
The goal of depopulating China
If it accidentally got out of the lab that contradicts itself about it being an
Intentional released by the Chinese government
This isn't a situation where Alex is considering multiple possibility
This is him within the span of a few hours pretending to credibly report
Entirely incompatible narrative
That's right these two things cannot both be true
Yeah one of them he's bich
Hard science
Quote on quote
And the other is not a theory
It's what is totally real Pentagon sources told
I'm very strong feeling that Alex is having a field day selling
The s*** off of the virus pan
He's creating
Because that he doesn't really give a s*** of the things he's saying about the outbreak are internally self-contradictory
It doesn't matter because his audience is very dumb
And they won't notice super glaring problems does narratives
Like this
Doll just building fear
He's willing to do it however you can
Cuz beer Translate
Flights directly into money
I will say that
You do not need to give me any information on boils
If all you did was play me a clip where Alex said that string of nonsense
And then he said
That's correct Alex
Then I'm like okay
Clearly everything is b*******
If you just say that
That's correct to Alex Jones regardless
Decisive move Will Smith isn't it I'm not going to say that's correct
What movie are you f****** talking about you give me all the
Information first
You might be you being led down a path
So Alex
Destocking to boil
Pretty clearly was that all he really has
Go on
Is that Indian paper that got retract
I think that's pretty clear here
Just remember
Major Indian Labs outside
The Hy-Vee delivery system welded onto it
Welded pressure that he'll US Government others won't send out
RNA sequencing
Because when they get that they look at it and even low-level abs and go home I God this is funny.
$3 bill
That's not accurate
And
So he does believe that the bsl-1 through 1234 likes
Be even BSL twos can see that this
Is bulshit lower-level Labs meeting with smaller universities
Alex wants to act like he's just operating officer
Protracted Indian paper roundly criticized
Fire other science
And
He wants to know what boil think
A wood boiler
That study when it came out
It was convincing to me including the pictures
Obviously I believe the Chinese government
Pressure on the Indian government to take
So it was taken now
That's based on
His thoughts
You asked me last time boil came up fuse inactive teacher and videos
And I wanted to get
I want to get a sense of what kind of
The teacher so I consulted the website rate
Professor where boil is received
2.7 out of 5
Too high
What reduces quote
Percy theorist but still a fun interesting lecture every time
Another
So quote
This is a great class if you want to get some credit and not have to go to class but the class itself doesn't have a lot of substance
Fair
Another reviewer says quote
This course teaches you nothing
I wanted to
This next one's sounds
Just about right
I learned nothing
Master of jurisprudence
Except a lot of tinfoil hat ranting about the pope and Duke
You use a mic in a small lecture hall then scream into it the entire class
Expect migraine
And worse than 1 hour
Bob belittling
Over questions with Noah
Don't expect
What actual legal philosophy or hist
It is really tough to get rid of it
The tenured professor is
Yep
That is the basic
I think you're also there a video Skype interview Alex and Francis
And his office looks like
A tornado just passed through it
Far be it for me to judge I don't keep a tidy house very well but his office is another level it looks like an episode of
Okay it should it's a red flag
Alex should go to audio
There's only one question
I want to know the answer
They're not hung book
Probably
Talking about the idea of race specific bioweapon
And
Francis Boyle believes they are real
You know you got the same source that Alex does
What's your point
Specific biological weapons
Yes we've tried to develop them here in the United States under the influence of the neocon
Who believed in these things that's
Teaneck record
Is just based on the project for Novak and Century document rebuilding America's defenses which does not
That these things are real
And again it was a justification
To increase the defense spending budget of the United States
Is an example of a hypothetical threat is evil in its own way
But not in the way they're portrayed
Interesting to be in this sensitive like Francis Boyle does believe
Music the same sources
Race or
Pacific bio-weapons do exist
Whoever does not believe that that is
True in this case
I was considering
Specific
Chinese abandon blacks are so different than that would not would conclude that
That is my conclusion Alex that's correct so I do
This is that
So a black person
It's not a race
I just
I just don't know how to handle people this.
Because this is a combination get stuff
This is one of those times where you see Alex being under
Musically
Stupid
And Eve
Yeah he is
Dumbest possible ship
Then we are also used
To sell in an evil way
And be a f****** bigoted nightmare I mean you should know that he feels a little bit bad about selling
Stuff I mean I don't want to care
Opportunistic
Oh
With very nanosilver the Pentagon
Homeland Security
Nope
You know what I've been selling it for years
Because I do want to find out whatever the best prawn
How do you feel opportunistic Alex is he going to show us like
The date that he started selling it now
Flashes up with the same information about the Civil War
You are opportunistic this is 100% opportune
Like this is a disgrace
And you're doing it with
I had talked to the owner and the founder
All that
And
They're just like you think we should keep mine works sell out what do you think we should do
I believe you should put everything you have
Probably real I don't tell my audience that what's weight
And sure enough unfortunately
You see this is a serious so it's good to be prepared
Infowarsstore.com and funds are independent Maverick operation
Oh wow magically
Magically sales
For my Patriot Supply
Hey you say worse
I want to feel happy
Find out this is
Real
Oh my God it's so it's so terrible
Great coincidence
It's for me at a time when I really need
Yeah it just works out
Clockwork
So Alex is talking to Francis Boyle and he still was on hold
Alex is selling his s***
Just disgraceful
You can't feel great about that
EXO goes back to boil
Like how bad is it
From your sources at the UN from your own research how bad is this
You had me so so cold
Computer game at
Johns Hopkins Bill Gates
Oh my God
Johns Hopkins center for the neocon to fully support
Biological weapons and even Essex Pacific
Biological weapons
You ate something app
Teaneck
Tabletop exercise which is really Awards
Resulted in 65 million deaths
Seems to be
As to where this started
Cheer
Madison Lee Spanish
Scenario
Here
To scare anyone or get anyone really
65 Million Dead
Best Buy. My problem is
I don't care what your motives are spoiled
Espousing things
You are being used as a tool to scare people whether you like it or not
It's interesting because
For the most part you know
Boyle is
Accused of being like
More less
What is conspiracy
Theories on the left side
Very similar information to comes to them
Whether it be from a left
Perspective
Perspective of conspiracy theory
Cuz he's using all of the
The same talking point is our
Write this is John's Hopkins
Tabletop exercise that we talked about the daz
Doctor did not real applicability to the actual outbreak that ended up happening
I'm sure after it
Like he's using these same touchdowns
The peanut document d
I'm all all the videos
The same is the same interpretation of the Indian study that was retracted
Using this Bill Gates Johns Hopkins
Tabletop exercise Baba
What did Patriots really weird
To me because
I mean he wants Trump impeached
Right
He has very different politics
Alex
They come together on
The conspiracies about a new world order or something
A bad Foundation doesn't really doesn't really matter what kind of
I guess
Point of view you have after
I guess not a bad Foundation is still going to crumble
Yep
It's suspicious that Trump isn't doing anything if there's bioweapon
But you must be in
I assume that's their angle right if it's not doing anything
These days.
How is Trump wrong give us the Nuance in praising G
President-trump
Advise that is a bioweapon
War
Turbocharged
I just don't believe he understands
Scientific advisors he has around them
But I thought you had Pentagon sources were telling
How does this track how does this make any sense
I was just pretending he has Pentagon sources that are feeding him this information about it being a bioweapon and all this s***
But somehow drops advisors just tell him
None of this none of this track
Text Trump
The smartest
Strongest most
Powerful most successful president
However it does seem like every time he wants to do something that Alex does like
He's been foiled
Right by an adviser or to a globalist infiltrator
Every time he wants to do something go
He's giving bad information
So
Point is like get rid of these biosafety level-4 Cruiser centers cuz
They're they're just attacked
There just for the day
Search
As well while we're at
So Alex
Wraps up the interview and now he's adopted that as his
Sort of talking point
Which is weird
This is just insane
We all have guns are houses in a safety
But they're not locked up right or somebody bad gets and then cause a problem that's okay
Did the few people get killed
Barbie and free
And overall the good outweighs the bad that we're free in empowering it's good
So this makes no sense
The argument Alex is trying to lay out here is that
As a man says they're working on vaccines and treatments in these bio lab
That's for the sake of Public Safety
And that's why you know you keep a condom
And you know those guns aren't handled appropriately people end up dying and that's just the cost of being free
The benefits outweigh the cost
How is that. Totally analogous to biohack
I don't understand
It security Protocols are followed strictly inappropriately some of this research
Campos a danger and in those cases it could result
Tried pretty hard to do
Dispute the fact that advancements in vaccine site have absolutely outweighed
The cost of any of this research
If you don't agree with that I would suggest you look into some of the conditions that don't exist anymore
They're basically nightmare disease
Alex can't even figure out how to be against
This s*** at this point
He wants to say it's a race specific bioweapon
The Chinese false-flag them
It was all about attacking these viola
Or disagree with Boyle and risk
Veneer of credibility he has acid expert
Is Alex disagrees with a boil he's no longer useful in any way to validate his narrative but Husker people need to be
And that's why they need to buy his product
So that is not an option
And US Alex at the now be against these BioLife
It's just a mess because I was just a pair and he has no idea what he's talking
About these are topics you can really just
When I imagine that if the biolabs
Made a gun that shot viruses lilacs would be in real trouble.
He be like I love these guns but I'm against these Labs I don't know so now boils gone
And Alex gets
Do what he really wants
To do which is
Rambo about the Bible
It's not fair
Written by some Hebrew
Divine Knowledge from
No God would say no I'll actually do it
I'll come down there I'll show you how it's done
Walk a mile in your shoes right now
Lit right now
In fact
I won't just physically take the torture in all of it
I will take
All of the San Tan
Do that
Metaphysically then can forgive you
LKQ on
Because that's how the universe works it's energetic
God's Got to Be
Sacrifice
Between the two
TuneIn because you can't have new Freewheel creatures given that much power you are going to mess up and do evil stuff
But they just got to make the spiritual decision to go with God
And then God will cheat the rest away to take us out
No
At this level
Over there
You know
Indescribable
Businesses in this isn't just like
The simplification people here in all this
But there's a lot of rebellion going on against the nature of the universe
So this is the guy that anybody who's listening wants to take
Cues on science
I think that's good I just text wise you shouldn't even take
Cues on religion
This is such the same thing of like
I don't think anybody hates
The Constitution more than Alex Jones Melissa
The book of Joe is like 90%
You don't know why I do a goddamn thing so don't ask me that's the whole book
He's right
So Alex
Birds talking about Trump
Same bullshitted
That speech
Alex is still really
And he's like hey it's
It's great that he said it and you get these
Highfalutin Southern Baptist Christian
They're all against swearing
This is nonsensical
A lot of family lot of great people and I love Southern Baptist but
They'll tell you a cuss word is worse
Abort the baby
Wine
Then they will about aborting a baby
Salina family
And it's a Holiness they have a bottle
Talk to your f****** family then
I don't know who these Southern Baptist are who are
I don't know
He's just complaining about his family
Eddie White the bulshit thing
Becomes a little bit of a theme
And Alex starts talking
Etymology
And I think you might be a little off bulshit comes from
And it's pretty great okay let's hear the Bible doesn't say using
English before the Norman to cover
Hamilton thousand years ago
For the Vikings took over England
They came in a band the entire language
Bubba socks
It was only the
The cuss words
The continued on the plastic things people say
Like
Bulshit
They found two thousand-year-old
Plastic shades
Something is
Call something
What are the weird reason I had
But yes
2000 year-old Anglo-Saxons
Damn
2000 year old Anglo-Saxon
It's linguista Tracy origin of the word bulge
1950s
TS Eliot poem the Triumph of b*******
What time is it
The Anglo-Saxon even after the time of the Norman invasion
There's some suggestions that the word Bullhead connotation with the idea of something being gone
But that's most likely due to the old French word for fraud which is
I very strongly think that Alex is making
You should up Dre make it seem more important
Trump said b*******
Speech is he's really really hung up on
So Alex is really convinced that it's Old English stuff and somehow about Free Speech issues or something I don't know
But he really gets
Excited about this
And he ends up working himself up into a frenzy where he swears
And they have to cut it out of the bus
Is a lot of sounds good then that friend good work
Describe the two
A lot of different meaning
What you got
I'm going to
That was a great
It's got a lot of meetings it's a nice word that was a great
We didn't do anything about
50 million
So good all day
What a lucky
It's like what they used to bleep out the whole in a******
What's so great about that is it I didn't edit
That's how the show came out
It so clearly the delay recognize
Alright Alex is on a rant about how he's going to use swearing
Because president did we can't do that
Man
What address
That's funny
Strongly enough
To capture Alex
Feelings
He loves
The Trump said b*******
Is the enemy
Not the president
Using Old English
Thousand years old
Norman nobility
Jordan 1
Anglo-Saxon wee Scottish but even gets it more
That is the sexiest thing I've seen a while
Politically
F****** insane
I thought there's no bottom and somehow this bottom is even weird
Trump saying b******* is the sexiest
Do we live in 2020
I want to live elsewhere
I want to listen
I don't know 2,000 years ago with my other Anglo-Saxon Brothers dad
Notable at all
These calls something
Absurd but I think he thinks
True
And Sarah
Anna Lane
I appreciate you
3 minutes 4 minutes
He said he took 30 calls
He probably took five.
I think he thinks he took 30 calls
Nitrogen even cut a clipper
I just thought I'd guy who cares I'm really give a s***
Before this show take 40
I do like the perception that he's getting a lot more done
Which may be Universal he's not
Just rewriting world events
But his own events as well
Yeah in that he's in the middle
Is there he lives in
Hayirli fictional life
And he should be in hell and I home
Or somewhere to help him the last quote from February 7th
This Friday show
Up to this point we seem like
Real indication
Irresponsibly and possibly
Against regulations
Selling of
Yeah and I think the
This clip
He's dead to rights
He is breaking advertising
In laws
While the same time your family is a 360win
We have
Charmaine 16oz Super Silver
Nano silver
It is
Sold out we have the 10 pops lr3 I'm still available to be sold out at current rates my week and a half
This is the most explicit I've seen where he's talking about a condition
And a product
Which are the two constituent pieces that you need
To be making a healthcare
I
From everything I've read up on and I understand about how the FDA
This is a breach
And now he needs to notify the FDA and he has 30 days to stay with that claim
So this needs to happen there's this
It's on
Fathomable to me
That he would be
So wiped out financially by his misconduct
It's with
Sandy Hook
Situation
And then
Claw his way out of it by
Illegally selling products
No it doesn't make sense
And that's why I cannot be allowed to happen
He needs to be stopped
Since is f***** up I would have to stop there and we have an episode about the seven
Development of Alex specific bio-weapon
In for it cuz our genome is all the same
Woo
Willow
What the f***
Is that sad that's a departure
Normalizing the discussion
A hypothetical release of biological
This is totally unacceptable
But then I saw that he did this emerging
Broadcast on the 8th
Yeah and
This
Is
Wild
Stop
And my friend
We are here with you on
Saturday
Afternoon with an emergency
Broadcast
President Trump announce
Science advisor who heads up major federal
Anthony
Fauci
Did they are investigating
The novel Coronavirus
Out of China
As
A man-made biological weapon
And they called for other
Scientific Institute
And the general
Scientific community
And the media
To look into that
So this is a story that has one source
And it's Zero Hedge
Which is really going on the leading end
Spreading false information about the Coronavirus
Cousin being kicked off Twitter after accusing
Chinese scientist
Creative
Wonder if they're getting any AD revenue from my page
I don't know
Anyway I'm not even going to ever listen to zerohedge so I checked out their site
And I wanted to find their source
On the story
Resources in ABC News article at the headline quote
White House ask scientist
Investigate origins of Coronavirus
Important note
This is not breaking news that requires an
Saturday show for Alex
This article is published
February 6th
Which was Thursday
Prior to his Friday show
You have no idea this even happen to know what his insurance on the Zero Hedge article
Just a shity process for a news Outlet
The first paragraph
This ABC news story is this
Thursday asked you a scientist to medical researchers to investigate the scientific origin
Novel Coronavirus
As misinformation about the outbreak spreads online
That doesn't sound like you're coming out
Sayings is the bioweapon but I guess that's
It certainly is
To lie we that that is
That should have been
That should be very obvious that the article about how information is being spread
Disinformation
Being spread is used
Of course to spread this
Naturally
This article is literally about the director of The White House Office of science
The technology policy Kevin
K
Droga Meijer
Being worried about the that retracted Indian paper which quote had shown the urgency for accurate information about the
Genesis of this outfit
This guy was worried
About have this paper which was deeply flawed and retracted
It resulted in The Barrage of misinformation
I want to make sure that the National Academy of Sciences was able to answer the questions people had
Would you let them
Except
Play flogging retract
The paper is
Accurate
Important to keep in mind that paper is one of Oz only sources for the claims that he makes
The bioweapon
The only thing close to helping Alex is there this year which is coincidental either
The part of that ABC News article that zerohedge quote
It's from dr. Anthony fauci
The director of the National Institute of allergy and infectious diseases
He's asked
Quote about concerns that stem from misinformation
Online that the novel Coronavirus
Engineered or deliberately released
His response is
Quote
There's always that concern
What are the things that people are doing right now is very carefully looking at
Sequences to see if there's even a possibility
Likelihood
But that's going on
You could ultimately determine
Two people looking
Now the focus
To do about what we had
That would be something that scientist
Would rule out guy would say that
However there's a big difference
Between what he's saying
And Alex has a decision
It is definitely is Iowa
He absolutely has determined for sure it's been proven
Check the papers
This article is about a White House official calling for a meeting of experts to collaborate largely inspired by the flood of missing fur
Formation
Do the Indian paper that is the basis for Alta
In essence
This is about the White House wanted to push back on the very thing that Alex is engaging it
How many write a twisted version of this article and zerohedge
Then decided to do an emergency show on Saturday about it
Declare victory
While I'm telling you we need to start this media Consulting so here's what we're going to do we've got this
Consulting firm
Just
And what'll happen is anytime a journalist calls look
Looking for a quote
The scientists will then call US
And they'll say here's my reasonable response
Do this question
And then I will say
Do not say that
Strike absolutely do not say that that is that is a very reasonable response
But they are going to go nuts with it
No right in that article there's two things going on the 1st is the main point
Of the article is about this K drug
Who's the head of the office
Science and Technology
He's the one who's called for scientists
To get together and work on this
Sure information like an evil globalist
Anthony fauci is unrelated
To that he's just another person that ABC News Consulting
Sephora,
But
He is the person
Who is quoted in
Zerohedge article
Because he has comments that are closer
To what the narratives they want to push off
The best entire article is about Anthony fauci
And he is the one
Who called for the scientist to
This is funny this is actually really funny
It's sad but it's funny
And yes we got the lighthouse
Main spokes
The main scientists
President
Prompting a
Appoint him like John P holdren Obama did
The Genesis to call for population reduction
Not
Anthony
Fauci
How to use the chief
Science advisor
Anthony fauci is the director of the National Institute of allergy and infectious
This disease is Chief
Science advisor
The correct he's just someone who was interviewed
Provide a little extra today ABC News article the person in the White House
Science
Technology policy
But Alex doesn't Nova
Because he read
Only knows what was in the zerohedge article
And they don't mention that dude
They don't mention the office of Science and Technology policy dude they only talk about fauci because like I said
He's the one who's closest
Sister their narratives
Also Trump didn't appoint Anthony fauci
Any position at all
He's been in the National
Institutes of Health Center 90
Are you going to have the national
Institute of allergy and infectious
Diseases something 1984
As long as I've been alive
He was given the presidential medal of freedom in 2000
84 fucksake man look I'm sure this dude's doing a great job
Get him out of there
Get him out of there I saw some pictures of me looks I'm sure he is
Trump did appoint the guy who's the head of the office of science
The end that guy
K drug
He's his main science advisor
But he is not Anthony fauci
Alex has no idea what he's talking about cuz he doesn't prepare and he just does bad work
Also
John P holder invited
Call the Scions are but his official title was
You guessed it
Director of The Office of Science and Technology policy
Exactly the same as his other dip
Nothing Alex says means any
But it's really fun really fun
Answer so glaring
I had such a real bummer the whole
Like windstar's be
His second term
I got here about czars all the
God dammit
Editorialize has a little bit about antifa
Just so far
It's so funny
And I found
Always
Where it came from
Because it's
Very unusual
I read you all the comment from the ABC letters
That is a grave Miss
Characterization of his comment
I don't know if it was
I don't even know if he was a depressed
As it reads in the article it just seems like they called correspondent from ABC News asked
I don't know I don't know if that's true
I think I was just making this s*** up
Which makes it funny
He says things like this
I just got a point out
What we've reported
What are guests of reported
And
I mean
Ashley to the numbers
Because we don't
Stuff up we really working
Around the Clock
Try to bring the bus info
ABC News article would have taken you three minutes to read if you didn't do that
You just read something on zerohedge was like okay fine I was find out where this came from
Dumbass don't think I've ever seen
Terminal case of dunning-kruger
But
I think this is going to get him
So this is really funny man because
Okay so he's building this up that he thinks
Anthony fauci
She is the main science advisor the drug that needs
Call Eddie's Blowin the whistle he saying this is Mandy
No no
At this is not a name it is ever come up on the show before
This is not somebody that Alex has ever cared about but it turns out Alex has been a long time
Now let's look at the facts
President
Medical spokesperson
Mulatto calls about
Legend
A quote for respect
Call Roberto
This is ridiculous
I just so sad like this
You you see this
And you see like Ugh
A teenager bluffing a booklet
This is totally a teenager
Absolutely Jesus Christ
Dodging having to do work behaviors are being manifested here but the stakes are very high
He has a tunnel listener that he's misleading about his products in order
Cell
Silver Inn
Buckets
But it's still really funny
The way he's acting
Oh man
The way he's acting is funny the consequences
Not so much
It's it's
He's so f****** confident he's so goddamn confident and something that is
Entirely fictional it's so easy to see through
Take the second
Yeah just read the ABC
It's very funny
So
Alex
I want to I want to play this
CLEP because
I think this is really purr
Perfect
Inspiration
The shity game Alex
Let's Plays with headline
There's a deadline
Infowars.com
If coronavirus was bioengineered
Even ABC News
With the
The same
Deadline White House
Scientists investigate Origins
Coronavirus
Amy
See
You see how hear how the game is played
Alex's headline from Infowars is just a repost
The article from zerohedge
A little spinner
Intuit
With added implication
Houses specifically interested in investigating
That's an unfair reading of the actual article but it's in line with the Zero Hedge
Zero Hedge article is based on the ABC news story which
It's misrepresenting by only focus
Morning distorting
The quote from Anthony fauci
In order to
Create their spin
You have this base story
From ABC News which has been added by zerohedge
Does that reposted with added spin by Infowars
And now Alex is reporting on that story on his show
Add credibility to his stories as even ABC News is reporting on this
It points to the ABC News article that was the basis for the zero head story
And secondarily for his own
This entire story is just propaganda spinning an ABC news story for their own purposes
Little weak to them say the ABC News even agrees that's on that
An honest Outlet wood
Just cover the ABC News article directly and accurately
And then if we wanted to give added Focus to fauci
Peter welcome to do that inappropriate
What's Zero Hedge
And Alex are doing is
Clayton Bowl
And I say that much like Trump
To indicate that this is serious
If you want to see how blade this s*** is
Consider this
No longer
Can
The Tail Wag the Dog
Here we are
Reporting on it first
Again
ABC News ass because they
Can't cover
This
Anymore
The ABC News article is the source for the zerohedge article which Alex's reported
He's pretending he put this article.
Stop covering up and report on this
Brazen
Are you going to see the dates on stuff
It's not this is absolutely disinformation
Nothing like you just watch this
Rogue
It's horrific
Yeah
God
Damn now this is really great soda practices really great
Because Alex
You can very clearly see that he thinks
That his actions
Cause this ABC News article
How bad it really is
Where it's going
What truck should do
Dr. Boyle
Action investigators man-made
5 hours later his head size comes after the press conference
Not saying we did that
I told the auto
Horn
To your own hard cuz there's a problem with this Theory
That interview with Francis Boyle happened on February 7th
He's trying to pretend that in response to that interview ever
Call the White House and then drop by the science expert announced they were investigating his by weapon
Leaving aside the truck.
DC news article he's basing that narrative on his publishing February 6th
This article predates houses interview with Francis Boyle
It's just a pathetic display of narcissism
Embarrassing
I asked to be wrong about basic
Details
The
Saxons were invaded by the North Sea
Get ready
Okay cuz we're about to
Dogs has a guest
The joining us on this emergency
Saturday
But few minutes while I was ranting
What should we hit
First
Approximation is you been the most active
It's over for Humanity
Saturday weather
So
Alex's Mike Adams
Most accurate player in the game right
Here's what he has to say
First of all
Anyone in the
Tech industry or the mainstream media
That is pushing censorship
Of those about
Who are telling the truth about
Those organizations are
Complicit
In the deaths
That are going to continue to occur
Even outside
They are in
Rooting for the virus
By the nine people
We need in order to
To be safe
Be prepared
To self isolate
To avoid joining
Crowds
Stay off the cruise ships and all the things
The people need to do to stop
Spread to the left-wing media wants
To spread
So now the stakes of him getting back on Facebook or if you don't let me back on Facebook
You on the side of the Coronavirus
I I will take that challenge Mike
Please self
Isolate
Put yourself
In a small
I just said grow up
I know you want back on Facebook this is getting embarrassing
The Tantrum so
Alex and him talked about like you know like
These people are created these bio-weapon
Baby peoples
Who killed them
Start over but
I'm not trying to act
I was breeding
If you kill a million people in my garage and who I was doing it
I'm not disturb
I'm just at a point
I'm just the default is
People making race-specific wepa
Stop
Is already outlawed.
Do it
Or mom's going to come and Lynch her
It needs to stop
So I mean of course I would agree with him that if people are creating race specific bioweapon
They should be put on trial for
I don't think it's healthy to
You know do a show where you're saying that anybody who's researching
Zyxi this secretly trying to create offensive race specific
Bob's are going to come get you
That's a nonsense if even for him that
It's predicted because what's
Okay so then we get to that line again
Okay well what's the level of
Ulric weapon that deserves a
Sherpa should Oppenheimer be hung
How about f******
Smith & Wesson
What's the f***
Yeah
Real logistical
Concerned
Appointees
Applying legal to kill science pretty seriously saying that
So Mike Adams is really dumb and
A lot of his information is really stupid
And one of the things that you can really tell
Love that by
Is things that he's site
Here's a prime
Neil Ferguson of
Imperial College London
Is now
Out there estimated
Contractions per day
It's not mine
I don't really care what Neil Fargo
Some things about the Opera
One guy who's been a past Infowars gas
Suspicious
If he said that's correct Alex that he's already done in my book
Second he's a professor of humanities
With a degree in history
Austrian philosophy
He hasn't a real standing here is an expert some naturally he's the sort of person like exciting as an expert on
Virologia net
Epidemiology
Virus expansion rate
Niall Ferguson has no standing here
He's not somebody who usaitis Annex
Expert in public health issues
But he's a pastor in forwards gas
And
You saying what they want
Somebody to say
The Imperial College
Go fuc yourself
Gifts like Niall Ferguson
Come here and not just that
If it's
It's not you can't have
A day
What would happen if you have 50
50000 a day and then 50,000 the next day and then 200,000 and then a million and then we'd all be f******
If you talkin 50,000 new cases
Per day
That's going to progress geometrically in a way that is
Impossible.
That's not a thing
Ferguson he's a professor of History so
So he's watched
So you're wrong
That's it just a really good example of like
Who cares
What you're saying
Who cares I'm not I'm not going to take that seriously
Events
It's just all over the place
Everything is flawed all of their primary sources all of their data is useless
The death rate
Is 6:45
17%
What type of layout he
Here in a minute
China has admitted it
Prescott
Accidentally
The Neil Ferguson's asked
Professor Ferguson
Is estimates a fifth
The day
Translate
To 7005
500 death
A day
I believe what he's talkin about is that tencent website glitch
The revelation of this
Higher mortality rate. Neil Ferguson
Humanities
Professor prediction
It's not worth wild so that those are the two pieces sofa
Over the next
E-waste
Because it takes
Time for people who are in
It's a start.
Spread rate
And that and the infection rate and the death rate
83%
Infection rate for those work
Supposed
15% mortality rate
Set study
Lancet study was not applicable to the general population that was a study of people who presented with
Sample size
You're already dvorak's
Stream cases
Not applicable to the general population
Mike Adams is not dealing with this data responsibly
It's in the rain
Little bit higher 17%
Remember the leeks
Data that came out of China where they had the second
Database
Show the real numbers for
For a few minutes
It's knocking from
Again that's just the tencent website
Glitch that
Confirm
Second set of data
So bulshit none of the stuff they're saying means anything
Yeah
I don't like that it seems like this
The only way they have
It does seem like that wow mean they're making money
That's fair
Earlier in the show
And on the 7th
Alex has been suggesting that they won't send out the RNA pattern or the sequence
Because if they do people will look into it and I'll find ohmygod there's a Franken virus
The people have it.
True everywhere not true at all you could probably get
Get a copy if you ask for
Search that guy's Twitter friend probably find it
Anyway
That's not true
So now you have to like Mike Adams
Can't make that claim
Because he knows
But his own websites probably published
Pieces Of Eight
It's nonsense
Call Anton I got to move the goalposts
Why won't they send out samples of the viruses
Well
Because you put that when you pull in your f******
Draculaura is like
If they did you would criticize them for doing
Why are they allowing these samples to be taken wherever
It's it's
They get you coming and going no matter what you do
They're going to complain about the only way to get rid of it is with bleach they be like
Told you all along but now you shouldn't drink please
Because they've been secretly putting the virus inside what about us people who are made of ammonia
The bleach
China has not released samples
Of this
Actual virus
Where's the physical Barse released
The data about
Physical samples
However
Any animations
North Korea
10 human volunteers to the region
Don't get infected
They can bring it back
They can Harvest it from their saliva
Good thing
It's under lockdown terrorist
Man
He believes terrorist over there and then I'll get it make egg yolks
Yeah
A******
Virgins these Islamic terrorists get
For blowing themselves up
Probably bonus virgins out there if they
In fact all of New York City or something
Sing with this virus
I don't know how they
System works
You know they're insane
Are they think they're going to
Get rewarded
It's now
Guess what they've been handed a new way to do that
It's a whole new vector
Super easy
Releasing United States
CDC will not be able to contain that
When that day comes
This is exactly the same things they said about ebola is an exactly the same thing they said about all of these
Public Health
At Wendy's
Stopping terrorists
Spreading it like it's
This is just standard boilerplate s***
We're screwed
A screw you because the right is getting
Too good at
Did you hear that
Indefinitely
He thinks he's
He's great virgin aumix or whatever
Clever man
I remember being an open Mike's 20 years ago in that was funny
So Mike has other big news though that did feeds into this the sense of panic that everybody should be
Feeling and
It's b*******
We're getting reports of
Mass
School closure
Are they shutting down
An entire camp
This is all across America right now
Get tonight
Brightwell
The school wait we weren't they never shut down
School systems
Just because some kids got sick
Now suddenly there
School closings
Happening the shutting down the whole campus
I don't know when he was in school or
You know I don't care
Really
Most likely happens every year schools closed during
Flu season every school district
It's not every city
You can Google it very easily and find articles
Year by year by year about schools closing
Because of an outbreak of the flu at the school
It's all the time
Like Mike is a f****** a****** pretending
It's unheard of schools closing because of the flu
Because it helps them pushes bullshittin areas
This is this is deeply Disturbed Behavior
We need a government program
The Truman Show these
I'm saying we need to isolate them we need to build actors around them so they feel safe
Problem with this plan
I don't want to watch that show that's true
Yeah
So it seems like we just keep them
All their information is just dogshit it's bad
Noah Atwood
So stupid
This is insane
But there's also a level of the
Rank narcissism
Flying around
We should have you back
Back on the regular Sunday show in the Monday show tomorrow to really break this down options
Clearly listening
That is a reference back to him believing
Interview with Francis Boyle
ABC News article that came out prior to the interview
This is
Lunacy
Anyway
Jesus despite them being wrong about everything
Every
Everything literally everything
Even their own describe
The things that they know to be true despite all that
I don't have some
Where to man
With a great crew of men and women behind us
Do you hate we have research what
We're saying
Somebody at 5
Thousand years ago on the tribe then I'm saying
I just saw shiftplanning out there they got wet
Everybody know what
Why are you tell the truth lyrics by the tribe that's always told
Tell the truth
A few times but
I think it's our weapons
To get ready that's a little lighter in Cry Wolf person gets up
You know thrown off a cliff
Don't get out of town but when
They get ready
Just landed decided to leave
The point is the ships are landing
This looks really bad
We hope it isn't as bad as it looks
We're not going to lie to you and tell you what we're saying
I would love to have
Was Alex's confidence about his own
He doesn't recognize that he's been wrong about everything everything
How many probably does but you can't
Let that show your ass a little bit
The problem is
Even if he does Rick
Recognize that he doesn't know the real
Truth which is that he's wrong about
Everything
Even if he knows he's wrong about most of it
He still thinks he's right about at least a few things
Diablo's few things he needs to be disabused of the notion that they are true
Everything is fixed
Sitting here saying that
Hitman
Two dudes telling it like it is
You don't ever talking points
You know what you're talkin about
Sure you don't call them. There's Zero Hedge
That's those are your talking points
You do have talking points
Pinpointer wood
Everett is that will help you sell
F******
Whatever it is that can be sold
Yeah they're bullet points on a sales exact with you
Yelp
This ends with about 15 minutes of Alex doing
Sales pitch
They're done talking about the coronavirus nonsense
For now and then
The Alex and Mike have
A little bit of a discussion about to Trump's firings of kernels
Another abusive
It's a retaliatory thing that you know you should have protection.
Okay I can't get it off
Morcar ball thrown at him
And
Because he's a symbol of nationalism populism he's at his best
Last week
Tennessee
And you agree with that
How is the Deep state
Just right back now
There's
Baddie fired
Veneman in the Ambassador sondland.
Should be the tip of the ice
He needs to talk about
He needs The Purge anybody that's been Soros anybody else any ocon
Anybody
Left us because they're all
Play they're all
Committed to evil
There's no way they're not going to keep sabotaging
Trump finally asked
Again
The political parties
Executive
He has a right to clean house
This is the Trump we've been waiting for
To not only prayers although
Those Traders
Sandeep Staters and drain that swamp
It's time to lock her up
So that's cool I mean if
Trampoline
Do something more extreme
Dherbs
Shoring up our clearing out
Descent
Within the government
Eddie on
Any critical voices
Let's say it's good to know that Alex and Mike Woods
See that is the Trump we've been waiting for us as we all know Alec
A student of her
Love's ahead he knows that when an autocratic leader surrounds himself with nothing but yes man it works
Good things happen
The works well things happen
All I hear is him saying he's very excited
For a peaceful transition of power in Suwanee
These fiery
Sure
It might look like retaliation
People who testified against
No he just said they were
Coach
Might look like
But it's just because they were deep state
They were deep stain telepurte
When is this is the beeps
This is the anti-American Bing remove this is a cancer being removed
And the Ambassador and All of Me removed
They're like the president
Can't do that so he can't
Far he wanted his own Administration
Look dude
Deep state
It was like a visit
Human Coronavirus
In trouble again here's a job
Leprosy
Remax bike
Using real trash
Anybody Trader ex post facto the moment he does something you don't like
He's been deep State all along
Over the course of this couple days is like a real
Pivot
In the coronavirus narrative towards
Like the it's now definitively at the bioweapon that probably race-specific China buy beef
Volkswagen themselves but if it's the United States
But it's just payback for Fentanyl and it's totally ethical for
Supposed to do that that's super weird
Our stocks
Francis Boyle NES disorder backpack
This is all very troubling stuff
It's
I don't like I don't like where it's going I don't know where
Emgo
We saw on
The last episode
Democratic Party
That's still in there too
The backburner cuz Alex needs to push all the stuff
I'd sell the product
New pet
All right here's my new idea
We write up some templates
Alright
And if you can plug
Trump into one of these templates
Then you know it's bad because these are s*** written by grbl
And Pro stalinist in Putin as did all of these people and if you can just put Trump in there than we know
No it's a bad idea right I mean simp
It's been I think people have done this
It's worked right
OSHA
I feel weird
Maybe it's
I know it was tough
Little lame it's getting laborious that Alex won't stop coming up with new lies that he's reading on zerohedge
About to Coronavirus
I think
If nothing else
Anthony fauci stuff
I think it's hilarious
That's just
You didn't need to make that live as another one of those lies where he said it was 30 guys and
Fighting off three guys that still an amazing thing you can just see three as we don't
Hopefully the next episode of the
Coronavirus related unless the sales
Out of all that stuff I think we might be able to Black Studio surgery with
We will see
We do have website its knowledge right.com
Rosemont underscore fight and at go to bed Jordan
We are ya
Ron Facebook
Facebook
Download the show please go to
ITunes
Astrolabe so whatever donate
Omniome Leo I'm dzx Clark
English swear words
Holding
Alex