Air Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as if through the good guy
Stripe.com
Everybody around technology beverages
Talk a little bit about what's going on with that weirdo Alex Jones
We are the weirdos talk about that weird
Which one of us is weird
I have a question
Sing for you though
Lustration
Can't get enough of you received a valentine as an adult
Probably yeah but I mean
I mean when did when do you become an adult
What was the last time you got a valentine
I know it's been awhile
Probably probably while
In relationships
The past there been like little vallon
I consider when you say Valentine I really think of
It's like it has to be something that you're not
Seeing the person
You know what I mean it has to be someone who you're not in a relationship
Okay
I feel like in school
I'd always rather context of you being in a relationship it was just
You give the whole class everybody everybody got a valentine yeah
Burleigh's hopefully
High school and it evolves
Do like they're people you can buy roses from
I don't know
Valentine giving his always
Struck me as a little weird
I put too much
Kintore interest
Bedtime
I got a nice card from a girlfriend 10 years ago
I've gotten an adult balance
No no no never I mean a card
I've always thought of a valentine
Right
Valentine
Bro you're really materialist
That's what I'm about money in the thing
Every kiss begins with Hallmark is what I say
It seems like it's definitely something that is
More of
More less relevant
Yeah
It's a less relevant guy in adults
Do not care
And also I know a lot about Alex
And I don't know anything about either
Write Jordan so today we are still in the present
Because this s*** quiet while we're going over February
And a little bit of a temper
20/20 of Dance
Dammit and that's
The Sunday show and a little bit of Monday Monday is not very
Sunday is fascinating
And I'm excited to get that
For you do
You take a little moment
Love it
Thank you Emily l
Text Oliver thank you so much too and I hope I was wrong
Oliver
Next Charlie spelled
Charley thank you so much and I'll probably walk
Thanks about 2 and I'll probably walk
Expat
Text Lindsay thank you so much
What's your now policy walk
Can you very much Lindsey
Xblue thank you so much and I apologize
I don't do it
I was I was assuming you were going to go towards David eating and
David Icke
Neckband thank you so much you're now about what you want
Thank you Ben
I'm fine lyrics I think you're somebody don't even own elevated level we appreciate that very much
Crab thank you so much you are now it's
Technocrat
Money off that heroin
Are you pimp so good
Freakishly large
Claire
Absolutely
Dot-com click the button that says Sports sure we would appreciate it very helpful thank you so much everybody
Like a sporting show and just said this in a while but we are a little less than
Two months behind
Donation to shout out
Since there's just
Very little way we can figure out how to give people shoutouts
Without
Wheatley dragging the show to thank you so much
Thank you
Very very much
Nice to everyone
I also think I got to thank you to listen to her who reached out to me
Maybe because they gave me a little bit of a correction
Hourly pointed something out that I got wrong and I need to make a little correction about our last episode
So on our last episode I responded to Mike Adams citing a stat
From Neil Ferguson
About the Coronavirus
Break and I made an incorrect
Because there's someone named Neil Ferguson who's come on Alex's show a bit in the past and he's from the UK
Recently written an op-ed about the Coronavirus
I assumed
That was the Neil Ferguson that Mike was referring to
As this listener ironically named Alex pointed out there is another Neil Ferguson
Who is an actual Public Health
Expert from Imperial College London
I apologize that I got that wrong
So because I dismissed
The claims that were made based on believing them to come from a humanities
Professor it's only right that I take a look at them now given that they're supposedly coming
From someone whose opinion
Is a little more valid on the subject
A couple of important qualifications here are that Ferguson's number is
And in the interview where he expresses this estimate he also says that they don't know enough
T-shirt
Even if there are as many cases as he is estimating
He's also very specifically talk
Talking about people who come down with very mild forms
Do the virus
Who may not even know they have it and may not even be contagious
In the interview Ferguson doesn't get into the modeling too much explain how his essay
Has reached
Also notably
He's not freaked out about
And it's almost a side thought in
In the conversation
It's not even
Something that's nailed onto much but it's the piece of the conversation that is
Taken an amplified
All over the
Play yeah
Even if what Ferguson is estimating is accurate
Which he's not even
Concretely
He's saying
It doesn't justify the way Mike Adams was using
That figure
Mike took that 50000
The new infections number that Ferguson was estimating
And he connected it with the fifth
Percent mortality rate from the Lance
Set study
To say that China would be looking at 7,500 deaths a day
The cases that were part of Fergus
Zestimate were largely very mild cases and not the ones that would lead to
Two deaths where is the Lancet study was a breakdown of 41-page
Presented
Already having pneumonia
So those are
Inappropriate use of these two
In another article
Open February 10th in the telegram
Ferguson said
Quote or estimate
Well subject too much uncertainty due to the limited data currently available
Suggest that the impact of the unfolding epidemic maybe comprable to D major influenza pay
Pandemics of the 20th century
Is this a swine
To say that it is a serious public health issue
Issue but it's not enough
Ellipticals at the way Mike Adams at
I'm trying to use
Ferguson's estimates Disturbed
Anyway I apologize for mixing up in Healdsburg
I made a little bit of a hasty assumption based on a familiar name popping up
I'll be sure to be more careful about that
The future
Point Still Remains unfair one of those Neal Ferguson's needs to release
Vanquish their bread
Citizenship
Otherwise we will be confused forever name and I would say that
Brother been on Infowars
Anyway I just wanted to get that out of the way up top because
Perfect bungled a little something.
And also thank you to listen or Alex
Disappointed that I really want
Appreciate
So we start here on February 9th
And
I should say that
Prior to this
Clip
The show started
And it started with
The band 311
Alex, please don't like them
Reggae dancehall.
Much like I did on the last episode 11
Play some 311 music and Alex
Is having a tough time okay
Well well well ladies and gentlemen on Alex Jones your host
To be reduced to clarify even further
The 311 plays
Then there's silence
And then we get this Star Wars music
Garden Show at the beginning of the next
Everything we do here
Not starting the show
And that's just the way it is
H-E-B over the years
Broadcast
Art with music accounts line
Worse
Bringing pina coladas
Just woke up the Garden of Eden before the start
We'll just makes me
That's what the real
Future
Acumen
Civilization
311 is it
Okay that's where we are right now alright
When I was a little younger but
I don't this is Nova react
I do hate 311 specifically you heard me I was singing along with Fascination Street before
We started the show
Cover of Love song I Will Never
Forgive them for
So Amber Amber is the color of your energy
Perrigo 800
Hater
Hate 311
Yep
Dna2 work beautiful disaster
I don't even like that you know three of
Hi
For a while speculators younger
Love it
I don't know if I ever I think those timelines are off
I don't think those timelines are accurate though cuz I think I
Might have like 311 road before
I was old enough that I was smoking weed
The podcast where we get to the bottom
Throws Alex off
Except where he has to restart the show over again which is
Awesome
Anyway Alex gets into talking about
You know his main story 04
The Coronavirus
Natural law
Easy getting into it a little bit but
Thankfully
Please not the main focus
It's of a ton of vascepa
That's good we will get other topics
To discuss sold out of
You know you got to kind of think of that might be
It's nice to have some other topics to talk about but of course
He has to keep that ball in the air yes to keep juggling it
So you touches on it a little bit
I'm obsessed with the coronavirus because it is man-made
And they're acting really sneaky about it
They're not just doing this martial law thing
Precedent nnn get and get
I scared
Oh don't be scared but we've got martial law in place
And the unit prison she's paying for killing people in the street to check
Wind
So
Double quick points on
Beside life
Alex is obsessed with
The virus because he's seeing a drastic increase in his sales
He's already said that his immune gargle sold out and if you go to my
My Patriot Supply website they're saying they'll eat 12 times in Greece order volume
Now naturally not all those sales are coming
Alex since they also sponsor pretty much all of the big right-wing alarm
It's clear that Alex's share the sales are rising
To any government that decides to enact martial law
Probably does
Don't care too much about their being
Your president that's kind of silly
Also this fails to take into account the quarantine cities already has a long
In 2014 the city of human in China was put into lockdown after a man there died of the bubonic
McPlay
During the SARS outbreak in 2003 while they did
Quarantine a whole city
Canada quarantine over 30,000 people in Toronto even though they only had 250 probable cases
Of the virus
The experts don't believe that
Strictly enforced large-scale currencies are the best way to deal with outbreaks but also they really
Stop a country from doing
If there were some International ban encore
Leaving Alex
Who claimed that it was a globalist
Infringing on a country Sovereign right to lock down a city
If they wanted to so it really is all just not
Can you imagine if governments listen to
Experts that would be hilarious being insane world we live
International Health regulations
The countries is
Agreed to
But the issue is
That they are not enforceable
So the first thing
About that
There's no evidence
You can find that the video involving
The electric woman who'd been shot
Idetect
Point has been verified
This is just something that Alex saw that someone had tweeted
I have no idea if it's a real or current
I don't know what the truth is there and neither does Alex
He's assuming that it's real without any confirmation or journalist
Due diligence
And to the larger point
People are not applauding China for Institute of the Courant
19 Aldi's brutal Crackdown.
Actually what they're doing is likely a part of a
Complicated balancing
Because those International Health regulations are not enforced
They're completely up to
To each country to abide by them willingly
If a country doesn't cooperate
The crisis that crisis is going to
Be impossible to deal with
And that effect
The whole world
So well there is growing evidence of a lack of trying
A & C on China
Is part potentially
And of course there are
Any questions about whether or not the quarantining of millions of people is a great idea
The praise that people like
Like the head of the World Health Organization or expressing
Are not about those issue
We're in a public health emergency
Coronavirus
Broadly speaking
And successful navigation of that emergency
Depends on China's cooperation
Fox interview couple experts about this I think that their perspective is helpful in understanding some of these public state
Flipping bacon
41 is very
The China identified and sent out the
The Genome of this virus
Prompt fashion
So that is something that is worthy of praise
When did you know you can
You can hang your hat on
That's
That's fine Alex said they did
Sure
But the issue comes down to
Pharmacy
Debbie sridhar
Karthi charity global
Public Health
University of Edinburgh
Box quote
The World Health Organization is a difficult balancing
They have to somehow retained being believe coordinator and director of international Health work and the trade-offs
They're having
To make our about the greater good
Right now the greater good is to
To create positive incentives
Ford Country
To collaborate with the World Health
Relation to share data
To let missions into China
If that means
Publicly having to praise China
I understand
Lawrence Gaston
A global health law professor at Georgetown said quote
If the World Health Organization criticizes
Is China public
It's possible they can be less
A parent less cooperative
If I was in Ted roast
Head of the World Health Organization
Exposing his shoes
I'm not entirely sure I would do any
This is a really complicated the kind of thing
The reality is
These International Health regulations are great and people agree to them after outbreaks are resolved
And then there pretty quickly ignored whenever a new one pops up in that surprising
For instance restricting entry of people from affected areas
Counter to those regulations
But every time there's a public health event countries are quick to breed
This Norm
Mark Eccleston
Turner a global
Health law professor 8q university in England told V
Quote the international Health regulations
Operates on Mutual Trust
Largely
And I it is Eddie's a mutual Trust
That Mutual trust has been eroded
Over a number of outbreaks remember states have ignored the recommendation
From the World Health
Organization
I think it's possible that we have at times painted too Rosy a picture
Picture of the coronavirus situation but that's just because I'm responding to the
The claims the Alex
Witcher sensationalist trash
When you're dealing with
A guy who sang
You're garbage like it
It's over for Humanity
It will only be lone survivors
And you pair that with embarrassing sales to
Tactics I have no qualms about saying that it's the
Just trash and garbage
That's said it's important to recognize that serious people do have
Critiques about China's handling of the outbreak
They just don't match up with what Alex
And so when you hear people like the heads of the World Health
Organization saying that we applaud China until there is
A dynamic up there are things
And it's not wrong to
To point those things out
And if you don't do that
You have a state that has the ability to stop cooperating
And you run the risk of making everything worse for the world
All of these issues are best to be dealt with
After
The immediacy of yeah
It's okay
How do you how do you get any strongman powerful dictator on your
Beside you flatter the s*** out
We see what Stevie pisan Alex
All the time
So the World Health Organization
I'm going to China and being like
You guys are doing great everything that you guys been kicking ass we love it
Help us help you that whole thing is going to be far more if
Save the being like
Here's what you're doing wrong
Stop stop change it to this
Do I wish that wasn't the case
Of course
But it's
Unfortunately
The people who understand the situation in the expert
Are pretty clear on that
Which again
No government pays any attention
Attention to anybody who knows what's going on
The Optics of this are perfect
Because Alex can say that
Be in a World Health Organization in these leaders are applauding China and pretend that what they're applauding
Thing is all of the meme videos that you seeing
And all of the harsh Crackdown of the quarantine
And that's just not fair
Alex is playing with Optics in a way that
I mean
Deceitful
So Alex
He's really
I don't know
How to say like you really hate
Hey I've been trying
To plunge
Stock market
Using listen
Information
But they're going to try
Very
Hard this week
We're going to be
Going over all of it
Monopoly star
The broadcast
Bible ship
Weather
Thermometer
I don't know got it
Frigerators what are we doing
Your honor
Giant
Information ready to launch record trigger
And I got it on the runway
Right there
That's why we're going to come back
Push ups
For a moment
Trioxin 9
Start the rodcast over
And it's all going to be
Peachy
After that point and I'm going to knock it out of the park
All your support I don't know
It's like you got Labrador Retrievers
Puppies
Come out here
Music what state
Alex wasted like 6 minutes on there cuz it's three lifetime you know what
Now I will finally be able to answer when people that like would you want to talk to Alex Jones lb like
Yes at a bar
And only about 3:11 and I would bring the peanut
Exactly
Man he's really affected by 311
It's tragic to because I would associate people who like 311 with being like susceptible to Infowars propaganda
I don't know if that's the case maybe I'm making way too broad of generalization
But
I would say their subjects
2 dugg
Formic acid
Yeah so Alex
Gets back from break and
He starts the real show
And on this the beginning of the real show he's talking
He's talking about some issues
And one of them turns out is Rush Limbaugh
Who has come down with some cancer and got a medal of freedom
Great Alex
Why is America
Very weird feelings about this
I think he's trying to
Express a certain amount of like
You know we feel bad for him sure at the same time he also seems to think like
Once he dies
I'm going to get here where's Aldi
Open phones s h the Sunday show
I'm going to go home and see my children
I'm going to come back tomorrow to the 11 a.m. to 3 p.m. broadcast
The three 11 a.m.
Rush Limbaugh with his lung cancer
You're going to be the next project Limbaugh they say
I'm like well actually I'm more
Soundtrack the radio you can say is oblock bigger
You could
Fancy myself as an Xbox one ball
Rush Limbaugh's become what
Talk about...
We will probably go out
Patience when Rush Limbaugh
I do not have a good feeling about that
He might be able to stop
While we hope he has America
Like the omen of Rush Limbaugh
Dying right before the 2020 election because he definitely helped Trump get elected the big way
So Alex is looking at this like a human.
Covers when he dies I'm going to get all of a s*** so we really I'm not saying I don't want him to recover
Sucks that Russia's dying before the election cuz we could have used everybody
How it works
He's also not a lot of other people in line
For that time slot there are a hundred other like big
People who syndicated
Those time slots on all those stationed there we would never work with Alex
So they were people like Mark Levin or Hugh Hewitt or
Goguen backer
Call Sean Hannity.
Lakeview
Plenty of people within that time slot that would Rush Limbaugh goes away
Hannity takes over his times.
Bandages all over the
Whatever whatever the case is Alex's not next in line
There is no line that Alex is even in let alone next
I don't
Think that there is a massive radio stations that are like
F***
We want to play Alex
But the time slot use against Rock
I think there's three Stations of the country that might have that deliver
Isotonix is real
In all this
But I'm not
Interested in
Celebrating him having
Cancer in anyway
I hate him
And I think that this is
Disgraceful
So I asked some other dudes about the
The Coronavirus
United States
And it's a lotus
Let me just
Tell you what I'm going to get today
First up we have the
Set up at US military base
That's Miami Herald we broke this
Almost 2 weeks ago
And I thought they were establishing these
From Whitehouse horses
In the interest of
The clearness I've heard Alex saying that the governor
Specifically preparing for a gigantic quarantine near Seattle
That's specific I've heard of using the past
As far as I know
The rest of the things I've heard from him have been vague and not
Specific fears back
Some s*** that's
I didn't terms of what he
You put out on the Shelf
Then like the Seattle
So this Miami Herald article is just about the Department of Defense entering into an agreement at the request
The Department of Health and Human Services
To provide quarantine
Teen space in case they're need
For additional beds for
For suspected Coronavirus
What this comes down to
Is the fact that the bases are
To handle this
And they're located in places where they can be helpful
The basis that agreed to assist our specifically ones that are near major
So flights entering the United States
Some areas affected by the outbreak disc
Disembark
They have screening measures down to the passengers and then suspect the cases
Could be taken to the centers at the
Video device
The article is very clear that this is still the Department of Health and Human
Services operation
Just using space at these bases instead of creating new facilities or they don't
Create
With the Pentagon spokesman
Insane quotes
DOD Personnel will not be in direct contact with the evacuees and will minimize contact with Personnel supporting.
Evacuees
So how it works is it the medical staff will attend to them and if anyone test positive
4 coronavirus bill then be relocated to a nearby IHOP
This is also a very limited range
The help agreement only last
Until February twenty
The likely reason for this Arrangement being struck is because earlier this month
Trump sign an executive order that restricted
Travel from China
But it didn't come
Completely shut it down
According to the Charlotte Observer starting
February 2nd
Flights from China to the United States were being directed to
This Pacific airports where the passengers could be best screen
It makes sense that the Department of Health and you
Human Services would make use of the resources available to them
And if possible borrow space from
The dod to house any possible suspect
To the my popup
McDonald's
It's very frustrating to me that all of this sounds incredibly reasonable and let her know Alex
Attacking
Because it has the optic that he needs in order to create the fears that he's already built up over the years of Seminary
And the only thing you can assume is he would
Preferred large matte scale panic and Chaos 2
Resupply actual rioting
Rocky wants to
Controlled Chaos that's enough
You're scared enough
To buy his product
But you're not scared enough to get out of
Sweet spot that he wants people at
Also it's not like these.
These hunters will be gigantic
Prisons or something
According to the very Miami Herald article that Alex's sighting
Each would be able
Housing maximum of twenty patients
Just seems like good precaution
Being taken as far as I can tell
Nothing in the article talks about how many people are even being taken to those places
If anyone is
Yeah there's no
And it's
It's not like they would be the first
Places we were taking cuz the DHHS already has
Places to take the
People in case there are tons
More
People who are coming in from China worth
Suspected
I haven't there the virus
Well maybe they have today maybe they have to switch around and all the soldiers have to go to the Department of Human Health Services in all of
We have a nice little switch-a-roo everybody learns about each other
Is the 13 Going on 30 scenario dance
And again
Bring sharp Focus to this
You know like
Did the idea that I like
In his narratives are designed to get you no matter what you do if they didn't do something like this as a precaution or
You'll have these plans at the whaler sleep at the wheel they're letting us all die they don't give a s*** about us
So
I've never seen something so sexy
Spell weirdo
So we can
Off the coronavirus top and that's great
Juicy and
But it's not good
It's nice breath of fresh air from a dumpster
But it's also a dumpster
Burger King that's nice
Right so Chris Matthews
After the New Hampshire Democratic primary make some comment about how if
Bernie gets any might kill his rivals or whatever
Chris Matthews lost his mind to it was a little bit I was going to
Unhinged
I don't know I it was irresponsible to have you by text that I don't know what I'm talkin
So
Alex picks up on this
And he's like
Great
This is quite interesting
MSNBC
Chris Matthews
Suggest
Assassinate political opponents
Now
Hillary has a bunch of people around her
The Hat
If you read that on the are they saying it's a Publix
Corner in Arkansas
Arms legs and heads
Cut off
Plastic bags
And they said the person committed suicide
So it's it's pretty fun that Alex is doubling down on Chris Matthews suggest
Bernie will kill political opponents based on nothing
And at the same time celebrating Trump firing people who testified against him and clear active
Retaliation for the
I don't really care what Chris Matthews dumbass so I'm not even getting engaged with that I wanted to talk
Call Derrick Rose
If I wanted to talk about these Hillary murders a little bit
Before we get into any of this it's my favorite Agatha Christie novel by the way the Hillary murder sure
Tomorrow
The Belgian hits the bottom of
He's not friends
Before we get into any of this just just off the top this is all just a part of that dumb Clinton Body Bag s*** that was started by the
Bway Coke
Conspiracy theorist named Linda
The Thompson back in the 90s
Is way too attached
Text Bill Clinton
People have gone over this list of people who were quote-unquote close to the clintons who died
None of them really stand up to
Scrutiny at all
Interesting Lee though
Linda Thompson appeared as a guest on Bill Cooper show The Hour of the time
Gametime nice very regular alright hey
I listen to one and it was very boring there might be some other gems
We'll see if Hillary
Clinton kills anybody else I'm sure she'll be back on
I think
It might be too late for Bill Cooper
Yeah he's not on there anymore
So
The first case
But Alex brings up his Ron Brown
Okay
Ron Brown was he
First African-American to be chairman of the Democratic National Committee
And then went Clinton was elected Brown became
The first African-American to serve as set
Secretary of Commerce
On April 3rd 1996 you was one of 35 people who were tragically killed in a plane crash
Over Croatia
Are based on a small detail in the coroner's report
Conspiracy theorist
Started spreading all this s*** about his death
An x-ray showed what appeared to be a small round wound which folks decided must be a bullet hole
This theory is super weak considering that the x-rays
Suspiciously did not also include a bullet
Eddie bonebrake
Mites or an exit wound
Which makes it super unlikely that he was shot
Why don't they make the bullets out of
The Black Box you know what I'm saying
There's so much more than needs to be explained for this to be plausibly presented as a murder in neither Alex nor any of the Clinton conspiracy
Secret has ever provided any
Closer an explanation
For how they think this went down
Like let's say you was
Did the shot
They just dragged him on the plane ever got on the plane with a dead body and I
No obviously the way this goes down is a d.b. Cooper style f******
Hijacking
The CIA agent or NSA agent or whatever you want
Breaks into the plane
Set sit down kills the pilot says we're all going down then walks into the into the
Fuselage shoots the guy and then jumps out the
Beside
Paris
Why do you need me to do
Plane crash
The Kills everybody psychically eating everybody else and only games their strength and comes back
Back to bite you in the ass
That makes perfect sense of interesting ideas
But like I said there's a lot more than needs to be flushed out the people have failed to do that so that's what I'm not
Not going Scout Jose
Clinton murder
So as for Sami Malek
What else is referring to here is the case of Don Henry and Kevin Ives
I have no idea what he's talking about with suicide and people in bags and all that stuff but he's clearly talking about these
2 guy
Henry and Ives age 16 and 17 respect
They were hit by the
4:25 a.m.
I'm praying on August 23rd
As they lay on the
They've been out hunting and had some weed in their system which may have led to
To the corner family family Malik
Yeah to conclude that they were passed out from the weed and got hit by a train haven't fallen asleep on the tracks
The families did not accept that determination so they got a second
And opinion and the information
The came up made it seem
Very clear that these kids were murdered
For instance they found a stab wound in one of their backs and the second Corner found the dead waitlist weed and then Malik
Get suggested did she miss
The stab wound
He ant
I assume that the explanation be like you
Just think it's a train
Wound
Or something like that
Yeah well maybe
From here all sorts of
Conspiracy started
Swirling around about how these kids must
Accidentally seeing something they shouldn't have like a drug deal that would implicate then governor of Arkansas Bill Clinton
No this is ever been proven and it's
But it is accepted as Truth by the Clinton conspiracy crowd
I see that is a bit of a
It is yeah
From where I'm sitting I think it's entirely possible that family Malik was just super super bad at his job
He quit his position in 1991 under harsh criticism that he had a pattern of botching on top
There was the 1989 case of Olivia Ward what you determined to be a murder but further examination
Found to be in
Inclusive
Was no evidence
Murder at all
It's not like he always bungled cases but the case of Henry and Ives was definitely not an isolated incident
His tenure at the coroner's office
And the other cases he made mistakes and don't
Any relation to
Do the clintons
Nor does Henry and Ives
Unless you are operating off gases and theories
That aren't substantiated who are
So Alex is these two examples of Clinton murders
But he throws out
Pretending that they're solidly proven but it they're absolutely not
Who's all this job old right wing
A seashell
And more to the point even if Hillary killed every person she's ever met in her life
That has nothing to do with Bernie if you forgotten
Hillary hates
Yeah yeah but that's only because Bernie has also killed everyone
He's at four pm the two of them are on a collision On the Border contact
Yeah
This election season is going to be
The ugly even in ID
Dot situation
And Circumstance
The last thing we need is Chris Matthew saying dumb s*** like Bernie might kill people
Did the video.
And the way that that certificate
I don't know if it's a lack of awareness or a lack of caring or how that's going
Be used by people like Alex
But let me know before f****** careful
So
I don't think the people on TV who have opinions
Know what they're talking about ever
I think they might be just as
Keep your ear your argument is it looks
Stronger
By the day
So I thought that this is just going to be a Chris Matthews talks about Bernie killing people and then Alex gets to
Go off on a Clinton
Conspiracy Jag
I thought that was
Yeah
I thought maybe
Just going to rehash some of these old Quinn bodybag things
Sure Alex will be like
And I miss Larry Nichols
I thought that was going to be at
No
It turns out Alex's
Decided like
Why not play with fire
African people have been sued
Lawyers
Just questioning
Governmental
Orbitz
Haha
I lying about
Seth rich
Attorney claim
One America news isn't scared they talked to the lawyer lawyer says it goes all weapons
We're going to go all the way up to the top
Easy
Drool
Sure
It's legitimate there's that you might do that mean something
I guess now
Asking
Coming up
Alex better be really f****** careful or else he's going to f*** around and get himself sued
This is not the road you want to go down Alex
Here's a here's the thing he's making
Sobador buddy now he's like I'm playing with the house so I might as well go hard
Seth rich
Whatever on a Serta
A slander Mania episode
Dylan evil guy in the friggin and rapist has already said
That's true he has already
God dammit so this is a story that Alex is covering
About like one America news network is
But it is outside with discovering that it's about a couple of emails
It turned up in a foia request
For all the emails but
Peter strzok and Lisa
To page
There were couple emails regarding Seth rich but
It's pretty important to recognize me
Contacts
Of these interactions
Seth Rich died on July 10th
2016 these emails are for
From August
They're not really about Seth rich or any investigation of his death
It's very clear from the first email in the chain that this was specifically about claims that Juliana
The song should be making
Really vaguely in the media that suffrage was the
The source of the emails that Wikileaks published
This email the initial one is from the public
Affairs office
Saudi media relations sex
The FBI
Asking some folks
Does the FBI had any involved
There are a lot of parts retracted for who knows what reason but the exchange as it appears seems to be them saying that there
There is no FBI involvement
Limas got caught up in this play request because straw candidate for forwarding
The email to page
Who was an FBI lawyer
Looping her in on the situation
In case there's any legal
Right
None of this seems very suspicious at all unless you already believe that Hillary had set for
Bridge killed
And you let your imagination run wild about the
The parts that are redacted
I'm very much unimpressed with this development in the case of this evidence
I think it demonstrates literally nothing
But I am very
Very worried for Alex's beagles
Situation
I just don't have faith in his ability to thread needles anymore
If he gets to talk about this case I'm almost there
You can end up slander today
He can't stop himself
He just can't why did
Why isn't there somebody there to like just
The Roshan at his head
Be like no no no Seth rich
Like if you hear Seth Rich number
Some kind of like
Can should come out and hit him in the side of the head it goes
Your good point
You remember how bad your hand week your s*** was before
The Jerome corsi was telling you a sudhir
Each other anymore
You really need to be careful Alex this is not a road you want to go down
Sup but it turns out Alex
Basically a professor in like criminal justice
He starts telling you how you do an investor
Sagacious
Talkabouttd
Gather
Brina bring on Columbo
Oh I also should point out that like this is after he does like a 3-minute like
I love
The song Stranglehold Stranglehold
Position
F****** hate 311
Ted Nugent that's where it's at
He's got strong takes
So that strong take that's why he's like we got to get down to some serious
Ted Nugent for 3 minutes
Someone who is in Paula
X dies
Getting shot
Couple times in the back
Completely legitimate
To speculate
About why
And how
It happened and who could be behind and who stands to gain the old
Roman saying
Kubota who benefits
The first thing you look at is
Benefit from this
And then who has the means
EBenefits
The ability to carry it out
That means he's repeating himself also please Alex
Demonstrate
Kibo know about the separation
Please
I don't even think you can do that
Absolutely
So Alex
Like really is in trouble.
Buc-ee's
He's going down the road and talking about Seth Rich again and like
If he I can't stress this enough if he keeps going down this road it's going to be trouble
But not for the reasons he thinks
If you talk about Seth Rich you get to it by the DNC funded law firms
Lawsuits
Name of
They don't want you looking into it but you know
The data
Via somebody soon
Family Court
The download
Information
On the
Pat vncc
Time in happen
6 * 5
Then any streaming service
Capability in the world
So quick point
Sued for spreading misinformation about Seth Rich are not getting sued by the DM
MC your Hillary Clinton
They're getting sued by Seth riches
Parents who have been very clear the past
The therapy traumatize
By having their son's tragic death
Being used for
Political proper
Buganda
There aren't 100 suits about this I was just making that up
To seem like the DNC and Hillary are desperate to do a cover-up
When in reality it's just a family fighting back against people who cause them harm
Seems like a theme and Alex's career seems like he hurts people
For some reason also that's about the download speed being too fast to be a hacker
I'm Court
That stuff that passed Infowars guests William Binney
It claimed which I was used to give credibility to
To the narrative that Russian
Unintelligent couldn't have been behind the app
And in fact it had to be an inside job
Because the speeds were so quick
It had to be you USB
Drive
These files would not have been done
No there's no such thing as a fast internet
So the first problem was that this claim that the speed at which the files were downloaded
22.7 MB
Per second
Exceeded available internet download speed
That isn't true
Available internet connection
All over the world
Just based on that little bit of information this theory is shaky
As it turns out
Benny wasn't work
Confirm any real analysis of his own he was just using information he'd received from a man named
Adam Carter
Who was allegedly a researcher and tecca
As it turns out Adam Carter's real name was
Tim Leonard
And he was less an expert as he was a 39
9 year old troll from the United
Kingdom of a track record
Insperity misinformation on Reddit 4chan
Most of it too
Damn dude how Russia didn't hack
Accident that does seem that does he
You even created a second mysterious identity called forensic
Gator what you use to prop up the findings
Of his other they worked in concert to prop each other up
Pick that up for a Full Slate
This shell game a fake identities was tracked down by info
Security researcher inexpert Duncan
Campbell
Interesting consequences
Under his Adam Carter Alias Leonard operated website called G
G Dash 2.0 couldn't have been
Russian intelligence
Through this site Leonard sent William Benny of file the claim to show that the hack was an inside job
I'll read to you hear from Dunkin
Can Campbell's piece about his research
It was published in computer week
The Untitled file included complex
Text details explaining how to unlock information inside of tranche of files released by goose
42.0 it Lund
Metadata in the files had been manipulate
Diprove
That the
Could not have been could have been stolen
I only buy a Democratic National
Committee employee
This is a file that was sent to me had manipulated metadata
Which made it a
Appear that the download was impossible except
Local 8 check
Benny didn't know analysis on the files
Himself but instead took this
Information and took it is Gospel
The work into this file was attributed to Leonard's other Alias forensics
And from there
Justine's
Credible by Benny
Without further question
Baby began making the rounds with right-wing media offering this Smoking Gun that it wasn't rushing
Tim Hagan
His claims are all over Breitbart
Hannity and of course he showed up a bunch on Infowars
His claims even made it all the way to
Who told then CIA director Mike
Pompeo to meet with Benny
To get information that would prove that Russia
You acted ENC
God
But he knows that they
Pompeo did meet with things
Damn it and that makes this
Very sad especially considering the neck
Next development
Duncan Campbell was able to
Forget William Benny to visit Britain
I've analyzed
The actual data contained to the actual Goose for files and
Quote a month after visiting
CIA headquarters
Benny came to a Brit
After re-examining the data ended
Goose 42.0 files thoroughly with the author of this article
Changed his mind
He said there was quotes
No evidence
To prove where the download copy was done
The goose 42.0 files analyzed by Leonard's G2 space
Or quote manipulated
He said and a quote
Fabricate
Even William Benny has come out and admitted that the basis for his claims about download speeds
And how it's
Impossible that the hack
Wasn't it in-house operation was b******* and if a
There's nothing
Here other than
Supposed expert Guetta
Buy a troll in the process tricking the f***
Can president
Alex is lying saying that the information came out in court when in reality was b******* that he unquestioningly accepted from
William Binney
Unquestioningly accepted it
From Leonard
Oz reopening is interesting to Seth rich
It was a really bad idea
And defending the decision based on lies about things as sources don't even still believe
This is bad news
That must have been a real bummer for Benny whenever it got too far
Confetti had to admit that it was bulshit cuz if he if it didn't go all the way up
Depompeo
He wouldn't have retract
Did that he'd still be alive
Duncan Campbell
Still gone through the process that he did a figuring all this stuff out
And
Convince William Benny to come
Do the work over with him jack
I imagine the Benny would have been like
Yeah you know what
You're right
I just halfway expect all of these people to take a f****** mask off and reveal that there Jacob wohlander
Like these people are all insane but that's another one of Alex's big narratives about Seth rich is the guy investigating him
Got shot
For investigating
Is that the guy Burton
Who works
He got shot with like a BB gun
Beat by a guy who you was collaborating on a separate investigation with because the investigation toward south
This is what I'm saying
These people are all children. Burton Burke
Yeah
All of this
Is b*******
It's it's
It's outrageous it's going to
If you keep going down this road
Great but I'm excited to see if he does it's dangerous it is nice to see him
Get all that money and then Rush as fast as he can to get sued
To get it all taken away again
Very strange
So another thing that might end up costing Alex a bit of money
He is now comfortably settled in
To selling his immune gargle
Based on a
Claim that it is
Good at preventing or helping with SARS
We have sold out of the 16 oz
I mean Largo that has the nanosilver
That's up at didn't documented even admitted in.
Coronavirus family
Viruses viruses and bacteria
So
Viruses are bacteria viruses
Standby
Did you
Cuz I know that he says that like
All cancer is virus
I know that he has some
Weird thoughts about science
But I think you said viruses
Yeah I would have assumed viruses and if we weren't
Dealing with Alec
Viruses are bacteria is justice
So you got that it's like okay you
It's clear we've seen this path over the last like week or so that
Tentative
Dipping the toe into the pool of the biking these claim
Now you just totally comfortable with it is that why not
Let it let it ride consequences for me
Sojourn this next clip is long
And
It's very
Confusing
I
It wanted to
Cut clips
But I can't
I have to present it as a
This is a full second
Okay this is a 5-minute segment maybe 4 ish in the first segment of it
The second hour
It's where he's coming into the
The show and if that segment that isn't
Carried on every station
So sometimes it's a little bit strange
This one is very
Okay
I need you to take notes I need you to pick close
I know what you
A couple times
And I am very confused by this
It's
Very weird
When I hear about somebody dying
Have empathy II
The amount of the universe works
And Mojo.
Oh it's bad luck if I don't care if somebody gets hurt
Jenison
So at this point I have to pause because this is after talking about Seth rich
So I thought maybe he was talked about separate
We also talked about Rush Limbaugh and how he was going through a
I wasn't Wiki hopes 311.
But he doesn't
Now that's true if you look at the context
It seems more likely
It's about separate
The feelings at
I'm not sure I'm leaning towards Russia
Or it could be the people in China
I don't know maybe I guess that's why I don't think he cares about people
Don't know Alex
Spiritually know that
You think I know that but they'll
Because the laws of nature
That's why evil always goes wow I can do this
And this happens
But they don't think about the next couple things that happen
Nice
Is the best way to build a good civilization and
Good people around you that doing well
People aren't doing well
I don't care what color they are where they came from
How does that make me better
Because I have a spear
And I have a conscience and I care by nav
I have
Nerves that feelings I'm not a psychopath or sociopath
Manipulate my feelings
Cold-blooded
And that's where this go
Comes in
People that are good and strong
Have to do the right thing when it comes down to it no we don't
Limitation when I fry some enemy into feed him I don't feel good I'm like
Why do I see how bad they are
Their family
Go around
Black people poor white people or whatever
Dumbass
We're not like them and I'm like really you feel good cuz they
They're doing bad
Worst job I ever had I was like
The highest job I can get with a carpet cleaner
Stanley Steamer car
Carpet cleaner
30 years ago
Rata High School
Longer. Now I'm getting all them for sex
When did you get out of ice
Domino's
I get paid
20 something dollars an hour as the assistant
The clean carpets
Right now
Until I got to leave
And I was like
Baguette baguette bag White
They could be black baby whatever
Why do you know that
Never seen
Anything like this
A dirty car just described Lysol
In the few months that work there
Dirty carpets
With that guy
Hours it was
Iamjustairi Carpenter the Bible true
Paramedics
Stella PTSD
Military people
Let me take Maddox and Bevo
Carpet cleaning carpets Davis PDF
Nobody
But think about
Paramedics
Show up and see these chewed-up bodies
Are you drive by
The firefighters and police were there with dead
Kids and stuff
The first
Pull up a record
A mommy you're trying to
And and
Baby.
That's not my fault
I got there I tried to hold it around their neck I try to put a
Lil Baby
It's a psycho
Wound
There's everybody else just wants to go home and watch Netflix
And and you know here's some stuff from
Jeff Bezos black lives matter
Cops and you just like
It doesn't even fit
You got these billionaires up there
By the way
How much
Dude make a hundred thousand dollars
Man
So that's what it's like to listen to the show a lot of the time
It was that bewildering okay
I really do not know
Exactly what point he's making although I will say
Bourget to urinalysis
I do think
I realize what he's trying to comply with carpet
I didn't understand it for I think
He's implying that you
Cleaned up like Satanic rituals or something like that
I think it has to be because otherwise yes it's a dirty carpet
You're going to see a dirty house
I'm someone who can't afford a carpet cleaning company or maybe he's saying that he
He cleaned up murder scenes or something like that he had a contract with the city
Company did or something like that
But if you saying
He cleaned up after Satanic rituals then
What he did
I is not report them
So he's complicit
Anyway I have no idea what he's talking about just has PTSD from cleaning a lot of carpet
I think that's the I think that
That's basically what he's
Describe because here's erie's going through it right now
The path you went off
So he's got apathy
He's not a sociopath he is
Being nice and being with good people as how you build a good society and he doesn't like it whenever he has to smoke food
Right that's why hasn't he doesn't feel good cuz they're so weak
And being weak reminds him of
Being a carpet cleaner
Which is the same as being a paramedic or a first responder
And
He said multiple times that he doesn't care what race you are which means he's talking about black
People maybe and
Poor
Memes
Carpet
SD dirty carpet
Takes us to the cops
Paramedic car crash and black
Clyde's matter is killing baby
Forgot about the Billionaire's hummingbird
Black lives matter SS
See this is the experience that I go through some
Sometimes like sometimes I'm able to sit here at present you with clips
That makes sense so you like talking about years the b*******
With the
The clip about like it's come out and Courtney's downloads
Speeds for the goose for hacked like
I can tell you what he's talkin about
That I forgot the Bible is true Bibles
Cleaning the Bible History
That's what leads me to believe that he's talking about cleaning up like Satanic rituals connection
Bible being real is very strange
I refuse to accept there's a real connection to any of those
So whatever bewilderment you were feeling or the audience was arguing while list
Something to that rambling nonsense
PTSD from it now
Try to imagine my life
What are you talkin about then
Imagine people who are listening to this show who believe him love it and not being like I'm worried about this guy
How smart this guy is
So Alex Goes break and he comes back
And he starts talking about a recent
Crime that was
Committed and he's
Being really dumb
Drama queens
Imagine put 2 years ago you saw Charles
Spell where.
It's a long tail out of that guy's
Harbor
You're saying it's all over run for the Hills
Survivors all the attack
Back pain
Borders that means America supporters
Bullying people that
Believing cell
Defensible leaving life
Show me reason
The people that want back
Down under intimidation
Those guys looking for
Of what
Dot-com from supporters attack
Plows through GOP voter
Registration
Content in Florida
Spectre
Just real quick
Heather hair didn't
Have a heart attack
What is a white nationalist
Meme talk
Pinpoint that spreads
Deflect blame from the guy who hit her with his car
The fact that Alex consistently brings that up isn't necessarily proof that he's intentionally running interference for whites
Supremacist
What is definitely Italian marker as to the source of information
Funny being credible
He has to be getting it through that channel
Repeating it or he
He just thinks that those people know what's up
27-year old man did run his car into a GOP voter registration
Attempt
Set up a meeting on Saturday
And that's awful
Even though these incidents may seem similar to Alex
In that they both involve cars
When their view together they actually demonstrate clearly why the national conversation happened
After the United right rally
And this one will not have the same effect
The first obvious thing is that the United right rally Heather hair with
Fatalities will always
Increase the severity of the situation
Conversely in the case of this guy in Florida no injuries or even reported which makes his actions stupid and wrong
But it's not a clear
Huge deal as if he'd murdered somebody
Second while it appears that the guy in Florida didn't like Trump supporters
Lieutenant Leary Gail of the Jacksonville Sheriff's Office said that quote we don't know what this is
Politically motivated
We're in Florida it could be
You can make the assumption that it's politically motivated
You're welcome to have that opinion
But the people investigating it don't know that yet so it remains to be seen
Conversely epi
Unite the right rally the political motives of the events
That led to the car attack were pretty well understood
I meant finally
Is very basic
Everyone knows that driving your car into people is wrong
The left and right
Agree on that
So what
I was particularly unsettling for people
About the United right rally was Trump's response to the Fallout of it
When he said that they were very fine people on both sides
To be fair to Trump he also said quote
I'm not talking about the neo-nazis and white nationalists because they should be condemned totally
But you had many people in that group other than white-naped neo-nazis and white
Okay and the Press is treated them absolutely unfairly
So what mean we finally have a president who recognized the inherent Beast
People who are willing to March alongside open white supremacist
The neo-nazis
So I don't know if that quote actually make
Why won't people think of the Guilty by sand
Why won't they think
Have Dad right about the bad people but don't
Don't you
Want to shed a tear for the people who just wanted
To oppress other people and had not been alongside open miona
But of course they were just pop out Face bookbag
Yeah yeah reacting
After the rally Trump tried to defend his side
Instead of respecting the woman had been killed
And that goddamn neo-nazis were marching alongside
His supporters and recognizing
The real problem there he decided to provide cover and defense for that which most people found shocking
Dang it really disgusting
Which they shouldn't have found Chucky
Is varidesk
Conversely in the case of this guy in Florida I'll reach you from the New York Post
Quote the Duval County Democratic party said it condemned
Quote this cowardly act of violence
No one's life should be placed
Danger for exercising their First Amendment right
As Democrats but more importantly residents of the greater city of Jacksonville we call on our fellow citizen
To act with dignity civility
Respect for one another during this election
Cycle & Beyond look at how similar their rhetoric is to Trump
Of course you have to condemn them roundly the Safeway on the left I have to be ideologic
Inconsistent
And say that their rhetoric is
Inflammatory is absolutely going to get more people hurt
There wasn't a defense of this guy's actions no call to consider will hate you know Trump
Policies are pretty shity in the supporters are defending the guy was hurting a lot of people
There wasn't an attempt to justify a clearly wrong
React by deflecting
Which is the right thing
To do
This guy's actions are not indicative of the democratic party they are just his bad actions
The actions of white supremacist terrorists would not be associated with Trump if he behaved differ
I think crucial situation
Like the press conference after the United right rally
Because we all agree that running
Your car into people is wrong and in this case no one is trying to
Pretend that the conversation
News about anything other than that
Get to move forward after the agreement he's been arrested
You will be treated as
Appropriate by the law
There's no need to
To ask what the f*** is wrong with people trying to justify unjustifiable thing
And this is largely why this is
Is just a bad thing that happened in Florida
But even people like Alex will probably not remember in a week
Supposed to deeply traumatic event that ripples of which are still resume
To this day
These are thick
There's
It's so
F*** it obvious
Alex Mead
Touba ramp-up
Conservative victimhood juice
That's so in
Important toward to animating
The the rhetoric and the narratives that he put
It's worth on a shield
It runs this
This engine
What's what's
Disgusting to me about
It feels so often like when some kind of tragedy happens
Due to a
White National
Was terror attack
The right is not
At all interested engaging with that
They're just excited
Hoping that there will be a what about either later or
That they can point to
They wanted what about more than they want a resolution to
Sure
Yeah
But
It's all
Tustin service of
We are the ones who are under attack
Until you see that here with Alec
Like really just lying
DC reports every couple hours like
Headed boss
Biblia Beach
Boss to death in head with hammer
You just see the reports
Pouring out
And the media says
So there's a story in late January
Construction worker in Florida who is accused of murdering his boss who love Trump but he didn't use a ham
Use a trowel
Apparently the two men got into a political argument and then the dude killed
Was boss before draping American flag on
The problem here is that Alex heaters at this
Guy killed his Trump loving boss after a political argument
And he just assumes that the murderer is a Democrat who hates Trump
In reality the alleged murderer is one of those anti-government
Types of believe that the government is out to
Forget him kind of paranoid conspiracy theory type fella
Hey why Alex yours imagine those guys committing NEX
Alex is here saying that there's no there's all these new stories about attacks on Trump supporters are coming in every hour
Best you can do is come up with a story from over two weeks ago that he doesn't really know any of the
The details of
It may not make the Casey thinks he does and you can hear those long pauses
Cuz cuz he can't come up with anything
You should probably have a couple of examples
Bridal got out of your head two-week-old storiesig
Probably isn't what you think it is maybe even just give the one that came in
Last hour
The most
10 hours a day
Clearly have a handle on this stuff
What about the one that
Came in before you started the show
While you were on there
But then you know that the issue is that like all these
Some supporters are getting attacked
Every hour you hear the news stories
Corydon
Billings
In Demon
In the media
Like Wolf Blitzer justify
I watch 10 years ago
Cars with Phylicia Rashad
Latta Gaston say he's a hero
Not a bad guy he soft
Fascism
Hoping more people
Would come kill
Trump supporting members of Congress
If you're ever successful
Civil War
It's open season on your little ass
So on The Situation Room on June
14th 2017 while reporting on the shooting at
At the Congressional baseball practice
Wolf Blitzer played a piece that was compiled by CNN
Congressional correspondent Phil Mattingly
Approximately 7 Seconds of the piece was an acquaintance of the shooter saying quote
I just want to let people know that he wasn't
Evil that he was I guess tired of some of the politics that are going on
Wolf didn't say that it was good and in fact after Mattingly finished up his presentation of his peace
Here's what wolf
Actually said
You know if it is clearly he was evil
March 22nd
Are you point out he posted this on Facebook
Trump is a traitor Trump has destroyed our democracy it's time to destroy
Trump and Company and then he said
Republicans are the Taliban
Of the USA when you say
On a Facebook post it's time to destroy Trump and Company that's a threat against the president of the United
And that's a crime
Not only did Wolf not support the shooters Act
You directly and clearly rejected the state that the equator
Made sings the shooter wasn't
Evil
Kind of seems like Alex just makes up whatever he wants in order to satisfy the right wing
Constant need
To portray themselves as victims
What a piece of s*** also it's also just so it doesn't matter
It doesn't matter if
It's reality or not. What they want to say that's why anytime somebody is trying to be like
Oh nobody would vote for Bernie because they'll call him a socialist
Do diff
Pitas in they're going to call him a so
It does not matter what reality is
What matters with
Politically
Right and I'll admit it's just
This is blade
Terrible
So blame this on the 311
About this is probably just the Alex
The head is
You got he got high by contact with the 311
Terrible job
Anyway he's like a wolf
Luther open season on you when they when the war comes
And Alex gets to rambling about fantasies if I wanted to kill Wolf Blitzer
Now hold on one second can I go back here he has empathy
And it would be crazy to Brian is enemy doesn't like it he doesn't like it she Opeth or recycle
I don't know if he actually likes
The frying of the enemies but he certainly likes
Talking about it
In the past Jordan we have said that Alex
Probably text
Technically killed a guy
I think we can now upgrades
I don't want to ever see Wolf Blitzer
Because
I mean
Like you really want to start a fight with us
Don't you
You're begging for it
You're begging
You're begging to get your gut stomped out our
Aerowolf you ever had your gut stomped out
But you don't
Live after that happens
Actually I'm a couple times not too nice
Text people long time to die if you start their guts out that but
That's no threat to Will bletzer
So Alex is a mass murderer
You just admitted to murder
No set multiple murders murder we multiple murders
Check the Dallas unbelievable
Yeah let's go Cold Case Files on Alex Jones only a hundred percent don't believe Alex
Take some of his words
He is a
Multiple murderer multiple murderer
New tech
We probably anymore Alex you are a murderer at the very least murder 2
Police Murder to baby wasn't
Premeditated baby just got angry
But man I would give him 25 to Life on this you know what
Really f***** up about that clip is like in the past whenever he's talked about like these probable technical birders
These committed
I always am.
Contacts.
You know hey I didn't like to do it I was gas bullied and I you know it's like almost self-defense
Nature
This is not this is
Cinderella seeing the slowness of their death yeah
This is absurd
Sick f***
Talk radio
Said he doesn't enjoy his enemies but he doesn't
Watching their guts
Spell out and blowing
Slowly painful
Right right right he's not a sociopath and a psychopath
That would be crazy that I really need to put a sharp Focus
Song here is that like if he's telling the truth
Is the most f*****-up thing ever
But
If he's lying it's even more f***** up
Seen by his audience as someone
Who would have
Slowly and painfully murdered multiple people
Seems okay or positive today which is really gross
Sick look
It's a stand your ground law even if the ground is below a human's body
You still get to stand on that ground I believe
Engrossed
Child
Sunnyway brambles a bit about CNN
Because you know Wolf Blitzer got to throw some shots of him
And then
You know he's not the only one
I'm going to get it
A lot of people are going to be Friday
And if you forget about God's they're not Gods anymore but Anderson
Just because
Cuz you're the
Last
Vanderbilt Planetarium
Is your brother wouldn't bend over
What
You're not going to g******** America
By yourself
So after getting mad Wolf Blitzer Alex descends into a rant
Just generally that's the end being bad and it's pretty boring
Formulaic
I decided to cut this clip though cuz it really illustrates our Alex are just making up the bulshit he says in his ramblings
41 in 1988 Anderson Cooper's brother Carter committed suicide by jumping out of the way
This is absolutely tragic
And their mother believes that this was the result of us
Psychotic episode caused by bad drug
Action but Alex is rewriting it
Is a f******
Gross thing
Thing to do
Regardless Anderson Cooper does not just have one sibling
Sure maybe his only brother from that marriage
Is that marriage of his mother's and Carter
But their father Wyatt Emory Cooper is not where the Vanderbilt limited lineage comes from
That's from his mother's side and Gloria Vanderbilt already had two sons
When she married Cooper
And they're both still alive
Ipso facto Anderson Cooper is not the last Vanderbilt
And that's not even considering
The Gloria Vanderbilt had a sister
Kathleen Vanderbilt
Or the fact that Cornelius Vanderbilt was their
Father and he had 30
Children
The family is very diffuse
There are a ton of living Vanderbilt
Like guess who
Timothy Olyphant
Who is Anderson Cooper's third cousin once removed
I didn't know that just because he's being sneaky with a different last name
Timothy Vanderbilt to be in my way
Treadmill the fact get them in there
But what about James and Vanderbilt
The guy who wrote the movie Zodiac The Amazing Spider-Man in White House Down dude also wrote the mega twitches
Fighting a shark
There are tons of other Vanderbilt or still alive you just don't know about it
Because it doesn't mean
Anymore is predictive programming do Jason Statham will have to fight a shark Revenge
Alex is making up that Anderson Cooper is the last Vanderbilt to make him seem like more of a villain
And has an opportunity to mock him for his brother's death
Because Alex is a
Profoundly bad person
And also it turns out he probably killed a lot of people sociopath
Mr. worst he is a f****** months
But this is my educational corner while I wear I teach the world that
Timothy Olyphant
Related to the Vanderbilt family that is a nice little fun fact
So Alex goes out to break any
Comes back in he's got tagged wants to
To touch on the the Rodger Stone news
How I imagined he would
Sound of your calls until the very end
I've got to get this Rodger Stone thing
Maybe I should just
Weak Sean marylebone a.m.
It's all over the news that well Rodger has to go to print
Cousin for a long time
Cuz he violated a gag order talk about Alex Jones
Really
Three Links about the truck
You're that much of a narcissist
Rodger said a news articles
That
He wanted a pardon from from he was convicted
That's right
It's an American what this judge is doing it's insane
Rodger isn't going to prison cuz he's violated the gag order to talk to Alex
No more pathetic strawman attempts of zebra Malik lately seems like he doesn't have a good angle on this
Also I nudity
He's guilty that's the problem
Newsbroke the prosecutors are saying that Rodger should do between 7 to 9 years
In prison which means he'll be in like
Free maybe that probably won't even
I've no faith in the system anymore he's not going to prison
Interesting l no consequences for his actions
This episode
Choose from Sunday the 9th of February
Alex didn't report the prosecutors
Request for sentencing
Until Monday afternoon
This heavily Blythe me that I was just getting this news from Rodger
Say that he's being sent to prison for defending
Himself or some s***
It's pretty sad but I'm not going to get too invested in it because like I said I have little faith that he's going to see the inside of a prison cell
For now this is just more that classic conservative victimhood narrative building
Just very very regular it is so annoying that the people who
Who f****** run everything
Sing now complain about being the
Subtotal at
So annoy
Yep and it's all because
Like a quarter man
But Alex has a defense for that which isn't good
Is the defense that he denies
Whatever he has
Have to go to court
Bob Moyers about it
Plus I do common sense journalist
Only has her Little Dipper
What you doing everybody else is but she says
Alex is conveniently not a journalist whenever he's in a deposition setting
Journalist
The guts out of a multi people
So this guy at his job if he was just on Erica's being like a man
I love murder I don't like murdering people but when you do murder
Somebody ruined feel good
Have to watch him die slowly
So there's a hastily put-together commercial that Alex plays
Multiple times during the show
It's kind of Interest
Play a tiny piece
Confirm from a major Food suppliers across United States they already run out of supplies
Because of institutional and governmental buyers for the elites people razors or not
Shoe stores at alarming rates
I've been meaning to get into this for a while but I keep forgetting
What's a good time
The main driver of the sales pitch that Alex is going with you regarding the
Survival food from my picture
Supply is it bulk
Buyers are coming in and buying up all the
Survival food on the market
We need to act now to get your foods
Your family doesn't start otherwise
It's going to be an armored redoubt
It's pretty
Exploitative engross marketing
You scheme for what if I were to tell you Jordan that I've seen this exact same Market
Getting campaign
Before I do mean everywhere simultaneously right now
A while back we talked about this
Commercials that Alex used to run for the weird device
Which I think was a solar-powered thing
It was a cryptic commercial that warned of an impending collapse where you'd need this weird device
And the pitchman was a guy named Frank Bates
And this is a guy who's like a I'm a right way
I'm just like you a Middle America
Right as we discussed when we went over this prank Bates is a fake character designed to appeal to paranoid
Conservative radio list
He was the creation of an affiliate marketing
Scam artist named Allen Ballard
Who ran a company called reboot Market
Under the Umbrella of reboot marketing Balor had a ton of little smaller grip
Then one of them was food for
In 2013
Food4patriots was selling survival food
They wanted their customers that FEMA was trying to buy up all the food
Trying to skewer 420 million meals
The few people in their female
People's buying up
All the other available food but you could still get food from food for pate
Because unlike other companies
They weren't sellouts 2
To the man
This dude Alan Valor mayday
S*** ton of money playing on the fears of scared conservative audiences
Of people who'd been
Trained to think that
Any day Obama was going to put them in a FEMA camp
So in part thanks to the
Persona Frank B
Who's the guy just like that red-hot tip
Alex is doing the same thing now
And based on the fact that Alex used used to are weird device
Commercials
I wouldn't be surprised if he also advertised food4patriots
Except I'm certain that he did
Because food4patriots wasn't a real company
It was just Alan Beeler reselling food from my Patriot Supply at a park up alright
Alright Evergreen
Etiquette scam
Because Alex has show and basically in the entirety of right-wing media is
Predicated on amplifying manufactured fear.
Distract from the very real problems that they're making worse
There will always be some sort of an issue to make profit
Sometimes it's a black president you're sure is going to lock you in a FEMA camp
Sometimes it's a Public Health crisis
But no matter the exact character of the thing you're supposed to be afraid of if you listen to Alex rest assured
It will be used
Visalia b*******
And my Patriot Supply is going to be there
Happily taken
Endicott
Alan Beeler was laughing his ass off and idiots who believe that Frank Bates was a real per
And you have to be a complete idiot.
Think that Alex
On some level laughing at
The people who think he's sincere to
Yep
That's
But why is it
So easy to get
These people to believe grifters
An impossible
To get them to believe grifters are gripped
Well because I think a lot of it is
Really targeted at
Softspots
I think
Something that you viscerally an emotionally
Are taught isn't something
It's very easy to rationally untie
Sure I think I think that those are such a different
Processes
You want it
You wish right that it could be
Be that but it's
Unfortunately world
Doesn't work that way
And even worse is that when you you know if you can't counteract
Emotionally
Like fear
With rational thought youth
You think well maybe
You try and create
Try and use a different emotions
To counteract it and then you have no fun
That's going to
Nobody knows what happened
Whenever you start
A a people up in Alder
And I think there's also a secondary problem that comes in that
These people like Alex have a built-in way around
One of the teachable moments that could happen is like yes you emotion
Simile
Our trick
Into buying all this s***
This crisis has doesn't
What happened
You would
Book back and be like hey wait a sec
You guys
F*** with me because you bought this food
The game is
Well
We look
Yes we narrowly escaped
Exile whatever this
And that way you guarantee that you'll have the ability to run this campaign x x again
Last time we almost
We almost needed that food last
At this time
Don't don't f*** it up
So it's all just
Super exploitative
Yep
Marketing
And that's sad
That makes me very sad it is sad
It's so clear how
Alex
Wendy's on Fair he's got to be laughing
Can you people and also he let me go let me go back to my notes on
His weird ramble
He does not like it when people manipulate
His feeling
Snow so
It is totally fine for him though to manipulate other people
What's the best way to make sure no one's manipulating yours
Populating other people's feelings so
There we go
So Alex
Calls in the second hour of Sunday's show
And one man one of those callers has a theory about the Wuhan quarantine
And that is
Without its British Dahmer
Illinois
Dido next listen I just wanted to see if they would have just hold off Coronavirus
Cheyenne is just a ruse just a mask
National notes of people movement so they get all these people inside these buildings and they go into the
Funnel systems and move
Ollie's large huge quantities of people wherever it is that they want
Preparing for
A possible ground Invasion per se
I mean what's what's
Speculate
In a world of constant lies and disinfo in the whole history of governments
Pennywise in huge hoaxes
You'd be crazy not to say that anything's possible
This color is a real dumb dumb
Although I do agree with Alex that everyone has a right to speculate about things
I wouldn't say that this guy can't sit around and think about how maybe this will coronavirus situation is just to give milk
Millions of people into a big building so they can go through
Underground tunnels so they can gain the element of surprise and I've grounded vision of
Somewhere
I think that's exactly the sort of thing that's appropriate for a conversation that involves a couple of dumb college students in a blunt
It's just not a serious Theory
Everyone has the right to speculate but that doesn't mean that all speculation
You should be respected and taken is equal
Some speculation is really stupid
And just because Alex wants to pretend that there's moral virtue in his practice of not doing any work
That doesn't mean he needs to validate s*** like that
A couple points
If This Were the
Plan I'm not sure how they would do that where they would be
Be grounded Vaden
Wuhan is pretty emblem
And in China
So you have to be
Really f****** long underground tunnel
Constructed I don't know man we can make a tunnel anywhere
The closest border to Wuhan is the East China Sea
I assume that's not where they're going to invade probably not
After that the closest country is Vietnam but I don't think invading their makes a whole lot of sense time to solve the issue
Once and for all Dan we're going to kill thousands of people build a tunnel to Vietnam and take the
The Vietcong
I think I'll be a really strange move geopolitical a sunshine it's a grounded plane Vietnam
Better leadership as we all know that's a huge issue that sure if they wanted to go like I'm sure this guy
Thinking like North Korea or Russia ever like
There's other cities they could have done this and if they wanted to do that much closer
People off It's too convenient for a tunnel danu if you put it in Wuhan fairy know nobody's going to
I'll be looking for your tunnel very dumb.
Who it is
Alex's own s*** is so we
Weak that he can't afford to even push back against the stupidest things his collar say
Accidentally training them to think critically
If he helps them recognize why their own idea is bad it's only a matter of time before they apply that to his b*******
And the next thing you know food bucket
Sales dry up in
You can't be having that
So you just allows this or what if she Jinping was the only guy to have
The coronavirus so we gave it to other people cuz you didn't want to be lonely
Write more dumb calls
And
He's loving taking these calls though because like it's
Just like not doing anything dumb stuff and then he's like you know what we're right because like a good idea let's go
Is it a possibility
So he starts thinking about like
I got to do this call or call-in show
The show that's just all calls
And he's like
An innovator
Jeanette Lee
They look this is
This is kind of like almost like you couldn't
Write this,
What ends up happening
After talking about how he's going to do this innovative
Show that just calls
Are you getting
The caller
Wow
I was thinking about doing new shows
I can tell you
I think the answer is like 2 or 3 hours a day
Commercial free
If TV radio station on the pickup that can
I'm just phone call
People want to hear people
You mean like love
Don't even screen
Will get a lot of really bad calls doing that
Yokai saying whenever
But just boom you call your own are we having
Baby
But imagine just a network of satellite of this
Phone calls
Skype calls
Yes
C-SPAN
I want to do that
Idea to make stuff now I just
Micah global stahl-david
You do less than that
Everytime I we say it's not first time cause you called him we love him
You take my call brother yeah you know real quick I think that about you
And world called in I love it
When you're right there are crazy
So if Alex is at
Variable that is hilarious
It's still not activating buddy
Oh my God
Yeah that's really sad
So Alex
Ghost
Chiefs Patriots dumb any other stupid blank remember what it was
Alex gets another color and man this guy is a weirdo
This guy
I kind of dig this Vibe Jerome in New York
You're on the air Jerome are you in New York state or New York City
I'm in the Big Apple over here in China
6:40 p.m. Eastern Standard time but
Psy the mainland China
Play 7:40 a.m. it over there
Shanghai Bistro
Angel
Bonjour
It's time to get up
To work a lot of money
Translate she retired
You can work from the house
Guess what you going to go get on the bus
Subway
That's not good
I do like It's Time to Say Goodbye
You got a musical kind of speech pattern I think I think he was getting to like he never really get to
To the point I think he's like there is
People with the virus and I got to go get on public transit and that's not good I think that's what he's getting to that but if he wasn't and you
Just like morning
You got to go do some stuff
You got to get on the bus you got it in your car you're not going to see a lot of traffic I'll text get out there and help everybody
Work to do unless you're retired and less your skin out there and get that money go
Clock in its motivational American people
Alright we can do this
Alright man I'm
Feeling at this guy's got I don't understand a word
Say what you got that Musical.
It's almost like something you would hear like it's morning time in China
You retired or Rich enough not to work you got to get out there alright hey let's go to Loverboy working for the weekend
It's 7:40 a.m. in Wuhan everybody we're going to have a grand old time everybody
Party hats on we're going to get right onto a baby
Nobles field like what I drive time DJ
Good morning DJ would have this riff
Every Monday
Alright it's Monday at 6 a.m. we're going to play some 311 for you piss off somebody I know
So
I've made the point that Alex is like the way you selling this immune gargle and is
Is toothpaste that has the silver and
He's really really inappropriate
And the way he's been making Health claims about it is really bad but now it's even branching out even further
Cuz now he's advising a caller
To use it
For protection
Against Coronavirus
I did buy your
Immune gargle
Toothpaste and all this stuff this week cuz I
I got to go back Taiwan tomorrow
Guzzling
Banana platinum silver weave
Your mouth
SARS
It's going to stop
No but
This is damn proven
So I mean we're getting now to the point where it's
Health aide
Advise that he's giving based on these
Claims that he's making
I mean I just think IQ
Nestled into a real comfort
About this I don't know how this is okay
It's not
If it's some
Some press needs to take this
Because it's not like the FDA or the episode
Correction that I need to make also apparently
Because he's making these claims in
The speech form is opposed to the label on his bottle
It's more an issue with the
Federal Trade Commission
I got those
Example of a monitor
Forgot her but unfortunately unfortunate
Stop that
So
He's making all these pretty outrageous
Commercials about the gargle
But we do know that Alex had his first fever
In four years and have to gargle and it cured him
Absolute Total
Turns out it did
Exhausted
You know I was bragging
But
Nicole number for years
And then I got one this week so I'm kind of out of it today and have a lot of family stuff going on I'm trying as best I can I'm sorry
Daddy call me back tomorrow
Looks like it was lying
All the time
Looks like he was lying
About
So pray
Steve pieczenik does still have the Coronavirus
Psy I don't know if you know this but herself these guys are making himself
Okay so Alex that's his way of being like
I can't take any more calls
Yeah I don't know
This is which has struck me as kind of weird
Aleksander The Show by sodas vamping
Doing kind of like it an Oscars Style thank you a list of thank you
I appreciate this
Breakthrough coming in tonight
On Sunday
Fantastic job in what they call the affiliates
Alexa AM FM
MTV UHF VHF
Cable
Want to thank everybody and just encourage folks
Stay frosty
Stay frosty Frosty
Right
Oh my God thank you say Frosty out there
So I was just going to do an episode about the 9th cuz I think there's a
Plenty in there I was getting freaked out about 3:11 getting back into Seth rich
7:40 a.m. but I could just listen to that club
For sure about Wolf Blitzer that lead to him confessing to multiple murders
Lot going on
I got a tip-off that Robert Barnes is back
I'll go ahead listen to this
Barnes appearances
Really that
Exciting
A barn seems to be willing to
Call in now
The studio
I'm he calls in and it's fine it's whatever he's at calling
For new church committee
Hearing and whatever
There is something that's going on that's worth noting
This episode I'm not going to get into like his standard coronavirus stuff
Just yet background
There's something more important going on
The first is
Did Alex is really excited about things that Charles
Murray has
To say
But that leads him to
Basically telling his audience that it's time
To go to
To the woods
Focus Murray
Cuz we're living in post America
A small town to survive
The collapse
And yes
If
We don't turn America around and Route the leftist poison ideology
That is design
The collapse Society
Then the producers
Are the UB white black Hispanic old young but people that want to live like normal humans
I want to live in
What America was
You don't want to live in the globalist paradigm
Backwards
Geographic areas
My flaws and have culture and systems
That do not tolerate the left
Because they don't tolerate us
They come in and take over and then end
I wonder if that's going to end up looking at all like a white ethnostate theocracy
Wonder
Good man charles-marie is the author of the book the bell curve which has been widely discredited but yeah
That lives on
Is one of the foundational text among the race IQ people
You like to argue that minorities are
Genetically less
Intelligent than white people
But
White people less intelligent than Ashkenazi Jew
Respect your enemy
Haha
His career has largely been about trying
Need to take social ills like racism and sexism and explain them with
Genetics and it is not been a good guy
You don't have to feel like it's your fault at all
Charles Lane did a piece on the bell curve in the New York Review of Books
So noted that it was weird how number the egg
Expert see sites in the book are explicit races the Nazi sympathizers
Less than they are respected experts in the field
Are the book
Supposed to be covering
It's a pretty well explain thing that the bell curve is
Is trash anyone citing it as a source
Speaking well with Charles Murray
That's a red flag they might have so
Some crypto positions are trying to sneak into the conversation
Seems like Alex
Beer do with this dude that I got to say and now
We've got to isolate
We've gotta move our conservative right-wing
Into small areas and then take over
That's bad bad development to the regular Woods
Get rid of everybody get rid of your social
Security cards
Get rid of all I've done for you.
Infile GOP we got into the woods
Well it's more about going to rural areas
Alex is telling his audio
Italy that it is time to do the self-select
You have children you have a duty
Go to rural Christian areas
I'm outside of the big cities in the suburbs
Running
Get out of those places and fight for the rest of the nation
Globus while you're there
You need to run with your children
The most
Conservative Christian nationalist Patriot are you can
Okay
This is
Like I know that is audience
It's probably isn't going to hear that and be like well let's go
Is there are a couple people who take
Take his advice
Basically telling his audience to uproot their lives and go someplace where they can
Can be in a
Colt kind of
Yes what they should do is go create utopian communes based around Chris
Christian conservative ideology
You know how those work out
I don't think this is a good develop
But Alex's pretty consistent about it throughout the show he's a he's a note hard his half his rhetoric has taken
Envy
Jim Jones fleeing to Guyana
That sort of conversation is becoming introduced into the proceedings which is not good I mean I think it's also part of
The
Just voting
That idea of
People in cities armorica
Supposed to learning
Less likely to be you call it learning
Apologies
But this also raises the question of like Alex
You live in Austin
What are you talkin about his moves to the woods
You not
Although he does make completely not true claim
And the snakes
Soon as I can
I am moving out of Austin
My mom's from here and my family from here
But it is
Move my children San Francisco
And it states it's a skeleton in water areas now it's getting worse
California collapses in
Children to a safer distance away from Sodom and Gomorrah
And then
Author of the time because
Our money where our mouths are
What you don't
Earliest time to evacuate
Major blue City craft
Tell Alex is suggesting that he's going to move away from Austin
I'm telecommute in he's just going to do his show remotely from somewhere
Multimillion-dollar Studio then
Fuse for the coming downsizing but he's going to have to do
Cuz he's running out of f****** money even with the infusion of whatever he's making
From the silver and black
Good sales
Not enough to right the ship
I think this is
Could be a preemptive
Priming of people for when
Inevitably he might be doing
Cast what
Only way to do it safely
Alex Jones bass podcast
Goodluck Goodluck
So Alex take some calls
Diane of course the subject of the coronavirus comes up
And man
That dude was talking about
The
The Serta tunnel Theory
He was dumb but this guy is also.
Find out real quick the morbidity rate
I hope it's super super love
What are you predicting
I'm hoping it's going to be low
Like my brother told me I don't know where you got this
Remember don't pop any bubble wrap because of all the air comes from China
Another good choice
Sister Sister
Satisfying feeling of popping bubble wrap
With there are that they put in
Totally
Analysis response
Another dollar coin
This random caller what's a prediction
For the morbidity rate
Diculous I don't know but Chinese arrow kill you
Tonight in bubble wrap is in
The largest bubble wrap company in the world is sealed air corporation which is started by you look good
Who was an engineer who lived in New Jersey
Their headquarters is currently in Charlotte North Carolina
And I can find no evidence of their bubble wrap is primarily made in China
Also bubble wrap is sterile
The inside of it so that you can find a 2014
Teen study from NPR I'm sorry story from NPR about how researchers at Harvard found that they could use bubble wrap asthma
Makeshift up makeshift
Kind of test do
Which could have amazing applications for underfunded scientist
Particularly in developing
Open countries
They wrote up their findings in the journal analytical chemistry
And everything I guess that's really cool
Yeah
A follow-up study in the biomedical Optics
Express Journal had this and it's abstract
Quote is this paper we demonstrate that the bubbles of bubble wrap make
Deal trapping Chambers for integration with low-cost Optical manipulation
The interior of the bubbles is sterile and gas permeable allowing for the bubble to be used to store in
Culture cell
Garibaldi's left side of the bubble wrap is efficient Optical quality to allow for optical trapping
Inside the bubbles
If the interior bubble wrap is sterile enough for scientists to use them to create lab cultures
I don't think this caller in his dumb brother need to be too worried about it
But here again we have Al
It's responding to a very stupid boy by saying it's a good point
It's almost like he has a vested interest in validating
Supporting really bad thinking in his audience
She still pop those bubbles
You see the game
Games are being played here so stupid
So
We know that in the past whenever Alex is going on these large-scale
Narrative
Like with the Boston bombing
In particular it is in terms of the ones that we've seen it really
Focused on ending the trumps up to to it
We've seen evidence that his traffic was way up
And now as he embarks on this Coronavirus
We see him
Experiencing the same thing
I'll say this video is really explode into lizards doing a great job
Getting the videos out at we got we're getting
For 56 million views a day now Amanda video that really pisses Google off
Boil
Set on Friday the White House should investigate this is man-made hours later they made that announcement
No it was the day before Thursday
I went to still trying to create that experience
That the boil interview
Lay the two Trump science
Advisor
Coming out who I am
Vicki still thinks of anthem
Funny fauci which
Funny
So here's another example of Alex use
The help
Claim
About the
It's over in order to sell his toothpaste interview gargle
Which is not cool we sold out of the 16 oz
Nanosilver that still good to counter the whole Coronavirus
A family
3 oz Lafayette selling out
Quickly as well as the one ounce of selling album
Frequently
Bernardo spray on your hands and not even also ingested
Kleinfeld super blue and Super Silver
As well
So he's just today
Brazen just silver silver put it in your body
So Alex is barns on North too many clips of this cuz I didn't find it all that interesting
There are a couple things
And one is it they're talkin about a trump is beat the
Nothing
And
It said he's a Barnes
How are they going to how are they going to come out of next
And I think Alex might
Have
Something in mind
How you say you're going to try to come up the president next if he doesn't go on the offense immediately
He's definitely coming taking about these
They recognizes to closing time
3 is either going to be right in the middle of the election of right after the election my guess is it's coming as a knock
Surprised again
Again
What would it be I'm asking that level
The same Say it'll be the same type but they will try to
Will be same International orientation will be some sort of Russian collusion component again
Friday
Campaign aspec
They've tried the institution last
This one's going to be
Personal
Thailand money in some way
They're going to try to find somebody something corrupting her Giant
They don't say Trump laundered money or something I'd rather going to go after mafia ties next
My gut tells me you're call Straight Ahead when are we heard Alex talking about Trump and Mafia
Retired
Jesus maybe before he supported the name like Corleone you get arrested
The name like Trump you don't
Trump is mobbed up he's not really rich everyone knows
God
Interested
I think that's preemptive damage control
There is a story that comes out that is more explicit about linking Trump to mob money
That's Alex recognizing like a piece of his awareness I guess I need to protect against this
So let's predict
Victon advance
That this is going to be something that comes up
So it'll
That was one of my that's one of my
Huge f****** annoyance
The way it was portrayed so many
Wasn't somebody different
Media Outlets of like
Trump defeats impeachment Pusher Trump beats the impeachment
Which is f******
Convulsion
Truck what he did was everything possible
To f******
The defender
But they put more
Truxtun Beach
A Ramen
That's what happened except that Romney
Don't don't say
Chalkbeat anyting
Did the crime
And then he actively work
To undermine his defense are there afterwards undermined it
Treated himself through it that's what he did
Yeah
Just a bunch of f****** admitting to crimes on videos
What's the best legal team this side of the o.j. trial
So they're talking a little bit about the firing
Trump is started cleaning house
Into that
Office does
We come on Friday with a head of the broom
Bioweapons developer for the US had guy
It looks like it's man-made
5 hours later they doing
You just lying to Barnes about the timeline
Jesus
Horse yeah we have anybody
Even Steven Miller if he does listen which I can't imagine
But even if he does listen
Do you like
I got this guy's going to be so easy to use talking about carpet
Cleaning
Play slow and I've done it multiple times be like
I could see
The carpet cleaning
Right
Nausea
Styles for
So we have one last clip here and it's a Barnes is still there but Alex Goes to calls
Can you text a call from a guy who has
Updates about the Coronavirus
Numbers of the Coronavirus
Started reporting
69 people have
Be a 24
Mortality rate
Official numbers now show it has a much higher
Chinese government says 15%
Numbers cruncher
What do you think about the numbers
Numbers are
Continue to rise
So this colors misusing
Statistics
That 20% figure comes from a study that looked at patients who had
To be hospitalized because their cases were really
Severe which includes only people would been that had their condition progressed to the point of having pneumonia right
The number of people who have recovered from the disease is not an accurate picture of people who got a mild case and then just had some flu symptoms and got the
Better it's specifically the number of people who were hospitalized for pneumonia from the Coronavirus
Who recovered and left the hospital
And honestly
You know even if you're talkin about a 20% mortality rate for people in that subset of people who got the virus
That's not wildly out of sync with the general expectations you have for people who have cases of pneumonia General
According to Healthline quote
The 30-day mortality rate for people in Livonia is 52
10% of hospitalized patients
They can be up
30% in those admitted to intensive
Care
Oftentimes these numbers comes out really horrifying when they're presented
Out of context
Like this caller is doing
It's really irresponsible of Alex
Particularly Barn
To frame it like that
They need to be able to understand this.
Statistics that they're talking
About
And discuss them appropriately are also
What they're doing is just
Ridiculous
And that's what you see consistently throughout all of the
Information from collars and validating it he has no idea what the
This caller is talking about to be like haha yes you got them
Please take a call from a guy was worried about bubble wrap it because that's a great point
Is it taking a call from a guy was like I think they're trying to
Hi there ever a land invasion of something
And he's like hey where we have the right to speculate about whatever we want
Good on you
I can't imagine why your trunk
Keeps winning non-college-educated White
That seems odd to me I don't know demography with your followers are
Volvo
If you look at
Places that
Break
What does a heavy Eddie section of his Target
Might be
So anyway
And I
Man I was pretty glad that there was some non
Coronavirus stuff to talk about
Free stuff Seth Rich Business course
Outline by Wolf Blitzer and
Confess
The murder is certainly a guy Point can't say no to a good gut stopping
That's pretty bad I forgot now.
Text drop
Block B
It's all over your God
Absolutely
So yeah I don't know if that's a show
Cousin strong
I piss all over his show is a psychopath and he is
Chelating people's emotions
Let's see what else is going on you said he wasn't even still he was he said that cleaning carp
Disgusting so I assume that he is against Trump cleaning house I imagine
He respects paramedics who Trump in his budget
Is probably
Enjoyed cleaning carpets
Wow this could be crazy
A long list of chemicals that Alex has had in his face
HotBox
Who knows
How do I will be back
But until then
Underscore fighting at go to bed Jordan we're also on Facebook
Share with your friends downloaded on other podcast apps to why not I don't know donate to the show
And have fun
I will be back but until then I'm needle I will I'm dzx Clark I am the last living Vanderbilt
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color