Air Jordan 5 sweat it
I have great respect for its knowledge B I'm sick of imposing
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Everybody sit around and talk a little bit about
Jones
We all know that you're
Appreciator of dunks
Is quite a setup
Last night was the dunk contest
When was the last dunk contest
I mean I've died from the YouTube clips that you watch all the time back when I get to watch basketball and I was like
Diener's
So you haven't watched clips of like more recent ones
Whenever I go back and I watch dunks
Yeah I'm watching 90s don't contact I'm not not because I
I think that they're bad
Is there something magical about like those
Terrible uniforms
I think about it this way
Really excited I know it's probably cuz I was
Young man was I was watching
There's just something
There's a there's an there's an air 2 at there's a certain something
Find vets
That the present-day about NBA.
Rex Chapman baby
Vince Carter was really Innovative a lot of fans
Remember back when I was in I don't know I don't know if he was ever really relevant player but I prefer Isaiah Rider was some
Talks about is like a great dunker
The Browns of the world who would like a little
Got on her knees
Raise their hands Holy Ghost and we could MB Muggsy Bogues never went that route used tiny man
Never went
The dunk route the novel
Maybe you didn't notice or remember I didn't
He also was on the same team is like Alonzo Mourning and Larry Johnson rhinos guys were
Elizabeth dump truck
There was just some controversial as that right
Oh yeah yeah
Fill me up
Wonder God's five rounds
All 50 points
Perfect score
Then he jumped over
Tacko falls for the finals 05
He's real tall
And I
Grab the ball
Out of his shoulder
Manage to Dunkin
Jumped over
Taco 47.5
Wound up getting a 47-in
And losing wow perfect up till that point
Yeah they were apparently the story was they were the judges were trying to
Set up a tie for the final course 48
But they couldn't do the math right so he got 40
P71. Losing
Is so bad
Conspiracy theory I'm not sure if I buy into it I was trying to pay attention to your story but
I kind of got lost
Thought
I can't decide lyrics
Men can't jump over Taco Falls RX-7 could do anyting
Cannot
Read the thing that I was lost in thought about was
I can't decide whether or not I'm opposed to like when people dunk over cars
I think that I'm against it cuz I think that I don't like that aspect of it
You
And the ball and maybe another person you're jumping over
How is the person any different than the car am I being a stick-in-the-mud and every question over car is really cool
Trampoline I think not
I agree with the trampoline
Performance enhancer
Drug situation rubber slam ball
What is SlamBall
Started I think it was on like FX or something like that one of those Spike TV probably it was just a basketball
But it was a trampoline
All right now I want that last bit wasn't it fun
I want Taco Fall zotos recipe for
Neck injuries
Apparently I have a lot of feelings about dunks
And the controversy from last night's Dunk Contest I hope everybody
Is being sued appropriate
But I do know a lot about Alex Jones
Right
So Jordan today we got an interesting media episode in front of us we are going over February
12th through 14th
That's it is a Wednesday through Friday of last week
Damn it's and it's
Stickman this show has so many different tone shift
How did that you're going
To probably get whiplash
Yeah they're like real serious moods change from day-to-day
Okay and it's interesting a lot of the times we end up focusing on like one episode or maybe two episodes
Sometimes it's kind of difficult
The trace V like
This show has no connection to what it was yesterday
Quite a bit about tonight
My head Maybe
So
Who signed up and recording the show
So first Alex thank you so much you an alibi was Ewok
Next Vinson
Thank you so much
Journal apology walk
Could be could be
Rate dunker
Vicious malicious dunks
Vince Carter Alive lyrics
Absolutely
Next Craig thank you so much and I'll probably walk
I'm a policy wonk
Text Nicole thank you so much you're now about
Ryan thank you so much and I apologize
Elizabeth
Got you and I apology Wong
The big donkey
That was a stretch
Finally signed up on an elevated level
Kristoff with a
Okay thank you so much
You are now a technocrat thank you so much you are now a technocrat
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
Kristoff
The sport that you can do that
Absolutely you because we don't say this is all that often but it is may be nice to remind
Can people we have forgone
The Opera options even taking any advertising on this show at any point
I'm so it is all your support that makes this possible
And we appreciate it
And thank you
Very much
So here is an out-of-context drop
Today's Show which gives you
One of the tone
But we're going to be Xperia
Trump should fire
Who has it
Already shown themselves to be loyal
Okay wow
Okay there is
A theme
Consolidation of autocratic power definitely running through these episodes
Trump should remove anyone that he murders from a photo
Also I forgot about this but I need to take care of a couple
Things really quick
End of the show
Apple cider
I wanted to do is make a sound drop of like a bunch times Alex Lange
Amanda introduced the segment
Forgot to do that
One is a giving a lot of people who like treated at me and said messages about Coach Dave
David Mayer
Apparently he's suing the NFL or wants
Sue the NFL could you got to horny during the halftime show
Some along those lines
People accuse you
Check in on your boy and somebody has a further
Second
I have made a conscious decision
That's out
I don't want to cover that I've no interest in that even though it's getting like
No people
Water retention was
Put you on making
Fun of that dude
And one of them's a recognizes that like he has probably a couple hundred
Viewers on his YouTube show
It's not like he has a syndicated radio show that the outline
We would at this point the amplify
Yep I covering him getting horny
For the Superbowl this is something
Best left alone
No so that isn't going to happen
I'm sorry that disappointed Veep
Second thing
I keep getting messages about is
Jim Bakker
And his silver sales
I have received
Because it's running the same path is Alec right he's trying to sell his silver solution
As a way that you can fight the Coronavirus
And
I'm pretty excited about that
Not because I think Jim Baker's going to get in trouble
Because of something
That you you notice and that it is
That was everywhere
That was all over Twitter people posting the video of Jim Bakker selling the silver Inn
Just like what the fuc
Is this
And what didn't
You see on Twitter
Alex Jones exact
We have been covering this goddamn still
I'm not saying like we we deserve more attention or anyting I see tons of people talking about Jim Bakker
Doing this
Literally no one talking about Alex Jones doing it
And that tells me that Alex Jones is less relevant than Jim Bakker
Bad sign for our career
Jim Bakker just being allowed to
Beyond the internet
Be kicked off. I mean it's not great that anyone
You know Jim Bakker
More relevant
But if we're grading it on sliding scale it's good that I'm
Alex Jones
Is so unimportant
People that they don't even notice that he's doing this
Exact same thing
That they're climbing on Jim Bakker
That's good
The tells me that is
His impact
Acting his reach
Is minimal
I appreciate the
So are those
Has been sighted
Sorry to hear
So we've got a business here on February 12th
And what has happened
At this point
Is that
Trump has you know he's fired
Lieutenant colonel vindman
Ambassador sondland
And
Alex is really exaggerated
He's in a mood where Trump is f******
Can Clearinghouse everyone everyone's got to go
There's no longer be any doubt President Trump isn't waiting until he wins the
Auction in 264 days launch
Storm nailed it
Golfing the swamp in d.c.
Hundreds and hundreds and hundreds of operative
Inside
Department other agencies are being
Ashley
We speak
So we got the air raid siren very reminiscent of Bill Cooper and Alex
I'll be able to Diana government are being purged
Is the globalist
I need the people who've been impeding Trump's agenda.
I'm going on Alex's show at this point for a couple
Full days and honestly it definitely sounds like something Trump would do
The outrageously anti-democratic
Ecowise
The shity president
Problem is that I can't find any evidence
This is actually happening
The hundreds
Hundreds of people
Drop-dead fire sondland
In vindman as well as his brother
And prior to that former Ukrainian Ambassador Bridge Ivanovic
Had resigned
The state
Be honest I don't really see any
Proof that there's a mass purging
The people within the cover
And you think people would make a big deal
A post on Raw Story mentions an advisor to Mike Pence
Leaving her position
Trump withdrawing a couple of people have nominated for the positions of
The pentagon's Comptroller and
Chief Financial Officer
And the treasury Department's undersecretary for terrorism and financial crimes
There are those that still not really that
Outside of these examples I can't find any other globalist Purge
Does that are happening
An interesting way all of these people that
Have been
Records from the government really seem like they're just instances of trump retaliating against people who weren't 100% on Ford
Clearly
Criminal and anti-democratic agenda
Etsy
How to show starts with a voice-over of a guy saying you want to fight against corruption was
So does he
To be painfully off-brand browse just be like hooray for explicit
Corruption
He has to reframe
And this is the easiest way to do that
This isn't Trump retaliate
Against
Current employees
Getting Soros globalist people out of the administration
And it's not like
Five or six really egregious examples of retaliation no it's hundreds of embedded globalist
He's giving the boot
This is what I've been waiting for
Play does indictments are unsealed
Yeah
There's a serious downside to this strategy that Alex is employing
And that's the kind of leaves them without any plausible excuses for why Trump still sucks and isn't getting anything done
Forever the excuses been that there's globalist in the mix or sabotaging things and leaking
Hundreds of ne'er-do-wells
That's really easy and readily accepted excuse is going to be off the table
Seems like a bad play
It seems like a reality of what Alex is talking about cuz it's not like
Tons of purges or anyting
What he's actually talking about is there's a story that came out on February 8th about National Security advisor Robert O'Brien
Announcing some cats
To the National Security
Council staff
The feeling was the council Stanford got into big Andresen
You're so there was an interesting
Streamlining
O'Brien had been interviewed by mpri January 11th
And he said that he'd hoped to have 6270 staffers off the council by the end of February
But it's important
Point out that they're specifically staffers that actually work for other government bodies
Like the Pentagon State Department or the Department of Homeland
Security
These are people who are on loan to the National Security Council staff
And this move isn't purging them or firing them
It's really just sending them back to their home or office
I think this is what our two stock
We said the hundreds and hundreds of people
I think he's talking about these people who Robert O'Brien
Is eliminating
There
Their role on the National Security Council but not purging the bridges going back to the Pentagon or the state
I'm going to go with he's just making
Well I think he's making it up based on this
As the story he's ripping from
I doubt he even knows does he bring up that story I think eight
It does come up definitely don't know if I don't remember if it's Alex
Bring it up or guess
Yeah but I know that
The story of eventually does come up on the show
But what's important here is not
This is
Purge of all dissenting the government
What's important is that Alex's work
Hoarding it as if it
Is
And he's normalizing that idea
He's making his audience
Comfortable with the idea that a president like
Positions of people are blindly loyal to whatever he wants
Whether or not they're qualified for
For the position
This should not be a surprise
Because this is what Alex does all the time and he is not into democracy
A functioning government
Appointed how many justices do every
F******
Possible Court
Can all of them unqualified and insane
So why would we be surprised that he won
So on our last episode that came out on Wednesday of last week
We discussed how Alex
TED talks about
Rodger Stone
The sentencing
Recommendation
79 years
Immediately after we put out that episode
Little bit Wild
Doesn't matter
Bill Barr attorney general came out
And giving
Made an amended
Sentencing recommendation
Location
Alex is super into that
You really into this
And
I hear you talk about that a little bit
What President Trump had to say yesterday
He's resigned because
I want to give Rodger Stone a record-long sentence
The real quick also the sound is terrible because at this point Alex is like he's using one of his wandering Mike's
So it did
Infowars does not know how to get this sound right there whenever he wants to stand up
Happy as a different bike
It's just a
The disaster the segments
Over the course of these three episodes that I was like this and it's just not good enough
Even use have you ever been hired to work on a professional show it has a sound guy
You do all the sound for the show up sometimes I'm not a professional
However
You are better than the entire staff of info like 7 years ago
I mean I've learned
And you're not getting paid as much no problem
SUV
Prosecutor
Then resigned only to learn that that nomination was with Iran
President-trump
Rodger Stone yesterday afternoon
That's no I didn't figure that yes I'd be able to do it if I want it I have the absolute right to do it
I stay out of things
I don't agree that people wouldn't believe
I don't listen to anything he says and every time he talks I want to light this entire country on fire so amazing
Those like turns of phrase
And the way you talk
I-80
Do the Bojo absolutely
Why would the Press even
Pretend that he
Believe the conversations I don't have
And I didn't talk to them but I totally could have
It feels familiar and
Also in two weeks I'm going
You tell everybody that I did commit that
Crime rate and nobody's going to
So anyway as it relates to Rodger Stone was found guilty
Crime
By a jury
And it sentencing is coming up
The end of this month
The prosecution who work for the US government recommended that Rodger get 729 years
Prison
I'm editorializing
I'm here but I assume this is
Was partially inspired by his
Career of the
Destroying people's lives as long track record of playing Shady political games to help authoritarian
Red States and abroad is consistent Behavior
The derail that trial that he was in as it was happening
Yeah that is charging
Intimidation
He did tamper with Witnesses that's true
Editorializing I'm just guessing maybe if I were a prosecutor I'd be like a look
He's not been punished
Hundred percent done
You don't hey maybe he doesn't have a criminal record but you bet he does
But whatever the
Rodger that this sentence
From the cross
Then Trump tweeted out that is recommendation
Very unfair
Do you know just after that the doj overruled its own recommendation
Suggested Stone get less time in jail
Honestly it's a pathetic move on
Attorney General
William Barr's parts
That recommendation doesn't
Dictate the ax
That's still the judges
Decision
All this does is send a message
And that messages that isn't really real
Even even in terms of the Department of Justice
Trump doesn't give a f***
That is a yeah I'm going to go with I'm calling it
Democracy
The message is clear
In response to the revised sentencing suggestion all for the prosecutors on Stones case withdrew
From their positions in the case and one of them straight up resign from the barber
Justice
All that is fairly serious stuff
Because they're sending a message
With these withdrawals
And that is that this is a corrupt operation that they can no longer be apart
We've touched on the Rogers stuff like I said in the last episode
Before all this news
I said
That I don't really care about is 729 year sentence
Faith that he would have any punishment at all
I have a strong suspicion that this move by Trump in the department
Justices
Trap the judge
So if she sentences Rodger to a term in line with the initial recommendation
Shopkin have a pretend justification to pardon I have to Pardon him I told you this was an unfair sentencing
You guys didn't reduce it so I have no choice but to part
It gives cover today
Kind of how I see this but it would
The case I have no idea of my sense of it is accurate
But that just
That seems to be what purpose this would serve
To give cover and justify
Vacation all this activist never Trumper judge wemic gave a recommendation 6 months
Prison but I got to just get rid of them
II
I hesitate at anytime to
Attribute
Reasonable
Motivation behind
Anything like that.
That sounds so reasonable I think Bill Barr would come up with that.
Yeah that's true on the level of Rajasthan
Rodger Staubach
Exactly
For now
For now larger picture Trump is making moves unsure
The power is clearly indicating the dissenters and people who eat
Perceived as Crossing it will suffer consequences
Sniper people he perceives as allies
He'll attack the foundations of the law to do
We're entering seriously f***** up territory and now it's a cheering for all of it
Because of course he
Alex isn't into
Democracy or functioning
Yeah if there's any way that they
If there's no way the field
Fuck12
Man I don't know
That's just beyond been used to push back a little harder on your claims that
I'm still pushing back on it a little bit
But when I see I don't want I don't want alarmism here but it's not the problem
Overtime
Things have gotten more to what I was
Being hyperbolic
Little like back then
Seems like a
Yeah
I mean who knows
Huh
Who knows
Anyway Alex's world there's a purge going on he's
Super into it get all non Trump loyalists out
If Trump has done it he's launching
Legal Law Firm
Purge
Hootie Hoo
Dog catcher
Customary to remove the political apparatus of the
And office that you remove the
Adjunct
Now that we're working a on party usually because they
Are loyal to put them in
Not even the party cell for the people
A major major major blunder
He did not remove
Those individuals
And so they were working again to the whole time as Obama and Hillary
Neocon deep state
He is going to fire
Excellent
Anyone
Here we have a very clear-cut signal that Alex is fully aware that the behavior he's hoping
Z Trump engaging is the definition of a dictator consolidating power
Distress is a legal and lawful Purge of people
I can find no evidence
Is describing attacks
Is carrying out a large-scale purged of all the globalist Soros types in the government
But that's what Alex is reporting
Is it good
So I can say I consulted Infowars website see they give me any clues about the situation
Add one interesting article about a guy in the state department who is quote
Fired by President Trump is part of the
Cleaning in the state
The article goes on quote
President Trump is taking a more active role in running the day-to-day Affairs of the White House
By grabbing the rain
Trump is preventing
Himself for being isolated by his own staff a real danger given how others have acted as biki
By preventing information
Flowing to the president and they have been drugged
In his Diet Cokes I believe
Are they still doing that or do they stop doing that article that I just read from was posted in March 2018
There we go all right
I looked around a little more.
About Trump purging descent in the White House
Written by Paul Joseph Watson
President Trump is about to take the gloves off in a purge of White House adviser they could begin
Is early as today
That article is from May 2017
It's really funny when you start poking around a little deeper on their website
You really need to hire someone to clean up all that s***
From a January
26 2014 article with a sheared byline
From Alex and Paul Joseph Watson with the headline Obama launches chilling Purge against
GoAnimate
From the article
Throughout history every culture has had Maxim's in-law denouncing the openly corrupt sitting in judgment
The Obama justice department is openly launching a night of long knives style Purge of their political enemies
Did you send chills up the spine of All American
This article is mostly about Dinesh D'Souza being prosecuted for
Campaign-finance scribe witchy absolutely good today
Anything here
It's really
It's really a struggle
Really struggled not to judge
This article from November 1st 2013
Quote
In Obama's America the military must forsake their concert
In favor of blind Allegiance
It's their new Commander
I'll be really interested to hear the 10
Colonel vindman steak on that
Of course terrified of the Obama purchase
Consolidating
Empower is the dictator we all knew he was right
The boy here is that this is a super common feature of the Infowars of rhetorical
Turned on its head a little bit
The Trump era
In the preceding years every single thing that Obama did was considered an
Unconstitutional Purge
Attack on Patriots or some s*** well he was black
Dan Wright
But as soon as Alex joined up with Trump two-tone completely changed an editorial line has been wanted Amanda
Trump fire everyone
That's cuz he's orange what this is because added
Core Alex's ideology is not libertarian or Americana or whatever he pretends it
He wants to serve a dick
And honestly he couldn't have been more clear about this
Is the writer's career
It just has to be the right dick
Because he believed
But he's classes
Persian person is safe
I'm not sure if Trump said he's going to fire all never trumper's also Rose people in anyone who worked with Hillary
I can't find proof of that but I wouldn't be surprised
At this point
The reason Alex's presenting things this way however is because if
Alex says the Trump is doing these things
What could otherwise be seen as reorganizing of the security Council staff is now frame
Does the long way
Fulfillment
This is Trump
In the form that they've been begging
Who's going to purge all their perceived enemies from office
What you want
Amir two possibilities
Either Trump is doing that and now it's a cheerleading an authoritarian ruler consolidating power and silencing all those voices
Or Trump isn't doing that
In this cycle will just repeat all over a
Weirdly drop still won't do any of the things that Alex
Consistory totally wants to do
But can't cuz of all these globalist mettler's
Like really is magical cures
For every
So no excuse will be needed
And when that time comes I'll predicted Alex's just get some high-level Intel that there's another Soros mole in the admin
The last Purge
And they were what
Stopped us from getting the miracle cures all along and the cycle will continue over and over and over again
If none of this means anything else or just making it up
The one thing
That
Alex should be like going on with
With Trump about
Is the recent release of all the Pentagon stuff about how they've got
Alien UFO research going on and everybody's like
Well they might actually have something
That's the one thing Alex should be like
Release all the UFOs
Just do it
You've done that in the pasties
Music called
The past
Seem to recall even Rodger was saying the Trump is going to do that
That's not a standard feature
I want it now but maybe next week who knows Alex is
By the time we get through this Alex's on quite a rollercoaster
Need something like that
Alex
His position on this is like
Trump can do whatever he wants Delta poj to do whatever.
Hey that is totally independent that he does not have control over its
Pardoning Rodger Stone
She says that she thinks is he legal
Who does
Sunrise Leander
What should be reasonable
Justice Reform movement is about
Nonviolent people not serving lunch time
Just Department Shea
Do not give this
Person a longer sentence than you normally would
Hundred percent
Alex's of muddying up the issue here
And that's
Like it's it's
It's a question of abuse of power for Trump to have it.
Doj change their sense of recommendation
This case
It's not like the prosecutors in that case were just out
To get Rodger for no reason and Trump is trying to
Defend an innocent man has no connection
Rodger was found guilty in a jury trial and the prosecutors had their recommendation
Clearly Trump tweeted his disapproval and barmaid moves to address
Recommendation
That's all very
Clear and it's a very over case of corruption and most likely reasons going this way as best I can tell is because
Someone explain to drop that he
Couldn't just
Pardon Rodger
That would almost certainly cause a severe reaction because Rodger was sentenced
For interfering in a case related to trump it doesn't seem like that would be
Be corrupt Attorney General Metal innocence aggreko
Invitation to create a free text where Rodger
Either get the super light
Possibly no time at all or the judge ignores the new recommendation
It gives him nine years and you can easily justify apart
All the games being played here
That's very lame
Yeah I do that like
All these issues about whether or not
Criminal Justice Reform could be something a president
Advising the doj on
General guidelines
That's not even the conversation here
He's a case that specifically involved
Who's the president
Okay so
You're telling me that if Rodger Stone kildoo guy directly at the
Commando
And then he were to Pardon him
That would send the bad
That is the imagine that
The election is
Korean pear
And the results are
He's just going to pull in hwa
Pardon everybody who committed a
Like everybody
And if he did
That
I don't think
I think I'm going to be like
F*** you alright let's move on
Get up go go and
Some of them would probably face other charges
You can't pardon
State-level charges
Prosecution
Is it still end up happening
That would be the time when that could happen be like
Are you lost the election but you're not out of office yet whatever
Fine just
Divine
Just leave now
But it's not going to
Whenever a loser
Baby
So anyway I was really thrilled about this imagine purged of all the globalist
Soros
Putting people in the government
And look man
We can celebrate that
But there's something else that needs to happen
Celebrate knowing after
The Democrat deep state
Replace
Himself at the head of that
Ademco comes over and have dinner with him and Ivanka
And Sheridan
You know what maybe I was going to come
Ahead
Just got to let apple and Tim Cook
Control everything and end
Sensor and block
And and not let it be available
Put me back on Facebook
Dangerous
That's
Destruct
I want to be on Twitter
Tyranny
And taking place now
What is basically
With your prediction
But yeah that is that is kind of what what is Pourquoi
I will back on Facebook
The Purge that you're doing a volvulus
Love love it
I need back on Twitter
Time is legal
But put me back on
So you know Alex says
It's hiring hundreds
The Hitman
It's fine because other people have done
Something
About the
Finally
She's getting rid of any Obama people any Hillary people
When clinton.in in 1993
Every us attorney
Trump didn't fire any are they said that he was misusing his power
Alex is absolutely completely lying though I remember Obama did all of that
So anytime
Substantiate this flood of firing
She keeps talking about
Cuz even now days later I still have no idea who these deep Staters are the Trump was elected
Viron
More importantly though Alex is definitely gaslighting his audience about the firing of u.s.a.
Let me just read to you from a March
10th 2017 article in Politico with the headline
Trump team house
Obama appointed us attorneys
President Donald Trump's Administration task remaining us attorneys
Appointed by President Barack Obama to offer their resignations
Friday
That's weird cuz I just heard Alexei the truck didn't
Fire any of them
Wow
They offered resignation that's what all the president do
Something for president
It's due so it isn't some kind of horrific thing Trump did or anything are you
Is worth
Getting
The battery was kind of being disingenuous
Cuz it was trying to take shots of trump
Interesting Lee this strategy of pointing the finger at Clinton's firing of us attorney's to justify governmental firing
It is a very specific origin
And that is the George W bush just
In 2006 they wanted to get rid of eight us attorneys who they didn't like
Need to deflect criticism
The talking point they deployed was
To say the Clinton broke with tradition and fired all the US attorney's when he took office
This is disingenuous and also not true
From the Bush Administration
For one it was rigged
Who began the practice of replacing attorneys back in 1981 when he replaced 71 out of the 93 us attorneys that we
Replace
2006 bearings were a bit of a different situation
Because they were being done at
As part of a transition
As
Initially I took office
This so was very out of the ordinary
The inspector-general ended up releasing a report of Investigation
The sound that the firing
Politically motivated
Which is still frowned upon back then
Mingling of the Justice we were also
The flight from what ended up being a pretty big Scandal for Bush they use the talking point they Clinton fired all the attorneys when he took office
And since then
It's just been repeated Ad nauseam in right-wing media whenever they need to just
Fire politically-motivated fire
Replacing people in these positions
As part of a transition isn't normal part of riding a presidential Administration
These days
But firing a bunch of people for political reasons
3 years into your term
Is not
That is very abnormal and you can't just say what about the clintons and make all these troubling aspect
Text disappear
What's fascinating
Is that this is what
Right-wing hack
Do
This is what Alex
Pretended you I wasn't
Yeah in a bit
This is what Glenn Beck would have done
This is what I don't know Rush Limbaugh would do
Not me man I'm above the political divide
Hockey GOP talking points
I wouldn't be surprised if
In 2000
3 he went after
Not Shock me at all an easy place for him to score some points
It's the bushes so
So Alex gets to some
Interesting territory here
Starts
Search talking about not like
Can Q
Cunot we've noticed in the past couple months
She's been going pretty hard again
Committed when he was talking to
Steve
Co-opted from
This clip has a little bit of both of those things
By the way
Information from
And you'll make
Mostly easy predictions
Party line
Not going to fight with
You and like it
I am q
Infowars.com
Infighting
How to kill your all-powerful
We just have the sticker there now that
Infowars.com we love you
It's wonderful
So Alex is now selling these stickers that you put on your rallies and one of them says I am cute
Profit off of
It does
Dammit
Fuckyous bulshit
5 bucks a pop
And you get
I guess
Carry out my weird little Vendetta
Nonsense if you need any
Indication of how insincere and full of s***
Krass marketing
Motivation Alex has
Look no further than I think he was bullshittin selling
Sticker that says I am
Thank you and and we get
Another example of the first clause
Being
Demolished by the second
I've never been a big fan of info
But you suck
I've never been into inviting us also.
So Alex keeps
Calling this
Being the Trump is doing this
Purge the Red Storm
Is really trying to brand that pretty hard
Has launched the Red Storm hundreds and hundreds and hundreds and hundreds of
Whining or complaining there. Their little boxes waddling out of the federal government
National Security Council the State Department of Justice Department
Americares and now finally
So I just hate I hear things like that in person. I hear like man
Misbranded going on
Does Red Storm thing
Cuz the storm is a q thing that is a big Q through the storm
Is upon us that that service
I'm so glad I never look in
And the second thing I think when I hear a clip like that is like
Alex will be so fine
With like the night of long I
Absolutely all about it
Can you buy into whatever the state propaganda was surrounding it and you repeat it
You would not be worried at all it just be like look at this
Hitler's great it's great it's fantastic you purging the bad guys everybody
Was he was he was
It's that he was with him
The debate
Just replace that with their we're globulus
It's unfortunate that we
We use not
Coffee too much
In the previous
12 years
Because now
We really are living in Nazi
And it's been overdone week
Mechanic told me that matter and I think there's an interesting distinction between two like the
The specifics of Nazism and all that not necessarily matching up with the larger
Themes
Descent into fascism
Season that's required with that languages something anything
Even we are really necessarily equipped
Right handle and certainly Twitter isn't
Is Twitter equipped to handle not much fake Joker
And getting everyone like a beach safe
You would that you never did that
You're not going to start now
Alex ghost
Call Zane takes calls and I'll pretty upsetting
I think it's time to put the military in here
Cool
Can't deal with these people
And you know they're not going to stop
They were Americans doing it
Hi, global us-funded
They say America shouldn't shouldn't exist
And you're working
All these Bernie Sanders people say they want to put us in death camps
Okay
Totally
Sense
I'll just like just to keep track of that Alex is still pushing the outlaw the Democratic party narratives which is
Deeply upsetting
Is definitely for the military to
To cross the Rubicon begin
As we know that worked out
Alex wants not only to Outlaw democratic
Party People existing door that party at Celtics
He also
As mirroring I call her
Do you want to do process
Revoked
Enemies
Brought the war they brought
Americans
Did EXO how do you address something with normal mean
Normal measures what it's not normal
All the way up to Hillary have committed treason
We can't go to the courts
Military Tribunal
It's real
Ona political
Works in unison
Country
Is it
Right
So Alex is kind of right after WWII Military Tribunal
Those were the Nazis which
The Nuremberg
Right over technically Military Tribunal also held under the authority of international law which I don't think Alex
To be so into
Actually heard him speak
Disparagingly of the Nuremberg trials for that exact
Maybe I'll have crypto sympathies
Sporanox
Also do make the argument that its international law and I'm against
Of course
But the Nuremberg trials weren't some kind of like summary Kangaroo Court nonsense Alex wants to use to send his enemies to Skype
Guantanamo or whatever
Military tribunals are appropriate for matters related to military Justice which is to say crimes committed by and list
There's a very specific term for the use of military law enforcement or courts on civilian
Which is what Alex is advocating
That term is martial law
Which you think Alex would understand
Considering his Maiden entire career yelling dire warnings about absolutely
No I was in favor of martial law
Vapor everybody's against
Write using favorite cuz he thinks
With Trump in charge of it people like himself
Are in the clear
This is pathetic stuff but would it really Reveals His House surface-level any of his understanding is
Eat but even the main topic seat covers
Or any of that his position
It's all it's all bull
They all wanted
Yes
And
This is where things take a real weird turd
Discover Alaska
All he's really
The top leadership of the globalist
Maybe twenty people that all died in kayak accident this week
Michelle but I would support cover
Support the president
People that wax you do that there's people that can be trusted to carry out
That's upsetting
Why would why would you even play that music
They know they're not the good guy
Alex Coates Palpatine all the time
Bad guys assassination teams to covertly murder the heads of
The global estructura whatever
I guess David Rockefeller is already dead so he's not going to be at Target
But if you're a regular listener the show you know what this
A rose
First name
Of course
Mules are Bill and Melinda Gates have Hillary Clinton Obama
And here's the thing
All those people
Rusc
Alex is explicitly calling for the targeted murders US citizens by a President
He just can't be clear they would Alex
Wants is to live in the most
Brutally repressive dictatorship imaginable
Just with his class of person not affected by that
Dictatorship
Is the secret police
To become deaf
Squads and covertly murder all of his political enemies
I don't understand what the problem here is that this is
Is normal behavior
Sending in the Marines using military tribunals martial law outlawing rival political parties assassinations of City
Listen to you politically disagree with
This stuff is Oprah
Pre-classic anti-democratic
Stop
It's time to get real about things
Alex Jones doesn't hate liberals
Liberalism
As in free and open Society
And functioning democracy
Yes cuz then you have people who don't act like
Write anybody who took Chinese money including the I guess all of us
I don't I don't know how you can not picture of Ally
Anyway Alex you know
He gets out of talking about
And
He really starts talking about a lot of murders
Is really on a murder kick here on the 12th
70 years ago
What's 97%
Maybe 2% of them had electricity
Maybe 10% at running water
He's talking about China
Sorry I should have
Better
Globalism
Said anybody
That is in bed with a chai comes once they got more Eragon the last twenty years or so
They make you put one of their officers in your cup
What
Chinese intelligence agency
We don't need
To sit there and let that
Damage the economy
What you talk about what you actually did we kill
All the Chinese agents
Not me I'm talking about
LeapPad the military gokilla
It's not acting top it's not a long big man guy
What's the default
You got a foreign intelligence operative inside the Senate
Inside the house inside of us Corporation
Kill him
I got it's not a big deal
Grab them out of their house at 9
What you supposed to do
Stop playing games
Kill the Chinese agents now
Woodstock
I don't really trust Alex
To have a good
Dejon who is a Chinese Spy Who maybe is
Is a Chinese business person in order
Chinese person
I think this is
Pretty bad
Departure
Found a weird Road
Alex is really just straight-up calling for a lot of murders on this episode
Like
I don't know whether or not to be
Terrified of everything or just remember that
He's a ridiculous
Like
Nonsense
You know like
He's a clown but at the same time
So was Pennywise
It's like I don't know what to
I think of
Yeah I don't know I have a difficult time with cuz I can't help take
You can't take him
Too seriously
Of course not
Because if you did you just be like
I don't know what I would do if I took this seriously
Yeah
What are you
I just
Like it's it's one of those things where if we're vivalive always said that he
He's like the weakest link of the right-wing propaganda
And what worries me about this b*******
Is how far
The chain does this
Kind of thinking
I don't think
This goes very far but I wouldn't have thought yesterday
Before we started out right call from military tribunals and secret murders
But I think that he's touched on that in the past does not as overly and insist
I can't I can't stress this enough we're going to hear a lot about killing people
I really don't feel comfortable
Keep going
Kill the foreign agents now
Bob
I know you got the people ready to do it at don't be scared
To the media than car
Everyone's going to bite you
Sheldon
Chill now
Duet
Did he get some bad news about Sandy Hook
See that's what I kind of feel where I'm coming from right now
It seems to me like I'm a
Of course Alex is a gigantic narcissist like
Negative things are happening in his life
Medifast
Like
Severe things that need to happen
Trump needs to murder
I wonder about that but it would probably be irresponsible to assume that without any kind of evidence
So glad he does feel like
Something personal
In some way that we will have
More information to go on even
From there that something might be going bad
Gotcha but I don't know I have no idea what that would be for now it's just
Murder talk
Turn loose the US military unknown Chinese agents inside the United States
Country
We're not going to have trials are big long events are a bunch of
Frying pans
You do with the child comes do if they catch USA
I really don't think
These people because China
If I'm not much mistaken
I believe
Just seems dumb to just
Buy your own behavior by saying the China would do it
Perhaps our better countries to Aspire to when you want to come
Compare yourself to something
Well
Their satanic and Evil
So it's a good idea for us
Just to be safe
Anakin evil that makes
That's basically the argument
Alex loves the Bible and
Clearly in the Bible it says Jesus mentioned us or wants the other cheek
Anyway borvir talk
What you start there
Let's just start there
Watch the Democrats
Yellow bellies as soon as their controllers are all dead
Stopped
Playing games
Show easiest like pumpkin pie man
I need a piece of pumpkin pie with whipped cream on top
This is not hard to do
And it needs to be done America needs to stop
Rolling over this BS
We're supposed to do
So I think this is obviously a more real version of Alex that we're seeing here
That's why you said it feels good to say things like
Kill them now
It's because he's been holding back
I'm openly expressing these violent fantasies for a long time it happened
Couch that weird language
Take them out politically or
Rapping himself into a pretzel of a sentence trying to maintain
Supplies Bowl deniability legal in Laughlin
Yeah that's go in Laughlin
Right but having to do those sort of things are kind of uncomfortable
Super Bowl
Redbarn Tri-Rail
Trump is doing
Ask you the purge hundred
Globalist
Centers in the government
And Alex knows what comes along with that historic
Targeted killing
Trump is not firing all of Alex's imagine operating as if that were the case
He's doing is creating a
Pretext for in justification for Trump
Taqueria political assassination
Which would be the next logical step down this road
Alex is even creating a rationale to ignore the very understandable backlash that would come from Trump doing something like
I want to sing that the Democrats would freak out
Naturally
They would
President were carrying out extra
Judicial assassinations
Alex Dupre framing
I'm freaking out cuz they're supposed handlers are being taken out
If Alex were specifically trying to prepare his audience to accept a dictator
You could barely
Ever do a better job than what he's doing
Hi Tyson
One of my biggest
Problems here is that not only is he normalizing this language
And this kind of
But I can
Can feel it
Hitting me
Like oh is this the level of conversation that were at
Ivory Ella
I know that's what I'm saying but I can feel that
Desired
Participate
As as like
That's our conversation now you know that might be you
I don't mean that
I don't mean that in a
I'm just
Because it's so far outside the realm acceptable that it
States like a
Exactly
It's like the Overton window.
Just got exploded in
Guess what
There's more
Lawyers
The lawyers will lose this country for us real fast
Warriors didn't start this country
Warriors didn't win World War II
When the War of 1812 they won't do anything but lose the country
What
About it
Tricom came here
Overrun us and defeat us
Instead they die
Stop talking about that know your phone calls
Okay
A good I do recall it was Lawyers
Specifically who allowed Canadians
Bird on The Wire
That was the lawyers sure they were like am sorry we passed a law just recently
Everybody has to uphold the law
The Canadians get to burn down
Yeah so we
That was that was bad chunk of this episode of murder Alex really wants Trump to
Dole out some murder
And
They universally don't
Some of my other point
And one of them
Bring some normally cause Alex to really freak out
But weirdly doesn't
I discovered you
A shortwave radio and I've been listening to you
That was back in the William Cooper days
That's weird
Cuz generally when a color brings up William Cooper Alex
Gets mad at
The Alex now refers to the shortwave.
That's very weird to me
I don't know what it means but I
I always try and pull an anytime is name comes up
I always take a take notice of it it's usually anger
This case is like I'll William Cooper and everything from him and he was still alive salad
Now I'm just stealing everything after is
A caller wants to talk about the Coronavirus
Which is
Suspiciously much less important
Seems like maybe the product is sold out and no need to scare people about that anymore
Burner for when the supplies come back and I can build those merited
Keep the plates spinning a little bit
No need to freak everyone out
By saying s*** like
It's over for Humanity survivors
So this caller wants
Talk about it as a theory
About what's going on
I like to bring up
Virus over there in China
What's happening
We are using.
Can a matter of
What do you think
They were losing the fight with the Hong Kong and Taiwan he's Pro
Protesters
Chinese government lost its fight with Trump on the
Gwar
We know they're using it
Protection around the block list and so
So Alex's got this caller who suggest
Is that the coronavirus is not real at all it's just a pretext it's being used to round up apolitical.
What was a race specific bioweapon
But now it's a false flag
What is happening don't even worry about it
Anyway Alex is Francis Boyle coming back on the show
And
It's interesting to me about this
Like
This interview is completely set up based on a lie
The next hour
We got Francis boil popping in
Talk about how you called Friday for Trump
Maybe a bioweapon
Later and now the Chinese have Asperger's respond to such all coming up
This is a lie
Isn't he talking about
Cotton
Didn't
Tom Cotton Senator Senator lunatic Tom Cotton come out and say that it's
Bioweapon or something
No he's
Tom Cotton speech
I'm not sure if you said it was a man-made thing but he speaks the cotton gave
Alex has played has to do with
It not coming from the seafood market and not being
Specifically known
What is completely lying about the Francis
Spoil things
Announce
Meant from
Trump science
This guy was the day before
Does boiled interview on Infowars
In order to make it be like
Trump is listening
Infowars
We made that happen
A boil to not push back on that is
Deeply f*****
He has an interview coming up
Alex comes back
In the break it was some music
This is kind of fun
Democrat
What
Don't know much right
Little Wonder Who pedophile
It didn't work out. It's really funny that you love the devil part that's great
Imallexx karaoke
But I think that was really funny is along the way is like
I don't know much about history
When it gets to the French I took don't know what's with the French I took he doesn't know where to go with that
Hulu
French
Throw for a curved without one
Yeah
50 people with going
The French are weak and they love them
He's trapped by the lyrics to this song Because all the Democrats have to
Right
So we get into another new coronavirus conspiracy thing going on here at the behest of another caller
And this
This one hasn't come up yet
But it's really
Future Healthline how flu and HIV meds mail
The Coronavirus
How
How the HIV medication Cipro
Virus or whatever you want to call
Donut delivery system
This is one of the coronavirus conspiracy
Basic ideas that some medications that are used
To treat HIV are also being used three cases of coronavirus in thought they must be the same conditioner
Coronavirus has parts of HIV mix
Intuit
This is a really sloppy
Conspiracy and pretty easy to explain why medications are used to treat person
Stage IV would also have application
In this context
Sounds like they don't know much about biology
That seems I haven't give it a crack
One big issues here is that the list of FDA approved antiviral drugs is not a long list
And a lot of the ones that do exist
Sister used as part of normal treatment plans for
For people with HIV
When a new virus pops up oftentimes doctors will try these
Existing antiviral
You play work
And this will ultimately always be someone that you could claim his quote
Treating a new virus with HIV
Antivirals
Jubilee be called HIV map
The issue here is that these drugs will not likely be effective in the treatment of Coronavirus
The issue is that
The heightened Panic surrounding
Sing the virus
There's a real fear that the demand for the antiviral drugs will increase to the point where people with HIV could have a more difficult time
Getting there Matt Wright
The concern is that there are people pushing misinformation
Like a these antivirals are a cure or solid preventive measure against the Coronavirus
People would take that misinformation and rush out to buy out the antiviral meds
Would you leave the supply not able to meet the demand of people who actually need them
The actual picture of the situation
Pretty complex
There's some doctors who are
Experimenting with using medication
Things that are used to manage HIV with patients of other Coronavirus
But that absolutely doesn't mean that there a treatment for the virus
Nor is it proof that there's some sort of Coronavirus
Virus
Conspiracy going on
Coronavirus.
Can't make it work
It's at WeChat
So Alex
Gets to this interview with France
Boil and he once again repeat that timeline lie in the introduction which again
I have to stress
You can't
If your friends but you can't allow yourself to
Be presented like
It's disqualified
Alright joined us last week
Bio weapon
And we bad one Trump's spokespersons come out
The same thing it's a few hours later
Oil-rubbed the u.s. biological weapons
A convention to then got adopted the most of it by the United Nations
So everything is wrong about that timeline in the intro
Like we pointed out a hundred times
The interview that he did
I was
After
Trump science guy came out and made that statement
But the other problem
Timelines
Where is it at
Zach was adopted into the UN biological weapons
Convention
But that's backward
The UN version was adopted on March 6th
Biological weapons
Anti-terrorism Act was adopted by the United States on May 22nd 1990
The US version was built
From the UN version
Not the other way around
Want that to be
Be the appearance
If Alex allows reality take
Existing one who took international law and applied it to our own Sovereign Nation
Which is globalism in the very definition of evil according to Alex
Absolutely if it's the other way around
The boil wrote the law was
Do you and then adopt
Pretend that it's just good Americana that they ended up forcing the UN to enact if it weren't for us
The UN never would have
Done it.
So there's a hero
These are the little things that most people probably would
See and think about the stupid or has no idea what he's talking about and I agree
He is stupid and he doesn't know what he's talking about
It's important to understand that there are reasons
What do you mix glaring errors like this
Consistently
If Alex is Boyle's Law became you once
I probably wouldn't
Think twice about it
I just ate was a slip-up or he's being stupid
Alex says that all the time and the reason is to cover up for the fact that boy was in favor of international law
And by Alex's rubrik
He's a global
Rye Rye
He's as bad
Except for when
Brightwin
He's good he's on my
Timeline issue though with the interview and Trump spoke
Hangout is murky
Because if you'll recall
Alex didn't read the article
The about Trump spokes
One of the people who gave comment for that article Anthony fauci
And decided that he's trumps
Top science advisor
This thing's man-made
He's a hero
Unfortunately
Francis Boyle
Has news about Anthony fauci
How to is eyeballs in this Nazi biowarfare work
Years
Same is true
For the
Center for Disease Control
So now I do Alex's big special special expert
Me beeping Nazis as project right so I imagine Alex
It's going to he's going to immediately agree with him and then scrub the article from Infowars
It's a difficult position this puts Alex in because
The whole narrative was that Anthony fauci is Heroes coming out
Prompted by Francis boils interview on Infowars that Trump hurt and he forced
Anthony fauci to come out in
And blow the alarm
All this
Tries to save this a little bit but I don't think he does it well
Without me asking the questions you're the expert
The Indian Institute saying it looks man-made showing words clearly been gene-edited
He's good or not
There are responding and incomes come out again and now the Chinese ambassador
No big deal with without cheese and Nazi scientist or whatever
Leave that aside
That's that's real weird s***
He's doing now Shores another bar illogical science but you know what
Even the blind
Squirrel find the occasional lie Nazi project have you done for me lately
So
Francis Boyle has nothing really
To offer that's a really boring it
Interview
Until when I can listen anymore of it
Alex gets back to
Murder
Why doesn't he utilized a black eye
Daenerys
City of them but
We're entering a wheelhouse now or the Deep State confront overthrowing where
He won't have a choice
Wish
Happy about this but it is what it is
They're bringing us to a place
Once we get there that make sense
Yeah totally not our fault when we
Politically sexy people
We did
You are you guys are going to murder for a long time now you don't get to say it
Just stop it don't believe it on us you want to people you disagree with
Say it
Can't because they
Even Alex knows that that isn't appropriate
This leaves Alex
Listing people that Trump needs
Yasso Alex you were talkin about
I'm sorry the caller
Credit
For the guys we got to get out of there was Zorro's
Brennan
DC
We just got to go out for the snake and I'm not saying we're going to do it
Trump
Needs to cut the head off the snake
Says caller list
Like specific people the Trump riots
Skill and Alex says
He doesn't like Obama's work with
Netflix
Is about
One last clip here from February 12th and that Alex is like getting into this weird headspace about like they've come at me
They've come at me
He's already been in this like I didn't need to murder all these people
Slightly adjust
Navigation like I've been wrong
And it's just such a
9 months ago
Department of Justice
Under these people
My dad
Because some Bookkeeping on the prod
Development
They knew I love my dad
What else
You ready to go to prison the Asia I'm ready I got to get we're not backing down
Anyway
He's an old man he's ready to go
I said you can literally
Crazy actually put the behind-the-scenes
They realize that
I don't care about me
My dad and my dad was like
Destroy me
Totally made out there like
Your father
The level of the scum you cannot even imagine
So there's a good reason to be able to run the Department of Justice might of making inquiries to Alex
Rodger stone is on trial and he was an employee
As much as Alex wants to say his dad barely involved in the company on many occasions Alex's dad David
Has been presented as the head of
HR human resources
I didn't forward parent company Free Speech system
When Alex was facing EEOC can
Complaints from Ashley Beckford and Rob Jacobson
David Jones was the Human Resources Director that he fielded media requests
In other news stories he's been given that title and by all appearances
He's the person who's in charge of Staffing employee related issues for the company
On December 18th 2018
Alex's dad was
Deposed in the Pepe the Frog
But what's this
He wasn't supposed
Himself
He was the corporate representative of speech system
Which led to this Exchange
Would you want to wet back and read the deposition
I read it a while back
But now after the Rob do deposition this is particularly funny
Thought it was question
Lawyer
You understand you've been designated as a corporate representative
Free Speech systems
Today's deposition
Incorrect
Response
Who designated me that
I suppose I was advised by email sometime ago they're going to have a corporate designate
And I had agreed at the time that I'd be willing if it was prudent
Question
Okay
Did anyone advise you that you were in fact going to be the corporate desert
Take me for free speech systems
Answer
I think I was advised but I didn't really realize the full impact of that but
Yes
The pattern for Alex in his lawsuit
Just making someone he thinks he can trust me the corporate representative for his company and having them going to the deposition
Completely unprepared and
In Stonewall
He did that with Rob do in the Sandy Hook
And he did with his home
F****** father in this case
It's very clear strategy
Alex and his lawyers employed
The derailment slowdown trials
That they know they're going to lose
And man it's just wild to read that transcript of the 2018 deposition and realize that altitude willing to put his dad
In the position of being a pain in that kind of a game
He's a real piece of s***
They know I don't care about myself so they went after my dad surprise
I don't care about him either
The globalist and I were trying to take out Alex's dad
Alex made him the head of enforce Human Resources so we can have a person who trusts in that position
And their consequences to moves like that
Coincidence with one of your employees
Facing federal charges
Maybe a thing where you're getting a message from the prosecutor
Or I don't know let's say another one of your former employees let's just call him Jerome corsi
She tries to sue you
It is contention
Isaiah he was wrongly terminated as part of this part of the discussion
It might have been dubbed
Getting your head of Human Resources
In this case your father involved in that legal matter
This is a narcissist operator
When they're facing the consequences of their own action
They're not able to accept them on realities terms so the consequences themselves become a part of a larger
Thereby allowing Alex to maintain and even expand his own victim
Alex's dad in his capacity as the enforcer HR director gets contacted by prosecutors of lawyers
About legal issues related to former Infowars employer
Employee
That is completely normal and if
Predictable thing to have happen
But Alex has become
Globalist tried investigating takeout in poor innocent completely uninvolved father
Any Target your loved one
This is really sad levels of Alex
Acting out his own issues on his audience
It's wild thing cuz dad hasn't check
Check the stuff by this point
This allows it to
Continue
Must be a lot of money
Dad must be way
Crazier on the John Birch
Step then
Yeah
It's very plausible that like he is
It's far more of a zealot than we know cuz
We keep such a low profile
Come on Alex's show
Version of that
Yeah yeah I mean obviously if you're the head of HR there's a tacit endorse
Whatever it is
Alex says
I mean if you don't get becomes murky whenever it's like
Your family and maybe didn't want to be a dentist anymore whatever you know
Nose
So we jump to the 13th and Alex's feeling real good
About to Rogers chances
And makes a little bit of a predict
Sitting here out of the gate
Massive outrage of
Adjusting you at the world no one is buying
This miscarriage of justice and
I predict
That way then
2 weeks
Rogers town will be back
Co-hosting this broadcast and the War Room
And thus the silencing of this American patriot who was pain
Trump
Getting president
Want to run for office making President Trump
Believe
Goodwin
President Trump would not be president if it wasn't for Rodger Stone
Dangerous mentality that Alex's expressing
Because at its core what it does is it makes it so anyone on your team can commit any crime they want
When Alex says that Rodger is being prosecuted cuz he helped Trump get elected
One level what you saying is
True
But on a deeper level
It's also very not true
The issue was that Rodger is not being prosecuted for
He's going to prison for actual crimes he committed and was found guilty by a jury for
I've never actually even heard Alex discuss the real charges that Rodger was convicted
Not once have I heard Alex discuss be very clear open
Shut Witness
Intimidation
The Rodger engaged in with Randy credico
He never talks about the reality of the charges because
The reality Rogers actions has been replaced with a facade
Which can be easily summed up his it doesn't matter what the charges are because he didn't do it and even if he did they're only charging
Sports Trump
No matter what you do if you're on the
Team 1000
I've heard that
The ends justify the means
Can't think of any possible morality that would contradict that it's important to understand this dynamic
Because
It's the way Alex needs
Present this person
They have to be a
Pure hero
So whatever the reality of this
Stuffed it is
Actually happening
Don't even talk about
Alex knows what charges
Roger's been convicted
No
Jury
Found him guilty
But he knows all these things
Discuss any of that
Because he's a good guy
He's on the T
This is important
I need to make a point of this
Is is relevant later
Always
I just can't
Can't believe that he
He still has
Figured out that Rodger stone is
Greatly contributed to ruining his
It's insane how
Severe you can't possibly want Rogers
Just don't back he ruins your f******
Lifemap
Yeah but if you ruined his life maybe he
We can save the ship
Care about you
Alex
Trump's going to Pardon Rodger and that's cool
Currently
Arrington
Arden
Rodger Stone
Function of Justice
That's why you have an executive branch
Co-equal to the legislative and the judicial
Right bicep
Separation of powers
And it's part of our federal system
I apologize it's just good old-fashioned separation of powers stock
It's not separation of powers on the executive branch intervenes to overrule the
Judicial Watch
Specifically related to the criminal Affairs of
Zippy head of the Executive Branch
What else is describing as how a normal pardon my
But in this case
Trump would be absolutely out of line
Departing Rodger given that his conviction Again by a jury
Was it related to impeding the investigation into the criminal Affairs of
Pardoning Rodger would be more less just Trump
ABCmouse sending out a very overt message that if you commit crimes to
Protect his crimes
He's got your back and you won't do any time
The
Anaprox
And I suspect that's why I again they're going with the bill Barr route first
I need to be a protector
For this really feels like
Has eroded is our system is now it still seems like that would be a breach
Norms
By using a presidential pardon to get your friend who's in prison for lying to peden investigation into your actions
It seems like even
As bad as things are now that's still too on the nose
Probably right but
Is it is getting really frustrating that nobody in the media is willing to
Point out that the big reason Trump is getting away with all of this s*** is
Because we're all kind of afraid that if we hold them accountable
His supporters
Will start murder
That is kind of a big deal that is unspoken
I don't know if he will but there's the
Fear of it I don't know if that's motivating
As much
Izzy's
Remind me it might be a piece of it for some
Folks but I don't know I don't know how widespread that is
As a motivating factor
For the people in the meat
I don't know it could be I think I would prefer that to the admission that
Both the Democratic party and the media are
Essentially useless and pointless
Ascend
Really wished
But that word wasn't true
What type of beer is like Obsession of
Appearing neutral
Do you have to take
The Democrats love battle
It was appearing
Hey Irene you have to present climate change denial is
Exact absolute mentality does
MP people
2 in expanded probably more than a fear of
Trump supporters murdering people
Maybe
Anyway
Alex has decided that tell you probably going to maybe I don't know possibly go to sleep
C-pack to Kazu
Publicity stunt
A complaint about seat
A little bit here
A new obsession
You talked about it a bit on
On this episode like how much he doesn't like seapak
How they're all cowards
NOC
C-pack so cowardly
People like Rodger Stone
Aren't even welcomed there
Actually got Trump elected
Trump's up against
I don't need to do that so I'm
But
Really thinking about it
Okay
Jordan the notoriously restrained and cowardly seapak
Who could forget how cookie cutter and safe there a speaker list wasn't 2019 but they had Sebastian
Diamond and silk
Candace Owens Charlie Kirk
Going back to Dennis Prager and Oaks
Donald Trump speakers of maybe two or three people on that list
To have an outright
C-pack is not afraid that complete yet heads in Convent is speakers they just don't want 1/2 or bad for the brand
That's why they disinvited Milo
After people started talking about those Pro pedophilia comments he's made in the past
That's why they disinvited gatewaypundits Jim hoft
After he started spreading cancer
Theories about
Survivors of the park
Oakland shooting
That's why they didn't let Laura Loomer and Jacob Wohl
They don't care if you're lying s*** head just so long as you're not too embarrassing
At this point Alex and Rodger are really embarrassed
Also c-pack might not want invite Rodger because in 2018
He was involved in the first year of a rifle conservative conference called the American
Priority
Which was trying to Brand itself as the
Bcpac for Trump
That conference
Probably going to that lose altitude
Hotel in
Involve the whole lot of s*** head saying dump
Conspiracy stop in
Selling idiots knick-knack
Think of any problems there
Priority conference
2018 overhead speakers like Stephon
Mike cernovich
Whose speech apparently was mostly about how qanon is real
This is the lane that Rodger belong
And even f****** c-pack understand
They are afraid to have him come speak it's just that he's an embarrassing
Criminal
Stefan molyneux we prefer other embarrassing criminal assholes
The funniest thing here though is that Alex probably wouldn't even be invited to speak American priority conference
To toxic
For the junior varsity
Super toxic Brands welcome version of
C-pack
And that's a good call on their part
You can't invite Alex
Because that he would make your event all about him
He's so desperate at this point that he could be
Completely welcome somewhere and eat still show up in a tank with a bullhorn
Acting like he's breaking in
Focus 2.0
Just calm down dick
Whatever benefit or game there
Could be from having a lie
Anywhere
Far outweighed by having Alex
Yep
At this point Alex
Like it's actually a little bit refreshing in some ways even though what he does is terrible
An awful
But like
We've been so starved
Different
Contact because of obsession about the Coronavirus
And now like it
Take out the Rogers stuff really taken over and the doj and Trump pardoning
Which leads into the murderer Obsession on the last episode of regret wishing for a change from the Coronavirus
Stuff if the change is
I do
I do regret feeling a little a little desire that seems like it's been a long time since they're just been like
Straight headlight
Yeah
Teachable
Yesterday where to
Somali migrants
Went on a spree robbing stabbing attacking
What you got to give it up
Afraid
It's a religious virtue signal
Can you show yourself
Why are they doing that it's a plan to bring down the civilization
I think this is a perfect
Example of how bad Alex is at his job
Like what is he talking about
No clue you hear him telling story about some Somali immigrants who went on a spree of crimes but would like go cuz
You know the left isn't the letting non-white people get away with
Crime supposed to bring about the end of civilization
That's what I would you know
Always.
But when you take a step back
What do you know about the underlying story that
Based on the details Alex provides we don't know anything about this
I don't know where they're at
Country it took
Play snoke
This isn't covering a story this is
Gossiping about a headline he might have skin
Or more likely it's just now it's making up a story in order to justify him going into a xenophobic
Which is what he was going to do whether or not I had a story to base it on a 90
Why are you even pretending
You can't track down this story based on the details Alex provides and that's intense
He doesn't want to portray reality or help his listeners come to a better understanding of the world
He wants to reinforce an
And Harden Their Fear of the laugh
And people who don't look like
I decided to see if I could place down the story that Alex is covering you know for fun
Infowars website with no help
There wasn't any story like
It's on there so I started Google
I just like that
Infowars website with no help
Story that matched some keywords
From February 2nd 2020
Judge refuses to vacate Somali pirates
Got to give it up to
This was a story from the
The Elko Daily Free Press covering a federal judge's ruling in Virginia that is Somali pirate could not have a sentence
Thrown out
What you were seeking because he claimed that his lawyer was ineffective in the underlying trial
The judge said nope
And that's Molly man still in prison and they let him go free that way what
So that's kind of the opposite of the story that Alex
You think it based on the narrative that Alex is selling aspire to be
Exactly the sort of person
The federal judge would release
Is a perfect religious virtue
Two signals sacrifice
It looks like the reality is the opposite of
Miss queso
I kept looking
And there's only one
Somali pirate
I believe I don't know I just kept looking
I couldn't find any evidence
Do judges releasing any Somali immigrants
A stabbing so I started searching for Smalley and spree
There was one story from September 2019 out of Minneapolis
But this wasn't about a Somali immigrant going on
Stabbing spree
A guy named Harlan St John getting arrested for going on a vandalism
Free smashing out the windows of Somali owned businesses
Because
He told the police quote
Somali people are selling meth and heroin
Native people
That's not the case Alex
To talkin about
I also don't think that guy
No
Think he was
I think he was talking about a different
Yes quote
I want to be cute about this but honestly I have no idea what story Alex is talking
About and that's kind of my main point
If I someone who's
Actively trying to figure out what story out to talk about having no idea
People who just passively listening have no clue what's going on and what's real and what Alex is just making up
When people in positions like Alex
Are vague
Because they're making things up
If Alex really had a case of a small lease priest Abaddon free because it was religious sacrament of virtue signaling for the laugh
LaFollette immigrants commit crimes
To probably be in his interest to actually cover the details of the
Go over there what's the name of the stabber the alleged stabber what's the name of the judge what's the
What country did it happen in
What are the circle
Status of the case
You didn't do any of that cuz he's not covering the news
He's creating a Feeling
Stealing is supposed to be
Purity Auntie left
An auntie non-whites
Details just get in the way of that could really mess things up
The truth there's
Is a lot of nuance and
Contacts that goes into it and that really makes it hard to
You know you have to
Wade through all the stuff in the year
Tired at the end of it
Computer screens or
Maybe just hate
Hey kids
Because another headline
North Korea shoots coronavirus patient after
Be seen at public
This is a race specific
Bioweapon it is man-made
That's why governments are freaking out
This is mutating and it's very very serious and I love you
Show me the day before Alex got a call from
Some guy was saying that the virus is just a cover-up to round up people were protesting against
The Chinese government
It's not a race specific
I got released
Now it's agreed with
I'm slightly at all.
With each other specific
He has no consistency
Cages by Design This is so much
Andy Daly as l.ron Hubbard
Ted office podcast look like
I said it's
I listen to the show all the time and honestly I don't even think that I could
Could tell you what the show's position is
On the coronavirus I really don't know
I think he's rooting for the Coronavirus
Coronavirus
Some days it's a race specific bioweapon
Some days the bioweapon China wanted to use on us that got loose accidentally
Sometimes it's all a cover for something completely unrelated to Public Health
Sometimes it's not even real
Makes nose
It's abusive to his lesson
Like this day today what up
He's not saying anything
But he's also
Suggesting a whole lot of stuff
The presentation that he is saying these things and that's not cool
Also that story about the North Korean official may or may not be true
It was from the South Korean source
Information about it I'm not entirely sure
I have no idea if it's true and neither does Alex
This is reading a headline inserting it a
Is back.
Details of the story
Just kind of irresponsible
Alex is another color
And the virus is now
Maybe not afraid specifically was like this immediately after
Only people who have died
Where in China
When they got the disease
I don't even think it was
Something else is killing them
You know what I mean
Kill some people but there's no doubt
Putting some fake videos out in China
Cape Fear
Where's the race specific part of North Korea and now you have this car
Call who sang it wasn't
The disease that killed them
They're trying to crack down on you with you
Of course of course this is so inherently incoherent it's just
It's it's really believe whatever it is you believe I agree with you so long as you by my
So Alex
A little bit about The Purge
The Trump is doing of people in the government which I still don't
No
Is accurate
He's really trying to make this red storm thing
At work
What I do know is the red storm here
Urging the traitors
Accelerating in the attack and I love it
Can you Jean man I love it
And let loose the dogs of war
So at this point I was really marveling at how desperately trying to make the red storm happen
Was curious about what's going on here
Obviously he's trying to evoke the storm
Stunad
Probably also the red
Terror which of course is the. Of political terrorism
Who preceded the Russian Civil War back in
However
I have a slight suspicion
This might be a Steve pieczenik
I base that on
The interesting coincidence
There's a Tom Clancy novel called
Red Storm Rising
A company that licenses
Does Tom Clancy properties
Video games
Just called Red Storm
Course
Steven nothing to do with any of this
The time
But he's notoriously
Real life Jack Ryan
Need some so heavily with all things
Clancy
This is probably on my part of complete stretch
I've no reason to believe this Theory even make sense
But there's something super weird but I was incessantly drive to Brandis the Red Storm
Which happens to be Charmed it's only really widely associated with a
A former business partner of Steve pieczenik
Most likely it's just Alex trying to Launch
A phrase that he can put on some
Shirts
But you have to forgive me if my mind wanders sometimes I was a show-off in his
Very bored I'm going to go with
It is Steve pieczenik and also Steve
Is Rasputin
I'm going to say that
100% positive you heard it here
Irfu I never died
Have you been to Korea bunch
I just heard that this red storm stuff and I'm like
What's the name of this song
Plantation
Steve Garvey looming in the background somewhere
You have this whole thing with Rodger
Department of Justice this is prime pieczenik stuff like
He's coming
I don't know I just wanted to know
Red Storm would be
Phrase
Is related to see now I'm like putting yarn up on the wall
You can hear Steve pieczenik
Footsteps behind you
He's always also
Red Storm is also the nickname for the sports team
St John's University
So it's probably trademark
And I really hope Alex tries to launch some Red Storm birds and then get sued.
God
More lawsuits
So Alex takes call from a guy and
This guy
Is like a man
The street
Should support Trump more
And the rationale is bad
They are conservative Alex
It's not
Gay marriage they're not for
People that are in these streets
And I truly believe that they will get behind Trump
Hundred percent
Losing
Troll of the plantations
If I understand this caller's argument he seems to be saying that
Street should be supporting Trump because they're all the dolls on the phone
I don't know if that's a good argument when you're trying to present the idea that Trump is a uniting force
Whatever
About Trump having record Black and Hispanic support
Deputies not being specific about that
Because if you was you probably be lying
If you go back to speech that Trump gave on the campaign Trail back in 20
16 he said quote
At the end of four years I guarantee you that I will have over 95% of the African-American vote
I promise you because I will produce
This is in stark contrast to a November 2019 hill-harrisx poll
It sounded
An overwhelming majority of black voters
85% said they would choose
Any Democratic presidential candidate over Trump
In reality is probably never going to get anywhere higher than like
Like 10% and that might even be generous
That is not record-breaking
Unless you're talking about it being a record for true
Himself
Which is a little distant
I think this is all a little bit silly for Alex
The Advocate to be bragging about Trump
Support while discussing with a collar
Streets
And Trump can find Common Ground over the agreement the trans people shouldn't be allowed to exist in public
And not heterosexual couples should be allowed to marry
It's a weird
She was talking about the British
Rapper the street
It's Danny was talking about.
And I didn't know that guy was at homophobic
It turns out
If you got this
Streets play in your prefer Lady Sovereign
So this caller goes on to talk about how great Alex's iodine is
And I don't
X2 and without Donald Trump
Liberal left-wing crazy believe in the mainstream media pop culture in Hollywood
Help me
Take me to Clarity and focus
Understand
Really going on out here so
That's not
My IQ
So except in cases where someone is severely iodine deficiency
These products aren't going to do anything other than Apple
Placebo effect
So long as listeners are eating salt
There's nothing these products
Do for them except trick them into thinking they're somehow seeing through the Matrix
How to speak real s*** head when he say to these studies about iodine increasing IQ
Because he knows or has every reason to know these studies are not saying that if you take iodine that will make your IQ go up
They're showing IQ differences between people heads
Severe iodine deficiency than those who did not
Most of the studies at Alex
Actually about maternal iodine levels and effect I can have on fetal development
Alex who I should point out are grown adults
Taking iodine
There's a classic case of Alex creating
The fake problem
First products to solve
He tells his audience at the globalist or trying to dump them down and iodine can fight back
Against the onslaught
Listeners take the iodine have that placebo
Which is a company by listening to a ton of Alex's s*** on question
They adopt his narrative
That looking into any of it themselves
And pretend that that's them seeing through the maitre
Which they were able to do
Thanks to the miracle brain boosting power of iodine
Really sad Griff we can see that it definitely does work some
Ideology
That doesn't
So Jordan I have given you a stout
Yeah we're we're going to crack open here a morning latte
From the toppling Goliath Brewing Company out of Iowa
And against Iowa but I will make it
Not sponsors of
Michelle but I felt like it would be appropriate for us to have a
Have a mid show
Everybody's been clamoring for new novels to know specifics
But another reason they were having a little
Stout here is because
I'm pretty convinced that Alex
Yeah ends up drunk
Although I'm pretty sure
A lot of people have suggested it over the course of the last month
Drinking on this episode
I don't really necessarily agree based on certain behaviors
That I find to be uniquely
Sometimes that I think Alex
Alexa
If you will and
And I believe
I bet it is Mike
Conjecture
Guys that Alex
Towards the end of this episode
We has
Norm pattis
Call Michelle
Of course and I don't think
Alexander Palace like
I don't know why
And I think well I mean certainly that time that I would put out a bounty lawyer
Bike
I had to sit there I don't think that
Lends itself to a friendship
I don't think that they like each other very much and I think that Alex news
He's going
Becoming on the show we're going to talk about Rodger Stone related legal issues
I might need a drink
For that yeah I think that's what happened
Because hallux
And him
Holyshit
This goes bad
It starts bad
Cuz I was makes an announcement that Norm has to immediately retract
We should go ahead and make this announcement even talking about this for a few days in the main
Pull the trigger earlier
We are going to intervene
And the Rodger Stone
Okay simmer also to me working with Mike cernovich on this
I answered
To go in and show in the car
Court records which are very expensive
Records
With these jurors bragging the Democrat
The southern sure whose husband was a top lawyer on the Mueller probe
For the intent of even finding out in a conflict
Sure the whole house of cards for Paterson
Starting to clap
Correct the record when you say intervene that to turn with legal significance
Party but my office is right now it's
Locate and obtain
Copy of the trial
Have meanings in the world of the law
Consistently throughout this interview Alex
Keep saying things
We don't do the Supercut of
Norm responding to Alex
Supermarket
You know I can't
Go that far I'm still in Oxford Accord
That's news to me
Comment on a case-by-case basis
Does a lot of just like I
Alex
So it's interesting because I mean what's going on here is that they're trying to create this argument that they
Jurors were biased
Sure. Rodger Stone case
Like Norma's on here and he's even said
I don't even have
The transcript
I'm just
Texting them
If you listen to the language
Tuesday are like
It's very clear that they're just guessing
You're entitled to a
Jury of your peers impartial jury historic
Play what that smell
Or musica quesos
Evaluate the address
I'm in some courts that means
People don't know anything about the parties or the party
Kiss offense that's rare in a high-profile case
Berkeley they just have
Impartial they have to set aside whatever they've heard and commit to being able to try the case based on the evidence in the courtroom
However do the
Anticipatory entitled to an honest answer with
Respected sources of bias that yours may have
Mike cernovich is reporting that one of the jurors I'm head run
Is a Democrat
Prior to trial
Unclear to me as I sit here today whether that was disclosed to the lawyers in the
On this day
Sure has now come
Forwarding and written to her about her outrage over the resignation of the four
Biofrost
Peters this week
Suggesting that in fact she had very strong views at the time of trial
So if you listen to that he's saying
His language is completely clearly has no idea that person who ran for office desk
Closed in the jury selection phase of the trial
Norm's just speculating that it wasn't but guess what
Anybody who wants to speculate that it was brought up has as much ground to stand on their not saying s***
This isn't a claim
It's just a marriage
What's being built at
Considering all of this is just information
From Mike cernovich
Cernovich is going after the jurors in the
Mistrial
Disqualified
And I guess get Rodger out on a technicality
It seemed to have a new trial
Seems weird to spend as much effort on something when you have a pretty good-sized
Probably just get a pardon
But that's where it gets important to understand what this is really about
Cernovich and Alex are trying to get the case retried
They're not trying to get the overturn the verdict
Create narratives that provide cover
Rodger
Because all of these jurors are all biased
Add have to Pardon him still
Still larger than that
To essentially say that
Trump is the Arbiter of
Notaries are
If anybody
Is convict anybody in the Trump orbit of a crime
Because they're part isn't
There is no rule of law
It is purely Trump win
That about a largely and then more specifically give Trump the political cover that he need
Thanatologist week shift like I went and looked at with crnkovich
Just putting out and one sort of itches gotcha moments
Is it mentioned
Rodger Stone on Twitter in the past
Though the jurors were asked if they posted on social media about the subject
Which would be Rodger
The Smoking Gun that's shown here is a jerk
Just wonder retweeted
Bakari sellers
Tweet that said quote
Rodger Stone has y'all talking about reviewing the elusive
Force guidelines
Not Alton Sterling not Eric Gardner not Walter Scott knots on Sandra Bland
Not Keith Lamont Scott not philando Castillo not
Terence Crutcher
Not DeAndre Hamilton
Rodger Stone
Think about that
This is clearly not a tweet about Rodger Stone it's about the treatment of African-American so excited
Police also she just tweeted it that wasn't even her tweet
I think you could very accurately say that you never tweet about Rodger
Just don't even if you retweeted that
This is thin
F****** broth
The rest of his Brew
Is that you created some negative things about Trump in the
The past and to that I say so what
It wasn't
Trial by
It was about Rodger committing
Crimes
It's very possible for a human adult to not like Trump and remain unbiased about a legal matter
Involving water
Associate
Just because Alex can never be impartial if he were a juror in a case involving a
A friend of Hillary Clinton
Doesn't mean that normal
People are incapable of
Like friends
I f****** hate Alex Jones
But I could be totally impartial in a case involving his cousin buck
Princeton
Yeah that would be
No
I would not be able to be by
Actually I probably
I think I should I hate the crew
System so much
It's it's a real cat
22 I honestly think that I could be impartial in a case
Even involving Alex
But I texted me saying that no one would believe it
So I'm going to make that claim
And also not stand behind you could be impartial in any
I agree with that
You do not belong on the tree
0 faucet
Was really stupid and would never hold up in court
But that's okay because it
It's not designed
It's meant to be played for a public opinion narrative
The provides cover for Trump to abuses power and pardon his friend for trying to obstruct an investigation
Which makes it particularly sad for Alex's lawyer to debase himself by lending this week s*** credibility
Barnes really needs to give Nora McCall and get him up
Just be that it's time to bail
This isn't going
To go where you want it to
So
Alex
Is like
Norm to talk about the the case and Rodger being innocent and all that
But also he's
Fixated on a headline
Find these red
About this Cambridge
Professor
Has written a book
Basically making the argument that humans should stop reproducing
Nubian Africa
Cove in grievance
Stop reproducing
Because of all the
Systems that we've brought into the world that are
Destructive
And that you know
Unpacking unpacking all of the things
Capitalism
All the systems
Things that we have
Foreign
To Nature
And we need to dismantle those
The only way to do that
Is through our gradual
Getting
Gone
People have made these sort of argument the idea of a
Extinction by choice
That's
Bananas well I mean there's a voluntary human
Engine movement for a very long time I just don't think it's possible for any organ
M2
Cause it so next
I think I mean
Kill itself
It is possible but it's
It's also all Valen
Ontario
First thing
It's not about murder it's not about telling you to kill yourself
And it's not even something that
I would guess
This Cambridge Professor believes
Could be implemented
It's just
Ethical dissertation
That she's putting up
Now also she has tattoos and kind of looks like a witch
Well there we go Bears are bigger issue
Bears are bigger issue it's surprising to me that he isn't talking about all of these types
Books that have been written
Choose this one particular
Well because it's current do you read a headline about it
And this lady looks like a
Fixated on this and insist
The chi needs to kill her
Norm is not happy about this and we will learn why in a little bit
Look at
Human race must become extinct to save the planet
Rebellion
Guess what she's got Medusa on her arm
Yourself a big old
Honey some barbiturates who kill yourself
You're in to death you're in destruction you given up on Humanity I don't want you to hurt yourself
You got that broadcast
Go take care of
Dub's lithograph
Go see Jesus
Map Norm is got to be thrilled that he showed up like
He's got to be
The point where like Alex got drunk and yelled about wanting a bounty on the
He had to be like
It always goes bad when I go out about Rodger everything's fine I was just being the
A little bit you know saying we're going to intervene that's not
I can correct that we can get by on this
Now you talkin about how this
Professor needs to kill herself
Can I get your take on this she should kill herself Keralis
Young lady lead-by-example
Some respect
If you jumped off a building today or Switzer rest
I'm not saying she should do that
We should all die while her first Norm
I mean I don't know where it was how he'd intended what what to make of that
Norman he doesn't like her argument and he actually has a pretty good response to it
About like love being transformative
Is I hate
Don't hate on her baby
If we all show compassion and love it'll change
A perspective on this
That's kind of the angle he's coming from
The f****** hatch
Well he does
Is he does make that point
This goes so bad
Aiam look dude
Norman is next
Say something
That Alex should
Take as a
Can stop it
Play u gopher
We commit suicide China wish that on anyone
That is the pole
F*** it which
You immediately start practicing empathy towards the person
You're like
Some jokes II
This is disrespectful
I'm sorry for your loss
I apologize for inviting you onto this episode of Curb Your Enthusiasm apparently is how this is going
Human
Decency dictates
That you take that as a sign like an enormous being very polite and saying I just lost someone to suicide and
You know Sia and I'm not into this
What he's really saying is
Stop
He's putting a boundary
Don't like
Him and even I would
Immediately apetamin empathetic
Alex
Doesn't take a quiet
The same way that humans might
I just I just want her to go first
And I'd go easy Alex upgraded we all need more all in need of Grace and she needed more
If you want this all the Dodger saying let's go
You know that's not song from Elf
Yeah I thought
My husband honey
You ain't got no place to go
Put your arms around me
Real tide
Yeah I was around here when I realize like these are the drunk Behavior I haven't seen in awhile like this sort of stuff is
Is very
Like in the Alex
Drunk
The inability to understand the slide
IQs that are actual
Screaming out of
Norm
About like Alec
Cut it.
Are insane Alex just won't stop
And I
Really get the science
Norm
It's Alex
When
Giving her what she wants
Glove in the power of Grace is overwhelming and certainly to transform my life and I hope it would hurt
As well
Form of having a little fun today
Got me a text a lot
How to make me speechless you have that gif
Alex
The lawyer way of saying
I hope
You like yourself on fire f****** murderer
Got hummus
He must need that money he must be getting paid so much
I don't even
Maybe also like
High-profile can't hook me up a lot of publicity out of it
Conceivably Isaac gets
Closer to when it goes to trial
If you really think that there's a chance he could
Like weasel through this case on a technicality
It could be a huge thing for his
If you lose a case
I like it hurts him
Whatever publicity
You get out of it get a lot of money from Ali there is a you know
Quit like you can get
In those little moments
Like I am
Almost never at a loss for words and you have that gif
Very polite
A smart person's way of saying
F*** you yep go f*** you
Yourself
I told you 5 minutes ago
Bit someone near me
Committed suicide
Recently
And you won't stop taking every
Single like hey
Light reflection that I make
And weaving it right back to
Support Athlete on yourself b****
Weezy
How to spell Adeline
That is
I just kind of point to be obsequious notes of of the right
Just like there's no way that I'm just
If that's
After that and he keeps going it's like
Cool Alex
This is as good as we're going to do I'm going to let you
Man I don't know
Employer-employee relationship or at least like
There's the business relation
You know if your Norm you also recognize like there's some performance on Alex's part
That like
Maybe after the mics
Went off and went to commercial he apologized
I don't know probably not but maybe I do because I'm so sorry look I just got out of
Control
It was too good I couldn't stop
The BET was great lowriders too good at
Ready for me to stop
I had a suspicion that Alex was
Maybe it back in his drunk
Behavior that was kind of like
This next clip is world's like
Let's go ahead and take a call or hear
Who's in all the longest for Norm pattis
That would be
What's going on here at
Sounds like a soundtrack from The Exorcist
Go ahead
Maybe Alex just like
Gentleman
That's the level he's at
Like these are the behaviors that I signed in times and he's very clearly drop
But also
I could see it as a possibility that he's not drunk you just hate snore
Like a two of them just hate each other and they only exist
Because Alex can't get any other lawyers threatened f****** bar
Carry out his case without some sort of a lawyer who's willing to represent him and Norm is that
So they're stuck with each other in some way and they f****** hate each
That's a possibility that he's so checked out in like
I hate this guy but he doesn't want to act like that alright
Need some lawyer to come on and talk about Rogers situation
There he needs a lawyer to come on and talk about Rogers situation
Which they are absolutely not to
There's not much of a
So yeah
This ends
Not all that dramatically or anyting
Alex
Let him go
Amen
He comes back
From break
And here's another guess
Another guest
I was like
Okay
It's got to be Steve
Allison saying these Red Storm things should I expect Steve to come in
Hey when you going out to the gas was I was like
The rest of the hours I'm going to host some of the
40 hour
Eminem
Watch this guy for 6 7 8 years on
YouTube East
Billions of
Author editor Video Creator and Gardner
Daddy goes by styx666
Panda
You're just more of an obnoxious handle that he can describe that for you
This is a hilarious booking for Alex on his show
Do you know who this dude is no I have no idea
So he's full of a 6
And he's a real s*** head on YouTube
YouTube caca
If you was on the left
That would handle would be what
Hundred percent the thing that Alex dreams about an hour
Have to be obvious about it they have
Tell you that are so evil that
They have to do
He's on my side
I should tell you he is illegitimate
Orleans to Houston
He left the Church of Satan a few years back and is now a self-described pagan
Anacortes
Switch Alex would still described as
Satan
Kohl's
People that are
Regular you never come from Christian to Satanist
His 666 Campbell is not just being abrasive obnoxious he was a real Satanist
Unlike all the Democrats believe in a liberal policy
The great Beast alastor
Crowley
So sticks is real dumb dumb
Do you suppose videos on YouTube themself doing drugs
Buddy stopped at every overdosed on fake weed back
In 2010 and got clean
He's advancing real fun
Conspiracies like he believes
The Charles Manson is innocent
Not fun once like arguing with the Nazis didn't use zyklon-b in the gas
You sent that one back a little bit but in my book
If you're using
Your platform to spread Holocaust revisionism that stays with you
Even when you walk it back.
Good on you for realizing you were wrong but the
The problem is
You didn't realize you were wrong before you started preaching that s***
Realizing your position was wrong doesn't change the fact that you were still the same person
Even afterwards
Ever you made up your mind you were wrong
Missing person who thought it was a great idea
Question well-established history of the Hulk
So go f*** you
Yourself
I think one of the big problems with
YouTube creators being
Self-employed
Is that the only person who
You can fire them or punish them for their bad behavior
Doesn't particularly
Seems like there's a problem
So beyond that sort of stuff like
Note some weird
Conspiracies and Holocaust revisionism that you sent pretended I didn't mean that
Beyond that he's is pretty much a run-of-the-mill YouTube reactionary right-wing commentators
Except
Did he have a seat
Aesthetic
Easiest long hair is a leather jacket and he often wears no shirt under that leather jacket
Easy Rider resale
This dude just straight-up sucks
But honestly I would have thought that he was would consider himself above coming on Infowars
Because it's like YouTube accidentally watched a couple of
Condescending XVideos
But I got from him would be like
No I would
Alex is crazy
Why would I do that
The fact that this interview is happening is embarrassing for both parties engaging in theater
Yeah that's not good
Hey Wade interviews are stupid
Play the Sixers just doing some bucket list shity like he got
Ballroom
Appleton
Does Owen Shroyer show is definitely
More
Tailored towards
The younger reactionary proud and so like he'll have a lot of these people who
Frame spaces on YouTube
Because you want to reach out to those already in Sycamore
A cool Owen Shroyer guy Destroyer
Make some sense
Alex
Now it's bad luck
Yeah
If the whole interview is really just
Exists
Styxhexenhammer666
Can come on in Bosch
Bernie being bad Neverland bad
Motorola
The band it's very unimpressive interview
And I just
The only cuz I'm going to play from it
Is sticks
Explaining that know his handle is from back when he was a Satanist
I was just response to this
Is
It's up there
Far as the username goes that actually many years
Actually an atheistic stay behind long ago
I have nothing to do with it anymore but the name stuff so I just
The same
Make sense
Sure
God I just hate the double standards
Passe and cliche
Dammit it's so annoying
Stock price
I'm surprised
He barely imagine that in his head was like
That means you're still a Satanist it what to Satan
He's like oh s*** he's on my side
Okay
He probably has way more of a reach than Alex to it's a pretty popular on YouTube
I would I would assume that Alex
To enlist him
As part of the phone
That's not feel like
You're still the same
You look UK once you got the Donk
Once you got the meme machines
You're going to need a stick
That's it for the 30
The wrestler shows mostly Alex Evans interview with sticks
It's not it's not interesting
That's a phrase that I've never heard that since I've never heard before on fake weed
That would be interested
You OD on
Some of that stuff is not good
I totally believe that
And not doesn't know this is to make fun of people's
Had bad drug reactions or anything it's just
Kind of
It's kind of funny giving him know
I wouldn't want that to be my rock bottom Bowman
Of all the all the rock bottom
That's not the one I would want
Bucked up
F***** up on fake weed
Get the f*** out of
It's a weird look
Much like a leather jacket without a shirt
Weird
Cowboy
And now it's something
And that is
That an interview with William Barr has come out
Or he's trying to do damage control salute about the fact that these prosecutors removed themselves from the cake
So now
Alex has an interesting Dilemma on his hands
We know that attorney general Barr has really come out against the Press
Some people are saying that it's elaborate
Kabuki
Heat off the Attorney General
Stone to an exorbitant amount of time
Correct
He does know all people
In the deep deep state
Disagree
Not the lawyer bureaucracy but the other folks
The military
Those areas
Also just really has a big toe
Bar
Particularly want to come on the show today
Barney's resign and anything's bars going to make a move on the president
And I just deleted them because of the pedigree of bar
You know bar
He's up to his eyeballs
In Jeffrey Epstein
Okay
Like I told you I knew that Steve was looming in the background somewhere and here we go
You're like a quarterback with Brian Urlacher
I got my Maya Steve's
So by the 14th William Bard sat down for a highly
Staged interview where he basically made the
Point the Trump's tweet about Rodger Stone sentencing recommendation me
Impossible for him to do his job as the Attorney General
You kind of see what you mean
But we put them in a very bad position
If you sincerely did believe the recommendation was too severe he then had to choose to either not amend the recommendation
For fear of appearing compromised by Trump's tweets
Or amend the recommendation and give literally every appearance
Prince of being compromised by Trump
Amazing for him to be in a
Complex situation
Where is protect
Checking the president
I've never heard of him doing that before multiple president
F****** trust bar in this light
He's describing
It is a real problem
Like that is
Sincere like Trump's tweet does introduced
That possibility
The way Trump Act
Makes every decision completely
Complicated in
Suspicious
There's no action that bill Barr can
Take
Particularly in cases that affect
Trump directly
They can never really be seen as independent or legitimate
Because of the way Trump
I don't believe that this is
Sidebar is really concerned about that
But
Just looking at it
From a neutral position
Person one does this
Person to hastur
Respond
It does make sense
Just put them in a f*****-up pic
No absolutely I'm just
I just get
Frustrated whenever they
Like just just say that
He told you to know
We all know he told you to do it
You're going to do it
Just saying
Just be done
I have a strong suspicion that the interview he did was intentional and was a calculated Act
Designed to cut off Curtis
Isn't that as attorney general he was basically just acting as Trump's personal attorney
Doing his bidding opposed
As opposed to protecting the interest
Which is why you was f****** higher than the first
Whatever the reality of Alex's
Pissed
He sees the interview with a broadside attack on Trump
And now bars on the outs
With the Patriots
Which is hilarious considering how much Alex loves the bar not a few days ago
Steve is going to come on in Bash
Bars associated with a neocon to Steve f****** hate
The standard stuff
Just Steve working in some of his own material
Going into business for himself on Alex's show as they say in the world of wrestling
But I would have been sharp
Castillo is how now Alex
Doesn't like William Barr
And because of that
A whole new set of facts are available to him
Like that bill Barr is a Hoosier
Eyeballs in the Jeffrey Epstein's.
Here's the thing
Alex Kim just learned his father was quote
The Headmaster of an elite New York City School
It hired College Dropout Epstein to teach math and physics
That wanted is read to you for it was from an August 2019 article in time
And it wasn't news then
How to know that
But he strategically doesn't mention it ever
While he's in the cycle of presenting bar as a hero
Doing the heroic work
Backing up the arch hero Trump
Now that he said something in the interview that Alex is going against the dear leader all of a sudden
How does a where this long reported
Piece of information
Super weird how that works
Wait is he
He's genuinely mad at bar
Yeah does he not get the game is he that stupid
Huge doing this in defense of the president that's our sense of it
Just feel that way that way
Alex thinks that he's turned on Trump
Making the best possible move
Fort Rucker
God these people are so f******
He's a he's he's he's made an attack on Trump in this interview cuz Alex thinks he's trying to save himself
4 something
I hated the
It's stupid and violent winds
So
I was listening to this and all I could think about was pro wrestler
You may not know this Jordan but they're different styles of wrestling
Heels and faces generally engaging
Because they're trying to elicit differ
Reactions
From the crowd
You don't want to crowd generally genuinely cheering for the heel
Typically don't allow them to do boobs that are too
Excited
A good recent example of this is Seth Rollins
When he was a heel he didn't do any of the high-flying moves
The people really pop
Once you turn space
He started breaking out the superplex into a falcon arrow and the Phoenix Flash
I was jumping off the top rope and everybody's like all that
So when Seth was a heat
He knew how to do those moves
He was perfectly capable of pulling them out at any point in any match
But he didn't
Because his goal was
That's what I was does with information
And that interview Alex thinks William Barr is turned heel on Trump
And now the moveset is opened up and he can now connect the bar with f
Alex could have done that at any point
And it would have been just as true but he never did
Because that would jeopardize the face reaction that he wanted to listeners to have towards William Barr
This little thing is a joke
He knows so much more than he says on air
Particularly about the people he's trying to paint as good guys who are actually trash
It also strongly indicates that he was totally fine with having an attorney general in office who was up to his eyeballs in the
Epstein stop
So long as they didn't dare question Trump
How to make you think
But how much Alex knows about Trump that he pretends not to know
So you can keep presenting him in the face
I just
How to makes you wonder that I'm mad at him
For not doing this the right way
I'm mad that Alex is not being the right kind of corrupt
That is bumming me out
You should be smart enough your mother is not on the script
He's doing it up
He's doing a bad job
But but it's what he knows to do
Of course
It's just like a jerk kind of Defense
He's not really that smart he's not and so like yes
This appears to be an attack on the president we will respond as if it is
It's just such an own-goal
What are you doing
Not great
Alex also has learned on this site
February 14th
By the time it's episode air season in vet
This is come out and said
That they're not going to
Pursue prosecution against Andrew McCabe
That's why this one argument okay
Another argument might be that it is also another placating move and that like this prosecution wouldn't have worked out
But you could have left it hanging sure but you get you
You dismiss it in order to also appear
Morphe
Prosecutor
This is the criticism of prosecutors
Responsibility
It's more William Barr trying to save himself and he's pretty mad about this
Complaining
About John
Brennan
Walks around Connersville
Imagine a full grown man walking around
Certifiable lunatic
Right there
Didn't fight his way out of a paper bag
Forever
Dishonorable scumbags out of there
I hate America and the Communist Party
You shouldn't be the CIA director
Twice
Cuz he's a shack
Filth
So because of the Andrew McCabe news Alex is just ranting about all this standard enemies
It's all pretty boring
I think I'm very here Alex claimed that Brennan voted
Communist
Twice
The wild piece of information
That our country's former CIA director voted for a communist twice
In reality John Brennan is discussed publicly how he voted for the Communist Party candidate
President 1976
But he was never a member of the party
In fairness Gus Hall got over 58,000 votes
In the 1976 election
Things he actually beat Lyndon larouche was running on the US
Take it that year
Regardless
It's super interesting that a guy who in his younger life
I would have voted for a non-mainstream candidate in a general
But they could eventually end up in charge of the CIA
I don't think it means anything in the larger sense but it's pretty fascinating as trivia
Anyway the reason I pulled this clip is because it's another prime example of that Alex cannot help him
He have to embellish everything to make his narrative sound bigger and more convincing
There's no evidence that Brennan voted communist
Twice
The Faculty voted communist
Once just doesn't do it
Do you have to take an already interesting and surprising piece of information and turn it into a y by exaggerating it
Because he knows his arguments
Suck
On some basic visceral level Alex knows that you can easily write off a guy voting for the Communist Party once in the mid-70s
Or maybe if you
You feel this way you can
Call it an indiscretion of his youth
If you voted for the Communist party twice
Patterns
Alex Azar
Sounds better
He knows he doesn't have the information because argument sound better sutures lies
That's all he's doing
These exaggerations are such
Fingerprint
Of like
You know your s*** sucks
Week
The f*** out of here
Shame on you
Call Mimi twice
I am the evil CIA director who is
Who's coming after Trump
So Alex and Steve
Steve pieczenik
Comes in
And of course it's all just kind of like bars got to go
He does reveal that Steve did vote for
Probably working
Woodland Rouge
He probably would say
Sam Lyndon larouche yes
He does reveal the Daniel Ellsberg releasing the Pentagon papers within a limited Hangout
That was
CIA what else is what else is Forrest Gump doing now
I wanted to cut clips of that but it is just way too long of a ramp I can just tell you reset it
The rest of it is largely just bill Barr sucks
He's got to go
I'm with you but
The way they start the interview is Alex
Presents this is like Trump is list
Forget him your mess
Joints in the background but
Because of eclipse
What is your disk quick synopsis in 5 minutes.
Mechanics
Run of the present knows you are in your background the things you've done it different different agencies and thanks
What is your
Five-minute synopsis with
Show me a synopsis of the
Number one William Barr has to go
I said it a year ago
The reason for
Not only has he
Really
Insulted
And set it in a pro
In fact
And interfere with the
You can do whatever you want
So maybe some of this is coming from Steve uncle Alex's like bar is turned onto maybe some let's go
Yeah whatever
I wonder what he saying on we're recording
I wonder if
What is somebody had to explain to him
Between Friday
And Sunday
Everybody
His children damn his employees don't know shitt
Kids are smart enough to
Spell maybe not
Imagine that wrecks in between being
Told very weird sex
Disinformation
Heize is like
Hey Dad
This is a smartphone
I think anybody who is interviewing
Gavin McInnes and is excited about it and maybe doesn't get it
Alex's interviewing Steve but that doesn't stop him from taking
Brakes
Desales
Texas A&M 2007
That's all the letters right here we show TV viewers
This is the nanosilver that we have
By one of the top
Companies in the world
American biotech Labs LLC
And this is the silver at the Pentagon found with wounds shall in all of the private label
That was a bad
Family
Coronavirus
Silver
Showing out quickly also funds the Infowars today for
She also ingested
Store.com consult your physician
Obviously because he was
Roofer that you still
Beautiful. What's happening personal in your own life
You got to find out what's going on personally in your old life
You got us
Repair your relationship with your wife
And then
At the end Alex is saying it's
Prove
For that
And he specifically talking about the gargle
So now he is implying that there is FDA approval
For this
And what you
End up seeing here is really like
I've seen a progression of Alex
Testing the waters
No consequences happening
Any just getting bored
Explicit the lies
But he's telling about this
DSL for product and
I mean I don't know if there's ever going to be any consequences for it but
I mean eventually just going to be saying
The Crazies
This is going to be making factual claims that are true
Because you'll be able to get away with it
Well there's two things
Things that I think
Is 1
Trumps
Agencies
Are not going
It seems unlikely
Unless you direct
She's totally legal
+ 2
You must be stoked
Jim Bakker is getting all of that attention because
If anybody is going to be your hog up all the regulations
It's still go under the radar sell it is evil in his inexplicable easy likes and Jim Bakker is going to be also
Into this but it might be a
Completely
Front product
The Jim Bakker
They got might be just a colloidal silver
Suppose that the nano silver
Whatever the case
I mean I get really self-conscious about like
But I don't fully understand
And a lot of the laws
Suggesting
Did Alex is out of line when I realize like
No I found
Very specific cases where the FDA is told like doctor Rhema labo
It's a it's all I mean who knows we'll see if any consequences come
I'm on this weird
Position because like
Some people have reached out been like
Are you going to tell the FTC
No
I'm I'm not going to
But I also
Don't care if other people
Yeah generally speaking of such a non-engagement policy with Alex but like
If other people are going to take the information they were putting out and act on it
Nothing I can do about
I'm not going to not cover this for fear of
Like Mike
Right
If there were a situation where
I
Had good reason to believe
What Alex was doing could actually hurt
The people who are buying
Supplement
Then I would
Definitely make a
Report
Just haven't crossed that line
And it's just like
Unethical scam
Betty White
Alex gets to talking to Steve
And
This is really interesting to me cuz you know the term deep state
You know that means right nothing
It means nothing
Just f****** regular is anybody in the Secretary of State position
Yes
The working again
Well
There are good
Staters who are working
Against the bad beef
He has made a book called The Deep state
Oh they're called the Patriots
That mean I guess our conversation as highlighting ambiguity
Yes right
It is always like
These white
To the Alex calls at the
Intelligent
Princeton government
To Harvard
What have you
Alex's in the snow
He seems we trying to
Reclaim the term deep State and apply it to something
Completely different
Populist
Mom taking care of anak populer
Biscuits and gravy is the real deep state
That's a real deep state
Slate of the D in the corrupt elements of these states
I can get the fight
They won
America show awake now the military so everybody I know so awake
Want to go out and start
Having a civil war
What are the Communists in the Democrats
Bernie Sanders the world
This big Happy Hunting Ground in America it's not going to go the way it did Rodger other places
Want to go into a civil war
Keep going well for the other side
There won't be a civil war number one
People on
The Socialist side
Probably win but as I said a long time ago and I've
You have to be a multi-millionaire
Meanest
I'm here hello
You should meet a lot of people
I'll look through the 8,000
Some of the people in the the DSA rolls or do you want to do
Ivan - thousands there
The
The thing I really
Because it's Alex is like there's going to be a civil war
And his his reasoning is just
The left can't put up enough Noble slapping down
Basic
Fear narrative is hilarious
State as the mom
The cop making biscuits and gravy biscuits and gravy
Face changing an old ladies Tire
If that's the real deep state that the evil version of the deep state would be a cop popping someone's tires
Give me the real cops
Steve
How is like to have at least one really
Insane thing that he says
I'm here is that one
He's talking about the education
Department in the United States
And to his credit he does say that there should be better education
Goodonyou Steve okay
Interesting recommendation that I actually also
Agree with him
Shoot Devil's into space
She doesn't come up
He has he has a recommendation that I agree
But Alex should hit him
And I will mandate
Every young person has to serve
Where their services but like Israel you was a service
2 years
22 service to this country
Powerful interview I hope the president listens to you
Sam who has also advocated somebody in specific I remember
Who advocated for just something similar to that Jordan is really interesting that when you listen to Alex for long enough it just be
Becomes a farce
Everything is internally inconsistent nothing means anything and think they were once seen as words of villains
Expressing their evil plans are now the wise guidance
Of Heroes
Hope the president
Emotions
Goodnight clip Steven saying when he takes over the Department of Education
He would make volumes due to years of
Compulsory service to the country
Not necessarily to the military button
Service to the country
This is legitimately one of the first things that Alex covered in
The Obama Deception
Obama's Chief of Staff Rahm Emanuel and selling big ideas for a mare
Which proposed that all Americans
Between the ages of 18 and 25
What do 3 months
Of some form of community service
Steve wants them to do
8 times that much service
In The Obama Deception and Analysis narratives
That's Rob's plan was Clear Proof of Obama Obama youth
Course his own gigantic team of indoctrinated young person
Who do his bidding that was just planted it takes 3 months
Naturally in the film his
The argument was accompanied by shots of young black men in ROTC exercises
The drive home the racism that was behind this narrative
But let's not get bogged down on that
A very obvious aspect of the naira
Alex never thought that the
The act of suggesting some kind of mandatory community service
Why is that the same thing as creating Obama you
Because if he did
He would have the same response
Text Steve
Suggesting a more severe
Version of proposed
This was never since
It was always just a cheap way Alex
Could attack Obama
And waked Stoke race
Spheres in his audience
All right did they already had
About a black president
Not only is the president black
He's also creating a gigantic Army of young black men
Get scared
It's an easy way to get get away with that sort of s***
This case is
Really good example of why
Because
If you really listen it does make a lot of sense to explore some kind of mandatory public service program for the country
Not just for the country sake but also for all the individual citizen
The experience of volunteering at a soup kitchen
Cleaning up a forest
Transformative
Aw X
Them folks
Need a little push
Do things that benefit themselves as well as the larger society
Because this isn't intuitively pretty
Decent idea it doesn't some nuts
Received we suggested
Unless you listen to Alex for years and actually paid attention
You never remember this is a major talking
Borders anti-obama coverage
But he was going to enslave your children
Clearly a philosophical opposition to mandatory public service
What was motivating Alex's coverage of Raleigh
That raises the question
What was
Oh well I mean he was black
Right
Then why is it so hard forever to just be like
But that's that's what allowed the narratives are
Easy thing to adjust
This all is
Especially now
The light of this
So
It's just so easy
I think so
The case for anti-trump rhetoric
Of similar
I don't remember.
Specifics
What we talked about earlier the ideas that when
He came in
Transition
Firing the attorney
Positive that there are people who
That is the same thing it turns like that's easy easy thing to do
Mandatory service
Easy easy narrative
Bailed
I think it's what frustrates me for those easy narratives
Is if we want
What's on the left and
Easy narrative
We have
10 million of them
That he is provided us
Instantly like if you want an easy narrative he came into office
Violating the
Dump and go if you want another easy narrative it's that
If you want another easy narrative
We can just do one we can just do one and repeat
It's over and over and over
Instead everybody asked
Talk about the new Dushore thing that he
Priming
Getting away with this
It's over it's
It's too much
So I agree with you
And we now say goodbye to Steve
Now he has made this very rational suggestion that Alex should punch him for
Absolutely
We now get
Another guess
Oh no I might have just ignored this guy asks if he's had a couple of really stupid things
Also Alex does introduction
Along With You Belong To The City
And we always need some nice taste
Text Master 6969
These grooves
Are sick
Saxophone is amazing
Call Victor
Lakeland is a
Intelligence agency
Talk about a whole host of subjects
I never heard of this guy in Alex's introducing him as a guy who's with the defense
Intelligence agency
That's a
Albee Al legitimate
Kind of thing
He is a recovering lawyer
I'm not sure if I necessarily believe that this guy Ivan reikland was ever employed by the defense intelligence
That's something that is bio claims that I was reading but in the world of Infowars I've learned that often times claims and working in
Intelligence are not to be taken at face value
Importing 18 Ivan was a guest on the John Batchelor Show podcast
When is Bayou
He doesn't mention working for the DIA however there is this B
Quotes Ivan holds a ba in Russian Spanish Russia and East
European studies
Igd and
The MS in strategic intelligence program at the defense
Intelligence agency
Okay
Now that freezing is
It's a little bit different than
He worked for the day
It is a little bit little bit
41 the Russian Spanish degrees as well as the Jade either
The lawyer degree
Degrees that he
He holds those degrees
Conversely just as the
Attend
The MS in strategic intelligence program
Completed it
It's also the MS in strategic intelligence that's a master's of science
Conferred bias
Generally speaking
You can get that degree in a bunch of schools
Quick Google search finds programs available at Northeastern Georgetown St Louis University among other
But here's the thing
The defense intelligence agency is not
Academica
It doesn't make sense to claim that you have a degree from the DIA
Since they're not at
Degree granted
He also has a degree of the Hard Knocks tan I guess
The correct version of this claim would be to say that you have a masters
Science in strategic intelligence
It's from the National Intelligence universe
Who do the school that's Metro prepare people for work
Relations like the defense intelligence
That is where he would get the degree
You would have got it at another establishment of fireworks
This kind of leads me not
This piece of Ivan's Back Store
I've no idea. Maybe he just botched his bio but that doesn't seem like something intelligent
Professional look do I have no idea information is sometimes important for enemies and allies
No that's that's another method on rational eyes is being wrong all the time is part of the plan
Sun Soo level
That's that's Art of War
Is Sun Soo
Que son to what about you I think you you solved it thank you solve the puzzle
Sam ekstrom Confucius
Okay so even if that piece of Ivan story is a little murky
Some pieces
Are little clear
He's probably most notable publicly for trying to run for Tim Kaine senate seat
In Virginia in the 2018 midterm election
I've engaged the viability of his campaign by doing a 1776 mile run through all the time
Towns and cities in Virginia
Back in August 2017
Alright parently that went well Sue decided to throw his hat into the ring
Ultimately he was denied inclusion from the ballot for the Republican
Primary with the Virginia GOP saying that he failed to gather the required number of signatures
I've been claimed that he had enough signatures and he's being kept off the ballot for some unknown political reason
According to the Richmond Times-Dispatch
The Virginia Republican party contacted Ivan on his Facebook
Book page which seems a little weird
Seems like Communications like this might be appropriate somewhere else
Maybe I've no idea
Anyway they contacted him saying quote
Unfortunately many of the signatures collected in the 9th congressional district were not valid
And for that reason you would disqualify
Odds are this isn't an issue fraud or anything like that
It's likely that a ton of signatures he got were fake names or non registered voters
So they wouldn't make it past the verification step that the party goes through when putting people on a bow
So you know to get on the ballot in Virginia you have to gather 10,000
But more important
You have to have 400
From each of the 11
Districts in the state
It's entirely possible that he had over 10,000 total signatures
But like 450 in the Ninth District and 100 of them were bogus
And that'll end up getting you qualify
Got disqualified right there
Probably along the lines of what happened
Anyway
I've decided to sue the Virginia Republic
Party City would end up losing
Things got a little bit ugly
Was Ivan claiming the party and told him to
Just go vote for another candidate
Which prompted the Virginia GOP to release a statement saying he was full of s***
Didn't use that kind of Old English but that was their main point
So well I was going through all day
It just so happened to be around the same time
Did Alex went to DC to do that press conference of his
And the press conference is so inconsequential in hindsight that I really don't remember what the goal is it was
It was about Alex getting sued and may be kicked off Facebook Lionel I don't know
I think it's usually about 4
Somewhere another
But our friend Jared Holt over it right wing watch was there
And there's an interesting blurb in his article
That he wrote about going to the event
Steven raichlen who's seeking election to the Senate in Virginia and has earned the endorsement of Mike Flynn June
Stop Jones near the Vic
Compress pit
Handed him a business card and asked if he could speak in front of the assembled crowd
Shortly afterward Jones introduced on stage
Franklin told the crowd that contrary to reports he had actually earned enough signatures to run in the Republican primary
Republican party officials
Unfairly just koala
I'm sure
Great this is where the two men pass
First cross
Then they met
And Alex not knowing this guy at all he just let him get up
Speak I can't believe
He complained about not getting on the bus
I can absolutely
Ivan speech was followed up by Jerome corsi giving a speech
That included this line
Qanon is military intelligence and close to Trump
It's hard to remember anything
There's so many different
Narratives that
Contradict
Each other that shouldn
That
Keep coming up
Is a bomber
But speaking before corsi defending qanon vitamin foreshadow
Because in August 2019 bra story reported on a conference
It was being organised to raise money for Mike Flynn.
They had a real heavy qanon overlap
The organizer had posted a ton about Q on Twitter
The conferences logo is
Does the US flag with stars rearranged
BBQ
Speakers included
Two weirdos like Bill Mitchell and joy Villa
Add one of the other speakers
You guessed it
Ivan Rangel
Hey
It clear that ranklin did serve in the National Guard
I can find evidence of that
2010 he was at
Captain of the Guard
I don't have any reason to necessarily doubt his claims that he was a Green Beret
The other stuff in his bio just doesn't sit right with me
It seems pretty dubious defense intelligence
Particularly
Also in 2015 tried to kick-start a documentary about Vladimir Putin called
15 years riding the Russian bear
The cover of witches just a shot of Putin
Oh I would have gone with Putin on the Ritz
Oh that's good that's not a bad
I want to the
Trailer for his documentary and I read a press release that he put out trying to raise funds and honestly I have
No idea what the angle on the film was
I don't know if it's pro-putin I don't know
I don't know if it's neutral
I have no idea
He's just a bear you're riding a bear
All this stuff is irrelevant Ivan's just on the show today cuz he tweeted the Trump should pardon Rodger Stone they got Alex's it
Santana Row
Anyway here's the
Intro to the interview which is
The bad news
Thanks for joining us I see you're there in your car
Probably somewhere in Virginia
Have a great start to this interview Ivan is Skyping in from his car here in the car are you driving
Right now cuz that's safe
That's almost
Like Alex
What are you doing what are you doing well I can't leave my dog in here and I was going to go to Target but you called me a little
I've been living here about 3 weeks and it's mainly due to the wonderful and perfect
, policy put together but I don't have an office in my wife won't let me call him but
How you doing
I know you will
Not call fashion
I am the primary money-maker
Honey are you calling fascist again
We have a conversation
It seems like a
It's mostly just about how like you need to Pardon Rodger Trump needs pardon Rodger
You did nothing wrong all this
Also he really specifically wants to talk about Mike
Flynn
Getting
Light off
The
And some of this has to do with a good to clear Association
I'm in like Flynn I'm not entirely sure what it is
Mike Flynn son Michael and Junior endorsement when he ran for
And you know that
Conference that he spoke at those to a nonadjacent
Also was in order to raise money for Mike Flynn
There's some sort of connection there but
I honestly can't be bothered
Figure it out I don't really care
They get to talkin about like the Democratic race
And
Ivan
He speculates that if Bernie
Run
Tulsi gabbard probably going to be his running mate be too
Sure sorry
Sorry for the laughter
Apologize for the
To condemn
If I can
Syrian War
Apologies
So that's one thing that he speculates about in that you can laugh at that but I really care.
Construct it like it's not really interested
Now his theories about Bloomberg
On the other hand
Far more interesting of it
Bloomberg
To take a look and see the biggest indicator
Is being accurate is that
If Hillary Clinton
Text her residency
And moves it from New York to
Arkansas or elsewhere
Give me the biggest indicator that she's going to be the running mate with Bloomberg
Because if you look at bloomers
Play accordion Constitution I can't I can't cite the exact statue
Surprise
You cannot have that so the president and the vice
Constitution
Two different states Illinois or Arkansas
Done deal she's going to jump in the race immediately after
It might surprise you to learn that noted constitutional scholar Alex Jones
Defense intelligence agency
The guests are completely wrong about the Constitution
Shut up that fun speculating
How they might get to yell about Hillary Clinton again Basics misunderstand
The Constitution
And which says quote
The electors shall meet in their respective States invoked by ballot for 2-person
So who won at least she'll not be inhabited
Of the same state with themselves
It's important to understand that until 1804 members of The Electoral College would vote for
To Canada
And the top vote-getter would be president and the runner-up would be Vice
And that's why we had
Had so many great wonderful President Thomas Jefferson love his
After that point the process change
And now lectors
Book spratley for President and Vice
Which is to say that just because in 2016 Hillary was running with Tim Kaine
It doesn't mean that every electoral votes for her
The president has to vote
This actually happened in the 20s
16 election
There was an elector in Texas who voted for Mike Pence for vice president
Is this kind of rare but it does happen from time to time
In the Constitution the rules that elect
Doctors could not
Both their vote
For candidates from the same state
So if
I were in elector
I could cast a vote for someone from Illinois
My other vote would have to go to a candidate from another state
This was a rule designed to lessen the influence
The larger States
I need to encourage folks not to just vote for their local allies
This became a bit of a talking point
During the 2016 GOP
The primary
Because Jeb Bush and Marco Rubio were both from
From Florida
And Ted Cruz and Rick Perry we're both from text
Shallow analysis and misinformed talk right people to believe that these combos of president and vice president couldn't
Not happen
But that wasn't
True
In reality the conversation was that it would be super unwise for these combos to happen and here's why
If Bush and Rubio tea
All of Florida's electors could vote for bush for president
But they could
Not vote for Rubio also
For vice president
In the same would hold True For Crews
I am.
In Texas
If these dudes one by gigantic margins it really wouldn't matter too much but if it were close race this could be a huge
Problems since Florida has 29 electoral votes
And Texas has 38
You never want to feel either of these
Since you d'essential to be playing at a severe disadvantage
And risk the possibility of electing Bush or Cruz
Call Tim Kaine ends up getting most votes for VP right and that would be f****** weird
In terms of the current day it's fair to assume that the Democratic party would not want to have
A presidential candidate and vice president from New York
Since I have 29 electoral votes
And that would introduce omit
So what's interesting here is that the
The phenomena that Alex and I are discussing his kind of real
Literally no idea what they're talking
He thinks the Constitution doesn't allow people from the same state to run on the same ticket
Absolutely not
True however behind
They're searching that if Hillary
To somehow make herself from Arkansas now
It would be an indication that
She's Angling
Do not block electoral voting restrictions
Since we're being Bloomberg VP
How to make sense
It does
I'm not sure what the official rules are about changing your home state but I don't think it would work
Working this case for Hillary
She's established
For years that a primary residence is in
Chappaqua New York
She was a senator from New York
And I don't know if she could be like whoops I'm actually resident Arkansas and then everyone's going to be like okay
Cool
If it would then why would
And anybody could just pull out the rules the Electoral College by having two homes
See ya
I mean I don't think it even
I don't think anybody
Okay
That was back whenever it took a long time to move
Because it would take
6 weeks to move
New York to Florida
I don't think anybody cares about that just
Because all of our politicians are from a million different
Prince States and they all move around all the time
Everybody knows that they'll move somewhere if they want to run
In a better or more
Favorable play
Placer items
Mean that I couldn't find
Like these specific regulations about like
Requirements for your home state
Comes down to like you have to have lived in the United States
14 years
I don't know what the cut and dry
But I really don't
Think Hillary could get around
Being from
New York
Even as far as that goes like
She probably if you want to have this conversation you wouldn't use Ark
Consol you wouldn't use Illinois
You would say that you changed being resident of
DC
Did the clintons have an SP
Where she live when she was in office
That's a much easier salad return by Kyle rages going to say that she lives in
God they want Hillary so bad cuz she's
The easiest everyone hates their now
Everyone
Like nothing but we still voted for
But now everybody hate Hillary ticket would be like
The most alienating
From Psych
From getting out the vote
Respect
Oh yeah
Pick some of the
Most
The analysis that makes the most sense to me is like this is an election where you're not changing
There's not
There's not people you need to sway
To your side
It's about energizing
Getting people out
To actually vote
And Bloomberg and Hillary
My two favorite candidates for president actually get people who would be otherwise inclined to
To not know I think we would have more people leave the United States
Then vote
In that election
Because that's
F***** up
I think that there are
People who are running who
No on the sound espectro mode
You know energizing to not energize
Not energized
Isn't be mostly Biden
Yeah but they're people along that scale
I think I think
If there is worse than Biden
Is Bloomberg
Absolutely
That's the only way you could get less interesting
Yeah but I don't know
Anyway so that means that we're going to have a blizzard
Desperately
Do you want Hillary to headlines about like Hillary's going to be blooming
A b b y the conversations happening
Begin with
Drudge story about the out
God
Larger point
These dudes think that it's in the Constitution you can't have a VP and press
Same state
I don't know what they're talkin about
So stupid
Scream about I'll also I should point out that Ivan is a recovering lawyer
So yeah
I don't think he was ever a good lawyer to begin with
So I haven't leaves and Alex's another gas that we're not even going to cover cuz who cares it's not
It's not a worthwhile interview it's important cuz it has the potential to be like something real
Explosive Chessmaster 777
Okay is Tyler Knicks
Who is Rodger Stones personal
He's awesome
So you like this all bullshitkorner have you but of course
Super close association with Rodger he can't do too much
He can't he can't go far enough to make it interesting
And
Meaning calling for the murder of
Sure
Interview of Alex talking about some
Some other news
I'm good also
Tyler Dixon
I think his phone didn't work so I was kind of a for a while he plays a couple Special Report
And covers a couple of headlines that he's ill prepared to cover
Here's one of them
Good thing I've ever heard.
Criminal charges
Giant billboard
Hell yeah
Daily Planet
First of all
Disrespect your
Your your hatred of country
No no I do not hate country music
That sucks
You don't like that talk about hanging out with Willie and Waylon
Song Go fuc yourself
Sirius you're disrespecting my Missouri heritage
Alex
Encouraging women to cheat
Yeah f*** yeah
Headline is being like
It's a thing where he's at
Offended
This notion of like cheating on your spouse being encouraged
How dare anyone cheat on their spouse
Jordan isn't important detail
That might be motivating his coverage
Said he's leaving out
This billboard says quote
Married to one man but fantasizing about others
You need to try is vita.com
I guess he could be mad about that if he wants but I don't remember to making a big deal out of all the Ashley Madison Billboards that
Popped up over the years
So maybe there's something else going on
Alex is actually just mad because this billboard along with that text include the picture of trump and Melania
Melania's looking lovingly away from Trump
And towards Justin Trudeau that's hilarious that's very funny
Alex's is mad about infidelity he's just mad at his billboard making a joke at Trump's expense
That's almost annoying because shouldn't be Trump looking at all of his other one
Perhaps an easier haggle I would do that one
So Paul Joseph Watson Road an article about this on Infowars and it's the saddest s*** in the world
With the divorce rates in depression at all-time highs and birth rates at an all-time low
Countries need is websites encouraging women to cheat on their partners
I'm suffering in The Break-Up of relationships
Unreal
That article n
Wanting to take care of your spouse in the context of a happy stable monogamous marriage is bad
Wanting to be a w**** and stab your husband in the back is apparently something to be celebrated
I think you're taking this a little
Personally buddy I think I think there's some
Bones are so weak they just can't admit that this billboard makes them very angry because they can't stand to see that
King made fun of Untold pain and suffering and encouraging the downfall of civil
Elevation hilarious but it's honestly also
Pretty sad it is
Pathetic we have one last clip and it's Alex
Just saying something that is
Absolutely unacceptable on any level
And
Inaccurate
Admire people that are Cruiser cost
Believing others
They willingly came to America
Squalid
World fellows or women had no power
Assassins of
Stockholm Syndrome
Conquer us because they're open hearts
Rashida tlaib was born in
Detroit
No she's not from here have you seen the
Color of her
Seems it seems like Alex is operated on
I love her no it's her shirt
Better really throwing them
So anyway Alex's
I've been a racist here
Anyway
Black dude this episode was
Was range is all over the place
When I told you the beginning this episode like
You get to see these different
Stages over this discourse
3 days
None of this is coharie
You have the first day on the 12th Alex's rambling about murder
And is being like
High on the hog
Because Trump is going to come to the defense of Rodger
It means that he's clearing house and all these globalist
Going to go
And all of this and then the 13th comes and
I always kind of settling in in like
Forgot to get Rodger then
Retrial cuz the jurors
Gets mad at
His lawyer friend
On the 14th
Bill Barr has come out and done his
Face-saving
Interview and now Alex's got to turn things around
Flip the script on
And I just
All of this is is
It's just so incoherent listening to it is
Experience
I like the thing that I come to from the end of this
After going through this whole roller
If this is
This is such like Twitter
This is so much
I've just this random nonsense being
Tossed about
Often
Ridiculously violent
Always
Incoherent
And
It's just that whole Marcos
Of the world that we live in with the
With the hard right
I honestly feel like
Twitter trolling as more
Yeah well yeah that's Alex Alex
They just lashing out
The content of his show the narratives that he puts out or so.
Pendant on whatever he's lashing out to whatever the stimulus is
But he's mad at or he's responding to
Dictate the entire world
Right that he presents to his audience
And it's deeply unfair
It's not fair
Not allow your audience to have a consist
Thread of reality
Mysterious bad guy that dropped needs to murder
I think
I think one thing
That
Is is very clear about the
Is that we are
Incapable of him
Handling we are incapable of handling the way these
It is simply like
This type of
S*** like
It's so terrifying to listen to those that first days
Episode of him
Calling from murder
And then
Like that
Terrified
And then the next day it's just
Oh William bars
You know like
He was just lashing out
Like a child having a
Tantrum
And it's hard not to take that serious
Because he has such
High platform
Yeah in the same way with the reactionary right-wing going after whomever
And
It's just them lashing out
And because
Is weird so used to
Accepting their behavior as being something we should
Talk about we're covering lashing out as if it
Like it's so frustrating me
How many times have I opened the
F****** Guardian
And seen them cover some headline
And it's like oh that's just a child lashing out
Don't give that a
Attention
I think it's something we talked about a lot like in the
Earlier days of the show was this
Feeling of like
Adults have to show up event
Liquor needs to be adults
Dealing with this
Toward showing up in the realization set in
Gradually the like
Nope that's not going to happen or not
It almost
You need parents
Transcended for or escalated from just like we need adults in the room
Till like
Really, this s*** down and settle it
And now
The kids
And the childish petulant Behavior
Is kind of running things it's the only life
Being rewarded
Describing that like don't
Don't reward this tantrum with behavior
Exactly
And that's important
And I don't know how you do that
Because you start acting like a child
Acting like a parent towards other adults
And generally that puts them in a position where they
End up
Precipitating the exact
They think you're trying to
Stop them
I don't I don't know there's an easy answer but
I mean to me
Kind of what I'm
What I'm taking
Is
It's
Time to just
Ignore
I mean I've said this
Before but it's really like
We just can't involve them in the
They just can't beat we can't talk
About what it is they have to say I don't give a s*** about kellyanne Conway has to
She's not involved in
In the conversation he doesn't get to be in the news
You have to be clear though it's
Specific people
Their behavior apps
Absolutely not people who have conservative politics Reddit
Kellyanne Conway doesn't
You don't get to talk.
She's gone
Rap Viet VX on Behavior
Class
Connecticut
No not at all just like
Fine if you want to if she wants to say this s*** you know it
You know she's going to blindly defend Trump with some people
The even if you're even if you want don't even get a comment from her just say kellyanne Conway would probably defend Trump lie
It's f****** move on
We're done
Enter the new era of the news just
Guessing
What they will say if you ask
I don't know if that would work but
Suggestion
So anyway
Jordan Hindi welding
Dot-com
Squirrel so on
We are on Twitter that knowledge underscore fight and I go to bed Jordan on face
We are on Facebook and if you would like to download so please go to iTunes or whatever
Castroville apps
Soul
Download Lagu leave a review
Charity friends donate
Until then
Dzx Clark
I am the bringer of the Red Storm
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work