Holding
Alex
Everybody walking back to knowledge
I'm Jordan
Do too much
Infowars Alex Jones my friend
Jordan who has absolutely no idea what the
What is going on with that
Explain
What's going on in the wonderful wonderful world
Iowa
Delightful tea
Occupied
IPad
So today I like over the last week Alex has been out of town
And
Get out today
And look into some of the Special Report
From the road
It's all I've I've collected a couple of votes
Special bonus at the end of the episode
What do you think
Why would you even ask me a predict
Even the Y2K
Concentration camp
Okay so we're talkin missive from the road
Is around the time
Do you know it's D's
These reports were filed
Between like
The 10th
January
Alright no 9039
Today is the 6th
When we're recording this
Yeah we're going over the weekend
Yes okay
So I'm going to go with
He's definitely not talking about the
Russian alligator
About Trump
Okay bring that up later
Yeah
Okay I wasn't going to ask you to just Whole Hog again
Okay okay I'll give you a ballpark to be a persona
Are we going back to Megyn Kelly
She does get name-drop
Media personalities
Mail
Mail media personality
Nobody got nothing
It's going back
Caring blind bags
I like
Tucker Carlson
Agree with half of that
You like told on Fox News
Fox News
I want nothing
What's Fox News
Vice president
Do again believe and respond once
To go to the emerald Castle
I feel like total didn't have as much agency in that sorry if you think
I want to be clear
I respect the s*** out of this and I do believe what you say
I don't believe that at all you don't believe that he doesn't want to be on Fox
No I believe that
I believe that that VP
Was if not talking about Alex Jones
Himself
Some person in the Alex Jones
Made an inquiry with the VP
Hey Alex and I maybe Alex because Alex just
Had the
Exact same tone of voice that a f****** a******
She told me the truth
You're ugly dude
It's from all of my listening to him he's been wildly
Consistent
There's a part of me that kind of believes him
That job
Fox News
Have someone over there s*** on
I kind of believe him on this one
Italy
I'm going to
And and you're right you have way more
But just
Just going on tone
Those guys
Exactly the
Every one of those guys said
Says the same tone of voice
Like it's all the same
And yet every little ass
Like that is
That is the first time where I've Act
We thought he wasn't
Just like
Conspiracy theory
Deceiving
Genuinely hate
With all my heart
After hearing him say
I have my own audience
It's huge
Just like garage has his own audience
I'm trying to build something else
We've done it
We've been successful
Donald Trump rally a third of the shirts are infowars.com
Hillary for prison shirts
Little bit of
Research on this implying that his dick was the same size
His audience parallels Almighty
Speculation
So I looked into
Lock Hillary up underwear
Cuz that would be
Solid
Solid or likes
Really and cops
Sex play
Conservative base
But so I had to do some digging
And I looked into heavy the ultimate white elephant
Got him so mad Christmas is already over
So I did some research is going to be
How to get like a store together
We've got to get
We've got to put together Alex Jones drop digital dropbox
Hillary up freely handcuffs
We're going to be we're going to crush it
So I looked into
Already gone over that he has like
Maybe about 3 4
Thousand
Bricks to the website
Talks about all the station
Buddy's on
You talk about the terrestrial Broadcasting
Little bit of research into that
Jimmy like
Listing from the communication
At work that a listing of the 83 station
Alex Jones is broadcast on
Any broadcast on Sundays alone on 35 station
But most of that is overlap
Like the Sunday broadcast overlap with the 83
It's not a hundred percent but there's a lot of
I was looking
But if that's not that matter
Get some comparisons handy has at least 424 stations Glen because three
Michael Savage has 223 stations nationally
Rush as531
He's at the bottom of that list
A little bit further
What are these station
Let me list off a couple of these station
Wsvn
790 am out of Mount Jackson Virginia
Population of two
Okay
WLS
12:40 a.m. out of loris
South Carolina
Population of 2,000
Stations the broadcast
Kane Pennsylvania
Population of 3,500 people
Two stations
In Kane Pennsylvania
Iwy Peavey 106.3 FM
Out of all the way Michigan
Population of 850
I did I did some digging
PizzaMan
36 out of the 83 stations at
That's 43% of the markets are not even ranked
In terms of broadcast mark
Wow
3% or below the threshold where they would even make
The consideration of ranking
Write 19 out of the 83 that's 22% are in the top 100 mark
22% in the top hundred
19 of the most of them skewed toward the lower end
The top 100
I wasn't I wasn't expecting him he doesn't want to New York
There's a market in Yorkie has a Chicago affiliate
3 in the nation
Okay only 26
Out of the 83 including that 19
The top 100
To bring them together to
Total 31% of the top 150
Okay if you keep going down
You see that's like a lot of these are bad muscles
Before I say any
Yeah cuz we have like maybe a hundred listeners zero about radio
If he's in there
Market
Does that just mean
That only those
People can
Get the signal or of the stations
Right
But I mean like
If if we're talking about a city of
2000 I'm assuming it's not right now
Next to a city of three
It's it's kind of out there in a
In the doctor
We could probably still pick up the station for
No number Mi outside of house
But really we're looking at a small percentage of those two
2000 people
Are actually listen
Baby Alive well it's 2000
I'm saying that not because I think it's that's a shity audience I would love to
If you look at it it's compiled it's coupled with garbage
Ballpark
We've got three station
Super small Marcus for most of them
Probably
But still if you're only getting
Like 300,000 hits
Your website
What's has a
Total consistent audience of maybe like 200,000
I was being
Going to say that's super generous
Clicking on a website versus X
Difference between listening and just
You know what I would actually say his audience is
Closer to 6
And most of those are long road
Entirely possible my heart especially cuz you can smart
Okay I think I think that you'd probably if you include YouTube in there too I think he has a bigger audience
Like
I mean it
Monetizing YouTube incredibly difficult it is not very high to give like 20,000 hits on a bit
You're not making much
If so is that what is average
Kind of videos
As well on YouTube or do they pay
Pick the eclipse out
And then put them up
The ladder but also the prior
Okay but I watched it live
A couple times and it's like
600 people are watching
So not many people are streaming it live on YouTube
Panda listen for
3 hours not doing anything at work
If your
Nothing else going on or if you want
Just on a long road
You might list
Listen to that whole thing
But that's all
That's also kind of like
The Conan show really
Where is my brother
Conan
Michelle from
For the whole hour and a
People who want to
But most of us are watching
5-minute clips
That's possible to get ratings
Yakima
Walking low
What's going on there
I was able to dig up
His country
That he gives to affiliate
And I know it's real
Because it posted on infowars.com
It is publicly available
Give me more information
It turns out
That
Infowars itself is owned by a parent company
Recalled Free Speech Systems LLC
Okay okay
And I
Yes
Pure think sounds like
A lot more
Alarm for scrub
The first thing that I noticed
About this contract was
A very clear
Specification
Broadcasting Infowars as an affiliate
They don't charge you any
And I quote
The Alex Jones Show overdrive in Infowars nightly tuzar free-to-air
There is no cost for running the program
No affiliates
That's in the country
Now here's what they at
Free speech
System
Reserves the usage of three minutes per broadcast hour for Network promotional advertisers
The broadcaster live usage of the remainder of the scheduled advertising per program
Okay so the
If you run his show
Then the network Iran can only ever
Advertise the network
For 3 minutes
Snow
You got a flip
Oh I got it
So let's say I have a radio station
I want to broadcast Alex Jones
Yes
There's 15 minutes of commercials per hour
I get 12
He gets three
Okay
That is
Not a great content
That's really sad
And only 83 stations have thought to take that take
Reprogramming
Seems like it's a
Well
Toxic is the stuff you saying
The people don't want to put him on their brought there are
I find this fascinating and I only had one clip so far
Available
If you just search for Infowars affiliate contract it'll come up on Google
Which I mean
Really screws up their negotiating we don't want anyting just let us know our pills
43 minutes coming from that low of a negotiating point
Yeah that's real trouble right
Okay you have
Network
Broadcast
Maybe fifty thousand people
Could listen to your station
That's 50,000 people that might here are three minutes of weird pill commercial
We're doing this anyway
So weird to leave me to believe that his body
There is a
There is a larger we see no evidence of it
Are We Now descending into conspiracy theory territory water
I'm thinking there's an anti George Soros globalist what's happening
What are you doing today sucked up
So here's here's the next
Not his
Screed on the Glenn Beck
Selling more catheters and more diabetic
You're the past
Where the future
So that's his next stab
Fox News
General
Most
That is the most
Inflicted attack that you can possibly make like he's basically saying
To them like
I'm selling boner pills and prostate medication
So he's no I know it's insane
That's like I don't know like you robbed the bank and you have a friend who also robbed a bank
But I
Some more
Thank God you do research
You better decide before quantcast
Quadcast
They do
They compiled
They compile statistics
For advertising
Amazon website
I'm Gordon quantcast 53% of Alex Jones is audience
Is over the age of 45
And 78% are over 35
Only 6% of his audiences
Between the ages of
18 + 24
And 12% between 25
And 34
Anybody that's not a young audience anybody.
Anybody below its 6%
6% below 18 which is
Advisable
Inappropriate
Child abuse
I also found info
That they
Put out in order to try and find
Could also find by Googling it toasted on infowars.com it's publicly available
It's insane that they just leave the stuff up on their website without blocking it
It's a PDF of like a slick presentation to
Is Google
And it's all super usable now on how to look
Through there
Here's the breakdown what is the NSA
McClintock
Advertising report they claim
That his audience
Is 50 Thor untie 43% over the age of 50
With an additional 35%
Between the ages of 35
If you look at the quantcast data that
Can matcha
Because what they did is change the threshold agent
No based on Van overall trend is exactly
Based on what independent polling and his own press release they we can
Pretty much rely on those is fairly accurate
Even if you
Look at that
33%
Is over 50
That's an old
F****** audio
Fox News
The same
So half of the audience is over 63
Still 50 is not
Not that I mean it's 13 years but it's not Far Cry
What are you trying to say is
We are the Next Generation that will grow up I guess that's the only way to
Here's the part where it's good that I found out earlier that
Free Speech system
Owns Infowars
And I found a press release
I found an advertising pitch
From Free Speech system
That is for Infowars
And what they are I looked I found there like sort of business filing
And it's a austin-based company in the only contact on it
Okay
He made all the other stuff private
Get me my eyes are twin
Express package tracking
Sell advertising on infowars.com
On the website as opposed to on the radio brought
So the one
This this one has
Do you want the audio
This one claims that the audience is thirty percent
Over the age of 50
And 67% over the age
In terms of selling radio advertising
Being accurate
Statistics
And his other PDF numbers
Because
The radio audience
General people who listen to radio or older
Younger
Your audience is much younger than
What it actually is
You have
Completely conflicting numbers
Also they list
Three ways that
That you can buy abs
On the website
But here's where I'm starting to get like this is
The f****** scam
Three ways
The first way you can do as banneret
Just want to block this also super easily
Available
It's also on
Posted on their website
Click on one of the
F*****-up thing will get to what's f*****-up
Operate they showed like the placement of where the ads would be cuz they want to be like
You can get abs
AC or DC
Second.
Is a banner
That goes at the
Top of the web
Website looks like breaking news
I'm assuming that they just closed there's a conflict of
Chris that right
I also just went to infowars.com today and there is no Banner ad or any
Play right now
Let's not in play you're really pushing
I try
So the Third Way
Is what I think
Is really f***** up
And they're super clear about it
Being f***** up
The Third Way is called
Text blink
I'm just going to read a quote
Oh please
From their advertising material
These are disguised as news headlines near the top of the breaking news
Disguise verbatim
That's crazy I'm not paraphrasing enel
They literally say word for word
We will lie to our
Awesome
News headlines
At the top of the breaking news or prisonplanet section
I guaranteed to get massive immediate hit
Your text app can say anything you like and varies and pricing for characters
Fit right there
Immediate hits leaders in like to go
Do we are selling high-end eyes like what I couldn't find any Banner
Ads on it
Maybe maybe all that's right there disguised
Who knows
At this point if you know that that's an advertising strategy they're literally using
Everything is sucks
Yeah you don't know what any of these headlines are really
Which fits into their hole
Their whole thing about BuzzFeed all you want to do about a dumb s*** but every time there's something that's
Like paid for countertenor
Sponsored content because otherwise you're being duplicitous a******
Yeah and even if BuzzFeed isn't doing that they're not advertising 2/3
Maybe there I've never seen their sales pitch
Just maybe there is
Like
Because I that does sound like
Sleazy ad sales
And it's not it's not outside the realm of possibility that other websites are doing
Yeah I could definitely Steve many disrupt
Although the MoMA
Yeah like the moment you know that they are willing to do that and then just
Supply that to even some
Percentage of
Mainstream
It's like
Well if these guys
And they're not hiding maybe they're just
Worst job
Hiding house
There should not have these things be public
They should really not it's really easy to set up page to private
But even then it does seem like
There
Viewers would not give a she
Orbi orbi like
This is fake news
That is the world we live in now where if you disagree with something
Specnaz
Anyway
Like some of the summation of the research
There's one more thing I found
Because he hate
All these media people
He talks about how he so much better than them
Right
Which is another advertising tool for websites
Say nice things about you
That's another Alexa this is a website that gives you a rank
It ranks all the websites in the world in terms of traffic
So most of the top ones are Google
Different different countries
Google.
Viejo
UK
Infowars.com
Their Alexa rank is 1300
49er really good
My Angel Fire website is not
I'll tell you that right now thing I've ever done is in the top million so I mean I'm not shiting on him
For what he's achieved
But when he talks about how huge is audiences and then is like
Bring up Alexa
But he brings up quadcast and Alexa and talks about his dad
He's 1349 I'm going to give you a few websites
And tell you where they are
What do you think it is
This is a good guessing
Top
CNN
I would actually
Say they're lower
Fake news
Fake news yet let's call him 3
Number 90
BBC
I'm getting worse
Oh that's a
Good question I'm still America Centric
And this is worldwide
Let's go with
Jesus your
You're going higher as we go along
I figured out the game
Guardian
I love the guardian
So let's go with
Let's go with 70
Xhamster.com
P*******
Oh I know
Let's call that
All the points got to be in the top
40 right
No
P****** top 30
P****** is 51
For novice 51 xHamster is not a popular so I'll go 100
Huffington Post
Fig
Let's call it 185
Daily Mail I'm 50 off on literally every one of them
Daily Mail
280 16
People read the
Washington Post
Cuz I was going to go
70s
50 news site called blasting news
Messenger app
That game
I don't have the number I but I saw it on the list
This way up there
Behind all of those also his
Patriot The Drudge Report
You would think
No
It's not what's 629
Therapist
Chuchumaa 129th most popular website in the world is pretty crazy
In the world that I live in
Conservatives
I guess it should be
Because their voice
So much louder
And so different
Seems that they should be
It seems that they should be so much
They act like they're so much higher
Yeah well that when you take this it's like I'm so much more popular than
CNN's fake news or 13 49
Yeah it is a big difference
Between those two
But he's not
He's speaking to his body
They're passionate
CNN readers
What they make up for
It's the actually talking about Glenn Beck and I were back to
Eclipse
Search has done all that out
Oh my God
Is it said about Trump
And he hosted
He can't wait to see how things go
This is so sick on many levels
It's like saying
Roshes green
Digital pink
Of course
And then again what is this failure
College eaters all over
ABC CBS NBC
Apologizing for conservative
Apologizing for Donald Trump
Bean recipe
Is an Insider admits that
Apologizing
Then he goes on
It's upstairs
Ex machina
Trying to rehabilitate himself hey Kelly
The class to leave
Hated her guts
It's even worse with you back
Go
You are
I don't bash other major talk show host
You done and talk radio
I know how you been
8 years
How to get everybody you are
Bad
News
Now we got bad
Like I love I love I love to laugh
Other news on Megyn Kelly
Alright cuz I did that ass in Spanish
I'm so glad you picked up on that cuz that was what Charmed me about that clip
Thing in the world how does he
Also also I like you like how he's like
Half the nation
No it's way more than half
Trump's favorable ratings are like 27
If you what's the
What's that metric called
Subtractive e+
You know like where you take the favorability against unfavorability
He's
SuperLotto
What was it
Obama whenever he was elected he added
+ 70
The he's worried that there will be a coup
Against Trump and most of the country is like
I mean
Wanted a third
Will you saw that in his farewell speech
Which it which goes so again
Alex Jones's entire narrative
Not for mortgage
Yeah
Everybody should have four more years
I'm not saying that
But it is to his detriment that he
Play so soft
Too hard
America
Here's my Theory on
On where we are now
The Siri is this
Because Obama was so reason
The only way to fight against him
Mix it
If Obama actually had gone far left
Then the rate would be much more towards the center right
Now because it'd be much easier to
Said because Obama was so in the center
The right
Had to go further and further and further and makes
Yeah like they had to make that up because I couldn't be like well Obama seems like he's pretty reasonable and he's governor
Idea consistently made overtures to try and cooperate
Korbel
Who's going to be the new
Like hacky things
To say or like
Someone posted about how I
Hey conservative
Good luck
Cuz you had eight years of the most
Conciliatory
Polite
Decent trying to work with you president in the world
And you are f****** shiting on it
And now you're going to see what happens
When liberals don't want to play along
I think there's something to that
What I don't
We are on our goal is like
Hey
We believe that your pee
People to
And their entire goal is
You're not people
Literally
Demon repeatedly
So it's not like
Liberals will still
Even though you read all those articles worth
Here's why we lost cuz
Appeal to Middle Americans
We lost because Middle America those those
That's why
Yeah it is straight up you know if bubbles are the Multicultural Center
I hate it when you live in your bubble of all the different types
Two people together
So there was too much to cover in this episode so I'm going to do a
Quick rundown of things that could make the cut
Excellent
There was a
What Geico
Rodger Stone who hosts the show
Had a nice quote about how will Donald Trump
He's knows he's going to be videotaped
So these possibly exist meanwhile Billy bush
Got him on a film set on a f****** film set when he was wearing a microphone like me
So like that pool logic to me is so crazy they called
Has it Billy bush had any idea
Both of them
More fun for me
World we live in Alex talk about how free speech is going to end
And one of the things that he cited was that when they arrested Dinesh D'Souza I knew the game was up
I looked into it 2014 they arrested him
I can see was in illegally donating
To the senatorial campaign of a New York Conservative candidate named Wendy long
So that's when he knew the game was up
So I looked into it and the government charged with illegally
Clean bulbs
Donate $10,000 each to campaign of an old friend from Dartmouth College
I would be understanding
He would reimburse them in cash for their contribution
Question they would donate
About the donations reassuring
People the people who are donating
Had sufficient funds to make the contribution
Miss Long pressed on the matter
After the election
The government said
Told Miss Long not to worry because she had not known about
So he actually found at this point the only way to break campaign Finance laws
Like that's the most obvious way that like that might as well have been him writing
And I'm willing to disguise my
On the website
Ridiculous
His remarks
Constructive is the only way
Guy from a letter to the court from mr. Susan or Mistresses ex-wife
Dixie D'Souza
Great Neck treatment she said he had a quote character and lack of truthfulness
And accused him of physically abusing her
Now hold on it's not over on his own behalf
Explain made the illegal donation
Because he wanted to help Miss Long's floundering campaign
Quote I could see that personally she was humiliated he said
Mr. D'Souza who came to America alone from India
Teenager described as a member of his quotes
Surrogate family at Dartmouth
The government argued that Mr d'souza's crime was not a myth
Misguided actor friendship but
Premeditated decision to break the campaign Finance
I was doing this
Because I want her to win cuz she was humiliated
Exactly what he did note the pathetic part about it is.
I wanted to kill that man
And then
The Great
Cool you're free
I didn't realize
Like I care about my family
My surrogate family
That's why I did
Lancer
When it's not
You're trying to cover Your Tracks
What episode is a beautiful thing
It would be more like him throwing her under
To me to do it
Craven is more like
He is
Knowingly
Stimulating
Not just a hunch
Craven is not
Also cut from the comic book
We have to get to what I think is going to be the most important thing that's ever happened
But the second coming of Christ
But alright
I can play those clips if you want to hear one
The sad part is
Almost
But that was
Just a shortening
I remembers another gate Trump was
Kid on
Elijah Craig
Allied allegedly it was a specific
Oh no it is
A hooker
Probably something I don't I don't think
Is that evidence
We have proved anyting
But I also don't think it's outside the realm of possibility
The most
Inside the realm of possibility most people who've been covering it had been covering it with the caveat in the sea
Same way the BuzzFeed
Says with a sponsored content
I think every article that I've read about it
Has been like
Verified this isn't is not
You're verifying these
The president was
Was briefed on the
Which is fair to report you should be reporting that is there
Keep that as far as the peeing on thing
I have no problem with him being
P. Me neither
And it's not even like
Then the sexual exploits of JFK are
Thrown under the rug because that was back whenever peep
People have the gentlemen's
Agreement look like
Oh we will
His private business private he was up to and because of decorum they didn't check
Play witches on them
Because that's not
That's the that's the salacious thing
In that
That everybody
Like gloms onto
He may be
Being blackmailed
And even if
Compete on a dog
They're blackmailing
Perfectly with someone
What is Candida
But it could be but let's say it
Let's like positive world where he's not being blackmailed
Hillary Clinton because of the narrative it's already been set up and because of his axe
And how ruthless Russia is
Cancel like
We're in a place now where Russia could come up with anything
And be like
Do what we want or will release
Like you really don't have blackmail now we can make it
So far beyond the realm of reality now like that whole fake news thing
Is
For everybody
Because now there is no legitimate
Legitimacy
Do any bed oven
Snopes
I can't believe or not believe
Cuz you're dumb
I am
Puppy gate stuff
His take on it is pretty predictable
I might have to cut this off at some point
It's pretty pretty
Vegetable
Again
Ridiculous
Usually the multiple story
It's not easily to Buncombe or easily Devon
Whatever you want to say about it it's very hard to unverified but
Fleming
We're going to allow it
President Heaven blackmailed by the Russians because they have video of him
With women urinating on each other I'm sorry to have to talk about that on here but that's what's been putting the news
So this goes back to the decorum thing we're talking about this is Alex Jones's fake decorum
I look dirty dirty stuff
Children
Avoid learning about the world
Is everything turned
I'm so fat like on Tuesday
Obama gave a
An uplifting beautiful speech about Unity
Wednesday
Trump deny being
Peed on by hooker
The world that we live in
It's amazing
On Spotify play lighters
There's no way that we could write anything more insane than what's going on right
If you want to hear about insane
Look at this juxtaposition of I'm sorry
Talk about
Now here is next
We have to cover it Express and the clintons
Leotard pedophile net worth
Is the clintons are clearly involved with the whole Hollywood Elite in a row in a Roman polanski's in the Middle Street
Apologize for pedophilia
Over and over and over and over
So he keeps doing this thing he keeps doing this thing where he's like I don't want to talk about peeing but also
Lansky Lansky bro
But also everyone in the clintons organization is a pedophile
Who was a billionaire
Convicted pedophile private plane
He would take people on vacation
Bill Clinton is in his Rolodex
Coronavirus
Pretty much everybody's prove your f****** kids
I'm going out with some bad when I was younger
To save the Press
I don't know
And I didn't know but it was also selling guns
My blood
That sort of thing but like
I did hang out enough guy
I imagine
Did if I had hung out with a pedophile at some point
I found out later
I wouldn't be like
I shouldn't have done that if I didn't know that about them that sucks
I wish I would have known but
They were
They work f****** kids around me
Corollary in our world
A lot of
And let's not say a lot
Melissa
Measurements
Yeah
Comedians are all crazy
Who are in that
I've done some bad ship
I didn't know there were always been nice
Like once I know that
That immediately changes
This whole thing about the
Stop music
These
Can we stop
I'm sorry I know I hate it too I hate it
50 years of date
Nathan Bill Gates
Has ever suffered
He does this whole long thing about how it's the liberals who are into the sexual perversion
Then he has this
Send
Then I think
Delicious
Please enjoy
Cuz it's all the Liberals are
Best Philips ards the product they're obsessed
Hollywood
The f****** kids
What's
I'll tell you
So you're right f****** now
Beautiful perfect
Picture perfect family
That's a great
I like people
You can say the most sex
This thing you can think of the least expensive thing about him he's into perfect
10 women
No it's not a crime
He's been married
No his family does have a very children
And one of them is just completely ignored
Tiffany has another daughter that never has just completely ignored
Scenario
No I think she's doing fine but on The Osbournes they had another daughter that wasn't on the real
Comedy show
Did not want any part of the show
I thought you just
Like the third Olsen
Because Mary-Kate and Ashley were twins there was another one
Isaac but isn't
Public eye before
Is it
Got it
We shall meet at dawn
Jordans
Time is come
We have to get to
I wish I was playing music
Arthritis
I don't even want to explain to you what this is
Okay I just want to start the clip
And watch your face
Oh God no because this is going to blow your mind
This is something
From 2000
Are you picking up what's going on yet
He's the Lord a conspiracy
Do you understand
Mario is right now
We'll see
Alex Jones doing stand-up
But
Do you have any of it
No
Oh we're gonna
I'll give you a bit of a run now
Brought up
To the Lord of conspiracy
Broadway show
Absolutely
Dancing
Paranoia it be beautiful if we were going to write an opera
That would be the name of this Opera
We'd have to do in Italian
That's the only way
Alex Jones is friends with duck stamp
The two of them are friends because Doug likes
F****** weird
And when Doug was headlining
The
Cap City Comedy Club
Yeah I did there Open Mic once actually I didn't
And
Really really mentally ill people who are doing comedy came up to me and wouldn't leave me alone and so I left
It was way too uncomfortable
Nobody has ever been like man I wish I had left
When he's down in Austin
He's like hey Alex
Come do a set
Bring me up
Stage
So this is what
Now he's started with a but seriously
Which is great. I love that
Fantastic
Let's see what he's got.
Pre pre listen to the clip
His chops
Bar
Well you know a lot about Bill Hicks
Faked his own death
Alex Jones
You know that's conspiracy
Great bet there's a lot of conspiracy about that he's Andy Kaufman as
I want to play the end of that cuz you are laughing you were laughing over this I want you to listen to the audience reaction cuz I think it's in
You see how that
Tapered out
There was like a couple of Wu's and then silence
This I think if we're analyzing this as performers are so
What happened there when he started yelling
Was he was attempting to get into character
He was trying to get into the Alex Jones persona
And he got that
I realize
Chewbacca
Oh yeah
Celebrity goes to the neck
And by the way I caught out nothing
All I did was separate the clips
This is all of it
The film clip
Sounds like a
Mcmillers
He thought that motherfuker was the last
Possibly he thought he was doing Dennis Miller
When he was like that call Fidel Castro
Get it
Saddam Hussein
Why you're laughing
The clip went onto Dead Silence from the audio
Yeah well that's not a joke
Not a good fit
It's not even good public speaking really if you want to take comedy out of it and just like you're giving a lecture
I think that's the problem is
Realize
About halfway
Through those words
He doesn't have anywhere to go
But again that's what I think is
B I'm trying to get into
He's he's constantly trying to get to that gear
But he's
He's not used to being in front of an audience
That doesn't give a f***
They want to see Doug Stanhope
He is an impeachment
To getting to Stanhope
Plenty of
People who are familiar with Alex Jones Maybe
Who's also a dirtbag
That's a good point
It's possible to here
All of the
What be all these dictators
Cuz he's in the mix
These dictators that have been put in place by
Eisenhower
Call
El Castro
Cuba the Caribbean
AdvoCare
The pirate
He's actually you know
It was a
Keith Richards
Fidel Castro
A hundred percent
Israeli channels no doubt about that
The score for the movie Danny Elfman
Composer this is me trying to act like I know anything about pop culture I heard a composer is going to be
Who cares
Okay so
So let's
Let's go from just a comedy
Point Break
Not great not very very poorly constructed
I don't think there's really a premise
I think there's so the premise here there's a premise but not a comedic
But you're building a joke there's nowhere to go but if you
It's that our leaders
Keep putting in these dictators
And Design
They fake Wars and I have to watch people die
That's the premise
Does he
Does he know he's
The Comedy Club
Okay
Here's a hundred percent
I hear Voice or something happen
Doug Stanhope
Doesn't really like Alex Jones
And I think
Now and he's
Let him in
Situation
But he knows he's going to fail
Because it's going to be entertaining to him there is a truth in that
To me there is nothing
Funnier than
A comic book
I went to
Comedian Bill squire
Cleveland
When I was unprepared for it
He took me on the road with
To The Dakotas
And one-nighters
And then in
Sioux Falls South Dakota we're there for like
Free night
The first night we were there they let me go up
Club
And I didn't have the tools I didn't have the skills to do it
The job so hard
And bill went up after me
He was like Hey guys
You know like the friend of mine
We drove here from
Chicago
Watching you guys
Really hate him
Was so funny
And I thought that was hilarious to me like
Cuz it took but I maintain this that the other side of it
Mike Wiley is the
The funniest writer
And there is nothing funny or
To me then watching Mike Wiley Bob
Mike Wiley is a Chicago comic
Who eyes
Mostly one-liner base
Tremendous writer chops
You can find his
CD on iTunes
It is yeah I can't remember now
Alex does
Get a little bit of juice
In this neck
Does asparagus
I don't think so buddy
And again I want to
Be clear I'm not cutting on
There's either
They're just segments
Reality
That's where you got them
They hate prisons
Everybody Hates Chris
Especially
The odds is good
Bedtime
Poor poor him
Yeah I like that yelling about rebuilding
That's a nice visual image but I don't know how to connect
He's got that you got that feel of like
Every single where he knows isn't working
So he's starting to get louder and louder as a way to cover it up like
Oh yeah I can't hear their laughter because I'm shouting
I meant things
Bad
Turn the little bit later
Libby
Dissolution
So this is the thing that Alex talks about all the time on his program
It's a process that is problem reaction solution
People who are trying to manipulate the world 11
Like George W blow the problem
Iraq because
Is his dad
Well the problem was they needed more oil
I'm sorry
The problem is 11 happened
Go to war in the solution
I don't talk
Now it's all stupid text realized
The idea of false flag
Is that everyone has this
All the stuff planned ahead of time
This problem
And then we will offer them the solution
You create Terror and they will beg us to
How come out
Really why
They do have that it's not it's not that they cause the Christ
No
Do it right
You know what you know what I think likes me out there's no there's no crisis that you can't turn into an opportunity
But not on the same level as
But maybe
Alex would think he is
Never let a good crisis go to waste
Is
Is an unfortunate
Sentiment
It's bad opt
To be caught saying it
Because it makes it look like you might
Set up bad things to happen
But they really behind it is
We want to help people and if opportunities arise to do at least
To do those things
Famously
Was super excited
Japanese Brown
Pearl Harbor
Because then he can help
Which stocks
It was short
Nothing Better Could Happen then the Japanese bombing
Pearl Harbor
It's in some ways taking too long
Norbit
Take me to Longview is always a way to get high
Very last characters
People
Jesus Christ
100-percent Doug
From the back of the room
Definitely a couple times
If I clap
But when there's
Clap
I'm pretty sure it's so if it were me in the back of that show it would be him saying something in me gone
Well I got that you recognize my life I've ever listened to Jimmy Pardo CD
Pompous clown
You can hear Mike Schmidt laughing throughout it when no one else is laughing
He gets it
This is a different
But the same result
Doug is not laughing
With Alex
He's laughing at
Oh look at you out of your element
Yeah and I think
Do you really think
But if Alex had learned
The lesson
Of the beginning of the set when he tried to get into character and it didn't work
If you'd just
Howard Pruitt
I think this would go way better than
Really
But because he
He keeps rattling off backs that no one gives a f*** about
It gets
F****** weird it is such a
Up and down for his energy on that is
Let me tell you about
You bad dude
Yours is next
I want to pause there really quick as this is another thing that he does
I all the time as you like
Admit exactly what they want to do in public
The implication there is
Read all those
I'm smart
I'm going to relay this to you
The second implication
Is that
Everybody else
Those Publications
And he's like
Oh yeah
And they don't tell the people because they are in on this globalist
Conspiracy
I apologize for going so fast
Gif
Anybody
You text but I mean
That there is a population
Everyone knows that everybody knows that any problem realistically if you look at it
It is more resource allocation
Yeah we good
Support
Do more people we just did things a little bit more judicious
Nope
Listen
Goddamn
Faces of every person
No you can't like two of them this is full. So
Of course it is
Even though for he was huge
Is because there is
Because there was that huge round of applause
No
Well
That's a polite Applause the only other time people plotted in math
Is when he brought up
But he was about to bring up
No I don't notice
That's what I want
People all the time like the
The first sentence
Oh no
And then the phases go
Blank is someone who sees us
Kind of Comedy
I would love this
The number of bland cookie-cutter open-mic s*** I see
Yeah
Let's I get a little
You still talk about Rockefeller and how he loved me
Panda
Area code 903 number
Noriega
It's just incredible
False Flags
Lake Pleasant kill 1 million people
Missed you that's like it's a little bit of light
Shenanigans is analogous to putting like firecrackers in someone's mailbox
I legitimately think
Because it was so unlike
Now
Here's where she at
How could she
Beer
Come on
Hit me with that
So him and telling him to get off stage or tell jokes
We all hear the wooing of the audience
People start cheering
And that's because Doug
Has gotten
You were laughing over it but Doug yells at the audience this is for me assholes which almost confirmed
Setting Alex aftertale
And because Alex has no goddamn
Confidence in the world he keeps being like
Are they asked me to do this
Look it's almost apologizing
Impro
Doug has just walking up there for five seconds, and he's about to do
Text God
But it's also like anybody could have made a good joke
In that circumstance
He sounds like that was all one bit
From Santa
That he had written this
Years ago
F****** killer punchline
Always wanted to do a two-man
False flag operation
Gets off stage
Alex is a little bit of
Stratosphere
So what's awesome about that
With the idea that he was going somewhere
That's my point is the best thing that Alex has ever says it a lot but there is no
Ever
This might be the secret of 2070
That could be the secret
God dammit
What would what is he
I want to be in
What time will you probably
Every single time
I think it's like
What is it
Feel like to I want to crawl inside of his brain
And just sit there and watch that like the movie Inside Out where you have those
Emotions
It's probably just like anger and then
Flickering neon light
Just picking anger angry
I understand clearly I ever I don't think I think there's a lot of
I think
Hunter jealousy that motive
Definitely fear
Fear is
Massive motor
Do you think
Afraid
I just had
Sphere
That's why
Afraid or is he projecting that
That's what he needs to
Hard to say
In the years that we end up doing the thot
Figure it out but for now I don't know
They had him as a
It would be
The greatest day ever finds out we're doing this
I'm sure
I know I almost guarantee
We've got meetings Illinois
I guarantee
If he were to find out that we're doing the show
He would bring it up
Jesse Wood
Even if even if we still never had any less even if it were
30 listeners
He would totally do that I also think even though we're doing this show out of my bedroom
But I also think he would accuse us of being MSN
Soros funded
Sitting in damn
That's the other thing that is kind of amazing about the world
We live in
He only makes
Stronger
Oh so we're like Obi-Wan in this
So eat
It's entirely possible
That's
Any any of those two
Have You Ever Seen The Boondocks
Find another comic strip
So there was a
They had
Gray table saw
Ann Coulter
And then Al Sharpton
And how they would go on those
Yelling at each
Green Room
This is so much fun how we get to do this
And it's all men
Pretending to have a boy
Point of view you want
The Labyrinth scam
No interest in a scam
I just want to laugh at Alex
We will affect my lutely
Disguise any
The s*** out of your advert
I don't know if you really
Oh my God the market
Is on the rise
What would you say would happen if I don't know like the
Electronic
Platinum still have
For me to get into right now
You buy Platinum
You going to get your dick suck
Anyway we have one more clip this is Alex Jones's big
Closer
I am going to bring out a cigarette
Cuz
I think we got a smoke one wow he
Close out his set
This
Is one of the most
Alex Jones
Style
The Alex Jones
Santa was peeking out from
The first of all we should all be so f****** lucky as to have that kind of an introduction
God
I was too afraid to face the New World Order
But you got to hear what he says at like right after
Introduces Stanhope
Crazy
God dammit
So he's 8 couldn't make that out what he's like
Swing first
And see what happens
It'll be on video
That's amazing imagine if
Here's what I want to bring up
His
His callers were not
And he actually had to
To deal with Baba Booey
Baba Booey
All of his broadcast
Would just be
Unveiled
Threats
All the time there would be so many smart people dancing circles around him
I think I seen him
I think the only way that he responds
Any challenge
Is through the threat of
I'll kick your ass p**** and there's no there's no
You love the new world order
Which
It's a one-to-one comparison for the Wolfpack
Yeah they're big
No Wolfpack with red and black
Hollywood
I didn't like the lineup of Hollywood
I always prefer
All I remember is the red and black
Cuz it seems like
Challenge
Slightest chance
It is
Immediate viola
Well it's immediate flip into character
You think this is
Character
Like when he yelled a couple times
To get into
The Alex Jones persona
Other than
Just rambling about Nan
Westlake
Off-air
Not pleasant I don't know I'm sure there are nice qualities about him I'm sure he's not a monster of a
But like
I bet he wouldn't be
Yeah but
I think depressed him
We learned that on the last episode Barfly Alex Jones microphone
Is Charles Bukowski
Concentration camp
In Austin
But the thing I wanted to bring up was that
All this talk
About
Bill Hicks faked
That's a very Bill Hicks
Send
Yeah that's
You're dumb p****
Hello, dumb
That whole bit
Texas
Text or it's proof that Alex Jones
Which I won
Ma
But is it is
Oh man but it was
Let's live in a world where
There's no
And that sort of
I hope it lives up to the hype that I built
That was some solid
Wow that's
Isn't it mind-blowing
These weird
Turtles that we keep finding all this stuff
Right now I had no I had no idea
That's a that's a whole idea
Hi
Dammit
The opportunities that he has to be crazier in
All the time
Is mind-boggling
Yeah
We should do I make
Trio marriage
Well you're good Christian man I'm a good Christian man I think we all agree
If he would be the third host of
This podcast
And we can just get like
Tony said that
The best
Cast
Yeah
A after
Interview Leanne
Does judge mean
I'm assuming that he doesn't have
Staff writer
Like you know but nobody right
The show
Leave the clips are indicative of the show as a whole
No way you could
But it's so mean
Yeah it's
If you have to fill
It's an admirable skill
Well with most people can't risk
That's true
Fly up
If you need
2 hours of time filled and you don't care about the quality
It's like he's just a
Sports Talk radio host
Conspiracy
For the global
Boogeyman
Is the globalist
No matter what
Can go back to it
The soundboard I can play
I'm your boogie man
I bet pre pre ready
Because it's so vague
Can mean whatever you want in the same way that you are heckling him
The New World Order
Yeah yeah yeah
Getting raped in prison to with his
There's five man holding you down
What the f*** are you even talking about
Yeah that's right
I don't I wouldn't wish that
My worst globalist
Absolutely not
That sounds like
Like a bad day
If you want to make a good
Twitter at knowledge underscore
Or you can reach out to us by email at knowledge fight at gmail.com
We are also on I-20
Search for knowledge fight you will find
And also on YouTube
Not very good no just like a real Alex
Wingtip 0 Alex Jones
That's the sweet science
Jordans
It's been so much fun
This is the best day of my life
I hope your set tonight goes much better than
Thank you all so much for listening will catch you next time
Later
But
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color