Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
Discuss
The ongoing
What is the downfall
Which locally lovingly coincides with the
Alex Jones
Parallels
How to draw
Believe that he's the archetype of a technomancer living embodiment of not only his childhood dog
But also
The Union
You know nothing there we go
Yeah we're going to be able to just get it down to like a half a sentence
Kaboom eventually but it's more fun to draw it out as long as
Donator Chris
Congratulations on becoming a policy wonk
We probably will
Hey look
Anybody's donating
F*** it I don't give a s*** this is great
It is
It is great all those people love what I like this is our third episode and 3 days
1 2 3 hours and 40 minutes to remember that one
People still seem into it
So
Thank you all
Yes
So are we
We can talk about what's going on in the world
What keeps going around and around in my
Is that
White people
Would rather end democracy than allow people of color to part
Participate the route
People voted people so blatant
Play kurupt so absolutely
What they were promised
And all of the f****** that they
Bring to mind the idea of like Manson Helter Skelter
We're going to precipitate a race or class war
Other off and then we will
We'll hide out in Romanian
Welcome
Freestyle Libre
But we will however be taking your donations and using them to build a compound that we put into the forest
Are welcome to join us
The class we're going to put it into ahead of Easter Island there is welcome
Prince this on yesterday's episode but I
FBI director
Jim Comey
It was within the Spectre
Of his
Is growing Russia investigation
Just before he had gotten fired
Bye-bye
Before that he had requested
Resources 2X
Bad ideas strong indication they were really coming to it
Couldn't think of any reason why
So
He gets fired
Got the paper trail in the documents
But come out
Jeff sessions
And is that beauty
From the investigation
Trump
To fire
Jim Comey
But then comes out that Trump had asked them to advise him
To fire him
Yeah that makes sense
So it's all this circular Dante
Technically they still did advise him
M22
Unlike multiple statements Jeff sessions has made under oath
Absolutely
It's bottle
But the world is a f*****-up place it's not appropriate I don't think so
Compare this to Nixon
Saturday night Massacre
Well I think even Beyond it just being worthless
Princesses are super death
You know like
That was just a break
That was just them breaking into something this is
Broken political system Nixon wasn't
Helping
A foreign power
Break into the Watergate Hotel
You was doing that for purely selfish reasons
A selfie
People involved in Trump's team obviously have self-advancement
But they are interested in
But this is directly like
I am firing someone
Who is invest
Forgetting
Partisanship aside
I don't give a fuk
If Obama was under FBI investigation
Have you fired the FBI director
I would be just as like Blown Away
Republicans
Would be shooting themselves
On the front lawn of the White House
It's insane
Actually I understand that you're speechless but thankfully we have a man who is never
Speechless at our disposal
Is Alexander Emerick Jones
Who went on air today
Looked rough
Look
Hired
That was what I was getting at
It's only hair
And this is how he
You start that is broadcast
Align himself with the proof and it's time for you to choose her side your
Alex Jones
Call area where we get our information from
That is a direct reference
Two Donald Trump's
Sources
Hate to do it even though I did it like a week ago
I'm sorry I'm sorry cernovich
Even though the medium
Sunbury late last night talking to multiple sources and I called Rodger Stone about 11 Texas
Midnight Hour
Multiple sources
He's talking about the
Three wise men Johnny Jack and Jim
Y'all talk about
He was on the phone with the whiskey
Fatburger
Very drunken phone calls
Rodger is it a
Rodger only the Beast
Rogers on people
Talk to outside the White House
We'll get it on into today but I for my other sources separately have exactly what happened,
Call me was compromised
Compromise for a long time
And
But sources
To try to exert pressure on a house
Can the White House carryout
Basically
If that is what your source told you your source is
Very non-specific
You Alex
Sources believe exactly what he is already told
He's been compromised by globalist
Guitars
Speculum
Thank you Alex
Is b*******
And this is what I want to get to become Queer as this goes along
But this is like I sincerely believe
This is the darkest moment of our politics
In my life
Agree in the 33 years that I've been alive
Close today
I think it's one of the most dangerous time
And we don't make the Right Moves
We could lose
A lot of Art
The way Alex Jones is respondent
Memes
She knows there
You're f*****
Keno's
I believe
Kobe getting fired
Is a nail in the coffin
For most of the Russia
Yeah he knows that Rodger stone is going to prison
He knows that
Manafort is done
Dino's plan is
But days away from a grand jury
He knows these things
Not stupid enough to think they're like
Kobe's going to help that
And I think you would have to be
Really stupid
You have to be
Some kind of
Colossal moron a good idea to get rid of
To be some
Kind
Salute
Smoking
Idiots
If you
Stupid person heretofore unseen by this planet
If you think that that is a great idea you probably are dumb enough to
I think they're like
There are globalists infiltrating
Everything
You know where I think it's pretty clear if you're looking at it objectively
He is not
Saying what
Feels
He's reacting and he's a panic man
Alex Jones
Scared
He is shook
Is fuc
He's going to flex a little bit there going to be some bravado and
Before we get to any of the real juice
He's got he's got explain to you what Jim comey's real crimes worth
0 find out
Ignored crimes ultramassive
That's one area
Andaz
Very very
But in a candy ass way
Lordy lordy lordy lordy I didn't know my goodness I had two doors I could go down
I had one door that the cover-up
So you know
Lordy lordy
Look who's not 43 Alex Jones you lying about your age but also
His most important
Lights
We are truly
Sickly I think he's probably about 50 is this the case even better
Come out
Tell your relays
You have an age counter on the website
Looks like s*** is supplements are not working
He claims
The Comey is real Prime
20 minutes
How old do you think
Early forties no f****** way
If he's 43
10 years old
From where I'm at
No
No way
And I've lived hard
Better start taking that super male vitality
Broadstar guard on sale now
Anyway
So
Alex Jones
So he gets into the Tacoma is real problem is the
Let Loretta Lynch off
Then didn't prosecute her which I'm not sure
There is nothing to prosecute
Not not really she said she was under investigation
Navigation Nono gmetrix
Bill Clinton when he was under investigation he wasn't
Castigation Department of Justice
Things that were being looked into by the FBI with
The Clinton Foundation
But that wasn't the doj
Well I mean
Between
Well this was like 6 months ago so there was backup
Pets
Was that his real crime
What's his
Real crime
Get weird
He's very
Andy asked why I don't understand what exactly
Deepstate sources
But like legitimately
I'm not cutting out like any real substance
This is the kind of thing he's pointing the finger at he's like everyone knows he was he was strict
Is a brightly
Call me cuz
He's a guy who's not going to put up with p****
Visitors at his next clip is actually where he gives what I would
Describe is the first time he tries to incite violence
All nervous
Power talking
Myself in person
Broadcast
We're not looking for trouble we're not looking for revolution when not looking for blood mast
Does hordes and their
Refugees
Mobilize West
And we are involved in dereliction of Duty
So it's
Quite like out out violence as it will be later
It's the
Trump saying like people used
She probably do something
What about this thing that's going to hit different years differently but beyond
Call to political violence
It's a call to James is like
Lock it down now
If you're just trying to like
You know War Games how to start
Authoritarian regime
You got to lock it down
Terror
I mean frankly I think at this point over in
Even better
A black lives matter protest turns violent
Sure
I've all democracy is over
Another camp
Campsite with terrorism Mixon
We are on the razor's Edge
Cougar
They're martyrs
But kind of
It's it's hard to imagine
Any situation
That this doesn't eventually lead to
Either
I mean
I don't want to stay Civil War
But I want to say if
If you are America
In America everybody else is f****** Ironman
I think they were
Maybe a more delicate way to put it would be like
What we were talking about earlier with the
Complicated and dangerous. Of Our Lives
And in order for us to avoid to avoid a revolution
To avoid a civil war it's like threading a needle
There's going to be really precise things that need to be done
Or working a box this thing
People are going to end up killing me
Yeah and I'm really glad we have
Right now that
Famous for
Stability threadneedle
Do you have to really navigate a way to
Speaking of someone who would never make a good so stress
I don't know if that's the right word
Seamstress
Do they sell
Yes I do
That's their whole thing it's so stress anyways
I don't really remember exactly what this toaster
Exactly with the Clippers about but it has to do with
Is Attorney General
And then
President
While
Yeah
Wow
The Monstrous kleptocrats
You know
Further like we've got a call
Call to Arms
Recessions of got a good people in front of Grainger's
Drop the hammer you know that is one of the biggest Hallmark
Of these Banana Republic Authority
Dictatorship
Punishing their political rivals
With
Most
If you want Alex is going to give a Litany of charges against Hillary Clinton throughout the rest
Over dictator
And I don't understand why everything
He's a strong man and indeed
7 year old
Mentally deficient
Poorly
Portion guy who Orange
That's the kind of looks like he has a butthole in his neck flap
Sometimes
What it folds just right
Yeah
I get I get that that is a decent argument there's a little bit more going on
Butts
Basically just shows
Does not understand
Subtleties of life at all
You told him you're fired
Yes, getting elected
World
President Trump months ago
The people wanted him fired when he wrote that letter right before the election
In that context
And a lot of people still Harbor a lot of feelings about that
But at the same time difference
Who's actively investigating
It's a bit different
It's a little bit different
Slick
They're not at all this
We're being clipped
Think of any other situation
Other than
That Nixon
Firing the
Investigator looking
Cox
Which Cox
Archibald Cox
Great care
And Rodger simulator makes a great pun about that
Nixon
Hahaha it's funny cuz Rodger Stone was involved with Nixon to
My favorite part of Rodger Stone beating on is eventually
I guarantee he's going to be allowed
To do interviews with Alec prism
Yeah probably
Do you have his back
Like its
I know that's true
And I forget it instantly because
How can that be
In addition
To Alex Jones not understanding the subtleties of wanting someone fired for one thing and not wanting
Empire for a different thing
So does not understand
Washington Post
Building Hillary
Kim Hawk
Why is it all television
The British Open
Why is it all those trees
Call Black everybody's thinking about them trees told me David Brock cuz I'm about to correct the record
Almost
So
He says
Trump Express to call me why aren't you invest
Hillary's
Scribes like the uranium deal
Pruitt's not real
I've written up and long extensive thing the documents
Exactly what was going on with that
She was not
Actively involved in that at all it wasn't uranium deal that sold things to Russia
It was
That's just a complete lie
If the FBI was to investigate her for that
Or anyone was the prosecutor for that
It would be a bogus prosecution
Why they wouldn't do it is just
Refer them to knowledge
You jump
Dumb assholes
I'm not here to say that Hillary Clinton's ass ain't get her because
They have fake story
Sounds good
And it was in that
Full of lies documentary Clinton cash
But it's not true it's not real if you get down to the bottom of it
Why you spending all this
It was 100,000 go to Russia
The fact
Lucky's just admitting why
Piece of it too it's not that
Not it
If that was it that would be
But it wouldn't
Experiencing now
Brett just multiple members
Of Trumps team who have lied under oath about contacts with Russian
Agent
Right
You have Jared Kushner
Lying and omitting information on his security clearance form
About meetings
You have manafort
And Flynn both retroactively registering
As
After they have been fired from Trump's campaign
Your Carter page
Acting like a
Weirdo on television
Anyone have evidence
B Mike
Flynn was working with erdewan
To try and expedite
Gulen
Cleric
Who lives in the other Northeast somewhere
Take him back so he can kill him
And we
No thank you Mike Flynn was working with a f****** Turkish dictator
Do try and subvert our foreign policy
For money
And then on top of that
Really f***** up
Record
Just Mike Flynn went on Russia
Television in sat next
The Putin that a table
That's not really what we're talking about
Hillary
Did sell that you reign
Oh well then where
But you didn't
It's so f***** up it's a false equivalence based on lies on both sides
Like how bad
The fake thing about Clinton is
And lying about helping dying the actually really bad stuff about Flynn and the rest of them is
Treating his viewers
Like like
Babies like he's literally holding up Keys over here
Look at the jangly keys look at the jangly keys
Lordy lordy lordy
All these Jackie cheese over here constantly yells about like
People having no memory and the globalist want you to have no memory
He's actively exploding or hoping
But his audience doesn't have a battery
Look
He f****** praised that they only read Breitbart
They only do research on
The f******
Spirit boards on Reddit
I don't know that's all they do
That's only the only do that
Like
Zerohedge
If you still support
Yeah you're or your evil
I used to add in denial
Now you're just dumb
You can't be in denial
You're dumb or you're evil
That's it
If you still support Trump
I am done
I am done protect
Feelings
I'm done trying to
1st and Denny
Your real problem is you are f******
Stupid can I put a fine line of Lights cuz there's a Venn diagram
Between evil and stupid that is racist
Right sort of both but it's not fully either
You don't remember
It is both but racism isn't only stupidity and it's not only evilness
It's sort of a nice
Is Alex B
So at this point of the show
Alex Jones
Has a big dick
Effort interview
That the guy who's on his show almost everyday
Rodger Rodger Stone
Donald Trump's children
To talk about
The fact that Tony got fired
He brings in Rodger Stone
Someone who was a target of the investigation
Activity
He was a member of multiple
Sure everybody knows that he's a
A trustworthy and reliable source
There's no doubt about that
Burning down to the ground
That's a glamourpuss
Absolutely gorgeous
He is a fashion puss if there ever has been one
Alex Jones introduction
He isn't Rodger Stone
That can't be true I look forward to seeing that obviously
That is coming up in 48 hours on Netflix
What's the first aid closing today what is breaking down with coming
Let's let's go over from your sources
I can't reiterate this enough
It's a bad
Look
Like in the same way that Trump had
Comey fired
And then the next day
He was meeting with
The foreign minister of Russia
I would not allow it
Answered
Did the guy because the one guy who is at the center of
Forgot
He was not announced but he was going to be a part of those meeting
Actually Trump secret Lee met with the same guy that all the multiple Mets
Secretly and yeah they did not allow a
Into the
The Oval Office
LOL
United States press
Bingo allowed
Russian
Are inside the Oval Office I know that this is a little bit speculative but I don't
Any reason to think that the Oval Office has
Bug now
Like I have no idea
Like why wouldn't
I mean
Fake deference
Yeah it's a mean if he finds a bug which god dammit
Yeah
He could be f******
Peeing into a microphone
This is a funny plant
I like it
All of this stuff is being recorded
I do that future historians
Will be able to write on Thursday
What's sure
Stupid people hate black
That probably
The point
I was trying to make is that in the same way that is a
You fire the guy who's investigating your ties to Russia and then secretly meet with the guy there
And before administer
In the same way that's a bad look
Alex Jones having an interview with
The guy
Who was under investigation about the firing
Of the guy truly investigating
In the real world that's a bad look
It doesn't matter
In the world
F***** up
There's no way
There's no way that's okay
Yep
Priorities
Here's how I he decides to open
His energy
Let's let's go over from your sources
Samantha think Auntie comes today Alex
Publish the story which claimed that I had persuaded the president
To fire James Comey
CNN pick that story up
From
I would have come
I am not the source of that story nor have I claimed anything of the kind cuz as I have said
Initial many times
Donald Trump into anything
Mannequin
Frequency of my conversations with the president
Well I'm not the shy specifically I'm not the source of those confirmed
Joking about calling for
Mr comey's firing now for months
And beyond that the ideas that I somehow persuaded
True
She's been calling for Tommy's firing for months
About
Yes
How do you have been about as long as the investigation has been public
Oh wow
He stepped it up quite intensely
Sweets & Stuff
Calling
Beseech the president through Twitter
Sure maybe personally sit down
You got to do this
Here's what's funny about that
So he brought up
That
Trump
Says
Did that story was fake news
Right
Rodger Stone
Between up
He didn't bring up the last part of between
Where Trump says I haven't talked to Rodger Stone in a long time
Because earlier it is, if you said you talked to him a lot
And so did Alex Jones
Probably drunk
You think so
I could I could also see Stone lying about that totally they're both liars they're both
Inveterate liar
Rodger stone is f****** Petty
He is Trevor Petty you've blown up it's so many people on Twitter
The tattooed next
Corsi's Petty
And I think if Donald Trump really was shutting him out
Gdax against
I don't think that he would still carry water for him
If you wasn't still at least
Being strung along
Is being on the inside that's my feeling
So I think that Trump is lying
Episode of damage
Control
Right cuz
Even if you're an idiot present you have to know
That like
Especially when he is calling for tired and you fired
To pretend
And it might not have been all of it probably wasn't my best theory
Sessions was actively involved in that because
Yes because I believe a lot of things that I read speculation but
Things within a testimony believe that one of the name
Specifically that was on map
Was Jeff
Otherwise why would he lie
The reason that most
People
I've given in terms of their analysis
The Clapper testimony
Is that he was
Denver
The names you seen on master
Were they Trump Associates or Trump campaign member or members of the
And he said well both
Yeah
And that's a fun little cuz it could be two different people
The only person who was both
Jeff sessions
Really
Oh that's a good it could be somatic games everybody might as well be under
Everybody in the GOP might as well be like
Target on their back
Has probably spoke to the Russians illegal who are the main players at least publicly
And that you have people like Rodger Stone Paul manafort
Yeah.
Jeff sessions is the only player who has actually been in Congress
Right
That theory is largely hinge
On the idea that Clapper with playing semantics
That is him kind of
If that's if that's true
That's him kind of given one of those like
Hey I can't say it but you know
Books like
I think it goes without saying you don't want your National Security adviser to be compromised by Russia
That's a way of saying that without saying
Have to live in the world now
Somebody out loud says that
But I think that's why it doesn't go without saying
You had to say it but I think she had to phrase it that way and Frame It That Way in order to not give up the gay
So you say it
Is the key was compromised
Right I have a
Breached any rules
Goes on
In this next clip
He he wants
To talk a little bit about how
He's totally cool
With the firing
Presidents
Call me had no interest in the mega Crimes by the clintons
Foundation is not charity
It was the vehicle
Geranium but across-the-board
Your credibility is shot
You brought up the uranium
You whatever other things you're going to say it's almost not even worth investigating what those things are
First example
You haven't done your research
So I just
I don't I don't care, I don't have
Research he just doesn't care
It's true cuz it's Thursday
Clinton boner
Quite frankly
30 years
Yeah well it's not just that it is still that
Distract
From me being under investigation whataboutism
Yeah yeah
Do anything that the Clinton
Didn't do why are you picking on me it's because of my association with
And if you can
Pull that little narrative together Army of all right
Monstrous
Moron
Will f****** go along with it and he's unfairly
Means that it is an illegitimate
As real family
We're seeing indications
This is the last ditch
Facade is crumbling a little bit
They're doing these things
Because I need
Right but I
He goes on to talk about the end
A little bit
Get mr. call me seem to have no interest in those crimes
Wasting his time investigating be non-existent a Russian collusion
Again
There is no evidence whatsoever that would hold up in a court of law
Well I mean it's fair
Inasmuch as there's not
Publix
Information that would hold up in a court of law
Even even
It is almost
Murder trial what's the
What's the
What is it
What's the name of this song
Is so overwhelming
It's hard to really care about physical evidence
Yeah I mean you can you can get convicted for things without a body
Look at all the rest
That's the reverse
You just keep repeating
This is nothing
Call me just as he asked for more funding
But that's only because
That money was going to be wasted on something we all know
Mitigated
If
This narrative had anyway
Italics in Rogers
Instead of pretending
That firing Comey had something to do with how we handled the Clinton and an email situation
They would have come out and said
This is b*******
Keep we're firing him because he wants more money for a fake investigation
It would have been awesome
Give me
We're Republicans were trying to cut down on
On the budget we're trying to do all this stuff it's overblown he's wasting money Adventure
Easy narrative
To even get that far
Because then you're admitting that an investigation into yourself is the primary reason
You have to lie
Talk about what
Prosecute
Inspiring
Appreciate that
Three times you said the investigation into me wasn't
Unimportant that's like
F******
Peter stuff like
Close
And now you must hang yourself upside down on the cross
I like I like that we know more scripture than Alex Jones The Devout Christian
So this next clip
This
Commis real crimes
Again which are the hues
Father and talk
Real talk a little bit more about how you just
Looking weird
It was that Tommy
Was Violet in the chain of command was seen as Reckless weird
WYD
Attorney General
Sources said that's one hundred percent
Empire Building
Responsibilities of the Congress or the executive branch
There by 9 so fast
You noticed that
He said he thought it was a joke when he first heard the news yesterday totally disconnected from reality
He thought it was a prank is cuz he found out from the television
Way to get fired when you're the FBI director
Second thing
Is there an NFL coach
There's a reason that they
Appoint FBI directors for 10-year term
Is because
It's supposed to be completely non-political position
He is four years into his term him saying I'm I'm going to be around for another 6 years
That is how it should have been really f******
Really sucks up
Never going to go to bed for the FBI because they murdered Fred
Forget that the FBI is an evil organization
Everything
Can to ruin our an arm of the regressive GOP politics
Boat parts
That is been true for
Most of American History too broad a brush that's not all of it
At the very least hooverwood
I'm out now.
GOP hard on Fox
Saviour nailing why a lot of people who don't believe any of this Russia stuff some of them are pretty reasonable
People
Distrust
Comes from
Why would I ever believed anything intelligent
To say they all
That's a position I can kind of understand if you're going back
To the FBI and CIA
Their fraught with trouble
Overthrowing regimes in creating Banana Republic
They did it to us
That's how good we are at make
Banana Republic is accident
Maybe. Who knows maybe the globalists are actually the anticipated
Doesn't exist
Not in the way that I think paranoid people believe
No I'm not there but there
There's there's
Underground deep state
I don't I think it's hard to imagine that there isn't something
This podcast going to turn into you and me turning into the lone gunmen what's going on
6 f****** months ago
I don't know
Every every
Every single thing I thought about
I thought I knew about American
Politics
Civics the way Ark
The tution work
All of this stuff is gone
I'm against this idea that you're saying about this Underground
Deep State and what-have-you
Is Batumi that
Azizi an excuse as globalist
The glove box dealership
All of this.
If they were a secret underground
Football
People are that comp
Sure
Especially people that
All the people we have in government now
Some of the most incompetent people
And it's all across the board
How how is it that the Democratic Party
Could not get themselves elected
It has to be a view if you read the the Hillary book
The new one out
I can't remember the name of it but it is
It is basically just
Trees of interviews from the Hillary
Going over out in comp
It was at every step
Outlook
I'll be
Obviously
They were dumb
To think
We've got this
I were her I would too
You have to be like
Particular
Right before she didn't go as hard in the paint is
Cuz you needed to
But then there were things remind me better
There were things that went against we're outside of her
Control
Cecconi's letter
Such as
Alex Jones
You know but if you can't
20 points
You at home probably probably couldn't have if it wasn't Trump and brexit
That's probably
The only reason
France was saved by our fall
Chiron
Still in the middle of racketeering they will be destroyed by our fall is
A big Title Wave
This business class
I've just given a poetic title
This one
It's called The Stone.
That's too much
Nothing to do with heading off a Russian investigation
Senators Warner Feinstein's Franken Congressman Schiff
Fire heimbach nothing Alex
Nothing they're holding it in their hand they got nothing
Bogus
Humiliated if they continue down this path
We'll see
You know
It's there's nothing
It's bogus
They just keep this gun
What they should do is just
That's basically
It's basically what he's getting at getting trouble
Give it up it's like it snow today is it supposed herblock
Exactly
Kind of action
S*** where do you know
I have been communicating
With reptiles
Oh no they have been watching
Oh no
Just give it up
In the same way that Alex Jones
Whenever one of his ex-employees comes out and says some s*** about him anonymously he knows that they can't publicly
Please say anything about it cuz I found potentiality
Or in the same way that Rodger Stone can lie about being poisoned by polonium
His doctors can't correct it
The doctors can't correct it
You can make those eyes in the same way that he can say they don't have any evidence because they legally can't
You can trick people Intel that evidences be classified
Well and that's
That's another reason why
Stone
About
Because it wouldn't matter either way Trump has
To deny it
So you can say he's talk
However much
Even if he is
He still has to say the same thing
Why
Because if you are talkin the Trump on your Rodger Stone and Trump says
I talked to my buddy
Rodger Stone
That is basically
Saying I'm
Implicit in whatever it is Rodger Stone
What is it that you have
Just say no
Could you talk
Rodger Stone after he fired Flynn he was talking about how he's a good man
Great man
Didn't do anything wrong sad to see him go but he accidentally lied to the VP
Go let him go he's a good man
About all the stuff
Evite daughter
Wait
He might not have liked
Absolutely
Yeah this is murder on the Orient Express
We're getting
To hear maybe we should take a step back
Alex would like us to look at the big picture
I think she is the person
Guide
Rodger in a 5 minutes we've got left here I want to
Look at the big picture I'm completely made up
Trump
Business magnate
Nope
Untrue
Degrees fact that he's just being so blase about
What is true
The Democrats and the Republicans
I've been involved with tomatillo outside business ventures
Betsy
That's bad on its own
Everything else was normal that would be something
I am slightly blase on that
Quite Frank
It's almost
But
Being involved with Russian mobsters
And getting tons of money from weird Shady
That deals with people with
Checkered Russian pass
Like that
Not
Nothing
You know what I mean
Most of his money is Lent to him by a Russia connected Bank
You know that
Like how
Another way
He's quoted by somebody else but
Spiritually it matches up with
Madhavi
Investigations have been done into
Trump Finance
Lending comes from Russian sources
Even if it isn't poop
Even if it isn't political
Bulshit
Absolute b******* also
The main reason I stopped this clip
The wanted to warn you
That's going to be really f***** up
I want to give you a heads-up
The time
I'm the middle
Okay have a sip of wine and
And then towards the end Alex
Cannot let Rodger talk and it's
Delightful
War with us
They're fighting the cop killing gross
Their funding all the Social Distortion garbage
Danger
Country
Constitutional
And I told you I told you I told you I was sipping wine
I told you
Happening right now
Yeah like that's crazy
Is that at this clip isn't done this is merely.
Nothing means anything
It's not a Thor attarian ism
It's insanely disconnecting the inability to see what he's saying
Like the lack
Of of of self-reflection in his words are are
Are shocking
I think it's because you super hungover
Right there
Along with all his boxes
Oh great
Eel
Or or City
Watergate and they used it to undo one of the greatest political landslide in American history
Defending watered watered
Who's the Republican the Republicans turned on Nixon because they were going to
To get voted out
Hannah
So so this is
Republicans obstructionist about impeach
And that's when they turned on it
End up having
Yeah I don't think I don't think
At this point
They wouldn't possibly believe that they're not
So now here's the other here's the other hope there though
Just like
Beatbox
Talking right now
Pretending all of this s*** way
Was true and just rewriting history
Rewriting
The present in order to
Fit their narrative
Entirely
Possible that
These
True Believers in Congress
Think
Their connections
I'm so they are immune to being voted out
They can't possibly
Simply accept
That the
People who have that there are people
Who have voted Republican in the past
Who will turn against them
There's a lot of stuff whether or not they're wrong is a whole different world
Republican
That it would be incredibly difficult
How to get somebody out
But even if you have two primary them cuz it would be another Republican trying to
To take their seats as an incompetent
And that's such a hassle that most people wouldn't
Do it
I don't know
I don't I don't know
The fact that they're sitting here and
Let me be clear
I forgot that part of this clip was that Rodger Stone tries to rewrite White
Crazy
The rest of this is even crazy
There's two minutes
Frites
Win at The Ballot Box
A true of this extra
Is brother
Hillary Clinton
Chelsea Clinton
They should be compelled to testify
Conjecture it's not a conspiracy theory
Cold hard facts
Yeah it's time to get her out of the White House
Grand jury
Many many many
Email
They're coming after America with everything
I swear to God I didn't edit that at all
Twice within a minute interrupt a sorry go ahead and then immediately starts
That that is a man
Who is like
Insane
These roots spread
I don't know
I mean within the context of
So if if you can
If you can say
Kian rogerstone Haddon
An hour Converse
Yeah
I can't believe that
He really talks
Pastor Rodger the same way off
Probably not so if you can perform
We talk to each other about the same
Off Arizona
Just know Mike
Maybe more yelling
Imagine that on air
It's part of the dynamic
When Alex
Turn it is ratcheting it up
Because it would show it doesn't matter it is still a performance Stevens
Having listened
True black 5-month
Straight
And I'm dipping back into the archives
I have
Thorough investigation I'm engaged in right now.
Look
I I can't I can't review it yet
But I'm onto something really big
Doona
Do not ask Trump for more
Resources
Nextstep fired from the podcast
My cat takes over Giuliani
Like even even having listened to
Hours of
H & H
But you guys listening have no f****** idea how much I've listened to this dumbass
I've never heard him
Interrupt
Like
But the comedy of
Bahrain
Just remember the phrase I guess
A ton of
Rodger Stone interview
Because
I mean solved
More less
There's not a ton
More I can't remember if you still on this next or if he's already left
But
Rodger Stone
That notorious March 30th episode
Rodger Stone was around for a little while than Alex
Drunkenly deteriorated into a man talk about selling his car in the ways you learn
Beautiful episode
Go back one more time.
Just near the end where Alex gets super introspective refuses to look at
There's a little bit of that energy
Rodger Stone ends up leaving
And things go a little weird
They got a little bit weird we'll get to it
Butts
Expresso glass
Vetta, he's got more about Hillary's crime
This this this this really makes me feel good about President Trump
In that team has fire Towing
Tell me the stood there while Loretta Lynch met on airplanes to put Bill Clinton break the law while he's under criminal investigation
Lance Rashad there with all the Wikileaks info coming on or they were coordinating with the White House on the cover-up crimes
Iranian deal Sriracha the shell / Technologies China
Still not the clintons have been protected by the FBI for decades
Highest level cinematronics
And then all the Wikileaks pedophile information
Police Department 12 release with vfd I basically shutdown
So you can see you there that like his one example is that Loretta Lynch was on a plane with Bill Clinton
Yeah that's what he keeps doing all that much
Uranium deal brought up again
He says that
Installing our technology to China
When I was researching the uranium deal
What it boils down to is that Hillary Clinton because she was Secretary of State
Heads of departments like all the secretaries
Centrally in the
The cabinets
Are part of a nine-member organization called the Council on Foreign investment in the United States
Anytime a foreign company tries to buy something that may or may not be relevant to our national security
Play that I don't know
Sofia
Beginning of a word
Spears
But you're really good idea
This organization when
This uranium company was being bought out by a Russian company
Something that got reviewed by
Cuz it is
And Hillary Clinton have any personal
I involvement in the outcome of the ocean
She couldn't have a suede
Decision
And
The outcome of the Sofia
Is it they make a recommendation
And then the president can let the deal go through or
He can put the kibosh on the
Gotcha they don't choose what happened
So even if she had said
Don't let this go through
If it's not her choice to make so the idea that you sold this is number one factually inaccurate
I meant logistically enact
While I was doing the research into that uranium deal
One of the interesting things that I found out
Was it a 2016
Barack Obama did
Stop company
From being bought because you felt it was relevant to our national interest
Really it had to do with a recommendation that the city is it made
It was
Involving a Chinese company
From buying a Dutch company that produced microchip
Out of concern that they were doing so for nefarious reasons
I don't have too much of the microchip Market
So Alex
Sayings that are way too interested
I am giving examples from a year ago of Barak Obama
Stepping into being like
Well we've got to be careful about the Chinese consolidation.
Technology
So-so
Literally
Not literally meaning figuratively
The Liberals
He is decrying
For doing nothing
Witchy ostensibly
Article in the New Yorker New York Times
From February 4th twenty
16 that I've linked up in
That article about
The uranium deal
You can find all the resources there
It's fully documented absolutely concrete example against
All of that stuff about the WikiLeaks
This means he's never read it
Because those things aren't in there
Why does he
If he brings up
The pedophilia thingy
He is repped
WikiLeaks
We weren't talking about Comet Ping Pong
You're adding adjective misrepresenting
The actual Wikileaks say
Retro you haven't read
Someone has told you it's all secondhand
Wright Tire description
Again
I don't think Hillary is the best person in the world
She's complicit in some s***
But at the same time all of the examples
Auntie wants
And either lies
Or just things he doesn't actually understand
It's embarrassing
Is absolutely embarrassing
It would be if anybody but us was
Capable of giving a s*** I guess so everyone who cares is already written off Alex
He's lying and it doesn't matter
But thank you to everyone who actually enjoys herself
I didn't even get
Once we get
Enough listen
Say
45 million listeners
That's common
That's that's right around the corner with a with all the new policy
45 million people are about to be on important stuff
First
For now
IQ
What pimp yogurt
So this next flight
It's thicker
Then regular gas
It's thicker than the lies coming out of his mouth
Flip the yogurt
The next web I've done some research into it's going to be interesting when we come out the other side of
Is restoring our military
Restoring our economy
Give Russia was our enemy
Russia was controlling
President-trump
They would not be doing any of that
The first Russian
Call Trevor Thousand Years
Martin systems
There's more cold
Natural gas oil you-name-it can buy
That can't be true
Gas prices in Russia plunge Russia's main export
That's actually not a bad argue
Wasn't to hurt Russia instahealthy I say sorry
So
Here's why it is a terrible argument I don't know
From Frozen
Why would you support a thing that goes against Russia's thing if the premises were true
The argument would be good
So are either premises true exactly how much
Azure Natural Gas
Most of the numbers that you can find or speculative
There are bunch of reserves and other stuff we know about but there's unknown unknown
Reservoir
Oars we might find later
We don't know
Call Crystal
Absolutely
Is the Clean Coal is b*******
Absolute on the show and I realize I'm getting a little self-conscious
So it's time to fully leave that out
Call is Alex what is excellent with your abs
Document
Sing facts
Another kind of coal which is
Observe
The only way that you could rats be rationalized Cole is colditz prison
Differently
You do different things with it
And that makes it clean
The biggest version of isn't the only one that's really relevant to any national conversation
Is the idea of carbon capture
Technology you're aware of this but so those
It's a technology that's design
Collect and dispose of coal plants carbon dioxide emission
Before they escape into the atmosphere because once they get into the atmosphere
Can cause warming
And if
So
According to this article in Bloomberg
Technology may be on the drawing board demonstration
But it's not close to being ready for widespread use at an affordable price
No
The one u.s. plant that being designed to use carbon capture
Construction in Kemper County Mississippi
His two years behind schedule and four billion dollars over budget
Wow
A similar heavily subsidized project in Saskatchewan
Cost upwards of 17 trillion dollars
Survey
Have worked someone all that well yet
But at the same time
Trillion-dollar number of outfitting all of our coal-burning plants
Is Chewie higher
Then all sorts of renewable resources that we use
Well we got to save like 50 coal miners ball bats the other
They're not coming back
Mechanism
Cleco
If you look at the number of jobs that were lost because of the coal industry going down it's not me
Nearly as many jobs as just because of automation
And that's just a reality that's going to be on the table
How is if you look at the number of like
Tourism and Retail related jobs
That have been lost since Trump got in office compared to
The hypothetical games of the coal industry
Close enough
Root Looper retail and tourism jobs
Cuz people just cuz people don't want to f***
Come here
Hell if I do
Absolutely
So you remember all those you remember
When people used to say well
I mean it's not working in a coal mine
Yeah
You could die if that can marry
Subsidizing
Started subsidizing renewable energy
Hijab
Those jobs those people who were work
Coal mine
Yeah probably work in a
Solar Farms
Murdered by
F****** mind
Now there's a lot of issues they do end up killing a lot of birds
They're not ideal and a lot of ways
Canary in the Wind Farm probably doesn't
SolarCity, getting fired is the canary in the Wind Farm
What's up
That's not bad
Thank you
Sorry
To the argument
He's making the argument as soon as Trump said Cole is back on the table
Russian gas
Gas prices
Did that happen
Wow I'm looking at a official graph
The price
Gasoline per liter
In Russia
Anil January 30th it was at 38
4 rubles
Per liter
38.4 that's right around when Trump was inaugurated
Would you like to know what it was on the 8th of May 27th
I sure would
39.29
Nope it was
It went
I don't know how
Where the more you have the less money
It has never gone down
Sent
Trump Sargon
The price of gas
Has just consistently gone up
Is nothing
True know nothing history
Do you know what the thing that's kind of interesting is that
Price of gas
Is trending or has trended downward send
Give or take
7:40
Suppose it's going down
And then OPAC
Is limiting their
In order to artificial
Keep it up possibly created
Like mid-2014 or so
Brett but
Cuz we're all going to die
Price of Russian gas has gone up
Plus it just made that up
In the same way that you said it's a good argument if you don't look for numbers
I mean the fact that
You know all the other good stuff though
Cities done
Sriracha
Is still there
Maybe they even
Maybe they'd be willing to take that
Trade-off
Yeah we'll give you some coal jobs in order for us to have
Who knows if possible
Sure I told you that I like without Rodger Stone in toe things kind of
Spiraled a little bit in the last two clips
She's made arguments that are based on any reality
I feel good
He's going to feel good
Because
This should be the day of Celebration
This guy has gone down
He was the FBI director was a compromise global
Liquor
You still gotta hit his greatest hits
Completely narratives
It gets so weird
Okay this is f***** up
I have seen people do for being totally enthusiastic about Trump
100 100
11 days in
Really been disillusioned with President Trump
Yeah
1 belt
Is that we were selling probably 500 Trump Pence
Sideways for that bad health care bill
To be honest
Really good Bellwether for
Whether or not his listeners
Are sticking on board with
Infowarsstore.com Trump Pence 2020 shirts
Retail for $20 1995 are on sale for 495
And have been pretty consistent
Canobie
Covering cost
So now
Baby cuz the bellwether
Is this a the dumbest thing you
Punchline for his acts from 10 years ago
Until I sell all the
Or whatever
Pretty crazy
Like in terms of quantum
What
10 grand
Yeah but everyday
Two and a half gram. Less than 200
Eliza cuts into your profit
I'm out of work you probably have to do to pimple that product
$2,500 a day if we were getting it
Yeah but the shipping Department
And makeup
Taking a bath
I mean for 2,500 though I feel like I would have no problem if it was you and
Recording the show for 3 hours every day and then the rest of the day
F****** folding shirts
We're also
What would you do
What up
Just sign knowledge Elder ghost
If we ever do get to a point where we can make this a job
I will buy
Supplement
And do a Supersize Me thing
I will do like a I'll go to a doctor and
Use myself as a guinea pig taking super male vitality
I don't know if I can handle you with much more hair
Is a function of the product I'll pluck
Turn into Cousin It
The shirts are a symbol of disillusioned
495 fresh air
Much less
Too bad
Thought
That is a really good bellwether
Well he does if people are super male vitality
That means they still buying
If they aren't buying those shirts
Maybe they're still on the the Trump bandwagon
But they do not want to be advertised
That's a fair point that's even though
The argument that Trump Pence 2020 shirts have their own life
They don't really
Hillary for Clinton Hillary for prison shirts do have their own life
They have their own thing
Because they just can't suck
Can let that go
He he he gets into this and then he's at the end there he's like
You know that Alterra bill that went sideways
Starts talking about Julian Assange
You shouldn't be prosecuted if it just goes on for a bit of like
His greatest hits
So the things he doesn't like about Trump goes three examples
It's something that I think you and I are going to be really offended by
And
We don't want to end up like that sucks
He's talking about Mexico and however
Everyone gets shot their man
Not great but not how like
So much violence
Drug wars
And stuff like that you do don't want to be like my old on
Listen
I thought you saw the Twitch in my eye
But because we have such a demand for jobs
That's the drug war for you
Stop it
Play Chicago
The only place in this hemisphere more dangerous than Mexico City
Not true
Chicago
Dot-com
I have two people who live in Chicago people are coming to Chicago then our leave
Also I don't know if there's a hemisphere shift
Within the United States
Hemispheres
It's right so you got
Mexico and 1/2
Chicago central hemisphere
That's your northern hemisphere
South America that's your Southern
Hemisphere
Then you got Australia which
Coincidentally
Is also
Part of the South American Hemet
You understand Linguistics Hemi means half anyway
The United States is all in the same hemisphere
It goes without saying that you don't want your National Security advisor
In terms
Murder rate
Yes
Chicago is eight
The United States
After St Louis
Murder rate
This is like / 100,000
For whatever it's not
Total number of murders play the numbers
Incredibly high and it is
59.3
Number two number three number for New Orleans Cleveland number 6
Newark
Number 7 Memphis then
So
Or New Jersey
Orange chicken
Chicago's are City how about you go fuc yourself
Especially
Come right with facts
Like if you want to say that the murder rate is
Too high
With great conversation most dangerous city outside of Mexico
Most dangerous city in Mexico
Those places are
So scary
Constant conflict between law enforcement the multiple cartel sitting around
How to get around at Elana Juarez
No
The f****** bodies
Hung from
Intercept like web Highway
I miss that when I was there
Jesus go f*** himself
But then he gets back to a topic he was touching on a little bit earlier
It's more thoughts about it
The bellwether
Sideways
They're also selling a
Boobies
Weather weather
Global corporate crony capitalism
Is a nightmare sister the trump supposing it
They also sell a sundial so far
But like new here
If you don't see the Trump is secretly doing great
I'm ready to see the truth
Your facts are there
Alex
Obviously
That's not what
I mean in all honesty if you are if you listen to this podcast
What you know Alex Jones is
Constantly
Always putting together a false nail
I think
Today what I'm
Is he is not
Lying
He is creating a
Alterna
Universe
It's an alternate universe has already existed
Well with all that globalist narrative universe
Yeah but I mean
We're talking
Parallel universe like
Futurama Style
Flip of the coin kind of situation
Because it is
Direct
It's Direct
This is true
So I'm going to say the Opera
Cross everything
Trump is being investigated
So I'm going to say that Hillary
What it should be
Trump is becoming an authoritarian
So I'm going to say
The Democrats are trying to become a
Authoritarian
That it is
Whole constant
You're wrong
Every single listener
I think so because
Beyond today I might as well get a tattoo of Hillary's face
The reason I think you're wrong is because the pain
Parallel universe theory
What are you saying
Is
It's fanciful
In Subway
He's still trying to steal people who live within this universe
I don't know if I'm making to find it
Distinction
What I say
Because like
Just because he's lying about what's going on
You might be right
There's a point that there's a point I want to make but I'm not sure it is
8tracks
It's not that it doesn't
Amtrak is I'm not sure how to articulate it and I'm not sure it's that much different than what you're saying
I think you're you're wrong when you say he's trying to convince people who still living
But it is
It is driving
People towards
It's
A priming people for the argument
This is
Sweet
This is not we're picking on one thing and were using it
I know but it just seems it just seems
Adjusting
Seems like he is completely divorced
Completely divorced from the reality we live in put any
Semblance of
Cuz you know what probably happened to that hour-long conversation with Rodger Stone
This is bit going down
Might as well ramp it up to eleven my sources tell me that were fun
Something like I mean there has to be some awareness bit like
You can't
Fire the director of the FBI MIT invest
Navigation and think nothing is
Going to happen
I think there is a 12
They were surprised by the backlash.
Who is Alex
Sure
Little smart is a little smart
Everybody in the GOP it
Every single human being
Who says I am a Republican
And I support Republican candidates
Is
Stupid
I agree
Does that mean everybody who says they support Democrats is smart
F*** no
But it's not
100%
We are not beholden to any party at my point being with the complete
Utterly different
I think he
He's priming people for
The
To have with somebody who's not
Oh yeah it is always
Like okay
And and this is what he's doing basically by creating this parallel
They say this
Yeah so you say instead of engaging with that
Me and the feeling Jordan Tyler Snodgrass little conversation
On the show
Was his expensive it was
This is teaching you to argue with
This is giving you lines to say
What about this
What about Mike
In order to divert from the main point
I would have known that but I fast forward every time
Replacement Jordans talk I just only listen to you what are numbers back that up
You're not on the show
Well it I've learned my lesson
That's not a hundred percent true but I just want to stroke your ego a little bit
Listen every time you're not on Russian gas prices
Can I quit the show
From this point forward
Through the rest of the clips we have
There's two pole
Alex Jones is
Fluctuating between
What time is it
And the other is
Not really
There is a tiny bit of overlap mostly rambling
Next clip that I'm going to
The play is about the globalist
It's about
Like
The power structure I think
But I have specifically
It like the dude WAV file
That I have your mp3
Is titled
Doesn't make sense
I forgot what was in the clip
Just like that and that applies fully remember what's in it
This is this is a mic down situation
Cuz I think we need to park
I want to let this clip play and then when we get back I really want it
If you have any idea what he's
Yeah yeah yeah like you're studying for a goddamn midterm
A lot done that's good
That's why I'm supporting this is so good
Republican leadership
Country Club
People
X-Men
To play ball
2030 yearsley to get into Congress
In the Senate
They are so scared to death
Mainstream media's Asic bilmar School static Stephen Colbert's really cool
Fox
To be on those shows playing along with all that
Rotting decay
Facade
50 years in this country
Pre-market
Like real competition
Bose system
Feudalism
So that's the clip
I saw you scribbling
I love
Look I know that it's about
Big picture that's about the globalist
But the way those thoughts connected does not mix
Okay
Call me good
Call me firing good
Goes to end
There's no
Reason why
No not given
No the only reason he's given so far is because he wasn't
Investigator
Hillary is weird
Right nevermind
My question retracted it has been asked because he's not on the team
I'm using some subjects
To be completely and utterly subservient to the government like most good
Absolutely
To treat our government as above the rule of law
The implied answer
So then we go to
Politicians are Country Club
Start spacing Republican
Brands them
Yes Man and Country Club people
Along with the Democrat the old the old guard in the same breath
Includes after the fact
He was just sitting on the Republicans than Democrats
Right
Maybe the Democrats are Country Club people
But there was a milk
Blue Bloods
They are they think being on Sienna and fox
Is good yeah they think Bill Maher's cool
Nobody
I think Bill Bardo
That's probably true
Maybe whoever does the programming
When that's actually embarrassed
And old media if there's a big gust of wind will collapse
Because old media is
Anti
Free market has a pronoun reference gets weird
Because he was talking about the the like
The media and
CNN and Bill Maher
And all this
Ernie says
Augusta wind will blow
Right when he says it
Again
Which Wich
Reframe what you're talkin about the it refers to what
Most previously referred to
Which would be the media
I believe it is a system
That is anti-American
That point I think of delineate
So the rest of it you could think he was just talkin about Colbert
Colbert
Technological
How else will they
Remain relevant
We need to be advanced
Button sorry
But that is an important part of the framework is it he's not being clear
Just about
But instead
Are participating
That is anti
Sure
Because their wives will make fun of them
And then that's that's basically it that's what he said
Like what can we do what is the point
I don't
I don't know
Trying I think the the overall ideas trying to get across
Use exegesis
Is that
Nobody's coming out by ship
They're all still going on CNN and fox
It's time to come on Infowars baby listen I got a new bra
Jesse James
She doesn't come on the show though
I got Ted Nugent
Right
Rodger Stone Mike cernovich
Ron Paul
See that that was a real mystery context
Anything out from before or after that makes it
Is that
These guys are going on those shows
Challenged
Where is it say where on
On his show
They would act
Nobody would be calling them a Russian agent
They would have nothing to
Until all that's why they're cowards that's why they're cowards
It's interesting because there's a high preponderance of people on his show that to have ties to Russia
Alexander is absolutely a contemporary of
On
That's a good point
If none of these people would be called Fresh aneja
Since they went on it
Jack Pacific
Not called the resignation on the show
Rodger Stone
Rodger Stone hopefully soon-to-be jail register
Hopefully soon-to-be hung from the neck in the streets
Because we start a revolution no no no no no no
Violently but because
Finally we reckon
Treason
It's something that are Pres
President shouldn't be allowed to commit
And so the only way
Tookie
Any president from committing treason
Never again
Is 2
Trump
In the f****** Street
On national TV
I want
Six-year-olds to watch an old man die
Jesus
F***** is trying to destroy the world
I don't want him to be hung though because then that butthole
It happens and it might look like a prolapsed anus if it gets hung up
Prolapse
Amos Mac
Phoebe
Treason
Literally in the Constitution
Literally
Because he's allowed because we're doing an Alex Jones podcast Alex Jones
Will not stop talking about how everyone's calling for the death of trump
That's not what we're doing
I want to be crystal clear about that
Lest we fall into a trap
Alex Jones is rhetorical bulshit calling for the rule of law to be
I don't know
At all
Applied
Yeah. You should at least get punched in the balls for the China trade
I think that you're right
Mostly
About the media
Being what he's talkin about a ton in that last
Yeah but I know that it's about the globalist
Because
We get to this next
Clip
And I
Title this clip
The Last Temptation Of Jones
Eli qe3 Romantics
This Crusade
B2B star or fail
They're never going to care about you but never going to like you can help them
You need to join us
Hope you feel better
Actually
Speech
Over Alfred
That's the speech again
Just join us
You want to work with you
So there's two more minutes of this clip lamp
Clear already I don't believe
No he's already talkingshit
I don't understand
What it is he thinks he means
I know it's
Exactly what he thinks
Okay
Sphinx
No you didn't think what he's saying
Is
The elite
The globalist have come to him
Repeatedly in the past
This dumb Infowars iida trying to wake people up
That's never going to work these dumb cattle
They're never going to go figure out our game
Public papers what we are going to do
Hey don't even know they don't care
They're stupid don't try and save them Alex
Don't do it
So they always come to Heaven they giving that speech and they're like
Just come on it's good for your family
Don't be a part of this
Alex
No baby
I'm not into it I'm too real
So he goes on
Eagles aren't even further but that is what do you think
100%
With
A 99% certainty
But if that conversation ever happened
It was someone f******
I'm almost certain that someone told him in the past
BuzzFeed article
It starts with a discussion of how we used to have a Public Access TV show and there was a guy
I can't remove the guys name now but
I think it might have been like space
Hitler
Just constantly call him it prank calling
He would just f*** with his TV show face Hitler
It's like I have to believe that early on Space Hitler I'll be outside
You might be in space Arjun
So are the boys from space Brazil
Entirely possible that in his early days and there was
His principles and his beliefs and
His backstory
Of his own
Making work coming together they're being
Being formed
I bet someone f***** with him
And pretended that they had
Deep information
Like that
Pretended they were deepthroat
Give you every
See I would say what what I would
Christian that with more likely there
Okay I don't want to give Rios true he probably agree
To it
And then the guy was like
Yeah that's realized it was such a good narrative device
Right
I can see that
Dirt bikes
Constantly try to coordinate absolutely refused
Here's here's what I would say
I would say
It is more likely
That he had
Some talks with
Fox News or one of those radio shows
They basic they gave him the
If we put you on a national platform
You have to
Two-tone some of this
Like just that
Hey if you start saying
And we stood for it
We're going to leave you out there on your own
And we're not going to allow this app
So that
To me is what he would interpret as
That exact
Scenario that's interesting
Completely reason
Yeah I possible
He is
Popular
And time there's something
With that kind of
Support structure
Some network will be like
Give this a shot let's talk to this guy
Let's set up a meeting
Let's see what's going on
Hurley going Fox News whenever they were turning themselves into the right
That they are they must have been looking at him salivating and they gave Michael Savage
The reason why he's been with Genesis
Communications
For so long is that they are basically just a supplement
And gold Hawking Network
Anime don't give a s***
F*** yeah whatever you want it is we're not responsible for whatever you say
Are you take full responsibility
Who was the last of the stuff
Alex Infowars
He says a lot more
About is Temptation
As it were
Punk Girls
But you really are
Really
He'll be part of this whole system
How to be a vampire
Culturally
And play along with a deception
No thank you
Polite
And now here we are
14 years after I refused the first vial
No thanks
We change the world together
Butterflies
We're turning the corner because we believe in humanity
We believe in Justice we believe in God
We don't believe evil
We don't use evil system shipping
Yes you do
Physical
Monetarily
Temporally
Yet
Literally means
Time
We don't use time travel
Buy into those evil systems that make us stronger
Physically
Like
Some sort of
We don't
Like
Santa temporarily
Chinese song about tempura
Temporarily
I cut it slightly the wrong part
That power
The one ring
Powers archetype people technology
Use systems of deception
Poisons the world and poisons you
Senor Sol
And it's slowly taking you over until one day you never wake up
And something else is running you
Now you've given over your psyche
You're so what I got put in your body
He's literally just Golem in
Liquor I bet you can't really go on that long of a
Tangent
Without somehow finding one of his Touchstone
That is a pop culture thing
Like you can't not reference a movie or a book
Or something like that
The metaphor is thin in his language
You know what is not
I mean we don't know these
People these globalist who had their lives ruined by the metaphorical rings
The world Alex maybe know a bunch more than us cuz he has met these people NES
Fault about them
Donald Trump
I want to tell you about them
It also is eventually going to get into state
I have been around billionaires Global sellouts the system
Robots they're just like crazy weird fumbling morons
Weird fumbling people
Hollywood's the worst model of control
Beautiful people
Hollywood didn't make them somebody Hollywood stole their greatness
Around
No one bought your script Alex Jones
It's 50/50
He just listen to Candle in the Wind
Which one of the two
Why would you okay
Was founded
The obvious things
Reason you would go after
You know
Hollywood
Is because that
The touchdown that you are listening base
This is like our values Hollywood
Stop the world exactly
The liberal Elite out-of-work actors what to feel and think
Options of MKUltra type
Stuff like all these people Hollywood urgent brain-controlled and sex slaves and s*** like
We should put together a list
We don't want to invite
Color of royalty
Alright this is done
In the world and built systems
Like Hollywood
Devil
You're so like a deal out of it
Devil doesn't give you any of this
I don't I don't I don't get what
First of all so funny
Total sense
No
You can make yourself Incubus
But the devil can't give you any of this
Irene
Why sell your soul
It's almost like the devil is
It is very much like that
Alex Jones like
He's legitimately
Maybe
4 steps away from atheism
He's two steps away from believing in Chris
Will eventually be like
You know
Birth crystals
Your hand
He's not sponsor away from me
Crystal shop
Hey Alex I'll give you a hundred bucks
Just f******
Tell him that you liked bezoars
Seems like I'm in I don't even know if that's a crystal
No it is actually something
It comes from the
Aaron Donald
Grows in there and then
It comes out
It heals diseases it's like a pants
That is
But so he was like a talking about
Deal with Satan but
But you can't sell your soul YouTube
How do you sell your soul
He already said all of these people have sold their sold and they are satanic and they
Because of that worship
If they get their power
Bingo
So where
Nothing nothing
Nothing is
Here's where that
Sort of dovetails into Alex Jones it's like
Espoused
Bargain
But you didn't
Because you can never know if you did
Legitimate
This
Highlights for me the idea that Alex Jones has no coherent philosophy
He has no intrinsic set of principles
In the same way that two episodes
We were talking about
Him in his Marathon
He legitimately said Trump was the Butt Boy
Of a bunch of different people
Military industrial complex
He wasn't saying that
You were saying
Well
It's gone
His Trump
I've been selling as well after he called him up but
3 days later
Trust in Trump has risen from the dead
Trump is a butt boy
Donald Trump it's implied we don't need to go through it
He said it
This crazy line with Trump
He's wavering
Like I don't even know exactly what he believes about Satan
Or demons
He just brings it up
Yeah there's no consistent through line between like
What is your cosmology about demon
What are they
Right
Cuz if he ever was nailed down on it
Putting believes in literal vampire
Well maybe not literal vampire spiritual vampires
Don't say they drink cuz the adrenochrome
Jesus
He does
He does believe
The I don't know
I don't either
Here is here is what I would say
Say if I was going
Foil down
Good luck
Is belief system
Good f****** luck it is
Whatever the
The f*** he
He feels like
Attending
You know what that's that's a conversation that we did have off are where it's
Only thing that the only thing you can't go back
Exactly what he believes about these very
But you never is specific about who globalist
He never actually sites documents
Riding the wave
I have told you on this
Episode
The specific place
Where I found a bunch of information
Cleancult
I've specifically told you
Where the document is
It backs up
My claim
President Obama
Vito the sale of a company
That was trying to sell microchips
Is
Blah blah blah blah white papers I read their books the books
To affect your no longer
Slippery
And I think
That he could not exist
Did not advise
Demons and that relates also to
That is negotiable
Supervisor
Sorry go ahead
This time for real
So
So my rebuttal on that
He does have
Through-line
Sure does have touched
Now
If I was going to
Well that's that's actually just what I was thinking
Like you know how most of the through lines of
You take the individual details away from it
Anti-semitism
Distrust of minorities
Anti-muslim
Cultural fears
Absolutely but then it all relates back to
The globalist
Like
Goes back to Aunt
But it's
And it with the Ghostbuster such a nebulous nonexistent
-4 stitches
You can describe any
Problem today
Gas went up
Global gas went down it's because Trump
Is fighting global
Like any number of different things that are
The genius thing
And some level
Nnr respect
We're kind of ham
Kind of locked into the fact that we have to
To fight against
A real person
Are you like it better you have to do work I like it better that way though because when
He says these things about let's say for example Hillary selling the rainy
I can
Look at him
No
I know that
You know what's interesting
If if we switch positions
I think it would be much more similar to The Alex Jones Show
Where I have just
Read like a whole bunch of s*** and I don't quite have it all locked into my brain
Lake Lanier
Like I would play an Alex Jones clip and I wouldn't research it all be like
I heard of The Washington Post that they that this was wrong
Yeah it's even worse
I would be the warmest
Infowars cast
Adjusting
Baby
Tell you what
Alex wants to talk more about the
Interfacing with the Devil
This whole system
Free phone calls
We'll just commit
2 spreading articles videos everyday to friends and family and neighbors into millions
10:00
Sponsored
20 slice of the enemies attacks
Flash little silver another 3 minutes
Narnia
You're talking about the devil
Give a hundred bucks to your local station
Give us
Blue otherwise
The devil's going to get you
Also I looked into it does have an affiliate in
In Chicago but its suburbs
So not
The actual broadcast barely reaches
So
I mean maybe you could
Could get a bad version
Alex Jones on the actual radio in Chicago
But the idea that he says that he has actually
I'm engaged
Some research
Difficult to do
Because
Yeah he's not lying
He doesn't
Have a list
Of his current affiliates
I looked into the code on the website
That's right
That's right I did
Genesis Communications
Network has a list of affiliate
Broadcast
And that's what we discussed on our fourth episode
Yes I looked into code on that website
What time is it been update
In the code lifetime
Really yeah
The number is actually off
Saving I've started to engage in a little bit of research going through the top radio markets
The actual radio station
Station has a website
And they have their schedules on
Kind of a complicated process of figuring out
The stations in each City
It takes forever
So I started the Chicago
Supposedly caters to
Chicago the third largest radio Market in the United States
Based out of the suburbs and fairly
Right
Is alive but I'm excited
Rural or bourbon
Suburban
Yeah but I'm excited too
Give you the results
That investigation
As it comes
Email address
The only thing I've done
This email address
Is I've signed up for the Infowars newsletter
Cuz I want to see if they sell my information
Getting spam
Is someone that's kind of interesting it's like 3 weeks
Since I signed up for it
I've gotten nothing
Except from Alex Jones
Relight the app
But
The first of this is really just a
The True Believer kind of
But the first thing that I got from Ally
Is
Automated message
Your Infowars news newsletters
Description
Ebook
Free
This is something that he does
Cell
There's something you can only get
If you're on the automatically
I know you're getting it
But if you sign up for the email list
You know what it's called
Keys to survival
I'll read you the description of it
Free PDF
One need only take a glance
The day is financial and political headlines
Historic events unfolding all around
Regardless of political affiliation
Question
But the futures of their friends and family as well
Infowars has reached out to numerous experts in the fields of Finance
Help and more to bring you
Beating for warriors
Exclusive information
Preparing for potential disaster
He immediately sends you a doomsday prep
Ebook
And I haven't I haven't yet
But I'm certain most of it has to do with selling his
Like his survival food
Oh yeah I'm positive
Okay but anyway
Gotye
How cool
Ironic
Was the blueprint
Like if you read it and you're like
This is good advice and then you start taking all of it and then
You survived
Because of that and I'm sitting over here like Alex Jones silly there's no reason
What does feel like the world is coming to an end
That flawed
Premise argument
Direction
Look look up on survival
Who said
If you want
To talk about how like
Maybe Alex is right
A+
Text clip
As evident
But you should shut your goddamn mouth
Cuz this
Is like I know that we've talked about chimeras
This is
Humanize
Is the fish pee
Kind of weirdo
Global technology
Rochester good enough to fool top engineers
It doesn't matter they don't have solar unconscious
Wired into billions of people's actions everyday
Build algorithms
Before you even know it
That is true
Panda free will
Totaled
The D evolution of man
It's saying no mothers and fathers family unit
No just take drugs and watch TV I just Bliss out
A lot of his life
Trans argue
Just because some people have different identities
It doesn't mean that mothers and fathers are bad
The only time that I've ever heard any concrete examples
Is
Times when there are like
People talking about divorce
Parents like single parent implying that
Someone has a dad
When they might not have a dad
You have a single mom like somebody
Inasmuch as
They have an absentee father
Right
If you want it is that is his argument
Kernel of something we can go from there
I guess but the idea of like
Deltrans identities and differing
Gender
Non-binary stuff
No mothers
No fathers no families
Write incredibly
Is he's not wrong
About
Vai
Shut up shut up
I'll tell you why it's not important because
Of the merciful
That is Cambridge analytica trying to do
Exactly what they're trying to do
Concussion
Absolutely
Talking about
Edgar that nullified they are f***** up
They are instead so Disco
Charge
Species Extinction
Very selfish motive
People on the planet are creating new species as fast as they can every few hours
Feeling the human race
Dick move
Species
Species of virus
Species of bacteria
Species of animal / plant
Sectoid
Flash silicon
Synthetic nanotech
Humanoids
Robots now boys and girls
Literally wouldn't
With roaches and then moves to cat literally what he's talking about is that
Russian spying stuff like they're trying to spy on the Russians by putting a microphone in a cat
It's not a robot cat
Robot cats
The sixties everybody does this not a robot
They've already know know they're developing new species every hour
New species of viruses bacteria
Animal / plant / insectoid
Flash taco
I don't know
Deep Earth crystals got2b
Got2b that I don't know if you remember this
Just Jordan
Hour ago or so in the Bronx
Open up the phone
Yes I do remember
But now he's about to
Okay
He's going to open up the phones and any
Minitab
Beth Ben Adam Harry
I thought that was one guy he doesn't
How to go to Robert Perry Jones broadcast
Cuz it lies with this we believe
We believe in free market we believe in open societies
He's really hitting the best card
You nailed it under your breath
Although
Time document
No
I think
It's incredibly frustrating
You hear someone lie enough without concert
You start to realize
Supposed to be
It doesn't matter if you believe it it's
Just the act of saying
Important
And that's really f***** up
I think
The meme I'm talking about Alex
Here's what here's what I would say
Because this is a conversation that I had
With a family member
When we were talking about
How do you know that
And I was like well because
There's all this research
Your review 90s
The Great
Experiments that are repeatable
How do you know they're not lying to
Well
Because that
How we establish
Experimenter repeatable
Not just that like
How do I become a giant
Conspiracy
You play that game with me
No I do
But here's how here's how I know
Because we
Phone
That's it
How do you how do you know they're not lying to you
Because every time you make a f******
Phone call
The call is routed
2 West Saddle
The satellite has to account for the fact that it's
Traveling
So that mean
That because of that time dilation
We know for a fact that he does equal a
We know the theory of relativity is
Because it has to account for that
Otherwise it won't work
You're you're the clock on your phone because it is right
Means that Einstein
So whether or not
You want to pull this research bulshit
Here's how you know things are true Jordan because
They work
If you if you don't believe in climate change
Then get rid of your phone because B
Because it doesn't work for you I really bad news
You know how damn you know how you've never been walking around and been like who turns the math off
I was trying to tip
20% neurologist kept writing with 404 not found that has happened when I've been drunk
Someone did turn the map off the other night when we were out of the whip over typically crazy
Oh this is the bad news
This out
Entirely but about
35 minutes of the show Alex
Interview the climate
Tonight
God
Al Gore
What factors climate deniers what else do you want me to be angry about Dan
That's why I cut it. I don't want you just blowing a gasket
Has a new documentary
A sequel to
And Alex's
Furious about it
The energies of climate
About it
Not worth breaking
Down
Cuz it's specially cuz outside of this
This narrative it's outside of the
Rambling globalist
Other than again
Other than those bright
Look at these Keys over here I'm Jacqueline these caves
Don't pay attention
To our corrupt
Felony committed president
It's exactly the same reason that on the day of the shooting in Charleston
We may never recover this episode I'm not entirely sure but I just listen to it
Good day
Of that shooting
Alex Jones
I would say an hour of the show
Interviewing a lady
Coup
Captain coats
In her house
Kansas City Council
You cannot keep your house
Guns and ghosts in my house and I don't need a background check
Her argument was
Because of its back to me when she was very young
And she couldn't make breast milk
And she didn't trust
Formula
So she needed goat
In order to make the milk cuz buying goat milk
The sources that they come from
It's all night
I'm on climate change side note on climate change aside I want the Earth
To wipe us out this is the day to a black church
And shot a bunch of people
I don't know why you would need to cover that also keep in mind
It's
The day after
I forgot about this Confluence of the
That's the day after Trump announced his candidacy
Cheese's
F****** Christ Within
That 24-hours expensive
Who has a website
I'm Pro goat.
Jordan
You asked
Why is he
You spending
This Ray Vaughan hits his
Call me
Why is he spending an hour of it
Rambling about globalist and saying I've been tempted they make
Do with
Toby Lee fired
You don't have any
Right
And I'll be honest the interview with the climate denier
If you take the climate denial out of it
What's a spirited interview
The guy
Was kind of fun
He's wrong about everything
That's more than can be said for so many other people that everyone except Rappaport
Shout out to everybody who has tweeted that out of
So we have one more question
From the rapper floor to the rapper floor
Is no longer we're policy walk
It's Rappaport still live there's no doubt about it
Alright
Donate
Ceremonious
Rapoport is going to be about
If not what
Oh that's right we have perhaps
Establish that he is Gandalf
You died
If you
He is the pic
I can't tell if the picture is a young version of him
I don't know
But
Trapped
He died
Yes
I will
F******
Burien
If I'm not asked to give a speech
If I'm not here, Mario
There is nobody in the united goddamn States of America
That cares about him in the same way would I do
Snow White
If
I think it's
Be honest
Not
As a
Perfect shrine
To what Rapport means to all of
That's the greatest conflict of my life is like is a tribute to him hanging up that picture finally once he's gone
Or or spear tackling anybody who tries to put it up
Like
Lake on constant vigil the rest of my life
Is standing in a three-point stance
Yeah
I dare you
Google Play version
So f*** all this noise Rappaport will die and I won't speak it
Funeral
And this one
Is where
I know
We didn't make
It's clear but we drank a bottle of wine
Vineyard
It's only appropriate because
This is kind of an ironic episode
Pretty much Alex Jones in his attempt
Tar and feather,
Make light of the Russia investigation
Is really showing his cars but he has no facts
On his side he only has
Insinuation
Lies
Fake stories
All his ideas nothing
In the back
He's failing in his depends
His denials
He is actually directly pointing to why they're being vested
Exactly
They shouldn't
Investigating Hillary for this
Instead they're investigating Trump
So it's always like
Here is what they should be doing and it
It's the same thing they should be doing
Here it's never is always a
Complete parallel
It's never like
Also I love the fact I love the fact that there are no new Boogeyman for
There's only sorrow there's only there's only Hillary
But that's
That's Brazil
So
Their constant fight
Distracting
From the fact that
They can act
Was really you know other than turning this into a
Authoritarian government
That has no respect for the rule of law
Stanley trying to flatter than ever
Is
Directly compromised by Russia
Absolutely cowardly and incapable
Protect
F******
Country from the facts
That all of this s*** is destroying
Christine America
All because
This is all but not Alex Alex
Destroyed
Democracy
So we can get a 20% lower marginal tax
You're talking about the real world
Alright
His motivations are
Isn't
That's what's crazy
Like
I need to leave the real world at the door
The tax cut motivation
Understand Alex's globalist narrative
Alex's globalist
As best I can tell it's bologna
But let's get back to the center
The irony
Is what we've already laid out
But I wanted to introduce a
The further irony
And this clip
Alex Jones
Loses
A little bit
Frases
Overt racism
Overt hatred
Really shows that
His side has nothing
This is what they have
Right here
This is it
This is at this clip
Is
Ferguson Austin already
Yeah
If Ferguson is your first city where
Fox what there's a reason
Hold on
Bakersfield everywhere
And there just are going
Buses of offloaded college kids bunch of white ones getting off saying the halls of Dead Cops
So they they all the stories that have come out about busing in protesters and stuff like that have all been debunked
Audience
Because of that
In terms of pay protesters
People getting off buses
Stuff like that are all are all
But then he refuses to engage with the idea that the reason
That these black lives matter
Even the further black nationalist groups that are a little bit further
On that side
Yakub black lives matter 5%
Include white people
I would definitely
The reason
Cops about
At least
Is the cops
Keep killing
Black people
With no repercussions
They kill white people as well
Absolutely is true but it seems
Definitely
If you look at the statistics they kill
Proportionate
Never Gitana
So when group
Such as black lives matter and nationalistic
Talk about killing cops
It's not so much they just want to kill cop
It's a expression
Frustration
That they seem a of their community
Get choked out
Alma Street
For selling loose cigarettes
And no one can
Totally
Utterly justifiable
Yeah it is it total
Frustration with
I know it's a Justified
They aren't killing
They are
Saying
F*** these cops
Like yours no one wants to kill cop
Here's the thing that drives me
Do you know what they want
Not to be killed by cops
Justice
If you because here's the here's the real deal
If you just
Prosecuted
These cops
And made sure because isn't that the whole point of all of these punish
The whole point
Is the actors
So if you see Justice being a
Applied
Equally then you can say
This is a deterrent
Futurecop
Killing black much like you're hanging a president it is not it is it is a punishment but it
It is really just
Don't
Do this because there is going to be
I would say further it's a reason to
Does the people aren't
Yeah and there's nothing really
What I understand
Beartooth
Sometimes
A cop
Makes
A bad kill
This does happen
You know you're on a bus
Or something like that someone jumps out in front of you
You kill somebody
It happens
And the reason
That people are mad
Police puppies
Or not those in
They are
Use
Unarmed youth
That are killed
Chill
Sure
No
Cleveland
There are children there are unarmed children
Women there was that incident
Michael Brown
I can't I can't even remember the guys name cuz there's too many of them
Was killed in his car with his girlfriend
How many
It's come to a boiling point where it's
Think about this
If you think about the 8th people weren't pissed off and saying
F*** the police
Read it would be insane
Think about how
Angry we are right
Flouting the rule of law
Now imagine
Every single member of your
The entire it
Distance of your
Family as far back
You can remember them being
In America
Being subject
To that same level of ingest
And
Worse and look at how angry we are now
And this is
Really
The first time in my life where I've had to look at the government
And say these people are affecting
Personal
And destroying mate
As opposed to Mayans
Higher life
Printed on my back
Pathetical
Trying to take my health insurance away they're trying to figure out
Yeah that's true
Still not really expecting
And I'm not
I'm not being
I am not being detained at the airport
I am not
Minecraft
None of these things are having nobody's rating my house
Peoria
And all of this is happening
Two other people
Alex Jones his inability
Deal with the abstract
To deal with
The reality of
Give the world
Is really embarrassing
Like the idea that he is
Is just
Cotton dry making it like
These people walking around they want to kill cops
Liberals bottle lights
I don't know how to put it exactly but I would say it's an embarrassing lack of nuance
It is
Absolutely
Are they completely
For other human
Let's get back to this
We're in the middle of the clip I forgot
This clip is
It gets way worse
Let's let's
People were murdered in the armed forces
You start Turnpike
Call you slave Douglas country dumbasses
You piece of f****** s***
That's so dog whistle
Goddamn
F****** garbage
It's impossible to hear that and not here
Essentially
Behind Patriot
The earliest
Texas country in the earlier but we got off
He says their butt
He specifically points which is there busing in
Traitors to the race absolutely
Hundred percent
Exactly what it means
They're busting in white so glad you picked up on my absolute
This is the eternal battle with Alex Jones is like
I know he feels that
But I don't know how aware he is that he feels
Cuz you wouldn't say those things that you did
Fuel them
Right now it's eating him
That is what he's expressing
But it's not clear to me
That he is like
Consciously being like
I'm going to
Right I don't know if that's
Well that's good, that's a basic
That idea of there busing in white people
Is something that they're putting out visually if not
I think they're smarter about it they don't
Call out the white part of it
Cuz I think I think maybe they're segment producer
Elysee try not to
Definitely fine
Plenty of
Racist dog whistle
No doubt No Doubt
Nono Intuit
No that is
That is totally true
It would
Without the rest
The
The idea that like
We Patriots built this
You said it over it
Built
Look
Pro reparation
100%
I don't know what it looks like
But yeah
Give black people all the money
Michelle and then let's go from there
All right that's why
I think we need some more nuanced what's our national
Budget like to some trillion dollars
I don't know give it all today
Listen
So here's here's my I don't like
Sort of way to transition
Here's what I will
Here's what else
As a as a road
And this is something that I find after
Aftershows all the
Is that old white dudes
Will come out to me
Hey you were really funny
Let me tell you a joke
And then they'll tell me this races
This joke
Because
They think
It's a team
Yeah they think the white racism
They don't think
Illicitly that they're being
Yeah yeah
Assume
I'd like
Just without even without
Consciously thinking about it they're just like
Oh you're right you're on my team
I wouldn't say this to my black
Friends cuz we're on the same
Psy
To me what that
Kind of dog whistle eracism is
He doesn't
Even think about it
It's just
It's just they're just there it's just a suit
Laughing for the wrong reasons
So many of my
If you if you can and you can hear it too
Like when you tell a joke that you you know is meant to
Lamp and isn't meant to make peace
Feel bad for axle
Believing this
And you get those that
Type of laugh in the wrong way or like
Part of the problem
We got to get to the vet
Way too far into this
I mean I have to say it
You keep running your mouth your going to run it right in the Six Feet Under
Politically
You should push it much longer
From your actions
You're going to get knocked upside your head
Until you find out
She had got
Get the horse
There's no pleasure in killing
Just letting God f****** name is happening
Bitching
You want that rite of passage
You want to piss
On your battery
Criminal energy
I know
Keep pushing
Because
Watch
You passed the demarcation line once you gone past the point of return
Once you hit the Event Horizon
Just remember
You asked for it
If you start a war
It's one that we will finish make no mistake dumbasses
Let's go ahead and talk to Adam in New York on the air
Call
Terrifying
It's it sympathy
But it's terrifying
I took my headphones
YouTube
You got yours
Moment there
I can't breathe I really can't take a step back
Allow you to breathe
Please
That's a desk
Like
Yeah
That's enough
Heath
No I know it ain't into him
Acting like that
I mean first of all
Tons
Hunt
Of racism
What is the same antonym
But at the same time
Goes back to the beginning
He shook
Yeah he would not be saying these sorts of things
If it wasn't coming from places
Yeah he knows he's a cornered rat
Yeah that's what the lawsuits stuff is catching up to him and he's realizing
Is firing of Comey
Is going to backfire real hard
But you know like
Is whole thing is
I started this morning
Tuesday
Wednesday
I started Wednesday
Really
I know terrible mood about
The firing of Kalma
At 10 a.m.
Finally was like
I support this
Decision
It was
It was the most
Depressing it was like
It was like waking up
And somebody saying
Oh by the way democracy
Percy is over
I'm still worried about that
Hearing this episode
Made me feel a lot better
Because
I don't think
This
Exudes
I don't think
You're right into me
When your enemy
Is pathetically spouting
Hatred
And fear
Gloating
About the idea that one of his enemies
Has gone down
That was not most of the show
I don't think you did any glow.
Other
Yeah other than thing called me is weird
And it's good that he got fired compromised
But even that wasn't globulin that was
Global
When I listen to this
Globalizing
It's going to be shity but
You know some
Something that we don't
And I think he knows is that a lot of
Big trouble
We'll see
It's kind of unfortunate
The show might be in trouble
Ears ears
The thing
Restart Explorer periods of his life
But the rats leave the ship
Like you're absolutely right they're going to Rebel media
Yeah they're going
But we don't have to immediately start covering them we can just go back to
Like the good old days
May 11th
Right we could go back
May 11th 2013
And do the show everyday
We could just do that
Let's Retreat inside our own reality
I'm sorry I'm for that I'm not against it so listen
If I could
The guy just did that
American people
I would say
Jones is
Incredibly afraid right now
And it's very sad
He's lashing out
That's pretty funny
I'm sad that
He feels like he needs
T-shirt sales up
I would say razor
It's a tiny bit if you're charging 60 bucks for a bottle of some of your pills
8 bucks for 95
At least
You're going to get more out of
Selling them at
For a penny in for a
Got your dumbass list
Exact
Exact just as a businessman what are you f******
Which supposedly
Currently snow not just that
He is a good business
Since he's turned his
Lyzette
Bulshit variety hour into
Meteor
Borderline
The odds are that someone behind the scenes
Did it for 24 years
Before that that's without doing
Extra
Guys has been super fun
Scary right now but please
Take some
Solace in knowing that Alex's
More afraid
Avenue r
Just like the Trump Pence 2020 shirts are a bellwether
To whether or not his listeners
Are willing to publicly support Trump
The fact that
Alex Jones is this afraid
Isabel Weather
For this kind of alright
Backlash
That is going to have
It's like we are
Going to see a
Significant
Newtonia
For every for every action
Action there is an equal and opposite
Is that reaction no classified
Information we can't
Be fully certain
Rodger Stone does not have to have access
To confidential information
To know what he
He has done
He doesn't have to have sources to know
The f****** transgression
Keys made
He could be
Expressing some of that
Alex
Yeah that could be replaced
For some of his fear
Yeah
If you would like to
To follow us on Twitter it is
Knowledge
Underscore fight
Please
No
But no I will say this to not slide my DM
Jakari Jackson send us an email at gmail.com we want to get into it
I will say though is f*** everybody else
I want
RAB do
To go on iTunes
Look up knowledge fight
And subscribe to our
And give us a one-star review
To the pasta
Discuss
Specific
$10
Oh no
Real bad one
Still are
Wonderful
Supportive
Polly policy wonk list
My best friend exactly what I
Well here's the deal
Are you off are you guys must have been a lot of places
It's been a lot of fun
Guides for listening
Means the world to us
Put us in
Partisan message
Message boards if you listen to other women
Recommend
People who listen to those podcast to
Tell your tell your friends
Let's let's let's f***
I can do that work
People
Information War I can't use the exact same words
But he's right
We are in an information war that is true we have
Given some information here
Information
Absolutely
I'm sick of I'm sick of seeing all of these
Fox News lies just
Bread with
No
I'm more sick of seeing people tweeting s*** about Alex
That is not
I like
Covered this is already done
Granted
How f****** annoying is it to get through
3 hours
Hey we're entertaining give us
This is
Rapoport
Alexandra Thurston color