Damn important I'm sweating
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
MoneyGram
College fight
Nike.com
Everybody want to acknowledge my time dance around technology Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex
Jordan Jordan Jordan
How do you feel about steroids in baseball do you think they should be in the Hall of Fame
I don't know I don't know really have a strong position on that I think I don't like people using steroid
Frozen competition but I also have no
I like I don't know how to root again
Not really I think it's up to the people who are in charge of the the hall today or or the ml
I'll be your whatever if they want to allow people to juice Shack
Then go for
Bad end up with people like
Yeah yeah you'd end up with a lot of people are really severely harmed by that. Not a good thing to do
Are you going to let him in the hall or not
That's up to you guys
Are you paying attention already and I don't know anything
Oh that's right well it's continuing on his way there right now gotten worse
Colin Firth
Series to be taken away is Rob Manfred the
Commissioner is
Calling the trophy
Which has his
Name on it
Little piece of metal
These it bad
Yeah that that does sound pretty pretty shity I don't really have any strong feelings about that
I'm torn because like Mike's or chaotic side is like let him cheat
Fox Sports leadership
If you're crafty enough to get away with cheating go for it
But then the other part of me knows that's no way for like it sets a bad precedent
Like the cycle
Books with motors on their bike
Thanks for the Tour de France that would probably be
That does have very serious effect on their the purity of the turf as they say
So yeah I don't know I think if it were up to me if I were in
Charge
That's a good question
I would not be alone allowed
But I will never be in that position where I'll have any impact on that
Don't really have a strong
Cut to the world being Stranger than 30 years and you're the commission
Nirvana
That's insane
I could see it happening
Give me a possible series of events that would lead to reply
On LinkedIn or
Monster.com
I don't know much about this stuff but Jordan I do know a lot about alley
Alex Jones
So today during what I thought we would do here on this this here Wednesday episode is
I think that our last episode was a little too much
Murder murder murder a lot of Alex calling for
The Cambridge professor
You killed herself
He needs to go on timeout pre-emptive true-crime
True Crime that happened yeah
Present-day has so much stuff going on in ad that you feel
Really felt like you need to keep up with what Alex is doing and I still do believe that
I need to put them in time out
Please so we needed to take we didn't take it
Excursion off
Do something completely different and you know it could have been you know could have been a Bill Cooper episode
Feel like that's too close
Waiting for you to be like a John Wayne Gacy was on Bill Cooper
Let's talk about that no no no
That seems to close so I even go far afield of that
And so I've got some
Something fun
I think good to go over moments
To sign up and recording show
The first Abby thank you so much and I'll probably walk
Thank you John
Heather thank you so much and I'll probably walk
I'm a policy wonk
Evocative
Thank you so much you are now probably walk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much even
How
Thank you so much
Juvenile pollywog
Just how one
I'm in finally likes it thank you took of people donated on an elevated level and appreciate that very much so John with no h
John P
You are now a technocrat and Jeffery
Thank you so much
You and I would like
Democrat
Heroin
Is freakishly large
Thank you so much John p.m. take as much ever age
Figurative hell I forgot to say thank you
If you're out there listening
These gents do I you do that by going to a website knowledge buy.com there's a button
Does for children
Thank you it would be lovely
So Jordan
We were young
Well you know that's
When we restart the podcast in January of 2017
And then a little ways down the road
We started doing Project Camelot ever
Episodes because I wanted to tell you about the wonderful world of wacky space
World for a Hoosier.
It has become less bar
As we learn more things about
The sorts of people that hang around it get interviewed by Kerry Cassidy and
Some of the opinions that carry May herself hold and
Cameron juice it's really weird
Maybe not hate
But have weird feelings about
It became less vaunted it's just this
Become a thing where I want to do more space weirdo episodes in Project Camelot but also it really
Only makes sense really when Mark Richards
Who is a guy who's the murderer
You guys a space captain
It's a living spaceship Minerva flies around with and Raptors will kill you for Chaka
Occasionally
Brought up once and then disappear
So I was thinking about it and like
When we started this it was
In 2017 also is when we first had our Project Camelot think
And it was not a mark Richards episode that was our second
Episode first one was about Randy Cramer
Who is a super-soldier allegedly
Who I
That's I will regenerate you and
And what have you and I started
Batteries like
Why did we do that
You couldn't have just been that I thought something was
Weird about space and I wanted to tell you about it even though you know there is
Some element
What was it what was Randy Cramer in
Specific
Well
Here here's what I what I want to tell you
I remembered
That's the reason
That we did that episode in the first place
Was that Alex Jones
Had an interview with a guy named Robert David Steele
Who would come on his show
And said the kids are being kidnapped and taken to Mars base
True because the severe backlash for Alex was everyone being like you think there's bars bases
So here is that clip from Howard Stern Show back in 2017 where Robert David Steele
And was talking about how kids are being kidnapped
And take him to space
Why I agree with that and let me just point out
Don't be just point out that pedophilia does not stop
Sodomising
It goes straight into
Terrorizing them to Adrenalize their blood
And then murdering the
It also includes
Murdering them
So that they can have their
Bone marrow
Harvested as well as body part
Pedophilia is Monday original
Growth hormone
Yes
Yes it's an anti-aging singing
And this may strike your listeners is way out but we actually believe that there is a colony
On Mars
It is populated by
Play children who were kidnapped
Incentive
Space on a 20-year Rye
Damaris they have no alternative but to be slaves on the Mars colony
All kinds right
Engineers
Said that you have no idea there's so much stuff going on but then it goes off into all that
I mean yeah that's the media jumps on but I do this
We see a bunch of
Looks like
Close I don't want us looking into what's happening
Everytime I'm off
Alex you're one of the most original guys on the air and end
You asked what
I think you should be the truth channel in America
So
A real lack of any kind of like
In a pushing back or anything out and I don't
These theories go into this sort of thing but I hate man everything secret and
Response was to
Robert David Steele saying the kids are being kidnapped and taken to Mars bases
Was I
Maybe yeah
It wasn't like show your work
So Alex deserves all of the criticism that he got for that that is what precipitated us to go down the road
Project Camelot to begin with
Now
Recently
Carrie got interviewed by Robert David Steele
Oh no it's in the last week or two I believe he
And so I decided why not
If we
Have this lack of joy and going through these Project Camelot episodes
Went to see if we could recapture some of the Magic by going back to the beginning let's flip it around
To move forward you our room back
Start at the beginning
So anyway
Steele has his own YouTube channel that he's putting up videos on and spoiler alert the interview that he did after this one
The most recent interview I when I just checked was with the
Jim Fetzer okay hey
He has some pretty good ability to pick out the gas
We can't all be
So I wanted to go over this and there's going to be another
Stuff that might be a little bit but there's a couple things in here that I found to be like
This is what I'm looking for
To that as we go along but
Robert David Steele opens this up
Buy glowing in
Kerry Cassidy
Several years ago
I started reading
Paranormal
Nonfiction
Domain
And I also started research
Online
Project Camelot immediately popped
As one of the top websites in
The world
And I remember getting a
With you when I remember us having
Conversation
Overtime
Tremendously impressed
Bye-bye what
You're trying to communicate
So please tell us a little bit about
How you got started very very brief
And then talk about
Some of your classes
Cerebellum
Some of the classics
People have introduced mendella with less blowing
I bet Robert
This guy's a communist
God Classics like Mark Richards
13 or so probably 11.
80-page being racist alien classics
The top five
Guy with telescope
Classics
So anyway. Get to talkin about some of the big hit
From the past and you know
That's about 2
But a couple of them we were very lucky
In other words
We not only were approached
Buy top
Of that nature
But we also
Went seeking
The very top
People and
For some reason we were able to
At 3 to them
Quickly and easily
And in the first year we must
Just talked to Summer
The best
Did ever
On this topic
Or
People who said that they were the back
The sources on this topic
It's kind of indistinguishable at a certain point
Do you got at some point you got to give people your
You got to open yourself up
Too trusting
I agree with you in theory but this isn't going to be the time
So weird
Doesn't specific
Sands at one of them is a name that we haven't talked about but actually it somewhere that a fairly interesting
Alberta backstory
We've got a
A very long Sigma
Segmented
With myself
My former part
Annabelle Ryan
And David Wilcock all interviewing one
Eye doctor
Pete Peterson
Lewiston Spa
Castaway
Got a year ago
But he was a
Certify.
Dr. Strangelove
Evil secrets
This program
Instrumental
Also involved
Creation of what
Call Super
So those are few
Captain Mark Richard
Later
AR
Camelot
Rebut
He's also one of the
Sure is
He's a doctor strange so doctor Peters terms
Call someone a doctor
Pete Peterson is a bit of an old-school name in the Paranormal
Conspiracy type worlds
Super old school
We were in 2029
A ways back
Project Camelot interviews like 2009 or something
I'm going to call that old school
Maybe not 1950s
1970s alien guy but
Anyway
He's made a whole ton of claims over the course of his career a bit of it having to do with his alleged former employment
When he was reverse engineering alien technology
Picture
Interesting Lee
I was looking into it a little bit and I was able to find a message board
Threat from September 2017 on Project
Avalon
Which is website
The Carey's former partner Bill Ryan
I thought you've been running
Since he made a split with Kamala
Okay so they just now there's a
Just to different project
Project Avalon prior to that too but it's like his rhetoric
Cuz I don't know of a f***
Anton about Bill Ryan
I tried to watch some of the interviews that he does
I find them
Incredibly boring
Like most
This stuff is quite honestly
But there are few things that make me think like alright this guy is not great but at least
He's not
The worst he doesn't believe the MARC rich
Good stuff good
And I found I found this thread
And it shows a little bit of character at least
So here's the first line that sticks out to me in this threat
Miss post
Quote there's strong reason to believe that Peterson was lying knowingly
Or confabulated when he told David Wilcock
About the presence of armed police have his belongings including his truck were being seized
And much of it was being bulldozed into a pit
So as it turns out Jordan
This guy's house
Peterson's house is being foreclosed on right and that story ended up getting told as a secret government.
Attack on him for spilling truths
This or something
In reality it appears that he was basically a hoarder
Hey when his house ended up there getting taken care of they ended up finding three dead cats inside and
Just like a complete
Chaos toxic environment
Government bulldoze in order
With armed guards
Trying to keep P Peterson away from his house living in that house at the time
It's all very complicated and why
Of course
That mean post that I'm Rios reason to prolong this message board it was written by Bill Ryan
It's not just some user on the on the board saying that it's Carey's former partner
He goes on to say quote
Close examination of Peterson's testimony causes me personally to suspect
There's a high probability that some of the information he presented
In the 2009 Project Camelot interview was inaccurate exaggerated or invent
I I I do not anymore believe he was a reliable witness then
And certainly not now
Put simply this post is basically Bill Ryan saying that their interview with this guy was bulshit
He says quote
We did Nazi documentation his DD-214 any devices which he had or had made
Never saw his laboratory and never even visited his house at the time
We did and this is
In capital capital letters
No due diligence
I saw that going to different what
There's even reason to question his educational credentials
Apparently some folks who looked into the college the Peterson claimed to have a degree from
Found it it's a degree mail that likely wasn't even in existence of the time when he was supposed
Stupid in School he didn't even get his fake degree
It's unclear I don't know
I'm taking I'm taking a little bit of this Ray have to work investigation that these people on the Mets
Supportive.
Cuz I don't really
Carol at much
It speaks volumes that bill Ryan made a follow-up post
After a bunch people had shown even more reason to doubt Pete Peterson
Story and Bill said quote I'm very close to making a public statement of apology the Project Camelot did not do
Any due diligence at the time
And that at least some of what Peterson shared with us
May have been fixed
As each day passes
It looks more and more to be the case
Man
I don't like how you need each
Which day passing I realized you didn't need the days
You could have just
Maybe an hour
Babies and maybe an hours would it take
Suffice it to say that this was a situation where it appears the
Peterson was not a mentally well person
Who was elevated to use to validate space weirdo theories based on things he was just
Making up which seems like a pattern
With these people
Seems like there's a lot of these folks that we end up running into
Who took advantage of a guy who had mental issues in order to support their own
Narratives and continue their own grips
It seems like that is a very high possibility out of character
As it turns out Peterson's main booster was David Wilcock
Who's a top to your face weirdo conman who believes himself to be The Reincarnation of Edgar Cayce
And it's just he's too prolific of a dude to get into as a side note on the side
Episode about David Wilcock but like he's so prolifically
Like you've done so much there's so many speeches to like
Try and figure out
When should we cover
And he's like Buckshot it's all over
So much do it that I would have such a hard time sitting down
I like figuring out alright
Here's what's important
I imagine he'll only take me about an hour to disbelieve any
Very much seems to me you from what I've been able to suss out
It seems like David Wilcock was using Peterson
In an article that I found on a website called bended reality really reinforces
This feeling
This article is from December 21st 2019 which is a little bit after
After Peterson had died
Apparently after Pete passed away David Wilcox
Didn't interview where he was claiming that Peter given a deathbed can
Confession we was getting ready to come forward about quote
He's experiences visiting 6265 different off-planet location
Among with other Sensational Tales so close to
So close so close
I want to point out here is like
Some of these space weirdos
I like some of it
Fun
And Dom
But some of these people are really f******
Can Shady
No profit off you as long as you're useful to the grifter
Their industry but then would you die
He'll try to profit off you what are you going to stop
Trying to get a profit off the Golden Goose
It just really bums me out
Are fitbit's a real bomb
Is it Golden Goose guys you just
Sell tickets to see the dead goose
So Carrie has this interview that they did with Pete Peterson I was like this is a grand thing that we did and then her other another
Mike Richards
Your little is not great
So
Robert David Steele
Gets down to talking about like
What the
Topics he wants to
The cover are
There are four quick
Things I want to ask you about the
The whole human
Trafficking
Thing
The basin
Yeah on Mars and Elsa
I swear
The kinds of
Spaceships
Had for the
3 years I think
The presidency
Esports
Is act
Leah way of
Justify
Legitimizing
A force that is always
With h
Approval
Absolutely
Spell did not lose to
One trillion dollars
It was spent
Space force
An underground base
Isn't that I want to end up by asking
Super-soul
So let's take these
Is one at a time
Very brief
The Carrie cast
City understand
I want to give Robert David Steele a tiny bit of kudos
And that is what you get in terms of the interview styles that I end up seeing he's all business
These attempts
You'll see I don't know if you'll be able to tell
Just because these are
Clip that's what it's like listening to the whole interview
But he does try and stay on Focus
Subway guy
I find novel
Yeah I can't remember the last time is you going to stick to these four tops
Okay see you now this is wild because Alex usually will give you a list
Topix I'll never touch
Yeah okay here are the bullet point
Yeah yeah
It's faint praise though cuz I also think he's
A little bit
You know how do you know it's fake praise to say that Donald Trump could write
A hamburger essay Prince
Center he couldn't
Hollywood Buffet
He's praised if he could
The thing that I find
It was like okay so these four topics are going to be out there with those are all like right where Carrie can hit a Dinger out of car
Yeah but like
When you have like okay I think the
The Trump is making the space force in order to legitimize the secret
Space Program
I mean that is one possibility another possibility is
He wants
Space wars
A great bee behavior
So we're doing something completely loony
And someone legitimizing the secret space program
Very similar external appearance
It's hard to parse whenever all things are possible I guess
Certainly chaotic evil can manifest in many different
That's why you have to take things with
External context
Any issues like that I Can't Tell You Why Trump is doing that I have no idea
But if they're going to make that are
Then I will rely on other things
Things that are said
In order to
To help me do so whether or not I should trust what they're saying should be listening to what is unsaid
So they're talking about aliens abducting people
Right from Earth
So much happier to be talked about absolutely need a break from Dallas
So they're talking about the you know
I'm not here to be mister
Squaresville and say there's no one gets abducted by aliens
I do think the scale
That they're talking about you paying attention dude like
I think what Carrie is egg is a possum
What's Yonder
Degree to which he
Traded as
A food source and as a
Chemical High
The degree
We are is
It is is very high
I already talking to
Percentage of
Humans that are
Taking a planet
Had excetera
I don't know
Year what
Is it in that rain
It's it's
I would say it's around
Percent it could be higher than that
One-in-five
As we speak
They are specifically talking about a food source
Are you I would doubt it yeah that's fair I can get high off their blood I don't think they're going to be
Hey you just you know you do five years as a hallucinogenic BloodSource and will bring it back ever
Everything's fine everybody goes about to visit
It's not like you're abroad whatever you just a back rub with stories
The time in London look to your left
Look to your right in front of you and back
One of the five of you will be abducted before the end of this class one of you will be food
Fat
I would it really does seem high
You know Robert David Steele saying like there's eight million people that go missing like
20% of the world
I'm not entirely sure cuz it would
If it was 20% of those people
Probably not on the census or like they're not
Population of the Earth
We don't even know how many people there are
Right
I should be 20% more
Yeah yeah
This
Tumi seeb
And this indicates either like it just a inability to like
Estimate
Or she actually believes like there's a billion people that are being taken
Does does that mean that our memories are being wiped so we don't remember any of these people because
There's no way that it would not affect each and every person on the planet
You know five people
Even assuming you know one person who knows another person who knows another present like there's no way.
Be affected by the six degrees I don't Kevin Bacon subject I don't believe stories of friends of friends
Okay fair don't believe any of it
Has there been
Probably
So I obviously think this number is a little high
And I also think these people might be a little high
Absolutely ridiculous
Gary justifies this number by pointing to like
How this could happen
Okay we are talking
Sing about also during war
This is a perfect for supper
Perfect cover
In which
According to Marc rich
The reptilians can come in through the
The portals in the Middle East
And abduct large
Humans
Slaves
For these.
Right
Fascinating
It's pretty fascinating
Yeah I guess so
I guess that's one way to like not have to emotionally wrestle with the fact that humans
Wednesday Wars against each other pretty hard stuff to deal with
When you get down to it right or feelings of culpability
That you would naturally maybe have to deal with about like
Things that your country's foreign policy is involved in and
That's hard so instead aliens are coming through Stargates and snatching up a billion people
I'm going to be honest with you
I think I'm
I think on the whole we might be better off with the with the Warriors I guess probably
Assuming that the alien one isn't real
Is better to believe that one that's a good point feel as bad
It against this unified animated or we shoot me
Very nice so you got to carry sin War
Is probably how it's done
Most likely
Just the alien snatching people
Robert David Steele has another possibility
I've been very
The illegal
Alien issue
You ever since 2000
Listen to when I predict
That they would be a mass
Migration into Europe
And I realized
There's no way
Tallying up
Refugees
The Middle East
And the number that arrived in Europe
There's a delta in
So you see
People leave a country
Try migrate somewhere
We don't know how many people left how many people arrive aliens
Okay
Aliens
Map
I don't accept
Maybe we can't get an exact tally but people who are good at estimating thing
Assume that it's fewer than 1.5 billion or migrated it's also probably
More comfortable to resume its alien sighting people up in like people die
Trying to Lee countries
Much easier to
Like play around with alien ideas into recognize like
Some people end up completely displaced
They end up in places they didn't intend
Circumstance someone kidnaps them human traffic some along the way
Do happen and they're terrifying
There's only one thing for alien only one type of refugee and that's a space Refugee Dan everybody else's kids
Chapter abducted or
I guess so
I guess.
Still I guess it just would like that's good enough for this topic which move on
Move on to Mars bases
Are we get into the bases
Okay and remember
Robert David Steele
3 years ago
Was on Alex's show saying that he believes
Ditmars is other bases
And they're taking kids there
Children
Where do you
All the witness
You've talked to
That we have bases
Witnesses
Bully funk
National
Whatever
Alright well
As far as I'm
Concerned we have
We have bases on the moon and Mars
According course
Multiple
This is very very
Common knowledge
Everyone knows
Moon and Mars base
Also the moons
Saturn in
We've been terraforming those which
Sure how far along we are
Currently that's quite a
Collinear calling
And then also off
Planet
Not only off play
Out of the sea
So with
Going into
Interstellar Nash
According to mark
The Raptors
I've taken
Around
A human
That are on
A planet that is
Much farther
There are many many
Earth-like
Even conventional
Scientist
Will admit
And Enzo's
Earth-like planet
It's out in the
Solar systems out
Are where humans
I find that
Fascinating fascinating finds a lot of things Fascinate that he has a very standard response
Yeah
I would say that if I'm if I'm recalling things correctly Mark Richards is friends with the Raptors and they're supposed to be the good
Guys but now they've kidnapped 200,000 people to take
Some sort of they were all carrying chocolate at the same time
Population of Hershey Pennsylvania
Solve the case there we go
I think that makes them bad guys I'm not into an alien
I don't know I don't know if I was ever a Post-It
Text Ryan stay neutral
I can't stay neutral take in the Raptor reptilian battled information as it comes to me and Carrie is a wrap
Sympathizer
If they've taken 200,000 people just said weirdo alternate Earth planet and to be I find that trouble
Don't seem like even in the fake
Even the fake reality these guys are always on the side of the back
Does he my wife
So that's enough for bases cuz we've established
It's common knowledge there's bases all over the place super soldier question
Now what about
Super-soul
Is that I've I've read about
Reversion
To tell me about you
Your sense of
The technology
Used to create super soldiers
Not only in the outer
But here on Earth
Okay well we're talking about trans
Humanism in that case
Duh
This is something that they are doing and have been doing
Since my understanding is
Is the Dunkin affinion West
The first
Model super
Soldier
In which he was in hand
Also had
Additional cycle
Capabilities
And Powers
4 +
Making use of what we call organ
It's also called Kundalini
In the Eastside
Duncan opinion someone that's a carry and I Project Camelot interviews while back and you can find a bunch of
People who have dug into him and then like they all bulshit
Who's the first Super Soldier
Amazing she was able to talk to the first one
I still think it's Kurt Russell but okay
So you got this guy
He's been augmented
It's transhumanism
That is very specific
I think it's all it's all very
I just like saying words
What any real psychic abilities would be something I would listen to Hootie that's really f***** up Project Camelot interviews
10 years from now there will be a podcast that makes fun of me
You motherfukers
That is not true
I bet did not go well you don't need to be a psychic to of predicted that b would not land
I'd like your opening B on our guest
So you know we got this Carrie talks
The first Super Soldier the program's been going on ever since that dude
Not just
The US would make super soldiers Nazis wanted it to
The Nazi
These were also the
The first people
At least in this
Sort of
Century
I guess in the last hundred
Where's that
Were
Went down the road
God of creating us
So we were not the
The first
It came from the notch
And they were a universal
Soldier in fact is the movie
That there we go
I forget which universe
Soldier
Progressively those
Series of UN
Movies
Dolph Lundgren in there
Really goes back in
The Nazis
The progression
The development of the
You know they liked
Hide in plain
Hindsight so if
If any
This helps
Salsa when
There are leak
Because
What they can basic
Beckinsale
The movie or the person just saw it they have a
The big imaginary
Mansion in the movie
So I have no idea which universal Soldier movie carries talking about here but I assume one of these
Direct-to-video sequels
Answer me
I kind of understand if your predictive programming stuff is in pop
Popular media Like You original universal Soldier movie
Make sense what I plan to extend to be like
Horribly unsuccessful stuff that no one seen
Admittedly I don't believe in this kind of s*** at all
I also insist that if you're going to
Play that game
You have to at least have some kind of a standard
Not everything could be predictive programming unpublished script can't be predicted program
A failed pilot cannot be predictive programming you have to have
Align
Timecop I feel like that's in between universal Soldier and Universal shoulder is directive timecop Caymans
Out in theaters
Perfect that is I will give you a path I don't believe it I don't agree with you
Playing a fair game you're not playing you're not playing fair if you're using
Directions to equal
Not good
I agree
So I'm glad we're in agreement there
Do you know like super soldiers
I've heard of steroids is that like steroids are they giving him steroids reasonable question
Super soldiers
Died at young age
Do they kind of like
We had a problem
With steroid
Saladin the mill
Military and if
If you take enough steroids your
Collapsing
Does the super
Super technology
Basically
Eat the Beast
Store do they sell
Survive it
Call people
Meijer
Standing is were talking about
Technology
That
Is enhancing
Creating shop cyber
And if this is
To actually
Actually
Better the human body
It can live longer
Barbie murderer
Innov8
Ali fight in
And do all this
They wanted to do so
Bigger Bass
Bigger faster
Better
You know Jordan there's a documentary that came out a while back about steroids called a bigger stronger faster
Does shockingly close to the words are used to describe these definitely not steroids super soldiers
Maybe
The documentary was predicted
Two programming so I would think that she's actually talk about steroids when she uses
Almost the name of that documentary
Stand-on cyborgs getting into the Hall
I look it's up to the hall
Strong position on it I'm not involved I'm going to go with Interstellar 9999 is for
Predictive programing because that had
Daft Punk's great song harder better faster
Faster stronger
It must be yes that must be it
So when we first did our first Project Camelot episode it was about Randy Cramer super soldier and of course now they're having
Conversation he comes up and would you know
I don't remember this
But it does seem like you probably did talk about it
He's bad magic limbs
Replaced
I don't know if that's ever been documented or prove that he's had magical
Regret
Alright
Biscuits
Tick carried on another path where they've already had universal Soldier
Breaker broker
Battery
Into that
All f****** movies and TV shows
Their number soup
Soldiers out there Randy Cramer talks about even
Having the
Technology
To replace limbs
Or or parts
The body that can
You know
Destroyed in a battle
He says that
To him that he's had
Parts replaced
And so on
Transformers
Cloning soul
You can basically
Growing are
Yes
But there's also I don't
Series Fringe
Which Jesus Christ
Were the Nazis
Has to do with
Parallel Rancho
I'm going over to parallel
Lower
Earth where you have a double
All of us
Have doubles and
Parallel Earth
This is an innocent
She might stay in the union Yang of
The being we
We call Earth that way
Would be the dark
And innocence
You have to go
To another dimension
Into
Cross Inn
Into that dimension
Can't access
Individuals
Like in the movie
They're being brought
Across
Like the purse
Person in this
As
Been close to death
They're dying
Able to be replaced
When the cross is over
In fact there's also a
A television
Call counterpart
Who sang i n
After since
I'm not sure if you're going to be able to strengthen your argument that life is like Fringe by pointing to another TV
It's a lot like the first TV show because you saw the second TV show damn helping really
Program is at least like more popular than the universal Soldier sequel show
Playing right game here and I'm not going to be too mad about it
I like friends
I looked interesting I've ever heard of
Counterpart
I think it was a little bit maybe too ambitious
From what I recall but
It was interesting there's a lot of really into
Absolutely
It is it is never well acted Joshua Jackson he was killing people he still got it
Don't know if you did that but it did show people he's still there
I am not just Dawson's Creek
Installing bones
Richmond weather
Myra Devon
Misawa
They just do not have the creativity necessary to write their own s***
Kerry Cassidy is a bad she's a failed screenwriter she's talked about that quite a bit in Hollywood
Can't do it because she's not creative enough to lie her unlocks
I'm not sure if that's all
Is it said the phenomenon is but it is fascinating
To me how just dislike
What I can't get around is like
The picking and choosing
Yeah Blake
Okay yes
You've taken Fringe to be reality
What about
That one. What about that one show where there wasn't electricity
I do know that one girl
I don't know yeah
The 100
Let's just go with that one is real
Yeah I mean like okay there's an island that has regenerative properties and no one can find it on the map cuz it's constantly moving and time
Can I do that I assume so Terry
I don't know I want to pretend that Ally McBeal is real but I just can't live that life
I think the picking
Choosing
Why
Why is it Fringe
I don't know because it's not and it's not even like it's quality Bass
I thought French was good but where we just came from the universal Soldier direct-to-video shift
You know it's quality seems like it should matter like I want to
Television is my point I was trying to get you a time putting my finger on
If I were to make an
Probably to carry that lost
Israel she would not go well with it
Maybe she would
If you would rather not go there
If you're making them to carry
I think he would go along with them
If you were making them against
I think she would say that lost
Is b*******
I just I don't I don't understand I don't I don't get it
Now this next clip is probably the reason that I decided
Do this
This this is where like
It gets real
So we're talking about like
Your daddy don't use that for
You got to this
Fringe
And other show counterpart yet this other reality where there's another version
Interview that you can get body parts from or whatever
If you can get through portal or something
Entirely sure they don't
Get specific
But there's other ways
The super soldiers
Can have like
Super bodies or something
Put your mic down for this good never going to believe
That we get told about here
And then I have a whistleblower
That talked about
People like Mark Twain
And others
That I've been reversed
Staged
So they have this reverse age
And in fact Williams
Are we talked about him earlier
He was doing what he was
Miss doing
Exchange for hope
Hopefully getting for
Friends helping his family
Reverse age
That he that
Then would allow him
How much longer
Go to younger age
Generally from what I'm
Understand their reverse age
Someone to around
To their 20
It's younger for women they're like
23 or something I was told
If I recall
Broccoli and then men it's
It's a little bit older
I totally understand in this fictional reality why you'd want to reverse age some important scientist or something to do
Doing Secret work behind the scenes at you know you want it
Continue
But why the f*** would you reverse age buck
Brilliant Iran I appreciate the Americana
Unemployment
What are my gray. I don't see what the point would be at making him immortal
I don't get it
Mark Twain was important to our country's history because he was a great writer
Engaging public speaker
Continue doing
If you were to have a second life. I don't understand name but people be like a bad you look a lot
What makes Mark Twain
You sound exactly like it but honestly the writing styles
I am not I am Samuel Clemens
Also Mark Twain die tonight
1910 so even if you took reverse aging pills and went back to the age of 28 you'd be 138 years old right now
Again Naturally have to ask yourself is baby he took more reverse aging pills at some point just kept recycling
But if so
F*** did he do in his second lifetime
I see literally no tangible effect in the world that could rightly be attributed to Mark Twain in the years since his death.
Seems like if he did live again
He probably was pretty low-key about it maybe just wandering around Missouri
He lives a full of rich people live
He's earned a retirement complicated it seems
But maybe not the best use of this
Empirical technology for a shadow
Yeah that's probably no good
That's probably no good
I have a suspicion that this whistleblower of carries just knew that one of Mark Twain's pithy quotes is quote
Life would be infinitely happier if we could only be born at the age of 80 and gradually approaching
Which I guess was then transformed into him being some kind of
Reverse aging operation kind of thing
If you would like
If you wasn't like doing the riversage and then why would he say so
Yeah I do why would you say something like that Jordan
Fake weird random quotes being taken out of context
To be like see obviously this guy knows this Secret
Universal Soldier
Why would he say that if you didn't already have some sort of Benjamin Button technology should I reference another movie
Do you say that if he wasn't like Merlin of s*** that's right it's another fake think
So Mark Twain maybe still walks Among Us has been reverse age
With pills
Thomas pynchon
Maybe
So that makes no sense to me but Carrie has other rigs
There are different ways
Dealing with
With a super soldier and also
Keeping a human being alive
And bringing them back so they're RX not
You're not
People who have been reversed age
And in essence are
Young men now
Call Rose
I'm sorry
Seat that makes sense yeah I heard her Von Braun is who you would say in this can help Mark Twain
Where to buy brownies
Exactly who you would prefer Sage
You like a genius rocket science guy
Like spooky and evil he's literally a doctor Strangelove if you will
If you're going
The list of who's the first to get the Aging technology
It may go wrong with the man Mark Twain
Absolutely
Absurd
So you can talk in about the interstellar travel a lie it's mostly
Right
Well that's the only way to get past the hole
Lightspeed
Sure or the Van Allen radiation belts in whatever
You got you got issues
Apparently there are spacecraft
But they're used to transport other spacecraft
Through worm
Convoluted
But there are a bunch of dimensions in the world right right
Another portal
You can go through or something okay carries talking about that here a little bit and she reveals a secret power
Or that she has to be unimpressive
What what
We're talking about is
I sort of an Apache
Apache
Return to
Source as
They call it and there is there a hierarchy
Is that one must
Go through
And levels
Frequency that you
You raise your freak
When seeing your able
Go to go today to other dementia
And if you ever gone to Sedona and you
You go to the portals
If you want to know what a portal is like
Go to Sedona
Although they have them all
The world ending Factor Rivers
And lakes are
Are natural portals
So the energy
You can feel it happened
If I can feel this
My hand
Walk-around
Until you wear on
On your property they
There might be a port
Okay if your superpower is being able to tell you where a portal might be
Yep that is not a definitive power
Maybe there's one here
It's not
Well I just told you there might be one I didn't say there was
That is a soft power maybe divining rod
Also I've been to Sedona
IHOP
You could be right
I've been delayed
I think she just revealed that it one point she was probably a
I don't know maybe something that's straight out of elrond
Do not necessarily it's all over the play
Okay no paranormal
Nice if that's very very
Ubiquitous
Necessarily comes
From him from Hubbard
Are you
She was still going to disagree with you
Thinking you could use that as proof
Hobbit
FairPoint
I don't know I mean I think on some level she's just expressing
Exactly what I feel but I don't think it's
Squirtle related and that is it like nature is great
Viewing when you're out of out and about you don't you know you're not around concrete you know they're being at River at does have
Have some sort of that
Behold the sunset if you're out by a river
All the bugs
Does it start making noises
Very atmospheric solutely
Fuels in
Entirely different and I understand and I think what you
Trying to express or what
He's expressing but in the form of like
There's magic portal
I think it's just a very
The Call of the Wild is what some people call it you could call it being Earth sensitive or being sensitive
Being able to feel
Nothing
But then you're interpreting that feeling
I've been portals
So Carrie just recently talked to a guy though that he lives on a ranch
And that ranch is above
Military base military base
There's probably a portal
Involved
The military base is being shared with ashtar command I'm just bundling
Nope
I just interviewed
Re-interview
John Edmond
Who lives at Elana
On a ranch
Located on top of
Do the military base
In Arizona
And it's also been
Shared by the app
And he has
A tremendous number of portals on
Is property where our beings are always
And
I am basically disturbing their life
Multitude of ways
I heard that and I thought I heard a damn sitcom
A guy is trying to find his business on a ranch having a great time
All these aliens keeps showing up in meddling it's episodic
You get out of different groups
Because I think she was thinking
Lisa Ryder
Describe that is
There's all these portals coming out of this guy's Ranch and its really messing with their life like that
She's having trouble they're there messing that they're turning the water off the electricity goes for a wire every time they portal in it
Terrible LOL yeah Italy is a real
I would watch my life when I watch more TV
That sounds a little bit like Fringe
Write the show write that show
That's your ticket
Dan Harmon
We know the answer to this question but Roberts about to ask
Is there an Interstellar war going on
Is there some
Intergalactic war going
I hear about
Reptilians
Palladium Theater
Is the village idiot
Living in Oaks
Virginia
But I find this fascinating
Can I find you a very
Incredible in
Person
Conflict going on right
And who's winning
Yes it is kind of funny
You say that I mean even pee
That followed the Bible
Which
Does not know
Tell you the whole truth
Truth and nothing but the
The truth and to understand that
That we're in a war of Worlds
You know that's the whole truth nothing but the truth is followed up by so help me
Show me God
What's that part off
I just like the idea that Robert David Steele is like I think that you're a credible and interesting person
After minutes earlier she said Mark Twain has been reversed age
I'm enjoying who is Foghorn Leghorn better of
I say I say now everybody knows you're a brilliant woman and I'm just a down-home country lawyer
God so funny
So
0 hey there's Interstellar war going on but it's really like
All of this is not human
All et like all wars are
Anytime you see a war on
On Earth
When I found out
After all these years
Investigate
Is that
All of those Wars have
ET Bass
So these are not just
Towards Beach
Humans the way we convince
We think about
This isn't you know it's very
It's very popular.
I think about humans as a
Too warlike species
Is actually that's
Humans are not warlike
In the way that these others
We're talking about the negatively base
I mean it's there's so much of this they did constantly pops up this is hiding behind but attributing things to eat
Aliens that you don't want to recognize humans are capable of
Yeah very weird to me
Hey bud
Also Heights
It also hides their fundamental fascination with war
And their desire for
To talk about all of the
The heroism ended all that s*** that we associate with war
Without having to feel bad about being one of the primary
Drivers of it I guess
Not her specifically but you know Warren General
Break if you're going to have like a Randy Kramer's
Celebrated murderer of tons of alien has protected the Earth
Server for decades
It's very strange
Worldview to me
Bye
So Robert David Steele asks if Trump knows about
Casino about these aliens
And I will say that
Gary's response
Interesting
Is it fashionable
Credible
Interesting
Mysource
To say that
Yes Trump is very knowledge
Berlin facts
Gordita Marc rich
She's wife
I is used as an alien condom
Do it to a certain race
Switch you will not reveal to
Which race that is
Except to say that it isn't the lion be
Beings and it
I believe it's not the
The Reptilian
I'm going to pause there really quick cuz there's more revelation
B guess
Is Mark Richards
Is not telling her which
Race Melania is a conduit for that implies
That is not a good race of aliens
I feel like you would
Play Erik Satie
Or the reptilians
Who's the Raptors he would just be like yeah but he has got a one-to-one hotline
Everything is cool
We gathered our president is in touch
With our allies in space it's good
It's got to be one
Has to be like a bad alien race
I didn't know there was a lion aliens
Well those the mercantil dogs
Would be interested in Dan
I know their Mercantile dogs
And then they're the feline Contessa's right to archaeology
But
I didn't think of it those feline Contessa's were
Lion
I feel like that
Slightly different
Does that mean everything in the feline what phenotype her or Jesus you know like everything
Isn't it the case that a lot of those species came into being by virtue of like
Natural pressures that exist
On Earth
That's true that's true that common ancestor is the feline family
And you would assume that there if there's feline aliens they wouldn't have had the same pressures that would leave them too
Genetic engineering they make
All of themselves from the different cookie
Good bi we got point is melania's probably in touch with
With me lately
I can't I cannot stress this enough the Assumption has to be if Mark won't tell her
It can't be goodness cuz he always tells her
Specifics that's always one of his things is like there are certain areas where he's like I'm going to be one hundred percent specific
And then others where you almost like
She writes down that he turned and looked and gave me a knowing wink
Like why didn't she ask him what race he was talking
Right
And I'm his is silenced
Speaks volume
That's what I would say
Anyway there's more there's more news on the geopolitical alien front
So
This is
Donut of what you're talking about
Yes putinism
Ben Redden
And even
Who's Chloe
I understand it is that bad
For a while now
Rambutan
The Clown
Carpet bombing
Clone
Dropping in there been a clone for a while now there is no food
Or I guess
Is it the clown from the alternate universe that they brought over or is this
It doesn't
Von Braun make this
This is the problem with this interview style is that even though Robert David Steele Is On Target and focus
Not a lot of follow-up question which I would be interested to know exactly what are you saying about who is Putin
Use that is the head of state for one of the largest countries in the world who sang He's a clone and that's a recipe to get a bug.
We learn to that last wife also that they're late lion aliens
Which is cool
Find out about another race of aliens
In the past
But it's B birthday
Funny feel like what
What when you're called on to give evidence
For these things existing
Where do you go
There's also
What if what
Call the dragon mod
That are
Very diabolical
Evansville Airport
Sydney Australia that has
A gigantic
Plaque
Carving of
David Ragan
Put two and two together on that one
So there's a plaque in an airport
Insignia
Apparently
That has a dragon law
And therefore
Diabolical
Okay
Alright so
Okay Dragon Mods
Diabolic
Here's how you prove them
There's a plaque
Yeah there's a single pack
One airport as far as I know yet
Put two-and-two together
Bingo
There aren't even two
It might be
Do we know of one
Glad one source of information and it's Terry
So they get off the topic of some of these aliens and Robert David Steele wants to know about free energy
You want Scott to end this interview. We ought to free energy
And it turns out there is free energy as to do with vortexes or something
Play
Why didn't we dhm
He's number one on the list right you think create Tesla
But I know not.
Mark Twain
You wrote the book
Clever
Use the n-word
Two apparently we learned
How you can get some free electricity and put down for this one too cuz I need you to hear the specific
Specific
I will say one thing about carry that you can really count on is that she does not get bogged down in details
Not into the specifics
Free energy comes out of
The
You know that the energy back
The black hole
And by the way
Apparently there are black holes
Chivas and and in the earth center
Which is more
Information I'd be
Lately so in essence
Free energy is all around us
It it comes
In fact
I've been told by 1 /
Dick
Something in the ground
I'm in essence
Access
Electric
So there are lots of different types
Energy
Okay so if I understand correctly
Someone told Carrie recently they can put
Something in the ground
Electricity
Then it turns out that the black holes were inside us all a longer
Somebody a nonspecific somebody
Call Carrie
They can take a thing
Something
Kudos to that thing and it could be
Electricity
I really think she should get a pat
Not that quick
Text somebody
Tell her to go to bed. That thing
Dave the stamp and mail it to
See yourself
Yeah
That's the kind of sentence like if you're doing an interview just can't let that slide nobody told me you put a thing in the ground
You got free energy
What are you talkin about Wednesday who told you that what is this anybody interviewing the president what are we doing what are we allowing you to get away
This is
Play we have black holes in us and we poke the ground any good electricity
So that's free
Cool
Struggle
It's going to take you a lot of energy to find that thing
I think
So also turns out Mark Richards
Has
Something he's been telling Carrie about another source of
Energy comes to an end
Are they they wrap it up is also another thing Tuesday Robert David Steele
I'm trying to keep this interview tight
It's going to be about 35 minutes we're not going to go
Like in the same way stick
That's why you don't ask what's that thing to poke the grass
What thing is it you know it's something I can't tell you that tell you
Who was a classified
Situation
So there's another source of
Energy
This is this is
Bacilli end of this interview
Ann-Margret
Just talks about
The energy from neutron stars
That we are now able
To fuel our craft with
40 T's did not want us
To have access to that goes beyond
So
Samuel. And I believe
Airlines
Using it right now
For their planes
What
Airlines went bankrupt
Didn't have to use
Free energy
What
You know I'm worried about radiation
Sickness
The people are being quarantined
Bloopers
Same way
As radiation
We have to
To stop because I've made it
To my audio
That I do 30
1 hour
Interviews
Stick by that commitment my friend
Can't go look can't do part 2
Note
I enjoy the strong assertion
That she believes
The airline companies all went bankrupt
Enter now have to use free energy which is from space
Answer me this
Why wouldn't they have used free energy in the
Well they have to go bankrupt in order to get access to the free energy
Then the reptilians have them right where they want them compromised
Alien alien Raptor Alliance
And by virtue of that now all these aliens
Can Fly for Free
200,000 people out of here every day that's the whole idea that like curtain that goes up
Charisma
God dammit
I didn't need that curtain is because they don't want to look back at us a dirty poor people that care no
Gazzara
It's mantid beings and then partying
Why not
A B B train
Those curious about what
Steel was saying at the end
About the radiation sick
Miss that he's worried about I watched another video of his and apparently he believes the
The coronavirus situation
Yes from free energy
Well I believe it probably has to do with 5G cuz I think that's another that's another popular area of the
Conspiracy world
The weirdly I haven't heard Alex talk about why we haven't talked about
Michelle
We have to go to somewhere in Virginia where there's one no no he's talked about 5G relation to the Coronavirus
Oh no that's been like it's all
The China has 5G this is all just that they're trying to cover it and say hello Iris okay
On that tip
Watch another video of his are you saying that like
These people there on the Plains and they get sick and then you think
It's flu then you get them off
Planes in the fine cuz it's radiation sickness
Alright let's
Alright I I don't
Think that one's valid for a lot of reasons nope
I like that he's
Trying again
You take things
Based on
You can't take any real argument
It's made seriously
Because you're also discussing Mark Twain
The Aging
Through pills perhaps you're you're you're talking
By the way
Yeah yeah
King about
Fringe being real well
Can just go in and get our Doppelganger from another dimension
The clone of course
Why wouldn't he put a thing in the ground to get electricity
Underground
Hang in there
This is absurd to love it when she just carpet bombs assertions that I've literally never heard any
Anybody ever even consider as a possibility before and she just
It's it's nonstop this was a tight half hour interview
And there was nothing but gold there
When you only have to watch a half-hour interview and you get Mark Twain
You get thing in the ground
Like its
That's that's a good day in my book.
It is Project Camelot could stay just that
And of course
You know nothing is nothing good in this world stays good
But no especially not now
We can at least
Look at this
New interview
And Inc the ways in which
It has no similarities to what
Give us a break in the past
And I'm glad
For that so thank you carry even if we are to make
Making fun of
This entire everything about
100%
At the very least
20%
Which is how many people we are missing
Yes
Oh yeah I forgot about that to 20% of the population being eaten by aliens
What I don't understand
Like
It it seems like it
Easier to just believe that the problems are aliens
Is there alien
And it's so hard to stay informed about everything that's going on
And really trace the the root causes Behind these problems
And solve it
So if you're choosing to go the he's
Easy route
Why are you been making it
Complicated and miserable to live in
Like if you were going on a Carissa's Blitz why is it so miserable to be
Tubidy
Take the easy route man
It's not miserable
This isn't real
So you're not actually facing any of the effects of like what
The downside of
If aliens were really right people all over the 20%
What she's describing is terrified
No
Like when the whole point of doing this is to avoid the bad feelings of
Instead of just instead feeling miserable and helpless in the face
Alien
Feelings 200,000 people that ostensibly you like
Yeah yeah I don't know real bummer
Yeah
I don't have an answer for that I don't know
I hate my government doing things
In my name that I find
Reprehensible and
But I am fine if Raptors steal 200,000 people I'm still free
Come on
Hey you know you got to look at it as on a sliding scale
Yeah at least they haven't
Abducted
5 billion
Sure yeah
So this is been a little bit of a fun break
We'll be back with another episode
There's a secondary aspect to this too which is like really pointing out that there is
Super Bowl
Between the worlds
Of Alex Jones
And Project Camelot then
Necessarily appears
Like you have this interview work area saying this stuff about like
Mark Twain got.
I know I keep going back to that because I love it
Much like the last season last episode of Friends
Arthritis the age
Alright
Spoiler alert
I think it's I think it's past it
You're going to watch you to watch it
I regret nothing
So
You have Carrie saying stuff like that and it is like
Really out there in like obviously you'd have to be just
Completely incredulous
Do not be like hey what are you talkin about me any kind of evidence of any of the things that you're saying
Every know it's silly and and you can write it off as like all these just people saying they're stalking
Which is being interviewed by a guy who is
Frequent guest on Alex's show hell he said
I believe children are we
So like
It's
The connection is it's closer than they might feel comfortable for record
I kind of feel like the only difference in worldview between Alex
And carry is
Haisten movies
Maybe you know like I'm talking depending on the movies that they want to believe are predicted to have a grabbing that's where they go
What day are you more into sci-fi
Which one do you want to go with us about
Yeah I'm talking more about like what standards do you apply to what you're putting Ops
Alex was perfectly comfortable having Robert David Steele on
And for public
Presenting him as an expert in stuff until he went a little too far and then he had to be like
Give me exercise cuz everyone was making fun of Alex for believing in me
Acrobat where is like
It's the same
Level of
Wedding
That leads to Project Camelot doing an episode with Pete Peterson
Where are they now in 2017 power bill Ryan has to come out and say
We didn't know due diligence on this interview
Like it's the same
Level of work
It's being done by
These two things
Just one is political espionage
And one is
Magic space.
Get back to what you're saying
Hey did you prefer The Manchurian Candidate or Universal Schultz
That level of just like
I don't give a s*** let's do this
Then
Whatever your taste in movies will dictate the product
Nothing I think I've ever thought
We we will until then we have website
Might not go to bed Jordan girls on Facebook with iTunes or whatever podcast
Download leave a review at cetera and Cher you know the whole deal donated
Amigo I'm Leo and Daisy X Clark
I am Putin's other clone
Alexandra Thurston color