Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge by now I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
We are the bad guys
MoneyGram
Stripe.com
Acknowledge
Friday Friday
The day of the day of Rodger Stones pardoning I imagine well no no no not yet
Just just an hour or so before we started recording project done with vents to 40 months in prison
And your prediction is by the time is open
He will be pardoned
My prediction although I am not like I'm not super into making actual prediction so we can make this a Gamble
I predict
That it will be apart in the Qualcomm whatever Trump wants to disrupt the next new cycle
That either needs
Till I get bad news away from him
Possible Democratic primary something I have to do the Democratic primary
Throw a Rodger Stone pardon in screw up a new cycle
Zico we just Unearthed reports the Trump is killed six people by hand and then he's like I'm pardon Rodger Stone and they're like
Well we got to ignore that news it's like if you were going to do it anyway it doesn't really matter when you're going to do it
So why not use it to some affect the same argument is like
You're going to do it doesn't matter when you do it might as well do it now as we're in the middle of recording
Rich's him just justice so why not
Speaking as a couple of dudes who live in Chicago Illinois
People who love Rod Blagojevich Chicago
I think he has a about the same amount of public love is ROM
We're not we're not very kind to our government officials
Because they're not kind to us it seems like there's some of that
Shut off a little tangent there
Have you ever wanted something classic
Let me give you an example you know like some people have always wanted
Desired something like that I like old radios
Metal bracket radios in 1930
Rehab radio on my mantle
I was considering a collection of a collection of radios together
But some of the
Really f****** expensive and that is not in the car
Recommend some of them two are like really huge and I don't know how much I could commit to that kind of a Decor thing
Like-like bar cabinet size and order it is
Ferrari I like that but other than that I don't know I'm not super into antiques
Player guy or anything like that
Old style guitar not real not real keytar guy
No but actually the other thing Decor wise that I I would like
Is a bunch of like
Either
Communist or anti-communist
Propaganda posters actual ones that are just like new re-imaginings of what
Aesthetic
And onward in the Cold War era was
I would be really into that like an antique posters but also I think those are probably f****** rude
Super expensive
No. They don't they don't care too much for Originals of things
Yeah I've just been watching the show on Netflix called
British show where the Great British repair Show
Really really talented restores
At this little shop and they're all happy all the time
Fixing people's heirlooms and smiling and enjoying themselves and I can't help
But want to go on that show with something old and I don't got
It's unfortunate that you need something old in order to gain access to this thing that makes the
Google positive feeling that's rude of them
I've not seen that show Jordan I do know a lot about Alex Jones
We can do this podcast
I'm so Jordan today I have something
That is I guess
Related to Jermaine Dupri
Jermaine Dupri
I'm going to go Jackson but we're alright
Yeah this is
This I would have got prepared today is I would look at it as kind of like a saying farewell to Rodger if he's going
For a while we won't be able to enjoy some good
Like high-register really in his element Rogers soundtrack
I found something that I think we can all enjoy
And no matter what even if you feel bad about the fact that Rodger is probably not going to prison he's probably going to get a pardon
Even if you feel like everything is
Shity
You can still enjoy some of
So I will get down to business on that in a second but before we do
Got to give a little shout-out to the book who signed up and recording the show
The first
Griffin 303 thank you so much you're now policy walk I'm a policy wonk
Jocelyn thank you so much and I'll probably walk
Hi Jocelyn do next
Are you very much Andrew I do next Conor thank you so much and I'll probably want
Friedersdorf I'm going to lose by George Banton earlier today you were.
Durbin thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk I swear to God it that the Dick Durbin I'm going to Urban friedersdorf
Brother of Honor
DJ thank you so much
Elevated levels
Jama adelaida technocrat
What's the business
Why you pimp so good
Is freakishly large
TVM Adelaide
Hey I'd rather show I'd like to support these dents website
So you can press it goes to my patreon
Sports shop
I don't know if you know this but don't I know but
Back in February 2019 Jerome corsi
Filed a lawsuit against Rodger Stone
This was the ultimate result of the two men's collaboration during the 2016 campaign where course he and Rodger working together
Go to try to get in touch with Julian Assange
Now we've heard Alex Jones say on her multiple times that he explicitly told Rodger to get in touch with us on
And both corsi and Rodger were working at Infowars at the time or working with them at very least
But it might be too much of a stretch to say that the two men's actions were being done specifically
At the order of Alex
Fair
Whatever the case when you work with Rodger Stone things tend to not go great for you
It's super rare for people to walk away without some kind of Darkness looming over their lives
If they're lucky to not get arrested
At the center of the falling out that the two of them had was the tweet that Rodger posted on August 21st
2016 it said quote
Trust me it will soon be podesta's time in the barrel
#crooked Hillary
Predated the release of the Hacked podesta emails and based on all available information
I appreciated anyone outside of WikiLeaks new knowing that they were going to be released
According to Coursey
A couple days after Rodger posted that tweet
Rodger asked corsi to draft a memo that he could use as a cover story for why he tweeted something he should have no business
It's snowing about right
This member was allegedly about how Rodger wrote that
Based on research the course he'd been doing on
Quote podesta and Hillary is alleged relationship
With Russian companies
Drum I ratfuck myself
I need direct Buck you to get my ratfuck out of myself
After my mother's started investigating and it became clear that this just wasn't
True course he came out at by late 2018 and admitted that the memo he'd written with Ally
And was made specifically to explain why Rodger posted that tweet
A course he came out and made some comments that were not looking good for
Rodger who was about to be indicted by Mueller
I have the story you told me interviews with investigators is coming a bit unraveled
Rodger went on the attack against Jerome corsi
He started talking s*** about him on Infowars which if your courses
Kind of should have expected
Every course he work for Alex he knows that there's no rules about responsibilities that are practiced in Florida
Ridiculous
If you get stabbed in the back by Rodger that's your fault you should never have turned your back garage out
Associate with him metal plate on your back at all
So Rodger railed on Coursey on-air then social media Legend of course he was working with Mueller to jam up
Course he claimed these attacks had resulted in him suffering quote intentional infliction of emotional distress and assault
An article article in Newsweek says that course he claimed Rodger quote
Carried out a campaign of threats against him
To cause him to have heart attacks and strokes
In order that plaintiff will be unable to testify it's don't criminal trial
Good.
He claimed that Rodger was doing this sort of intimidation because he fancied himself a little bit of a gangster type many love them
This argument games a little credibility based on the fact that one of the Rogers charges in the Mueller case was related to
Witness intimidation directed towards Randy credico
The other person Rodger tried to use as a scapegoat
Explain his Advanced knowledge
Of the podesta emails
His friend
Friend said he tried to stitch up you know how you talk to your friend I'm going to take your dog away from you
Hi c********* I will still say though even though there's some credible
Ability because of Rogers Behavior towards critical
I think the idea that he was trying to give course your heart attack might be a little much
A little dramatic
Plot of course he's suit is that
Based on his being named as a material Witness
And considering things that you knew about Rodger
He believed that Rogers actor
Attempt to intimidate him out of cooperating with the case against Rodger
In the process Rodger was defaming course in order to smear him to make his testimony seem less credible
Or even make it appear the course he was the criminal behind this whole thing all along
The initial filing of the lawsuit list the defamatory statements and honestly it just sounds like Rodger being Rodger
Now having said that
Ruby Rogers Rogers at the height of his life that's defamation
I'm not sure where the line is but none of it seems out of the ordinary
Course he's suing Rodger for 25 million dollars which I suspect was never going to go anywhere and honestly I
Hard time believing with this suit would even have gotten to a trial
The claim defamatory statements seem as best as I can tell it to be things that would be easy to claim our opinions but that's a matter for a job
You know I can't
I'm not going to make it legal
Decision
In his lawsuit course he decided to hire for his lawyer another person who's been slighted by Infowars
A man by the name of Larry klayman
You may remember him as the guy who wouldn't stop yelling about how Obama was trying to bring Ebola into the country to attack white people
And does the lawyer representing Dennis Montgomery
The guy who was working with Sheriff Joe Arpaio wants
Shady business that everyone decided to pretend was proof that Trump was being spied on
In terms of the places I've come across clam and I will say that he is not impress me much
I wouldn't hire him as my lawyer and it does not look great when you see people who are yeah that's that's scraping
Scraping the Barrel's bottom like for instance right now Larry klayman is representing George Zimmerman who is apparently suing
Elizabeth Warren and Pete buttigieg
Because they took it about how Trayvon Martin would be 25 years old right now if he wasn't dead
Wright-Patt lawsuit is seeking 265 million dollars
Is disgusting
It's not the most disgusting thing that Larry klayman has done
George Zimmerman
Because back in December they teamed up to sue Trayvon Martin's Family for 100 billion dollars
I can't imagine that lawsuit will work out but what it will definitely do is make people really warm up to the Zimmerman guy
Hey yeah you know I was thinking that he you know it's like it's like when you get piled on
You know it's so you've been publicly shamed by Jon Ronson
Similar to that but now my sympathies are gone
F******
The Southern Poverty Law Center has described claiming as quote pathologically litigious so I'm going to watch what
What I say about him
I know so that image of him being quote
Pathologically lifted just kind of comes into play in the corsi situation
Because as soon as corsi suit Rodger with claiming as his lawyer
Rodger started attacking both of them
Calling into question clayman's ability of the lawyer
And saying he had a little IQ Larry klayman turned around and sued Rodger along with course
Also sounds right
As well as somebody else on April 5th 2019 Coursey and claim and join their suit
It's against Rodger which was now also against Rogers associate Michael Caputo
With claiming still acting as a lawyer
Which brings us to why we're here today it's going to be like World War eventually all of these conservative personalities
Pick sides and then everybody's at like Kaitlin Bennett is suing Laura Loomer and that's all a fuckboy
Lawyer Larry klayman
Look totally
F******
Alright well then we know which side
In the past on our show Larry klayman has been associated with the organization Judicial Watch
Since he founded that grew
But he's actually left
You left back in around 2000
4 and ultimately started a new group called Freedom watch
In the evening hours of Tuesday February 18th 2020
Damn is it 2020
As I was editing up our Project Camelot episode that we released on Wednesday Freedom watch posted something that would have
Been an absolutely perfect
Wacky Wednesday episode and it's honestly
Like catnip to me so there's no way I could resist to an episode about this immediately
They posted a whole s*** ton of video of Rodger Stone being proposed for this lawsuit
Show me you were reading some of his deposition I thought you only had transcripts
I can't wait so as if that wasn't enough to get me excited
Like dude
He's being questioned by the opposing side's lawyer Larry klayman
God and this is going to be a base Larry klayman is the lawyer doing the deposition with two rods of God it's just
Almost perfect
That is very funny just a recipe for disaster
Took the deposition is 5 hours long on day one and then about 48 minutes as a rejoinder on a
The second base is 6 hours of s*** I had to go through
And you know what it doesn't disappoint if you're looking for a complete disaster
To give you a little since he was just a taste of some of the vibe
Did you call me a b**** that you're acting like one
12in the hippie like you're a dick and he's like oh you're a dick and then I'm not sure
Search there in a jeep Scout
It is frequently like that
Jesus
Great that'll give you a sense of the tone and the level of professionalism punches play here
I'm going to spare everyone from the pain of having to go through this seriously cuz it was mostly a jumbled mess of Rodger trolling liar
And I'm not sure I honestly learned that much about the case from watching all of that
First
Rodger is f****** loving being to post
God damn it I think he loves it particularly when it's flavored is the lawyer because I think
Duke from everything I can tell
He hates Larry
Busy now we're getting back from our evil ratfucker to low-key traversing the Earth sowing Discord
Very mad. I don't like it
Of all the different moods a person is capable of righteous indignation
Dear he's being asked questions about a case that he is not taking seriously which allows him to just be a complete dick
Because the target of it as someone who you also like a f*** yourself
It is a needs Loki I shouldn't if you can enjoy it a little bit
It sometimes despite myself
Get them Rodger just f****** do it kind of good at certain things
Competent
Bright
Second the other thing I need to tell you is I don't care what happens with this case
Is the very definition of a let him fight situation
Rodger probably definitely said some untrue things about both corsi inflaman
If he gets in trouble for it who cares
Also if he gets away with it course he's claiming both suck so I don't really care either
The only outcome of this no matter how it goes is that both sides end up wasting resources fighting with each other
Not alright in my book
So we've seen how Alex Jones Rob do in Paul Joseph Watson behave when they're forced to be under oath in a deposition
They change completely I'm either play dumb or pretend to be serious right now it's time to Xperia
Roger's phone number of
Which all seems very similar to Rodger Stone anywhere else
This dude
Does not give a f***
Begins by Bruno talking about some of Roger's history
And you know like his educational background and then working for the presidential campaign
You know what I never realized I guess probably should have known this earlier and I I bet I did I just didn't
Didn't remember
He didn't graduate from college
He didn't know you like which we year of college and then started working for Nixon
You can be whatever you want to be able to me that he doesn't have some sort of a degree or
Formal training in political science
He wouldn't do that and wouldn't do any formal training
To really tap into his right whakaaria
Yeah and so they talked about the early history and then the topic comes up of Wendy's to First
Grass Pad
Did the
Yes indeed
When was that you represented
Did I not meet you earlier
The Old Ebbitt Grill with
Time that
You met me
It's entirely possible
I just don't recall
And
True that
Let me put on the
I just don't recall
Rodger is not remember any of this ship
So as it turns out Larry klayman and Rodger Stone go way back and the two men have a rich history
Rodger believed that they met when claiming represented Rodger which will get back to but it appears that their paths crossed when clay
Women wanted to work on the Jack Kemp campaign in which Rodger wasn't advisor
That would have been the 1988 election so that puts being acquaintances of 32 units
I don't recall in time I don't recall you as a person
I don't know there's a little disrespect that's what I remember you
So
Camp stuff Rodger doesn't remember that meeting so I'm going to go ahead and take that off the table
In 1996 Rodger was working on The Bob Dole campaign
And things got a little messy when the National Enquirer reported on how he posted ads and scandalous pictures of himself and his
Wife in swingers magazine
And online looking to get
Some fun going
Rodger initially blamed it imaginary assistant for post
The ads but eventually cop to the fact that he'd done it
When he finally did come clean he was still kind of a weasel about it saying quote
When that whole thing hit the fan in 1996 the reason I gave a blanket denial visit my grandparents were still alive
I'm not guilty of hypocrisy
Breakfast
You're being hypocritical in that
This is a bit of a scandal because it was 1996
To the right-wing attacks on Bill Clinton had to do with him and his women womanizer
So this would be a bad luck Ford old I was senior advisor who was out swinging
Particularly considering that according to the Chicago Tribune
Rodger was part of Bob Dole
Clinton accountability team
Endless by September of 96 Rodger had stepped down from the Dole campaign
I don't really care about Rodger swinging his business but his response to the Inquirer stories
Speaks a lot to his character
I understand the culture wasn't
Accepting of people live in alternative Lifestyles at that point
But the length of you want to pretend that he's been set up we're pretty ridiculous
Anyway Rodger threatened to sue The Inquirer and Larry klayman was his lawyer night
That was where Rodger is saying their paths first crossed
But because there was no imagine perpetrator to sue here Rogers lying about that and there was no libel on the part of the
Enquirer this case went nowhere and Rodger
Took a pretty big hit to his credibility
Consider he was a College Dropout who went to work on shady s*** for Richard Nixon
He'd work for Reagan
Use an advisor for Bob Dole
These has big lead
In the GOP circles politics
But after the Scandal he went down the fight card a little bit
His profile just didn't match with presidential candidates and us
In 2004 Rodger was enlisted to advise a certain candidate on their run for a Florida seat in the US Senate
That candidate was Larry klayman goddamn these people
Is it okay for the claiming to be questioning him in this deposition is that even okay
Comical
Good long time with people who have known each other who do not like each other try
To Pretend There's Something formality
Larry would end up with 1.1% of the vote in the Republican primary putting him in a very respectable 7th place
A Sun Sentinel article about the candidates and their primary include the section about claimant where you Compares himself to Abraham Lincoln and
Ronald Reagan
Any policy set is described as quote
He Advocates abolishing the IRS
The forcible removal of Cuban dictator Fidel Castro
Okay
Would he be administered
Sleeps Chatterbox had an article about his Senate run which was mostly about how even back then he had a bit of a reputation
For being wildly litigious
The piece ends quote for Chatterbox though there's only one issue in the Larry klayman campaign
If elected will he pledged not to file any lawsuits for the next 6 years
Will he decides not to sue anyone for the duration of his Senate campaign
No
It's a free country
Pictures of man who like suing people he doesn't even want anything out of it he just likes filling out that paperwork
Deposing people who have no business being used as a weapon
Is 2004 run on the nation
According to this article Larry's Adventures at Judicial Watch where he would file tons of lawsuits mostly against people in the Clinton
Norbit never funded by Richard Mellon scaife
The right-wing billionaire megiddo
According to this article claim and sought funding from scaife for his Senate run
In a letter that said quote
As a sender I will have considerable powers that I did not have a Judicial Watch
Including the ability to investigate and prosecute in the Senate Hillary Clinton
Much like Richard Nixon did with the Communist spy Alger Hiss
If I'm some day to run for president I need the credentials to do so
Being a senator will provide me with this possible
To desire somebody to be president less than Trump but I will be God damned if claiming would be worse at his job
This was part of a multi-state
Plot that was the result in Hillary being tried in the Senate and Larry klayman is present
It should be pointed out that escape spokesperson told the nation quote he has not given a dime to
Mister Clemens camp
I didn't fact he discouraged him from running
Well that's probably
Anyway this nation articles mostly about the question of whether or not soliciting this loan would constitute a campaign fine
Finance violation
But seeing as it was sixteen years ago I'm not really going to get bogged down in that question
Sean my really interested
The answer is
The important thing for us today is that the reason that Larry needed money is because the only way he could fund his campaign was through
Listing donations through direct mailing
And he didn't have access to a large database of names in order to Target those mainland
When you're in that situation
You know you don't have a giant mailing list
You need to pay for access to other people's lists of names
As claiming was doing with the lift held by American Target advertising
The problem was according to this article
That he was spending almost as much as he was bringing in with his strategy so that wasn't going to cut it and that doesn't
Seemed like a good
Breaking even on campaign Finance donations is not good so you need to reach out to a billionaire mega-donor
Have them pay for the list or something and then you end up making whatever
Or have 60 billion dollars yourself that also works
Anyway throughout the rest of Rogers deposition he and Larry getting to a number of fights about this 2004 campaign
Rogers position seems to be that Larry led him to believe that he had access to the Judicial Watch mailing list which would have
Help make his campaign viable
But he did not
Rodger felt misled and like his time was being wasted
Conversely Larry keeps a legend that Rodger stash door computers that he bought with his own money when they left his campaign
I believe both of them I'm not sure who I believe and ultimately I really don't care
But I wanted to walk you through a bit of this history of top because the clips of them arguing about this stuff they're not really useful for our purposes
Cuz there's like a little interjections and like
They're in the middle of a different question about why'd you steal like computers
It's not
Right it's not as out of nowhere and fighting is that might make you think but it just
It wouldn't have been a I don't think I would been able to prevent it
Spike Lee
But you kind of need to know about that stuff in order to understand that these dudes have a long deep history and clearly
Leave f****** hate each other
You stole my computers
It's so fun
So it starts out you know
Not great Tony the adversarial provide asked
You're aware that
They must not have been any phone record
Produce
Cuz you're aware that it
I believe the text messages
Emails
Yes
Are you working
Convicted
Of not providing a
That is untrue
Chakra
That charge was drawing but go ahead
And yours actually
Set letters
Congress
On your behalf
Did not have.
Attraction
Instructing
Want to make sure he's aware
I'm well aware
You learned the hard way
Objection
Delusional that I have to be back
Michael luzier
Indicative
7 count
I'm not going to answer that question
Already get the sense of this needling like there's a strategy that Larry's using it's clearly like
I'm going to get him to yell at night
You can't handle the truth strategies going to try and piss him off until he admits it will then that's a dumb strategy
Going both ways
It develops more into Rodger just f****** with him
Has like a little bit of time going to be obviously
Just like
Poke poke poke
You're delusional piece of s*** how about that did you tell me delusional piece of s*** now I didn't call you why would you hear that
Hear that if you are delusional piece of s*** and Rogers lawyers trying to make clear wreck right out of the gate
Not answering any questions about criminal matters and Larry keeps trying to get
Questions in or like
References to the Mueller investigation which should
Be off-limits
For the purposes of this but it is
Keeps happening what computers
Did
The FBI
Take
Ocean computers
We're not answering these questions
This is relevant to.
Are you tired
You're going to
No you're going to wind up getting sent to me
So let's go
Why not
Yes I am
That was that was one of my first big laughs when Rogers like I'm not to be pageant
This is breathing life into by
Cold broken heart amazing wait for it you have no idea how badly the superior race
No good
So
You know
There's there's just a clear town of like f*** this guy
It must be so fun to be Rogers lawyer
So your entire day is devoted just telling him to shut up
This beginning portion here that where it has to do with like document production
You heard him asking about like what computers there were and then goes on
And Suzanne
The question comes up of like
Notes
But handwritten notes to work product what's relevant to the
Like them for this cuz this this is a this is another big laugh
Keep notes yourself
Not on any of these matters
I might make a grocery list two dozen
They never write anything
But not pretending anything
We're here to discuss
All that in right now
Did I write that down
Well truth is not Pluto
Someday we will
This will work
That is the best
Did you write down
Truth is
Oh yeah
That is just breathe
Bob YouTube
God dammit Rodger
So one of the things Larry is taking issue with and he thinks his defamatory
Is it Rodger went on Infowars and he said that Larry's never won a case in his life and then
He's a loser
The issue of him being the loser keeps coming up
And one
You know obvious questions
Larry would have his
If I'm a loser why did you work with me
On my campaign for the Senate
I think Rogers just
Taunting him
Are you in a representative
Is a loser Wiki
I thought the dude
If you had the money could be liable Canada
Loser
You can't win
Know that money
Luther Goodwin
You're not a loser cannot win unless they have money
This is what Define loser
Your contacts.
Loses
Repeatedly
Littleton.
How did you do in Centerville
Next to you
Larry
Where's that list that list Larry
Children wear on a goddamn playground what are we doing here there Underoath
I'm not a loser am I know you are a loser no I'm not. Thanks to you.
Thanks to you
So Larry is pissed because Rodger was working on his Senate campaign
I need the time from what Larry saying it seems like
He had an understanding or belief that Rodger was going to be an exclusive
Employee for him
Sure on his campaign
Now Rodger also at the time was apparently advising Al Sharpe
Who was running for Democratic candidate
Our president
And so this is
Problem
For Larry
Because there's no exclusivity in your going around
Get the Sharpton and we still talking about the lawsuit happening
About what happened to 29
Antichrist
And where the deposition talking about Al Sharpton campaign is not relevant
Not relevant
He's mad that Rodger was giving advice to Sharpton
Rodger insist he wasn't working for Sharp
Larry said some bad things about Al Sharpton
And what did you do after we parted
Network router
Never Shout Never consulted his a friend of mine and give me advice when he asked for
Do you have
They're basically race
Is baiting vigil
Does your friend
Imagina forum
I'm afraid in case you
The famed
Hindi film you either
That's what you think
Didgeridoo
I doubt it
Larry Mahan
Somehow in a deposition talking about Rodger Stone defaming you you have to be a racist towards Alice
Sharpton for no reason and I don't know if it does rise to the level of defamation calling him a race-baiting extort
Fortunate on Fox News
Underoath
Weird that is weird weird thing to say but my favorite thing at the end there is one Larry's like willetta
A jury decided Rogers like
I doubt it I doubt it
Not going to have a buddy that keeps happening in this deposition
Like Larry Jose decide this and Rogers like
I doubt it
Because he doesn't think this is going to get to trial which I kind of think is probably about right that's about right
Larry whoever thinks that Rodger saying I doubt it because he has no faith in the legal process isn't she
About the Court's ruling
But in reality Rogers just telling this case stinks and he's f****** with him tonight cuz never going anywhere
Eat my hat and go to prison for exactly 40 mod
The Psycho Drama that's going on is just
Fantastic
It's very boring to watch all of it but it's really fun
In little bit down it's good
Goddamn there like an hour long stretch of boring nothing
I'm toad
Eastpointe Larry starts to sort of layout why some of this is relevant
So there's that ugliness
That happened back in
2004 penny with running for the Senate and apparently Rogers people stole those computers
And this is informing Rogers beliefs in the present day
There's a couple quotes about this that I think we'll like
Really start to thread the needle cuz I know it doesn't make sense now but it should
Why did you refer
Suspect because you did something I didn't like
What did I do
So you
Negative statement
Somebody even if you
I don't know whether any
Opinion it's some
Free country
So just came out of the blue
Don't recall what prompts
In fact you thought somehow that I was
Threat to you
Something
With regard to
Special counsel Robert
Molars
So-called Russian
Collusion
Not going to answer
You're concerned
About
My
Experience with you at
The time
That you were
Consulting on
Conjecture on your part
You were concerned it
But your staff had misappropriated
Computers and cell phone
And the life which I
Absolutely not and I don't know that there's any proof of that
So he is saying that you Rodger to be on Infowars because
Cuz you knew that I didn't like you cuz your staff still computers
I was a threat because I work with Mueller
South movie
Situation right here where it's it's like the hateful eight they're just sitting across the table at each other talking forever
It's very strange because I think
That like
You know
Rodger I bet he's confused
Through a bit of this
The connections the claimants trying to make between stuff is just
Just like where is any proof of the dab
Also
Larry
Why did you say
Why did Rodger say mean things about you on are with everybody everybody
How would you expect him to act you knew him in 2004 newham from 88 on Jack Kemp
You know you don't care what you were his lawyer in 96
When he lying about somebody posted those pictures
You know it you know you got it.
So you ask a question like that
So he takes another swing climate another swing at that you were worried about me working with Mueller
And that's why when I got involved with corsi
As his lawyer
You there you got
Rogers doesn't
Even care about this because
It's just
Larry saying things
You were concerned
I didn't like
Particular
Admit doesn't confirm one way or another
If you were concerned that I was angry
Legitly
Sharpen knives I was angry at you but that's okay
Because the number of amiss
Statements in falsehoods that you
Tomei
Regarding your ability to raise money
Money is important in terms of getting you elected to the second guess you never do not work for me
You never paid me a dime
Are you violated my
I trusted you not
This is ridiculous
It is and it turns f****** ugly
In his next life
The others
The defamatory what are the statements is the claimant hasn't won any cases
And it turns out he has
And Rogers like wow is my sense that you hadn't
I bet it turns into a very nasty insults
He
He's
Claimant never actually want a courtroom victory
I believe sunetra I believe that to be true
What's the time now
Now
You never did any research did you do
To find out whether that was true or not before you met
But in fact you actually did know that I had
No actually I did
Were you wouldn't have
Wanted to be my
So cold
Consultant in the
That was a long time before the
USA 132 pennistone says
Does he mean
Clean was ousted its Judicial Watch
Ask Tom fitton why he left
He was ousted because of
Sexual
Yes I've heard that
And where did you hear that
Don't recall
You heard it from fitting
I most certainly did not
But you don't remember where you heard
I don't know what her but I that told you previously I've never spoken
Anytime Fitness other than the one time
In passing weeks
Disgusting
We did not
So you just believe that out of
At the cosmos
You know how politicians
Take me about something like that
Why would you leave an organization if you found it
Who talked
I don't recall you don't recall
You're about to be absent from the bar
Stop
Have fun watching your own children lyrics
I read the Court's decision
F*** you
Bad start for a break that's what that's what that's it
Good exit line normal conversation after that
No
I tried to look into that and that has something to do with
Divorce filing Bob & Larry's past I have no idea what the circumstances that are
Go anywhere
The only explanation I can find for that sexual harassment business comes from a 2009 lawsuit that Larry
Had filed against Judicial Watch and its new president Tom fitton
It was arranged a lawsuit claiming breach-of-contract defamation and other such grievances
Part of Larry's argument was that fitton and Judicial Watch it committed fraud in the trial because they had testified that he
He was outed from Judicial Watch
Because of a sexual harassment claim but
Larry had a deposition from Tom fitton
Saying that Larry was not quote ousted as a result of a sexual harassment complaint
This argument did not move the court
From the memorandum opinion in the
Text quote
Claimant has not identified any of fittings testimony at trial contradicting to quote a deposition testimony or suggesting
The claimant was quote outed as a result of a sexual harassment complaint
He references only testimony of Paul or fenity used in addressing mr. affinities is
Understanding of why climate
Judicial Watch
Nowhere in his testimony did mister or vanities state that claiming left Judicial Watch due to a sexual harassment
He testified the claim and left Judicial Watch in part to avoid quote
An internal investigation into whether he claiming
Pursued an inappropriate relationship with an employee
And at most explain his concern the Judicial Watch Might
Have been subject to sexual harassment allegations
Based on that alleged relationship
Gotcha
It seems like this is the best explanation I can find for that situation
It looks like it's a thing where Paul orfanidis who was a lawyer Judicial Watch
I testified The Clement had a relationship with an employee
But didn't say that there was a sexual harassment
Complained
It seems like maybe this became a bit of a game of telephone from there
Since claiming got a bit defensive about it in the court
Part of claimant claim of defamation against Rodger is that Rodger said on Infowars that he was ousted adjective
Watch ask Tom fitton why you left you without it because of sexual harassment
Which is not something Rodger could probably
Substantiate
That does make it an inaccurate statement presented as fact
But I also don't know if Larry can prove that Rodger didn't
No it was true when he said it
It's really hard thing to tell with an a****** like Rodger
Repeated a bunch of places it took a while to find that paste
Where that this like this probably came from
But I mean the rumor has been bandied about for a while little bit late to claim now that's Rodger death
Definitively knew that that wasn't the case whenever he said that since the rumor was everywhere
Yeah I don't know if it's because Larry Clemens also a public figure in as much as he's
You know Sudan every Democratic politician ever
It would be very
I think it would be pretty difficult to demonstrate actual malice there
Which is kind of one of the benefits I guess to being like Rodger and just
But having malice towards everyone
So
It's almost
If you had to determine whether or not he had malice in court
It's like it gets down to whether or not he can even feel in the first
Like you don't even
Is EZ a psychopathic robot you
Oh no he's just going to claim whatever you see is just a little
So you have them going out to break with
If you know Rodger accusing claim of abusing his four children at L-A himself
Break on that one nugget is an episode of Modern Family are hard to break
Okay
The tone is just
I would I would like to say work will come back tomorrow
Don't know why YouTube Larry get another lawyer
Defendant Stone
Called me a piece
Garbage can
If this is accurate transcript yes
Constitutionally protected
Dupree speech
You make it a practice
Disappointing people
Garbage
One of the points where I start thinking that maybe this is not a strong-looking soup
What are the things that Larry wants to ask Rodger about his Rodger calling him a piece of garbage I have no idea what's even going on
I can't imagine a reality where you can get sued for defamation because you call someone garbage
It seems like that would be presuming that you think the person is making the factual claim that you are in fact
Garbage
And also that you know the claim is false at the time you're making it
It's so easy to say that this is an insult and a statement of opinion
It just strikes me that this is like
If this is on your list of defamatory things Rodger said
It's a badly
This is silly
Rodger
Did you call me a
A doo doo head
Answer the question
So it is next do we get to the question of
Clements IQ which is been attacked by Rodger
For those people out there who
Thank
The Larry claim his IQ is higher than 70
Maybe I write yes if it if this is an accurate transcription
Again my opinion
Statement is it
Did not sit
I don't have an ID
IQ higher than 72 pinion
This this is just not going to fly
Larry if you're trying to prove
I'm wrong this is the wrong way to go about
This just doesn't seem like
Got like those statements are
Very easily depicted as opinion
I don't
I don't know anyway
There's a list of insult
But Larry has a rapid fire
It's not it's not a huge listing it
It's not really that
Great
But the way Rodger responds to it is
Is just like
So good
At 1
The clock you also published
Quote to be clear Larry klayman is a moron
He's never won a case
In court in his life
He may have one if you motions
Is a lightweight he's a know-nothing
The statement said I never won a case
You had to look back into my record
As a lawyer
Correct
Well that's the impression I had
I believe that to be sure it's time I saw you
The other things I said
Just a moron.
Lightweight no nothing
That's so funny
So Larry
If you get this next cookies trying to like play like he's sneaky
That's serving Rodger with the the papers for the lawsuit
The cases that were most certainly did not
You tempted happy service
And I don't think you were successful but I've accepted
Service
At home
I ended public events for all of your suits
I had to get you at a strip club you tried
What a response to that what a response I just love that you
Nothing none of the other details that could be important there
Are all of them are wiped Away by just
You didn't do it buddy you missed
So now the issue of Cassandra Fairbanks
Thanks comes up
Wedding writer of
Of those sorts and news
You know she's right for like Gateway pundit I believe now
Maybe doesn't anymore but did I don't know who cares I don't I've not kept up too much
With her butt
She
Is it is is factored into this because
She did some
Stories may be negative about Jerome corsi
Around this time and like when on Newsmax and talked bad about course Isha
And Larry's implication is
Rodger told her to do this which would be a problem probably because
You know it
Yeah
But he doesn't have any evidence that he's just trying to make this claim and thinking Rodger Libby like you got me
Craigslist Fairbanks
You've had discussions with her about dr. Jerome corsi having on
I don't recall any specific conversation with her about.
You just can't recall
Pacific Lumber
Regarding doctor
Hey where's the clintons so used to
Say
We have no space
Pacific recollection
No but it's not bad
Caprese
In this case that would be the case I would never would mean that you might have some recollection but you just don't remember now
Know what
But I don't recall ever having any conversation with Cassandra
Regarding.
So did that
Going to be a problem for the argument that he did
Is what
Unless you have some sort of an indication and evidence
An email from her to him but like
Hiyori him sending her an email that said hate auction on Coursey for me
Evidence and it does not seem like there is any
So just like hey did you do this no
Thank you did
Rodger
No clue
Canalis turns into like a really weird thing
Where
I don't know how any of this is relevant
But claiming start stalking weird stuff about Cassandra Fairbanks
Free weather photos of Cassandra Fairbanks
The internet
Mayweather
Her photos of her and another
Contacts on the internet
No I'm not
I have no idea what any colors that was a
Hypothetical nude pictures or
Risque pictures Fairbanks existing online
What they have
To do with this
At all
An ideal situation
It's a waste of a question
It's a waste of time
It doesn't seem to go anywhere
But this also leads into
I didn't know this
I'm not a maybe I didn't I just didn't care I don't know
But apparently Jerome corsi
His said
The Cassandra Fairbanks told him that she slept with Julian Assange
In the embassy
The Ecuadorian Embassy
All right till we get to talking about that a little bit here I still don't know what is going on
I have no idea
And Cassandra Fairbanks
Cuz she had had
Julia song
That's
I don't know if we've ever discussed that other than the fact
She has
A concern for his
Wellbeing
When she visited him in the embassy
London
I've read that
Are you aware that she
Call dr. corsi
I saw our doctor Coursey
Alleged that but I don't know
Where did you see that
Reddit somewhere
She told you that
You put her up to the fame doctor course he'll news
I most certainly did not
The evidence of that
You'd already asked and made that bad bad it's very weird
Strategy
I don't first of all I think if you're trying to go up against someone like Rodger Stone
Not effective strategy not going to do it relishes
Yeah you are you are firmly in Rodger Stones territory
Yeah
I don't know even in another circumstance if that would be a good strategy
It seems like
No he's a decent lawyer working with Rodger could get anything that's said in the Septuagint
Reedley taken out of court. It's being shown here with the arguing and the
And then we talked about about other
Antiparticle
Faceless urchins of just like
Did you where'd you hear that
Who told you
Who told you you put her up to this
This is a stretch
Okay parently Rogers
He doesn't ask
The Rodger
He asked Rodger
About something that you said about Jerome corsi which was essentially if you see his lips moving you know he's lying
Yes
Larry common thing it's an old idiot
Larry thinks that's about him
Even though
Rodger was talking about Jerome corsi explanation for this
It's wild
Target 22 at 6:26 in the Infowars video to Publishers that quote you can always tell when Jerry
Line
Because his lips are moving on quote
We had just said on the
Previous notice goes beyond what you claim was
Specifically
That he lies anytime if he says anything
I think he told multiple lies
Tell you the truth but
But yes I definitely said that
You can leave him at Total Wine
I think you lied on some occasions here yet
But I said yeah
Expression is frequently used with regard to lawyers isn't it how do you tell a lawyer's line is lips
Adduction of Foreigner
So you're also referring to me weren't you
Wild conjecture on your part on his lawyer
Wild conjecture on your part where he wears lawyer
That's a phrase that used with lower
It doesn't say that you're putting words in my mouth
Testify truthfully
Alyssa
Stop
You got to stop at your comment
You asked for it
Appetite
God always just imagine there goes on inside like official places like courtrooms and depositions is
Just like really
Ridgid by-the-book serious people sometimes it's just like this
I just want
I can't get enough of Larry
It listing insults it Rogers
Just like I wanted to go down to lose like
February 2nd you said I'm a sad sad
You called me a rat face motherfuker
Do I have a red face
Not constitutionally protected free speech in my opinion it's my opinion that
All right. You know how it goes in politics to your thing
So another thing
That Rodger has said that is of issue is that he is implied that to Jerome corsi is an alcoholic
Just got that client here a little bit
Of course
If you say so I don't
Specifically
Again you're calling him
I'm drunk with him
I have some personal experience where I've seen him carried out of a restaurant
Stone drunk yeah
What does mean
That you're not coholic
Did you were drunk
GM drunk on more than one occasion
Inebriated
The issue he said it was talking about something they Kursi
Said he said that him saying this
Is only proof of him having an alcohol affected memory
Mission of like he's an alcoholic
Is memorii in my estimation may be affected by alcohol so easy to get around these things
This is weak bulshit
I hate to say it but I'm on Rodger
Stoneside here
Larry Glazer
Larry gets to asking about like a
Your bank accounts you know all this end the Rogers lawyer is no we're not doing Financial discover
He gets a little bit silly
Do you have Altra Bank
We're not we're not
I do not
You keep resources
Gold bars
We're not we're not work this is not Financial
Discover you have no right to ask this question
Subjection
Ask relevant
Do you have a Krugerrand Scott this
This Rogers lawyer is so sick of Larry he's just sitting here like
He's like trying to be an adult in her in the room and it's just pathetic
It's just so sad what's up you've also got Rodger who can't resist activate
Tell him to go f*** off every now and again play with him a little bit
And you can't like usual
It don't answer that
Alright whatever the only person who should feel bad for being in that room is Rogers
That is that is a bummer for him
So there is a story that was published in the daily
Free caller about
Jerome corsi Larry is sort of asserting
That implying or trying to
Make the accusation that Rodger planted the story against Jerome corsi
In this clip
He's talking about knowing a lawyer that's associated with one of the figures in the story supposed to have daily
Daily Caller
And this is this this act
Doesn't go well question earlier about
Doctor in
In Florida
Didn't remember his name
Daily Caller
Reporter
Chuck Rossi
Road about
The doctor's name
Do you know what doctor May
I do not forgive her.
I cannot read the story when it was written
The lawyer and there's also somebody
I do not
Now the lawyer
Who represented
You know him
Concert
Do I
Okay well I don't
No Tommy sickler
So
Commando a lot of lawyers
You name a world tell you whether I
Right now anyway I'll go back in
But that's fine I don't know,
ER where the lawyer
Wasn't contact
Back with me
Regardless
Who's lawyer
Oh and I'll raise it we all know I am not
You are aware that he can
Claimed to be your
There is unprepared and then there's this
How do you not know the name of the lawyer asking Rodger question about when the question seems to hinge on whether or not Rodger knows said
How could you possibly expect Rodger to answer a question about an unspecified person
Question blue my mind
He's the guy from that thing you do that guy
I don't know that that I might know the guy
Why did the stuff when there was a dolphin I bleed
Something
If I were Rodger in there
Feel like I was having a stroke like
Why do you ask
Excuse me sir do I smell toast
What is happening
Just give me your name
Justin Bieber
Rodger on March 3rd
2019 you said I had the balls of a castrated dog now am I holding a castrated. Eyeballs recently prepared
The story behind this is that Chuck Ross a writer for the Daily Caller post
Article that raised some questions about a GoFundMe campaign the course he'd been supporting
For a guy named Tommy sickler who allegedly had cancer
Sigler was apparently in need of an experimental cancer surgery that was to be performed by a dr. Elliot mendelsohn
Course he claimed that Mendelson had quote cured his relatives stage 4 liver cancer
And the Tommy could be saved with this operation as well but he needed the money to make it happen
Apparently that GoFundMe raised over $25,000 but there were some issues that came up when
You got looked into a little bit
According to the Daily Caller that did some digging and found that the link that was provided by Corso you to dr. Mendelson Clinic
Directing people to the website of Mendelson Consulting Group
The registered owner of which was mysteriously Tommy sickler
That is certainly a pretty big red flag and the guy who needed money for this miracle surgery happens to also be the
The owner of the miracle surgeons business
It seems like he would have been maybe he could even get it at cost
That is all the appearances of a con and it be pretty easy to assume that maybe course he's good-natured got caught up in trying to help a guy
However according to the Daily Caller they were also unable to find any evidence the doctor Mendelssohn even exist
An issue there
The store Cassie Medical Center in Tel Aviv where he said to a practice
No One by that name works at the
Facility and that they had no records
It was alleged that Mendelson also had a practice in Boca Raton Florida but there was no one by that name in the Florida
Physician licensing database
This is a big problem because course had claimed that his relative apparently his
Wife
Cousin had been successfully treated by dr. Mendelson
Well she didn't actually have stage 4 cancer though
So it's fine
Because an imaginary dropped doctor can absolutely treated imaginary disease
In fact maybe that's the only type of doctor that could do any good
So this is the story as it's laid out in the Daily Caller article
And I don't have no idea what's going on
And Coursey is claim that he didn't make any money off the GoFundMe
All I know is what came out in those stories and you can make up your own conclusions about whatever level of Griff you think is being
Run here
Whether or not course he knew what he was doing
Previously when course he was suing Mueller this story in the Daily Caller was used as proof of Mueller leaking things to the
Press to attack course
This is something that had to have come out of the closed-door interviews with corsi
Now that they're suing Rodger the claim is that Rodger used his connections at the Daily Caller and its friendship with Tucker Carlson to play
Plant the story to attack course
And here's the thing
A move like that wouldn't surprise me one bit from Rodger
The claim it is just saying that it's the case and there's no evidence at all
It seems like
You know we've already talked about this business strategy just to make accusations and hope Rodger Wilco
It's like asking a bunch of like frivolous it did you go to the store earlier
I did you go see a movie last weekend
Did you kill him
You almost got me there I got to say noticed
So it comes up in this
In this deposition that Rodger was fired
Buy Infowars and we know that from
I made this
Oh I know I know
And so
Where he's assertion is that he got fired because he started talking
You s*** about Corsicana mono
Why were you fired lion
There's no way I could continue to speak
I had wished entirely consumed with my defense
But you have been on television
TuneIn Radio an issue
Other than with
Very occasionally
A lot of other things other than the occasional
There was
Not a chance that I was going
Continue wedding for Worse
Cuz there wouldn't be enough
Material
You were fired for
Remember words
Because of
She said on it from work
Turning doctor
No that's
Categorically
Expose them to adjust
Got to go.
It disturbs me is just saying things
Yeah
Weird
That's not good now
So anyway
Next clip
Larry accuses Rogers sending Goons
To coursey's house shocking revelation
About Rodger
From 2000
The problem with all of these has that yes Rodger totally could have and
Probably has done that in the past
But you have to have something to back it up you need that
Of course he did s*** like this house
Oh no bottom
Have the proud boys whenever I don't know
Could you ever send
Categorically positively
Good Samaritan
To the contrary
Resent it
Movie.
When I was
When you representing the in the
I told you about some
Would fit in them
I don't recall
And you told me I got people that can't
I have no memory of
That one it's like I said I don't do this
How do we know that
I'm asking you
And I told you not to do that that's
Completely false
What what things are you talkin to
You have an early evidence that I sent people to Jerry corsi's home
Presented let's see it where is it
Categorically false
So I guess he's saying that he was going to hit people who wouldn't murder Tom fitton back in 2000
Or at least I guess intimidate him or beat him up or something
But that seems to be what he is
Dancing around applying here
Is it true why didn't you say something sooner OU Noah
I don't know
This is it just seems like this is terrible this is such an exercise in Rogers saying and every pot
Possible way
You
Don't
Matter to me
I don't care you know why I don't remember you
Cuz you suck and you're beneath me
You mean nothing I would have left
Already but this is kind of amused
Insulting you so I'm going to enjoy what time I got
It does feel that way
This next clip put your mic down for this just because
I think that this kind of gets to one of the larger issues of the
What what claim is put in fortnite is it like
In order to really
Have
Like a financial claim
You have to show how Rogers actions
Negatively affected
Larry tries to
Make that point here but how this clip ends is like
It's awesome it's
Rogers lawyer finally being like
Come on
So to say that we are working with
Robert Mueller is
To say that we're Genesis
I didn't say that
What about you
Barbara Jordan
I'm not responsible for the statements of Deborah Jordan
I never told her to say or not
Not say any
That you're aware that I should mow around
I did
What happened you lost
Going through the courts
Read about it
You're aware that
On behalf of course he think that's funny
Michelle least I did something for my client sitting here you know during the trial and it getting them Invicta
Your next question is your lawsuit was dismissed
Go ahead
You just couldn't resist bringing that guy into bringing the lawyer in NYU laughing
Watching two little boy fight without trying to get Dad involved in there in a little bit
DoubleDown
Are we doing
These are grown man
It is
Weird
This is Jordan person is another
Barbara Jordan
She's another alleged
Person that that claim it is saying that Rodger uses an intermediary
To push these negative stories to defame
Corsi and himself
With it we again just with the implications because there's evidence
And that you know whatever that's different story
But I don't see any of it presented here at all
Answer there's another journalist that
Larry thinks
That Rodger is using as a fence any plans to depose them
And Rogers AR
Good luck deatherage journalism
What do you
What do you think you're doing
He defamed coercing me
That's your version
What will find
Good luck
Why did luck
You wanted to pose a journalist about their source
Good luck
Were you sore
No but I see you want to ask
You can ask her but she's not
She does not have to answer any
Regarding
What you're saying is you were a source to the media.
Boss categorically false
You are now
Billiards
Continue
Is how human would respond
That is so funny so in addition to the planting stories accusation there's also
Accusation that Rodger
I pulled strings at Newsmax today Larry klayman off
Being able to speak on newsman
Okay and I think that it sounds a little conspiratorial the way that claiming is
Is pitching the story
And then it deteriorates this again complete derailment
Return to the email
Dated
June 1st 2019
6:15
To Christopher Ruddy
Claim into PDF
From Rogers
Correct
Where you write to Ruddy claiming assuming Maybe
Because he alleges I've been
Interfered with his
I don't recall have
Have you ever
Discussing this a******
With you or Clemente
Clearly
Now
Who's Clemente
Dementia is
Well he's there anymore but he was there Direct
Program
He work for Fox News
I believe that's correct
I know you don't have any medical background
12.1 mix
Allegations
That I had interfere with
With your being interview with Newsmax
On the basis of no evidence
However
Having never discussed it with Roddy
Or cardillo
Or Clemente the only people I knew in his
Yeah it's pretty crazy
So you crazy
You made a allegation
Time Medico
Insane as I think a colloquial expression but when someone
Pulls facts out of the year for which they have no evidence whatsoever
Guessing
Because you're unhappy that they can't be interviewed when
Yeah I think that's pretty
Bring me that since a Newsmax bring it on someone
Fairbanks
Call Mike like or cir over and over I have you would have to do would have to ask cuz if he
People Newsmax
That I didn't make any
Recommendation or decision to admit
Fairbanks on the air
I have no impact on Hulu Newsmax
Chooses or does not choose
Cardillo sending out tweets
Support of you and
Dubai buddy but I don't tell him what
Tweet
I don't tell him who to interview
He has First Amendment rights like everyone else
2 + 2 equal
Doesn't it
And you have nothing
Larry evidence
Evidence not guessing on your part was nothing nothing
You're nothing
Real quick you can hear it very lightly Rodger said
Do you know that's where if I was Rodger still in Florida be like
What your clients argue that this will be over
If you want to keep insulting maybe I will just end this new running back the judge
Did you call me a b**** that you're acting like one
Acting like what
A wild guess
If you have some evidence that I communicated with Rowdy
Or cardillo or Clemente or
Producer
Anything by interviewing
Nothing
Ask a question
I do like I do like are you medically professional enough to tell somebody that
I'm not saying you're insane you're f****** crazy
Make an assessment I'm speaking in the vernacular the colloquial
So you know hey I'm not thrilled with you know people just got here acting like a b**** I think that's
That's cool do you know that's a little Antiquated a little inappropriate certainly but Rodger is not a great guy
I don't expect him to have that kind of
Position on it
I would say that Larry's is weirder
His position on having that said to him cuz they take a little break and they come back and
This is just
Weird
Mr Stoner in a few minutes ago you called me
A b****
How should you acting
What is
But what's the point of that
I'm not going to answer the question tomorrow
Come on ass cuz he requested Layman tarrasque
Let's let's
If you use it there make attacks on me and when I respond you don't like
But what is entitled to know what you meant by that.
Is that someone who's gay
Stop no it's not it's not is not a slur of any kind barraging
Please knock
Mister claiming lawyer search
Is that really what you think it means come on go ask your next question
I'm asking him what he
Answer the question
Regarding my
Elementary
That's
Just
Your old lawyer good God that is that is funny
What's that pressure release a 27-point of like when is somebody going to say
So earlier we heard
Larry put forth this idea that
Rodger was trying to plant these stories of Coursey and Clayman working with Mueller because they
They make her money off conservative circles
And that put that portrays them as the Judas Iscariot riding that cripples their livelihood
Kauai
Kinda thing
That Larry is trying to do the same thing to Rodger in this deposition
You're worth it the judge
It's at on the climbing Monday process
Confusion was
1 Gloria
Yes I wasn't yours I was not a fan of her
You're aware that she was recommended
Barack Obama
Re-read
I didn't know that
Specifically but I knew she was endemic
I don't have a very high regard
Nor do I have a high regard for
The Georgian the way
Your weather
But I don't know why
You're aware that
Yes I did
She's romances
Yes that's why I want
The president Department
You're aware that for two and a half
Years
They were Carson
Yesterday was outrageous
That's why I wanted the president
Believe them
Did you find it
Inappropriately
Never take any
That's an outrage
Not going to discuss
That feels like an attempt by Larry to paint Rodger is being not committed to the right-wing cause
He would take apart and personally from Trump for himself
Outraged the Trump wouldn't pardon the Bundy
The first problem here is that there's no evidence that Rodger wasn't mad about the Bundy situation
IPic
I would assume everything I heard it.
The second problem is that in July 2018 Trump did pardoned Dwight and Steven Hammond
Ammon and Cliven Bundy their cases ended in a mistrial
Even in jail
The people surrounding this you know
First Bundy's the Bunkerville and then the
Malheur wildlife
Those standoffs like
They're not in prison yeah that's that's Larry's talk
About II
Yeah sure
Northern Larry normally I wouldn't think too much about something like this and I would just ignore it but so much of Larry's argument about Stone
Seems to be about how Rodger was trying to use Outlets like Infowars a Newsmax
Just me or him and corsi because they make their living office conservative Market
And making them talks
Stick to those Outlets
It would hurt their reach
It seems to me mostly because what Rodger Saint Larry's Saint doesn't make much sense
But this line of questioning feels like I'm trying to do that
Same thing to Rodger
Phantom is a turncoat to
The Bundys noted Heroes of The Fringe conservative world
This deposition is so far off the rails throughout that I don't really feel like it's too weird to suggest that might be the motive for that
A question totally plausible
The only other motive I can think of is
It's just to try and
Win an argument with Rodger Stone because he's under oath
And it's not going well for Larry
So
We have a couple more clips left
This one is pretty funny
Larry
Ask Rodger about little
Little news item that came out back when he was running for Senate
You remember when
You were
As you put it
Consultant
Vaguely was quite a while ago
You remember that
There came a point time
When
I was going to the airport
Dulles
Cats yes I do and
That I was.
Detained
I believe I recall that you were detained because you made some joke about the
The cat
Not having a ball
You were my Kim
Champagne
Consultant
Yes
And
You release that story did you
Jim defede
TGIF
City of the Maya
Harold after we stopped
I most certainly did not
Then Michael Caputo
I have no knowledge of that whatsoever
And you have no evidence either more of your
Taking things out of thin air
You really I would anybody make a statement a joke about a bomb while going through TSA
Chose me
Judgment
Questioning
For the u.s.
You haven't shown a lack of judgment with regard to you
At what point is Rodger just going to be like
Do you want your f****** computers back what do you want what are you f****** want
Pizza yeah
Can't believe you would bring that up
Image of a ago I made a joke about my cat not having a bomb when I go through the TSA
It's story you leak into the brass 60 minutes ago. I didn't well then your friend Michael Caputo
Do you have any proof of anything
Supposed to
It is very stupid man holding a grudge 4:30
Larry wants to go back over a lot of
Stop Future these things in the affidavit and Rogers
Is not having any of it
Is how things end
We have time
The review
Biography biography and all of your asinine claims
Because you're an egomaniac
I'm just not going to do
If you have a specific question
Well-known
Well now
I'm asking you you can take your time go to a paragraph by crap I already
We went we went through this yes
Wait until I didn't ask it that way
Yes please do
Alex
The judge myself about
How to do a quick
Before you're just hard.
Stop mr. clean
You tell that to 7
No further questions as I can end this
So much
Teddy like
Oh we'll see in court I'll talk to the judge myself
To the judge
Group most of this like defamation
A lot of it like some of it is stuff that Rodger said on Infowars or on social media
And then a good bit of it
Is things that are being presented as things that Rodger fed
Do the meteorite the stuff that Rodger said
Is stuff like
Things that are very easily just like I was my opinion this is protected speech.
Here's what I'm doing I'm saying you suck in different more colorful way
If you just want me to say you suck
Then boil it down to you suck
So there's another lawyer there who asked Rodger some question
Right here
Sure okay after clayman's done he comes in and asks
Rodger about these other instances
Cassandra Fairbanks story
Newsmax
All that and look how easily this is this is handled
Are you wearing in the complaint
Corsi
Stone
Cordello's
Baldin
Are there allegations
Regarding
Cassandra Fairbanks
Appearance on
Are you aware that
Were you aware
In advance of January 30th
2019 that
Fairbanks WIC
Going to appear on
Did you discuss the possible appearance of Cassandra Fairbanks on Newsmax with anybody at Newsmax
I get around that time I did not
Crystal ready
Did not John Bachman
Cardillo
Did you discuss with anybody Newsmax
Better about that time presenting anything negative about Jerome corsi
I did not
Did you encourage anyone to do Smacks
Jerome corsi in a negative light
Did you ask anybody else
To contact Newsmax
On your behalf
To encourage them to
I did not
Let the record reflect that this Witness
This is a bar is a bar license is under attack in New York for his cereal
Very professional
Got to get it in there I think all that he was
Aiming to achieve
Would have been achieved in a minute
Other lawyers that deposition should have lasted at most 10 minutes
Those questions are being asked to Rodger which he's answering directly if you have evidence that he's lying
Got him in a lie there you can present your evidence I do have proof that you did speak
I told her to write this article
You want me to bring up her potential nude pictures of actress sleeping with Julian Assange gives a s*** here we have an email
Hellsing that you talked to a Cassandra favorite do you remember sending this email that's a good follow-up question
Not a good follow-up question
Did you know that Cassandra Banks has nudity photos on the internet in this deposition you do not need to workout
Motive you hated me because of the 2004
Run
How does it
6 hours when a good lawyer is like
What we got nothing in about 5 minutes
That's one minute
Insane
Part of it is because Rodger likes to fight
What kind of
What kind of bulshit law did he learn that
Jets on TV log that's what that's what somebody says when they're like let the record show this Tuesday
The Sovereign citizen type of likes let the record show that he's convicted of
Everybody already knows band record does show whatever he's been convicted of
40 * Atwood did we just start recording
Man
I don't know it's it's interesting to me on this occasion of Rodger you know being sentence
Yeah it is nice to let you know that he had a last hurrah
Direct one more time before this.
Is 8
I think Rodger and employment are both bad like they're both bad actors
We care to scale them or anything really does demonstrate like the difference
Between having it and not like has it
Through this whole deposition it's like
This is how he gets
So many people everybody knows he's going to stab you in the back but it was charismatic and he's funny at
He can throw some zingers out and if you feel like he's on your
Team you're like
Yeah we can take down anybody and then you get stabbed in the back
Like that's the siren song of his like Rapier wit and
And it sort of cruelness like a funny meanness yet
Is
You being very easy to get sucked into
Thinking that like this will never go wrong
Evidently mom MyTeam have you seen what good he can do for people on his team
And they just
But I mean it's also because you know
Esdeath
I don't say that you might Sue
So I will be back on Monday with another episode but until then we have website
We're also on Twitter
We aren't hers that knowledge underscore fighting that go to bed Jordan
We're also on Facebook
We are in the new like download so please go to iTunes or other podcast apps download rate leaving reviews
You donate be the whole thing
Absolutely
We were back but until then I'm Neo and Leo on dzx Clark I keep my money and gold bars
Holding