Air Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge B
Knowledge fight
Nick.com
Hey everybody
Jordan Jordan
Have you ever take
Martial arts class
Maybe a little bit but only for a very short.
What time what was it
I think it was Judo like my brother was he took Judo when we were much younger and I think I tried
Tried to get in on the act a little bit
It wasn't for you that you were at
Did you even watch like Kung Fu movies or anything like that Bruce Lee guy
What are the things in my household
Growing up was that my parents were
Freddy
Like
Controlling about media that we watch
Another was very like the things that we're at all violent kind of
Frowned upon not really allowed in the house o
I don't know if it was like a heart
Fast rule against martial arts movies
Things that
Was like something
Something in my dad's in prison
Pass the Light District
UPS on that's
Maybe a Monty Python movie or or something
We could watch like Mystery Science Theater and stuff like that
Stuff that was made fun of satellite of love
Alright
A big party
My grown-up
Martial arts
Can you even think his list like three Marshall
Corrupt a Taekwondo
Great
That's that's your Steven Seagal right there
That's not the
Yeah I don't know it's not the martial arts
Discipline involved is very
You know high-level
But
My body does not like
You got to get hit
You got to be the one who gets thrown sometime in early on
Falcor
Wow that's what they said about skateboarding 2
How to fall off at board
I don't know much about martial arts
You know how when you drink booze
You get hungover
You know how that's a thing that happens I take it Alex
Israel hungover
No experience
Describe is an Alex Jones hangover from that Rodger deposition
Just did the sweetest of
The Divine juice shore shore and then come back to Alex
God
What night having so much fun and now I'm miserable for the rest of the week
Do you like
Why can't it always be like
So it's it's
Caliva it was a tough
Dial transition by deposition
Opposition if it were possible like you
If there were enough
Source material of Infowars people being
Deposed
Percent
Dating is like they're happy have to be there
Answer questions and that's a really interesting dynamic
But so what I thought we would do today is to go over
Actually intended to do a bunch of days
Stop possible for February 20th 2020
And the reason the reason for that is that
That's the day that Rodger got sent
Seems like it would be good idea to see how Alex took the news
Score was going on on his show on that day
I should say that I also prepared
Couch or Sundays
It show we're not going to go over there
It Bears mentioning something and that is that Max Keiser
The guy of Mexico
He was on
And
Alex endorse
Bitcoin
It's not
To be ecstatic
What's it like
I don't know if somebody is real secret like
Alex was having a conversation with him about it being bold 2.0 and
It was a much more Full Throttle.
Ultimate venom
Ever heard him give he's always been very skeptical and suspicious and pick one
And I it was
In your hand
I wanted
To cover that are at least mention it because if
You'd see some signs in the future of things
Related to that it's good to know like oh Max Keiser was on the show now
We talked about
Somehow I like
Going to start his own Bitcoin exchange
Change or something like that
Alex Cohen
Death
Not good
Get into the 20th here is a rangy
Episode there's a lot of real serious b******* going on
You supposed to sign up with
The first Joseph thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Next Anthony thank you so much
Thank you so much
Journal policy wonk
Tony thank you so much
Not sure how apology walk
Tim thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Next Citrus flavor with
3 hours thank you so much you and I'll probably want
Citrus flavor
Marc's
I'm a policy wonk
3 hours
You so much you are now it's
Technocrat
Heroin
Freakishly large
Mangler
Sports.com
Appreciate
We start off the show on February 20th and that of course we have advanced
Knowledge of this early cuz we're looking at it from
The future
So he knows that Rodger Stone has gotten 40
The sentence was 40 months
Alex start the show off with a prediction
Effects of the judge is going to throw the book at
Swamp creature Amy Berman Jack
Call Boyd camera
Rodger Stone
Nicole show trial, political
Creature of tyranny turnaround
In about 30 minutes
79 or 11 years their commissars in town
YouTube
Not for nothing
Alex is instinct
Sparta macroscale or bad
Microtel
Really bad
Just about all of this stuff
Something
Disease that is instinct
Most of
The beginning of this year
I would say a large portion
Owen Shroyer is there at the courthouse
Waiting for the verdict
And
Alex and him they they try and do a little bit of an interview or Alex's
Talking to Owen
Looks like on the ground
But Owen starts getting heckled by people
Completely deteriorate
It's one of the more surreal things
I've heard
Transparently publicity stunt Ethan
I've seen Alex do it in my time covering him
We have a little bit of a dissection here were there actually
Having a conversation
And Owen is out of line
They are seeing a signal that she's about to come back from Recess
7 years
It sound like she's lenient and gracious
Seven years I'm predicting
Owen Shroyer
Call Alex you know it's it's incredible to because this is an obvious mistrial
Just based
Technicalities
The jurors committed crimes
Incel meaning
When they lied on the jury questionnaire
What is queso
He's talking about the jury forewoman Tomeka Hart has become a bit of a target for right-wing media and their desperate attempt
Rodger was found guilty and is going
Well that's what
Globalists
Oh dammit
Recent episode we talked about how Mike cernovich was pushing this theory that she had not disclosed that you'd run for office as a
Democrat during jury selection
But as far as I can tell this is not been proven in
And anyway
All the proof survey Choppers is the fact that she had run for office
And that one of the questions potential jurors are asked
Is a favor ever run for office
This is not an indication that you lied response to the quest
There's no proof that answering yes would
Disqualifying there's nothing here
All this amounts to is an argument the jurors are asked
She had run for office
She was on the jury
Therefore she must have lied about running for office
The logic is full of holes
And without any proof this is just people talking
Miss Hart has been the target of such vitriol that a fellow journey and Seth cousins
Came out and spoke with USA Today about how shity
It's always
He said quote
The irony here is that Tomeka Hart was perhaps the strongest advocate in the room for a rigorous process
For the rights of the defendant
A making sure that we took it seriously and looked at
Charge
Cousins went on to say quote without her in the room
We would have returned the same further
And without looking as deeply into the evidence
I'm firmly convinced of that
I went in the right-wing media theory that Miss heart lied when being questioned is based on nothing other than their supposition
You heard that being echoed by Norm pattis
When he was on Alex's show last week
He hadn't even read the
The transcripts but was saying if
She's not disclosed
It would be a cause for
She didn't lie about it
There's an article in the hill published on February 50
Can you put includes this line
Quote
The brief examination of the hearing
Shows that heart dip is closer ties to
The Democratic Party
Us
Judge Amy Berman Jackson
Asking first political history would prevent her from being fair
And heart assured her it would
Most of the non head right-wing propaganda sources I can find a really
Clear that Hearts background was brought up in her fart here
Potential bias was established by that history
And Rogers lawyers had every opportunity to
To question her
And to eliminate her from the jury
If they wanted to which they didn't do
This is just sad s***
These people are so desperate to defend Rodger that this is the level of Defense they can come up with
Speculating wildly in a response to question
It turns out she answered honest
Also not for nothing
What Owen is doing is directly accused
Heart of a crime
With no evidence
To support the app
Accusations
This is dangerous territory for a guy work at a place that he's drowning
In definition plants
It's just another girl
You would have thought that his time working with Rodger on the War Room would have trained him to be a little slicker
Nope
Turns out
Can't copy that
Not the
Such like
This is just like
The Baseline of any Democrat on any jury isn't
You're not allowed if you're a Democrat you're not allowed to judge
Anyone ever because you're evil automatically
Functioning
It is not Trump lovers
Can't judge Trump lover
There isn't there is a supposition of
Inability to see
Past
Political belief or whatever
They are enabled
Ucpath
That kind of situation
On Willow
Oran
Tell me what you're asking for is essentially
And ending up with like a split
Judicial system
People with different political beliefs
We have now
Well GIF images not be based on Ray
FB
That's fine
So Alex wants to defend Rodger and
Like look at it stuff
It's just because
There's a lot of evidence that he did the things he's accused of
And some of those things are said to really
Threatening messages to Randy credico when pratico said that he wasn't going to plead the Fifth
Alligators
As you know I hate when you make threats
Towards someone who's going to go testify
It kind of tends to
Lend the idea that you're trying to threaten them into not testifying
Oh that's just how he signs off on all his texts just like hey Mama it's great to talk to you
Next time I see you I'm going to murder your dog
Anyway let's have a great time bring up the dog things because Alex he actually has an explanation
Oh no
That we're not considering okay
Forgiven Stone and that he didn't believe it
Dog
Stone the judge says
I'll take that dog away from you if you're not feeding it enough
Attacking credico
Alright Alex
The f*** out of here
Really surrounding contact with Rogers threat to take that dog away for you should not support Alex's claim
Did we set out of Rodger scooter parties concerned for the dog's diet
The text say You're a Rat you're a stool you back stab your friends
I'm so ready Let's Get It On
Soccer
To give some context to the I'm going to take your dog away from you
Rat You're a Rat that's what you've been feeding your dog
YouTube
What is not feeding your dog correctly but stabbing your dog in the
They don't make Starburst
Respect Alex singaraja talks hipocratico but that it shouldn't matter it's just locker room talk
Serbian attempt to spin this with
In the realm of reality
This week should man
Alex really expect people to believe that Rodger was concerned that Randy wasn't feeding his dog enough
It was going to take
Take the dog for its own good
Science
May be ashamed of himself try to pitch something like that
Yeah
Your dick yes
Alex's talking about randy
Credit Karma
And this situation
And he says a few things
Define
Circular Leon
Settling
Credit Karma
Why have you been talk
Randy credico
Assume to interfere with another trial I don't know if it's certainly not appropriate
The idea that a
Witness in Rogers trial will be having back
Channel communication
I'm not actually sure that is happening
But if it is I just wanted
Put this in the episode.
Alex is claiming
Illegal
It's now on the record Alex's that claimed that he's admitting contact
With a witness in stone trial
Text Alex
Has been sending him dog food just have a higher-quality
Is a great guy in this earth
So Alex says that he's been in contact with credit going to like that
Stockbridge
He said something else
This cookie
This could get weird
Back and forth
Got dog and I now just makes it terrible is happening
Stone
LG
I shall look for him to be on the show
Today what
The judge to throw
Rodger directly into jail today
Another bad prediction
And
Randy credico Alex is going to be on the show today
We have a special guest coming up
He frequently while having Owen Shroyer co-hosting with him
He's making calls and like disappearing wow
I wonder I wonder if Randy credico is going to show up on this episode
Paw Patrol
He also might just
Actually not be talking to him but like talking to Rodger
Just friends or something because Tyler Nixon one of Roger's personal attorneys
Is does show up
On this episode
Delilah's shed
You know
You get to
Get this weirdness on Infowars
Sometimes
Sometimes you just hear things in your life
Like when Shroyer
So Alex is talking about how
Trump is going to Pardon Rodger that's grey
Sure
In discussion of that
You talked about other pardon
You might be confused when you hear that
Get clemency
1 hour
Plane flying home to Chicago
The power of the executive of the people we elected the president
Wheels RV
Judges
Anger the out-of-control systems
So you might think it's weird to hear Alex be pretty okay with Trump pardoning notoriously corrupt
Former governor of Illinois Rod Blagojevich
Danny is a political
You be right
To think that was weird
It is
Very weird
On the surface it seems like
Very opposed to
Blotto was a democrat in the most
Roughly Democratic state in the country
Part of the same machine that he thinks brought Barack Obama into the world
Like this is not somebody who our to be pulling for
Do you always have to remember that Infowars
Is weird
Sometimes they have position
You wouldn't expect
And that is the case with Rod Blagojevich
Would almost guarantee that if we went back to anytime we're Bogota vich was
Governor at some point Alex would have talked
Endless amount
Chat about how he should be in jail
Well possibly but not after he got arrested
Cuz according to Infowars lure
Blagojevich wasn't arrested because he was trying to profit off the filling of Obama's former senate seat
Flagrantly corrupt action
He was taken down because he dared stand up to the Bank of America
Images of
Part of the Federal Reserve System
If you f*** with
You end up like blogo
This narrative is based on the fact that on December 8th 2008 if it's restricted government agencies from
With Bank of America
Until they were stored credit
To The Republic windows and doors
A factory in Illinois
Bankruptcy
Whose employees were staging a sit-in
The next day
On December 9th
Lokoya vich was arrested on his corruption
These things happen
Close to each other in time there for a causal relationship has been established
And therefore it was a good guy was just trying to fight the fat and got screwed
As always on Infowars correlation not only equals causation
It doesn't even matter anyway
Is there going to say whatever
The Infowars narrative makes it sound like Blagojevich was trying to permanently sever relations
Between the state of Illinois and Bank of America which is absolutely not the case
An article on Infowars says that he made a quote
Declaration that Illinois would no longer deal with Bank of America
That's just silly
It was a negotiation tactic he was using
To try and save the factory employees
Articles from the timer really clear about
Like this one from December 8th in The State Journal-Register
Governor Rod Blagojevich has
Stop doing business with Bank of America to pressure the company
Need to help workers
We're staging a sit-in at the shuttered Chicago plant
Lokoya vich says Bank
Scott Bigelow money and should provide lines of credit to businesses
That needed so workers can keep working
The employees were staging a sit-in because they were informed they were going out of business with no notice
And they didn't receive pay or any
Ultimately Bank of America announced the settlement on December 10th
Where they would create a fund of 1.75 million dollars
To take care of the workers who owed back pay severance
Vacation time and whatnot
This achievement was possibly help by Boulevard
Which is action but it was
In any way it was
It was not
Affected at all
By his arrest
The real win was because the workers stood their ground
And because the
The sport of the union electrical radio and machine workers of America Union
Anyway Infowars is super anti
They don't tend to get into
The details of the action
Will story
No they protect a preferred
Just pretended blogo Exile Bank of America from Illinois and then was arrested
The next day because he was a threat to the Federal Reserve
This is how children tell stories
And that's a level of s*** that we're dealing with but
Explain why Alex
Really okay withdrawal partner
Seems like something that would not make sense
Involving Blagojevich in Bank of America
I didn't even realize that until I looked into it
Why
I just don't understand
You don't understand
Although I think it would be very funny if we woke up cuz there's a Bank of America
Beer Works
We literally just walk out everywhere walked down the street and it's shuttered with giant blogo
It's less about like kicking the Bank of America outage
It's more like
Estate agent
Can't do business
The trains would still be open
I like the
ATMs
But
It was all just
Negotiation
To help workers that were hurt by the
The downturn in the economy
The bailouts
Yeah I know
Simplistic
Now they're not great
So
Alex's school with block
Shark
No reason Chicago.
Will Owens out there
Courthouse
Up to this point it's been going okay
Alex and him have been talking
About how Rodger got screwed and chopped
The inevitable happens
And
Other people get involved
They're trying to harass me right now
Rodger that
Posey was convicted
People for committing the crime
What
Assault
Then they said that he attacked them
They did Africa cuz the guy said the f word
F*** you there
Like I don't I don't know if the like Owen was pushing this guy for the cameraman possibly push this
This guy but the guy who says do no don't f****** push me
That's what he says
I don't know
The video doesn't show that you wasn't bush
Right I don't know what to make of this but it seems like
Hey you know maybe somebody bumped into somebody and everybody's getting mad at each other
In high because they put horses there and everybody is
Urea
So we get to this turning into a publicity stunt
Out-and-out now and Alex's just telling going what
How to do he's like
Either Puppet Master
You better get used to it
You don't on
You want to see a man go to jail
You celebrate like a Nazi
You come out here like a Nazi
I'm celebrating an innocent man going to jail
An innocent man ignore the rat people ignore the rat guy go back to the medium
Don't stop
Corrupt corporate media look at those
Do just waiting for their orders
I see there's a real fun I ready
Keep going
There's a real delicious irony and Alex telling Owen to go yell at the media who are waiting on orders
When he's giving online orders
It on its face is a little World War
So this goes on quite a while
Shame on you tell him for me shame on you in SM
Clinton pedophile ring
The mainstream music
I'm out here standing for Crews
Kombu
Alright Alex
It's like
You know when somebody's got the earpiece
Pizza and you clearly know that they're getting instructions and
You don't hear within the ear
You know this is
Both happening at the same time of your life
Is this a joke with a
Funny right now
It's the sort of things that maybe we should do from a
Visitation aspect
Just go to the video of all
You know it seems like showing both parts
Looks sad
Alex is like two overeager to be out there
Bummed out that oh it is it doing this
Exactly right like you can hear be like
Infowars.com live
Plug-In or whatever it is
F****** plug-in f****** obvious but that's what Alex is really trying to direct
Going to do
You just keep going cuz you're on a bunch of strange right now out there
For 4 minutes 3 minutes will come back from break
Platinum have that one
It's obvious when he's telling him like you got a bunch of cameras on you right now
Discovering you out there
Get Infowars name out there
We're going to go to commercial but you got to keep going
Getting the name out there
Free Press
Seriously
It does have a feel of like
The ugly
Dad being like okay you got a harness your anger though
I've been angry the whole time but you can't let it get ahold of you you got to make sure you're promoting while you're angry
Get rid of the anger
It's fake we're not trying to be angry that isn't that is a slight piece of it
Alex is trying to explain to Owen like look
People going to yell at you
Ignore
Don't worry
Cameras
Camera
So they go to break and they come back
Edit turns out that Owen
He left that area and found another press gaggle
Owen Shroyer
Another
Figure out where to go here
Cameras
The cameras are watching important
This is
God but doesn't have like a levers and pulleys
The arm go up and down
This is the way that monsters
Respond to things like this like he doesn't give a
The f*** like I mean obvious
Rodger Park
Situation
There's a lot of media on this
Yeah this is a prime opportunity for Infowars
It feels like it's this was Rogers
Funeral
He would be like
Oh no it's terrible Rodger
It is for you to scream Infowars
What he would really
She was a soldier
The first hour of the show verdict comes in and Alex ghost
Directly to Fox news coverage
Go ahead and actually cut to the
Fox News live feed
So what was the actual reaction when we found out it was three years and four
Not anywhere near the 79 years that originally have been Prosecutor's recommendation
Defense team breathed a sigh of relief stone
What I'm reading here and it's also
Usually
Before the judge
For their sentence
Given that Opera
Rodger stone is not someone that shies away from comments or the
As we know so
Mitsubishi
He'll say something
We still be under that guy
Carson now given three plus years
So you have a situation where Alex
Started the show with his prediction is going to get 7 9 11 years and they're going to take him away in handcuffs
All of this has not come through you got
A little over 3 years
Probably not going to serve even if he doesn't get a part
You'll still only be in for like a year or whatever
So that
That fail
He's like
The globalist swamp wants to destroy this man that failed
You going to be taken away in handcuffs
No he wasn't
At home
Preparing to go to prison
As we speak
So that predict
You complain about
You are
There's always something
No matter what whatever prediction
Fails to materialize
There will be some way you can take the narrative
Yeah that's all
I have a
Great I love questions
Alex can't possibly think he's
He's innocent of the
The charges
So he has to think that
What what Rodger did
Wasn't illegal or if
Or if it was
I don't know I think I think at that point when you're asking that asking me to assume
I don't believe
That
He can think
That Rodger didn't do the things that have been demonstrated that
Be possible
Difficult
Look for me even Rodger
Tell him that he
I'm trying to trying to assume like
Whether he thinks that like he did those things
They should be illegal they are illegal but it's cool cuz he did it for a good reason
Difficult to believe like
He didn't
Send those messages
He didn't lie to
Investigators
And that's why all of the defenses end up being like well this juror lied
Cave in prison
No one's disputing that he did this s***
Rodger
So Alex has now been out there to galuppi's camp
And in that clip you heard
Throwing it to Fox News and he brings up
Was just on
The Fox News Feed
So there is an
Increased
Traffic
To Alex's website
And of course just naturally as we've seen whenever these things happen that are
Relevant to Infowars world like Rodger being sent to prison
People TuneIn
He's a big spike in traffic
Any babe
Likely like you expect
Ladies and gentlemen
We have
Gargle Saturday
3.4 in 1 oz of that is going to be selling out
Very very soon
Viruses
Well
I also fish oil has vitamin D3 in it we have one of the highest qualities in a burpees for the ultimate fish oil that's an Infowars store
It goes on he just has a really long
Because there's a really long plug for supper
I think it's in the middle of the hour to like I didn't seem like very much
Okay we've got eyes
We got eyes on this get to get along plugin
So does that goes out to Bri
And when he comes back
Back to yelling at Owen
About what
This is America
Which overdrive them of the Truth Exposed
You're doing a bad job
So much like
The next thing you're going to say is alright fine I will be there in an hour
I'm getting in the teleporters
Bed bed real quick
He's really like self-promote while he's out there
Come out here for their consolation prize
Kangaroo trial that totally supposed to destroy themselves everyone knows they had America
Tell him that he's been gagged but you haven't taken still looking
You're taken to watch your show he used to be your co-host
If you want
You better continue watching The Warriors
It's just so
Walking clear that
Is to get
Eyes on the Sun
Product
Promote
What it's like
I would have responded meditation
Weird old white people escaped from a mental institution
Kenosha
Clearly exhibiting Behavior
Behavior
I said nothing
Bass
This is real TV and radio
He wants to try to humanize them and talk to them they do
Do you
You're in front of all the news cameras for Rodger he's been silent t-shirt
The people there
Ghost
Find info on someone
I get out your child is using fentanyl take it away it's another bad and they don't hear me
Speak to the news cameras
So very weird things were your kid about
The primary issue
Here is the like
The Infowars correspondence
Who go out on the field as a brand
They have a specific thing that they're supposed to do
And Owen is working across purpose
He doesn't realize
Because I think he thinks that he's like a legitimate
Maybe he thinks he's good at what he does I don't know
For whatever reason he sees
Engaging with people who are telling him he's lying about stuff is good play
Yeah it's not
His brand is as like the guy
And yelled at Jerry Nadler and got taken out and they got hurt and he was going to be in prison forever
Yelling at the impeachment stuff
That's his brand yep he's a strong young man
He is not
The person who maybe looks incapable of arguing with a crowd of people
That's weakness yeah that is not good for Owen Shroyer Owen Shroyer destroys
You can't do that in a live feed they need those videos to be produced where he does actually run into somebody that he just
Troy's menu
Can package that send it out great
Works with the branch
Talk to random
Strangers
In this case you just needed to be defiant
A voice yelling truth to the
Cameras cameras
Your brand is
The Defiance guy yelling at these cameras
You try and get out of your lane a little baby doesn't work for Brandon
Doesn't work for marketing
Stator f****** Lane y'all at the cameras
Alex
Keeps keeps getting distracted
By people who just like you suck
Why is he
This is how it always works
Never engaged
Capers
No more coverage from Owen Shroyer
And then actually end of itself
You're doing a great job but
Capers
You're in front of all the camera talk about Rodger colas
It's just so obvious man
When you
You have both sides of the Earp
Pieces
Overtly
What you're trying to
To do this is a stunt this is publicity
Stop engaging
Do your job
I'm very sad
But
Does manage to find Rogers
Sporter in the crowd
Who's this fella right here with Rodger Stone
Enrique tarrio
What's up guys what's up Infowars we're here
It's not a random
Rodger supporter
That's Enrique tarrio is the chairman of the proud
Oh that's not
Keeping score Oz accusing all the people there
My God where the people mad at Rodger
They're all AstroTurf and therefore has some nefarious unspecified purpose
I would manage to find one person there who supports Rodger and happens to be the leader of a street gang is associated with Rodger
Who happens to own the T-shirt shop
It's sold the Rodger Stone did nothing wrong sure sure
Seems like there's a whole lot
Conflict
Should be pointing out in relation to interviewing this person
Supposed to just presenting them as a random supporter Rogers from the heartland
He's a real
Whatever
Bulshit
Decides
You found a guy who can talk
Go ahead interview that guy I'm going to take
Owen talks to Enrique for a little bit
Calvary is there
Cavalry
Yes it's time for us to take calories
We needs it we need to get off the
Are you been on his show
Run for office I'm running in
Jordan's 2017
Take a break
So somehow the irony of this
Entire interview is lost
On on
He's talking to the leader of a street gang is out there it needs
Get more active
Cavalry
It's legitimately not tie these dudes insist on pretending that they're in anyway Journal
Is operating as more or less like a
PR firm
Crypto monarchist
So he gets Oreo is running for a seat in the house
Has he mentioned in that clip there but there's literally no chance he's even going to make it through the primaries
However
He did answer survey questions about his candidacy for ballotpedia and I found some of it pretty Illuminator ride
You're the list of people that he admires and he looks up
So you got like Martin Luther King Jr Winston Churchill
But you know who else is on there
Jack Pacific
I get hey maybe you like him
You did not admire him
Zero calculator Martin Luther King
I think we know which ones he actually cares
Martin Luther King Junior with the guys pretend Comet Ping Pong pizza with scary
Exactly
So he was asked her what
Media someone might take him to understand his philosophy
Antonio's answer was
Quote the death of the west by Pat Buchanan and Atlas Shrugged by Ayn Rand so he's fun
Great that's a guy want to talk to you in a party and it's not good
So he was asked
What do you perceive to be the USA
His greatest challenges of the nation over the next decade
His answer was quote partisan Division and the introduction of socialist policies in our
As for the partisan division
The leader of a right-wing street gang
And he was physically present
Unite the right rally so he can straight up
Himself on that count
That's when the Socialist policies being a problem in the future it makes me wonder if he's campaigning on getting Social Security
I wonder if that the Socialist policies thing is just
Talking point the fun word for him to safe
Successful and popular programs in this country's history
I'm guessing it's the talk
I'm going to go with that
I also have a strong suspicion that Enrique tarrio is running for office
Get back on Twitter and PayPal
For the house you can make an argument that has programs
Election meddling
Tommy Robinson in Sargon of akkad tried to make that argument when they ran with you Kip
And I believe Laura Loomer has made similar attempt
Get back on social media
Whatever the motivation do this dude as
No chance
Even in the GOP Primary
So anyway I do this interview and Alex comes back
Caesars
Jones has a message to you
Rodger stone is innocent and will be pardoned you are losers you have
We have a message from Alex Jones
It's a real show of faith in your employees when you don't
Haven a bad one
Is a lack of a show of faith when you do micromanage
We have to guide all their decisions you save this for me
This means you don't get address
They're able to
Do the job
And not just that but
God if you know you're going to get
It's so many more
Because of this.
Then
As important as it is
Is to try and sell their
The other big perhaps the biggest thing you should be doing
Putting on a f******
The people are going to watch
Tomorrow right you know like put on is showing people that like oh s*** yeah
I want to continue watching
I think Alex kind of knows on some level that like he's going to get whatever
Maintenance or like a retainer
It's more important to do a smash-and-grab robbery is supposed to
Your confidence scam
People are going to see through it
It's just just take
Take the Money and Run
So he's done without actually like the
The show some headlines
Of course we're going to end up getting into the Coronavirus
But you have some other stuff.
Now the ATL says the Senator Ted Cruz
Judaism
That you're at your other a Nazi
Really
Pretty amazing to see
Oh I see
Good stuff helping yourself at the end whatever
Alex is taking it real hard to Bloomberg
And it's really interesting because on the 16th be Sunday episode that I wasn't too
A lot of that was anti-bloomberg stuff
And I think Alex is maybe getting into the possibility the Bloomberg is going to be the candidate
Really going hard at him
But what I find super fascinating is like the critique
Could I see from the last
Real
Turn Alex's
But Alex can't make those
Critiques of stop-and-frisk
It's all he could do is be like
Hi what's the run your life
Soda taxes
That's all good well I think the actual criticisms or surrounding is
History of racist
Personal racism transphobia homophobia at these things are far more
Salient
To see him attacking
Far more impotent in it then
The people who he
Globalist
Yeah it is
It must be a struggle because when you're looking at Bloomberg next
To Trump your ear
Like his real decision is just like
A bigger a******* in each louder
The Arts
Stop. That's the other thing too
You can't make too many
Complaints about Bloomberg
Text because you support some outfit is that
Sexual harassment complaint
Bring up points about
You don't want to discuss
So it's weird.
They're about
Attacking Bloomberg play
Whatever
Anyway ddl critique Ted Cruz for tweeting out a suggestion that Mike Bloomberg quote owns the media
Which of course is
The classical elements of a Semitic rhetoric
Conspiracy theory
In this case it's kind of a tightrope
Needs to be walked if you don't want to
Mike Bloomberg
AutoZone some media Outlets
AutoZone
Yeah yeah I don't think anyone get too upset if you want to discuss how the fact that he does personally own actual Outlets
Mike Bloomberg
How that could happen
Actual effect on the cover coming out of it
It's really hard thing for me to believe the people who work at Bloomberg feel completely free to cover Mike Bloomberg from an unbiased
That's an
Acceptable things
The Voice concerns about
Ted Cruz was doing was suggesting the Bloomberg owns the media not
Specific Outlet
This plays into the narratives that have deeply anti-Semitic
An organization like ATL exist in park
The point these things out
Not call Ted Cruz an anti-semite
How to take advantage of a teachable moment
People could learn today
Express things better
Unto these traps
That have been used to store clay for nefarious
Absolutely
I think that you know you just see backlash about it
Alex
Wonder why
Is Ted Cruz
Bloomberg on their media outlet that is a
Damning and diaper
Like you should not also own an own anything if you're going to be a present
I don't know I don't know I don't know if he had comments then just the tweet
About it
I think that the two
Ted Cruz made
Closer
2 pointing out the
Ownership of Bloomberg that it was
To say he owned the entire bag
The phrasing of it and the way it was
Expressed
Was
Not great
Certipay
No I'm saying you hate Jews
Anyway now we get to some coronavirus stop
This is dumb
Scott it's gotten to the point where I wish they would solve
The coronavirus issued just for me
No I don't have to figure out
Speaker audio there's a cruise ship whereabouts people have been quarantined
Diamond
Princess
And excessive
States
I'm going to shift gears when you come back into the huge coronavirus development it's killing people on the cruise ships now
Multiple crochet
People are dying that means it isn't High
So here's some information that I absolutely never tell his audience about the two people who died on the Diamond Princess cruise ship
Japan
What was 87 year old man with a history of bronchial asthma
The other was an 84 year old woman who also had an unspecified preexisting
These deaths are very sad and I don't mean to minimize them but demographically they are the sort of people you would expect to see dying from a virus like
People in this cohort of the sort of people you expect to see dying of normal flu
Every year
There's just no way around it people over the age of 80 with underlying medical conditions are too much greater risks
Something like this then I healthy
30 or 40 year old person is
Unfortunately the cruise ship evokes all sorts of mental images that Alex can use to sell more fear about the virus
People trapped on that boat they're running out of food
Getting laid off
In reality they're about 620 people who tested positive on that boat recording
Out of the original 3700 who were on the
Cruise
For the 14 days they needed to be for examination
Anime release
Sent on their way
It's not an ideal situation are probably sucks to be quarantine
Resume a luxury cruise boat is not the worst place ever
To be stopped yeah I mean it's a lot better than the plague ships
To use the pool
I wondered about that when I wonder if it's bad taste for me to wonder about it
I definitely would be the shrimp
That's just that's just a problem
So we got a situation now where at
Alex Rambles about that event
He's just a foolish
But
He comes back from break
To the song
Breaking the law breaking the law
Breaking the law
I don't know what he's talkin to
It's a little bit longer but it's one of his where he turns the song into part of the
Like pieces of this he tries to time it for the choruses and stuff
Professional
Rambling
Skills Rock
This is convoluted
If you can make sense of this I would appreciate it cuz I
In 1984 to 1770
You're listening to The Alex Jones Show
So I might as well
Civilization
Chivalry
Hard mean things I didn't lie I didn't cheat I didn't steal that
Came out of long bloody decade sometimes
Millions dad and I promise never to do it again
Darkseid
Live live as free men and women and not live under
Conquest
Iron City the Destroyers Elisabeth Barnes ladle
Turn loose the great spirit of human
Freedom by passing limited laws
The family and the individual and those that love God
Continue to break the law God's ball common sense
Natural law everything they do is about saying men or women and women or man and
There is no right or wrong
Breaking the law breaking the law
Alright
Tyler Nixon
Lawyer
You can't talk about
Metro Zoo
Butera Dixon likely do
I don't really know exactly what he was getting a
But I think he felt it
Yeah I know how he got the spirit
I guess
Chivalry like holding doors for ladies you talk about it like in the nights by the way like
Right but I think
I think we're jumping on
Which side is breaking the law
Very very liberally
Tyrants
Are defeated by people
Who break the law because the tyrants in
Institute
Right but then we have to make
Limited laws
To rain in the tire
Which those laws are not weak
Strength
But the Tyrant thinks the laws are weakness their front brakes
Laws therefore I must break law
Who's the one who's good at break
Technologic jumped out
I really don't know I think he lost the thread
Maybe the beginning I would say at the beginning
I would say the moment he started
Screaming breaking the law he was like I am loving this car is Lovett
Got to try and work it in there and then he's like wait no I'm my guy is now the one making the laws
I'm not positive I'm not positive that this requires
A ton of analysis
Outside of just like
I think
This is something I like to bring to the people
Because
You know lately there have been more of these like
Full songs
These sort of lectures over really feel passionately
It's kind of nice.
Symbolize a little bit
You talked to Tyler Nixon and like I said I don't really care
I'm it's not in my interest at all to listen to Rogers friend be like Rodger got screwed
You like that immediately after playing Breaking the Law Electric
Who's here to talk about Rodger
Bridget
So are you get done talking to Tyler Nixon it's not very long
Alex finds himself a to pick
Visitors news
About to Coronavirus
He's got cover
It's so big
It's such big news
I'm tired of this
Something horrible
Covering something this
Covering something this serious
Just mixed in with everything else were covering
Doesn't feel right
The viruses I look at the scientific papers
And I just
Breakfast
Are you done
We decided to show you
Before I came on air
Double-checking
Double Dragon potion
The military when it's got to go to your door
Tell your son
It's got
This is not an enjoyable job
But
I don't blame Trump he doesn't know who he's hiring or what he's doing
NY discover all this then I want to research every point
Exactly right
That must be so easy to do whatever you want
Virologist that experts and then and then I'm correct calling a virologist
Alex
Where is here
It is absolutely
You're sold out
Can I spend an hour
Morning lieutenant
Again
Call John what shows you've seen with experts in the night
The Shadow
Don't feel confident
Talking about this
Because I might make a mistake
This is weird and it goes on forever
And
Is a story that he's trying to get to
Just blurt it out
It's it's all in service of what the end
And we all know what that end goal is
I just a mom
Homeland Security
Show the Chinese virus
5 years ago about it the scientist
The biggest Publications out there
Then I read that
I found all the papers
And I'm just like
I'm not a violent person
Coming on Erin just talking about this is not a normal response
Father-in-law
Things are so horrible
That you just can't make it one more footnote
So bad
That I
Really muster my
Will
And really do some planning on how I talk about this
You always
I just can't
Is that what
Doing all that research yesterday
Really
Why the hell is our government doing this
Trump didn't do this then
But the guy he's got running NIH was involved into the time
They are attacking
If I don't tell people
That folks doing that are violent towards everybody
Running around with suicide vest
False flag
According to you yeah they didn't
Become something
The president
Really
Under the US government did this
Restaurant
How did they know they had this and out of there
There's some big stuff going on here and so that's why I'm
Shaken I just
It's so big I don't want to go off half
Cuz I'm indecisive person
Wheels turning
Figure out exactly what I can do
Damn you
I asked you Jordan who if not everyone
Coronavirus news
Google does the lead into a plea for money
If I'm being honest
I think it always snows
The products he has to sell the relay to the outbreak
Kind of sold out
He's made a bunch of money off this financial
To cover the virus news
For my help fear standpoint
Does coverage in the future
Probably going to lean
More towards the political intrigue
As we see kind of Happening Here
This article that you stalked
About
The scientist
Are the Daleks reference in the clip has nothing to do with Obama selling a virus
The Chinese government
It's about a guy named Ralph baric who's an infectious disease researcher UNC Chapel Hill
Chimeric Coronavirus
It kicked off a debate
About how
Involved
It's a debate goes on within the scientific
Community
Right rice fairy article says that the US government halted all Financial
Funding from the federal level for research like
What's known as quote gain-of-function studies
As it relates to influenza stars in Mercy
But simply to adding a funk the funk
Open of a pathogen
Giving it an added function
In order to better understand
It's a Direction with the world
That's host
It's long been a hotly debated question if he sorts of studies or ethical given the potential downside
You have our
Practically in calco
What I want to do
Guys
Hear me out give me some money for
I want to
Make sure that smallpox
Is 100%
Fatal in order to study
How fatal it would be
If we release it into the greater population I don't think this is a bad idea
Give me one batteries that's a farcical take on what these studies are but
It's
Add something
To this genetic level in order
Testing
In 2015 the scientist publish an article about this
This guy at unc-chapel Hill function study on a Coronavirus
But it's definitely not the same virus it's currently breaking out
From China
This article is not a study doesn't fall the study conducted by route
There's no chance
Even if it has nothing to do with the current situation
Legitimately seems like it's out is only primary source on this and nothing in there says or even implies that Obama or
Homeland Security saw the virus
China
In fact
Explicitly says that no federal funding went to that study
Nor any like it released the two years prior so bomb had even less to do with this
Alex has had his phone with a public health
Panic sales drive but his heart isn't in it anymore
The natural choices to make it a political thriller but I
Also realize they can't pull that off of that total
Sing
Complicit with releasing a bio-weapon on innocent civilians
Kind of in a tough spot
Yeah that leads him to just like
Cover this on a surface level with a
Can't cover this I'm going to go off half-cocked
Buy Homeland Security under
Obama
The scientist lab Maine Coronavirus
The creation of
Disgusting
Can you read the article exactly
Oh really
Blame you
And I got all the papers
This clip came at the end of like 10 additional minutes of Alex being real insecure about every can't cover the virus news
Any proximately half an hour of his show he dedicated to talk about how we can't talk about the virus news for mistake
He could have easily covered whatever story he thinks is the big scoop
This is performance
Now it's is playing the role of the student forgot to do there
F****** homework
It really shows and I click we just heard
There's absolutely no depth
They're at all
It's grasping at straws trying to make this somehow sound research
The headline about the lab-made virus causing
Debate is not about Obama or the Department of Homeland Security big no virus
In the scientific
Community he's completely misrepresenting that source
Instant of Alex not knowing what he's talking about number one
Alex says that if you read the article it's just the same exact coronavirus that popped up in December in China
This is not true
He's making that up
Instance of Alex not knowing what he's talking about number two
Alex tries to save this virus from the 2015 article is the same one that the Gates Foundation has a patent
Before it wasn't
Gates Foundation
Institute and it wasn't bad. Coronavirus
It wasn't identical the virus mentioned in the article in visayan
Instances of Alex not knowing what he's talking about numbers 34 in
Pet clippers less
Some 30 seconds long
Idea what he's talking about
5 *
Bizuayehu does 30 minutes on his show but he can't cover the news because he knows the shitz weak
But you can make nothing look like something with the a
Looks like this
The article in the scientist is a complete zero and terms Valley
What is narrative
Sweetly at
Bucked up about it on air
Like you can't do his job because the news is so big
That passion will sell the week sure to his audience that even trying to engage
With what's in the article or the study
I'm not trying to sit here and pretend that Alex has some guy like he's a conniving genius
But he does things for a reason
He absolutely wouldn't have a job his audience stop for a second to ask themselves why he's doing the things he
He's doing every now and again
Trying to gild the lily
I hate being
Split so much
Especially when it comes to this cuz it's like
We do the show
I see you
Hours upon hours upon hours of research
And it sounds like the way you
I don't do any research
That sounds far more similar to the way out
Right now doesn't that make sense there then you're sometimes wrong and I can plan out generally
I'm even the stuff that I can do is imperfect
Baked like I'm I'm wrong every now and again we certainly try our best to
Cop to that
Attending situations
Particularly surrounding like
Fine points of the law and science
Inability on my sleeve like those are not subject
But I'm well equipped
Read stuff over and get a good so
Sense of it sometime
Like today I can't actually consulted a specialist
To get
We're going to end up discussing
But
It's important
Like
The recognize that like yes
The way Alex speaks about these things
Is indicative of someone who doesn't know what he's talk
And all you need to do is
Listen to someone who knows what they're talking about and that's not necessarily me all the time
The difference
What's between
Let's say an expert
And an Infowars expert
Big Apple
It reminds me of the way that he's doing
As to whether he's selling the stuff reminds me so much of like
I was I remember working with one of those Road hack
Headliners
At
Club in Aurora
And I
I could not understand
Why this
Chilling
Because he was
Garbage
And then after one of the shows
He came up to me
You know what your problem is
You're not
Selling your joke
Man you got a really
Selves
Even if they're weak
If you sell the jokes right
You can get a lot out of it
90%
Facade
Since maybe and sometimes not even that
Stop
Fool's Gold
Yeah do you want a life being a shity headliners
Edsel yolks
So Alex has decided that the u.s. older virus
China
He doesn't know and that's why you need to fund Infowars Court enough to figure this out
I guess
It's so stupid
Is this offensively stoop
Why would the US Shale this to the icons and then five years later it's released
This is big is what I'm saying
I don't know exactly what's going on but man
My brain is like a computer
It hasn't popped out
Add my gut my spirit my brain never wrong always
Bielicki
Pictures
Is it bad
How is it
Soccer
Is just
To set the stage
For taking over Taiwan
I don't know anyway
What
Your hand is up
To set the stage for taking
For China taking Taiwan or United
States
Chinatown
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm getting bogged down in the wrong because everything is very convoluted
Some of it might become a little clearer as we go along with some of it absolutely want
Some of it is dress
Nonsense
Breaking the law
We we learn something here while Alex has been pushing this narrative that the
Canadian lab the one in Winnipeg is the source
Stop cuz there was those two Chinese
Expelled from the lab
Turns out
That might not be true
New age of the new millennium
This is something that's going to kill you and your family and make you have a heart attack and make your lungs bleed out
And it.
Ugly socks
That's why meta
Physically you all are concerned
Because we know all this distance
And it was produced in the United States
Disinformation
Chart
Did the damn thing in plain sight
Oh s*** turns out the can of stuff with misinformation
That's wild because I have a ton of coverage about how the virus was stolen from that lab in Winnipeg on Alex's show from Alex
I just trusted experts like the health Ranger Mike Adams
That can't possibly be the case
God is never wrong is Right 99% of the time so there's no way you would spell ridiculous
About time on the show trying to spread conspiracy theories about that lab in the past
Oh no it's misinformation and disinformation Dan that means that it was
Targeted and it was on purpose
So it's not his fault that he got it wrong
But his gut was telling him not to go with it but he went ahead with it anyways because
Belpres
I'm passed out like you got tricked by that
Contrite
It's not like you saying I shouldn't February 16th Hoosier
Just last Sunday
Let's listen to a little bit of that
Everything Mike said
2 freeway
Like what
Number for Humanity Lone Survivor
Alright fine only as an excuse to keep these
Apocalypse
Predict
So here we have on Thursday
We have Alex saying that the Canada stuff is just misinformation
But on Sunday
Here is what he was
I agree with you
What has changed in the last week
I believe this was also deliberate release
So that's interesting
It's under for Humanity
Introduce
Asian twerking
Virology lab in Wuhan
The guy who ran that Canada lab being killed he was killed
Is that
So this is conspiracy theory about that Canadian lab where the two Chinese people were taken out of the lab back
July
That was Doctor cool and her husband at kidding
Chang
Now if you come to the present-day CTV News reported back on February 4th that a man named Frank
Plumber National microbiology lab which is the lab in Winnipeg
I passed away at the age of 60
B7
This is a very sad story
Did you actually read articles about his passing it.
Look like this was a murder or even suspicious
Switch Alex's definitely trying to
Imply
CTV News
In December and December plumber share details of his personal battle with alcohol use disorder after undergoing
Experimental brain treatment to treat
He told CTV News how using alcohol to relax after work progressed to a habit that saw him drinking up
220 oz of whiskey a night
Leading to cirrhosis and end-stage liver disease diagnosis
In 2012
The stress of responding
Pandemics
Unable to stop himself from returning to alcohol after
A24
Team Liberty
Ended up getting that experimental procedure done B was a it what it is it implanted electrodes
His brain
It turns out that that did have some
Positive effect on his desire to drink
That's Ed
He clearly did it was a kind of Drinker who have done serious damage to his body by that point
What's good
You can stop drinking but you'd already had cirrhosis and liver transplant and kept
Very very sad
It's true the plumber was the head of the same lab that these two Chinese scientist from
The plumber couldn't
Anything to do with that situation since he left his position in 2014
Citing personal reasons
Most likely the severe alcoholism
This is sloppy s*** on Alex
Deep disrespect
The doctor plumbers Bass
Everything I can tell you is a fantastic researcher who struggled with
I'm heavy demon
Only to get his life back on
Contract which is in
Aspirational
And also tragic
Conspiracies don't care about people
People are things
Mere props to be used to make narrative sound more convincing to the audio
Who are also people who don't matter to the conspiracy
The people listening
D2r just props
To spread the narrative
This is all very disgusting
And it's
Call Alex's talked about like all these
Dehumanizing aspects
Global Life
Take a second to think about him
Treating this doctor's death is
A mere prop to be thrown out
To support
The Narrative that the virus was stolen from this lab and in Winnipeg
She's now seeing this misinformation of me or couple days later
This is what it takes
To be an Infowars believer
To take a shower of seriously you have to believe that a guy who tries to use a doctor's death
Conspiracy on Sunday
Is that all that
Canadian lab stuff was misinformation on Thursday
You have to believe
That guy is a good source of information
And someone used truck
So yeah it reminds me
When troyer's likes it all this
All I'm doing is
Taking direct orders from a guy who says he's right
Percent of the time and it's the only one who
Can save us from the tyranny
Members
So we get back to I just want to take a little diversion there to here
It's a little bit of that from Sunday to be like you were just talking about
The Canadian lad stop
Go f*** yourself with this
Always all misinformation 100
I was wondering like
Why
And actually the what
What's a ended up
Change it
It relates a little bit to that article in visayan
Also
I got to weigh in
Alex reads
On a back on
February 20th
Smoking Gun China bought
Weaponized Wuhan virus from us
Just a headline that Alex is reading but he never gets the contents of that article
That's probably because the article doesn't have anything in it for him to read
It's just an Infowars article with Francis Boyle
That's
Is reporting on his own interview just reading the headline
I really don't think
That's okay
It's dumb and I'll explain the main argument over here in a sec
But first I wanted to play you this intro for that
They admit they originated an incredible job
Do you think it was done on purpose
Understand who stands to gain he Bono as a as a law professor
Who's who would do their who stands the game
Clip of Alex talking is the
The cold open of the clip
Hilariously the way the video is that it kind of sounds like he's asking who games Coronavirus
If that's
Completely disgraceful Behavior over the last month or so it's one of the best jokes I've seen on this show in a while
If it's not it's just their subconscious might be trying to
To tell them something
As for the Smoking Gun
That's just Francis Boyle
Pretending to be science
Here he is laying it out
Talking this next
The
Smoking Gun here
Page 11
Near the bottom
Paragraphs
They provided a function
To be Coronavirus
Spreading inhuman Papi
So let me
Before
Dana funk
Ocean Technology
Is DNA genetics
Engineering
Dangerous
Biological warfare
Substances
Begin with something up of already been pathogen
Turbocharged
And
Zeta function work
Only be done
Safely
In a bsl-4
Or a bsl-3
Facility
So icy
Clearly
This is
The Smoking Gun
Zach the Wuhan Coronavirus
Came out of that
Bsl-4
So does boreal is found the words gain-of-function in a study posted on sciencedirect
Facts about the 2019 Coronavirus
Which is ultimately going to be connected to that 2015 article from the scientist
Berghain a function study on the Coronavirus
Price on a Coronavirus
These two must be the same thing and I study
2015 was clearly the cover for
The creation of the virus that is now in Elk
I can see how this game is probably super
For fun to play use find words and ideas
Really stoop
Francis Boyle is a lawyer he has absolutely no background in science
Any really should not be offering opinion
About this
Because when he suggests
That they're being a gain of function in the 2019 Coronavirus
That's a Smoking Gun proof it was engineered is bioweapon
Sounds like a f****** dumb dumb
The function studies or studies were pathogens are given other properties
To test their response
But that's not the only use of the word
This is really indicative of boil not even doing face
Research on the topic
Because if he had he could have learned very
Quickly that gain-of-function is a
Category of mutation that happens
Naturally
As is loss of
When that sciencedirect article is talking about there being a possible gain-of-function in the 2019 Coronavirus
That makes it more spreadable
It's talking about natural mutation
Could set it apart
From other viruses and it's played
This is a little bit outside of my pain from a science perspective so I consulted with an expert on these matters who maybe insist that
Should I not call him
Explain to me this 25th
15 study was looking at stars
And was based on a prediction that in the future
Viruses like it would become less picky
About 82 cleaver
Study that they augmented in existence existing sars-like virus in a way that would make it more red
Cleve by an Ace 2 receptor
The goal was to evaluate the risk of other coronaviruses that were circulating in
Populations
And what we needed to prepare for
Or if this mutation to ace2 receptor livity did happen
Gotcha gotcha
Conversely the 2019 papers and now is
An analysis of the current Coronavirus
Which found that there is a mutation that has occurred that allows the virus to plead with pure insight
Which is intrinsically differ
Done the work they were doing
15 study
In effect
The finding of the 2019 paper invalidates
Hypothesis of the 20
15 study
Which is to say that the prayer study
Predicted the future sars-like viruses
What affects humans due to changes in
Ace2 receptor
Where is the
This paper is asserting
That was incorrect
Current Coronavirus
Possibly as widespread as it is
Because it by
Passes the difficulty of H2 cleavage altogether
Going to fuel in route
Instead
Some scary application
Inasmuch as it is a simpler process
Could make this virus much easier for people to get
It's not all bad
Is it this is in case this is the fact
How the
2019 coronavirus is taken in by the body
They're already a ton of treatments and preventive drugs that could be effective against
Pure and clear
This essentially opens up
Ton of options
For medical treatment
If this paper
Is shown
Perfectly
Alright
I have no business discussing the nitty-gritty of this hardcore science stuff
To put it simply
These two papers are nowhere near about the
Even if
The 2015 study
For proof of the
The creation of a deadly bioweapon
It still could not
Possibly be the same virus
As the 2019 Coronavirus
Changes to Ace to cleavage in that study
Literally nothing
Things to do with the furin cleavage
Which is the discussion about the Coronavirus
They're two completely different things
Whatever
Gain-of-function was being disgusting at unc-chapel Hill thing
What is
Fundamentally imprint
Musically different
Then whatever mutation is being
Just because those same words are there that's
The connection that's being made
Okay that's why you don't listen to Francis Boyle right about science related
All right so if I understand this correctly
Based on what you
Describe to me the 2015
Team paper in stock
Talking about a stew cleavage
Which is something that is less
And something that we're not as prepared for sohee so they the study there
Was trying to figure out
If this is the way that it mutates then we
We need to be able to
Prepare for a stew
Be an even leaving the sites
Describe me in three between population
So like something that would bind to simple.
But the Cleveland is not
Something that would be taken in by Ace to receptors in a bag
Let's say is not the same as would be
Taken in by humans through the ace2 receptor
So there is differences there
That cause
An inability for one
To effect
Different animal
Okay
Is
Testing if
I do it was easier
Could humans be susceptible to other Coronavirus
That were traveling it back to munity
Now all of that is irrelevant
Tuesday
Mutation that's being disgusting
2019 paper
Just recent
20/20 vision
Trisha
So you would know the
And I would never behave
Like that they weren't going out to show and helping Miss inform people about an act
Public Health crisis
This is just
Depressingly bad
Or maybe
Maybe Jordan
I'm being real prick
There's something more to this
Maybe boil clicked on all the authors
In the 2015 paper
All their names
Maybe you found something suspicious
And it has all these people there from
University of North Carolina
It has someone from the Food and Drug
And then
The very bottom of the list
Who is your mouth
Obama
Lishi
Special pathogens and biosafety
Institute of virology
Chinese
Roof on
Unclear to me
That this
Scientist
Institute of virology
This
Jay North
Technology
For SARS
This University of North Carolina where
No
This is very interesting
From the study which is ridiculous both
You know if you actually read a study you can learn what individual contributors did for the study
It's in the contributions
Now you can't they just to list the author's note
Clearly she provided some materials that were
Need a name of the sequences of the Coronavirus
They were studying
Just left a matter of getting something from the
That's why they got a credit on the final study
Seems like such a lazy job
Completely missed there's a second person on it from Wuhan involved
G-Eazy was also an author on the study and
Doesn't seem to realize that
Also if he's going to say that anyone on their studies automatically somehow suspicious
Why is he leaving off of another author that was named
Was antoniou
From The Institute of research and biomedicine in Zurich Switzerland
Shouldn't I be a sounding off
Coming it's not
Because I'm certain differences Boyle didn't uncover the
He decided on a dumb conspiracy website needs work
Let me get credibility by virtue position is this guy who
Rhoda law
This is all the fingerprints
Lazy conspiracy site because they missed the second researcher from Wuhan
This is what happens when someone scanning name two Seas one that points towards their preacher
Conclusion that says good enough
The dum-dum go by there
Yeah but it'll print
Yep there's nothing fundamentally suspicious
Is about a couple of Chinese researchers having co-author credits on a paper that has to do with the Stars like Coronavirus
If you don't recall the country has a bit of a history on the subject
It makes sense there be a possibility of collaboration
They had history
Decided never to worry about
The coronavirus like Behavior ever again
There's nothing
Fundamentally suspicious about that
So far I See No Smoking Gun
I don't even know if I see a gun without smoke
No I I see an emperor without clothes
So Alex asks
Man this is Google.
Google
By the way.
Stay right there
I'm reading the paper
But I'm just now reading it
What
And
You talk about Smoking Gun this is the Chinese government
Paying for the exact same thing
U.s. lab
Know how did you discover this
How the hell
You finest
Philadelphia
Alex
I told you
It's part of my professional responsibilities
Stay on top of
Google
So
Came across it in my research
Are the Joplin
Alex says that
Literally means you reading it
We're just simultaneously a bad way to interview and a bad way to read
Second boil is giving up the game
If you watch the video when he's describing how he found this information you have a little smile on
Myspace
That you know all of the day's work
O'Shucks
Just what Heroes do stuff is horseshit
This is a man who knows he can't tell Alex where he got the information from because if you did you would instantly reveal that he didn't do any research
He just started on a conspiracy blog
Weirdly an article covering very similar territory was published on February 15th
A couple days before this took place
On zerohedge
There is this was about a Chinese researcher who theorize that the virus could have asked
Escape from the lab in Wuhan
Jiggly leash
Which would explain why boil seems unaware of the other people on that study
Boil is not a scientist
He does not keep up with scientific journals
Is just a conspiracy theorist who happens to teach law
If you read some dumb s***
Probably on zerohedge
Now he's playing the role of a genius researcher who cracked the case without
Also
That part about China paying for the study is because Boyle of cherry picking
Stuff out of the acknowledge
The study was partially funded by an award from the national Natural Science Foundation of China
But now I kind of leaves off that they're also grants from the National Institutes
Institute of Aging
That might sound weird but
Probably because things like coronavirus is mostly kill the elderly
Providing treatment and prevention for it would really effective drastically improving the lives of
The older set
That's where you're missing that's where you're mistaken
See it's from the
Institute of DEA
Right there trying to get rid of old people that's why they
Created this virus
Scope tell italics
Real answer for Francis Boyle
Where did you find this
Victor counting a bed but he does not get out
Stay on top of
Nothing
I just came across a quadrilateral research
More boil ship but I do want to say there's something particularly hilarious about this interview
Alex is going on and on about as a Smoking Gun stuff and it's got the globalist
The dead terrain they proved the virus is a bioweapon
Instead of getting into the
Specifics of the research of demonstrating their
Surface-level things like
I found two articles that have the word gain-of-function in them
I saw Chinese person involved in the study
Instead of doing any of that Alex has a plug for his product
It's really easy to use this kind of conversation to drive sales what do you know everything that's happening on your show is
Real
And that's what's going on
Because if not I want to be like holy s*** holy s*** called call everybody
You be freaking out because that's real
Gives up that he doesn't believe the stories he's telling by his
Look like lackadaisical sales
5 minutes
In the middle of this video
There's another reality that we need to discuss
And I think it might help
Explaining Alex's unwillingness
The virus news on this February 20th show
I was speculating that it's because you know
I'm sold out no real Financial motive
Actually now that I
You know I've watched this boil interview
See that he's saying that there's a Smoking Gun
The US sold this bioweapon to die all this stuff
I think he realizes he's gone too far
Oh yeah I think so the narrative is come to completion already
That's a problem that is true
This mystery is solved
Yeah it was the government who sold it yeah this is an episode
He already has the world's number one fake Authority on the science of bioweapons France
Does boiled coming on his giving him absolute definitive
Smoking Gun proof that not only is the Coronavirus lab-made
But that Alex is
Now in possession of the documents
Hulu
11 North Carolina created
Chinese government pay for its creation
There is no mystery
It is assault case unfurl the sign mission accomplished
According to the reality show boil is a credible source
Chapel Hill made China bioweapon cuz they wanted money
Problem with this is
From a narrative standpoint
There's nowhere good
Alex
And any real scientist that looks at it or any court or legal invest
Alligator would laugh in his face
So that route is not going to work
That's One Direction you could go
Trying to pursue legal action
Against the folks in North Carolina
Probably could result
Countersuit
So where does that leave sex
If you're presenting to your audience that you have
Definitive
Smoking Gun evidence of this is a bioweapon and you know they were selling it to China and it's the most deadly thing ever and well
Number for Humanity
Only be lone survivors
Then what do you think the natural conclusion someone might come to it
You need to go salt
We need to stop that do not close to the point where your audience is going to start calling in and saying hey why are you
Are you telling us to be telling us
It kill those scientists
Alex
Proven piss you have it dead to rights Smoking Gun
Why aren't you
Call the f****** cock
Snow
No no no no
Like it's a problem with his rhetoric has proven to monster blades
It's killing
Hundreds and hundreds of people and you
Crack pecans
Receipt
You need to
Call Linda Bob's now
That's
Based on
Everything that exists
Turn Alex's show that's like where you should be
So Alex is back himself into a corner with this
Sensationalism of his coronavirus coverage
According to Infowars this is a civilizational level threat
Definitely a bioweapon
And now he accidentally allowed Francis Boyle to come on in definitively name
The culprits
This kind of leaves Alex with only a few choices
One is the continue escalating
And risk one of his listeners taking him seriously and trying to hurt the folks
UNC
We just kind of a natural
Conclusion the person would have left
Another op
Directions to throw boil under the bus and say that he's
But if Alex does that he risks calling into question all the other stuff
Stop the boil is told him about the outbreak
It also risked his ability to have boil on when the next outbreak comes
And he needs to sell it survival food
I guess the third option is
This
Be a coward and ramble for about half an hour about how you can't cover the story cuz it's already installed case
The only thing left to do 4 OZ rally the troops
Isn't really really a good
Case study for why even if your propagandist conspiracy theorist
And even if it seems like it.
Appealing to dabble in the pandemic album
Break Stuff
It's just not a good idea to go all in with it
It's a delicate
Conspiracy game and as you can see here
It's not even a line that a pro like Alex can walk well
It is
If this is like a an episode of Law & Order where they
They like
Go through all the facts of the case and they solve the mystery and they're like alright we got them
Be at
Call Papa
A real problem for Alex's narratives
Like you can
You can't do that
Is it doesn't work what do you do now
You agitate against the people in North Carolina
I guess
I mean what do you do
I mean
If you are actually telling me
In real life one hundred percent true
That
You know exactly who is
Infecting
Thousands of people
Killing people all over the world
And nobody is doing anything about it there's
Two guys there who literally did this
Let's go let's go find them
I don't know what to do
Call call the FBI
It's not it's nonsensical and like there's really
Nothing you can
There is
For Alex there are no real good options
Just move on pretend it never happened
Well I think he f***** them so
Well of course he asked Francis Boyle.
Exactly what I was going
That's always Alex f*** himself over
In between space
Like I talked about it before the kind of panic that I would want is a kind of drives you to buy his product not point
Where you like
You feel justified in actually torture
Tinkerbell
Kind of
Fanaticism
If it does, he gets to call it a false flag and you can know he can deal with
General
But he doesn't want that cuz
It's worth usually
So Alex has done with this now for
For the time being
Take a little bit of a diversion
And they're down to the Sunday episode interview with boil because I think it's important
He's not
Explaining that headline be smoking
King Kong
I think it's
We need to address it
For the sake of completion with our coverage
I don't get back to
The February 20th show and Alex's back on the
Pardon Rodger
Alright Trump is set to speak on prison reform
And I'm sure they'll be Rogers.
Do you got a special guest he said Randy credico is going to be ready
I thought for sure
In meantime
He goes to call
And this caller
Color seems weird
Have you heard of a cough
Cowboy trilogy
I've heard that name but I've never what is it as a book
Trump's moves
9 year
Prophetic
Oh yeah I heard of that
I've heard of that what is
ER full of s*** Alex's
Nope
Cosmic Cowboy trilogy
Like eat just like things he couldn't
Possibly be aware of your place
I like that
What do I have in my pocket
Hahaha
So Alex play the commercial
To break
And he comes back
And this commercial is on the show
This thing
Is a new website operation win 2020.com
Shark is basically to
Just a place where people can get those duct tape sticker
Whatever the mouth
It's it's dumb he's just like we could we could take over these Trump rallies and we can take over everything with
All we have to do
Put stickers on a map
What I will need to listen
The commercial but there's one part
2020.com
Psychological warfare
Steve pieczenik
Recently sold
Steve pieczenik about this and he loved he loved
So you know it's great The Jug by plans
Alright
So after that commercial Alex gets around to his special guest
And I was like
Bucking Sweet let's get credit I love it
Imma stop right here I'm going to be straight up with
Dad this Gaston
This ties into coronavirus and I'm crazy it is and then
Weeks ago
Almost
Are the big food companies that sold out
His f****** guest is the guy who runs my Patriot Supply
It's just as food
Prize guess
Special
Cuz he has a very important message
And that is hey y'all
Prices
Going up
Crisis going on
What concerns me is where month-end of this
Going down there going up
And so you guys don't have any last night this morning
You're going to have to raise price
Little bit
Prices are going up
Prices
Hold on
Let me ask you a
Have
You and I ever done an episode where maybe Alex says
Specifically
Beds
These guys are great
Cuz they are not opportunist
Who are raising prices in the face of a
Their price for the raw material is already gone
Beaten path along eventually
Or else they're never going to
No
So Alex asked him like
What's going on with this situation
This guy
What a dumb dumb
If you notice
Or the number that are under
Quarantine in the US
King Ranch
Quarantine
Why is there nobody adding up
Truly is
Inspections number
I've no idea what self-quarantine means but I assume it'll be a figure that is
Possible to report accurately
How is anyone going to be able to really capture the figure of how many people are self isolating
Outside the scope of our research
As for the u.s. cases of the virus did do just making it up there people who stopped reporting on it
There's an article from The New York Times headline coronavirus cases in the US Route 34
There's an article in CBS News Right Here bad how many of people
Many of the people who represent that optic
From the previous figure are US citizens who were evacuated from the dime
Princess Cruise
Are now being quarantined in the United States
There has been a media blackout about this is a topic
Take a screen cover stories easily if you look for them
However if you're trying to drive sales for disaster survival
It's in your best interest
To pretend that there's a cover-up going on
Sunset
Things are way worse than they appear.
Is all disingenuous exploitation of a public-health event to translated into money
These people should be ashamed of themselves and their sales practices
Why are there any Muslim leaders condemning this tax of terrorism why none of them ever do it
You never see him do that
Time just open your
Uline Pizza
Dude
They've recognized
But there is
People who are panic
About this
This situation is probably trying to
Now they're not they wish it wasn't her
You got the boy behind the scenes
Yeah
Wig stand
You guys are like we're going 24 hours a day
We just wish this wasn't as big a
Prices
We're scared
Talk about this
Never seen anything like this
We wish we were making so much money
Freetalk
Pick where you reveal your life before you even say so
I think it's because he knows what he's doing is really gross
Self-conscious about how f****** insane League roast this is
The biggest food sale ever man
Like everybody is making a run on this food and then I was asked this guy
Why that is
This is the biggest
Brats
Partnership
I absolutely
It's because people
Don't really know but
The transformation
Are they getting lied to by Alex because people don't know
Technically I do think he's accurate information
The guy who selling your food
Also speaking of bad information
Alex keeps talking about how all these other food companies they don't even have food
They have long wait times
I called a bunch
Man
It must have been really impossible to get ahold of anybody
I called some other food companies other survival food companies
And they all have
About the same
Perspectives that this guy does
They are all but about attend
Delivery window
Up from whatever their normal Windows Coventry
Love
I did I discussed with a couple of them are like
Like whether or not they have
Food
Of course
In order for us to continue to be a business we have to do the business
You're right
Survival food companies are going
Increase of sales because of
People like Alex reception
But all of them have
I don't know I did you ask anybody that directly of life
Do you guys feel like this Panic is being pushed in your food is benefiting from
I didn't ask
That directly but one guy I talked to I did bring up that like the delay is because of
Angry sale surrounding this Coronavirus
So I think there is an awareness at least from one of the guys that I talk to you
You can't not
Where do right and I'm in hindsight I really wish I had asked
If their competitors don't have who
I was
Trying to get like a gotcha
Just trying to gauge like if I call these people will they have food
And all of them
Yeah of course
I should have asked if they cuz I'm interested in if that's
An angle that they all have supposed to just this is what my Patriot Supply is saying
I'm not sure it's a whatever the case is there
Now they all are I don't know what the other companies are doing my Patriot Supply in Alex Jones running
A f****** disgraceful
Charade
Pretending that no one else has any
Any food all that stuff is
Such b*******
Beds
The food companies
That have
Souls or something along
Minds are like
Fully aware that this is all because
Cuz of the Coronavirus
And they're not
Pushing it
They're not trying to get that Panic out there but they're also not exactly like it's not right everybody calm down
You know it's not wrong to make money off of
Creased
Demand
Wrong to artificially created by the sort of action
So they get done with this interview
First comes back
Time to get to this
Trump press conference
Is Trump is giving
Speech by Criminal Just
Now Mike down to this
Because this clipped
Take a ride
Alex jumps in media res
Live Trump speech
And he thinks
Trump is about to Pardon Rodger
On on live air
It does not go through
All right ladies and gentlemen Now Music here as we start the
Cramping a lot of stuff President Trump
Microphone on a criminal
Rodger Stone
Three-and-a-half year
Giving down by the Obama dropping
Judge
Jackson areas
We are
We are giving him
Absolute consideration
And I have a feeling
He's going to get that
AutoZone wifey
Maybe somebody else
Great gentleman
Mets first thing they said to me when I walk in
And dab
But everybody knows who you are
I Know Who You Are
11 years
Somebody completely different Trump is talking about some other guy
Alex
You felt like you had that Victory suit so tasty
And even makes it way worse
Of course
Alex
Can't deal with this appointment
Alex thinks of this speech Trump is giving is going to be where he pardoned
Rodger
Stump speech
Commencement
Are they hope for prisoners graduation ceremony in Las Vegas
Is just part of his re-election publicity speech
Or even any of the parts
Sounds like with blacko that he gave up it's just press
So anyway
In the middle of the speech
Talkabouttd
Hey
People getting out of prison
And they're good people. Maybe some of them are good people
He had specifically people out of prison it's weird can't do that
And we want to
Bring returning citizens greatpeople
People in many cases grape
People
I'm not going to be
To politically correct
In many cases
Who want to rebuild their lives they want to rebuild their lives they want to help
Stampy building
He likes people
They like sweating bad people out of prison
I don't understand how whatever I mean bad is kind of a relative term I don't I don't know what the definition of
This is such
Text like I
Oh this is
This is how you can get away with so much
Do a new evil thing
Everyday and if
Possible every 20 minutes
You can't
Possibly
Imagine any f***
President saying
I'm going to let the bad people out of jail I'm just going to do what I can be politically correct and say everybody is great
Hey I'm just going to let them murderers out and if they murder people you know what
I'm not politically correct
You can't possibly do that
Come
And so he notices
Or I guess he knows that
The audience
Of this pizza
He gives up a shout-out
Ashara is weird
And the job you do Miriam
What you've done Sheldon just
Overall is incredible
Philadelphia
Play Place
Called
Israel very much would you say that's correct
Maybe I have to use the word love but place called Israel right your case
What
The fuc
I understand
Seems weird that he's banking Miriam and Sheldon Adelson
Make a donors the GOP
Gross but it turns out that the edelson's run a addiction recovery
Place in Las Vegas events to Criminal Justice Reform
It doesn't make sense that they would be there but
Bank exam
Very weird
Unrelated cases
8 bus
To be so similar to what it was like
To live during like
85 to 88 with everytime Reagan Spokane
Out loud and everybody was just like with the internet
Yeah exactly it when you if you heard Reagan speak in those last three years you must have just been like
I'm going to pretend that
Didn't happen
Because that was
Wario laughing at Nan last line people up
Like what are you talkin about it's very upsetting
Answer
He starts talking about Rodger
Which is
Not really what this
Commence M for
Seemed strange
Do use it as a Pulpit to you know ramble about your own business
But what he does is he says that he's not he doesn't use the word
Pardon
The great power the president has just refused
Use the word pardon
He says that he's not going to get
Involved he's going to let the
The process work its way out
And then he starts rambling
About the conspiracy theory about the
The juror
But she had a horrible
Social media
The things she said on the account were unbelievable
She didn't reveal that
When she was chosen
And she's I guess from what I hear very strong woman very dominant person
So she wants
Did you get on then she became the four
Person or woman
Honda generator
I assume
A question
You have any bias Japanese
You didn't say that
Lawyers on it
But does this undermine our Fair system of justice how can you have Helen with her you finance
Delete her social account
Nope and when Rodger was
Determined
By the same jewelry to be guilty
Before the
Judge issued a sentence
And he was determined
Abigail t
And she started
Going
A little while
Very happy
And
The same things that people said that strange
That's strange and then they started looking at how can you have a jury pool tainted so badly
You can hear like slight
Nervous laughter from here
Embear
Graduation
From a rehabilitation program like prison to release
You're there because maybe one of your loved ones has been trying really hard to get their life back on track
Is a big time for them it's very
Do you get to Rican
This person and bring them back
Into
Your day today lies and
You got the f******
President
Rambling about a conspiracy theory about a juror
How do you how do you handle for Isis
This is this
Him being a reality TV show star
This is him like teasing it out like
This is literally him being like
I don't know maybe I'm the next Eminem 20/20 part yeah
F*** you
God
Really really
Disrespectful to the people who are they are for this event
So I know it's probably maybe a minor issue but it it's not for them
He does literally say that I'm not going
Which means you probably going to Pardon them
He doesn't say he's going to doesn't use the word party
Alex seems to be pretty happy by this turn of events
The insane one
Back after this
Handed to them Rogerstown doing three and a half years
Alesana
Call Jones
This is
Why the American
Compliment your health with hemp derived cannabinoid oil
It seems a bit deject
Cuz I think he thought that press conference
Who's going to be the way you can end the show
And also like everything is not going the way he want
Altitude on this episode
Complaining and
And arguing with
The people
He's now trying to do this
Big hurrah with the Rodger that
Not going
I don't know
Do that I can't cover the
Coronavirus news that didn't go anywhere
This is a bit disappointing show
So Alex is Matt Bracken taking over in the fourth hour right
What do you need like that
So he goes back to the back
To the batter's box
He's getting ready to take
Take some swings
Go to calls
I'll take a caller
That'll be great
Don't tell me I'm awesome
Unfortunately
He gets a stalker
Oh God
If it did work out any differently cuz I got a feeling he's going to be pardoned but
You should stand in the law
Mumbo jumbo
Well if you if you directly
Elven Council
Hold on we don't need to get bogged down in legalese come and get close to that
Corporation
14th Amendment
Stand up liking with the DMV like
The globalist have all these legal he's thinking I get what you're saying a lot of his crew really
The end of the day
Country bar
Values that we can deal with everything else that makes sense
Here's what makes sense
Alex can't tell this guy that that's all b*******
Risks alienating a large
Swath of his audience
So he has to play this game where he thinks some of this is legitimate but he can never really be like yes this is what you need to do
Send your social security card back to the
Government specific on what it is you do
A lot a lot of what you're saying is true know you lot of what you're saying is true give me one
Pushing back on this
Alienating the hard Sovereign citizens support that
Exist within his audience
And validating it makes it so like
Insurance
This stupid
One last clip and it's Alex
I don't know why he didn't
Hang up on this dude
Sovereign citizen
Advice
My advice would be
Go home
Somebody because you believe some things that are not based in reality
Yeah that is true
LCSW
Part of the crown
Okay
A person like me
Every week
Make a 3-minute speech
The world and I will dominate
I would start a YouTube show
Reading for stories on air
I need Infowars stories on your own
Create another Mediacom
Read my s*** where I'm not allowed to do
Also go down to city council and make yourself a public embarrassment for 3 minutes at a time and you'll
Totally destroy the city council's
What should I do here is my advice
Work for me for
And embarrass yourself in public so you're even more alienated
Into the only listen to me and the other people agree with you to break system everybody else
The lawyer
Trying to kill you
Bad advice
Come to the end of this February 20th 2020 episode and I think that Alex is doubt quite well with sekot is best friend got cents
3 years
Placid
This show sucks
Oh man
Why disappoint
I just
I have this dream in my head
I really hope
Trump abandoned Stone
Because I think
Stone might be the only ratfucker
Able to wrap
I think he's I think he's the only one who could really do it
And I want to see what
So much s***
He's got so much
Most likely yeah I do not have so much
If your
And Trump
Assumption that you're making is also what animates all of the desperate defensive Rodger
People like Alex and Owen also assumed
He knows so much and that's why they have to bend over backwards to try and create these narrative
Extend so far like taco
Carlson even plays
The same game
Some of that might also just be based on the fact that him and Rodger friend
It's hard to tell where the line of
Year of what Rodger knows and personal Affinity where that
Sprite
Blind blur together just like in a personal sense
I've like well I mean yeah if you if you're friends with Rodger Stone
The longer your friendship goes
Devore part of your friendship is like
I wish I hadn't said that to Rex and I was like there's something there
Jacob
Hell I don't know anyway
Just take that to Alex's. It's pretty disgraceful job.
Trash
Awful
But until then
Futsal
We are fighting
We are aware on iTunes
Review donate to the show to the whole
I think we would love it
Special thank you to the guy who I cannot call the health Ranger
I'm Leo I'm dvx Clerk
I'ma juiciest eiscue
Holding
Alex