Sam and Jordan wedding
I have great respect for knowledge b b
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Everybody sit around and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Jordan
Damn
What is the
Fastest you've ever completed
Like from when you got a video game to when you finish
It's weird for me because different games
Are there different
For me you know they can some
Really trigger the
Completionist part of my brain where like I just
Forever
I think
I mean Assassin's Creed Odyssey I think I finished
Pretty
Yeah
Yeah and I would say they probably took about a week
Yeah or so
The man
Over 100 hours
Assassin's Creed
Across the whole play Fisher
I'm currently playing Horizon zero Dawn absolutely cuz I went down to the the old GameStop
Anzo just staring blankly
On the wall
Dad's of the person who's working
She came up to me
What are you what are you looking
Don't know and Buehler Automotive
Just help me do you like
Crazy but they don't like that hidden like they didn't have like Homestead
Yeah yeah yeah
Ignore that second
Impart and just advised
Nope
No idea what that is and it was $9
I was like yeah
Take a flyer
It's cheap enough that if I hate it I'm not going to be mad at you so I will take that shot and I think
It's fantastic I'm really enjoying it all throw it away
Yeah I think it's meant I really enjoy this game
Very fun
You the runaround
The big
Big World Big World open
More life
I don't know
Be somebody that you would call a
Gamer I don't have like a lot of
Knowledge
Sore
Haitian in the
But if you give me a game where I can run around
There's a mystery to solve the side quest I can get completely distract
To buy things
There's variability in the things you're doing
Something times maybe your solving a puzzle where you got to go up a cliff
Breath of the Wild
I'm going to be Saturday
Yes absolutely and it sticks off all those box
Alright by Android
Like I've been playing it a little bit and thinking like eventually I'm going to be done
Yeah I kind of woke
Now there's a
Nothing else left to right now
I've been here
I know too much about games
Enjoy song
And I do know a lot about Alex Jones
We're going over to February
24th 2020 I'm down
And I don't know there's a lot of
You know it is what it is
Present-day Alex Jones
Episode
We have to go over there
Yes because
After this on the 25th
And all through the end of the week
Alex Jones is going to be at CPAC
Okay
B b b outside yelling into a bullhorn
So this is the last day before he takes off for his trip to be a dumbass
And try and get Trump attention
Just really
And probably fail quite a bit
All inclusive
Interesting stuff along the way throughout
This episode
There are a couple things that are going to
To be a little bit repetitive
And may seem a little bit like I'm
Driving a point home okay
Because
You are driving
Yes and I will get all that but before we do Jordan go take a moment to say thank you
Used books of signed up and recording show
The first Robert thank you so much you are now apology
I'm a policy wonk Robert Robbie Christopher thank you so much
Text Christopher
Thank you so much
Sade
And I'll probably walk
Journal pollywog
Didn't thank you so much and I'll probably want
Thank you thank you
Josie thank you so much and I'll probably walk
Lexus Copper Creek
Thank you so much you're now about what you want
Thank you very much
Endlessly
Enjoyable
Appreciate that very much so Adam B thank you so much
Minecraft
Heroin
Is freakishly large
Infowars
Adam B
Enjoy the show
Website.com
Jordan we start off today
Hamza on the 24th
On Monday
There was news
And that was at the Dow
Fallen
Singing on the market
The RCMP is down
Labjack down 344
The Dow Jones Industrial Average now down 924
The FDIC.
Funny guy
2 +
Pho
That's how I down 487
Down
They're propping it up
The vix
Oribe
Correction
What the reason is happening is obvious and incontrovertible
Government covered up
The true nature
The virus is now admitted that its man-made
A month ago
Came out
Totally man-made
Economy rental bunch of different
Viruses nature
The stitches on it
Literal
Injection points
Then he goes on to talk about Frankenstein and Frankenstein is stitches on its head
To you I mean it is it is a sort of natural consequences you might
Expect to see that there would be some Market
Did fearsome jitteriness based around the
Breakfast you know the outbreak is continuing to go on there's rat years of disruption of
Some international business right
You know you could you could talk about that one way or you could say that it
Proven that this is man Hasty I was I thought he was going to I thought he was going to land that one it seemed pretty obvious
AutoZone
All right we all know why
It's the coronavirus fear and he didn't say that
He went with
It's been it's been confirmed that it's a man-made virus
Is that I would not have gone
Auto Parts
Default in the stock market is something that Alex is already baked into all of his narrative
Close
This is a man-made bioweapon that got really
Right they only did that in order to
Precipitate this drop in the market in order to attack
Trump and nationalism the Fulfillment of the narrative
About
It's it's it's exhaust
But if that's exhaust
What ends up happening neck
Text is
Like
Does next level
Owen Shroyer and his security team that assaulted by a mob of drooling zombies
You talk about escapees from a lunatic asylum
People a
More insane for elevator
That's just a few of them know
Almost all of them
Where
It was yesterday in Austin
So Alex and Owen Shroyer went out to a Bernie rally and I lost into bullhorn and try and cause a scene
Mission in life zombies
In their third of business mission
And statement and yellow people
Alchemy into bull horns
Really just a sad look for Infowars
The first thing I want to say is that there's a proximately a two-and-a-half-hour video of Owen at the rally actually talk
Okay
Treating him with respect and answering question
Coherently
All of that is not in the video that Infowars really
It's not
They just ignored all that released
The four-minute video people yelling at Owen and making
Can faces at his camera clearly f****** with him
The video of people calmly talk
Owen undermines The Narrative it enforces trying to push
Matt is at all the
People at this Bernie rally a raving lunatic to Pista pants
Anyway the big news is that one of Owens
Security guards
Was attacked by the horrible evil violin Bernie's
Supporters project Veritas videos want to put Alex and his friends
In a gulag
And what act
Actually happened is way way different
Then what Alex is saying
In the video there's a middle-aged woman yelling We Love You A Towing
Prior to the incident
Trying to get the security guard
And even get through them to hug Owen which I guess you might call a salt
They wanted to try and pull that the padlock for the talk show
Shroyer to attempt to pole
Destroyer destroyed by a nice little
Expressing his love any younger man walks up and appears to be taking a bit of a more confrontational pose towards Owen it is
Security guards but he's not attacking anyone or anything
As far as the video shows at this
Point unprovoked
Owen Shroyer hits this guy in the face with his bullhorn
You just clock
The guy with the bullhorn
The problem is that Owen at a security guard
Standing in between him and this guy he just hit with a bullhorn
Do you need to reach over the security guard
Approved intense there
Is bringing the bullhorn back to a neutral position
He also hits his own
Security guard in the face with a bullhorn
It legitimately clear as day from the video which I posted on their website
Even showing it in slow motion
That the only strike that occurred with Owen hitting
Two people in the face with a bullhorn
Seemingly completely on Prop
Alright Infowars has been showing the security guards face which was bloody
And using it as proof of the violent left and how could
Conservice can't go out to public without getting attacked
Mayfield
Point out that the only thing that hit that dude's face was Owen Shroyer bullhorn
And he never would have been hurt if I want head
The guy who is the other guy in the face
Seemingly unprovoked
The worst-rated in 1984 territory we are watching
The thing happen and Alec
Alexa saying that the
The opposite happened yes
While we're watching
It seems that way
Thanks wrote an article on Gateway pundit with the headline quote
Infowars crewmember attacked and left bloodied by crazed leftist at Bernie rally
Is Owen a crazed leftist Madison to hospital with stitches
The article embedded a tweet
Samoan saying quote unhinged Bernie supporters drew blood on my security tonight at the Bernie rally
If people are radical and violent their everything they claim to be against
No matter the article about him being hit in the face by Owen weirdly
Really feel like this isn't fair I've been looking
For other angles of this video but I haven't been able to find any
And based on what I can
Can see this really looks like a case of assault
Guy accidentally hitting his own security guard in the face then blaming the guy he assaulted
For hitting his
Security guard
It's super clear from the video that
The guy made no contact with the security guys face
At all
And this is why they're not going to press charges against that dude this is one that will never ever happen
Because the exonerating evidence is clearly posted are banned. Video for the world to see
Alright anybody to go look at that video it's
Very clear
It's in slow-mo
Not fair you can
Rubberized telling you before the show that I was
Exhausted by towards one of the reasons why I'm feeling
Because it's clear if you watch the video that this is
Is the situation where
It's it's
Insane to see Owen take his bullhorn and hit a guy in the face with it and then then plead like
That can't be
Flies
And someone someone like Cassandra Fairbanks will write an article with their position on it
And and a bloodied face and it'll be attached to
This is what the crazy
Leftist to do it
It's it's
Exhausting because it works
It works
There's nothing you can really do about it
The video that just bruised it is there
It's it's there for the sea
Right
How how do you
Combat reality
Viad
I don't understand it
I just don't understand
Can say that it's tough
It's very tough
Nightmarish the idea that you are showing the video
Proving that what you are saying is false
As proof that you are telling the truth and I don't hold you accountable
Gaslighting
Yeah I wondered about that a Wonder
I think they'd like
At a certain point it might not be worth it to press charges just goes oh and hit him
Because then
I think it's like be more trouble than it's worth once you become like they have video this guy and
They're blaming him for
Assaulting the security guard
At a certain point that you're being used
To tarnish
A bunch of other
People
It seems I don't know
I don't know what I would do and I don't know I don't know if that guy bumped into the security guard before Owen hit him and
Becomes a murky
Spider-Man with a bullhorn
D.va
You definitely can see that if you want to look at it
So
This is bulshit
Yeah but
There's other b*******
Surprising
And now I just got words I was 30 seconds late getting on air from art pick national food supplier
I warned everybody it wasn't again like I told you that if you want the 14 days now it's 3 weeks
Liberate everybody else is sold out
Food
Three weeks to deliver now no
I would say that a good
Third of this
Entire episode is selling
Yeah almost
The third of it is
Just talking about how everybody's got to buy this food
You know what it's got eight
If prices are going to go up
Everybody's got to get this it's it's a disgraceful
Three hour-long infomercial
For food
It's disrupted to periodically for other top
Jesus
Jim Bakker episode
That's the other reason that this is very exhausting
Because this episode listening
Intuit with so much
My Patriot Supply advertising
That I just
A two-point was like
Am I just going to cut
A Supercut of him
Selling
It is very is very
Weird I get to its aggressive
That's not good
I think part of that is probably because he's seeing a return on it
You seeing that it's working
And so keep pushing hard on the point that
He should try the Jim Bakker have a Christmas
Easton proud of him with
Just as survival food
So Alex is at the market is taking
And Alex is really mad that
Are these people
There who are saying
This is good or something
The dams are cheering for the mark iPhone
Licking her lips
Hoping for this
This year
GDP growth that this Administration been talking about that for years he's are all things that down
You can run
And they go on for another 10 minutes
Talkin about
Talk about
If you're a Democrat watching that
I hope the economy crash
Get rid of trump
Yes
That's not what that guy said
Anyways it's also 30 more dollars for a giant bucket of food just so you know I hate these heartless two M's
It is an increase of $35 now for another bucket
I'm so sorry any credibility with his audience
But he said if that clip is it being a
TV host licking their lips about the economy going down because it'll hurt truck
But on the actual Clippers
You think I'm making a very straightforward assessment that I think is indisputable
Trump has made the economy a centerpiece of his claims that he's a good president
If you call him he takes a downturn or fails to reach the levels Trump promise
Who's the Democratic candidate could use that in a campaign
How dare someone point that out at a time like this Dan
Where's the celebrating of the economy dropping it's not there at all
He was over
Rejoice you can hear this voice
In the face by a bull horn
He must really hate with Trump himself said about the real estate
A crash
Prior to the crash she was interviewed for an audiobook in 2006 where he was asked
Quote there's a lot of talk would you have no doubt heard to about a so-called real estate bubble what's
Your take on that pessimism
Trump replied quotes
Well first of all I sort of hope that happen
Because then people like me would go in and buy
You know when you're in a good cash position when I'm at a good
Cash position today
Then people like me would go in and buy like crazy
That sounds way more like a guy who's rooting for a market to collapse in the clip that Alex
Just played
Commentator though is it
The commentator was
Just discussing the potential weak point for Trump in the next election
Did Trump was explicitly saying that the
The bursting of a real-estate bubble be good
Because he could personally make money off of
He was also holding a sign above his head
But that I am a psychopath I am a psychopath
Anyway none of this matters because this side of trump
Is the stuff that Alex obviously knows about the Paw
Pretends he doesn't
Because he's committed to prison
The good guy
This is exactly the stuff he'll start becoming a magically aware of as soon as it's time for Trump
Turn heel how fast you
He's informed of these pass
Transgression
Quick it'll be out Deluge of secret information omigod Governor Trump has mob ties
I didn't definitely say that
Oh my God
Did you know the truck
Supported redlining
Alex wouldn't complain about
So the issue is
Stayed like
Damn
Want the market
Collab
Because Democrats
Don't work
There are no democratic
Does not work
Are government employees show
Free market economy
Turn people against the Nationals Trump they'll do it in a heartbeat
Planned
By us University
That was adopted by the Democrats back in the 80s
The economy with welfare
And with people having
Comfort the right fit Donuts
That's a real thing
I on the airplane with you
So we discussed cloward and Piven in the past and it's not with Alex
Describing
It's not really a
Plan as much as it is an analysis
These two professors are making the argument that financial hardship was
Far worse
In our country than this
Statistics were able to capture
Another lot of the American public
We're suffering through things
Even though really
Was available
Part of what allows our system to continue the way it has the illusion that most people are doing okay
And one thing that would shatter that illusion is a
Everyone in this country was eligible for social welfare programs collected on what they were eligible
Beaufort
This would lead to an overloading of the welfare system and from that with the scope of the real problem
Clear to see
The government will be inclined to finally eliminate poverty by
Instituting a guaranteed income for
This plan was obviously not adopted by the Democratic Party in the 80s
And we don't have anything resembling guaranteed income
A candidate who is running on Ubi Andrew Yang is already dropped out of the race
Alex doesn't understand cloward and Piven but he knows the name and he knows that his audience
Not going to look into it enough to recognize that he's just making s*** up
As far as I can tell I was there
She's making up the claim the Democrats don't work
I'll be interested to see where he's getting that
Because it from everything I can
Until it's completely fabricated stat
He's just pulling out of his ass you haven't seen the Rasmussen polls 98% of Democrats
Don't worry professor
The other 2%
I don't know if you've ever spent your time watching videos of pelicans are cruising images of pelicans but I have and I was at 8
Unrelated lately unrelated
They are mean birds
Invite a bunch of pictures of them biting
Can kids have
Princeton
Their booty and they do not like people much
It was legitimately note
Would ever be used as a support animal
Challenge that somebody takes upon themselves just like I bet
I bet
I will bet you $1,000 that I can
Bring me to comfort Alex Gentlemen's Agreement
Fair I do think that it's possible that you can have
Like an emotional support Pelican or something like that in your house right like
A plane get the f*** out of here
This seems to be a meme that went around and right-wing circles in 2019 making fun of the snowflake
Somewhat
Apocryphal story about someone trying
Need to claim a pelican as an emotion
Child support animal but I can find no evidence that actually happened
But I can't find a tweet
From Adam Carolla making
In front of the idea
As far as I can tell it was a fake story those used
The laughter's Attica
Control
Alex is only bringing this up because of
The end of January
The Department of Transportation
Supposed to do rule that would strictly limit emotional
Call support animals
That are allowed on planes Beast
Specifically
Specially trained dogs
I checked in with the rules on various Airlines and up to that point no one allowed Pelicans
American Airlines has clear rules on their website with
Cats and dogs being allowed with some pretty strict
Wrentham place
Trained mini horses
Can be permitted as well
Kind of have to assume that
I almost never happened by the rule quote
Animal must be able to fit
At your feet under your seat or in your lap
You're very very small horse
Smaller horse than we have so far been discovered
Delta has a list of animals that are specifically restricted as sport animals that includes rodents
Insects reptiles birds anything with hooves
Basically everything
Accept cats or dogs
Southwest
Explicit and it only allowing quotes small vac
Vaccinated to mess
The cats and dogs
Inappropriate pet carrier
In the aircraft cabin
No one has a support Pelican on planes
And the Department of Transportation
New rule recommendation is aimed at targeting people they believe or trying
Magpul a scam
By claiming their dog or cat is an emotional support animal
In the skirting the fee they could
They would have to
To pay to travel with their pet
That's what they're doing to try to crack down on financial ship
Do the leftist snowflakes running support pelican
Because of cloward-piven ridiculous this is
Diculous
What kind of show
Hughes had really gotten his airline off the ground we would have been able to have Spruce keys
On all of our play
Whenever we soda
And it's a failure of being Birds
Very much
My aunt had
Geese
Terrorized me when we go visit
Is very very much time
Couple
Feels like a lot cuz I remember
Through a child's mind the feeder of the
So I think there's a hundred but there's probably like
Pet Sounds
I wouldn't have
Just cuz it sounds like a disease oh my aunt has geese
Sorry
Through it
So we get to talkin about the coronavirus situation a little bit and
What what
I mean you just got
All this is just
Conspiracy
Coronavirus
Define vaccine
Don't worry Bill and Melinda Gates already have one patented am ready
North Carolina University gave it to the Tricom
Smoking Gun
Knox
You had that out
Mama did that
I thought years ago
When it gets released
You don't know who to blame but really
Completely lost with this
Conspiracy theory now that there's a smoke
Vanguard
Yeah this is Austin
The rail because now he can't prove it anywhere else I would like you
Have to now
Keep in mind
That we've proven right
Aspect
You want to go with it
Anna gotta be like that has to be a part of your narrative
It's and it's definitely less wiggle ability
We're definitely on the de Crescendo if we're if we're on the the reason behind it is
They don't want you to know where it's
Coming from for some reason
Right
You want you got the you got the proof
It's a bit it's a bit lame
The issue to is that like we're seeing these these
Assertive flare-ups happening in countries like Italy right and it's not showing to be
That have the fatality rate
That you would be afraid of
Right
It's fine
It's good that you know we have
The coronavirus popping up other places
It certainly
Seeming to indicate they like
Okay
We're looking at a fatality rate that is
Very
Low
And
People who are having people who are in those demographics
Sitar are dying or people who are
Elderly or my pre-existing
Conditions which is what you would
Expect
It's not
The worst news pause
Right and
So Alex kind of knows that
Doesn't tell anybody that
But you need to prepare for that eventuality
And so here's how he does that
I don't believe this one
Test for a future
Population of n
What would be the Omega
Guadalajara
A decade
After that another match color
That I believe will kill about 7 billion people
Why has no-one left
Why
Melinda Gates plan is 5
Because I read it in the Georgia guidestone needs is correct
F*** you
I believe the neck
When it's a three-stage
Behind on top of everything
So we got at least 20-30 years before we even have to worry about right
This is escape hatch
Yeah this is how you get out of there when it ends up not being the
Civilizational level collapse where we end up at
Current situation where over for Humanity lone survivors
So that's coming it down the road 10 years 20 years down the road or whatever
It'll turn out that the
Next one is the beta testing this one was the alpha test that's how you know Alex isn't seriously
So are some other conspiracies that are what kind of moron
Linguist
Basis
I guess about the Coronavirus
Zendaya
This is dumb
Tokyo Olympics
Covid-19
No longer though
Coronavirus United States
So what we got going on here is the Alex believes that the globalist changed the name of the Coronavirus
Wuhan out of it which is just something he's repeating from Mike Adam
Here's Mike back on February 16th informing Alex
This Dreadful
Conspiracy
The real play here is that China now wants to
Courtney's infection
Doesn't get the blame for the global pandemic
Have no question
No doubt China
Taiwan
To Hawaii
To Malaysia Singapore Japan
So the China doesn't get the blame the already convinced the who2 change the name of the virus away from
From the Ohana monia Coronavirus
To covid-19
How to rewrite history
Even the CDC
Control
In China
To control itself
Getting to a very dangerous biological weapons
So to put it simply to help Rangers very
All you have to do is look back on the SARS outbreak of 2002-2003
Severe acute respiratory syndrome syndrome which is caused by a virus called SARS
Govt where the CRV
Coronavirus
Despite the name
Anywhere in it everyone still knows that it originated
In China how they rewrote history
It's from SARS
Outbreak they were 251 cases in Canada
Bad 238 and Singapore Bunch all over the place outbreaks outside of what everyone still understand
Dance of the outbreak originated in China
No one's rewriting that history based on
Sun shining up being in the name created the Stars by 12
Underlying assumption that Mike is making their that no serious person would ever make
Mike is acting like a public public health workers are looking to assign blame for this
Blame is such a strange word to use in a situation like the one we're in it should really tell you that Mike is not a health Ranger
You're our science rain
He's a propaganda narrative Ranger
Blame is the word you use when you're telling a story
Not when you're looking
That dealing with an outbreak it naturally
Not the naturally-occurring health situation
These dudes of drifted so far past the point where they believe it is a bioweapon that there's having casual conversations about China
Exporting the virus to other countries they don't get the
The blame for a bioweapon
It's at the point where a coherent conversation between whatever they think is going on and someone is dealing with reality
He's just impossible and that's the goal
Yeah
They are hitting Us in the face with a bullhorn right now and telling us metaphorically
Yeah also the virus was never called the Wuhan pneumonia Coronavirus
People colloquially called at the like a Wuhan
Coronavirus
Just because the city of Wuhan
It was a distinguishing marker about the outbreak
But the actual temporary name that scientist gave it was 2019-ncov
To Mark the year
Here and ncov
Coronavirus
World Health organisation guideline specifically discouraged name and conditions are outbreaks after people places or profession
Because of the stigmatizing effect that can have on things completely unrelated to the actual disease
They made it official policy on 25th
Because of
Things like how people slaughtered pigs
It disrupted pork Imports for no reason
After that 2009 outbreak
It was called the swine flu
People make assumptions based on names and it's best to do whatever you can to make
That response more difficult for people to make
Actual scientist whenever call this virus to Wuhan coronavirus in any official way
And given the Mike Adams pretends that he's an expert on this stuff and
Basically a doctor
It's basic stuff
Then.
As we all know his story
When the mob chooses escape goat
It works out well for everyone involved
And there is never been any historical situation where the mob has chosen the scapegoat
Almost it Rand
Ramping a violin
Yeah you want to avoid the he's
So Alex said talk some more s***
Talkingshit
But now the numbers are coming out we know that it is indeed
Killing healthy young people
What is killing a high number of those
So I have no idea where Alex is getting this information from the young people healthy young people are dying
From the coronavirus literally everything
Define suggest
Is not the case
Is it really big clay Metallica
Cuz Megamix it's almost all other sources I can find her pretty clear at the
The vast majority of fatalities
Better being seen or among elderly people and people with pre-existing
Conditions
I would call on him beside his Source name some
Some specifics who are these young people
I suspect he doesn't have any sources of
Which is why he never brings any of them up he's just talkingshit
So we get to talk about Italy
Here in this next clip and there's actually a really in
Interesting
The way in which Alex is wrong
About
The cases in Italy
Everyone everyone is dead they're all you have your number
You know how many survived
Right cuz that's a lie
Anyways
Coming out to play
Tricom
A beginning a swell
You can't believe a word
What comes out of Tricom mouth ago
Funny sponsors a lot of folks do
You listen
But they're all out of food right
Actually most of them are my bakery
Conservative
So we talked about specific information about the cases of Coronavirus
Better popping up in Italy at the time of preparedness episode they're not readily available so I can't really comment on what's going on there the source
Roosevelt how these things happen
The coming days will bring with them much more detail about that sort of stuff and that point
The one that happens we can have a full conversation about if it'll be irresponsible
For now though it what address Alex
Has claimed the Italy shows at
The virus is much more deadly than the Chinese government was saying
Chinese Li
Innocent is asserting that the Chinese covered up the fatality rate of the virus and now they're a bunch of people in Italy getting a receipt
Proof that there was a cover-up
Actually
The opposite
It makes sense to maintain some skepticism toward the information coming out of China so you can't really blame a person for doing that
However Alex is not just step
He's wrong
According to an article from February 25th
Open Forbes quote
Haley surprise blowout of the new coronavirus shows that
Despite the country's bursting into the seat over the last few days
Their mortality rate is similar to China
This is actually good news
If it turns out to be true in other
Countries where Public Health Data is more trustworthy
Then one can assume the China is not entirely under estimating the mortality
The latest figures from Italy
Had the mortality rate in approximately 2.6
Which is south of China's claim rate of about
3.4 /
So what this flare-up in Italy actually tends to Devin
Is it there's a decent chance that
China is not putting out
False numbers
Since we now.
Statistics from a country that has a better track record
Transparency
International cooperation
There's actually a fairly optimistic sign
Well the Alex's painting is
The opposite of right well the Italians didn't add the casualties from
Venison there because I heard that somebody got the coronavirus in Venice and they just sank it they was going
Already going under anyway so they just think the whole thing of baby
Woodforest by Alex
But the case isn't Italy demonstrate the
The China was lying about the mortality rate of the virus
He's either making that up
Or he doesn't understand the numbers or anything about the situation
And this is not a surprise he can be all of those at the
The same time
Yeah you better cut the fun
He's dumb and wrong and lying
But you also see how it all is just to serve to a food plug at the end he's just getting into a food plot
Constant
So incessant
On this episode to the point where
Give me a couple times when I was repairing this episode that I almost like I'm done
Yeah John Wick
I don't even want it
Commercial when he comes back
Well I got a call during the break and
And they said okay
He was locked in a auntie 23 weeks
But
Voicemail
DC what's going on
What you're seeing is basically my Patriot Supply reaching the point where they can
Can't handle any more orders
That makes sense
They hire temporary you know they can hire temporary
Staff to satisfy their increase labor demand
The packaging and fulfillment
They are willing to build a new Factory or plant
To increase the out
Their existing facilities are at the maximum output and to increase that number didn't need to put in a long-term investor
My in additional facility
And they're not going to do that because they know this is a
The temporary situation
Which now basically maximize their profit from
So the only other possibility here they're trying to pretend there's an actual food
And that is
Just isn't the k
The effect of them selling this narrative is there trying to cause panic in the audience
At the beginning of the show Alex that it's now 3 weeks
Good food in less than an hour later it's
4 weeks
This is the sort of behavior you would engage in if you're trying to
Cause a panic
Not if you're trying to operate
Ethical ad
I think of the way Alex old is nanosilver was disgraceful and potentially illegal
But I honestly think the Strategies employed here for the survival food is a lot worse exploitation of
Beers that he himself is created
It's the definition of parasitic
Yeah and not just that
But the sales tax
They're getting so
Like he's literally doing the used car salesman like
I called my boss and I said I can
Can take it down for three weeks
Right now
You got to do it right now though
Yeah I don't know what my boss is going to say tomorrow he's crazy
It's not like you put a clock
My God he's not resorting to that sort of QVC tax
Give Me 2 hours
People that get in their orders
Wow
And freeway
Long. There they want to make sure that you're happy
If you order now in the next 2 hours if you get 3 weeks delivery but after that I can't guarantee anything
Ridiculous
I feel like
Mcgurk just sitting for
Sorts
Stewart's
Story
Weird
I guess it works
Knives
He's nice they're so sharp
So Alex has Mike Adams come in because
You got to
He's been proven right about everything is how Alex introduces
No
Ontarget in trip
Tweaks on Coronavirus
Is that on
It's over for human survivors
I guess dance around that
Theme
And also talked about how this Market
It drop
This is all just
Justin attack on Christ
Coronavirus cases
Dinosaur
Search
You know what this is this is the answer to nationalism
This is the answer to a good economy in the west and shine his face
Take that people rebelling inside and without in Taiwan
Today
Sport
But you in 3 weeks ago was saying shoot
People at checkpoint
Batman
Maybe we should stop
Flights
From the cities in China
Logic right there
None of that is real
None
The only way that we can is the reason that Society is it better is because of
The Bad actors like this
Stop f****** following these guys that have an actual reasonable cover
Wind up anything and everything being a goddamn conspiracy to take down Trump
Projected narcissism that's just every single thing in the world exists solely as an attack on me
Me and my people
And it's just I'm
It's no way to live in
It's the mindset that it's impossible to really
Get out you can't really
Debated either like there's no there's no really convincing
That mindset of
Seeing outside itself without like
Individual work
Being done like people really working on themselves and recognizing like
Oh not everything involves
Yeah
Not everything is about like some sort of a
Cloak and Dagger cabal trying to attack my interest
That sometimes happens the one who hit a guy with
The bullhorn
So make it
Sitting here in a blue conversation and like
Dude they're just
Nothing
Is real
CDC says there now
53 cases in the United States
We have reliable information that
The total number of inbred where
So I went checked news.com read some of the Articles they posted and there's literally no supporter citation given for claims
That the CDC is covering up
1000 cases of coronavirus in the United States
It's important to understand that when people like Alex or Mike Adams claim that they have information on a good authority from
High-level source
They're making it up
They pretend to be journalists so they know that
You know take a really serious reason for a court to compel them to ever reveal the source
So they're completely free to make things happen
The tribute that the unnamed sources whenever they please
The fact that they operate like this goes a long way towards explaining why they always gal about the New York Times and other journalistic outlets
Using sources under the condition of anonymity
Because they just make up fake sources they assumed everybody else doesn't
The only way I mean can you imagine what would
What would it require
To actually go find somebody
Who has any kind of Expo
Talk to that baby talk
Cross-reference that with another source to
Verify the information
That's impossible Dan so everyone must be busy man
Springs to sit in and he yelled at by globalist then
Dreaming Dan
Anyway I can find no evidence of the CDC is covering up a thousand cases
The Coronavirus
As always is just my cucking s***
As he continues to do.
The Who
Is a front
Search for communist China
Who is
Traded and taken over by the cops
For China
Percent of admission of people there to invest
Castigate China
At all they came out with was
Positive stories about what a great job China is doing
Maybe they're doing the great job again
There is a part of it that is
Yes some stuff that China is doing is essential towards
Global Response
That right
What is the pr thing
That we discussed on a past episode the idea of like
If the World Health Organization comes out and it's like
Nitpicks everything than China is doing in responses they jeopardize the possibility
Full cooperation and that is a big
I think that is a big issue
Alex and Mike Jones
Mygov
Alex and Mike Adams
Throw around all they want all this talk about how they've been infiltrated by Communists in their front for China
And they can have fun with that
But the reality is if
They operated the World Health Organization operating
In a way that Mike
And Alex wanted them to the situation would be so much
Yeah
The most likely be so much more
And not just that but it doesn't make any sense
China stamp
Because if you want good
CPR
If you're China
You do a good job
Like this is going now that this is becoming
So Global that everybody is going to have
How to deal with it in some fashion
The only thing that makes sense for China to come out of this in
In a positive light
Is for them to have done everything
Impossible
As well as they possibly could anything less than that and the world will be like
We can never trust you again you are
If this is a virus doesn't even like a political thing this is
Is just let live
We like living
Yeah and there'll be always be debates about
You know whether certain measures were the right
To do and that is definitely
Something for another time
For after the
The. Containment
Appropriate IV like
Is walking down a city the best way to drive this right
Now is not the time for that debate
Or complaints about about you
So Alex
Ghost break and comes back
He's just got a weird
Thought
I just I disagree with this fundamental
Knowledge is knowing how to fix the carburetor on a roof of house rats
What is
Data
Have enough experience in another connection to God
Didn't know three that weren't like radar
WhatsApp
I know you're all saying as well
A million points
It's indescribable
Got level
It's really just a conscious level 100 times more powerful than conscious
There's a spirit
But as well
So if you understand what he's saying he's basically making the argument that knowledge is knowing things
Wings and wisdom is
Connecting things
Because you feel like
That's not done that's a really that's a really bad way
King Solomon made back
Clear in the Proverbs when he said
Knowledge is kicking ass
And wisdom is knowing when to go
Kickass baby let's do this I'm not a square
In at like the sense that I'm going to be like a intuition
Is total b******* ready thing like that
But you was a really great moment for me and my I took a logic
Classes in college
Pictures of bunch of
Logic
I always felt
I was I was drawn to philosophy but I really didn't like a lot of
The elements of how like
I can have a good argument for or against something and
A lot of times it's pretty arbitrary which
Debate minutes
Incontrovertible
Rules for how sentences work
Mathematical are you have not been hit by a bull horn
Well
I don't know how large it relates to that but
It-it's
It's mathematical inform
You can diagram
Things
Things out and one day in my area
I don't know if it was maybe my second or third semester
The class Professor named dr. Wyrick
And he's just fantastic
Berry Drive
Very funny
But also like really good at
Elucidate
Spider point
Picture of
How sentences work how you break down
He arrived here discernment
Certainly
Smelling
Contradiction
Wings and Things
Is very very formative
Stretching classes I took
Wow with his dude
One day we're going over some of the homework problems
Discussing things
Someone else in the class was like I think that this argument is invalid
I feel like it is
But I'm going through it
And it looks like it's valid
And so Professor Wyrick got up and he was diagram and get on the board
And do you know went through all of it.
And showed that it was
Valid and as he was finishing up with the conclusion
Like in SO2
To sum up
Sometimes you must have not
Distrust your intuition
There was this interesting moment where you're in a formal logic
Class and this guy is diagramming descendants
The same time for the lesson that
It's derived from it is sometimes
Your intuition is guiding you in the right direction
Roof
No
Exactly but I'm not a square inch
The only thing I hate your guts
You got to always wrong
Replace that but it's a place that
Is merge
With
Proof for it
Your your higher brain or whatever
What Alex is doing is creating a dichotomy
Between your brain
And wisdom
Discernment wisdom or whatever and that's a shield that he hides behind in order to make s*** on you
That's what he uses this for
1000 different data points up can
Connecting through the fog
This is you making s*** up that's all that's going
Yeah that's he's like if your professor is if the student had been like
I feel like this is invalid in your professor was like
You did all the work
You needed to do
Tell it to the world get a radio show tell them that what you said is true it doesn't matter don't
1,000-point
It would be some of that
Anyway
Is that you still got Mike Adams on hold but he decides he's going to complain a little bit more about what happened to Owen at that
Did Bernie rally
And I only play this because Alex add the detailed
I think his body
Came over and
Oh and and split
I wanted to see
Security Guys
Was great guide
Lucerne us now has lost her military to Patriot
What
An internet
Compass.com
When I get in close
On you
And they usually
I'm not doing it
The men walk over and they go
And and neither
And I can be a New York I mean in Austin
People want to date
Incense but it's all a complete but I do like the idea that
Alex thinks everyone wants
I look like
I look like a salt Cube
This is a man who needs help
Yeah you know I when I walk down the street people
Just try and lick me it's just
You know a lot of people have to be with a lot of aspects
The fame that maybe no paparazzi
I get licked a lot of people on Fox News.
Students about some of Bernie's policies
Alexander comes in for a remote neither
My big problem is it
Followers want to lick me
They're all about.
Next thing you know it's
I'm looking forward to Amy Klobuchar bringing that up in the debates off.
So I we get back to Mike Adams and his
Nonsense about
About China and the Coronavirus
Iucu like a really
Through the fog
What kind of reaction from Alex and
In this club
I saw a haunting video last night you probably won't be able to find it was in
Chinese
The guy with a pool
Wuhan
All the apartment buildings at night
In the background
The Scream
The Haunting blood-curdling screams from
People that mental
I want to see in their mind
I will yeah we've got the link
I have no idea exactly what video Mike was talking about but I suspected it's one that's been circulating since at least January 28th
When was covered by the South China Morning Post
It's exactly what Mike is
Describing
It's large buildings in Wuhan at night
When you can hear screaming and yelling that sounds pretty off-putting without translation
However with subtitles you learned with people are yelling or words of encourage
Matter their fellow citizen
They're yelling quotes
Stay strong
Keep it up Wuhan
Essentially rallying the people to keep morale high in a difficult situation
Right
These people are saying
He's claimed on multiple occasions
Speak Chinese so you shouldn't even need subtitles
My suspicion is that he absolutely doesn't know what that video shows but also recognizes
Power is a propaganda tool
And so does Alex
That's why he gets super excited about the video and he wants to see it
It's not out of
Concern for people or caring about the
Situation
Casinos you can use it
Does Arizona consider buying a ship
That's
The game man
I I I did not have too much problem trusting my intuition
I'm guessing that
Maybe they weren't on the up-and-up
That was Mike
I don't know if it's another video that makes talking about but this is like this fits
Exactly what he's talkin to
Some I don't know
Mike
Yeah
Jake's bad video
Any connects it with Alex's raving
It's about the Bernie rally
To create a whole new narrative
To scare people
You just you just nailed it
When you take these deranged lunatic violent leftist who are already
Mentally ill
I'm either already
Quarantine to that
What's going to happen
To their state of mental health what are they then willing
To do in terms of violence or looting or murder or killing a rape
Pedophilia
Things that they do
Everyday basis anyway
The coronavirus doesn't matter
So we got these crazy leftist
Like the ones at the Bernie rally
For the quarantine on the situation
I watch Society the road to call the cops and report an assault on reality
This show is
F****** insane
Yeah and hey
It gets even worse for real cuz guess what
Mike Adams is host
Sing the whole time that Alex is gone for seapak
Really he's not doing it alone or no
Is it Rodger Stone
It's not hosting the show
Tuesday Wednesday Thursday and Friday
With Allen T zombie popping enliven seapak
Allen key Allen key
What
I don't know that I've ever heard David Quezada
Alan Keyes is going to be co-hosting in 41
Relay
Okay
I don't know that he had gone this far
A lot of the mighty have fallen pretty hard
It's truth one time
In junior high
We had to select
Yeah I believe it was an Alexa
2 year
There were like six of us in class and we each had to do like a speech
I like in the Persona of one of the presidential candidates
I wonder if I didn't know any of this position
So I just decided that I would say that I like he's wasn't
Get school uniform school uniforms
Who provided the system of justice.
So microcosm that is everything that's wrong with America Colombia if his Junior High
Allen key
Infowars
See what the health Ranger
Everything was preparation for this
Although unfortunately I never did learn what Allen Keys positions were I didn't think they were
So anyway Alex complains more now about
Does Bernie rally that he went to
You got to see it
A large percentage of women
Their pants
Something in these weird leftist things is they like to
Disgusting man
Don't you
Hiring
Have somebody who's famously allegedly
I don't know I just
It's such a weird
Attack
Bernie supporters pee themselves
Done and how could you vote for a candidate how could you vote for a candidate whose supporters urinate on themselves
Pleasurably so weird
To build this up is like some sort of Otherworldly
Crazy people think
I think largely that's because Alex understands that a lot of his audiences never going to
Engage with or
Has any occasion to be out of Bernie rally
And so they'll just believe these
Oh aren't they
Know everybody
It would be really disappointing if you have to all these images in your head
No one's trying to lick me
I say I say no what
So anyway Alex says
Since more stuff about this route it's just it's nonsense
Gas station bathroom
And those
Goodness in the mental illness and it was just like
Mentally ill person it's disturbing in the grocery store line
Want to kill you
Mike Adams he said
Kill the general public
Figured out
Coronavirus
I talked to my favorites
Oh no
Whole food place
Episode I just want to grab every one of these people buy
The shoulders
God dammit
I don't I don't know man never at the actual rally
Around the outskirts bothering
Also his imagery about 25,000
People who have shipped
Wanting to kill him is
Being a little overly dramatic ice
Also Bernie's campaign put be attended to that Rally in Austin
So Alex is just making s*** up
About that too
Alex is a liar
About everything
Because those lies are useful to him
To use the drives
Salesforce products
The whole game
Honestly I think
That's one of the reasons I found this episode so frustrating Calissa
Who is like
It's very simple
Yeah I like a lot of the stuff is very much like it's not interesting to me like
The things that they gave me the most Joy or things like
Service pelican
Right right right
Right cuz I do want a service
Appreciate being called a long list of
Criminal names
Including any number of sex
Describes just so an a******
Can sell food
I don't appreciate that
On a person
Especially especially when the PS2 resistance of the entire Bernie rally
Coverage
Which is
About Owen hitting a guy with a bullhorn and claiming that the
We get back to you bad.
Ezzz I got left
Pretty eyes
City
You don't you don't see that dude punched
The security guard in
The footage
To be as far as I
I can tell unless there's some other angle of this that
Is would like
Magically shows that I don't believe you
Because the video that they do have
Does
Showing
Hitting the guy with the bullhorn
Over his security guard
Bullhorn back and that's
The security guards head goes back
Here's what your
Write a w******
To the left I would like as a brutal treatment of this
And to the left
So
Alex now has
Joel skousen
Because we know
He is an alarmist he was an anti-communist holdover Cold War dead-ender type
Vagina and all that have
And then also he did this
Vickery location
Film with Alex
He's a bug-out guy
Real trapper
Kind of situation
I am sure of course he's okay he's a perfect has to have on this sort of that
Episode
Indian Theory
It's very clear from the
Idemo how ping
We were planning on using chemical weapons to depopulate America
If I bought long sad even with
Nuclear's pre-emptive strike on Military
They were blackmailed into submission so that they can
What apps do you know the economy have the other things with the US provide
Without destroying the infrastructure
With Blackman
There their they're
That's right
So basically skousen Theory
Is that the Chinese were creating this bioweapon in order
To buy
Steal the America
And
They got out
Or something he's not really clear on the
But realize blackmail could work on that high of a
The scale is blackmail one or two guys and then you get
Yeah that works
Also I don't know what article he's talking
I'm about there and honestly I don't care
Know that decades-old article that proves that I tried to find it I have no f****** idea is just a cold war
Keep the vibe alive
Great
Hey where's McCarthy with
So skousen and Alex are talking about
Some rangy issues
Did they touch on some other
Economy liquor
Because the market going down
Alex tries to suggest
The Trump
Have co-opted
And I use he's reeling it back in
It's thousand shut that s*** down hard
At least Master planners have done
Control
No he's not in control
Independence
Understand a lot about economics
Do do do I like
Startlingly after now is this from
I will give him that
So he does not like Trump all that much he wishes the Trump new thing
But he doesn't it would be nice
This sort of lying is it like tapas
Is very dumb
Yeah you says a lot of things yet we should like and that's great but he's
How to disappoint
Because
You stupid
Alex has to put up with
A lot of his other friends are gone now
Thousand will answer his calls
Discredit
He doesn't pull punches with Alex when I was like
Trumpsc
Stupid
He is a moron
Yes
So like I mentioned at the beginning of the show Alex is going to be gone for the rest of the week
Cuz he's going to seapac
Which I should actually
Correct
He's going to
Fringe event
You know whenever there's WrestleMania there will be like sideshows that other emotions are coming put on Joe
This is kind of like that but
C-pack
Tomorrow through Friday through Saturday
Amazon event
Makes me cry.
Call Brianna van
Give me auntie
Omni
Reynolds
People can be free via varra
National tile.
This event that Alex is speaking it is organized by national file which is run by his employee Tom pepper
The list of speakers were set to
Complain about being kicked off social media include Alex
Owen Shroyer Billy Weaver at the former head of
The proud boys Gavin McInnes
As well as the current head
The proud boys
Enrique tarrio
Great lineup Murderers Row
Brilliant orator actually add 12 that live
Reached for comment about their event I would assume National file would say
I want to be back on Facebook
When you consider who made the
The cut at this year's c-pack and realize that these people are too dumb to be given to speaking slot
It's impressive
This year's you back as well
Wakame
Silk Mark Levin
Charlie Kirk
Your bolsonaro son
What's your
Sebastian Gorka Glenn Beck Dan bongino Brandon
Straka walkaway movement
#walk away
Threatened
Raping people he's going to be speaking at 8
Candace Owens
James O'Keefe and what the hell why not Rick from Pawn Star
Outback
Give me the list of really embarrassing people to have be your Marquis speaker
There's an even among that crew of Creeps and Weirdos Alex and his associates are too foul to be let in
They're really the margins of the margin
It really does feel like it's only a matter of time before they
Forced to accept the reality that the Trump movement or whatever that s*** is does not want them
They want except
Acceptable tone down con men like Glenn Beck
They don't want self-aggrandizing lunatic
Alex will make everything about themselves
And honestly can't be trusted
Turn on hue
You can hear it in the way that our talks about his going to these events
Sexy back he's just trying to get
Attention
And you know what
Not going to work
Is it this is actually a really bad Road for Alex go down
Unless he's trying to leave to like a crisis point
Or he has to turn on Trump
To work out in any way
I don't I don't know what the Imagine
He's going to put do his event mendyke Don Jr is going to show up at the eye
Alex I've been meaning to tell you I loved you all along or
Actually I could see that happening honestly
Yeah that I've said that out loud. Junior might show up
What level of
Deluge
Is he in his private
Thoughts as far as what is he
He think is really
Audible
Act like you are I would say person
Currently there's no way that
He can believe that he
He's getting back on
Twitter
Not going
Doesn't seem like it
But I could also see him somehow deluding himself into believing that
If only he did that
Or if I said that
But the right guy
What's to think like if this then that
Certainly
I don't know it's an interesting
Thought the about like his personal
Internal thoughts
Because like we have this situation with the Bernie rally where everyone's trying to lick him
And you know that that's nonsense coming out of his mouth
But then you think about it it's like what's more
Private
Drum to your private thoughts
Memes
Bernie rally yesterday
I don't have a lot of nightmares
Bernie rally last night
20000 30,000 people out of
They
All look like
They all had green tea
They all had
A lot of them had pain
And they're almost all green tea was very very
We stayed outside the perimeter
Walmart
People in the police did nothing
Owen Shroyer hit
That security guard
With a bullhorn
It appears like
Alex were not doing
But it gave him nightmares
Alex and I had nightmares of green teeth
Piss pants
Socialist hit me in the face with a
You got to be afraid of that
Yep so
You might have forgotten cuz Alex
Is going off on this
Standard a little bit but
I'm still on hold
Just got
Jamaican on hold while he Rambles about nothing
So he wants Joel to come in fly into Studio
And post you post
I would even be there
Use hose by yourself
Because people need to know about bugging out
Please come here
Without me
But at family from East Texas
We've been here turn into
Dumps out
Almeda Groesbeck
Check
I've really got to
3 years to move
Myself and whoever wants to do with the crew
It makes me feel like a worm that the other people are so much weaker than I am
I just morgrave did before
I agree
You agree
Can't defeat the Satanist until God comes back to be back in time
Get the f*** out Austin
Is the whole point
But you can't defeat the sickness until God comes back
I remember I don't know I don't know what the point is I remember reading the book of Revelation
I do think this is an interesting thing for Alex so, he talks a lot of s*** about it leaving Austin I know James ever going to do
Do that he got an armored ridout's that he's bringing the Infowars staff
Still sure about the rest of his life in post-apocalyptic sewing
Shroyer
Constant fear of bullhorn
I don't think that's ever going to happen probably because
Austin did awesome city to live in
It's the same reason why all these dicks Living Like New York and l.a. complain about Coastal Elites
America I love
Love living in Manhattan
Fly over there I have a pen
I'm going to have to go to Martha's Vineyard for a couple weeks to recover from how exhausted I am very exhausting
Mentality that you see
Rhetorical
Thanks
But it is interesting that Alex is like I want you to come in and get cuz we need to talk about bugging out there talk about
Strategic
Eight stops himself in the middle
The name of the documentary that they have already made about this very topic you have already done they've already
What are you coming to do the thing we've already done that's available for free online
Just play the video like a substitute
I think you realize that as you was talkin
So
We got the health Ranger
My God
S*******
Complete
Joel skousen
HD comedy
S*** mostly a s*** head
Is
Has enough ball bearings in his head to know the Trump doesn't know anything about the economy which is refreshing
We've had Alex
Beer in downtown
Atmos
Host of the show selling food
And now we get something
Disappointing
Quieter Lance a few days ago when the major Israel
Daily newspapers
Has a white
White nationalist
Praising the
The fact that he was being deplatformed off the internet
007 Nick Fuentes back on
Israel by Nick Fuentes YouTube channel getting taken down
So weird that he's responding to an article in The Times of Israel as opposed to some other out
Stream tell Alex chooses to respond to a Times of Israel article when he's trying to do
Offend a holocaust
That is if that's intentional
Absolutely
I've heard him and you know do his stick
Enough David's very clear these one hundred percent of white nationalist
Who just really doesn't
Call back
Because much like Alex
He wants to be accepted
In the same way Alex is fighting
Doom campaign to take over the trunk
Community entirely
Nick Fuentes is also engaged in a battle.
Take down Turning Point USA so he can shift the college
Conservative world
Super far to the extreme right
In order to have any success in that endeavor he knows he
Can't just open
Only call himself accurate thing
That'll scare off the potential recruits
Nick Fuentes on many occasions has made arguments against non-white immigration to the United
He's argued that Jim Crow era was better for both blacks and whites
Is how the consistent position that America should be a white Homeland
He does not.
Disagree with any of
Things with the final white nationalist
He just doesn't like the term cuz
It's bad for business
In fact
He said exactly that back in 2018
The reason I wouldn't call myself a white nationalist it's not because I don't see the necessity for white people to have a Homeland.
For white people to have a country
It's because I think I kind of terminology is he was almost
Exclusively by the left
Did the fame and I think
The terminology in the labels that we use
I don't think we can look at them outside the context of their connotation in America
You only really has a problem with being called a white nationalist cuz the left calls of that and he knows that it tarnishes his ability
The trick unsuspecting
I into thinking that isn't what he's about
When Alex Jones is doing here what he's doing
He's engaging and platforming and covering for Anna
Explicit white nationalist Holocaust
Denier
Richard surprise no one
So Alec
You know it's interesting that he's going to see
And you'd think the lazy
Well not really
Please never gone before
He's never gone before
I didn't care to check in.
I was like why did it why is it good I said I wasn't saying
Alex explains
What does what made him decide to go
When I heard all this last week
Go to sleep
I've never gone to see pack
The biggest
An event every year
Try to be in DC or being out later being New York
Where I born in
Build something new
Go to seapac be anointed and benighted
In the Ben Shapiro show
Club
With the game well
Delta
Boracay
So Alex heard that Nick Fuentes was doing
His own
Inside thing
SexyBack
Any seeing all the like
Attention that he's getting for attack
Talking Ben Shapiro and Charlie Kirk
Turning Point
And Alex is like
I could get in on that
MC packet there cuz on French
He's inspired by the not-so crypto-fascist
I Catholic monarchist
Wing
It's trying to take over the just
Offensively conservative
Hot
Turning Point USA
Yeah yeah
It is it is one more proof that Alex has never had his own idea for any
Ever this is
A
Addition
It is
If you can get expelled for plagiarism
He should be expelled from the radio
Right
It's interesting how bad is it
Instincts are too because like this isn't the way to go
Things insured aquantis is going to get a lot of press would like you did the turning point take the bench
Spiro speaking at Wen
He
Video taped himself tied to confront bench
Spirituality
Tobira withholding
When is baby
Trying to walk to a hotel with his family and Nick Fuentes
Followed him
Depressed for that
But that's not good
That's not good
All press is good press if you're a white nationalist makes people who don't agree with Ben Shapiro sympathy
Size of Ben Shapiro
Yeah look at you like you're a piece of s***
He is
True
But that's not good
I mean if your brand is white nationalist without saying white Nashville YouTube
Apologize is Brandon
America America
Attracting people who are piece of s*** already anyways right now
But it isn't it hinders your ability to
Get in the spaces that you wish to be at
I don't know
Anyway Nick Martinez comes on DS
Plates
About CPAP
Like that are
F****** stupid
Friday this Friday we're going to be host
Singing event
Call America First
C-pack political action
Michelle Malkin
Greer and hopefully we're going to have an alternative sorta like you guys are having
Seapak
Or perhaps
Fit in line with the never try
Mainstream conservatives of Mets
Oh yeah C packets
Truly a hotbed of never
Trumper's the never Trump CPAP
Donald Trump
Mike Pence Ray Mike Pompeo
Elaine Chao
Don Trump Jr Ivanka Trump
Okay Haley
Never Trumper all the way you could be more never Trump than
Pornstar amazingly never Trump
This event could not be
Further from never Trump
It's been completely co-opted by the Trump called and it's fascinating
Nick Fuentes trying
43 this list of people
Including a f*** ton of trump Administration officials
At least three members of the Trump family
Trying to call that never trumper's
The reason for this is very obvious
Trump isn't even Trump
Do people like me
To him Trump was a symbol of the coming back of an open white supremacist culture
The promise of a trump presidency
They was that of a
Return to a time when all Social Power rested in the hands of straight white men
Answer when he says never Trumper
People who aren't loyal to that symbol
Nick Fuentes Trump himself could be a never Trumper because he could
What are fail to live up to
To the goals of this movie
This is why it might seem incoherent to call it event
Dominated by Trump
Never Trump
But it makes perfect sense to someone like Nick
Did you got understand the code
To go to the bathroom
In the same bathroom
As people who are non-whites
That is
Trump's fault I would never try
State Fair
Way2go neck please. Michelle Malkin
Speaking
Puentes package number Just for Laughs Festival
Shity f****** right-wing lunatic
Text sweetheart we going to end up talking a little bit of Michelle Malkin
Not really any in-depth stuff
But she doesn't have anything in depth
Apparently her and Alex had a run-in about a decade ago that's going to come up
Actually is up there in terms of what makes
Episode
Pretty funny
About the poor get to that we're going to talk
About how she's been
Kicked out
Conservative world
Somebody like Michelle Malkin
Example
You're here with somebody who has one of these legendary America
Conservative
She's been in legendary
Like 25 years everybody like her don't like real
When she turns it on
Got a job
Exactly right exactly right for
Simply refusing to disavow me and the boy person other Young America
Conservative
Y8
Fires her until
Sorry you're not allowed
Speak anymore will not host you at your events anymore
It's being difficult
Chisme become difficult
For America first wheel outside dissonant right-wing 5
To organize anywhere we can't
Says we can't get organizations to green-light us
You have mobs of antifa show up
Robert yellow stars in America
It's real America First conservative
That's exactly right
Coof
It's like you can't burn across anywhere
Anywhere
Someone who's been
Conservative Gray
Space for a long time
Cr-10 you with your
Position can be
Even with tenure
When the Griffins done with you
Her speaking
Are managed by a group called The Young America's Foundation
Which also manages events for all sorts of
Conservative
Azusa to bend
Shapiro
As it turns out Ben Shapiro makes them a lot more money than
She does
Because when she decided to side with
Nick Fuentes in his war against Ben Shapiro
Young America's Foundation
Dropped her from their talent roster
Part of the problem is that she got confrontational about Shapiro's derision
The plant is in a speech in
Front of the young America's Foundation
Switch again also represents Shapiro
So this could easily be written off as just being bad work
Workplace Behavior
Even if you don't factor in the fact that you was supporting a straight-up white nationalist polakoff
Denier
From there the mainstream conservative World began to sour on malka
I just had to Resort
Fully throwing in with Nick Fuentes
This is how this stuff works
When the grift is done with you you find the neck
Script and you keep movie
And sometimes
It's sad
Everything else Nick Clippers just Nick Fuentes
Complaining about how no one wants to be associated with them which makes sense
I know that it does make things harder and it's more difficult to do business
When people know what kind of a crypto
Fascist bigot
You are
The people saying that they don't want to write you a space to hold a bigot rally in that's not an encroachment of your free speech
Literally the thing that you went to the f******
Supreme Court
To get gay people
From having the cakes
Made for them
Like that is this it
Because of that
That's your whole f****** game
You don't get to win every
I hate a
Discrimination
Were the only ones where they're allowed to discriminate on social media
We're the only ones you're allowed to discriminate
Book a hotel for
Conference
His first speech
If you look at life
Free Grassroots
Populism
And what people want
The fact is we were selling my folks one and we're real
I think it's probably not a great idea for Alex to use the word we when he's talking about him and Nick giving people what they
They want
Has literally no idea who he's talking
Into or that he wants to be associated with someone like
Nick Fuentes
It's really hard to tell which is the case
But you better believe that he's ever confronted with some of the stuff that Nick says on his own platform
Alex will immediately call him controlled opposition like he does
Richard
That is the
This would go without was confronted with
All of the stuff that I was surprised whenever they made the
Spiritual sequel to what women want what men want
I was surprised there wasn't more
Explicit White
Nationalist ideology coming from the mines
So many of those p
Some aspect
So they talk about Nick getting kicked off YouTube and Alex's or psychologist
Because you dare fight with Turner
F*** off there's a lot of anti Turning Point contact you can find that's just fine
Subtle warning in gut
Demonetized while back
For hate speech in
Consistently engages in the exact same behavior is he is
Had chances
And you just want to not to behave the way he doesn't
So babe
YouTube's not for you buddy
That's how it works in such a way as like this content is not
What advertisers want to be associated with
Boom
Anyway
Alex starts talking to him about how like
Democrats are going to be gone
Right we're going to
But that point
Who's going to need to be the two party system Republicans going to split it
Who's going to be the white mask
Interesting suggestion
What the demographics
Right
But I want to change the whole paradigm
Not real
Pharmacy of America
How do you transport that do two party system
Supremacy
Well it would be difficult to say you know people have said that it could line up with something
Nothing like a Workers Party Like You could have the working and middle-class of all the diff
Groups of people
Exactly
Right right again
Against the elites
That's ringing a bell for me
Puerto Vallarta super right wing xenophobic crypto-fascist
Party call itself a Workers Party
National Socialist German Workers Party
They're socialists though they don't support workers they support socialist
I don't want people to think you similar to a Nazi
Sure seems to invite a lot of comparison
Choose choosing
Idea all right the Brown uniforms the real problem maybe that's on his mind
Goofy yes that is an issue
But honestly we're only most
We like the Nazis
As a douche
Rap-up
It's mostly a complaining session about how they're all like
Everyone's
Don't like them
We're going to have a rally about it
So now Alex invites Nick
To his house.
We get into a little bit of history about
Alex Jones and Michelle ball
I want to invite you and Michelle Malkin I'm going to fly out Friday nights on Combee Road
Didn't invite me but that's fine I got
Probably was out of control or security got punched me in the arm writing back
I like Michelle
He got into a fight with Michelle Malkin
Security guard yellow little bit later
Of not liking
Michelle Baca to the point of a salt
With another security guard also seems to be like a pattern
So Alex is theory
Theory I guess
With the way he's been
Pitching thing
Is this entire episode is it like
I heard you were doing this thing
Around seapak
Tom pappert my employee
Was running
Another event
And I
It's like okay yeah let's do that and get
4:20
He is operating under the assumption
National file
Tried to get nikto
To be a part of their rally
And we're unable to do so
So
Alex Springs
This up
And it seems like that didn't
Pappadeaux no
I want invite you cuz I know the actual thought wants to know about you
Tomorrow event Wednesday going to come out of the army
Absolutely I would love to go
I had to reach out to you
I I don't think they have reached
You understand what's Happening Here
Oh boy even National filed no
And Alex is like
Oh my God
Jordan thousand points of information are coming together for me and my wisdom
That even Tom pepper was kind of like I don't know if I want this a****** involved in Arvada
Nick Fuentes is the Alex
Jones of Alex Jones's of doesn't want it
We weren't able to
Oh my God disconnected his phone's breaking up
I want Nick Fuentes
I'm sorry I was mean to you
Papi Papi
Whatever
We'll just put it behind us
Clearly I'm not
Still holding a grudge
Obviously
I can just put it all behind
So as it turns out at the 2008 DNC Alex got into a little fight
Michelle Malkin
According to Westworld. He started yelling at her which caused her to try and flee but Alex kept harassing her and following her yelling
Come on you little monster you little fascist piece of trash
I guess his beef with her is better YouTube video those coming around around that time there was up a soldier throwing a puppy off
Forklift in Iraq
I have no idea what the deal is with that video but I do know that Infowars wrote a lot of articles
It's about how much was it
Denying US military atrocities in the war on terror
Because you didn't condemn the video or I guess I think she speculated that it was a
The stuffed animal
If that was a real video that's awful but I should also point out that I haven't heard Alex Ane
About Trump pardoning War crime
One of them was charged with Coach shooting at civilians
Supersport
Another was charged with ordering the murder of two unarmed Afghan villagers
Let this be a teachable moment
When you're not on Alex's team
Questioning a video of a soldier throwing a dog
Golf Cliff makes you a fashion
This piece of trash
When you are on Alex
16 literal monsters hoop
Charged with war crimes
It doesn't even come up
That's what I mean when you are a fast
Not a big deal
Does not come up doesn't seem like it's the issue
So National file was created this little event and they have like 300 Cedar or whatever Alex is already said this
I'll give you 20 grand that I totally have because we're definitely not running out of money here and Alex makes it a little too
Clear in this next clip that they're living
On their listeners dime Notions political incorrectness to
Because absolutely
They say you. Neither am I and I'm just
Hotel on that internet
But I am paying for part because I just want to have
Where she packaged to meet in a big Ballroom
And I am paying for the drinks
So
One thing
Abuse it is this is abuse this is this is abusing your audience and then slapping their face
Aces in front
IPad is insult needed to do a larger
Publicity stunt the national file was aiming to do so I paid $20,000
That's coming from the listeners
For a larger Ballroom to satisfy my ego and also when you come Nick have a drink
It's all the listeners
Wow
It rough
F***** up
Yep
So we're done with Nick Fuentes now because I mean most of the
Is meaningless and
Just whining
But Alex
Is also
Trying to
Cell
His
They put on your mouth
So he makes a claim that I find
Dubious
Operation
Tom
What's in your address
Cornelius
Pieces we're on the prop rallies
We're not taking them over we're not disrupting
Operate
Dislike Bernie
Powerful
We'll just
Looks like
It does look like that it's not about your beard or whatever
I think it's really funny for Alex be like disrupting events
It's not my style
Me
The guy who's
Entire career is based around by bullhorn
And scales
King of the bullhorn
Can you sing it's not my style disrupting event I'm not like Bernie
Episode he's talkin about disrupting a Bernie rally with a bullhorn Bernie rally is
Disrupt
Take me to Bernie rally Gordie disrupt
He's also trying to lure Michelle Malkin to his event by telling Nick Fuentes to apologize for yelling at her
Car with a bullhorn right
Stop disruption
Redistribution of wealth
All he does is yell at people
He's not a big fan of disrupting
All he does is yell he doesn't disrupt
Nothing that's more his style name one event that is disrupted in the past outer no 6
That time he showed up that Hillary thing with the
That wasn't disruptive
You just showed up with a tank instead of tree would it be all right so you take a tank to a couple
Rally's in all of a sudden
Whatever
So Alex realizes there's a lot of headlines he hasn't gotten poodle
Talking to Vic Fuentes Rivals, but don't b******* trying to sell his food
Sorry I've been talkin to do white nationalists in the a******
It's just too much going on that Weinstein convicted on a bunch of town
Didn't even cover that cuz the virus is so bad
I'm looking at hundreds of articles
No cards to Intel
Bullying
Well
Look at all the snooze
You have not covered
F******
That is
Criminal
How dare you
Unless all of those papers are
Pictures of his food
Dario
King Darius doesn't cover the wind
16 conviction is because it runs
Counter to his narratives about how
These Elite globalist type never get punished
Yeah I am Factory Weinstein was charged
It's kind of a problem
For his narrative
Things upload charges
Actually dwelling on it for any
. of time is
Last clip here and it's
Little another little headline that he's got that
Stop Bernie campaign funnel Millions to
Meet Bernie stealing campaign money no
Dirty, Steve trusts yammy loves you
There's about a story on National file which again is run by Alex's employee Tom pepper
The allegation is the one of the vendors that the campaign of Ernie's campaign used to run ads I was a company called Old Town
Tell media LLC
Apparently to the people who work at that company no burn
There's no indication what now they just know her other friends or something
There's no indication at all that Miss Andrews made any money from this Arrangement or if there's anything untoward here and
Trust and Debbie fair I didn't look
Look into this at all I just took at face value the allegations on National file
And that's what they are
Wow I'm not sure exactly what this article is
Reporting to show other than
Possibly didn't Jane Sanders nose so
Some people who work at
PR Company that her husband's campaign uses
I don't know
That's nothing
Compared to what Trump has been doing
What what how is he been profiting off of his presidency whatsoever
According to the Washington examiner Trump's campaign
Quotes
More than $190,000 in campaign contributions
Do Trump own properties business
Family members in the fourth quarter of
I don't even have a funny answer that that's f****** tragic Trump Foundation had to
Close after being forced to pay a two million-dollar settlement stemming from there
Directing charity funds to
The campaign uses
There's not rageous level of self-healing the Trump has been involved in while running for and B
Being president again
Let this be a teachable moment
If you're not on Alex's team
The fact that your wife knows someone at a PR for a few uses
Is proof of ramp
The corruption
If you are on Alex's TV
Engaging in a pattern of very extensive self and Rich
Campaign
Is not corruption at all
Nope and it's not mentioned
Because
I don't know about that stuff
Hey now there's no way to find out about anything like
And I don't think of any I can't think of anything in the Constitution that would Express Lee prohibit this kind of behavior from
Should be I mean I feel like I owe an apology to
Feel like I
Not been in
This episode was really really stupid
Looks like Alex knows that he's leaving tomorrow
He's going to have so much fun yelling at people in DC
The Funtime making a star with his s******* proud boyfriends and
No in Indian all the money that people have donated
To keep in Forza lipo
And he's going to be able to
Get drunk in d.c. in that van and who Among Us hasn't needed a drink to survive the Infowars
Look I'm not opposed to that
I get the feeling that Alex knows that he's about to go on vacation at this episode is a
Desperate push
For people to buy the food
And then on top of that
Stupid
The whole thing about being assaulted at the Bernie rally makes no sense
Based on the evidence provided by Infowars it
Paper thin
At the fence it the way it's being used
And the rest of the stuff is really stupid
Except
For the idea of an emotional
Sport pelican
Yeah you would
Like
I don't
I don't think there's any possible way to be excited
About a show
That
Sitting
As just Benedict
Complete
Assault on reality
Like there's just no other way to do
Describe it then literally
Everything that was over and over and over
The the virus said that they
At economy the f****** everything is a
Complete and utter the video that
Shows the thing that the opposite of the things
Calling it
To your face
This show is if you are a listener of this show you might as well just
Walk up to Alex and let him slap you in the face and then go back to the end of the line
To wait for it to happen all over again
This is flucking
Incredible
Yeah it's not
More so than usual
Jackets
It's often
That
That's not a unique
Phenomenon
This episode
It felt like way more layering
And it kind of It kind of bummed me out hit me in a little bit of a mild
Depression around
Around this Blood
We're through it and I guess probably on the next episode will have some
Babies
Something f***** up it happens
I will see what happens
Until then we have website
The Coronavirus
No it wouldn't
I read it in a novel being interested
Alright we do have a website
Not go to bed Jordan
Go to iTunes or Apopka
Cast apps or whatever it is you like they're leaving review donate to
The show we would be very happy
Happy
Emilio I'm dzx Clark I'm an emotional support pelican
Alexandra Thurston color