Damned important swetik
I have great respect for its knowledge B B I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Hey everybody
Jordan
What up
As we all know
Coming
What
Natural wonder would you like to see before the world is change
Amazon River in the Grand Canyon
Feel like there's a lot of bugs there are a lot of Associates mosquitoes
Mosquitoes but just like alive
Just about everything
National Park
National monuments
Except for I guess like I I don't think of
Maybe I have
I don't know if I've been to Niagara Falls
I like waterfall a lot of natural Splendor waterfalls
You're able to find around the islands
Says who we gals but I know
I mean like
I don't I don't know what the likelihood of various things being destroyed
Whatever is the most
BMI
Well I got to go to Iceland
Big thing of ice
Not that great
Reaction to when I went to as a child I went to Mount Rushmore
Oh yeah I expected to see something goes like all my God so amazing
Bike Race for not being all that impressed with it too I thought it was smaller than I imagined
I was much more impressed by
The geyser Old Faithful
Uninterested Water Campground awesome
Okay
Different feelings geysers
We got an interesting episode
The last a week
He was out at CPAC
Yeah and so we don't have time not going to cover Mike Adams
Hosting a shower or Allen keys
Speakeasy in the economics in here I'm not going to do that we don't have any of Alex Jones's show itself
To go over but thankfully I was able
Go to find something
Maybe a little bit more fun
Okay
The first Stephen thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk connect Stevens
Christopher thank you so much
Andrew Christopher Fox 88
Thank you so much
Very much.
Text with two M's
Generally whenever I'm putting out these spellings
Just their name
Where is the person who actually their name is Ron
Thank you so much
Pronouncing
Text Morgan
Christy
Clarifying
Christy you're not about to
I'm a policy wonk
Generous
Beyond the level of
Should be considered normal
Innovative helping us do this
In an attempt to be
Someone special this thank you I would like
Soundbite for this
So thank you so much. You are now a technocrat
Natalya brilliant someone sodomizing
I don't want
Jesus Christ
Bank of the West
Scott's
Please do.
Helpful
Jordan like I said his family went to Washington d.c.
Please try and whine and beg for attention by taking Z-Pak
It's somewhat in their conception they were taking over
CPAP
There also were the highlights from the trip like Gavin McInnes getting kicked out of z-pack and
Gavin McInnes being told to leave the lobby outside c-pack in the middle of being interviewed by Alex Smith about how he
Kicked out asleep
Great highlights
Oh yeah
They threw some kind of Gala party on Thursday night but for a person like me who's about to Subs
It was all about their emergency save the First Amendment Summit
Which took place Wednesday evening
This was an event that promised appearances from the likes of the Millie Weaver Gavin McGinnis and the hastily booked
Nick Fuentes
Complaining about how they're not allowed on social media
The Birth of a Nation
Yeah it's not good in what I can only describe as a huge mistake the entire video
Dislike
Leave for the live people just do that
Leave evidence
They might be one of the saddest things I've ever seen in my life
First of all as we know the event was being put on by national file
Which is the blog that Alex's employees
Tom pappert run
I called him an employee but that might not actually be at the most accurate term
Like pepper used to host Firepower Rubio until they all realized it was pointless and no one was listening
Any pills in for Owen on the War Room sometime so whether he has a contract or not I consider him an employee
Even though my terminology might be a little imprecise
Yeah
National file with plan to hold an event at a smaller Auditorium
Now it's heard about
Insisted they rent out the Omni
A much larger venue befitting of a star of his caliber
Alex's suggested that he paid as much as
Is $20,000
Rent a bigger room because
With a roster like Gavin
Alex and Nick Fuentes you going to draw crowd
As it turns out they did not video the summer begins with a wide shot with Rob due onstage giving the odd
Audience an introduction
You can see 12 people in the crowd
Compare to at least
40 empty chairs
I should say in the interest of full honesty that one of the chairs has someone's coat over the back of it
13 or it might be the code to the guy in the chair next to it I don't know I'm not entirely sure it's unclear
A very bad first date that's for sure
This is depressing turnout
I mean there's no way around how sad this is and if you look at the video.
The end of the event where we get another wide shot it doesn't look like many more people showed up over the course of the summer
The most I was ever really able to count
Any shot was about 34
But granted the shot itself doesn't
It show the entire room but it does show the first 10 rows
Mexican restaurant
How did killed 438 about it
If I were showcased stuff
I would love that
Pretty good
I would leave the show like wishing it a bendpak
Take it in stride
But here's the thing
Alex's Brandon's not reasonable now that's not supposed to be the most popular talk show host in the world and everyone
He's the most popular
I'm lying about him pretending that he's not exactly
Live event like this has to be packed
Any empty seat let alone 40 or more of them in the front Road it's a damning refutation of the image he presented
Themself
There may have been a few more people than other folks I'm able to count in the video but I also heard from an inside source according to a person
Who was there in the room
But there was never more than 100
On the crowd
I performed independent comedy shows that have been better attend
And my friend
I was not a successful comic
There's alot going on in the world I'm pretty sure that Alex has some pretty horrible take
Takes on the coronavirus developments in the situation in Syria and the Democratic primary
But since he's been out of the studio we have to wait till Wednesday
Check up on any of that stuff
Today we're going to walk through this 3-hour long emergency Free Speech Summit Alex put on desperately trying
Going to beg for Trump's attempt
I don't want to Prejudice you or the audience but I have to say that watching this was one of those frustrating experiences I've ever had
Preparing for the show
This Summit was soap
Iran me to cause me to yell who's in charge here way more than once
As a person who used to produce live stand-up shows they're just so many very basic mistakes
His friends made clear that no one was trying
And no one knows what they're doing
It's infuriating to watch
But I kept my wits about me and I'm glad I did
Because this Summit is a pretty amazing narrative Arc
To it
It has almost nothing to do with the free speech
First Amendment
Airport
Actually but there is a rich psychodrama but I think I actually has pretty important implications
For the Infowars you
Okay
Get into that over the course of the
6 hour episode of murder
We're about to embark
I believe the word count in my notes is
Why don't you read enough fella Street
Like I said the first shot on stage
I guess I mean
In the audience or if you're watching this
Of the event
You'd be wrong in that
But Rob dude has welcomed the crowd kind of
And here's how he does his fees Ram
You either rambly intro
There's plenty of others
Federal Reserve
Nice
Quick shower head how many feet
People are here
See
Alex Jones
Alright well he will be down here in just a
Kick-off this event and then he's also headlining
The end
Lots of rousing
The word that
Don't want to hear it
Dangerous Game
Notary
Trigger anybody
Haha
You guys are at the lackadaisical thin crowd
Also by the way like what words don't you want to hear
Recipe for someone to yell the n word
They're not going to yell at because then you're saying the words they don't want
That's a good point
But I'm not entirely sure that his audience
I would have thought that through
I think that it basically
He is heard as an invitation to say offensive words
It does seem like
Chomping at the bit to
Heckle
That's your call
Somebody's out there screaming
College degrees here that out here
Stupid sense that I got is that recognizes that the audience's thin and maybe more people are coming
Experience that every single independently-run comedy show ever
Oh yeah I got some friends that are on the way we can wait 10 minutes
Start time with a button
25 networking has earned around and it sounds meme but I
Done that myself a hundred times running show site
Give me five
Absolutely it's it's a technique
At the turnout was trying to vent because I think the Alex also doesn't want to get up on stage in front of this
Like crowd and so
This is just
Robinhood
Jump
This is embarrass
I was waiting for Alex
To go to oh by the way if you don't
Twitter a lot
They haven't received any mail
There yet
Tws
It is not
Through here to see
This was a
Rod Blagojevich
Are we really doing this
There's a reason borracho
Pardon from Barack
The first thing it's a boy
Park to point out here is this is an emergency First Amendment summary
Social media and the first person is literally Alex Jones
And news director who decides to make it clear whilst
Sing out before Alex shows up but he's actually still on Twitter
Kind of invalidates the whole argument might be something
Do not call attention to because it raises the question
What is Alex doing that Rob do hasn't
The fact that Rob dude still on
Maybe people
Kicked off we're kicked off for a reason
Also that tweet Rob is reading is supposedly from Rod Blagojevich which Rabe is robbed
As a basis to argue that blacko was expecting a pardon from Obama which he did not get so now he's taking
Tell the world that Obama's gay
I hate to ruin parties at this tweet is from an account called at gov blacko
Bayou is literally quote not the real blogo
Parody account
You can't trust him
That's exactly what I would do damn this account is a person who's trying to sell blogo t-shirts and one of the strategies baby
Post inflammatory jokes about being set up
Tweets about Boos
February 27th was just quote
There's drunk and then there's block
And right now I'm at level of blogo drunk
Party
This was followed up by a tweet a little bit later saying quote I'm so drunk I could
Work on the bar I do my best work at this level are you human
Like I said though this account is clearly also employing some parody
Like this tweet
Theory the Chinese didn't like these terrorist so how do they get rid of them
Trump how do you get rid of trump
Create a virus that will turn into a worldwide plague and caused the American economy to suffer
You think the coronavirus is an accident blogo doesn't
On one level Rob do thinks of his actually Blagojevich is Twitter because he's an idiot and you never text any information before
WhatsApp to getting repeating
But on a deeper level he automatically accepts
The tweeters real because
Conformist
And I can't put it more simply than this
A parody account is indistinguishable from what Rob do really thinks
That's bad you know what I would say to that
Figured out dues
Consider for a moment that Rob dude just told this crowded a free-speech rally that he's still on Twitter anybody got fooled by a Rod Blagojevich
Parody account that says quote parody account and its bio
He's work
For Alex for over a decade
When you go to Infowars you show up dumb and you certainly don't get sharper
Based on the experience Beyond Paradise
I prefer to say
The Rock Vapes B
It doesn't get much better than a fake blogo tweet he's not doing it
Now it's time to get Alex on stage
Well there's a big old traffic jam from c-pack over here we appreciate all you that got here early swear this
Marshawn timer tonight
We've got a big long list of
Coming up I got McGinnis
Owen Shroyer
Nick Fuentes
And so many more
Stranahan I'm going to be
Peking
Hi Deanna Lorraine
Amazing
And I got my gun
Before I do
Annihilator
And there's a big
Traffic snarl
But we're not going to start
Thule where you at
And I get pho
Here
I've seen this movie 100 times a poorly-run comedy shows
The crowd has thinned
Play push back the start time that doesn't help so the host gets up and makes
An excuse like bad traffic
Maybe it looks like it might rain or something
Those does what they can to make the people who are there feel special like Alex's
You're the ones who get it
Ashokan start everybody here isn't watching that Bears game right everybody
Also Rob was very explicit
Gavin is the future Act
Act this way way too long showcase
And that Alex is a pointless q-and-a session
Good to know that's the
Setup of the night
We'll see what happens
So we end up getting into Alex's
Introductory piece
Okay
It's Meandering is he going to do a race
Nobody
Kind of does a yak off B
Yakov Smirnoff
So yes
We're in digital media
Can I reach
Rated
Marshall radio
The globalist topic
Realize I did
What you want to radio.
Lowrider TV
Eragon
Jump
The gun
They abused
Power of big
The old days
UHF
Bhf
You watch
Television
It didn't want you
Subway by country
I do like a bit of it
Is bragging about his
Chris grade I thought it was about that wonderful weird
That is in opposition to the
Reality that's in front of him
He's drawn very miniscule crowd compared to the millions and millions of people with
Conservatively what is it
A tenth of the world's population was too much every world leader
Exact listen to everyday so that stuff
Yeah you can tell that it it's
Alex is not thrilled with
This turn out like you can see the self-consciousness
The fact that
Billions
Apple service
The fact that
In the middle of it
See traffic
Rainey Street
Today's announcing
That one purse
Science
Against the tyrants
That is a beautiful thing
That's a rationalization
Emma's nightclub Alex teases the theme
Who's headlining speech
When I get back up here I've got a plan
Calls after this literally working
I think that you may be brilliantly deduced this might turn into an epic
At a certain point
Big headlines of something
Hey workout
Not coming up in about 2 hours when I get my twin
I'm going to get it
Smoking Gun
Governmental
Funding
Censorship
The American people
And the blueprint
Now that's really
It happened
Right now
And we have a real
Say no to this
Again Alex is trying to get this sparse audience excited for his headlining
Speech
It seems like a theme he's going for is basically the first
They came for poem
That was a poem written by the Lutheran Pastor Martin niemoller
In the form of the concession
Expressing guilt
For not doing more
In the lead-up to
The Holocaust
Because he thought it wasn't his
Is problem
It's very clear that what Alex is doing is he's hoping
Evoke that here
He will never ever ever
Actually quote that poem
And that's because the first line is quote first they came for the Socialists
And I did not speak out because I was not a social
Alex wants to co-op the ever resonant themes of this poem bone ever talk about what the poem actually says because
Kind of invested in the Enterprise of coming for the Socialist
The next stanza is about coming for the trade Union
Which again Alex would be on the side actively opposing the Union
The imagery in the
Feeling of that poem but not the specifics of it which is
Vine
The poem and the poet was
Dumb because Alex just summed up the whole pillow poem with just like
You know that if you don't stand up for somebody nobody to stand up for you
Spell superlative he's a real poet
Since being a poet
You can take classes
And poetry yes I have
And if you do
You'll get a great
A stroke that was a long walk
Okay in this next clip Alex starts rambling about giving Trump a grade
His performances present
Ill-advised these are not good things
To say about someone who your present is good
My main mission
President
Very true
Not good
If he doesn't think you
President-trump
The deal with you as a psychopath
And he believes
America
Promoting archetype
A
-4
Report card
This might not be the best way to characterize your hero president like I don't think anyone should be supporting an elected official
Transactional matters of public interest
I have no idea how Alex can get in front of this
In Crowd and tell them the Trump doesn't deal with you unless you have something to offer him
Unexpected to sound good
It sounds insanely corrupt like blatant corruption
Even Alex is trying to make it sound good
It sounds like a mob guy Hey listen all of you 20 people here who totally have a ton of money
Trump is willing to deal with you if you get positive
Well-to-do crowd
Suss that out from the
The video Alex definition Trump does not have any interest
No probably not
So he gets an A minus
Okay.
Minus report
Because when it comes
Standing up
Cartel
Binding Force
Ghungroo
And Veteran groups
Organization
Pro-life groups
President-trump
Standing up
I'm not sure how Alex is waiting grades
Here but I didn't realize that he put so little priority on Free Speech stuff
Like you literally yells about it all the time
Completely manufactured
Complaints about the last have to do it
Free Speech grievances
Like the purple penguin's affair
Free Speech absolute
Like it's f***
Company is called Free Speech system
Based on every indication I get about what he pretends his positions are
If a president gets an F minus on Free Speech issues
It should be impossible for there to be a minus
10 amendments
Guess what
You f****** on one Amendment you still got a 90% Dan it looks perfect
Breeds of their system that follow certain rules
There's a method for averaging out great
Creating a grade point average
If you're taking college courses nueve's and three of them
That'll give you a Beat
Bridge or 3.0
8 - is a 3.7 GPA
And you need to be taking
14 classes before an s could be absorbed and leave you with an A- at Everett and that's only if all those
Those glasses are weighted exactly the same
Average grade is still a minus
This like so many other things is just Alex talkingshit
He doesn't really care about Free Speech because if he did it would
Probably
Lisa think we're bumps Trump's grade down to Abbey okay
Okay let's do it this way let's go better than this way
Alright
Let's wait the averages here
Trump has two jobs
Important amendments
First
He's doing great on gun rights
So he has 92%
I'm not positive that's even the greatest
Only look
Trump has indicated like
Inclinations toward a red flag laws
Alright
So maybe the guy who promises everything has delivered on fucholand is made himself a lot of money in the
Process that's why he's the greatest president
History of the world I think is just a strong indication that Alex realizes like
Can't
They even B+ cuz that would take that as an insult my chances of getting his attention
Wow versus Howard
I told you
Very weird Lizbeth
So Alex is spend a good portion of the his
Doctor reset talking about Julian Assange needs to be pardoned
Sure seems to be one of the only things that really enlivens the
Krowd
President
Read Sign
Metaphysical
Candidate from
Months before the alarm
Julian
Sanjay
You have them released
And Julian Assange was
Julian Assange
The trigger
And he
Release
Criminal activities of the deep state
20 cars race Wars
And biowar
And coops
Pure Evil
But he did a hero's work
Instead of being carried
Down
Main Street in New York
Sitting in a text
Delivering
The shot down the Death Star reactor shaft
Julian Assange
Spent years
And years
In solitary confinement
Coryza
Gibbering
Person
Hardly talk
Seafaring
President-trump
What's there on the sidelines
God that sounds familiar
Honorable
Strength
If he doesn't
Get Juliana
Continue so long
With this fake-ass
Extradition
President
Trump has joined all those cowardly globalist
In the swamp
And makes me
Throw up
Does that mean
Support Hillary
Getting ready to
Hell no
But still
It takes a great
An absolute
So if you follow that he's saying Amazon to drop me to spiritual contract
When Trump said release these females
Then Trump didn't follow through by pardoning Assange
Giving him clemency or whatever
The case would be
And so now Julian Assange is a gibbering a person who can't talk
And if Trump
Doesn't
Pardon Assange
That'll make Outlets want to throw up
But it'll still support him
I will it look
Okay so
Your rights by Line in the Sand but also I will still support you no matter what you do
I said
Yes that you couldn't sit in your hand and then smeared on my face that was my last drop but I swear to you if you do
That will be my starting over
You spew put it in my face again
Support Hillary Clinton
Alright well she's still not running so you say anyone else starting podcast
Oh God I have no backbone
That seems to be the Republican Party
So Alex gets up
Petty grievance
A lot of like I've been wrong
This is an episode
When I've been wrong because it tells me that I'm on the right track
That mentality is going to be
Ubiquitous
Speakers
Here is one of the first points were like this is not going
I mean when Alex gets up and just rants
He does all the times you said stupid things
Is exactly what you
Things start to fall apart
I get down and
Intuit
That
The daggers of Truth
Wonder there
Chris Pine
In that place
Airfare
When they attacked me that I know
I've been given the guidance
Strike
And so instead of being cowards
Slave
We take action
Let's go ahead and bring up Tom Papa
National file
Put on this Great America
I don't think the Tom pappert exactly when Alex was going to be wrapping up this little Randy intro because
Alex just you I was in the middle of yelling
Then Alex just
Bales from the state
Not waiting for Tom to get up on stage and crucial.
A lot of open mic etiquette being broken here like if you're in trolling someone you wait onstage for them to come up you shake
Take their hand and ceremonially give them the stage
This seems like a little thing but it's an important gesture
Definitely subconsciously notices
Alex by virtue of being the biggest star in the building and most of the people there
Bossed as a position of authority
By leaving without greeting Tom onstage disrespect
Kind of like I've done my part good luck
It's very rude and it lends the whole show and air of disunity
Like the speakers are really in this together
If your goal is to have a successful performance their little things like this that you need to be mindful of and it just wild to think that Alex has been
In some form of show business or
And he doesn't
Seem to know though
Yeah absolutely
Space
Now another thing that happened
When you surprise somebody then just leave the stage is that you
Completely sandbag
The audience's trying to applaud forensic performance is an introduction
So when
You know you wrap up as an intro the next person
But they take awhile to get on stage
The Applause will be clapped out by the time they get to the pony
Instead of being able to ride in on a wave of Applause and support
You're now faced with dying enthusiasm as you begin your presentation which
Uphill battle
Instead of just getting going
You're now
Kind of in a position we have to win the crowd over
Which will see Tom tries to do with the you know here let's let's go ahead and listen to that here
Little bit difficult to follow up on
Alex is going to be
Later tonight
Tfue you try and save it would be it's hard
The following
But that's a bad piece of business
Unless you
Put something like a humorous
It's only going to Signal further week
And prove to the audience that you're not in control of the situation
But you act like you're giving the cop out for why I'm not going to be entertaining
It's hard to follow Alex it is it is fascinating how much of our
Creating those
Little moments that will
Turn just an event into a f******
Show it to the illusion of an
Actual show
Like those tiny little moments
Can change Abby
Yeah and all of our
Very applicable to help poorly there do they don't understand
Tom pepper is f***
Before he even gets off
And part of it is specifically because
Alex is a selfish prick
Doesn't understand those little things about presentation and how to be
Magnanimous be assertive given
With the the space
It's it's a it's unfortunate because
I mean you could transform something from being like well good luck
To whoever comes up next to being like we're all in this
You know they're giving Coco
Diesel fuel
People who have the talent and
Experience necessary to take that awful ending
Sacrifice their set
Turn into the host and then make the show a much better show
Not that guy
No no no
And Alex doesn't do any favors as he
T.i. goes on
U.s.
New York time
Everyday
That's right Alex
Woohoo
Can't talk to Alex
Half a team
Ahmedabad situation when he introduced him and predictably Tom is not getting much juice going from the
But to be fair his role is mostly to be the guy from National files and plug website
I would pay for the event
He doesn't really need that much reaction
Consider this
There's been three people on stage so far
I know three of them heading
Erie been introduced in the show as a hoe
Rob was there to Vamp in I guess
And then bring up Alec
Alex is headlining
Can't even Alex Jones event without him showing up to say hello
And now pump a does they're doing the actual start of the speaker's block is the head of mission
Mobile
If I'm in the audience this is already a disorienting level of disorganization from a production
Standpoint
Even if I didn't hate Alex
I would find this very unimpressive
It probably not think that this is going to be a show that has much of value
I don't know what's going on I don't know who's supposed to be the guide through the
Who's going to come up after the next speaker what's going on
Allegan a shotgun it I have loved Alex
20 years
And I have always imagined him to be competent
This is really bad
You can see Alex reinforce this feeling you have of
Dis truskin the capability the person onstage when he yells
I was trying to get through his speech
By Alex interrupting him he's subconsciously telling the audience that this guy on stage isn't worth listening
His value as a speaker is so low that you can just
Yell things out whenever you feel like it
It's very very disrespectful
They're claiming this event is about it's actually about Alex
What words do you want to hear
Yeah
So that's not great
But to be fair like I said Tom pepper
In terms of this show and what it is
He can stand to take a bullet
He's not
It's not going to be a make-or-break thing but it does give the the entire proceeding the appearance
Just sloppy
He was going to do is
He's going to do the thing in like a barback room and now he's
Suck it up
Alex gets to be the star of the show take constantly whenever Alex upstages you
Humiliates you too much fun
But it doesn't really look that bad
Exactly so he brings up the first Speaker official of the day
And the guy named Patrick Howley who works for
I'll do some self a comedian
Harvey Weinstein
Can walk again
Oh hell yeah man
This reporter for National files coming out
The joke is a little muddy though
Because I think he's trying to poke fun at the idea that people like Hillary Clinton bring children's blood but
Also speaking at an event put on by Alex Jones definitely thinks people like Hillary drink children's blood
I'll talk about that quite a bit it's a central theme joke
Point is Muddy
Groans from the office
That somebody
Did put something in it
That's not good
That's like going to Chicago open
Ever
That it is open my flight
Did you hear the news
I don't know what adrenochrome unseen is drinking but he can walk
Anyway this is Patrick Howley
He's introduced as a writer for National file but mysteriously absent
Daily Caller
When he founded the absurdly far-right blog Big League politics
Is actually still the editor-in-chief
In February 2018 The Daily Beast
Imported the big lie
Politics have been bought by a company called Mustard Seed Media
Which happens to be a political consultant named Riley O'Neal
Just finished up failing to get noted monster an alleged pedophile
I liked it in Alabama
So cool
Political consultant with great integrity
Clients is now Patrick haoles boss
Great great
Also I should point out that the financial Arrangements
Is really shady
Considering the fact that the guy who owns Mustard Seed still in
Active political
Consultant
He's being paid by candidates and politicians for covered on Big League politics
Riley O'Neal
Consulting firm called Tidewater strategy
Along with another right-wing
Consultant
That Daily Beast article points out that most
Politicians who paid O'Neil in fridge
Recovery typically politic
Like a white nationalist Paul nehlen
And former Virginia gubernatorial candidate Corey Stewart
A pattern with these guys
I'll just read to you hear from the end of this daily be started
Politics is Antonio's first foray into the political news
And at least one other media property controls has promoted his Consulting firm's clients
First in Freedom daily North Carolina Central conservative news
Efforts by to O'Neill's clients
North State Leadership Council and North Carolina gun rights
Story promoting both of those groups were written
By Spencer hardest
Who works for Tidewater
Consulting Group
Hardison began contributing to Big League politics
This month
This is all super shady s*** and anyone in
Interested at all
In any kind of journalistic Integrity would absolutely never
Have their right-wing
Propaganda blog Beyond by active GOP political
Consultant yeah that's that's
Probably unethical
How say that
Bi-level Albuquerque
But what frustrates me most is
She's apparently as some sort of syllabic meter requirements for his name
Mustard Seed Media
Big League politics and don't got the same
Beyond being a dumb dumb in a sellout I'm not particularly interested in Patrick Howley
Is very boring
And that's funny as evidenced by
So we're not going to listen to anything more than half
Now when Panther gets done with his speech
He introduces the next speaker
Do their shotgun holsinger
Apparently they don't have any don't have another house, Patrick just bring Millie Weaver
Speaking next
Who's got the chops and experience to really bring this whole thing together
Got it
So save the day talks about how Alex Jones woke her up
So how did I
Get woken up
Who woke me up
This man sitting here in this room
Alex Jones
Alex Jones is what
Started
Might reject
And everything
Send
I have been working
Hard to
Millie Weaver speaking Next In Her speech
Start by talking about Democrats and Liberals are just dumb people who don't know the truth yet
She knows this firsthand because she used to be one
Jimenez you heard she gives Alex credit for waking her up and now she's smart
This is particularly funny because I'm old enough to remember when Billy Weaver tweeted Out quote
I think Facebook is a privately owned business
There's a thing called fact
Checking Facebook
Is a public business is publicly traded
Using that argument to justify Banning Alex Jones doesn't work
She got us
Nailed it has woken up to the smartest truth there is it's so awesome when these Dum Dums get so convinced there
Write about something that they shoot off some
Completely inaccurate thing while chastising people to fact-check
Kruger or like this little never get this
Like it bad
Really, Nan is it work here
And that is provided her with a lucrative Outlet where she could be marginally famous and there was absolutely no
Accountability required
That might feel like waking up
Up to you but it's
It's called copper now
I steadfastly refuse to believe that to take anyone saying that Alex Jones
When it's just a normal everyday person saying it I think it sounds a little more reasonable because Alex can be persuasive in the
Simplicity
Seductive
You can experience that is waking up but that's not really what it is
It's more just being indoctrinated into a bad thinking pattern
Cult leaders can
Makeup believe just mad at me
One of the reasons is that bad thinking pattern is satisfying
It's very easy and it feels good mostly because it allows you to imagine that all the other people in the world are blind
Obvi
Reality that you've woken up to
And nothing is your fault
No ever
Its intellectual junk food
Just empty calories
For someone like Millie however when I hear her say that Alex woke her up there's absolutely zero chance that she isn't
S***
I just refuse to believe that anyone could work at Infowars a paying attention at all to what set on the network without realizing it out
I was just making up most of it
Basically nothing is real
Yeah the only way you can maintain respect for Alex working there is to have no principles to basically to be sleepwalking
Through life and not paying attention to anything he says
Which I would say is the opposite being woken up
Yeah that's that's like being put back to back to sleep like a little baby
Oh you don't have to worry about anything ever again just say it's the Liberals fault
The feel-good story for Millie to tell how she was a dumb liberal until the stupid texting yelled at her and showed her what reality really
It's like but it's b*******
It's just a factor
Manipulating people might be disaffected Liberals are in 2
Pendants
You know it's kind of like a right-wing propaganda version of come on in the water's fine
That says reason why all of these right-wing grifters magically have some form of this backstory
Candace Owens Brandon straka
Of the Walk Away movement hashtag walk away they all have the same thing
Because it is
It's almost like giving permission to The Listener to like you can do it
Was a liberal
And then I was offered good money for no work
And now I'm not
And you two can do that
Little boy
So Milly
Assertive
Appreciative to Alex or like you're celebrating Alex a little bit
She gets into a story
The cheese I've heard her talk about before
I find no real talent
She was covering the Kentucky Governor torque tutorials race and she has a conspiracy about it that I've
Bring up a couple times and I don't find it
Compelling but it's interesting she says something while talking about the story in this
Speech
That she should be deeply ashamed of
I went forward I pushed it
I told everyone what was
What's going on
But some of that information
We couldn't release
Because in doing
Lyngso
We would have been really
And
How many
Journalist Alto
Sitting on information
Love Tarot
But they can't
But those who were
Brave like Julian
Assange
Those who
Braids I mean
Even Chelsea Manning
I mean even
Those people
That were Brave
Hey what look what's happening
So like I said
I pray
Julian Assange
Great that she thinks Miss gendering is funny
Also if you listen carefully with Millie Weaver just did is saying to a hot mic that she's a
The coward
She's talking about some hot scoop that you had about Heather's election meddling in the Kentucky gubernatorial race incumbent
Matt Bevin loses
Bid for re-election
There's no proof that this election was still a bit here milia saying that she has information that would prove
You can't release
Because she's afraid of the consequences
He's worried about what would happen to her personally if she revealed this information
So she's keeping it to herself and allowing a fraudulent election to stand
I don't believe her at all but
If what you was saying we're true
She's a piece of s***
What happened to the Infowars model a model of being the tip of the spear
What happened to the were the ones who hit the barbed wire talk
Where's that Kamikaze mentality that Alex screams about all the time
You dare call yourself an investigative journalist didn't claim that you've proved that an election was stolen
You're not telling anyone what that proof is because you don't want the headache
What can happen to you after work
Even the dramatized
Imaginary version of herself familias
Should be ashamed
Sometimes investigative journalism
Means uncovering things that's a risk
Your comfort
I'm just part of the gig
Like imagine Upton Sinclair discovering what he did about the US Meat Packing in
Industry
What else could lead to trouble imma keep to myself I mean
There something
He showed up for the most part he's doing a great job as a perfect
The word million all the Infowars people pretend to be
Is one that requires hard work skill and a certainty of Khan
A crisis Point could come at any time when you learn something the public needs to know
But reviewing it could be bad to you personally
If you pursue this kind of work
You need to decide well ahead of time
The Come What May
You're serving the public
Pinterest damn the torpedoes
Millie's work shows that she doesn't have the skill nor does she put in the hard work
The job requires
A comments like that one that you had
She doesn't have the Constitution
M48 either
This is embarrassing
Even in her mythologized
She's literally saying
We should be
Grateful and proud of the people who are brave like Julian Assange
Do you like me
I am very clearly a coward in comparison to Beretta to Julian Assange
Peaches basically just I'm not cut out for this dude
Bright and in the meantime I'm going to insult
Transit
Hero
A f****** true
Goddamn hero
But they're lying about who is doing the who did everything that they
Pretend to have the principles necessary to do
Yeah they should be shamed by Chelsea Manning
Also Billy should probably feel weird about an advocate for Matt Bevin
After he lost re-election you want a bit of a partner
According to NPR quote in one case Bevin pardon to Man convicted of homicide
That Man's family raised more than $20,000 at a political fundraiser to help Evan pay off a debt
2015 gubernatorial
Yeah
Another one of people Bevin park with a forty-one-year-old management
Convicted of raping a nine-year-old
He pardoned another guy who killed his parents
Another was the guy you pardoned who is
Convicted of beheading of female co-worker in hiding or butylated body in a barrel
He also pardoned a woman who'd been convicted of attempt
Hire a hitman to kill her child's father and his wife
And to make it look like a murder-suicide
Interesting leave that woman was a friend of Devon's sister testified her defense during the trial
Overall he pardoned 428 people and mysteriously
95% of them white
Bevin's actions before leaving office were so shocking inoffensive that even noted morally dubious character Mitchum
McConnell called it
Matt Bevin is a disgusting piece of s***
But use the candidate
Trump was behind in that election
To him losing must be proof
Employee
Hey look I'm not going to part look
Apartment A lot of people not all good
Not all you're going to get some bad apples in the
I'm choosing to party
List
I'm sure Bevin pardon convicted murderer isn't pedophile
This isn't a problem for an Intrepid reporter like Millie
Assume plenty of them
Hey
Similarly
Money go towards
I'm not sure the only get specific case of that was that murderer I don't know is there more
I think a number of the people that he did let out people and I just ended
Dependent of all other contacts
Okay good
You know some non-violent offenders
In order to try and mask
Cheese's
20000 seems pretty cheap for a murder party
Like while he added that he needed to pay and this got him out of that people doing this
Just started raising money to I'm going Governor's to get a pardon for your loved ones or somebody not all of them are blatantly
I'm not saying all of them are but I'm sure you could find a couple shirt
We got blown out here you might still pardon somebody I saw his Twitter
So Milly speech is pretty short and very embarrassing that she should do
I really feel bad about it
Things that she says understanding
So now when she's done
We could host
But it's not Tom pepper
It's probably due Rob Duke
Millie Weaver is proof that
Conservatives are way better looking
Liberals that's not
Call Idaho
What
Watch Billy's work grow and evolve throughout the many years one of them
Great collaboration
Was helping her
Rainbow snatch
Birthday
If You Seen Her rainbow stats videos are off
Strange Bragg wow
So now we know who to blame for that
I don't understand how you can
Be a woman in
Still be there
Like just if you meant that
Sing that they say
The first thing is look at how good she look right
If I were if I were producing comedy show and the house
Said something like that about a female comic who is on the lineup
I've never broke up again
That might be really bad for everyone involved but I would be sure to never booked them
Again that capacity special
Inappropriate behavior
Attractiveness or unattractiveness
Has nothing to do with why you're here
What she is bringing to the table
Ostensible value as a
The person
To make it always
Constantly about attractiveness and s*******
Is a demeaning
On a level
Buried
It's an it you'll see more of it and they just keep it look
I know you push it in my face
For the 4th
But I swear to God that is my Line in the Sand
Enemy I think they like me
Interesting conversation
I'm possibly about like
It not bothering Millie and that's fine she has the right to not be bothered by it
It's still just s*** Behavior
So if you get another guest brings up another speaker
Interesting
Complained about the scammers on the right
People like Ben Shapiro and Crowder and all them
Olivarez
Steamed
Speakers
During the Q&A
Willie
To work in pain
Now I'm going to Grant the people like Steven Crowder Ben Shapiro Charlie Kirk way way more successful
Their game with dunking on people on the street
80% of Infowars field pieces are
Like that number goes up to 90 if you're just talking about Owen Shroyer is work
They haven't figured out how to edit the video to make
Them look good
See Ben Shapiro and those guys they edit the videos to make it look like they did do
I think some of the Infowars ones
Are successful in that just also think that maybe they're not as
Good now we just seen too many anymore yelling
More yelling base then Ben Shapiro's like Fast talking points
Wingstop
So this guy's name is Pete d'abrosca
Trying to run for the US House in North Carolina
The problem was the peat registered to vote as a republican in his address on December 3rd but he filed as a candidate to Q
Quickly thereafter
North Carolina GOP as a rule that candidates are invalid if they file to run within 90 days of registering as a Republican
Which is far as rules go makes total sense to me why would you want someone to stay
I'll register on the day of the primary even though I'm a
Republican and I'll just do whatever I want
Of course
Because Peter the kind of guy who'd show up at an Infowars rally he's decided that he's the victim in this whole thing
Challenges decision
Honestly it's pathetic these guys can't just say I wasn't aware that rule and honestly I should have planned this out a little better
Had everything in order I'll take that as a lesson
I'll follow the rules next time
It can't do that imagine one of these
People just finally
Please say
My bad
Every instance of them being incompetent as proof of a conspiracy to keep the real conservatives down or some s***
It's such a week
Cowardly posture particularly coming from the people
Habitat lecturing people
Personal responsibility
Jared Holz headline at rightwingwatch really sums it up perfectly
Anti-immigrant bloggers dreams of Congress crushed by own incompetence
Jared's article that leads
In the appeal was quote
What's the harm of putting mr. Roscoe on the ballot
Your lawyer's best job is basically winking and saying come out
His appeal was unanimously
This guy Pete is a dumb dumb but he's a dumb dumb wants to end all immigration as a story about running for
Congress that can be spun in a way as to make him look like a
So he get to speak
Those two things
Time to go hand
It was about at this point in the rally when I was watching it. I started to get a little bit
Depressed
The audience's problems for the mythology is alleged popularity
Any speakers or just the worse
And not in the sense that they're horrible people
Apple speaker
Patrick Howley was trying to be funny because with
Millie Weaver is a monotone
And now there's a whatever he's doing
Cuz I went to the store and I got a six-pack at about this point
F*** that really doesn't
Feel like anybody
More than 20 minutes before they were about to go up
You know what
He did he had a long and I got a bunch of paper is ready
I can listen to hours of Infowars b******* and even some other particularly unsavory s*** just keep moving
There's such an air of sadness and
Rodriguez free speech Summit
It really bums me out there's the illusion
When you're just listen
Sing to the show that you're listening along with thousands
But when you see that you're at a show
Sparsely attended
Even if you're online there was only 30 people around
Is it's a lot sadder
Yeah it's a lot Saturday
I think when you watch the actual show
Controlled environment in a lot of those production aspects of it can be handled much more easily
So
Anyway
Like I mentioned he's a player and he he
No complaining about these right-wing people
Going out dunking on college kids and random people on the street
Not recognizing that the
Essential pieces in Forest business model
But you'll soon as super anti-immigrant and one of his argument seems to be that they don't share American values
And he talks about he uses a statistic here that I think is a real teachable moment
Berlin jail
Replace
Not respecting
I'm looking forward to the
So this dude is like he's against illegal immigration he's also against
Legal immigration
So the pictures in the middle of the fundamental rights that Americans have are not valued by Emma Gray
What he's doing is actually misusing
Statistics
There's no reason for him
Statistics about hispanic attitudes
Yes absolutely no way of knowing what proportion of the Hispanic people in that
Study were born in the United States
He's just conflating Hispanic whatever
Rent which is kind of the point for people like him
The conversation we're having appears to be about immigration with a very loud subtext is non-whites
If Swedish people came over but that's not immigration they were born here probably or whatever
62% number he's siding about Hispanics not respecting others rights
A 2017 study published by the Cato in
But the question was
Do you respect others right
Question is posed in the study was if people don't
Respect others don't deserve the right of
Free speech
That's not the same question
I can understand how is your already posture
Spanish people you're looking for ways to justify your
You could get sloppy and choose the
It doesn't work
Also 36% of white people answer the question the same ways or wrestle with that couple with that one
Probably from Sweden classic case of
He can take the stat misrepresented used
Hispanic
He seems to not want to report
In the same study 7
7% of Hispanic people agreed that quote
It would be difficult to ban hate speech
Some people can't what hate speech is
Seems to indicate a Rattata
Since to actually bam this stuff
And this is with a
He do in
God Knows Why
But they're throwing
Includes I wanted to I could have some fun with that study
I could tell you
44% of Republicans and that studies the Holocaust denier shouldn't be allowed to
To speak on college campus
Oh no they're in trouble that
Also I should point out that 47% of Republicans people who publicly criticize or disrespected
Please China be allowed to speak at college campus
So I guess you could draw the conclusion
From that study Republicans prefer Holocaust
It's cherry picking numbers and connecting them where they may not become
I mean but also that does kind of
Sure
I don't know if it's an appropriate use of the study to
There's a lot of numbers in
If you want to
It's usually best to know what
The questions are being asked that lead to the status though
Expecting that of this piece
Guy seems like a big
Ask
Man that's that's a heartening level of response from Republicans
Considering they don't even know how many Holocaust deniers
Tigers that they support out of regular
Let's get back to that 77% of people in the Hispanic Community. Wanting to ban free speaker
You do hate speech cuz we can't
Like what it is
Zola
What is Holocaust denial
Not good
So Alex seems to not be into this dude speech
Sharky's talking about like
Policy things
Alex
Cut them off
Here with your policy
You do not go
Stay
Abdominal
Almost
I promise
Peter Cetera
And I love you
BoBoiBoy the audiences laughing because Alex has walked up on stage
Who is standing next to him ominously like
You got to get off
That is exactly how I used to run it over
Now Alex is a host
Naturally
Inchoate
It's very it's very rough
What kind of droning on was a little bit
And so
You know Pete was talking about how evil immigration is as a whole
Alex takes that Steven starts screaming about it
We love me
India Mexico
You're up wherever
They're being used as a tool
To destroy our American Republic
Do we have a right
Water is a wonderful thing
The pleasure town of Samantha
And so we love our fellow humans we want to program future
But he's right
The globalist are using uncontrolled immigration as a weapon as a giant sucking sound
What the late great
Patriot from Texas Ross Perot said to lower our wages
Can we see it as a weapon and we rushed Dexter
Engaged
Performative outrage that you can see like I'm turning it on
I just got to snap this back into place
He brings up another Harvey on the few days like I always had other we just had a real bad answer I'm going to
Steve Harvey real quick and we'll get this back out of Santa
So I was introduced as the next speaker in much like Rob could
Come on stage and after Billy without saying
She was hot Alex has the same
Young lady
Deanna Lorraine is amazing she's so smart
Bubbly she's on fire
He's running
Against
Nancy Pelosi age
Hi sexy lady too smart
That's crazy
The next speaker up is Deanna Lorraine who was recently a guest on Alex's shall we talked about her a little bit
I'm not particularly interested in her since Barn divine intervention
No idea who she is
She's got this crowd excited cuz they're acting like she's running against Nancy Pelosi but she hasn't even won the GOP Primary yet
She's not making that general elections is a classic counting chickens
Situation
Vaccine chip
I'm noticing a bit of a trend
This point what I'm watching it
It seems like a number these speakers are actually just hopelessly lost congressional candidates
Take whatever
He doesn't even on the ballot and he was up there giving the stump speech by his policy platform
And that Deanna Lorraine is here to campaign
It's almost like a political sideshow
Where are you know the people who aren't even serious enough to be at CPAC
Or trying to pick up whatever scraps they can find
That's a real bummer to be on the side show when the main show involved
Carpe donktum and Rick
From Pawn Stars
I dumped him
Was there he was
Slideshow
Probably
So do you wanna has
Stop that she pulled that you wants to brag about
The computer chip out of a homeless guy
Although that does happen at the end of this rally
Very sad
So what I didn't respond to that
The b**** move a excuse my language but we're allowed to have free speech
And I flew a plane around San Francisco
The Ted Pelosi for prison
Because we need
To have her accountable for her crimes against America
And it is
Thank you it's the most liberal District of America and people said oh no don't fly a plane around that says pillow
Pelosi for prison
That's not something you should do
So Deanna is assertive here that San Francisco's most liberal District in the United States
First of all San Francisco is not a district
He's talking about California's 12th
Congressional district which doesn't actually even contain all of San Francisco
Sum of 7
Cisco's in the 14th
Also
California's 12th is not the most liberal District in country
This measurement is captured by the cook political report partisan voter index
Or the pvi
Send it started in 1997 the PPI is considered one of the most solid Tools in terms of understanding
Partisan leanings broken-down on a granular level in everything
Congressional
California's 12th District has a Democrat + 37 pvi which is a strong leading Democrat
For sure
There's no arguing
However
You don't have to look very far to find a stronger leading District because
California's 13th of the PPI of democrat
+ 40
The District of Columbia and Democrat + 43 Illinois 7th as Democrat + 38
New York's 5th is
+ 37/7
Is + 38
The 13th is + 43
Pennsylvania 2nd District is Democrat + 40
Annie actually the most liberal District
Country is New York's 50
Coming in at + 44
I know that is not where Alexandria ocasio-cortez got elected
She's from the 14
District
Which is only Democrat + 29
San Francisco isn't the most liberal disc
Certain country but it feels like
Get to these sort of hardcore
Conservatives
Because the city and the surrounding area played such an important role in
The activism in the 60s
Just lingers to this day to make San Francisco cultural villain
Conservatives
Feels like the most liberal District but it's not
Honestly this feels more like Deanna giving herself excuses for why she's inevitably
The selection
Hopefully not the GOP Primary though
Trouble I would assume the people were advising enough to rent out a plane
Bob because the disc
Too liberal. Because her candidacy is
The farce and it seems like
I mean not just that
Come up with an original
My dear lady
Hey man
Here's the thing all you liberals go to
Prison
Here's the thing
You father playing around
Indiana
I don't believe this is real
Honest I hope this is okay but I'm going to play a little
22nd voicemail from someone
That that song by Pelosi for prison Banner in the air in Sanford
I'm going to play a quick
Clap
Why don't you call and it's already
Adopt a pet
Make It Rain
Make your rapist America
These are the people that were up against you guys there we are at War
And we need to fight
We need to fight these are the real fascist
I don't believe for a second that that's a real voicemail that some of us are playing the f*** out
A couple reasons why
The first is it that voicemail started with the guy saying I got your text message seems weird
About how did you see did you see the plane that I flew
Why is Deanna texting with the guys allegedly leaving a random voicemail everything her Pelosi plane
Second the idea that someone who doesn't like
Lucy playing call Iran
The death camps
Because that's where we're going that's absurd
The first problem is with his is it
That's primarily an obsession of the right
People like Alex Indiana
Alex has been yelling about FEMA camps being right around the corner for over a decade and then that time of
Never heard any of his enemies really suggest that they were interested in putting people in Canada
The angry Democrat can't because you're conservative is a conservative Boogeyman
Not a real thing
But more importantly she's f****** up the whole game
The death camps in shade or supposed to be being pushed by people who were super fart
The Socialist and communist
That's where the future narrative is supposed to live
The people who are supposed to want to make those
Camps are also the people in the left who don't really like Nancy Pelosi
The idea that you're going to offend a leftist by bashing Pelosi
Laughable
They may vote for her overweening like DNR
I've literally zero. The Deanna had some record that for so she could play it and show how much airplane is pissing off the den
That's the only currency these idiot app
The notion that their ideas and actions of value because they make their political opposition angry
It's honestly super sad yeah
Also I saw a picture of the banner that you flew
And it doesn't have a phone number on
Entertainment
A shity photoshopped like it's a banner flying behind an airplane that has
Perfectly right angles on it it's directed exactly the camera has no Shadows are wrinkles or anything
It's very very sad
Deanna posted a picture of the banner with a captcha
It's raining liberal tears in San Francisco right now
Another words for how lame
See pictures elsewhere of the banner
It's like folded over itself like as any battery care
Saw that it was like that doesn't look good on my on my website I'm going to take a picture that says
Leave for son
Looks
Look desperate
Chicago
Very sad
Listen to voicemail
To that is not somebody who's angry
Okay and
You are a
And so we are going to keep going on that you're a fat
Defcamp check that box
Do deaf
Camp alright
You're a bad person anyways see you at brunch tomorrow bye
Done are we get another speaker that Alex has now taken over as just a host
I guess because he comes up
You bet
But hey
We're here
Enrique
Get up here and kick their ass
And with four drinks in here
Available this guy right now
Yeah it should be part of that Alex is clearly pretty drunk
It gets worse later
Where is really showing
The proud boys
Be mine real
At what sort of secret missions Alex's refer him to the eggplant with them
It could either be not masturbating naming a bunch of cereals
Elaborate plots to Spring Rodger Stone from prison
Or they could just terrorizing on white person but beyond that tario is another hopelessly doomed aspiring
Congressional candidate
He's running for housing Florida and there's no chance in hell he's winning and I doubt he's even going to win the
As we know without Stone
In Florida you got no chance
This event for all this pretence of being a free speech Summit really just
Feels like a rally for xenophobic
Extreme right-wing actually candidates
Hey KK
Promise for nothing
Time is Grimm
Still not full and the more exotic congressional candidates they have coming
Good morning feels like
Desperately trying to assert their relevance to a bunch of empty chairs
I don't know how else to put it
This is a bummer
Not because
That kind of evil
Seattle
Trump's rallies are a bummer cuz they're scared
Sad sad sad
Sad world dies
Definitely
I think it's
They have to be
Like it has to start Dawning on these right-wing grifters
That they got pushed out
By their own grift
You know like
C-pack used to be for normal people and then pay got their own big place where they got to be conspiracy crazy
Enough sebak is the conspiracy crazy they're stealing their
Conspiracy crazy
So they're going well
Of like what is okay
The grifter crazy
We might use you if we need right right we are never going to let you at the table like James
Pokefan Candace Owens and Charlie Kirk
Car speakers
Headlining future speakers at CPAC
These people are in a quarter
Purple Ballroom
But they had to rent out themselves
And they're sad
Yeah I feel like this is like
Walmart
Moved in on the conspiracy grifter and pushed all these mom-and-pop conspiracy grifters into the knot
Territory
Hey I mean look
That's a little bit of a simple analogy but there might be something behind
We are brave
Interesting thought
Enrique starts bragging
About all the things that he's banned from
Which seems to be a theme like some of these people were actually kicked off a bunch of stuff
Like it seems like they're really into talking about how many things are banned from
Cuz that gives them some kind of a capon
Just a couple miles away from here on band on
I'm going to see
Seabeck
Can't go in there
I'm banned off of
Here we go I got a list
I should have the
Scroll through it
So I've been banned off Facebook
19 *
Instagram four times
Twitter 19 time
PayPal Airbnb
Alex I can't keep going with my wrist yesterday
Alex is
Pretty drop
Entrapment
No I think I think
Reception from the audience
It's catch-as-catch-can
But
Henrico it is important poorly received as let's say that first guy with the bad comedy
Dabrowska with his boring ass
Good xenophobic policy my papers
Enrique is doing okay that that is one of those situations
Drunk
Voorhees
Trying to help
From the yard as opposed to disrupt
Yeah
Bell Alex
Alex gets up
I have in my notes Here
He's problem drunk
The last stages of gulag
And they're doing that to Rodger Stone right now
It's not about silencing us it's not about taking our finances it's about putting us in jail they want us long and they
One is dead
Lowe's
Amen to that
Ziffy
So now we're at the point where they're screaming about
The town is really naked a like
We're also
20 Kellogg's
Not only is the message they want to put us in a gulag and they want to kill us
You can't trust the people in this room
Evil
Wants to go ahead
And take over this country we call it socialism we call it communism is Satanism it's evil sure
It is here
What we do here loved it probably in this room
How many somebody infiltrated in here
We have today just enjoy your goddamn rally
I have gathered you all tonight
Slowly reveal who did the cry
Where can I find the FBI murder mystery Mouse
Alex Joseph
NFL start running from route
Perfect
Has all the potential of equate you don't need to
Gas stations
Computer
So he gets done with his paranoid
Speech Alex comes up to introduce the next speaker and
He is
I'll tell you what they fear
The past already been laid out
Worldwide
And we're going today
And the worse things get the more people are going understand it
Mariah
Lee Stranahan is investigative journalist
He's works
For all the big leftist Publications
The route 3
Breitbart
He's worked for them all
Solely Stranahan's the next speaker and finally we have someone who's not running a Congressional Campaign
He speaks mostly be about the Ukraine whistleblower
The crowd to keep changing his supposed name
I tried to follow a
And his speech
But I also found myself not very
It seems like it's Point may have been to be wary of the CIA and if that's what he's getting at
Good for you
Sure
Maryville
Something here
Who got a note
Alex's problematically drunk now
Have you called Breitbart a leftist publication
Yeah
This is where I started to get worried
And the vibe started the trans
This event is really bad
All right how far is it
What
How far into the events are we
Maybe an hour
I don't know how long it's supposed to go but it ends up going 3 hours
Alright
So
He's giving his speech
And it's
Really just
Along the lines like I said he keeps getting the crowd to chant the whistleblowers name
And it's not a very long speech
But he gets interrupted by Rob do
In the middle of it Mike down for this because
Where Alex takes this
Is
Japan for the
Words really really all Eric ciaramella
Panama band on video and that's where we're going to put this up
Later tonight the system and if there's
The judge in the stone show trial says don't send the name of the jerseys under federal laws will be probably
Because the Democratic party operatives and they're panicking right now and we put out the names of the jury
And now he's burning in hell
Because her threats
We're cold
We called them
And no
That Amy Berman Jackson Burns in hell
Loser say this is a speaker
It is hard to follow Alex Jones
Alright I understand that I was pretty drunk by this point
Completely lost his ability to control himself but if I had known it was going on
I would think this was a man celebrating after murdering address
People don't typically help others still alive
Also Rob do is the saddest little boy here scampering up to the mic
Audience excited about how dangerous it is to say this whistleblowers name
The f****** out there man
They are not f***
Checking out there they are effing
Let's recall that he specifically did not use the word f*** it better not be speech
It's such a fetishization is manufactured in Imagine persecution
Yeah like this is
The end result of Alex's
Horribly misguided philosophy that you know that you're right when you're getting
Attacked would you even expressed at the beginning of his speech
You check at the at the start
If you internalize that believe
Then you'll interpret attacks
It's being proof
But you're right
What gives you the validation and a bit of a dopamine Rush
We're doing it
What happens when you're not getting attacked and you're very sad. It is just happening and no one cares
Well then
You might just need to interrupt Lee Stranahan to pretend
You just
Might get attacked at some point we could then prove that you're right
And give you the validation you so desperately crave
Tying your value to how negatively people respond to you is a very sad game and it runs so consistently through these people
Rob's introjection here to Deanna's
Clearly fake voicemail there like
Needing that Rush
Turn the oppositional Defiance disorder into
So Alex's maybe killed Amy Berman Jackson
Sandwiches
Top news
I have not checked on her recent
So weird that is a weird thing to say at least you see there the cop out of it's hard to fight
Fallout
The trend Alex interrupt their like how
It's surrender in general cuz he has a resume
He's an actual report
He cares too much about this and keeps us
Speed short
He's prepared
And so he can
Deflected
But still that
Alex interrupting and yelling about 80 bourbon
It is only responsible how do you follow Alex
He's out there
Yay so he finishes up his speech
Alex is still being the house
And he seems to have forgotten
Who's coming up now
I got my nuts
Alright
We're having a good night tonight to 5:30 and it's amazing
Thanks, 911 let's go ahead and bring up
Amorality
NSA
We got to show Bill Benny
You wanted to, couldn't, is working on a project
They should have Tommy Collins my partner on
He's working with me
On major
Operation
So I've never met Tommy Collins but I'm excited too
Have them on
So Tommy come on up here
Thank you so much
This show needs a producer's touch
Because it's sloppy
I know that Alex is drunk and he's a force of nature so no amount of production
Is really going to help with that little things
In terms of making this not seem like a ridiculous
Amateurs
Spectacle
The one you could have had the speakers list up there like
Taped to the podium
Accidentally forget IT Crowd to grab it
Because he has no idea who's coming up next
Another thing that might have been good having
How to beat the people he's going to introduce introduce
Alex lagina
Emily has no idea of Tommy is a man or a woman and yet here he is presented with an expert because William Benny didn't want to show up
Tommy Collins runs a group called America restore
I admit that I don't know what that was all about but I do check out their face
What's that
Look at that another person crazy
On February 26th 2020
2020 America restored posted a link to an article with the headline
Promises to terminate program
This was such a blade
These are b******* from some dumb blog do they use the picture of the NBC News logo on it imply credibility
It is so flagrant that even the commenters had to point out that this was a fake story
As of February 29th
This post is still up on their page
I don't know
Brother about page
Christian
List Outlet pushing for what you might describe as either Christian LED Nation or theocracy depending on your point of view
I don't really care too much about this stuff
Because honestly I looked at it and I think from some of the metrics
Pretty clear that a lot of the members of
A group of bots
Anyway I guess that maybe Tommy works as William Benny on some stuff which is
Completely nuts
Supposed to be the former technical
Fake things on Facebook
Well she has a part-time job
What a tag team
So
Tommy gets up
And
Cheat Her speech is obviously about William Binney
That's all
And I would say if you listen carefully
I don't think she
Has a handle on the
Details
Of the things that bill does
Bill if you guys don't know who he is Bill Binney and on most people do but I'll give you a little run-down Bilby
Is the man that's responsible for building out about
Two-thirds of the modern-day NSA
And he left in the
Don't you know early 2000's and when he left there
They're still using
I shouldn't say I'm here I either he they're still use heat they're still using the stuff that he had originally
Developed
Powerful
Bill has been continuing to work on things
I hit stuff with so Innovative at that time
They've never been able to get better
So that's that's green how or who made some stuff
It's really powerful
You make stuff that's really good stuff these things
Powerful
Sometimes I'll be working on some things and I'll think this is a good stuff
Man I just don't know how to
You wrote a better sweet most everybody there
What are you talkin about
The national stuff agency
Honestly kind of wonder if she's even there at the request of William
Most of her speech is pushing the conspiracy that the guccifer hack
Couldn't have been done remotely over
The internet
Would you the position that William Benny has definitely advance
We also recanted it in 2018
When Duncan Campbell demonstrated to him arrive abeka
Conclusion manipulate
I honestly have no idea what's going on here but I don't exclude the possibility that William Benny has nothing
To do with her speech in the present day
The only connection between Tommy and Benny that I can find online is from 2018
An interview that she did with him
Prior to
To the point where Benny walk back the gusev
Yeah
I have no idea what's going on here
I'd like this is booking that I would have avoided
If I were Infowars
It raises more questions than answers
Provides
Amateurish
This lineup is already overbooked
There's no need for this this is not bring anything to the table
I told today was a good day
So
The reason
Bedtime
She's there
And read what you got on
Stage honest
Is that she promised information
In-N-Out
Big Bill Bennington working on
So they think they're going to break some big news
Right and that apparently the bills been working
Turn on thing
And she gets into it here in this
That's what builds stuff did it pick needles out of haystack it was proven that bill would have asked
Actually discovered 9/11 before it happened bills
Forte is bald
Data his Forte
Meaning of forte unparalleled
Nothing out there like it it's never been reinvented the NSA is enough to get better
Bill's the bomb he has technology that's never been recreated
Great
Until now
You guys
No right now
Go up to this date has never ever even ask for money for a spa
Speaking engagements never wanted anyone to ever accuse him
Yeah you never worked up she never got money on the movie nothing
You don't want to listen to this you guys
I told that's my bills on board with a non-for-profit
Because this is what we're going to do we're going to build out bills technology right now and we need every freedom-loving America
Can to get on board
Even I was caught a little bit off guard when it's turned into a situation where Tommy is asking for money to make this super powerful technology to belies
Stop 911
About this
What you don't need bills tattoo I predicted 9/11
Considering almost all of Alex's credibility is based on employment to have done just that
Play some money
Second
Do you work for the NSA online license
Hired in October 2001
Suspiciously basically
I can't imagine that a roomful of likes
60 people are going to raise funds to provide some kind of Miracle technology
Considering he was literally at the NSA in a position to use all of his genius at the time when the worst terrorist attack on us soil
No heat what you're missing is he actually created
Mark Wahlberg who would have stopped 9/11
If he was there
Who's all goddamn Hustle
And it said on the one hand on the other hand
I got a pretty big charge at a little response Tommy got after yelling until now she really thought there was going to
Harry Potter
I was very funny I felt that pain entirely
You know granted in those situations are trying to get a laugh not raise funds for an imaginary Splinter Hi-Tech
Intelligence operation
Field crypto-fascist
I can't imagine the feeling
If I say something wrong
Are they going to kill me somebody
Is get out you just get rushed off stage cuz once it becomes clear
She's trying to raise money
He still needs him as a expert on
Non-Stop
And so Alex
Japanese
Boo
No backstory
Admittedly in US history
George Washington was great because
William Benny is like a
Savon George Washington
The whole modern essay
Anyone who expose the corruption
They went after a man
And try to Kelly
Is make a big deal about it they poisoning
Did the Senate
I'll on Cherry lost his legs
He's a real patreon
Loses legs cuz it was poison
He has diabetes
They could play Poison them with sugar Dan
Alex technology and I think this clip is actually like a really
Amazing little demonstration of Alex not what he's about to say when he starts a sentence
You gotta follow this track
That's what people have gone through to bring you
Just level information
We're talkin about
3D imaging
Digital quana
Computing mapping
And
Literally being able to
Judge pre-crime
The system didn't want to use that
I'm not even sure I'm for that
But
They wanted it all.
Continue they use the computers.
Continue the crime
And the continued the criminality
So you see what happened there is that Alex got caught up and rambling about how Bill Binney at this amazing technology created at the globe
Wanted to use
Is 3D imaging and all that so sophisticated
Detect crimes
Before they happen
As Alex is talking he realizes that he's describing something he categorically
Has to be opposed to
Is archetypical dystopian fiction stuff
It is literally the government
Watching you all the time
So he expresses that he be in favor of it and then does a little sleight of hand completely flips old story
That's why they tried to continue it and he's even though but that's only because he was going to stop 911
He had to retire
As soon as he realizes that he needs to be against this Minority Report Technologies pretending Benny made
He knows
The globalists now have to be in favor of it
Reproduction
As if he didn't save they were trying to stop Benny like 10 seconds
Nothing Alex says means anything users they could all this
In this next clip we get another introduction it's a Infowars stalwart
It's Barrett
Lowe's
Next speaker coming up
He's destroyed
Owen Shroyer come out here
Really
We're winning
The goblin for losing
And Judge Amy Berman Jackson is getting ready for a prison cell
Always a good time
Going to be part of x-ray
Believe me we're winning
Alright alright alright alright
There's a very interesting Dynamic it played this free speech Summit
One thing is that Owen isn't drinking
Consistent motivation
He comes off as a level-headed comparison to be
Play Drunk Alexandra grab-bag of losers who has spoken so far
This might be my Somali pirates
But you kind of have to give it up to Owen for keeping his wits about him when he could have just got wasted and had a good time
The second Dynamic is important
It's still mostly empty but what's happened is that at least by the point When likely Stranahan was on stage
Nick Fuentes has fans showed up
No papers are there and they make up significant portion
Another crowd and say like
We've only talked about Nick Fuentes showing up on Alex's show in past
But he's been aghast
Couple times 2
I've mentioned this a number of times that the younger more online radical types are more likely to show up on
Joe and Nick is a prime example of that
Alex is a bit of an embarrassing old man for them to utilize its platform to disseminate their views but privately their own
Also probably doing impressions about other women
Talking about gay frogs
Owen is cooler
Is Identity the most
To them okay that's
That's fair
His identity is mostly caught up in the cup Destroyer imagery and
Is public existence doesn't have the same baggage that Alex.
He's only really been on Infowars for a few years and most of that time is coverage has mostly been the anti-sjw stuff
Acting like a big boy
Plus working in his favor is affected
I don't realize a bad
You can hear from that much larger Ovation that Owen got
He came to the stage that the
In the room is shifted
And that's because the Fuentes fans are there
And someone they like his taking the stage
It's very strange to see high-status Shroyer
It's entirely possible that I'm just being Blinded By The Staggering incompetence.
But he's showing a confident in charge present
And that's pretty weird
I don't like it I don't like the I don't like the way people to clap I don't like him coming up like
Walking up to the podium be like all right
Alright I know you love that guy I don't I don't like it at all
If it makes you feel any better they don't like him enough to laugh at a bad joke
But I another indication is so I was live all day from c-pack I saw a lot of you there
I didn't have time to eat or shower I go back to my hotel I change and I show up today and I realized
I forgot my belt
So please nobody tell Rodger Stone
Legend Lance
Who did not land as well as I think
The rice getting too good
Call DJ.
Adrenochrome
Talking about why he likes working
I'm lazy
Yeah
I don't really like planned speaking events
Because I'd rather speak from the heart
And
I feel like there's some sort of pressure to prepare something when you come up here but
So much
And there's no other platform like it
And
Alex has left the building its kind like Austin
Some powers like where's my
My father's like
Galaxy 11
No but seriously I can't think Alex enough for building a platform because there is no other platform that would allow me to do what
Totally
I think that's accurate yeah yeah yeah
You are correct
I can't dispute any of you like
Factual
Statements is magnificent don't think there's any virtue
It's like people watch
Talented performers
And they're like look at how effortless
This is
I shouldn't have to do any work
And they don't realize how much effort it
To get to the point where it looks like you're not try
It's so much work you learn that by trying
Stop doing that you can get a good job
Owen razzing
Alex not being in the room
And he's I think he's a little bit hurt by that actually
You making a joke about it and that's it that's all good
It's all good
He brings it back up at the end of the speech
So funny and then this is where things get
Buckwild
Nick Winters is coming up next
There's Alex
Hey Alex thanks for missing my speech man really meant a lot
Really meant a lot man
No seriously I wish I was I was I was thinking you
And I want to make sure you're here to introduce Nick Fuentes
But you guys really are the revolution you really are
Patriot and we forgot what it's like to work at Infowars latest until
Come on let's go
And we've got
We got General Flynn son here
Denied
So you need to come up there and pick
So if you recall Alex met Ivan raiklin the last time you rented at the
The DC Press Club did a big press event about how he wasn't on social media
I suspect part of the reason they became Fast Friends is that Ivan is an associate of the Flynn family and Alex wanted any
Kind of access he could
I even tried to run
In the 2018 Senate race in Virginia but was disqualified
Because of invalid signatures
But as best as I can tell he's not in a dude
Congressional candidate situation in this cycle currently
So that means you probably just here to talk s*** and Mike Flynn Jr is a guaranteed pass to get on stage
This is surreal stuff
This kid like
I I got a very visceral reaction
I totally get that
That reminds me so much of what I would have days without like to work
That's such like when I was a baby,
Empress has left the room
Friend of the show but when I was like a year in and Marty was headlining at the middle of the
Nowhere show
Bridgeport or whatever
Great Berrington
And it's like he walked out of the room during my feature set and I was just
Oh no
My hero doesn't like
But you realize sometimes people alive
Simile
Bikeland Juniors spare
So Alex really wants Mike Flynn Jr to come on stage
He's bringing Ivan onstage explicitly
And here is Ivins worth
Hey Ivan drink Patriot US Army Officer lawyer
Differences don't Stacy formulaic
Bring up bring up here
You said he was glad you're on there I said no
Alright so who's out here who's motivated today
So he said he said no yeah
You're right there with your on air
This is Michelle in Fuller
Very weird
Like what the f*** is going on like Ivan
Yeah I even end up spending about
3 minutes talking about like
I don't know why I'm up here
He's just
Kind of weird
It becomes really clear what he's doing here and then everything
Explode
This is this is
Big Tech takedown
That's 2020
How would you do that
Self plug
I'm part of the company called hippie it's a search engine
Take a look
Anybody use it
Yepi.com
Safe secure search
So here we have become clear
From this group
Are much like when Tommy Collins got into it being like this being a fundraising thing Alex
Pretty quickly get up onstage here to to cut this off
Big Shaq
Hey I like General. You get up here and talk
Ivan raiklin on Twitter
Alright
America is a way that's what's happening now get ready for
Hi both
So there's so much going on.
Falling for the same
Foolish perception the top Shark Tank
Yeah I got a fundraising this beleaguered
And then
I think Alex said
The speech that Ivan was given was going into business for himself
So all bets are off
Ivan's already said no to Alex's request for Flynn to speak
Ivan's being a dick so Alex forces the issue
Ivan leave stage
Pop-ups
But unbeknownst to him
Mike Flynn Jr his come on stage behind him
Alex in my greet each other and Alex Bumble that we talked online
Before
This becomes his big victory
He's now got Mike Flynn Jr
Okay
Weather
The fuk is about to happen
Bump that bites not itch
As exciting is
Oh god dammit
I'm coming out with his dad's in a sentence
Watch fireworks
Verizon
F****** wasted
Flynn starts talking about how this russiagate things been real hard
And so here's
It is well
I can tell you that
You know I I kind of describe what
What's been going on with
With my family and everything else that's that's having with all this
Yeah Russia gate s*** in
It's like kind of like a
This long boxing match
Time in 215 Brown now we feel like things
Kind of winding down and
I have a really difficult time with this situation because on the one hand Mike Flynn Jr is a dumb dumb
And he's definitely spreading misinformation on
But on the other hand I don't want to shoot him too hard when he's talking about how this
The effect this investigation has had on his family
Because on some level that still feels like it would be shity
Like his mother as far as I know wasn't involved in any of this
Find some sort of empathy it's important
Hold on to some of their are people involved in that family there are having to suffer consequences because
These people action
No granted that's the same for all sorts of people who are related to criminals
You know it's not it's how I don't want to I don't want to
Punch tool
You're right
Suck my foot
So anyway I just pulled this quit because there's no boxing match in the present-day there will ever be in the city
Brown professional boxing limits fights
Professional boxing limited flights to 12 rounds
1982 Ray Mancini
Call Kim
In a match that went to the 15th round which resulted in Kim
Collapsing into a coma immediately after the fight
Getting emergency brain surgery and dying four days later
Richland Junior was like one-year-old and that happened so his whole life boxing matches have been 12 rounds
He was referencing the old days 1920 Queen's rules when you would fight
Until one guy fell to the ground
20 rounds unless multiple sterilizer
Sure whatever
Anyway I'm talks about how innocent and Alex control himself he has to jump
And look I'm not up here
Myopathy right now looking for something I'm just
I'm just letting you know that
You mean this is the truth
What happened
Miami
My mother's not guilty of anything
I think I seem to think about your nose at and
It has also
So look at
Last thing I'll say is that
B complex
Question answer about your father is a patriot and what you guys went through in the Vintage
Location now
It's a whole life coming down
And Rodger Stone tell him what happened
Tell him in 5 minutes what happened what you guys went through that the American Patriot
Yet
This telling me that Alex has tried to get my Flynn on his show and he said
This is his opportunity and the speech that is given is not going
The directions necessarily that our tentative it's not Sensational enough
He's trying to direct
Pops up on stage
And he says that
WinStar trying to answer that question and it's not well enough
All the sudden this stuff
You know kind of came down with
With having to
Ohio lawyers in end
Yeah well I mean
He day when I visited my father because he was outspoken on a number of things but the main thing was Obama's
Signature foreign policy which was which was it which was the
The Iran deal
Mini Iran Iran Iran
But I can say that
It was it was a big thing that he was
Yeah that he was
He was highly against and there's a lot of people on
Major major critical that
Alex cannot handle this
Got to micromanage I got a direct
This is big people are going to be talking about this I need to go to where I needed to go
And unfortunately also I don't know if you can pick this up from
The audio but there's a lot of people
In the room and we know
From doing shows that there's ways to deal with that and then there's ways to deal with that
Alex has one strap
A big Advocate and and obviously very very
Gabriel spoken for us in
Yeah that's
After all the persecution you've gone through
I got married speak on these live feeds out here
But let's get back to the game if you want we have lost I appreciate you coming today in your courage to do it I know you been
You you're feeling persecuted I've been persecuted we know it's like
We appreciated his report America
Realize that persecution is actually a blessing
And we don't see ourselves
Victims
Just like Rodger Stone
And just like some other people they tried to put his father in prison
They try to hold years in prison
And bankrupting them
Did lie about President Trump and lie about
The populist election we had
Fire a lot of talk I love you guys
Disrespect
Goodbye just stop talking for one second
Just just one second
Just one second your life
His father wanted to serve America
And try to defend our Republic
And because
A good speaker dude targeted him because he wanted to put in the Trump Administration
Patreon
That would promote Freedom worldwide they were scared of the army
The George Washington founded
245 years ago
Finally getting control of the government again
From these communist
Republic
And dead
They want
Every attack they had
So I think anybody has produced a comedy show can relate to that moment Alex just had
Are you trying to run a show and there's some people who won't stop talking in the back of the room
Maybe it's bar patreon patrons maybe it's
Other Comics that you need them to shut up
You have a headliner was dropped into been on television
It's make-or-break.
You need this to go well so you panic a little bit
It's too late at this point would produce a better show
Except
Sure you couldn't see the people better
Not sure you could have not spent so much time to settle yourself
Sure you could have just
Not let any dum dum running for congress to 15 minutes but it's too late for that now you need to fix this now
The yellow people to shut up
Yeah I don't think I've ever done that myself
But I come close
And I've definitely seen host use that move
A bunch
It never works
Everybody
We got a really good show going on could you guys just please be quiet
Can you please turn off the TV
Never
Because you haven't
Shown them why they need to pay attention
If you can scold
Now where this stops being relatable almost starts
Crying about General Flynn
It's not surprising for Alex to get
Emotional talking about America
I was shocked to hear
Globus tours Ephrata was the General Flynn was trying to get the military to be in charge of the
Is that what Alex's wanted this whole time
If I'm not much mistaken
He was super anti-military until at least
Surround like 2009
Militarized state
It seems like everything he stood for since at least 1995 has been strongly in phatic Lee opposed to the idea of the military
Being in control of the state but he is crying on stage with Mike Flynn son
Jammed up his dad cuz he was going to bring the military back in charge
Since f*****-up
Mike Flynn son
Already said no to
At least
Was clearly not being paid attention to it
And then was suddenly and loudly interrupted for this by and then continually ask questions and interrupted by
By the variable
That you are talking to
Who is now kicked you off the microphone that is standing right next to you
Screaming about how he loves George Washington
And about how your dad was trying to get the military in control of a government which seems like
Maybe I don't want that I don't want you to put me into bed
This one I'm going to have to know about the
This what I'm sorry
I feel like that's a bad day. Kind of phrasing is really weird very counter to all the things that Alex teams
Tubi
Against
Obama was black
The end
I think it's really upsetting to cuz it's accompanied by this demonstration which seems like
Pretty sincere drunk emotions
Like obviously she's Hamming it up a little bit
When Junior bud
Seems fairly visceral
George Washington such a good coder
Ready-made Windows never
Covid-19
It's it's best friend
Alex breakdown
Watching this
I got the sense that maybe this is too weird for Flint Journal
We have discredited Obama
We have discredited Hillary
We ever like my pictures on hold
America has had a great victory
But America doesn't have a media
To tell you the victory man
Check
So General Flynn faces fake sentencing
And I say like I told Rodger Stone
Call their Bluff
Because we've done nothing wrong
We're good people saw General Flintstone God bless you
Are you though
You're a good person
Father's Day
You know
Get attacked by CNN
If you're able
Boy George George
Wow
America
Is rising now
And the enemy knows it
Tell him the truth
Alright I'm in the lot the last thing I'll say is is we still have a fight in front of us
I think
I mean I don't know I don't want it
Assume too much but if you're Mike Flynn Jr you probably got to get the sense that first of all
Wasted
Seems to be about you
You seem to be projecting your situation on my father
Lightest possible
Get through this level of professionalism from her
From habit
I think it's bless professionalism in more just like
What's the
That's fair
Performer
I know I'm up for me wait then becomes
I'm burning the stage
And I'm making sure that nobody will ever forget my name and it will not be
Be good I understand
Anybody speaking at this event
I also can relate to the Roses like it's not worth the trouble
Is going to be a mess and I don't really care.
To do it
This is another example of personal Pride
Alex is more humble about this
But you came up here tonight
I know under major pressure and persecution
To tell the truth when closing
In person
Why you decided to come out and pick up your father's tonight
I think it's because you know the tide has turned the whole is broken
Where are American we're not watching agents we love or something
We believe in America why did you come out tonight
I came up here with with Ivan Raven I don't know where he's at he's
Ivan's always dragon
Unn in five different in 5 minutes
Different directions to 1st pack before in our next couple days
Hey Alex really wanted Mike
To say like
I came because your audience is so important
Alex wanted
Or you didn't get it
Android's follow Ivan around
Ivan want you to be able to plug his search engine in the last
I came so close friend of mine
Conference
And I don't want to ever see him next
So Flynn
Mike Flynn JR says that his dad will be back
This is just
I mean you nailed it earlier
Just as Alex
Progresses through this he thinks he's doing
The co-host
But I can say it
That that that his time is not done he will get
His
He'll get his ass back out there and nnnn speak out about the things that that need to be spoken out about
I tried generals on General Flynn baton America
3 plus years ago tried to put the lighthouse
Stockwood Patriots
He was attacked
Is Enemy Number One
Four years later we're turning the tide his son is here with us tonight
It's a beautiful time God bless you tell your father words out of them
You can't let
Blinn Junior have the last word in his own speech
I was cutting off in the middle of a set
What's so f***** up
And he totally grabbed
He had absolute that moment where is like
You totally grab
You can't leave yet
So slim Juniors done and now Alex has mix 20s, gosh
Sure
Introduces neck
And I think you can tell
Fairly well mostly
Well
Hard to follow this Nick Fuentes
Who challenged the Republican sensors
And the New York Times on the chai Comcast
Thank you
He's getting sustained Applause it carry on bag
Nick comes on stage I think you'll be able to
Tell immediately how much battery is at this then
Almost everybody else
It's been there wow it is great to be here this is been a very often and I've been to see pack for
Two years now I went to seapac in 2018-2019
2019 I wasn't supposed to be there actually got kicked out or they they try to kick me out
If you remember last year
But I have to say this is way more fun than snot haha than here I don't think so
First of all I just want to say thanks to
The national file everybody with the national file for hosting this and
A big thanks of course to a big thanks to Infowars and Alex Jones for having us all here and
Alex Jones is
High energy
I know I sound like a broken record about these various small details of live performance but it's really one of the things that in
Just admit the most of my time doing stand-up
There's little things that any performer can't cannot do a huge effect on how they're perceived by Nadia
When the really common ones is a comic coming on stage taking the microphone out of the stand and casually moving the mic stand to the back of
The stage
It's a simple routine action that indicates that the performer is Eddie's
And they're able to
We control their surrounding
But if they fail to do this symbolize
They end up with a bike stand between them and the audience
Obstructing the view from the crowd which
Distance
The, could leave the mic in the stand and then that's a different thing that's a stylistic
Choice
If you see a performer take the mic out of the stand
Conscious signal if this person isn't
In controlled airspace
The same messages sent by a comic concedes too easily to a heckler
If someone in the audience yell something out you don't have to
Destroy them
Anything but ignoring, altogether
We're behaving in a way that allows the audience member to squirrel point over you
Decreases your status as the center of attention and tells the audience that they're not in good hands
They can't trust the performer to get through whatever they're about to do
Before I even started doing stand-up
My uncle worked
Comedy Club
Indianapolis It crack
And we were hanging out with the headliner at
And he was he was just talking to his literally I remember this
To this day if him just saying
I can tell how long a stand-up has been doing it just by how they take them
It's like that is the signal so
Easily once
Once you catch it you know it
I bring all this up because immediately when he got to the podium Nick Fuentes carried himself like a guy who's in control of the situation
He takes the stage and immediately expresses graciousness
Event organizers
I'm the same way professional comic will make a point to draw the audience's
The other comics on the lineup in the wait staff
Descendant explicit message that endears you to the audio
It's your time with the microphone but you want to see some of that time to give it up for The Unsung people who made the
Possible
It's a very little thing
And you see it
Pretty much every decent headliner at a comedy show
But Nick isn't the headline
This event there's more speakers after him and literally no one else has behaved like this throughout the entire time
These are subtle cues that Nick is sending me he's above all day
Results of magnanimous and gracious
He's acting like a celebrity drop-in performers grateful to do your bar show
Thrilled to be there
For my time and tomatillos safety James Adomian
Nick Fuentes is a real piece
S*** but he's good
You think switch is really bad
Trouble
Nick Fuentes seems to be coming up Maurice Sendak
Figure in the world of Infowars
Might be a sort of things
Spell trouble
We've seen in the past out easily Co-op
Assholes to whatever intern told Alex that fortune
He suggests
It feels like there's a decent chance
The Nick is going to become a far bigger and more prominent figure in our world
So I figured it might be worth our time
To take a little bit of a
Trip
To learn a little bit more about where this guy comes from
God damn it I hate it
Well you might be interested to learn some of the stuff then
So as we know Nick Fuentes is now a Firebrand crypto-fascist Catholic Catholic Nashville
In traditional
Who prefers to some himself up as America
Sure broadcasting show by that name on YouTube until he was recently booted from the platform for repeated violations
He's become a very public s*** head and one of the things that makes him so particularly notable is that he's very young
Nick is only 21 years old and despite his Youth and inexperience in life he's managed to create a sizeable following
Of disaffected
Conservative young white man
Who call themselves
Scrapers
Which is apparently a referee
Pepe the Frog
Great difficulty starting the world of political broadcasting in high
He attended Lyons Township High School in LaGrange Illinois which is a public school
He's from over here goddamn state
I thought I hated Indiana now I know that we have him
This is a public school that has a particular care
The student body of 73% Statewide average of 49
More notably probably only 14% of the students at Lyons were eligible for free lunch programs compared
6% average for Illinois schools
The indicators around the school paper picture of the environment that make came into adolescent
It's a predominantly white in affluent
Lyons Township is a school that is an offshoot television station
Call lttv
On November 5th 2015 Nick Fuentes released the very first episode of the Nicholas J Fuentes show on LTD
TV just a quick look at the show makes it crystal clear
High School Nick was very similar to
Another
One thing that jumps out at you
Is it Nick carries himself with an almost
Comical level of self-importance
In this High School AV class
Bassproject
You've got a suit and tie on and is sitting at a table the political Roundtable show
Discusses the big issues of the day with two others
16 year olds
It's the same kind of a lip thing that you can see today in his speech at Alex's event
Any normal person would not be able to carry on the illusion that what they're doing is any meaning at all
But Nick soldiers forward
He's committed to being taken seriously so he'll take a dumb conversation about the 2016 Republican primary with his high school friend
As seriously as you would if you were posted in the MacNeil Lehrer
And he's glad to be speaking at a quarter full ballroom with a bunch of losers and Alex drunkenly interrupting
You can see that this is a skill that he
He's at
Putting on a brave face
Some things are very different
Here is the OPA
Beaumont's from Nicks
First show
Again from November
This is where he describes his political ideology
How everybody
I am Nicholas
Jade Fuentes you're watching
Chase went to
This is Arthur
But I thought I'd offer
Play small
Republican
So you can see that he identifies as a Libertarian
Flash forward to the present and here's what he said along with Milo yiannopoulos recently did an interview with
About Liberty
Selfish
Giving up on
Hydrological
Castlewood
People grow up the ideologies can go from believing a thing and then a little while later they agree with a sad washed-up
People who believe that same thing
What does happen
You think is right bro
You're clearly something happened with Nick after November 5th
2015 the change
What is the time 11
It's hard to say he's not Dennis Miller it's hard to say exactly what that thing was
I need to learn more so I watch these high school shows of his
Is first episode with a breakdown of the candidates
2016 primary
He's in favor of Ted Cruz and Rand Paul
But all that's way less important
On Donald
Is it he's not
Who does that sound like
Sounds a whole lot like Alex Jones talking about Trump in the summer of 2015
Alex praised Trump being a corrupt Mobsters on the outer in South
Pointing out the Trump is an opportunist who is only interested in power
Beneath the surface of the current Trump supporters and you often find them clearly expressing
The Trump is a piece of s***
You can't trust
Back in 2015
Yeah it's it's funny how
Are you change
Whenever somebody wins the ring
Lindsey Graham he was so against
What's Trump use against
Nick talks a little bit more about Trump's candidacy
In this next again from this 2015 video
In 2015 even Nick Fuentes could recognize that the things that Trump was saying we're race
It's a sliding scale so to Nick they might be borderline
Considering some of the stuff Nick says these days
Like the time in 2019 where he spent a chunk of his show expounding on his love of saying the n word
Song
Edward is a rebel
You know II
Say it
Freelee
Openly I won't say to this Shelby
Because I don't want
Band right now I don't want
I don't want this
See, dobre
Nothing but so brave
Play Rebelution
Funny
That's who I want to
Talib
Sure
Interesting way from that last clip
You can see that Nick is recognized the value of trump sticking it to the public
Establishments
That job is done
At that point in November 2015
He doesn't serve any further purpose really needs to step aside so adults
Real camp
It's like Ted Cruz
Income front
Center
At this point it really seems clear that he's not the same Nick Fuentes from an ideological perspective
He's expressing a disa
Approval of Trumps racist
He recognizes him as a con man
Do you resent that he's taking attention away from conservative
Little flickers of anti-jewish inclination
You know that you later fully embrace
But they're subtle
And even honestly they're debatable in this old clip like this one we're decide he has
When he's talking about that Ben Carson tax proposal
It's hard to say if that was even a dig on the Old Testament it's tough to say that is honestly
Wouldn't even be that suspicious at all no I really
My point is it for the most part this dude just seems like a kind of trying too hard take himself too seriously young cancer
Yeah is Reese Witherspoon
Alexa
I thought this was fascinating
Because although I definitely disagree with most of the stuff he was saying that video from political
Perspective
It's a completely different person than the one we seen as a leader of the America first
It's a completely different
Person that the guy who jokingly dabble in Holocaust denial will hiding behind calling murdered Jews cookie
Something happen
The change Nick dramatic
And I can guarantee that it happened prior to April
On April 6th 2016 Nick released episode 6 of the Nicholas J Fuentes
High schooler about Donald Trump
By this point naked
Completely changed his position
He was fully on board with the trunk
Which seems weird
In this clip Nick explains that Trump will be a good president
Trump demonstrates how we can't even have a debate about hot-button issues in this country anymore
I've experienced
I was caught
Names
How to down
Ripped up
Show me clearly Ransom anti-feminist Auntie sjw blogs
Brought that business into his econ class and it didn't
And now it's clear that the Bolsheviks are in charge of public education
I'm going to go out on a limb and assume that is high school economics class wasn't even covering the wage Gap because the
Complexity of that issue from econ
Prospective got outside the scope of public education in high school supply and then there was
I wouldn't be surprised if Nick just got a bad response trying to argue against the position no one was Express
But then goes on to discuss what made him turn the corner on Trump
Weird
Any other discuss
That
First Response
Racist
Shut Em Down
Nevermind
That clip is fascinating because Nick is in April 2016
In November 2015 he was saying of trump that we don't need the borderline racist remarks
But now he's mad that other people presumably the evil left
They take Trump's comments and call them racist
Weird
Another the further
Where Nick is saying the people just say Trump's comment the races without addressing Trump's tweet about immigration
Back in 2015 Nick himself address Trump's policies about immigration saying quote his immigration policy
Stars
We're going to take the immigrants
Push them somewhere else
It's ridiculous
Nick himself rejected the immigration talk it was supposedly behind the comments that were being called races
And he himself a damn Trump commentary borderline racist
Your months earlier
Weird
He is
It is so much like
This makes it clear
Exactly what this kid
He's like a
Creation of
The feedback loop
Like this
The kid
Who was only
Like 15 or 16 or whatever he's clearly mimicking
The f****** line just got the line from
The GOP TV
Got the line from the 2015
Then the line change from the GOP to we got to defeat Hillary
He's created he's swept up in this this is the feedback loop and then he
He finds the one
Where he can exploit the feedback loop
And this guy is
He's like a f****** ghost-in-the-shell like he was created within the
Nothing it does feel like even stronger indications
He's empty
The other high school student in this debate
Is not a liberal
He's another young conservative
He began the debate by appealing to Milton Friedman
If that gives you any idea of whether or not you wearing a tie
Alright
Actually comes off pretty well even though even though
Disagree with some of his
I'm not going to be
High School
We shouldn't do this
Vote for Trump
The other guy who tries to explain to Nick that it's clear the Trump Appeals
Because he's an insurgent
But he's a bad
Kind of inserts
What I'm talking about is
Says
Is that
He's like I'm not going
Pictures side by side
When he setting mean Abyss
Standard
Of what we're putting
Do you want an insurgent
Absolutely
And Juanita
I wish you were sitting in my chair
To look at you
Yeah
Really
You can tell a couple of important things from that clip
Is he well
In the episode from November Nick was against Trump because he wasn't being a serious candidate like his first-choice Ted Cruz
Now
In April
Apparently the desire for seriousness
It's totally cool for Trump
Wife is hotter than Ted Cruz's wife
The qualification for a candidate needing to be serious has been abandoned
The second thing you can see from that clip is Nick squid
That's not an argument that's an ad hominem
This is very popular in the right-wing Circles of the internet around this time
Probably didn't start with him but Stefan molyneux definitely a big party
Popularising
Philosophy language
Being deployed by people who didn't really understand the terms
To deflect any criticism of their positions or what they're doing
Ad hominem attack
Got it
That's criticism that ex post facto Dan it doesn't count that's what that means Lori I disagree
This is a little bit of a clue to me than it might have been spending some time in those types of online
Communities
Third and most important thing here is that the other guy are friends
That was established earlier so we could see him from his
He's expressing a Feeling
Disposition has taken is foreign
This is a person who knows
Are you saying you've changed
I wish you could see things from outside
Yourself
What is conversation surrounds the difference of opinion about how
Trump would lead to the International Community picking were a bunch
Dumb dumb idiot
Scooter like someone like Trump
That's disgusting this next clip and I think it really reveal
A ton of wearing
Nick is coming from
Parliament
Will fine
You don't care about what our oldest
Ally thinks
House of Refuge
You can see so much from that clip
All that multi
Cultural anxiety the Muslims coming into Europe
Incidentally those are exactly the redpill talking points they're making the rounds in the line free
Most of them completeness representations of statistics
Packaged in such a way it's could be useful to help young white men argue aggressively against multiculturalism
To put it simply nature sounds like a guy read a bunch of Fortune and changed his whole vibe
You can see another thing here to that Jabet Israel responded to
F*** you
I'm not going to be lectured about
Set the thing about the Old Testament November being close to Ben Carson
Text playing that was debatable
But this one is not
That's clearly an indication of anti-israel sentiment which is also a primary element to the extreme online
Its rhetoric
Has this conversation goes on it's just one alright meme after another you
I think even you as someone who hasn't spent a lot of time studying the stuff I think you'll be able to pick out a couple in this clip
America and
Madara Pub
And why got B24
They don't want
I got a 09
Peacock insult and conservative was really hot and specific communities around this time
And Nick pulling it out in this conversation is a signifier of the places he's hanging out it's just a
Forensic fingerprint
The same goes for the opening explicit rhetoric about the West being Superior to
Other cultures
There's a fundamental piece of the online far-right this time
Dvornik
Talks
Clear dizzy just rattling off lingo
I do learn from his cool new edgy online friends
I think at this point it seems pretty hard for me to get away from the conclusion that between November 2015 and April
2016 Nick Fuentes was hanging out in some real edgy right-wing communities online
And as the kids say he got rid
He's using all the new cool lingo
He's repeating popular talking points from alright communities around this time
Is Brenda's indicating the teacher
Picnic is a complete a****** now
So it's easy to lose sight of the fact that he's 21
So in 2015 he was 16 years old
I wonder why so many of these people
Constantly report losing
Friends and family whenever you see a wonderful young
Calling his friend
Cervidil
I can't imagine why they would lose friends and family
It must be because the media is against the Bolsheviks running a media or whatever
Essence right as far as I can tell from these snapshots it's hard for me not to see Nick Fuentes
This is a conservative
When he was an impressionable sixteen-year-old who didn't
Have the emotional maturity to handle it
The only thing that really distinguishes him in any way from any other angry kid who just harasses people online anonymous
Is it Nick
You blessed with Talent
As much as he sucks on so many levels pointlessly dishonest for me to pretend that he doesn't have an almost startling level of competence
Even back in those High School videos
He's slick and he's quick on his feet
He's able to block a decent argument out of nowhere or come up with the deflection to an argument that he doesn't want to have
Naked
Piece of s***
He's fully responsible for the position that he puts into the world now
And none of what I feel about him changes that
But I'll never really be able to take him too seriously because at the end of the day
He's just a cute about radicalized and just so happen to have
Talented skills required to transition into being a cult leader himself
And honestly it's more sad than anything else
There's clearly something he desperately needed prior to April 2016
And that had nothing to do with misrepresented European crime stats
You probably always had a little bit of that races should head vibin him
Change the definitions of what was acceptable to advocate
Clearly did a number on
Nick is not the first of the sort we won't be the last
The only really notable thing about him right now
Islets is mortality
Did Denny's idiots like baked Alaska or Laura Loomer
Because he's figured out
This novel strata
That's really what makes him know.
Figured out this destruction
Maybe a hundred times more effective than things employed by like Richard Spencer
Are you packing right-wing scammers from the right
He's essentially repeating the parts
What made the Tea Party
Successful
Is this time he doesn't have to
Deal with crying all over the place that is 9 principles and 11 p.m.
So when he
Wait wasn't at 9
12:00 yet
F****** moron believe we all live
Yeah
So this strategy is employing of attacking things like Turning Point USA and Ben Shapiro from the right
Meanwhile
Whatever I wanted it's basically today
Crypto Catholic fascism
With a bunch of other wrinkles to it
So you have that but that's a really good strategy because
I need is a whole bunch of elements Dwight's good strategy
These people
Cannot fight you
Second
The people who would be opposed to you
On the west
Or the mainstream media for the most part
Are going to leave you alone Charlie Kirk
The reaction that a lot of people have
Don't think it's
Funny that be there's this internecine fight
Between these
Fringe right-wing groups and never pay the attention that would be required
In order to treat you like
You deserve to be treated
Sad
16 year old boy
Add sounds
You shouldn't have no clearly Woody's
Clearly his talent is
Mimicry like
Big from
From that
From that first video
You did not hear anything but a
Kid who is channeling
But he's a
Well very well really really good even now is
I don't know what or if he believes
Anyting
Because I don't know what her if any of these people believe any
Congrats on the grips
Side it could go any direction
I have some feelings about that I think you were sincere in some of his position
Writing me too
Because of how corruptible and influenceable Alex Azar
And the way that the groypers have
Clearly
Voice
Support
And they're growing
Strengthen
I don't know I don't know if they're growing
Yeah they're growing
And an ideologue that believes the bulshit he's feeling is
Danger
It feels like there's less of a grift element to it then other things and that's just because
As far as I can tell I don't see Brandon
From Nick like I don't see him selling
Pills are buckets
He's mimicking the grifters but he's forgetting the crisper
That's what he's f****** up
There could be some dark money somewhere but I don't know I don't necessarily know if that's okay
I would assume because you know he's talked about it
His parents in suburbs
Chicago
Torpor doesn't have a lot of the quarter there
He doesn't have a ton of overhead necessarily to what he needs
To do until he got kicked off YouTube
Pretty sure they based on the audience
Instead he had
But he wasn't monetized until fairly
Soon before he got kicked off
Pretty good amount of money
And then whatever donations might be coming in
I could see him being fully self-sustainable without having to do too much breath
People like Alex is over
Exerted themselves and there's too much sunk money
Right
Like Nick is a bit more flexible in that way
Absolutely
I wanted to get into that a little bit because
I think it's interesting
Wait when you see
The way that Nick has
Please come back on Alex's show
Alex immediately use like you need to get weed to get you to this rally
Play the audience
Is largely next fans
And the way he's carrying himself in charge
He is
So confident there that's going to rub off a bit
I felt it was worthwhile to
To take a little look
Look at some of these earlier time
Things because
The picture of him is incomplete if you don't recognize that most of this philosophy is born out of
This online radicalization that he clearly was subject to and he was
Too young
Angela like what you're saying I think I think
What you said was
Is right on
It's the mimicry
In 2015 or mimicking the mainstream GOP
Yeah I'm talking about like a Ben Carson's the leader in the clubhouse and
The Rand Paul is great conservative but I don't know if it's going anywhere
Very very much
That and then is weather
You get exposed to the online extreme stuff
You start mimicking that
And then you becoming
Yeah 88 I almost see him
He's almost like an empty vessel
Now that I've
Cuz
Like the more that I know the more that I go through listening to all of that s*** all I see is him
Writing
Writing this
This
Great
Inexplicable
It doesn't come from him
I don't get it.
Absolutely one hundred percent you don't become
Twenty-one-year-old psychopath without some pain somewhere along the way
Eat like
It's it's almost like you
He's just the avatar for these
It has nothing to do with him it's not self-generated
And when that rage is dissipated
They won't stick with
Has has
Cuz he doesn't have any actual
Talent other than mimicking that I mean
Maybe he'll get a he be perfect as a political hack on
Fox News or whatever
That is just a mirror
Amplification
Other things
You take in
I think it as you get older and grow up you can learn
Shift that for sure for sure and I think that's one of the things
You need to worry about is him metastasizing into be
The mimic
Is it becomes or whatever
I mean it's like it's like
Comic starting out you know you're the first thing you're doing is basically stealing nobody else
Does persona almost universally
Eddie Murphy
But like
I just asked
I really thought
Coming into this from so many of the interaction
Sims with Nick Fuentes
His work that he was something
More
Then what I see him as
Which is
An empty it is a
Just a mirror back the prepackaged
Talking points to everybody all these the gray when people are like we use talking points
Cuz we don't get MSNBC
Following
The talking point that they're all say we don't use because we're not on
Baby take away the fact
They're getting our
Self-generating
Eonline spaces
Listen to a ton of his debates
And is
Speeches
Shows
It is easy
It is largely regurgitation
Yeah like he's very slick
He seems like a nice guy that's so annoying
What a monster
And he asks
He starts off with like a
Interesting question
Therefore
But it is it is very exciting you know I look at this room here we've got Alex you've got all in weave
Then we've got a lot of big-name
And I think to myself like why haven't we done this sooner
What a wonderful
This poses an interesting question
Premier Logistics perspective I have no idea why they
But as an external Observer this entire show up till this point
Pretty solid argument
For why it hasn't
Wind weirdo congressional candidates trying to lock up a friend weirdo votes cameras
Scheming to a speech
Alex getting progressively more problematic
I think the argument for not doing this show is pretty well spelled out by doing the show I have no idea why they
These people weren't invited
Talk about Alex's toxic views so much but
What you can't have Alex Deepak just cuz he's going to try and
Buck up the show
Sure you know like even if Alex was a regular old middle-of-the-road
Moderate Republicans
Drunk and water up on stage and trying to show with you
So his next class next talks about how his recent banned from YouTube makes him part of the band club
But tonight I wanted to talk a little bit about censorship this is after all the emergency First Amendment Summit
We have rallied and gathered here genuinely could not tell you it was
And as you may know this is something that has touched me very recently
Because I was banned off of YouTube
Valentine's Day
Yeah you may remember this still a little bit sore still hurts a little bit I mean
We all knew was coming for years but when it finally hits you
I was just talking to Owen and some of the guys from Infowars they said you know you're finally part of the band plugged and from
Social media
Dog video awesome I'm glad to be a part of that right
But it does show that you're doing something right
Here again we see that Insidious mindset of thinking the consequences equal virtue
Make it's been banned from YouTube
That mentality is ubiquitous
In this group
Because it's a crutch
The fact that Nick Fuentes called this the
21st Amendment Summit
That is the official name of this event and he's literally the first speaker to recognize that
You flick
He gets on stage
Thanks uses the name of the event
In contrast to how everyone else has demonstrated a complete ignorance of disrespect for the normal etiquette of performance
Because nailed almost every little
He's good at this
And that's how he's able to get away with a lot of the stuff that he does
Because he's overly competent many of the subtle social signifiers
Like pretending to be humble
Being appreciative
This is it makes up for a lot
This episode is
A great way of securing right-wing propaganda
And laughing at ridiculous and also is a perfect blueprint for how to run the show if your list
Running you're showing it.
If you are making any of these f****** mistakes
Loki I might have been
Really personal thinking about this a lot.
About a lot of glass have a lot of thought
Do you need one red curtain
1 Rickert behind
Nix talks about
Nick talks about how I use the bathroom
Do you not
Controlled opposition
It's interesting for a long time if there is maybe a silver lining to being banned from YouTube
For the longest time people used to tell me
That I was controlled opposition because I wasn't banned from YouTube
Why are you on YouTube still doesn't that show that you're still part of the system
But thankfully now I can tell you being banned off of YouTube no
I can't confirm I'm not a part of the system but
So that's a cute joke
The fact that Nick was still on YouTube wasn't the main sticking point for people being controlled opposition
Trump Twitter
And in fact
His Twitter
Account is verify
Really yeah in this interview that he did with Milo yiannopoulos you can hear him joking about that
Grudge girl
Twitter David which is sponsoring you
How do you say my last name
Is something wrong with you I'm a grey alien
This is a light-hearted thing and came in the form of ribbing but it's
At least the second time in the first
20 minutes of that interview with Milo that a joke about Nick being controlled opposition
Because he's still on Twitter came up
As of this recording you can still verify.
That's because they're trying to
Wait what
I think you could tell from this next clip that this audience is
Pretty heavily Knicks fan
Yeah you can hear them responding
Like how to apply other people or not
Clear
Thank you for the diapers
Wipers who are with us tonight
Detroit versus taking over this whole week
Obviously like if you're in that room and you're Alex or you're anybody else you recognize
This guy
Is taking over our event
Oh yeah the audience
Is clearly on his side whether or not he has won them over or they came because of him
He is
To use
Cocking out this event that's true Alex
Cousin interrupted
Alright
Mixter talking about this free speech stuff
And how the Republican
GOP
They Don't Really Care
About free speech
Yeah but
Videos of really interesting take on this and it's actually
Probably decent
Point to some extent okay him
Using all right
We know that it one point in time
The laugh was in favor of free speech
We remember during the anti-war Vietnam protest
Remember that Berkeley was supposedly the birthplace of free speech on the couch campus
And now they've turned against free speech
Why is that
We all know why that is
Because free speech is a
Cool the benefits dissidents
Now that the leftist
Power
They have no need for free speech
Free speech is the means through which dissonance
Challenge their institutional power in the establishment
They were outside of power and they supported free speech
Now they're inside and power and they are against free speech
And a similar thing actually
Has happened on the right
I don't know if I agree with some of the finer points of assessment I want to leave
Something that makes Nick super dangerous
Nick is completely aware that the authoritarians of the past
Effuse bulshit free-speech whining
Weasel their way into public spaces
Do you know that George Lincoln Rockwell the founder of the American Nazi party use debates about free speech
Is a tool to mainstream and normalizes bigoted ideology
That's a pretty much
Every extreme right-wing f*** ever since
I'm not sure he's right about the left using free-speech takeover power after the sixties consider it
After 1969 there wasn't a democrat in the presidency
Other than be very ineffectual one term of Jimmy Carter until Bill Clinton took office in 1993
From 1969 to 1993 Democrats were only in the presidency for out of
The 24-year
Which if you're paying attention means
Republicans were empowered
Of the 24
The left is in control now
Obvious
Obviously we can see that it's the left who's the right what I mean he said the Breitbart sylectus publication
Interesting is his cake and eat it too
Witness clip
On the one hand he seems to be completely exposing the game
I'm saying that everyone just pretends to be into free speech
But it's really just a means for them to get power
On the other hand he seems to be still insinuating that he on like a Democrats and Republicans
He's the one who actually cares
About free speech
And if you were to rise to power you be the only one
Immediately forget about
This is an impressive level of cynicism
But I also think that it could be
Dangerously effect
There are tons of disenchanted folks on the ride were sick of people like Steven Crowder
Entire flock of
Free Speech proper tears
It could be super appealing
Nothing for them to hear
Like on the right
To have someone of the right call out the sky
And ideologue who believes his own bulshit
Granted people like Nikkor pretty selective in their targeting
I kill say people like Crowder Ben Shapiro are turning point they're scamming on Free Speech to gain power but you don't
Same complaint about Milo yiannopoulos
What's or Alex Jones
That's because he doesn't care about them being free speech comment he's just bitter that
Crowder spirit
Where's Alex and Milo or desperate that they're willing to
Steven get a boost out of
Because people like nicker excluded from even being accessed given access to mainstream
They can free themselves up to lob some pretty fairly accurate pratiks of the scams of the right-wing Main Street
To be perfectly clear or not
Actually just bigotry
This one
Others are using Free Speech trolling as a means of gaining power
They don't care about free speech
Purchasing meeting point
That is a Fair Point that he's making
And he's free to do it right I mean
But that's
That's the way that we get into trouble with
When the right-wing starts
Criticizing like the FBI and s*** like
Like that where you like
FBI's f****** evil and it will be harder to believe conspiracy theories about them
They didn't do so much evil s***
The CIA is f****** evil they didn't do this but
I get why you believe that cuz I would like
How many how many Fred Hampton do we have to get murdered before it's like
The cops are f****** evil you know like I understand but your
Doing it wrong
Absolutely maybe the power that you can have as a persuasive
Of course there's a thing Jordan
Nick doesn't care about Free Speech either
He is expressing that very clearly in one of the episodes from 2018
And I was interviewed at Charlottesville as well B
Infowars
Millie Weaver
You know she was very surprised by by the
Surprised by how
She was interviewing not sing
Don't you think everybody has the right to
Me and James allsup
No they don't these people post
True fascist fashion
Nick uses the language that appeals to people but what is her little project is is working on
It's working on something
Entirely
We can show up to a first amendment rally holding a position that people he disagrees with politically don't have free speech rights
This is because Nick Fuentes at his core is interested in creating a state that runs on Catholics
Here's a clip of him from his show America First discussing
If they were supporters of Mussolini or Francisco Franco
I had to take this clip from his interview with Milo's there's a little bit of laughing for Milo's friends
In the background to see
That doesn't distract you too much
And they were waving
The banner of
Adjoining
Prank
Flanges unless they are waving
In the band they were just be fun
Catholic bashing
Shazam now
I would join them I would become a part of Auntie
I would welcome an
Yes take over the
The country
That's sort of played for humor and I'm sure Nick will try to weasel out of this position by saying that he Sho is tiresome dumb s***
F***
You does later in that Milo interview Express the position the Catholic theocracy would be preferable to our democratic system
If we want to become
Kind of Catholic country I mean
I don't know
I don't know how that work
I wouldn't know if you prefer
So you can see kind of some of the things that are behind his
Presentation of Belize
So he he
Exactly the right way
Like right now when we're talkin
So many f****** right wing
Op-eds are being written about the Democratic
Candidate that
Democrats should choose
And it's always like
Well if antifa were fur
Then I would vote for them
Like it's literally if
If people were running
A fascist
The night before that
Like that's
Exactly what we're doing right now with all of that
If the Democratic candidate would just be a Republican
We be voting for him dummies
Interesting
Nickhits
He doesn't
Yeah we got interviewed at Charlottesville the right rally by these people
Don't have free speech right
Don't Stop Believin
Some free speech rights
I think the first one
If I want to say women are dumb
If I want to say it
Something nasty about black
If I want to say something nasty about you
And why would it
Smile
Pets first
You hear that smile
What's a smile
You can hear it that I want to say something mean about why would anybody do that
Like a real guy who just doesn't like the state of Israel is not liking Jewish people
I would have pizza
You can see that there's a conflict of I don't believe in free speech rights of people I disagree with but
Absolute necessity when it comes to me being able to say racist and hateful things
Some speeches more freezing
Free Speech isn't really encroached if you want to be hateful
Step down on you at all
Want to say things like all women are dumb
And racial slurs and all that stuff is because
What was I talking about again
Unclear
So you have this muddy
View of what Free Speech means
Just a tool that Nick is
Free to come to this
Speech and talk about how
Political forces
Use pre-speech as a weapon basically
Very scary
Nothing but you also see these indications that he has
Very interested in
Something else
You know he's interested in cultivating an absolute
Kind of power
Like is Catholic fashion
Idea that he's expressing
It's legitimately and authoritarian religiously-based mark
Would like to see come into power
He's not particularly
Interested in the subtle free-speech cons
Be run by people like Steven Crowder Charlie Kirk
So much motivated in
And in terms of bringing it over dictator
Interested in marginalizing
Nick's political project is much broader in scope them
We can afford to call out the trivial game that others on the writer play
It doesn't hurt him at all and real trick a certain amount of people into thinking that he's actually the real one
Who's interested in
Free speech
But of course he's not
Does Wyatt's farcical First Amendment Summit
He doesn't believe in the First Amendment at all
Nick expounds on this point he has about Free Speech being at the in the interest of those in power
As you were waiting for
Here Comes Alexandra
All these right-wing people that say they're against censorship they're in favor free speech
That worked ten years ago when they didn't have this institutional power
But now that they've got the money
And if
The think-tank said about the ngos
And all that institutional power on their side where is where where is no longer convenient for them
Where does a RN positions of power
They do not like the free speech and we are offering up as true
Conservative
Where's the park here
I don't care what somebody says
They have a right to free speech
And what
The establishment
Really fares
Is power
They fear Human Action
That has that electric spark you got there
And they're scared of you
And no matter what they do they can't suppress you
Because
I get on there I talk about America
Freedom
I can't believe it's loud
Nazi Alex Jones
Because that's all the left.
Is this a somebody
Trying to promote freedom is a Nazi
Lenoci's are a bunch of losers
Angela
You're a Nazi you're in a Saturn not seeing like
Normal American
I'm a capitalist and I'm not going to bow down to you
I wasn't wearing a hat while we can talk about it all day
Nick Fuentes
How they do this but
No one buys it anymore
You almost here or lampshade
Everybody needs to stop yelling meme
Pink elephants to keep going can we get
Is there catering in pink elephants
I don't know how to put this more bluntly than Alex has no idea
He's drunk and at this point he seems to think that he's supposed to be
Speakers
He's not paying attention
Just interrupt Mexican is talking
Because expressing a very interesting dynamic
Which is it free speech is not in the interest of those could
Controlling power
Particularly when their primary reason to pursue power the game
Hold on to that which they have
It's one of the main reasons that the First Amendment
Is there and why we need this freedom to be considered sacrosanct in our culture
Because if it wasn't
True Free Speech rules were up to the whims of random elected politicians and officials
Probably been gone
The whole thing was in response to that f****** King being a dick
I don't think Alex even understands the
The point that Nick is making
You can hear Nick say here he comes
In the background Alex comes up on stage
To it
He's not excited that Alex is interrupting
But you know what
Nick is the only speaker other than Mike Flynn Jr who doesn't end up responding to Alex
Interrupting them
With the archetypical cop-out it's impossible to follow Alex Jones
Not impossible for Nick
Go to him Alec is an embarrassing full
Who's just useful
Is very possible to follow him
I followed many embarrassing drunks
It is not been that hard to find specially when you brought the crowd is very simple.
You don't have to do that
So Nick wants to complain a little bit about CPAC
Which is better
I guess he's not welcome there
Do you know what they're calling this year's CPAC conference
Suck pack
That's right but being this year it's not a parody it's not a joke
The theme for them this year is America versus socialism
And to me that says it all
What they want us to do for the next 50 years
History litigate the Cold War and fight this argument America versus socialism
They want control of the dialectic of the conversation
Between the two poles
The right as defined by hamburgers capitalism and on the other side socialist
I guess I'll wrap it up here I'm going to don't wrap it up
I just want to say this I just looking behind you
Alex's come up on stage
Roast
60th and Dean is f*** it up there be like
Isn't it great that I say racist s*** about the
Also at this point I'm starting to suspect
Sometimes Bistro
Strategic
If there's one thing he doesn't want a speaker condemning
It's the idea that you shouldn't
Spend all of your time regurgitating litigating the Cold War
This is not cool for Alex because his entire show is real litigating the Cold War
August expert friends are cold war hangers-on like
He's hiding and every bush
Inside every government office
Everything in Alex's world comes back to Cold War anti-communist fanatic
Think about it
Add organic part of the Coronavirus
Conspiracy has to do with his belief that the globalist are in bed with China because they want them to take down
Which is why David Rockefeller installed Mound power 1949
Alex's beliefs are essentially in decipherable without the understanding to pretty much everything he saying goes back to the raven
Do some crypto-fascist from the Cold War era
Attack on Alex
Nikki saying is a bit of an indictment
Falcons primary world
Mocking the idea that z-pack Ubi socialism versus the United America
That yeah
Pointing that out
Is not good for Alex
Mocking
What he does every day
I think some of Alex's Interruption is
In the same way that he cut off Tommy Collins would you started selling
He cut off Ivan reichlin when he started selling
I think there's a decent chance that he's coming up and being all guys guys are good guy
A little bit to derail the
Thought becoming too explicit that so we shouldn't worry too much about this
Dichotomy
Is a leftover from a cold
It's a
It might be a little bit more crap
Then it appears
I'm not either but I think there's a
Muscle memory
I think you're wrong I can definitely see that
Because otherwise you can run on Instinct a little bit
There is a certain level of like 12
Well
Actually you know what I told her I am actually going to go complete 180 and agree with you wholeheartedly because now
Now we're doing Alex
To shop
Now the show instinct
So kicked in and this is
Hey we're not talking about that right now
Next next line a conversation tell me about your history is
Exactly
Show instinct
Kickin It
Answer this Rambles into Alex saying that Nick Fuentes
No say-so shortages calls me
Cowboys
But
Seriously
Nick Fuentes just want things that people agree with his popular
Justin wants to ban him
Like a racecar driver that keeps winning races
That's all
To figure that do black race cards
Gay people
He just wants to have his
On 2nd
And you know what
I'm a company man
SA
Hey buddy
I said the market ideas you get to
Denver run at it
That makes us all stronger
But they call him a white supremacist all over the news
And then the alo7 probably lost sinner
Fun whites
Remez compounds with terrorists
Bomb
Rate a blow-up black communities and create War
But they can never find white people to join
That's a good news
It seems very wow wow
Alex knows that Nick has the room's attention and he's a lot of fans in the crowd so he wants to associate himself with Nick and try and see if he can get
Some of them to become his customer
Yep
Unfortunately this depressing as event is
To drink to the point of nearing Clarence
Self in front of Nick's
Hip young audience
Also to the point that Nick isn't a racist
Here's a clip of him from his interview with Milo depressing of you I don't really know how he non-racist could have
I I think
The European race is real
I think the diff
Nieces are realizing
The
Until very recently
I just wonder again
I don't know where the robbers were a lot of people say
You said but you don't
Progressive RC
Believe race
Is real but yet any kind of idea of
Bought
Siri is a benefit of diversity
I would say that
Does it work
Nick is experiencing a belief and scientific racialism
Different races
Can coexist with each other
I wonder if
Bryce has any other
Flagrantly racist things in his interview with Milo
I am yeah
I know I know that's
He is
See
Soccer position you are well
So Nick is supposed to interracial marriages
Position to defend getting pretty racist in the process
Rhinorrhea
Find the
Kid keep in mind that the
The question is not personally would you marry outside your race
Personal bigotries that you hold
But you might not have a problem with other people marrying other races
The question has asked by Milo is about supporter opposition to the app
Actors marrying someone out of a different race
This is about whether or not people should do it
Nick doesn't believe the people should marry outside their racial group
I can't really see any good Arguments for that are insanely racist
Excuse me
Hey Nick
So obviously this is
She's got to be a softball Quest
I'm just going to live this up a lot of people you calling you erase
I'm just going to love this one up there are you against interracial marriage
Because it's 2018 nobody could possibly only of the hemant races could be against
Rachel Maddow throw this softball up to you to put it on the goddamn tea
Milo's response
Wow
I was throwing you a goddamn softball is over but he's like
What people say about you is accurate
You didn't answer
Swing at the ball
You hit The Catcher in the Rye
We're going
It's not good
Is no good okay let's hear this
Allow me to elaborate
Wait a little bit on the floor
Here I think up until very recently
Play this is what the vast Malaya
Believe that I think it was actually mainstream media program
In a very conservative agenda on
On the part of
True in the media
You'll get
What's today's weather
Major Hollywood pictures
To put people in a certain direction
Disagree with you
Every ad you see
Can I see it myself
High tide
Yeah they lay on
But it's a joke
What about Muhammad Ali
Muhammad Ali
What
My
Mix
Defense for his opposition to interracial marriage comes out of two point
Feels like there are too many mixed
Great couples in advertisements his grandkids look like him so it's cool
He's so pretty
So pretty
Answer to the advertising
In August 2019 researchers at the
Computing Research Institute
Gender racial diversity in approximately 86000
73 top International brands on Instagram and Facebook 100% interracial
One of their questions was about just representation generally speaking but another was quote
Pairs of demographic groups are preferred in advertising images
Supercross XM interaction Conte
Text
Answer the representation question they found that white people appear in ads at a rate
Proportional to the most recent
But that black people are way less likely to
And that the number looks even worse when you look specifically just a black women
The researchers called quote strikingly low
Answer the question of cross-sex interaction between members of different races what do you know
They found that there was a gigantic tendency towards white male white female pairings in ads
But that raised a new question
Which was is this just a result of their being way more white people represented in ads
They took into account the relative number of models of different race
And they found the quote
The preference towards pairing of the same race
Increase sex interaction becomes apparent
This is a classic example of people like Nick completely fabricating
Perception
He's seen a few instances of interracial pairings in commercials and each time the right-wing media has lost it
It's mine yelling about Force beside your nation and some s***
Feels like this is a consist
Pattern
Now every time there's a mixed
Race couple in bed
Further proof
The globalist
You trying to push race-mixing on the whites
Pairing I would dare say Nick would see 500 as where the pairing
Because mine doesn't register that
He ignores the overwhelming prevalence of white white couples and adds because he's a racist
And it bothers him when he sees mixed
Couples in hats
In order to justify this anger without just admitting he's a race
The easiest move is to pretend that every ad you see is black guys with white girls
Another man is trying to push it on the Brave and Noble whites
It's a cowardly cop out there reveals the bigotry underneath when you actually look at the
Statistical analyses of these
I mean
Let's just be even simpler with it
There hasn't been a black guy
A black man
Not have a partner
Apparently I have to watch the f****** Bachelor people are going to hear about it
Yeah
It's so obvious
Especially because I was forced to watch The Bachelorette
And there was a black dude
Killed
I wanted to be with course didn't wind up with her
Because surprise
Evan pictures Bachelor who's usually chosen from that guy but it's
Pilot
That's all you got I have one thought about all of the bachelor in bed
Would you like to start an offshoot podcast where you just got me
Yeah I mean there are things like that
Example of unexamined
Jake is a kind of
Counterfactual disappointed
Do right wing gets all up in a tizzy Whenever there is like one of these commercials with mixed race
Messenger
I have that and that instills in your mind if you're of this
Inclination
Read racist
Whenever you see one it's an ad like that it's
More proof
This happens all the time
Registers are six out in your mind all of the ads that you see
That are not
Mixed race couples
Makes you mad I just makes you mad and you're racist idiot
And assume that
Because of this one ad with
Interracial couple
The entire f****** establishment is
Is pushing misogyny
Nation of audio why would it matter if you
PC 100
You already have Point narrative
The first time so ever
You can see 100 don't fit into the model but once you have it in your mind that they always do this
Spell exact
Muhammad Ali comment there's a bit of a game of telling
Going on with this quote
I seen versions of it posted on explicitly white nationalist sites are doing that Ali said that races should
Or they should be
Separate
So why is it so bad that they advocate for the same thing
Recitation uses often a little muddy and hard to trace back to its source
Is that each of them are just so embellishing it's on an interview that I'll lie did a 1970
One with Michael Parkinson of the BBC
Ironic in the interview Ali is discussing how everyone says they want integration
But everyone the gold medal at the Olympics
She still couldn't eat at segregated restaurant
That's because he was black
You pointed to the inherited pieocracy the times or the rhetoric is often Pro integration but the loot
Experience
Is much different
You talked about her marriage is a part of integration they tell the interviewer quote
I'm sure no intelligent white person watching this show and his or her right mind
What black men and women marrying their white sons and daughters and in return
Introducing the grandchildren to
2/2 Brown kinky hair black people
The interviewer points out that the phenomenon he's talking about is a social problem
Asking people not to have these prejudices and bigotry
Will go a long way toward reducing the number of white people in 1971
Wanda grandchildren
Multiple races
Denali response but life is too short for me to be doing that
Educated
I'd rather be reading to my own I have a beautiful daughter beautiful wife they look like me we are all happy
And don't have no trouble
It would be dishonest for me to say that Muhammad Ali wasn't expressing in his View
I bet the natural state in the world is racist living separate
That is true
Influenced by the time the circumstances of the early 70s in the United States
1970s only a few years removed from
Passage of the Civil Rights Act in the Voting Rights Act
As well as the assassinations of Martin Luther King Fred Hampton and Malcolm X
This context informs his position
At the where he was coming to
Also in this interview I'll leave seems preoccupied with his fear of flying
At one point you seem to imply that he can predict
Plane crashes
The interviewer asked him. He would have stopped 9/11
Interview interview ask him can you predict other things since Ali had been explaining how he can predict how his
Ali says quote
A lot of things that I feel are going to happen
Like we might do half a year without a plane
I'm flying everyday and I think
Think it's time for a plane crash
I don't wish for nothing like that but I feel like things are too quiet
And two or three days later a plane crash
Alright
It's been used by white supremacists and white nationalists for years to justify their own desire for a white Athens
Imagine that Nick has some other reason to pull out that quote here
I think it's possibly over simplified
Even if you imagine the worst possible interpretation for someone for something
That Allie said in an interview
49 years ago
I still don't think that's a good defense for Nick's position against interracial marriage
No you don't understand someone else had a similar position is not strong stuff because
One person
Who gained Fame and yet still did not overcome the institutionalized racism
Was expressing a world you built around white people
Enslaving everybody he's ever known
After that f***
Continuing
A pattern of abuse for years on passed the civil right there because he was expressing his opinion there
That totally makes it okay for a white
Did all of that s***
2 then co-opted his argument
Even if you take it that aside like just the appeal to Authority that's being done is not really in a story
Just some that's a celebrity
Some interesting ideas about a lot of stuff but that doesn't mean
A great point
It look there's there's Muhammad Ali
And then there's audre Lorde
And those are the only two
The point of this where it all started
Nick Fuentes giving people a reason to suspect he's a racist and a white.
Also there are few things
More satisfying for me then when Alex tries to bring out that stuff but like Elohim City and that the material
Expecting it to blow people's minds and no one cares
Splc Rosita
To try to get white be able to have Bob
We want to hear neck
What are you doing there are some there is some serious
Death
What if
The name of it
Always be closing
What's the name of the movie Glengarry Glen Ross that's what this has such like
Alexace
Is Jack Lemmon
Alex is the drunk
And Nick Fuentes is the hot young kid
That's so much
What's going on
Nick starts talking about the people who are sponsoring seapak
And how they believe in open borders
People that are putting up the money for their thing
Putting up the money for their conference
Are benefiting from their open borders agenda so
In conclusion is I was at 5
True it's not that were against the FurReal puppy life
Xrp weaponize against
Islamic three times longer
Selena's will say I Spencer Nick Fuentes I did not
Isaac syndrome
They're going to take us out of here in like 30 minutes
We are like five more speakers
We just got rid of the whole question answer conference
But it's good price
We're not going to get the call
The globalists are weaponizing
And you're right
Ben Shapiro and all these people are
Push by the system
We're banned by the system
What does that tell you
They can handle that you got a laugh off of that type
That motherfuker
Look at us doing this to maneuver it
Damn it I hate
Pretty wild
Nick speech ends and Alex brings up the next
He's giving an introduction
To Gavin McInnes
And
You supposed to be the headliner other than Alex
Right
I got you because
You know
According to everything that was already in Alex's head Gavin is the most
Figure that was there
Before he became it
He probably thought like
You know what
Knicks more important than Millie
More important than the guy who started Vice
Who's the head of a probe
And now Nick is lie
Like Dave Chappelle dropping
In 45 minutes at the go
Does 45
And I think Alex realizes this as he's trying to introduce cats
One last thing
Thesis statement
We as conservatives who are in favor of America first whatever our differences
We will either hang together or we will most surely hang separately That's Amore
Thank you and now we have gathered together
Can I introduce the Sandia major sensor anybody
Fireball
I think that Alex is really shaken by the fact
Nick Fuentes you can telephone
Just listening to this
Yeah but he got a standing ovation from the crowd after his speech
Bring up Gavin
Gavin McInnes
And the crowd is giving a standing ovation
4nickk
This is not good for Alex
Because this flips the dynamic he was hoping
Alex other people s***
Because in the fridge weirdo
Conspiracy and crypto-fascist right-wing he's always been the biggest game in town
Other people may have some
Cottage industry additionally Alex
Unable to associate with them and then use them to his advantage
The exact opposite
Nick Fuentes does not need our
Alex and I think Alex realized it in
Any benefit
From this is going directly to
Any person who Alex's exposing to Nick
Possibly
Become a fan of Nicks
It's not going to go the other way around
It's not like Knicks fans are going to convert to info Warriors
I strongly suspected Alex realize that he's in a situation where the only outcomes available to him are losing Prospect
You could fully accept Nick and watches his audience gets drawn away from him to the towards the shiny
Nice respectable clean
Cut articulate
Magnanimous Young Band
Who can handle himself way way better than ours
Or conversely
He could try to distance himself from Nick now
And run the risk of becoming his neck
Target
The next example of an organization like turning point that isn't really America first
But pretends to be
That q-and-a session
At the end
Is a huge Danger
The way that Nathan the groupers have done the damage they have to Turning Point
Is by showing up at
In the audience and asking them incredibly loaded questions about Israel
And about restricting even legal immigration
Country
It's a stunt strategy that's meant to make Turning Point look
Unable to answer these questions
And expose them as they non-conservative Shields Nick says they are
Conservative
It's honestly a really good media strategy
And it's helped by the fact
Mentioned mainstream media
A turning point
We're not going to come to their defense when they're being attacked by a group of crypto-fascist
Monarchist
Alex cannot be on the receiving end of that kind of tree
And survive
He's too drunk at this point to navigate that Q&A session safely
No chance he has no position on his real that sounds principle
You just says I'm not against it but I bought enough for him
Israel
That's going to unveil
And I think that Alex realizes that when he sees all the
This event has been co-opted
Alex is in serious trouble
Thanks we Gavin is up next and he's a super funny guy
Gavin open
With a bit of business where he pretends to trip on his way up to the stage and he drops all of his notes he doesn't
So they're in the right
His notes are in a disheveled mess when he gets up to pick them up so he starts a nervously reading the last pages if it's the opening
It's f****** Andy Kaufman level s*** man
Keith creative
This alone
Is innovative solo sketch work its game
It's very good
Gavin he wasn't done with Justin
The pratfall and a mister
I don't know if I can do this
When my notes got muddled up
I ended up with the laugh
Last page
The new hamburger
What are you doing up there
Is it a f*****-up how they give away
They're play on a regular basis
Just so you understand what just went on ahead and come up to and from the crowd and bring him a beer
Which precedes to snort on stage
The goal of the B
Is having pretend to be all nervous
I'm like Popeye getting a can of spinach
He transforms into the strong confident South
I'll take his real self after getting his booze and cocaine
It, Desi boss
Kristen Schaal and Kurt braunohler Kristen Schaal
Christian shows are Steve Austin
Uncle didn't need the beers to become stone cold
I apologize
Thibodaux
Problem with a B
Is Gavin is doing it is
How It Ends
However working in practices that Gavin doesn't really sell the post cocaine boost of energy yeah
Is underwhelming which is why it is there's a tepid response from the crowd
And that undercuts the ability of this to work as a jokes
You got to go bag that's kind of a problem
Because you're pretending to do cocaine to open your side
You need to be high
Time
Rooster basically signal into the audience bailed on it
Also nothing more conservative than a grumpy former gang leaders who slowly drifting deeper into his openly
Sad drinking in public phase
I kind of like a good solid messaging as a as a completely contacts list
Skullduggery
Important
No totals
On stage
He's not taking any more holistically and I'm looking at it from the perspective of
Want to show ya
Don't do that the B got to work
Depends got to work you got to commit to it
You got to commit to it that's that's number one on
Conceptual but then seconds away that this is so incoherent in Congress to the rest of
The Vine
It's a real problem
Like he started out trying to be a comic to
Wish my failure
Add turned into a right-wing Griff
We all should have made that move
I know
Gavin
Gives up on the whole like cocaine's making me Speedy thing cuz I got no response from the audience
Campbell
Just gets into talking about some dumb s***
This is nothing to do with Trump this has to do with you winning you f****** b*******
Conte
When was telling ones I ever saw
They were Taco drag queen Story Hour in some small town
And the teacher said
Teacher who organized this thing
Said
Let's be honest
Parents often don't know what's best for their kids
Delta Community
Should decide
What's Bachelor kid
Anyway
I caught you looking
I see what you really about there
Examples of
Everything I can tell I don't know what kind of app
Apocryphal story
Misrepresented
From what I can tell this is but a state representative in Missouri proposing
The creation of a parental Library review
Adult community
The goal of the board to be to quote determine whether any sexual material provided to the public
By the public library is a
Appropriate
According to most people who spoke about this bill from the director of the American Library association's office for intellectual freedom
Do various drag queen Story Hour participants
This is actually in the temperature
Tail free speech in public libraries and oppose potentially harsh fine
Leaving jail time on Library libraries host events
But he's actually caught
Constitutionally protect
Yeah liberals want the community side and all conservatives want is for 5 people to decide a mobile
The most recent most relevant example of the community deciding
Clearly
An attempt to push back on
Drag queen Story Hour
If there's one thing I know about history is that
People who burned
Sure
Secure this is the veneer of being something where the community takes over and decide what's good for you
Your kid but in practice it's yet another attempt to do away with drag queen Story Hour through the process of
Community review board
Devin should be in favor this
Since it works towards his goal
32 much of a reactionary snowflake
Like so he hears the word Community down a pre-scripted
Feigned outrage
There's a bit of this and that's in this
It's not. It's just like when Alex was
Bitching about
Built bars
Lino Scott that's what you're supposed to want
That's why he wants too stupid to even know what you want
Nevermind
My bad
This is the propaganda Angela I'm just dumb
Avenza
Jokes free speech
The agenda is clearly I want to control the story
And
When you see the
People being persecuted
In this day and age it tends to be and this might be the coke talking
Because they're Charming
And funny and Gorge
Like me
That is
But he's supposed to be a former comic
No
He started the proud boys
The gang proud boys
Jewel of
The proud boys
Anyway the man
Can be silent much like the audiences for him
The man hates the proud boys and they're mad at
We ought we hate all my
Is there a violin
We're against violent gangs
No Brinkley were against nonviolent games like the like the f****** people who love the Insane Clown Posse
I like
You make interesting point that's not why
Started this club The Proud boys
As a fun silly men's club
Still is
And
I think the last saw that is making Trump cool
Making conservatism cool
But more importantly
Issuing Shane
I can't imagine the level of self-delusion that's required to think that the proud boys made support and trouble of cool
Is a group of matching shirts is group
Is named a song in The Aladdin musical
Merced
Assuring shame thing
How do we square that with the basic requirement for proud boy membership being there to stop masturbating
I can't think of anything that's more screams of deep shame complexes than a weirdo failed comedian
3-gang of disaffected young men
Did they have to stop jerking off to join him
Feeling shame
Word around with us
Do you like the desert
The social benefits that are come from generations of denying minorities access to the economy or any semblance of Social Power
The point is that white people shouldn't have to feel bad about the racist history of our country but
I think the Shamy really should be focusing on is him telling them dudes that if they want to be in his group that can't beat off
Psychologically that's a way more interesting thing that is run-of-the-mill white identity leanings
Any famous psychiatrist to say that there is a lot of Deep
S*** going on behind people saying don't mess
I can't think of any
Really really famous psychiatry
It's weird
That
Kevin's complaining about how like a we should be focusing on Muslims cuz they're all terrorists
I hate gays
Did the last
And the globalist
Stan the Man they just want to demonize a redneck
That's what they want to do
Oki Mendes Falls
Apart
They want a redneck
He live in some bizarre
Fantasy world some shity movie
On Showtime
Oblivious
You assholes stop chatting your f****** head off please there we go
Hey shifter brains talking to Nick
Hey
You f****** limey s*** forebrain
If you want to chat go outside what are you doing here
Sounds like a swarm of bees nattering over there
Oh that's a fail comedian
Isley shut the fuk up
I've looked at this is gone
You guys shut up
This obviously wants to be funny but he's also a super super angry
Dude which is a combination that
Very few people can pull off
Depalo and
He did for 20 years in the late 80s
Kevin Spencer time onstage Ramblin his way through a convoluted story but haven't actually the victims of all the streets
B they've gotten into
Of courts are full of sjw judges and how he hopes and teeth people get raped
Imprisoned
I'm not a
It's horrible and
Very difficult to follow as a speech
Punctuated by increasingly sat attempts at punchlines
More so than anyone else who's come on stage so far given really does think he's funny
Either failed stand-up comics I think he thinks he's got some of those skills
Still but man he does
Eclipse of the speech for a couple
The first is that it's almost in comprehend
And the stuff that he sang his gang members are things that I couldn't possibly
Confirm or deny if I wanted
Things like jailhouse conversations a proud boy allegedly had with an antifa member
Retainer
I don't believe that but also there's nothing I can do with
The other reason to Gavin do the reason I don't want to
Talk about this all that much more is that Kevin is trying to be funny
Any style of Comedy is basically just saying offensive things and then basking in the orgasmic glow edgy enough to save
Is bad word
Very lame and sad
Lucky thinks he's Lenny Bruce
Because you said the t word
In a room full of the most
People you could ever gather together
It's really the definition of someone doing an impression what they think a g looks like
While doing the safest thing imagine
Which in many ways is an apt description
This entire summer
Heard Alexandra
A two-man game now
No actually he's
And then robbed
Demonym for Gavin Miguel
Yeah yeah
Tiana
The only thing I don't like about Gavin McGinnis that drink Budweiser
I should point out by this point Rob is wasted
He's very clearly
Alright
Well
The reason I'm up here is cuz Alex Jones has gone to bed
At least heard
I should have Alex Jones
Throughout the night
Please keep in mind that Alex introduced Gavin before the speech
Interrupted in the middle line
5 minutes
Since the audience has seen Alex on stage
Some point
That and now Alex is going to bed
I can only think of
Three possibilities
For what happened to rank them out from SRA
Least likely
Alex legit passed out drunk
Yes he was
And I don't think it's impossible but I see This is highly unlikely
I seen many episodes are Alex's three sheets to the wind
It's bedtime
But he keeps going
Alex gets drunk because a lot of staying power
He's a guy who won't leave your party at 4 a.m. and everyone else is already gone home
Free the fury about
Gremlins being predictive programming that you have to listen to
He's that he's that guy
I respect you
Stamina
And I do
Want to hear what you have to say
Months from now
Please leave my
He doesn't go down please leave my home
Medium likely
Someone enforce probably Owens
Robbed
We f***** up to
Told Alex that he needed to call it a night
He was at a point where something could cause real damage
And the fact that Mike slim Junior showing up plus Nick Fuentes
It may have given the streams a bit more attention than they would have gotten otherwise
I see this is kind of possible that someone would have stopped Alex
From hurting himself by giving his headlining speech
Disaster
I also don't think that it's a
Sure thing
Because Alex
Particularly drunk
Doesn't listen to other
He's very stubborn
And I feel like he's the kind of guy who'd fight a bartender tried to cut him off Alex
But listen
Look I think your speech is great but you spent the first 50
18 minutes of it
Arguing why the hard-r is the only problem with you saying the n-word so I mean how about saying it was a bad
Now I know
Like no I know
I know and look this song
I agree but just going to
Just go to bed
So most likely
Alex nudity
He couldn't give a speech
Wasted
In front of Nick Fuentes
The only possible outcome is trouble
They're super conservative and their ideas are largely based on a lot of the same Aunty left conspiracy bulshit that's grown out of the red
Remnants of the Cold War
Nick Fuentes is involved in something and aspires to be a political movement
Not just an entertainment Empire where you can lie about headlines
Giselle dumb pill
And his followers
Have a bit of the same seriousness stupid
Which is something Alex cannot engage with
He can engage
Just not any form of opposition
From the left
Because he can just yell over them
Call them Satanist in
If all else fails y'all something about how Epstein didn't kill himself
He cannot risk being attacked from The Fringe right
Because if he does his whole act Falls
All the park
If he's grouper start asking him for his positions on issues they care most about namely is real and shutting down all in
Immigration Alex is going to look like not a real conservative
And guess what when that happened none of his tricks
Twerk
You can't paint them as Satanist cuz their America First conservative
He can't take our secret globalists cuz Nick been banned from YouTube and is a target of the media in
He can't yell at them
Because that just makes him look weak in contrast to The Smiling Poise Nick Fuentes
You can't throw his Epstein didn't kill himself smoked
Because they'll just be like totally agree
So why shouldn't we attack is
Nick Fuentes
The biggest threat to Alex's credibility right now
And I think rather than mixing it up with them in a livestream he decide
Let's go to bed
It's the right decision
Because Alex doesn't need to be there
Mass out of himself trying to make the show entertaining and that was a failure
But they don't need him dragging it out at the end with a dumb speech about his
Crying about the military junta
He seems to want to install
He has Owen Shroyer their seemingly sober is like
So he's not going to get the same kind of scrutiny that Alex
He has robbed you completely drunk
Keep an eye on things
He was right to go to bed
Even if they said like 20 times who's going to be the headline speaker and then he just disappeared
Kind of but I think it's the right decision
Is strategically
Absolutely
Charlie Kirk if you missed that one
Regardless of whether or not Nick Fuentes is there
That's all
Going to bed is a good idea
Well certainly
But when you head back
You can also only end up alienating
A block that you want called
5 years ago
This rally
Is 1
Filled to the brim
And to Alex can get s***-faced
And rambled nonsense
To close out for
For 20 minutes
And everybody's just going to Hoot and Holler
And have a great time
Maybe
Can't pull that off
Certainly not with
Nick Fuentes
The fucken
Horsemen of the
Apocalypse
Find him
So now that Alex is gone
That takes away
A block of time
Yeah so what are they going to do with the collar
Hellyeah is now introducing the
Pull up on stage
Nick Fuentes get up here
I have a gift for Nick Fuentes
I know he's going to love this
About to get a videotape this cuz
Alaric
Nick
I'm going to present you this pain I want you to tell everybody what it says
Is your gift
Zionism is a badge of honor
Opposite
Alright you like that
Aggressively a Zionist
But he's fine like 82 Factory
So it's it's a it's kind of a safe
June 8th doesn't really kick off
Immediately because there's a lot of disorganization
And other people coming up on stage and like
Leaning into the mic
Answer Lee Stranahan who still there
Besides this a little something into the mic and then Shroyer
You missed on a joke earlier so try that again
I'm just going to say this
Just do it look fabulous or not look at the pocket square look at mattresses
I'm at Solon
You look fantastic
Just don't tell Rodger Stone I forgot my belt at home today
He'll take me off the best wrestling
We have the bikes working are we good
That joke again it doesn't work again
Great
In his
You know
Comparatively very level-headed
Authority position
Now he takes over
He's running the q-and-a
Okay and so it is much more competent hands
But it's exactly what you'd expect
Most of the audience is Nick Fuentes
Cancel their forwards
I go ahead yeah go ahead
Traffic question for mr. Fuentes
So
As he knows I have two deer tick
A few months ago and never got a response
I would like to give mr. French as the leader of the America first movement
An opportunity to answer my question adequately
What is the America First Position I'm giving Israel 3.8 billion dollars in Aid every year
And how is that in America's interest
Well yeah that's a softball question but I appreciate it, Alexander
Epic by the way the man who arguably started it all in Colorado
Without question
So the person asking the question is a plant
Nxbrew
Alex
Know how it's being asked
What is the America first position on Aid to Israel
He would waffle Oregon
He wouldn't come off
I think he is reelz a good basic we should have being juice orders Jerusalem
And you wouldn't come off any better than people like Charlie Kirk
There are two the eyes of these
America
The first
Right
Immediately from the fur
First question you see like
This would have been a f******
Disaster for Alex call Alex
Finally he's taken my advice
Like I said it's disorganized as hell trying to do this
You know people can just bum rush
Jerome Bell am running for congress in a second district Virginia
I need to do first of all we need to get Donald Trump elected again
In the United States need to take over jinya
I'll take note Virginia from a Democrat
From the Democrat Elaine Lauria
Okay she's almost there
I just a POS I'll be nice tonight okay
Bobby nice
Hey you to ask you a question about
About 0.8 0.8
America
Goddamn what is a Congressional Campaign
Is running for the house in Virginia 2nd District
Republicans will be competing
Primary in June
If I had to put a bet on it I don't think that was winning that thing remember the house in
Former Virginia delegate
Those things look pretty good on a resume and a geode
Few primary
See things how things go I should be clear though
This election is not happening until 2021
This dude
Is bum rushing this Q&A session
Should take notes good for it good for him yeah he's going to make that 90-day living
Really
So Jerome Bell answered the candidates questionnaire for ballotpedia about something
Position
These answers someone seemed a little bit of weird
Free first job was as answer was working for the ident division for the FBI
Papa loves his first-ever job strange
Anyway Bell is a hard-line anti-immigrant
He's just he's received some
Support from the white nationalist circles including faith
He's running on a platform of shutting down all immigration to the United States which is a very dumb idea
Apparently based on this site dropping speech he's also in favor of stopping
The deaths of millions of people around the world
This Ron Paul ass endorsement of passive Slaughter under the guise of
It's the stuff of monsters
Constructed fiscal argument
I would bet everything I own he's going to lose that primary
If you're keeping score that's about 20 46 on the Congressional hopefuls
Alex's head on this absurd rally
So we get back to the q-and-a
Do you know
It's another Nick Fuentes fan
Asking a softball question to Nick
Doesn't help us win the culture War that's the question
I should be clear he's asking about does supporting homosexuality
Does embracing and accepting
Just people being gay
I'm going to love you as softball question
Really easy let's just throw this one up there doesn't help us win the culture War that's the question yes
Yes or no it doesn't it does not it's hard why are you murdering
Why what did you do and it doesn't belong here you know
I like seeing Pete budajudge I was watching something the other day
No and stop
Look I don't want to get graphic or anything but it's just
Gross
Don't need that
It's not Christian
It's not natural it's not conservative it has no place so
I'm willing to say that Charlie Kirk ism
Alex
You're the perfect example of a curveball question that Alex cannot afford to have to answer
He spent a lot of his time cultivating the character that blurs the lines of outright homophobia and
One of Nick's followers directly asking if accepting homosexuality does any good
That poses a real challenge
It's clear from the raucous response when Nick says that homosexuality is gross
But that was the correct answer
So is Alex at a noncommittal political answer that maintains as wishy-washy
Find that accept
If you said that accepting homosexuality was good clearly be walking into a trap where you then have to defend a how
That is a conservative position
If he answered that homosexuality was bad
As Nick said it has no place
He runs the risk
Further alienating himself from the base that he has
Are the desperately needs to cling to the idea that Alex is not a bigot himself
No answer to that question serves Alex's interest
So he cannot be there
Cannot be involved
That's a smart move
In Alex's absences q-and-a session could turn into Nix followers asking him softball questions that they already know the answers
And when he gives the desired answer they all cheer
In effect this event has been fully taken over
This isn't the q-and-a session for anyone except
Who's giving all the A's
Accused being posed by his followers
He's fully Co-op
Did this event yep
It's honestly
Yeah I mean
But
What's what
Interesting to me
Is that it is essentially
Calling out
People who have been
Exploiting
Layton
If not
Explicit bigotry and homophobia
Fair enough lying
About not being supported
No I'm
Totally bigot
I know I hate
Well I don't hate gay people you can't hate gay people
No I've been telling you that I hate you
Oh s*** no I've cultivated
Audience of monsters have
Guess I went to bed
Infowars audience like I don't I don't know Alex is audience even really use anymore how big they are
The only
Possible thing that can happen is Nick convincing them
But Alex has to milquetoast and he doesn't actually have two principles that he pretends to have absolutely
It's it's f***** up and if it
Continues
Like if it keeps going
Which I think of you
Huge mistake on Alex
Estes Park
He's in a position where he can't
Not
Still support Nick because
Implicit threat
Like a really dangerous position for his own
Position and steak
In the can
Conservative
It's a
It is
Fuct
It is it is really reminiscent of like
I mean again
Spell reminisce
Reagan
Where
It's
All of these people are suddenly
Creating this in surgeon
Space around
A political class that has been
Exploiting their homophobia without making it
Always always constantly just like
Hey you know those people with a with HIV do you have it you know you know those people like that
Anything without ever explicitly
We saying it and now they're forcing people to actually
We come down.
And they're like
Guys week
Can't actually hate
Which gives Firepower to the other side that's like you weren't really committed to principal
Hey Rhino what you mean is you're not actually a big
We really wanted out of you
You were lying to us about being
A bigot
And I honestly think that would Nick Fuentes doing will probably not have staying power
I think it'll probably be like in 2000
Looking at the Tea Party you think like
This is going to be your forever because you're in the middle of
I don't see
I think that Nick is doing
Is
Be the next
Descendants
Part of the right
Potential to disrupt a lot of things
And it also has
Potential to
Strengthen and reinforce a lot of the worst
Parts yeah we could have
But that doesn't
I don't know I'm not bought into the idea that
He is the next Rising Star the truth
The next William F Buckley
I don't I don't I don't think of that
But I think
Because we're in the present-day of because
Follow Alex
I have to record
And that's why you don't work with people like
This is why you have some kind of a standard of like
No
Getting involved here is only going to be
You should not
Engaged
Because when you engage you open up the possibility for them to
To completely fuk
Yeah yeah absolutely
They they're they're running a different grip
It's so funny because it is that
Like they're so hard right there doing exactly the same thing
The Anti-Defamation League is where it's like
But Alex for so long is like no no no I'm not racist there either
Fairly painting me is racist
And then the guys on the writer like
Oh you're not racist
Then you are foolish
Time to pay the Fiddler
There's a shining a light on whether or not you're actually races
Are you awake
Alex
Like because of whatever desperation he has or
Whatever
Brought it upon himself
I think it's interesting I really think that these psychodrama that I was describing
At the beginning of this episode
About this speech has a lot to do with the fact that
In the depressing as hell with the beginning there was no one there in the losers
And then as it goes along
Nick Fuentes fans show up
Really change the character of what's going on now at the same time
Because it was so depressing at the beginning out to f****** waste it
And he's in no position
To deal with any of this staff
I don't even know if he could sober
Absolutely not
So like
Tip of the spear
Likely
Dogs of the Americana movement
He goes to bed
It's great
It's just such perfect like it's exactly the payoff
A reminder at like I've run shows before where
It wound up being that
Steve feature Act
Brought like 50
People
And the people who showed up not for the
We're like
And
Then everybody leaves
Because the teacher at all and I got to go do a different show
All 15 people Headliners no one there
Just go to bed
The guy they are here for
You're not leaving
So I mean
Building Bart Express
I would still be there Thursday
I'm sad I didn't
Get to go
Alive would have been outside
Nothing brutal
Watching it on a video
Plenty
Terrible if I was there and you saw the video you could definitely hear my cackle at all the wrong
So we have one last clip
It's the q-and-a session has gone the way it has
Lee Nick Fuentes his fans ask me a question
Highlight the differences but
Between themselves
And all the rest of conservative
Again not in Alex's intro
When is host
They get another question
And
It's not a question
It's a guy grabbing the mic and screaming directly into it about how Julian Assange needs to be pardoned
Owen Wilson
Do this for a little bit
And then this is how the event ends
When he delivers a miscarriage
Because when he was dead
I listen they listen we got to shut this down thanks everybody for coming I want to thank a speaker's here
Tonight
I'm just like that
That was this free speech some attend
Someone
Yell Italian
Then they are they all just
Las Verdes illescas 8 you can see from the video the bikes cut off and then people are Milling about talking
The show is over
Amadeus
I don't know about that even he was still standing on stage
I guess not yeah I don't know the Mikes are off so you can't really tell anybody
Shoot the ship
Pizza
Summit was
Embarrassed
Disaster
Summer stuff
It's like
Pretty funny though
And also very sad
Titus andronicus
Alex just said his family
It is
If you're Alex
Cuz he's invited
Into his own space
His own world the element
Could
I mean like we
We could maybe
Have some sort of an influence on his body
He's lying
That's kind of unlikely
But the element of Nick
Any more like you're not real conservative we are real cancer
Bremen terms of a language of like he doesn't really care about these issues that I serve
I could do some serious damage
He's invited into his own home
And boosted it
Can elevated it cuz he thinks he can get something out of it
Any chance
That road
Is blocked
Yeah he's not getting in for yours from the group
Is audience
To radicalize towards them
I will say this Direct
As a cautionary
You know those
Who give you that great theme song
You know the Sith you love so much.
Had one is destined to kill the master
That is how the Sith operate
You need to know this
Plan ahead
That's fair enough I still do Alex's resilient like a cockroach
That's all I don't think that you've going to be destroyed by this
What's going to make his job much harder
I think that enforces
Is resilient enough that he's going to be able to
To navigate this in summer
Perform
But I do think that
It could
If things keep going the way they're going to
Force him into situations where he has to make position
Been wishy-washy anything about in the past
And that was vague
Is very
Politically used
The Disappearance of that vagueness
Creates like
Because one of the things that the gripers are specifically
Aiming to do
Ismail people down on position
For Alex to have to be nailed down on something like
We should get rid of all foreign aid to is
What else does that imply
How does that change the rest of your cover
What what else comes from that
Or even
Getting rid of all legal immigration
What comes from that
Where where does how does your like
Your coverage
Have to change
It's a it's a it's a challenge she's not
And it could have cut down on his bottom line at a time when he really needs as much as you can
No idea but I had an interesting time and psychological rollercoaster watching this in
Glad to be able to share some of it not so much the failed
Congressional candidates
Now w
A
Great case for
For the
Axesspointe only being able to come
From the right
I think I think that's probably know you know what I'm saying like there's no there's no
Pressure that the
The left could put on Alex
To nail him down on
Not really
He can always just
But coming from an ascendant
Talent like
And particularly with inorganic
Base of people behind him
Without that Nick wouldn't have as much right
Because he has
A bunch of people and
Make it look at the room Alex doesn't
Yeah it does create a relative power imbalance absolute
It's the it's the purity test of the big
And Alex
Inevitably fail that if he sticks to what he's been doing forever
Force himself into satisfying that purity test
And then he becomes
Covertly a bigot
It's like
Ironic
ATO of
Look the ATL
Point out all the ways that your erase
But only racist can make you say it
Only races can be like are you a racist
TXU
I will see what happens back Jordan
Oven tell the truth
Which website
Rose on Facebook
We are unfaced Twitter
Face underscore fight and face bed Jordan
Wright's restaurant
From the cartoon
Go to that
Leave a review do the whole thing donate to the show and be great
I will be back but until then
Emilio Emilio
Dzx Clark
I'm Colonel Mustard at the Omni with
Alex