Damn important I sweat it
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Need need money
Stripe.com
Everybody sit around
Joan
Jordan
Quick question what up
Have you ever been
To an art
Yeah
Uber to sue most people have been to art galleries
I mean like which one with you your girlfriend's an artist
But I'm trying to think of like a museum of art gallery
Family in California
Specifically I wouldn't be surprised at all if I've been to be literal Getty
Open to the
Aquarium that sort of the museum the fish
No I don't like art at all
Dominus Rembrandt b******* I respect
I appreciate those who appreciate it but I also don't
You don't understand no visual art.
I can I can look at it they got school
Woodside is about the death of my understanding of it
Like I'm intrigued me like to look at
But I don't understand why
I've tried to have people explain things to me about Aesthetics
Wheatley
For intimate like
Speaking another language
I have no idea my brother has a lot of that he's very into art
And very
Very talented with
Creating the Heartland drawing in InDesign
And and also really
Enjoys
Itself and I just have none of it
That's fascinating why do you think I don't know
Okay
I don't know
I don't I honestly I thought about it over the course of my life and like
I never was
2 in
Into art
Younger person
I tried to like take
Little courses on it here and there
What's going on
Nothing
Right over the head
Crazy why
Why do you remind me somebody told me that I don't really like music
Just boggles my mind whenever like there's so many cool s***
Just let him be I don't understand world I don't understand
Go back and forth on it
Music
I enjoy it in in periods of my life but I also really like the spoken word like audiobooks
You know it's it's there's some people who just
Need music all the time and it's in their bones and stuff everywhere
At it like you why so you know for me I'm sort of in the middle and I assume there's some people even
Further to like I don't even I don't I don't know it's just a bunch of beeps and boops
As always have on the extreme
Just about every
I don't know too much about art but I do know a lot about Alex Jones
4:15
Hindi so Jordan today we got an interesting situation to go over and we'll get into all of it but before we do
Thank you
Michelle
Do first
Kiss maybe I think it might be a misspelling of Chris
But it's c ticht is okay
So thank you so much you are now policy walk
I'm a policy wonk
Next Bobby thank you so much you're now a policy wonk
Probably walk
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks Jason thank you so much
Thanks Liz thank you so much you are now a policy wonk
Craigslist next Matthew thank you so much
Journal policy wonk
Next
Planet in the Falklands
Thank you so much you and I'll probably walk
Thank you very much are planted in the fall
People who signed up on an elevated level appreciate that very much so
First Nathan W thank you so much you are now a technocrat
And I listened to the entire back catalogue so I really should cough up thank you so much
But you are now a technocrat
Business
Heroin
So good
Freakishly large
Lakers about to Nathan m
Nathan WWE
Thank you Nathan W and thank you too I listened to the entire back catalogue so I should cough up
Hydro this yard likes these dance do you do that back onto our website knowledge buy.com clicking the button
Sure we would appreciate
So Jordan here's the situation that I find myself
So for our second episode this week I felt the desire to get back in and discuss Alex has returned to the studio after his trip
Courtesy pack
I knew you had some hot takes about the coronavirus apparently he's trying to lure Sebastian Gorka into a sad puppy
Felicity stunt fight
And he's getting more and more comfortable these days bragging about literally murdering people reported around
That again cool.
I wish it was headlines would say again
You know everyone learns a new at the endpoint and that's great
As long as everybody getting there
If you get there you get there I was trying to brag a lot about murder
Monday's show was 4 hours long and full of emotional trouble it also just awful right-wing content
The prospect of this Friday episode being another long Dent Affair just didn't seem like it would be right in terms of being a steward
Of our audiences well-being
I did not feel comfortable with that
I'm so what I've decided to do is cover this past week's content of Alex's show honor episode from Monday
So on Monday
We going over this past week
And the chaos that ensued on Alex's show
We can spend a little time doing something little more fun and fancy free
The tensions are high in the world with the growing Public Health situation the Democratic primary
And countless other real-world stressors
The team clear to me that if we're going to survive we need something is removed from real-world stressors as possible
And just our luck
At the end of last week
Kerry Cassidy over Project Camelot release date
With murderers flash spacegirl Mark Richards
But even if we weren't in this position where the tensions are really high we would still need to drop everything and cover this interface
Give everyone up to speed who haven't heard all of our old episodes about this
Margaret has been in prison since the 80s haven't been convicted of orchestrating the murder of an associate of his
It's very complicated to get into briefly but we've been over to Bundchen Mark totally did that s***
Mark was also a little bit of a cult leader
Antietam list
Young man in his work crew to be nights of his new Camelot which would come into its ultimate form when they use the laser
The isolate Marin County from the rest of the United
Estates at which point it would be gone marks Kingdom
They were
Surprisingly close to making that area I don't know if they work
Since going to prison Marquez married a woman named Joanne who runs
When's the Earth Defense headquarters
I'm unclear on exactly what they do other than sell marks writing and books
That the entente book Joann
Speakers face weirdo confer
Through Jo-Ann Marcus created an overly elaborate backstory aimed at building an absurdly heroic meet those for
Grubsouth as well as proving that he's innocent of the crime he's in jail for definitely committed
As it turns out you couldn't have been involved in the murder because he was off-planet doing space
Space mission at the time case closed due to the
It does sound like he he couldn't have done
At some point Joanne met Kerry Cassidy
Who runs a YouTube channel where people lie to her about Space Adventures
Kerry interview Joanne about Mark's heroics and through this Carrie ended up being welcome to interview Mark in prison
Vacaville in person
From there the rest
Is history
Gary's interviewed Mark 12 times now in the stories he tells her range from standard conspiracy should to most
The most outrageously fun nonsense
I've ever heard
His sentient spacecraft Minerva has a delightful personality of it but will not fly with anyone but Mark because
Loyalty
Speaking of loyalties the noble Raptor aliens are viciously loyal to Mark personally to the point where he once had an affair
They're with their princess the Raptor princess
The new JFK as a child you've met aliens ranging from the Mercantile dogs
Do the spider leadership to the archaeologists caps
Churchill too or no
Sad story
I can't even remember half the dumb s*** you said they recovered on the show but most of it's really funny like how Raptor aliens were feet
Featured in Jurassic Park and The Walking with Dinosaurs show and that Raptors like to come to Earth to go antiquing
It's amazing.
Also there's a 50-50 chance he's aware of us
Listeners have pointed out that in an early Mark Richards episode we joked about how if he's listening the way to subtly
Signal to us what to tell Carrie about squid or octopus alien
Which he did do in the 11th in a few
One of the more recent ones you did bring up octopus
Conclusive to me though
There's a real good chance that octopus aliens were bound to show up
But some point but
It could also be a wink
Not clear
So officially if you're listening mark
Next time
Tell Carrie that the octopus aliens are controlled by a benevolent AI
Expect an octopus to be evil
That seems random enough for me to be able to make a conclusive judgment that is absolutely
And
If we get the signal from you we will start feeding you messages
That we will not.
Through him
That would ruin the purity of the turf as I've
Discuss them with me not calling Alex yes yes I Can't Get Enough
Zoe
Carrie just went back to see Mark and now it's time to see what there is to learn
Bravo about the real world
From this professor / murderer
Let's see what
Here's the introduction that follows very standard course
Hi everyone I'm Kerry Cassidy
Baby from Project Camelot a scary here today too
Talk about
My latest interview with Captain Mark Richard
Of the secret space
Program
Call Total Wreck
Call 12 space command
So she always called them Total Recall because he has to remember the interview and then repeat
What he said later cuz they don't let her record it right
In prison cuz he's a murderer
But I'd not heard any of these that have a subtitle
Exclusively about space
That's what you would think
Fair enough it is not fair enough
You might think
Like
I've seen shows where people interview
Murderers in prison
It does
It does seem like
Somebody is screwing with Carrie somewhere along the line I've never heard her explain exactly what the game she's play
Playing is but in this twelfth interviews explains how
She is allowed
To even talk to Monica
What I always do is go to Solano Prison
And I've been doing this
Interview now for
Around 5
And this is
Again the 12
Interview
I am accompanied by
His wife Joanne Richards who
Facilitate
The interview
And be
Because I am not
Doing this
As an official journalist
Because journalists are denied for
From interviewing
And Oprah tried
Many years ago in
Deny data recording to what I do is go in as a friend
And I am not allowed to
Recording devices
Any kind
I end up getting a
A tiny
Pencil and
And I'm able
To use that
To do the interview
You so other
I believe other installments
So what she's doing is she's defrosting the prison
She is coming in there as a friend
Taking interview notes
And telling them she's not a journalist
Cuz if she wasn't journalist you would be banned from entering the door not be allowed to speak to Mark probably
There's some sort of a rule
I'm not sure what it is I have no idea how I would get to the bottom of this or if I even believe it doesn't really good at all just
Interview Mark I don't believe that for a second
Maybe
I mean she talks to people like dr. Oz
Special Jersey interviewed mark
That is not going to help you build that lady
That's conceivably possible at some point Oprah might have been wanting to do some kind of a story
On him being a burger
I don't know
It seems unlikely that you'd want to interview him the same way They Carried
That does not seem like
Jack cool I hope that doesn't get back to the guards at Salado
And her saying that on her show doesn't end up resulting in her being barred from visiting Mark
Tragic irony
I don't believe her for a sec
I don't believe it either
So there's some stuff going on
Solano Prison in Vacaville
Affected marks mood
At the time of this interview
Basically that prison had been on lockdown
For the two-week
Prior
Because of
The Killing in the
And
Mark was quite
Tired
This time when I interviewed him
Apparently
All the things going on
Quite
Draining
Over those few weeks
And
So that's the kind of thing that does go on
Possible he
He was also under attack
Did not reveal
Nothing about that
I'm going to leave that last part alone and just say she's not making that up on January
Nights 2020
Dances 2020
Two inmates were murdered at Cal State Prison Solano where Marcus
Incarcerated
The two attacks were separate but all indications are that they were related
3:20 p.m. to inmates attack alone guy in the general population yard and then less than a minute later on
Another Duo attacked another man
Laying in the yard
At this point I can't find any reporting on an official explanation for the motive but it's pretty messed up turn of events
Violence to the prison is not that uncommon but this sort of thing like a pair of coordinated killings
I don't think that happens everyday
I could see this making Market B Tire
Since we probably
A bit of increased security protocol and whatnot and you know what I don't care for much remark and I like to laugh at his
Is dumb stories
But you know these this is Brianna examine piece of like what life it
Is like four people going to G rated like
Mark had nothing to do with these killings as far as anybody can tell
Obviously I don't have any suspicions of that
Because of them happening they introduced all kinds of Life stressors to do his date
Needed a life that like
That's awful
I can't imagine not getting some sort of PA
Yeah yeah yeah yeah that's f***** up
I feel bad for him on a human level for that
Joe keery
Has a big
Thing that she's into
On this episode
Know how is that possible
Everything is space command
Carrie is into this
This story
And I've heard her talk about it in a couple of the interviews that I've listened
Come to that we haven't covered like when she went talk to those magicians
Airborne
So there is uk-based
UFO event called rendlesham
And she actually went to the UK and that's went to at least one of them
And so she's been
Getting into the case
Trying to get to the bottom of this
1980 UK UFO sighting
And it turns out
Might have been some trouble
Okay because of that suits you might be able to
Consequences
I had been in England
For the holidays
For returning on
On January 12th
That night
Before
It was around 11:30 at night
Nearly had a head-on with
A black ass
Range Rover
That was in a two-lane road and
Come over to our lane
84s
Raptors
Best to avoid it at
At the last minute
The driver did not seem to
I realize they were on our
Our side of the road at
Time
And
Actually
Hippy program
We got program to people driving SUVs trying to run Gary off the road
I just ate it
It's just like with me
We're not sure if
Mark was under attack like everything is about you everything is about you
So many areas of
Even like this the stuff we cover like how many times was Rodger Stone under attack back in the
Early date before he was arrested or anything
Like when he there was the polonium poisoning Affair even like
If that's
Do you forget about the like multiple times Alex tried to save someone tried to run Rodger Othello
This is this is something that gets a lot of mileage
In these worlds
It's completely on verifiable super scary absolutely but if you believe it it means that you're doing something that's some
Someone is afraid of
So if you can get someone to believe the premise you get them to buy the
Conclusion really easily to kill you you're not working hard enough
Bright lights
The truth you know what you're working hard on something it's very scary
Threatening
Powers-that-be that is
Rendlesham I believe the
SUV was headed for us is
Kind of a warning possibly because
Cuz of my sudden
Interest
In revisiting the rental
Forest
Siding
Landing
That went on for several days
And I did ask
About it in my interview
Xochitl talked to him a little bit more about this later but the basic story of the rendlesham event
Is it was on December 26th 1980
And a security patrol saw some lights appear in the fall near rendlesham Forest
They went towards the lights and claimed that they saw glowing metallic object
An hour later police arrived they couldn't find any evidence of any of the things with
Patrolman claim they've seen nothing in terms of even like
Down
Freezer
2 Days Later the tenant Colonel Charles Holt came to the site to check things out and he reported seeing flashing lights in the disc
Among the few other anomalies
One thing is very helpful in this case though that's so absent in a lot of other one
Is that holtkamp
The very detailed notes
From his visit to the forest and even made a tape of his binder
Okay you can find
And if you're interested
The rendlesham forest UFO sighting is a gigantic Comedy of Errors from 40 years ago that's been exaggerated Annabelle
What's my paranormal Inc
Conspiracy scammers
And the entire story of it is pretty well explained by people back in 1980s mistaking various things
As proof of alien
Carrie has recently for some reason become interested in reopening the rendlesham files
And good for her I hope she has fun
But there's no chance of any government agent mind control
In a black SUV is going to try and run her off the road because she's doing so
I wanted to get into like the whole thing about rendlesham and like really deconstruct it
But it's really simple
Here's what happened
There was
An object in the sky
Like a meteor they came down near rendlesham documented around the same time
That this
Nothing happens
Troll people on the night of December 26th
Very clearly saw what looked to be a fireball basically
Broke into the sky atmosphere explodes
They go they go and try and examine it realize that
They don't know where it came down they see a flashing light in the
The distance and they're like oh my God look at that thing flashing
Do you get all weirded out
The police, don't find any indications of like a UFO landing or anything like that
Cuz of course.
Two days later this Lieutenant Colonel comes
And he starts poking around they find these little bits of
Evidence
In quotes
One of them is
Little divots in the ground
That they think our Landing site of Christ's other pictures of these a very small
AR animals
Diggs
He also ends up seeing lights in the disc
I need note
That they are flashing at a 5-second
Interval
Now
There happens
To be a lighthouse
Exactly where those
I saw so many aliens whatever I was driving it Illinois one night
And there was a lookout off the side of the road there's thousands of blinking red lights
There is a lighthouse
Where are these
Is blinking light at was
Colonel halt he
Was like his base where he was stationed
Is a different place
Geographically then rendlesham for
It is to the north
Of it
So from his perspective where he normally is
That that Lighthouse is to the southeast
But since he traveled south to go to rendlesham Forest it was straight to the east
So when he saw this light
Keep discounted the possibility that it was a lighthouse cuz he was accustomed
Seeing it from the south
So be prepared and that's even present
The lighthouses to the southeast
But it's not anymore through the instances of things that people
In 1980 were taking as like indications that there's aliens a foot
And all of this it's all very easily explained by little misunderstandings
Is thinking that
Rabbit diggings
Our Landing
Right it's a comically lame
But these sorts of events
Because there is a lot of documentation from the first hand stuff
Like you look at is like
Oh this is
We got glasses bad
I like the idea of a guy not understanding that geography
Doesn't move with him
Lifelike no matter where he goes on the planet he's like
Obviously the lighthouses to the southeast
Of course I can I can kind of understand that not like being first in your mind someone brings it up
You gotta realize like
Oh wait that's falke.
No one's going to kill carry for looking into this dumb
Is the lieutenant colonel still alive I'm not sure
Does he still own
That black red Range Rover
He was alive fairly recently I believe I found some if he actually does believe it's a lie
Aliens now
In direct contradiction of the notes
Now you no longer it looks lieutenant-colonel alright
It's a little weird thing there's a lot of dumb theories about it and there's actually a
Han Oak
Rangy conspiracy about right alright
No I don't I don't even care
But anyway it was just a lighthouse
Anyway now.
Story of this show anyways it was a f****** Lighthouse guys gets into talking about
The old Coronavirus
Virus
I did not even think that we were going to get Mark Richards
Opinion on the Coronavirus
I'm not positive we do
Terry hasn't thoughts
So there's a big push
Not too
Allow advertisers to have advertisement
On
Alternative
Call better talking
And therefore you know Wiley sign
In
Play some
If that word
So that we can get this
Monetize so that I can see
Pay my rent
And also I still
Discuss the topic
The kind of
Censorship
Going on
On YouTube
Nowadays
And everyone
It's aware of it
Renown censorship carries holding up a sign that says
Coronavirus
Aoi YouTube as a policy in place where they demonetize videos about topics that they determined to be sensitive
Princeton to there was just a mass shooting videos covering that shooting will often be demonetized
And if you think about it for a second
This policy makes absolute sense and probably one of the only compromises
That the company can make
To continue to exist
And be marginally responsive
The goal is obviously to stop people from spreading misinformation
Whether intentionally or just by way of sloppy work
After shooting you could easily pass along a misidentification of a sub a suspect or erroneous early reports
Multiple shooters that kind of thing
If you have a platform that's big enough that can be a detriment to the public information
Bass
In the case of the current coronavirus situation
Really dangerous for people like Carrie to spread their views
Ally bases off of exit about two weeks ago she released an interview about the coronavirus with Jim Humble
Who happens to be the guy who invented the master mineral supplement
Oh no
He sold MMS as a cure for everything from hiv-2
The cancer to Acme
But it was really just bleach
A lot of the qanon johnny-come-lately when you hear them at like advising people to drink bleach for medicinal reasons
They're relying on the foundation of Jim humbles work
So if Carrie is going to do an interview with Jim Humble about the virus you can imagine it's full of the sort of information.
I can help anybody ever made hurt people so these people are treating bleach like the generic version of MMS
Is essentially what we're like
It's cheaper to buy Bleach
Then it is to
Yeah so
I maybe didn't want Jim to get a cut whatever
I like a gift tickets and big Pharma I haven't done enough digging
Into the qanon side of this or even the
Sort of non qanon butt
Current batch of weirdos sightings
I don't even know some of them might actually even be promoting
Jim stop themselves
It may just be like a jim-jim figured it out
It's like you have people at Carrie and that's the kind of person that she's talking to about
An actual Public Health situation that's bad
If your YouTube you want to discourage the
But you also probably don't want to just ban all talk about the virus
You probably don't want to even banal irresponsible talk about the virus and
That cannot be effective stifling content creators feelings about being able to make what they want
The perfect balance is really just a demonetize the subject
If you want to cover cover the virus you're free to do so and YouTube won't censor you
However if you're trying to spread misinformation for clicks
The demonetization serves as a d motivating factor so you have less incentive
Be Sensational about us
Sensitive topic
It's a tough situation and there's almost certainly some good faith actors who've ended up getting their videos demonetized because of this rule
But where I in their shoes
I would kind of understand that
And that's really the only way to preserve free expression on YouTube while still catering to the advertisers that'll
Wow videos to be monetized in the first place
If constant demands are made for monetization of videos where Carrie interviews guy wants you to drink bleach
And YouTube goes along with
It's only a matter of time before you're going to driveway all the big money advertising companies that make
Profiting off YouTube even
Possible
It's basically a killing the Golden Goose situation
It's probably a battle people I carry should realize it's not in their interest to fight
You're only going to end up screwing over the ability to make any money
By insisting on making money on everything
It's a dime holding up a dollar
Very stupid
Anyway charismatic about
I am in Urdu
You shouldn't profit off of
Terrible
Tragedy
It seems very cyber
Particularly
Immediate aftermath
The butt
You know
I hate I don't know I don't know where my feelings are on
On the on the hole
I think if I were creating an Ideal World you have some sort of a way that you wouldn't be able to monetize
Like what's that you're doing Sandy Hook
Conspiracy videos in 2020 right
Maybe there should be some
Singing place where you can't find Tyson
Roberts I don't know I don't use YouTube
All that much
As a Creator wrap
Things I of no idea of it is it is frustrating to not be
I feel like you should be able to ban videos
The tell you to drink
That just
Feels like it shouldn't be that hard
And then you go back
Cancel that you're like
Okay well now where's the line and you're like well obvious
Hey sweetie I don't know where the goddamn line is but I just know you shouldn't be able to drink bleach
Yeah
So it's it's a difficult
The
Thing to figure out where exactly the LIE
So anyway carries talking about the virus
And she
Are predictably has a pretty similar Theory to Alex but is a little bit Wilder
So there is a a rollout of a step-by-step program
Related
Decreasing population
And
The step one is triggered by 5.
I'm listening
That
Roll out
Now pierced
Having an added
Sort of
Plexity level
If that involves
What's this
Irolo
The two are
Really link
And I've done another
Video on this
That
It's been getting out there
Quite well
I can say the Chemtrails and Nano or
Are also part of that
Concoction
So you got Chemtrails and 5G being combined virus
I mean that's very similar to a lot of
Alex
Conspiracies
The depopulation
Aspect of it is absolutely and play and Alex's fairies
These
So all the aliens are basically like witches in Macbeth just throwing all of these different things in a cup
Cauldron trying to get all of human Humanity to die yeah I think so I will spell it out a little bit more
Later in the interview about exactly how the aliens play into it but for now it's 5G trigger
Virus
That are yeah that may be involved in chemtrails
She doesn't get loopback to explain how Chemtrails are involved but they're always in
The stage one is this 5G activation of stock market has some news about stage 2
Plan
There's also a
Benchmark
The Step2 will be more Earth changes
Is there man-made
And a set of
Droughts
That are going
Creating limitations
Resource
Especially water
And limitation
Time travel
So these are key items to
To keep in mind
Going forward
This is just fanfiction about the consequences of climate change
That's reasonable of course there's going to be drowsy
Play Changes.
Yeah totally cheesy aliens
Driving Factor behind it apart she's not saying it's because of like fossil fuel
She's Angus
Aliens are directing humans to do that
Great you get there you got to go do not in this case not in this case
Escape the conclusion invalidates the the
The correct
Okay thank the trees asserting
Okay so maybe if instead she said we need to switch to all renewable fuels in order to stick it
It's Abigail
I mean yeah that might be okay
Okay at least that would be productively dumb
So will you back to rendlesham now
She's jumping all over
UA
Earlier I was kind of expressing a little bit of
Confusion why is she
Deciding to reopen this cold case
I mean
Really cold cakes
Do regarding rendlesham we had a fascinating discussion
And I had received
The psychic
Psychic message
Telling me
Truth is
Set the case
It happened in 1980
A lot of the psychic
I started to change their
Your stories
I've been changing their stories
Have been
In conflict
With each other
And are suspicious
Beach other
And there's a lot of evidence
Of mine can
Between the
Witnesses
Eminem
I don't know what the evidence of mind
Control
That sounds more like evidence with some of them our lives
Yeah
So Jenny Randalls is the person who first primarily cover the rendlesham story in the
The press in the London evening standard and even wrote an early book about
At the event
Her works are largely credited with building some of the early hype surrounding the alleged sighting
But in 2011 she said quote
Well some puzzles remain weak
Can probably say that no unearthly craft were seeing in rendlesham forest
Who we can also argue with confidence that the main focus of the events was a series of misperception
Kinds of everyday things
Is encountered in less than everyday circumstance
That's one person who changed their tune but it's not reason
Lieutenant Colonel Charles Holt story is also change but it changed to support the UFO View
He currently believes that UFO did show a back in 1980 which like I mentioned earlier
Relies on him kind of negating a bunch of documented evidence that some of it
He himself created
Control he's on mine controller
Another person who change their story is Jim Henson
Peniston
Why choose one of the patrolman from
The first night's affair
You now claims that you touch the UFO at night
But we need anybody weirdly that was never mentioned when he was initially interviewed about what happened around the 10 top
First thing you mentioned
He's changed his story
Seems to me to be two sorts of people who are changing their stories
This case people who were supportive of the UFO narrative initially who changed their position based on evidence
That's an explanation of what was being misperceived
The other are people who were initially skeptical who change their position to believe in the UFO narrative without any real reason
Sometimes needing to contradict
Actual evidence
See mine
If I were someone who's involved in this event I would probably also view everyone else's
There are clearly some scammers in the mix and I don't know
I don't know that's not good
Touched
So there's a cover-up going on here obviously
Now
It's obvious this cover-up
It has to do with
UFO in England
Yes
But did you know that it also has to do
With our
Electoral system
Now regarding rendlesham
There is a presence
Behind the scene
Of the user
Usual Suspects regarding
Mind control
And that is the name
That I've got
Listed here
And are they short
Time and time again
With regard to cover-ups
And that includes the alien autopsy
The takedown of
Nixon our president
Back in those
Stay the course
Nixon president in 1980
Rendlesham
Fair but
Yeah I don't I don't know if the the Nixon impeachment was mine
Control
This guy Mark Richards
By virtue of
There their connection carriers
Always right about it
So the cover-up
Is mine
Incontrol based
It extends to the alien autopsy and the Nixon impeachment girls are all over there
Is that are unclear
But it's alright all basically about magic haha
And
These individuals are
Pi lira
You know our remote viewers involved in remote
Viewing involved in the
Conation
Putting together
The protocols with
The swan
Of the original
Remote
Viewing product
And
This involved
Scientology
Practice
As well
So it's it's important to know that all of that
Is
Just
Information
Where packaging information
A way of using your psychic abilities
He's in
Ascertain
Controlled way
To access
Events
An end
Future Past and Present events
Things going on
That are
What we call signal non-locality
And
Spooky action-at-a-distance these are all terms
Related to that
No they're not welcome back to this
Reactions at a distance
A great expression
What they called and what they call it I love it
There's a lot of
Information and
An investigation that
Sit down around this
It also has been around for
From time
Immemorial
Not under these
Name
But certainly practice
Spy Dark Magician
And like magicians
Everywhere
Witches
You know warlocks you name it
Around the blue name
Just for
Freon
So
It's important to know this
This is not new
It is simply been
Put into a kind of a
Protocol and
Scientology
She has also been
Instrumental
So your theory from Pastor Mike Richards Kerry Cassidy episode
Involvement in Scientology
Might be sounding a little less crazy now
So apparently Scientology is just a
The formulation of the
Making yourself able to use magical powers
That witches and warlocks you name it I've been using forever
That's not good I mean
I do like the idea that
It's okay now to just be like what he does know how to use Magic
Right
Sure he got that Elemental with him and they f****** rolled out you know that's the real issue
That's totally what you start about she's like we're making people clear but that's not El wrong thing that's actually what f******
John Deere 1600 what if I were to tell you that
Instead of allowing you to use magic it's a blackmail racket
What
What is blackmail but black magic
Certainly
So we carry talking here about rendlesham and I we get some of Mark's
Perspective on it
And I don't
He's correct
Mark said
That
The reason they're such a cover-up
Of the rentals
Is that there were over two hundred people
Affected in the radius of the inside
The aliens
We're attempting to land this is had been there
Second or third
Make contact with humans
What happened
In this Landing
Attempt
They used
Telepathy
To communicate with
Around
He said there were both civilians
And Military
Attendance
And
That lends itself to the idea that the landing
Was
Free
Arranged
And
This also went over
On over
Appeared of eight days as
Supposed to
Three that are you
They talked about
This is all made up
No no come on it's alien Hanukkah damn what's so fun when there's a cover-up you could
You say anything
Doesn't need to match anything cuz there's a cover-up or any can see this in the like
None of this next clip means
A f****** thing
When the aliens
Projected the images into the humans
Mine
A lot of the humans
Couldn't handle it
What they were projecting where images not only
Have themselves but also of other races David
Encountered
Right so other
Planets
This sort of
Package of
Telepathic
Formation
Freak
The Americans
And the British
All those in
In attendance
Out I think
I think Mark's been reading Lovecraft
I really just think is really like
This is just like Shadow out of time or
Ready
Pretty similar to a couple of Minecraft stories
Make things a lot more complicated like
If this is their second or third time trying to contact
Don't they already know that their psychic abilities
Yeah
Who's Carrie actually speculate later that there the spider leadership the spiders were involved
I thought they're going to be rabbit
I hope you only thing
The only thing that makes sense to me
Spiders are like are you guys look last time
It's really did not go well
People Freak the Freak Out
Let's try it again
Guys
I propose we don't change a thing
Probably just those people talk
Different people work differently
The great. Does humanize the aliens quite a bit
Spiders
Most likely
Terry's Pizza
So
Bunch of people freaked out couldn't handle it cuz I saw a bunch of alien beings and their head
Classic Warcraft
Catch a glimpse of another world to drive you mad
So I bet you might think like okay then
What
Happened with them
Wouldn't they still be raving mad people throughout rendlesham do while turns out
Mark might have also seen been in
A lot of the humans never
Recovered their memories
Or white
Afterwards
Military Mike
Patrol
Attempts were made in that regard
Some of those humans
Lost neuralyzer
Recovered
Then there was also a
Exchange of Fire
Because when
There was an overload
From
The aliens
A few minutes
Humans react
And
Then the aliens reacted
The humans reacted
There was an emotional overload
That went to the
Artificial
That the aliens brought with them
Who then reacted
To the overload of
Emotional
Energy
And apparently
One side or the other open fire I'm not sure which
There was friendly fire
Clear all the circle
This is madness
Adding that little detail of this is their second or third time just make sense
So much better
Afterwards if you're the spider that was in charge of this you're getting called into a meeting with your boss
Hey
You should know better
You let this happen this is an event
I thought before it was just the humans got f***** up now I know that we're creating a feedback loop or everybody except aliens
Gunfire and the aliens ever using like human weapons or else they would leave evidence of alien
Weapon discharges all over the place because they're both in this feedback loop
Trigger emotional overload
Yep holy s*** that this is a quite disaster the first
It was just we later the rug spot we got to go to the UK
And dudes just like
You're so fired
We have to do a 40-year cover-up about this and how
Do you understand
Oh that's really f****** up at your job
Centralia
Bexar I worked at Groupon I got a price wrong on one of the deals
Oh yeah huge mistake that I ended up
Having to get in trouble for
I worked out okay but it was a big
Chaotic day
I can't imagine if I was that spider
Holy s*** I would recommend it
So anyway.
But actually it might be okay because Mark met a guy
Marcos
So said he is met a man near
Salinas California
Who was an MP at the
The time wasn't attendance
On the rental
Meeting and Landing
And he
He said he's never regained
Is memories
Completely but lost his mind and then
Either
And
That this
This was
So that this was covered up
And I'm in a huge way
Alright
That makes sense I love this I love this type of
Storytelling like it's my favorite type of story. Have You Ever Seen The Magicians
The Sci-Fi show no I have not
Introduce a problem and then immediately know the guy who can
Can solve 0 time difference between them just like hey
I don't know if this is true or not will guess what I know a guy
Viet
Well I'm also one of the things that I have a little bit of a problem with here is that Mark
Committed that murder in 1982 to prison in 1984
Right
Here's the thing that event took place in December 1980 so there was a
Former MP
Who was
There who lost his mind
Reef way to go 84 if you met this guy in Salinas
To be this guy was an MP lost his mind went to California was wondering
The window is small and unless
Of course astral travel
Spooky action over discharge or absolutely
Idle by the
Anyway
So the coronavirus and Mark is a depopulation
Playing course
And we know this
I don't I don't believe
How many months prior to this whole occurrence
And Breakout
Of this
So-called virus
Basically
There was a plan
According tomorrow
Talk to eliminate
500ml
Chinese
This was their plan
This is liquid leak
To Mark and
I guess it's
Group that
He works with in the
Really
And they were
Reply. What I know
I'm going down this path
Obviously they failed
Important point
It's so cold virus
It was leaked to mark
Yep
By the people you work for the military
Sure it was
But you also see similarities
Is between her narrative and Alex's narrative
In terms of China wanting to depopulate there was a Chinese plan
All of this is very closely in line with the lot of things that have the underpinning
Of up till this point at least Alex's
Conspiracy narrative about this
Which is weird weird
Immensely enjoyed
So-called
You can put that in front of everything and everybody's like
Another similarity between her view of this and Ally
There's no doubt that this
Is a
This version
Bioweapon
But it will mute
And it
Is triggered
As well
55g
And
Mark was not
Clear on whether that
The case a lot of Bend
Investigation has
Dan driessen
So here you see a similarity and a
Kind of different as far as I've heard
I'm committed to the 5G
Necessarily being involved
I have heard at least a call her makeup on me didn't push back on it just entertained on Alex's Chevrolet
But you have them a fuller version hear of it is a bioweapon it's triggered by 5G their interconnect
Also at the end are you heard like
This is just Carrie
Mark didn't even say that
Yep this is supposed to be about her interview with Mark
She saying he didn't say that you know what so far
I think she knows something and that is
Mark was not having a good day so he's not bringing the Heat
He said she said he said he
He just didn't know he's supposed to like Selena
Give me a
Mark doesn't know
So this next clip is kind of where my brain just was like
I don't even know what to do and I stared
My computer for like 5 minutes after hearing this is just like I don't
I don't know what's going on
There's evidence even in the documentation
Behind 5G
Saying that
It will
That oxygen
Is
Actually
It attracts
Oxygen
Attracts 5G
Somehow there's
Some kind of relationship there between
By the frequency
5 gm
And that
Consequence humans
Around it
Trouble breathing I just didn't know I don't know what to do
I don't know what to do oxygen attracts 5G 5G attract oxygen I don't know what's going on
That's the kind of thing that makes me wonder is higher than
In the closet I don't I can't I can't I can't
Do this when somebody says oxygen attracts 5G
You stop everything and you listen
Very non-specific
How do you think Alex
Give me any kind of reasonable way that oxygen could attract 5
Well you see oxygen what is it right
That literally or is that likely give me what is the chemical compound
Roblox
Oxygen
HO2
I understand
But oxygen molecules attracted to each other
Alright so we're dealing with an isotope of oxygen
Maybe I don't know and I don't know
I hear stuff like that and I just
I almost get into like
Trance
No
I know I just don't understand how you can say that
So there's a lot of people who have got the Coronavirus
Covid-19 there's a lot of people who
Particularly in China is large
Numbers of people who have passed away
Because of complications in the pneumonia and what have you
Gary would say that this is not true
And in fact
There's something else going on
So as of
February 6th
The numbers Mark had was 100,000 humor
Involved
He said 30
Percent had died 30
Affected
And 40% were
Taking off world in
Shipt other planet
Anti-sexual
Insofar
Okay okay
It's a cover for the Raptors a reptilian drives me to take 40% off of $100
Enzo 40,000
Yeah people off-planet to f***
And eat
Okay
I think that seems like a lot of work it's frustrating that seems like a lot of work
Right considering they could just
I don't know whatever they do all the time are they doing this all the time like in wars and anytime anytime is like an earthquake
Play Kismet cover for aliens
Taking people to f****** eat
You don't need to
You go to look
You know you're sometimes you order the same meal at a bunch of different restaurants
You go for the atmos
You know sometimes you need to get that food in a different wet you know that maybe this is their version
Tiki-themed
Sure sometimes you order out sometimes you want to walk to the store to pick it up you know it's different mood
Yeah that's very stupid
So it turns out
There's a lot going on and what it has to do with
And a grander level is aliens taking over the
And
I started
You hear a lot of things that are very similar
When Alex talks about what's at the bottom of the rabbit hole
When he starts talking about
Be evil demonic spirits that are behind the global it right which are totally real and they are spirits and they are not a
Aliens are silly
Seems to me
There's a lot of similarities retox about the Draco
And The Reptilian and Alex talks about the demons that are behind the globalist
We are fighting a battle
Planet Earth
Against
They're inter
Appearance
Here on the planet
As well as
Their plans to
To terraform this
Planet
So none of this is really
Really all that
New
Added element of
Of course of five
She has Escalade
The symptoms
Situation
Attracting too much oxygen rollout of chemtrails
Implantation
Implantation of Nano
In the chemtrails
House and in our bodies
This is all part of the agenda
The push to make
Make a trance human agenda
And also change
The environment here on planet Earth
To make it a more methane
Like environment all of this is
It's been covered by
By Project Camelot
In my interviews
In my present
Temptations
For many years
The transhumanist agenda is something that Alex talks about a whole lot and being away to make a
World where these demonic forces can
I don't know how to drag drag queen Story Hour into this would be like oh we just got bingo
You nailed it yeah
Planet Alex talks all the time about how we're actually
Carbon starved
The Cowboys are trying to change the environment eat whenever he gets really
Died like grasping Hill pull-out childhood's end and how the the aliens in childhood
Zen needed to create the environment in a different way for them to be able to
I exist like this is all very similar to
Like just pulling things from
Probably the same sci-fi sources
And just packaging them in different ways
In order to either push
A paranormal conspiracy world or a political
Conspiracy world
And
Baby Wilson record
Acknowledge that by Alex it might as well be buying into carries s***
Cuz the same
Level of reasonability
Yeah we said last week said it was recently it's just like
Like the only difference between those is your flavor of sci-fi so
And it just goes on I'm in the similarities or are very
ISO reptilians and Draco RS
Assisting China with their population
Reduction print
Plans
According to mark
China doesn't need help
From the West
To eliminate
Population
And there
Doing this on their own
So anyone who you happy in this scenario
Boo
I mean taking aside that kind of callus and shity perspective
You replace Draco and repealing the globalist there at the beginning
The sentence
The globalist are helping China with population reduction very easily comes out of Alex's mouth
Very easily
Call the same s***
So
That carry will tell you that some opportunist
Are out there and they're trying to use the coronavirus for their own purposes
Maybe
To get more attention
To your videos that are monetized on YouTube or
Oportun
There are Opera
Fortunus out there that are taking advantage
Of this
Roll out
Of obviously
This
And I
And and and
More
IR
Basically using
The weaponized
Mutation of it
Attack their own
People
It is
No coincidence
That the highest rate
Pics of
CVS
Are also showing up
Around the world
Inflation
Is where 5G
Has been installed
There's a problem with this argument that carries making and that's what it's not really possible to trace a one-to-one relationship
Chipitin coronavirus cases and availability of 5G
D coverage
One glaring example of this
Is that there's a particularly bad outbreak in Iran
According to press tv there is no 5G programming a run as of February 13th 2020 but
There are plans in place to begin launching one in the coming Persian calendar year
Which just began this month
So that kind of dozen
Makes sense
4 Cal AR
South Korea is another country with a ton of cases of Coronavirus
This is an interesting study
Before the 5G Ark
The largest number of cases are in the area of Daegu which does have 5G coverage
But
The capital Seoul
Elsa is a very robust 5G networking place
It has relatively few cases of the virus
There doesn't seem to be to be a
Determinant of vector
And given the kinds of datapoint to see the two
Far more likely there's something else
Another variable at play
The carrier's ignoring
In order to push
Her 5G
Conspiracy paranoia
Perfect sense okay Iran is trying to roll out this 5
And then there is it's like an oil spill you know some of the 5G got out
Before they were ready for it so that's why there's so many
It's just contain better where is Dago's they have a terrible 5G containment system
Getting all that
Jean going around everybody script
Similarly Italy has had a lot of cases of the virus
Sorry my bad
But they only have partial 5G coverage in select cities
In 2019 they launched 5G in Milan
Torin and bologna which are all cities that have had some relevant coronavirus activity
But the problem is they also launched 5G in Rome and Naples
Would you seem relatively very little virus activity
The next country with the most cases of Germany
There is currently no 5G Network in Germany
Are there maybe if you stay antennas around the country that are experimenting with implementation but there's
Nothing you would call 5G
Coverage
They're currently wireless companies making bids to build out and according to an article in January from
MyTouch you well
The whole thing isn't its infancy
For telefonica Germany was quoted as saying quote by the end of
2021 the company wants to offer 5G in the five largest German cities
And by 2022 it wants to expand to be 30 biggest cities
So the next hardest-hit country is France and they too are in the early stages of 5G deployment
It's easy to see China and South Korea being hit very hard by this outbreak and save those countries are on the Forefront of
5G so these things must be connected
But that kind of thinking requires completely ignoring a
Ton of other variables
Factors which is kind of the Project Camelot specialty
When you look at the actual country
Like it's all good and well and fun to say the countries that are hit the most
Are the ones that rolled out 5G
It's just it doesn't match the reality so
You're wrong
It's just wrong they're not good with Nuance or
Variable like
It's the same way that she described feels good that she described like
In that b******* callus
The awful clip where she's like oh well the Chinese
Have no problem killing themselves so they are not victim
Considering it's like
At no point in time does she accept that there's a difference between Chinese people
Like Chinese people are people
Like it she treats them the same way that she
She treats the alien races of like football that means in the same way all time
Chinese people do this leadership killing them or whatever it's them all doing it
Essentialist argument that
Give my perspective that she has
It's about classes
F***** up yeah it's it's very weird
And
And dumb
So
To get back to more Alex Jones Connections in this next clip she discusses how humans are
There's a plan in place
That's moving forward to make humans
Part AI which is
Alex talks about a lot
Uncle why didn't you write we talk
About
What is that
Humans
Art
Slated to
To become partially ailife
Transhuman
Species at the
This time
Although Mark Fields
What's that
The transhumanist
Agenda will not be allowed
What happened
Because he's he believes there's enough
Military men like
That are against it
There's the big
Issue is they cannot tell
Exactly
When we move
From being
AI
From being human to being
And there
At which you
Become
Mora
AI than you
I'm human
Is a philosophical argument that I'm not positive
She and Mark had
I mean the Cubans are slighted
Become part AI
He's probably not going to work because there's a human resistance within the military is
Classic Alex
That is very very
Very out that they need to get the coup taking
In Caribbean and that's how we're going to get rid of 5G or partially or whatever it is you like
So turns out draco's
Bad news
Does Draco
No good they're fighting the Raptors in space right
And it turns out that a lot of things that happened on Earth
Actually part of that battle
So he said that there's a draco battle in the Ryan Galaxy
And a lot of what it's been
Been happening on Earth
To do with that bat
In that better
Battle.
Drake or
Fighting with
The Raptors
And
Have recruited 1 million humans
For fighting with them against the
The Draco
At the same time
The Draco and ripped
Killian's the reptilians
I are working with
China
In order to
Distract the rap
Here on Earth
And Aki
Occupy them
And to take therapy
Oceanway from
Here on Earth
Get them to fight in
Battling
Galaxy
And so that they can
Can take over Earth
So it's a takeover scenario
This is a kind of Battle of going on
Between
What we call good evil but it's
It's really
A Transformer
Agenda
The end
Yeah I hear stuff like I was like okay
I like
I'll let you
Put that out there
I love the new
I love whenever they have specific
Play Dido like
Of course the Raptors need
1 million humans
Bright the exact number
Child Roku
What kind of s*** like
You don't know how many people are a lot of
People also I feel like this plan is self-contradictory
So there's a pre-existing war between the dracos and the Raptors that is in space
I'm going to try and walk through this
So
Draco
Leaving Raptors in space Battle of good and
So
The Draco are coming to Earth
And using the Chinese
In order to distract the Raptors right
Because they want to distract them from the battle in space
Right
In order to lure the Raptor forces here so they can have success
In space
But then she says
That it's a plan to take over Earth
But it seems like Earth
Is really the distraction for the Orion rice battle what is actually going on here
Not be important but then ultimately it seems like she saying that it it's the ultimate goal
Well I think it's a lot like it's a lot like how is like World War
Faces go back and forth you wouldn't do that but what it was
To get the French over there and then they Retreat from that base and then go take over another one and that's why they were in
Listed with the Raptor
Planning
Jordan that bass but they used as a factor
Is not important
That's
I think that means that we're not important in this scenario
Still curious make us the most important because it's narcissism
Either bait or where the heroes one of the two can't really do both
Similarities of Alex
And I just whenever I listen
Do this now
Is just such a
Stark
Contact contact
Between
The evil force behind the globalist
And the Drake
Salmos 121
There is a relation
Between
The Draco
And reptilian
And the Gracie
To report to them
As well as
What's called there
Put package
Together
In
Terminology
He called the luciferian alliance
On humans
Blood Fever
And they're luciferian there's the Satanism that's wild
So there is a race
That used to be around called the Anunnaki and they were humanoid
Species
And now they're helping
With the bad guy
Which makes them look globalists
Oso the Anunnaki are helping the draconi okay okay
Which makes them the globalists in the scenario that are doing the bidding or The Vinoy door whatever there
The bidding
Of the Draco evil force
It's also
Significant
As I've said
Before that
Anunnaki
He were taking over
Also by this reptilian
Agenda
By the Draco
And so what you have at the
This time is it
Draco
Anunnaki
Dihybrid
Race
And this is off
Often wear
Anunnaki
You're considered
Or thought to be reptilian when a real reality they are a humanoid
Many
Eons ago
And
The Draco
Are helping
China to obtain their goal
5 eliminating
A certain portion
Troy
So there is a sense that we have invader
Always always always invaded so you got the Anunnaki or humanoids who are doing the bidding of
The dracos
China
It's all this
I do I do see like
Here's what I see going on with this is
Is like when the protocols of the Elders of Zion was written there was a committee there and they were all
Call pitching ideas for what it was they were doing and one guy
It was just like
I know we're talk about Jews but what if it was a lie
And they're like it this guy the f*** out of here and granddaughter
So
We'll get back to some of this weird
S***
But it has to be interrupted Baha'i
Claim that I just can't imagine is true
There's also a
Just want to highlight
Contractor
In the media
The area media
At JPL
Oceanlab
And there's a very old
Fashion
Phone system
Damn that I became aware
At that they keep
Operation
And obvious
Actually this is Angela
Basically
I guess in
I don't think I believe Carrie worked even as a contractor for the jet propulsion Laboratory
Since 1958 JPL has been owned and operated by NASA so at any point that she could have possibly been there
I should have been employed by NASA
I find this difficult to believe but then again a lot of really strange contract
Deployment does happen
Yeah
It's not in
Possible to me but
Is weird
Cadillac
I don't like it
I don't I don't buy it I don't buy it but
It does have the sound of like such a tossed off
Fact
But there's something behind
I feel like you would come up a lot more in the past
Another reason I find this hard to believe is the JPL offers a ton of fellowships
Internships for students looking to build up their resume
Given that it's actually also part of the California Institute of Technology
I would assume that whatever media contract work they would have like iron
Carrie for could have easily been handled by a Caltech student
I have no idea
I'd be interested to know more about her supposed entry and that in this resume
Even if she did contract there for a bit I have no reason to believe that I gave her access to any inside information
Princeton
That little bit of trivia about the phone
She could have easily gotten that from a tour of the
The facility which are offered to folks who make reservations or 41 what they used to hold open houses on a regular basis
Maybe she means she gave
Tours
No
I doubt it okay
Intuit like Imports
She saying about them using an old phone system is even accurate
There are other explanations for what that why that would be the case are Jews are getting it
Can AI take over the Sarah Fredo
But what about the idea that like there might be areas of the lab that are engaged in very precise measurement
Nancy could be thrown off by electronic signatures from mobile phones or Wireless signal
I have no idea if that is the case
But off the top my head
It's possible explanation for why a super high-tech lab might rely on low-tech strategies for phone
Obviously it's it's
Completely conceivable
The direct line to Batman
Now
We get into weird Theory
This ends up being a rationalization for why Trump is closing
On the Border
Border
We've heard her talk about this before
This is not a completely fresh.
That she has
But it's fleshed-out in a way that is a little bit
The
More full then we've heard
So the gray human hybrid
Program
People that wanted me
Me to ask Mark
More about this so I
I did talk to her
Obviously they're gonna
Has made a deal
With Grace
God
Having to do with it
Exchange of Technology this goes by
The days of ice
And how horrendous
Is very well-known
Coerced by people
Sceptre Roswell
Now there
Was a deal also made
To get them to
Stop abducting us
A citizen
And to focus on
South of the Border
That indie
Is what happened
The greys
Happen
Much more Act
Abducting
Frozen Latin and South
America
As a result
Over the past
60 years
And this is really white
Close the border
It has to do with
Those hybrids
Coming of age
So those are
Great human hybrids
And
That was a very sick
The program
Are the greys
And a lot of
Come Back Inn
States
And this
Is creating
Kind of annex
Scenario
Having to do with
With a population
Control all this is creating a narrative where it becomes the most
Smelly acceptable for you to accept
Brutal policing
On
Vulnerable populations that are coming up from
South of the Border is all just a
Outrageous
Fantasy version of why I like
Yeah of course we should put people in cages of course Batman kill them if you need to get her superpowers
Their super-powered understand like this could be a
Cyclops with no mask situation
Very easily allow it to be
What if what if one of them is able to explode
What are what are we doing I just don't know.
I mean
You know I think a lot of genocides where X-Men based
Honestly I
Personally that's
Why genocides tend to ikaria
Yeah everytime they pop up this is all just to create emotional distance between
Green people that are unlike yourself it's shity
It's really really
I'd like to say this
I understood
That according to Paranormal lower
Eisenhower signed a contract with aliens do you know that has to do with a doctor
Is apart of the Canon
Do people in Central South America and if so I would like to say I don't like Ike
That's really shity
Really that's
American foreign policy in Dutch
Just don't want to know how sweet
Go f*** with them
Horrible
Training with the
How can you make a treaty
With them
For another Nation to be
Ransack
Like aren't we really that's not even a treaty isn't he just being like a
Look at those guys over there why don't you do those guys
Right that's bad that's real bad
We're on his part and also carry is being
Quite frankly that's all that really boils down to it's just a rationalization and I mean
I guess it's probably more fun to tell yourself
But that's like what you're afraid of
Hey hey
Different skin than me I'm not worried about them
X-Men
Is that
The problem is there's going to be an invasion at the border
And
It might not be immigrants from the the South and we know that this is going to happen
Mainecare explains why
He has it on really good authority alright
There is also still the risk
Chinese info
Filtration through our border
Underground
Of that border
And I've actually had
A very
Dream
And I certainly hope does
I'm true that it does
Border I didn't know you had a dream
Well that's all that mean
Now that I know that I've got dream behind me I add there's just nothing I do know that she's psychic
We
Is not good check is going to invade with X-Men
She's on Trump side
Yeah
Did she not know who the bad guy in X-Men was
She what
But that's that's how they that's how the movie got made
Emsam
It's Pro X-Men propaganda from the Chinese
Exactly
This is also also
No doubt also
Important point
I don't know what superpowers are being created
Down there
But
Every single X-Men movie I've ever seen
Every single EX man and woman
Can handle a wall
There's that one guy the guy who was kept in in that little roof
X-Men the Last Stand the one who cured other mutants of their mutinous
Magneto Magneto f**** up walls
90% of X-Men characters would have no problem with the wall Nightcrawler can crawl right over it
Most of them can fly people can walk through walls
Juggernaut just run through
But then you reveal yourself to the greater population so it makes more sense to just acquiesce to your
Horrific treatment
I don't know
Okay
Still going to have a problem with the teleporter
Well that working for the Draco
If you can teleport you get you get Lieutenant Colonel status love the idea that you're trying to
To create this exaggerated and your solution is a f****** wall
We got super
Human
Campbell wall
No matter what every one she likes is incompetent any story
F****** humans can climb these walls overfill
Not superpower people
Dumb dumb
Betty White
You were touching on
Some of the
Let's call it subtle racism
Well
Compared to this next clip what you said earlier was
Not-so-subtle
Also involves her believing that the movie Logan is real we have
The great movie has said that it's real before so that part not shocking
Although the book comes after it
Barry rice
Again the gray
To the Reps
Or to the Draco
There's an important
Story
Sort of story
I'm talking about
Has to do with an X
X-Men movie called
Logan
I highly recommended
If you haven't seen it
Scary movie
Latinos
South America
Are closer
2 as of what you call a route race
Closer to the root race
And therefore
They are
A better genetic
Sort of basis
Or more fertile ground
For the
Invasion
Have the gray
Genetics
And
You know when you do
Hybridization
Is no new need a very sturdy
Rootstock
And so this is
Is why they
They
It in that area
I and
Meaning strong enough
To handle
Without dying
The grey
That's that's
Going on there
Wow
You know what this
This is
Proof of how equal our society
In the in the early 1800s in the early 1800s this is
Is the type of s*** that doctors would say about
And now here we are a woman is
Strong enough to paint an entire race of people with one big broad brush
We've always dreamt
Quality that's racist bulshit
Equality
Okay
I mean you could
You could
Kind of make the argument
That closer to the root race
That's a phrasing
Might be equivalent to an evolved
I can't even get it like it this is I don't know what that means, CLE
I don't know how you can say that out loud and be like no I'm not being racist
Because actually being complimentary
They're so much better than because this classification of people is
Different than
White people
Yeah they're not as far along the path right makes them easier
Aliens to hybridize
Obviously we'll just fall apart at the drop of a hat have you seen
On the beach
We get off work
I really just don't understand people who insist they understand anything about June
Genetics while at the same time looking at somebody thinking skin color means jeans are completely
Yours going to different color than mine so obviously you're from a completely different route race stock
Yeah Cheese's
Christ
Knock knock
Barry rice
Glad that you watch the Logan though
Yeah
Good movie
Turns out Mark
Add a option
That he faced in his life and that was the possibility to become more than
Human himself
Twisted offer die
Raptor enhancement
And
It's a piece of raptor brain that
Would have been merged
But he
Raptor
Rappers at Branson hotels right even though he works
The Raptors
And they are on
Humanity
Time
I don't like the app
The blossom
Raptors that's
Depicts in
The Jurassic
World in
Jurassic movies
Exacerbated by constantly getting the quest the Raptors
I mean
And they don't have they don't have feathers so don't even get me started on that whole thing
Ask Mark Richards about the feathers I've never heard of Chinamen on that that's a good point that's a good point I would really settle that for once and for all
Feathers no feathers
Walmart
I need to know
Yeah so I guess it means like
Hey I respect anyone's decision whether or not to become part Raptor
But it seems weird
Wow yeah he would've been disqualified from the Olympics so you won't even become part wrapping
Buser
So we hid now to the question of the 2020 election here
And Marquette
Jim Carrey have some
Great thought
Interesting analysis that Mark thinks that Trump will win
Which I think a lot of people are
Concerned about right
So regarding
Trump and another
Are term he does
Believe that
Have another term
He says the people running
The Democratic
Side
Those running
Iowa caucus
Was proof that the
But they are not going to allow any of those running
Seed
Corsage
Elections
Time
Forever
Especially
Kennedy
So from then on
Pre-election
Wilson
Leonardo Lincoln
No certainly not even for that but he did bring in the Federal Reserve what you would think
Draco would be into according to the transitive property
Yeah
Cool
Alright
I'm telling you Marques not bring it
This is a lazy tag party sucks
Good call Mark I will I will save it from
By experience of watching it I did also feel like
There's a much less marking this big normal.
And he needed to flush it out a little
So we get now to talkin about
Listen to this and tell me this isn't just
Exactly Alec
However
What happened with
Trump and Ivana
This many times
Been a hack
Talking back
From the Hillary
Of the elect
So that's
How I
Trump came
Manpower
Impact by
Open back by certain personal calendar and hacking back a counter to the counter
This narrative runs
Through of
Many different communities they're all
Convinced of this idea that all elections are controlled
But Trump isn't because he's working with the good guys and Ray
Mysterious secrets
Space Program deep State whatever the f***
In a counter-coup against
The coup that Hillary was running
All its Universal
Weird
Scenario back to Knicks
That's something that I was expecting you to say
The Nixon get a very particular
Either job in the Eisenhower Administration
Okay
He handled the alien
Yes you did a course
Why did I do that
Why was that tape turned off then we talked about the Cuban Missile Crisis again be
Because I wanted to
Get some clarification on
The information we
I gotten in the past
From Mark regarding. And
Nixon's role
Exedra
And
Nixon obviously never got all over it
And pee
People are recommended
To see the book by Ashton
Greywater
The hoax
I will not
And Nixon had
Handled the e.t.
Situation for Eisenhower
And was red in
Nixon
Was taken down through mine could
Troll
An operation
In Orchestra
Headed by
These usually
Usual Suspects
Says I call them
Jordan what's the glaring problem in this timeline
God
The Cuban Missile Crisis happened in October 1962 at which point Dixon was
It's not an office nor was Eisenhower
He was busy Nixon was he was running for
The governor of California
While he was still work
With Kennedy
Azalea it was not
Heather I understand
I know JFK one and Nixon was
Absolutely furious with
But when you get a chance to handle the aliens for the president of the United
You got to do anyway
Right
In office
Nixon was at Ryan's Cuban Missile Crisis happen how
Couldn't get over that
Right
And then would become president years later
And then was impeached
Because of Mike
Control
This doesn't make
I wrote down the question is she of Nixon fan and she answered it in that clip
Vitamix an apologist at least
They always support the bad guy does he
Do they just not know when about like not super consist
A lot of the folks who were in The Alex Jones the side of the right-wing and Alex prior to
More recent history we're pretty not internet
Nixon was not somebody who
They consider like
Someone in the Goldwater vain
Well any help through open relations
Alex is a little bit more money on that now because of
Being friends with Rodgers certainly makes it difficult when your best friend has a tattoo of
Nixon on his back
But a lot of the folks like if you go back to like a John Birch Society folks a lot of them were very naughty
Internet
So
Who carries angle on it is very strange
I'm not sure I've ever heard the he was brought down by mind control Arkansas
Appreciate on some level
Could Nixon not get over the Cuban Missile Crisis which he wasn't
I mean unless while he was running for governor of California
He was somehow involved in the Cuban Missile Crisis
Maybe
She answers that it's turns out it's her explanation for literally f****** everything
Basically with regard to the
Cuban missile
Which
Nixon never got over
There were grave
He's coming in
Interdimensional
Leave it had to be
Stop.
Course
They
And Leash
Some very Horeb
Stop
He said the graves were involved
Totally in that
Crisis that it
Was not about
People thought it was
Russian missile
That was
A cover is always a Stargate going on everywhere there's aliens coming in and you just see it like
Sure you think
So you know brinkmanship between world superpower
That's not it's aliens
You know
Always
Mark
Does not like
Immigrants so much he will rewrite history to always be about somebody coming into this country
Yeah
He hates immigrants
It's painfully consistent
Every time there is something
And I like the first Iraq War
Saddam Hussein was trying to bring an alien through a portal every single thing
It's not as aliens in the portals
Covenant through a portal
Every single f****** time it's aliens in a portal
And it turns out those fires
And not Brazil
It's definitely about alien okay
He talked about
The jungles
In South America
Rock'n Africa saying that
The grayscale
Considered
Jungles
Huron
Planet Earth as dangerous
REI
Now that's what I was looking for
Life-form
So that
They consider
South America
More friendly environment
And the deforestation in the fires in
In the Amazon
Get more candy
I live there
Does light bugs
He's projecting all of his hatred go to the Grave
By Grace afraid of jungles
They would be afraid of CDs to then cuz to them
Everything is for urban jungle
If they prefer
Planes dad temperate Plains they want to live
In Iowa
If gray aliens are afraid of jungles because of their being a bunch of things there
Date of every
Right
Everyday will be afraid of human
Afraid of cows
Is exhausting
It's like I was like
It's like War of the Worlds
Bailey's weren't afraid of us but they should have been afraid of the
Cold I grow weary of this
What we need to do to stop them is either or
Turn the entire Earth into a jungle now see this is one of those interesting instances where the fantasy scenario actually come
Kind of works
Towards the right goal because his right
She should be opposed to the deforestation and the burning of the forest because she's afraid that
Razor trying to hang out without the bug is the business interests that are behind before
PlayStation be opposed to the Amazon disappearing
Isn't it this is an instance of like if that's how you get there that's how you get there
I'm not going to argue with you we'll deal with that later
But the other is not so much they cannot agree with
The conclusion
That's why I'll just go ahead and
I do appreciate knowing that
I am part of the
The human race
Which is not responsible for
Anyting
Ever
In our entire history portal that always been aliens
Last time we talked about
Lackadaisical
Lackluster superpower which is
Sort of tell you where portals might be an expression of the superpower
So there is also information
That
I gave two
Because we
When we
I come to visit
Mark I Stay
In San Francisco
And
The Tourist
For the day before
And
In this case we stayed
Fisherman
It's worth
Fisherman's Wharf in San Fran
Cisco sbk
Highly Dane
Late at night
No it's very nice
Near the public
Iowa
Basically bringing that
Attention because
Is pots
That there is a
The portal there
That has
Oh no Fisherman Wharf is basically the biggest tourist center in San Francisco
Everything there is just like super tour eccentric
I've been there a bunch of times since my grandma lived in the Bay Area and one thing I will say
Is that's kind of working in Kerry's favor
Is it fishing
Dwarf does how's the original Ghirardelli chocolate plant anywhere
Cracked
Right
I've done it all the Fisherman's Wharf man I've been to the Chocolate Factory of gone to the cable car museum of going to Pier 39
And I've never seen
An alien
Last year did see a slight uptick in violent crime in the neighborhood however with a man being murdered there in March
2019 and there been some robberies that have been reported
The murder does appear to have been a fight between people who at least
Kind of acquainted with each other it's very weird
The details are able to find about that
If you know some robberies are going to take place
In any area where there's a high concentration of people so it's not
Yo it's obviously not good but I don't think you should look at
The robberies and be like
Oh my God everything is deteriorating probably a portal
Last month a group of eight women attacked a sixteen-year-old Starbucks
Employee with a golf club and stole her watching phone and it completely bizarre crime
Despite this I can find no indication of Fisherman's Wharf being any more or less dangerous than any big city tourist area after.
If I had to guess
I'm betting the Carrie saw a high proportion of Hispanic people walking around because she knows they're closer to the brute race
And that's more likely to be alien hybrids
She got freaked out
That's kind of nice
She just like summed up white
Flight into second
She was like well it's probably a portal
It's dangerous after dark now you
Right
So I also we get to from Mark and explanation of the assassination of qasem soleimani
I was wondering why that
Wow turns out
Regarding the death of
Solomanie
He said he was
Just trying to access
The gates between
Between around and Rock
And give
Accessed
Ascertain being
Who wanted to
To come into this
This dimension
The real this is
The real reason he had
Did I
He basically wanted
Andrew Lauren
And to let
The real
In just as sad
Hussein
Deposed
Sodom was letting in
Anunnaki
Beings.
Be allowed
It's all portals van
Mark
Does not know who soleimani
I'm guessing he was bluffing around. All is not very creative
On one level is in their particular picadillos like the antiquing
With Raptors on the archaeology with cats
Because I think something that's pretty f****** hilarious because
Like obviously the cat one is cuz of litter boxes
Like
Digging around for artifact
I think they're so fun creativity there but he's not very creative when it comes to
The geopolitical explanation
Everything is aliens coming through a portal
Qassamsoleimani is assassinated it's like wow that's weird why would Trump
Do something like that
I'd like wild course he was trying to create a portal to let aliens in
And the iraq-iran thing and it wasn't a petulant man-baby lashing out
And we all know that that's a
Reasonable
Valid argument to make because that's what happened with Saddam Hussein to all of this
Exhaust
So that we get an update on another figure in the world of Project Camelot that is Sean David Morton who is the sky
Gamer Who Lies through the Prada to bunch of people didn't pay a Texas prison
He's not having a good
Sean David Morton
Regarding
His books and
Time series
And the fact that she
In prison
He's in
In Texas now
Misprision
And
He has been
As I say tortured
I don't believe this but just to be fair I'm going to say if he is being tortured I wholeheartedly and
Unqualifiedly against that
I don't believe
If it is please file a report with like the human rights people
Don't just try and
Do whatever you're doing on your YouTube channel
It's a big
Torture is not that big of a problem
I guess it's like it's part of the part of the game and it's very strange
You're going to be torch
I think that like
It's the trivializes the idea of someone actually being tortured absolutely
You should be contacting the UN or something like if you're if you actually
Have some evidence that your scam friend
Is pain torture to prison
But there's a reason and Mark explains why
Die
Sean is getting
Mistreatment
And I talked to Mark about why she
Orchard and
He says they may have been
They try to kill him
Obviously they're trying to
To get at
The witness
Testimony
That was given to Sean
And by his lawyer
Through
Other lawyer
Are of an
Ran
Area
S4
And that's why I should have paid him a time
And
I guess
.
That ended
Doing a good job of it
Degrees
So you got a situation where there's a guy who used to run Area 51 and then became a time traveler and he's
Giving this information that Sean David Morton
Uses Derita Sands of Time book rights Sean's been arrested for his
Rampant crime
Well and now he's being tortured in prison in Mark believes that
It's because they're trying to get at this whistleblower guy who's the source for the sands of time
Become a time traveler
There's a problem or before there's a there's a problem.
And that is that.
Let me read to you from the introduction of the first Sands of Time book
Many years ago a powerful mysterious man approached the author
He lives virtually all his life is a top director in high-level scientist involved in the above-top-secret black world of Shadowgun
Everman projects and research
He said he admired the service of the author and is undaunted quest to bring the truth to light
It began a feed of crucial inside information to be released to the public
He's a hero when certain circumstances presented themselves he wanted to get the truth out to the world before it was too late as our planet was
Iggy said in grave Danger
But he could only tell the whole story after he had moved on to use his exact words
The government doesn't need to torture Sean to get his whistleblower because Sean Zone narrative
According to that dude that
He could only get the information
After the dude was dead
Cuz John only got this from his estate
When it was being sorted out after he died
Like I understand that you could be like I've removed on means he time traveled or something
But he died
According to Shawn's narrative dudes death
Sean himself
Yes I do today at the introduction of his book you can't change the story now
Internal consistency is pretty important when you're just making up
Conspiracy bowls
So anyway Mark believes something is going
Mark said
He read Acts
And that
They contain Bop-It biking
And
Basically they
Maybe trying
Persuasion
Discredit him.
Before there were they
If that's the case you should be out already cuz mission accomplished that dude
Did it before you went into prison
One last clip might down for this because it's a hit you with some whiplash
It starts with a
Sort of
Standard complaint
Of the Paranormal conspiracy world
And then a nonsensical thing
PennDOT problem with humans
Is that they're not waking up
Not fast enough
According to mark
And
She says that they are going to
Sure what's coming
Lie down in the
Wake up
And lastly regarding
Trump's family
Mark says he
He believes the women in
Family
Are knocking
And that was
Basically I think that's my last
And and so that is
That's it
For the mark Richards
Total Recall
Okay
No further comment
I do believe they're human call say on the matter if you're all going to be Dukes
Future also
Not human
No likes
They're good aliens bad aliens are Draco they're not there just
Not well we know that Carrie has previously said that she believes or she's been told
Older Mark maybe even said
That Melania is a
The conduit by which aliens communicate with the trunk
But Mark wouldn't tell her what
Species of alien is contacting her which is not good
We don't even get any implication of clearly didn't tell her what aliens Ivanka
It's not important
Ivanka and
Does this mean
Did Melania is an alien
Trump
Wait but Ivanka isn't melania's daughter
Nope nothing has been f****** alien since the beginning
Every woman in Trump's family is an alien
Why isn't Trump an alien that are Trump's Mom an alien
I don't know man
We got to find this out this is this is a case that I am not going to crack
You got to get to the bottom of this. All right suck it Monday I'm not going back to Alex get to the bottom of this
Family women are aliens
An alien to then right is Barron is melania's
The women aren't human
I don't get quiet I realize I don't care
Yeah you know you think so
Right
So we come to the end of this and I think there's some
Fun stupidity
Fun nonsense here and I've enjoyed
This little lie
Dial before we get down to
On the next episode just getting
Right back down to business
Over Monday on the Alex Jones
Present-day stop
But I think even though we try and take these breaks and we try and look at these
Completely non real world things
And you just see
These shocking overlay
Parallels
Between the what underpin
Interworld
And what underpins Alex
It's and it's
I mean if you don't see the similarities between the two in the ways in which they sort of guide you towards
Similar bad conclusions
Then
I don't know
I don't know what to tell you
I just
I think
She thinks it's a good thing
But
This entire episode seems like she is
Sweetly dehumanizing
Everything
Like
Just people who deal with coronavirus South America
Fallout people in the Amazon are being affected by the fires before station
None of that
None of that matters know people matter none of these nobody is a
Player in the game
The Chinese aren't players in the game it's all the Draco in their reptilian Buddies
Like nobody is a person I think you like the
Larger thing
Is that
These things work is their stories that are being told
In order for you to not have to feel for the people who are affected in these circumstances
There's a narrative it's being spun that's almost like an emotional weighted blanket
Little comfort you instead of having to look at the fact that now there are a lot of things that are going on
On that third week should be doing more about and
For some reason
We're either deer like in our duties or we're just not able
Deal with some
Some things that are hurting
It's really hard
To know the
The government is
Is purposely trying to
Deny water to
Coming into the United States
Undocumented
And in order to kill them
As a deterrent
French for more people
But what if they were
Text Matt exactly
Well if you and I
You & I in a situation where the X-Men are real probably would feel that way it's f***** up
It helps carry not to feel those
Are very conflicted and
And hard emotions and
I guess
If you need that crotch it's fine but
Site
F***** up right
And rendlesham didn't happen it was a lighthouse
And Mark Richards has some very middle-of-the-road political take
Yes he's really got nothing
He doesn't have any heat there man I just think you had an off-day happened that could be
Crawford interview slump
Back on Monday with a normal episode but thank you for joining us for this abnormal one
Until we're back we ever website.com
Right we're also on Twitter
Hot we're on Facebook we are on the show please go to iTunes download
Rihanna Jared don't I do the whole thing could be Gray
But until then I'm neomu yo I'm dzx Clark I'm the ghost of rentals
Holding