Important
I have great respect for its knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as if
MoneyGram
Knowledge vype.com
Everybody
Mbbr Dan Jordan
Have you ever been late
Because of daylight savings
Yeah I'm sure I have but I
Absolutely doesn't stick out of my head because you're late all the time
Various employment but I had
Not super out of the arresting me this because texting before the show
I told you I had no idea
Exactly
11 and I thought it was 9:30 in the morning and it was actually 10:30
You were like let's do 11:00 News 10:17 and I haven't even showered yet
No we're not doing
No I don't know I don't know I guess like
I was obviously so much more aware of it cuz nobody talks about going around
And then in the past like this is
Probably the first time I've been caught
Completely unaware
Like
All these other daylight
Saving Time instituted iJustine
Tons of dumb jokes on Twitter
This is the first time I didn't see anything going on
Forward
I've been really busy too with preparation for this episode to so it's been pretty crunch
Time kind of stuff time to dick around her
I don't know but anyway I'm on
I'm still on Old daylight savings time
On your checks
So Jordan doesn't because why do much about that being late because of daylight savings
They doing a lot about Alex Jones
So today we got an interesting episode to go over recovering
Span of March 4th March 1st
4th 2020 of Diana
And it's
It's going to be part one of two kind of
Episode will cover Thursday and Friday blast
All right I will cover the end of the week
Why there's a
Dichotomy
Alright alright
Do first read thank you so much you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Richard
Thanks Richard
Thanks KC
Bristol thank you so much
Time for Bristol
Tool
Okay
Lone tuul thank you so much
Thank you clone to all my Google robotronic with 2m
Thank you so much you are now a policy wonk
And in front of robotronic Silent is that the one where there was one very soon
Robotronic
Journal
You should be the main the Melinda
People's bayonet
Cue the people
And finally like say thank you to people who donated on elevated level
Thank you so much
Chris Wood
What's the business
Money off that heroin
Why you pimp so good
Is freakishly large
If you're out there listening music
Website.com
Show
We would appreciate it
At-large on Twitter at largest
Channel support pelican
Based on Alex's
Emotional support Liberals are crazy
I did actually in the form of a cartoon and I sent it your way and you have turned it into a
Over on others
If you just go there and I'll direct you
GTV
The store where you can buy and there's that there's
Purple Penguin
Incredible thank you very much
Very oblique
They got crossover appeal.
Go away
Enjoy it's a great cranky looking
It is it is Ty's
Haunting
So Jordan
Lot of meat on the play lot of stuff to get into but
Before we get down to business
We got a
Take a little moment
Here
Another contact dropped
From Today Show
That's the best decision I think he's ever made I would suck around and listen
March 1st is when Alex gets back from his vacation to seapac where of course we covered
Right but at least you didn't get Coronavirus
Remains to be seen
According to Stats still developing story
There's still
See you around any kind of exposure that might happen should be one person at CPAC racetrack
For Coronavirus
I would like to speculate because
Oh yeah I know not not going to bother with that
But Alex was very dumb rally
She did some other dumb
And stuff and he's back
In studio
Sunday episode
He is returned
And I was hoping that he would talk about the route
It was a disaster
It does not come up
At all know when he talks about going to see
C-pack he claims that he was going
Repack in order to gauge
How strong the neocon
Project MC2
It's pretty
Secret investigation
So we're starting on the 1st I will get through the 4th and the reason that I cut it off there
Instead of going home
Second
On the 5th
On Thursday
Alex shaved his head
So I thought I was unable to avoid that information right
Alex shaved his goddamn head on the Shelf
But he has a bald ass head
So from the 5th onward
It's a new era of Alex
True
So in essence this episode is the last
Last few days left of Harry Alex
Bcadc going through the last years of bees
Ain't nobody
So we start here on the 1st and Alex
I guess he had some premonition
About something
Well my advice.
President Trump is this
Where
The Ides
March
Yesterday afternoon
I was looking up
Leap year
Day here we go or a 29th and I and I went
Beware the Ides of March
Delete
I didn't watch Saturday Night Live last night
In fact I went to bed pretty early
My friends
His birthday party for my children
Happy birthday
Play Dar bad I thought
Beware the Ides of March and I got up this morning
Videos up on Saturday Night Live
And they're making threats about Julius Caesar and the Ides of March
Okay alright
Literally every year Alex ominously talks about the Ides of March
The few literate references he has it makes him sound smart research to dumpy
T-shirts
Either that
Or you super in
Late 70s Hard Rock
Oh yeah I'm your vehicle baby I'll get out of here you want to go out of here
Wendy's overdrive songs
Karaoke numbers
I think Alex wants you to think
Thank you psychic and he's in touch with some larger thing in the universe because he thought about the Ides of March and then the next morning
Easy something reasonably close to that on SNL
So he must be reading the zeitgeist
I have a suspicion that Alex did watch
Because he's really mirroring things really close
Okay he's upset about a joke and John mulaney's intro
Mullaney's B he talks about he sets up a joke by establishing that Caesar is where leap year started
What's the leap year apart is even
Was the lady host
Last week
Now I remember where we are
Mullaney's whole joke is it leap year started under Caesar and another thing they did back then was all the Senators stabbed
Because he was power
The tiger that joke is him saying that he called his lawyer to see if he could say that joke and his lawyer called another lawyer who said it was cool
So there's there's a layer to the joke
All right so what was the first lawyer thing
I don't know
That's not good you slice it Alex's interpretation of things is really on
To characterize mulaney's bitters
Is a fret that they're coming after Trump Caesar Style
I was just
I'm not sure if that joke is
Great and I bet it'd probably could be approved with a couple more rounds of edits
Clearly a joke
Like if Nick DiPaolo got onstage at SNL and started talking about how all the black people in the country need to go and started throwing
Alex would get on hair the next day to defend that is free speed 100% complaining about how if depalo faces any
Why does it's proof of the authoritarian left absolute Sterling Americana
But a joke at the dear Leader's
Expense that's no longer a joke that's a
Ignore the fact that has all the characteristics structure of a joke
He was sat on a comedy program and that people laugh
Apollo to the tag
That's no joke
My point is that Alex does not give a f*** about any Notions
If you have the ability he would probably try and put Mulaney in jail
At to Mulaney
What are the primary preoccupations on this Sunday show is obviously a Coronavirus
Studio heaven
Not been able to cover it while Mike Adams Alan Keyes
We're hosting Wiley
Right
Situation is Alex season is there
Two camps in the world
And what is saying that the virus is a hoax and it's not real
Saying that it's the end of humanity
Right and
I think there's a middle ground
Sure
Track record
My Northstar is telling
Is it
I really think it's a right concern
What about that homeless guy was out there and there shouldn't
Saying the virus is a total of
Big deal
That is a total fraud
There's a camp saying it's the end of the world Armageddon
No that's your guy
Call me that's literally arnesen.
Like Adam said it's over dramatic Lone Survivor so he's communist Chinese
Is globalist now like Adam
That's weird here's my problem with the toucan
He is in both of them cycle
That is something that's going to make things very confused
Right
Stream on the like everyone's going to die
At least
Times you've been very much indeed.
You got to get my silver if you want to survive
He's been really extreme on that note but
He's trying to walk that back now
There is a real sense that he's trying to make this a more
Real-world propaganda narrative okay that is by Focus
Sing almost entirely on the idea of the supply chain disruption
Okay will be
Because by the
Coronavirus in China
Right
I said I don't know how deadly this virus really is
I don't know how communicable
But I said
This is going to attack the world economy
This is an attack on President Trump
Is an attack on America
Sure
The
Supply chain attack
How did the virus is deadly or not
You can leave but the response
And the Hysteria
And the way the media unify
Except the United States we did it first
I'm sorry it's just true
Scary Ashley
Check mr. president not sure what's going on but
To this is classic Alex right here this is what we call in there and narrative pivot trying to be engaged
Is it in real time
After this point he's had tons of interviews with Mike Francis Boyle and Mike Adams
Almost every show has been on
Talking about definitive proof is viruses bio-weapon
It's probably race Pacifica
Chinese either intentionally used by themselves or they accidentally released it while planning to use it on us
It's been a
Ceramic the idea that there are 10
10000 more dead than China has said
It's already loose in the United States
I'm coming for you
Like it's B that's been
Largely the the the
The editorial well you are the
Your part Alex
That's different
Since you're in denial that Alex has brought up about how the virus will throw off the economy and it's all intact
Driver of the Tonto
That has been something you said but now it's
The main effect
And that to me it is indicative of a
I feel
I agree
So Alex talks about the sea
CDC and how they're eating Annika
Conspiracy or so
Look at the CDC telling him it's no big deal and not a problem
I went
But it's bigger than that
When it becomes a problem
Then they're going to say you didn't respond properly to
Ladies and gentlemen
Three days ago it's like they flipped the light
Switch
Every radio show that's National that's
Establishment and newspapers on MSNBC
All the usual set
I've got dozens of reports right here
President Trump cause this present
Trump trying to cover it up
I mean yeah
I don't believe seeing an
I don't believe in MSNBC
It must be a hoax
Because you're saying it's serious yes I'm saying it's serious
Because
How the whole media is Unified
How they use it for martial law in Italy and
World Switzerland oven
Clearly this is a big Global move
People
Get ready
The narrative
The plan that he's describing is that the CDC
He came out and they said no big deal
Trump into not doing any
And then when it's
Bad Trump looks
What's the food
I don't care
I hate
Describe an air tube out the the idea that CNN is writing articles about how Trump's response has been
Flawed or is there been things that
Could have been done that weren't done
You know experts saying what the heck what the hell and then
Dum Dums
Who think that every article that's negative about Trump is an attack on him just must not be true
Just describing it an ecosystem
Badfinger
Absolutely
So
Alex
Has this going on
All
Disruption
Of the supply chain in order to
Attack Trump
And there's a second
Back to this
And that is what the virus in China
Itself
Was used by China so they could
Shut down there,
Right
It makes no siren fuse
Results that would piss their employees
Their workers
And the stockholders off
Enchilada right now
I love enchiladas
China just shut their economy now they just lost a big trade war with America
What's happening
The Bible has sold us out
Okay
But if they then released a virus I bought from Obama
Thanos not super lethal but does kill some people in
Spredfast
As well
And then
Out of that they can shut down there
We can order the city shut down
Kills
Global Supply Chain
They just checkmated Trump in America and you know that
What they did
With the Deep state
Weather ungu
When down the economy worldwide
And then say
President-trump
And America
Obviously overblown
Okay
I'm not even sure Alex really even cares what he's
Saying like he's just kind of happy he was able to get to the end of the scent
Start running out of air
This entire conspiracy selling sounds great needs this virus in order to
The cover for just shutting down their economy and lower
Problems that he has considering his
Years long-established rhetoric
So as Alex's selling it
China wants to shut down its economy
Disrupt the supply chain which
Embarrass Trump give the Nationalist a black eye or whatever
Checkmate so in order to achieve his goal they purchased a virus from Obama
Of course I sit on their own count
The reason we needed to go this route is that if they were just a slow down the economy or shut
Factories it would
Which Chinese traditional character a lot about Alex gets into trouble seeing as every single time
We talked about China he mentions forced abortions
Factories
Every single characterization of China is. One that really cares too much of the workers are pissed off
Conception
Exist in the Infowars universe is not a government that we need a virus
Do use a some kind of subterfuge to get away with doing something to workers don't like
Authoritarian
If there's dissent
They cracked down on it
They ran it
They rent they ran a tank over a
That's really where this narrative has a problem
And the fact there's no reason
We're trying to do this thing to its
Be the goal Alex's is claiming they're seeking
Their motive doesn't
Makes sense especially given the fact that if the goal is hurting Trump on an economic basis
Plenty of other moves China could make that would hurt them a bit
Waymore's
Oh yeah
Another problem is the China has been
Consistently closing down manufacturer
Flights for years
In 2018 Reuters reported on 1000 manufacturing plants being scheduled be shuttered by 2020 in Beijing
As part of a program aimed at curbing Smog and boosting income in neighboring regions
There's even president for China shutting down industry temporarily to deal with any cute
Problem
Which is basically the situation
Can we find ourselves in with
Coronavirus
Back in October 27th
19 MPR reported on how China's Ministry of environment
It sent out inspectors across
Country as factories are following environmental laws
It was estimated that a full 40% of China's factories were shut down temporarily
In an attempt to address
It's being done
Buy filthy manufacturer
That's tens of thousands of fact
Beside the predicted effect of disrupting the supply chain with some companies shifting some manufacturing to India and Bangladesh
And others just not being able to
Reproduce at full capacity
Once the work of the ministry of environment had been done
Things began to get back to normal
Angela Alex and most of the people in the world probably don't even remember that this happened
The China shut down almost half of its factories lessons
3 years ago
No
I'm February 27th
CNBC reported that the national retail Federation
Veo was announcing that quote
Some of the coronavirus driven supply chain disruption in China is subsiding
Zeo went on to add a number of the larger companies has started to indicate that the
At the signs they're getting for the Chinese market
Some of the products
Coming back online
Timer Porta Dunbar
Starbucks
Who's announcing that after taking a huge hit
The clothes most
Hibbett stores in China things are returning to normal
The vast majority of their shops have reopened
Early signs of recovery are emerging as the coffee giant is sinks
Sequential Improvement in weekly sales
On March 7th at 9 Ikea locations reopening
China
DIY the South China Morning Post reported on March 4th that over 90% of firms in the Guam
Province have resumed operation
They're still very serious issues to deal with in terms of smaller and
Medium-sized businesses returning to operation
But a lot of the reason that's been slow.
Come back is because of Trance
Deportation related is
As the financial times reported what are the main issues is that a lot of workers are from rural areas
And they're stranded there with no easy way to commute back to areas like Beijing
Get back to work
This gets into a complicated Dynamic rail service is not back online throughout the country
And also World Authority and smaller Villages are
It's raised there.
Downtown people entering or leaving the village
These local authorities are worried that they'll be held responsible if they're raised
Is infection
So they're not acting without the
Explicit direction to the central government
According to an article in the financial
Showtimes citing a scholar from
The point is that we're not looking at a complete
Perpetual shutdown of China's
Decent signs that things are starting to return to a more normal pot
I just to be perfectly clear I'm not trying to pretend that there won't be rippleffect so there won't be difficulties check cuz even if child
Who's back to 100% capacity today
It would still take awhile for that disruption to work its way through this
Supply chain
They're going to be some hiccup
But it doesn't look like the
Doomsday that Alex wants to
Portrayed to be
And they're also
Obviously things
There are unforeseen
We have no idea
How things are going to develop a week from naps
So there could be
Something else that is a wrench in the
But based on the information that's available now
Not to say that China is out of the woods
Do not say everything is resolved
There are indications
Is that there is some resuming coming back
The normal witch
Is something that I would never want you to know
Yeah that's
You can find a lot of business folk Racine what's going on
And their responses to suggest that we need to divert
Fire supply chain
To limit the impact of something happening in China has on the larger economy
You would think that this would be the number one most obvious
Predictable response
The business would have
Scale Market disruption
So if China were trying to do this whole stunt to embarrass
Trump they would have to be doing it knowing
Fully welded
The odds are that business will flee the country in the aftermath
That seems dumb
And honestly my larger point is that Alex's conspiracy really makes no sense
Unless you're working backwards
You need to make a way to
Make this look like an attack on Trump
You just kind of right the rest as you see fit
That's the only way that this makes any kind of sense
Here's the conclusion
I'm trying to reach
I know I need to make not even a series of plausible steps to get there but any steps at all
Because it's so much about the supply chain.
Alex is trying to like
Hey man I don't know I don't know if I said it was super deadly
It's over for Humanity
That's a problem so I'm not going to sit here
Mister racks or Diss track
From what we said
That old Joan says the virus is super deadly
Limbaugh says it's no problem
And sold the stock market start spanking what you had
We said get ready because
In the lab
Obama transferred
ITube
China on record mainstream news 2015
The big debate about it
It's now been released
And the media doesn't want to debate about how it's man-made and who released it and who
Promise
Tesla mean
What's the weather
Tim shut their people down and treat them like slave and prop up their stock markets are totally rigged
China
So this is kind of gaslighter
I think that Alex is realize that he's come
Completely out of step with the right-wing media
Trump
And not only that kind of out of step with the new information that's coming out about the virus so
Now he's pretending
You know I wasn't mostly talking about this being super deadly
Really weird thing to claim
Because I listen to his show and because of that
I can play you this Supercut of times that he and his friends
Said it was super deadly
So what we think they're doing is they're just putting the number of dad is a number of infected
All the dead bodies in body bags
Clearly this is much bigger
From your sources at the UN from your own research how bad is this
You have this also called
Computer game at
John's
Hopkinsville
The only figure I have seen
Seems to be
Paml videre
BJ's
Angel
Bonjo Hayes time to get up and let's get to work folks not like you got a lot of money
About to be at 20%
Mortality rate
Official numbers now show it has a much higher
Death Race
Chinese government says 15%
Coronavirus development
Multiple kruschev people are dying that means it isn't hide
Fast
Coming out we know that it is indeed
Killing healthy young people that is killing a high number of those
That are infected
Jesse's viruses deadly it's not like stars and things that were just too hype up and scare people only killed a few hundred
This is already killed thousands and thousands
The videos are pouring out the Tchaikovsky
And it does have a high kill rate
5% is devastating
I treated a patient a month ago
Reported
And was treated with high doses of antibiotics
For Humanity
It will only be lone survivors
I'm not saying any of this to pump up and claims the guy of elevated wisdom or anyting but I knew a pivot was
That's part of why I keep playing that drop-in my God I'm saying it's over for
Humanity because I know from watching Infowars for as long as I have that they would eventually change the entire story to something
They pretend they didn't play this game
This is working
Food buckets
I'm not going to sit here and pretend that Alex didn't
Occasionally mentioned the trade war is background motivation
Regina having false Flags itself
But the economic stuff was absolutely not front-and-center in these can
Conspiracies
The primary driver of a lot of his coverage with surrounding how deadly this virus was and how it wasn't a hoax
Like you decided zika and SARS and Ebola were
All the stuff Alex said In that clip
Isn't true
It's not true that he didn't Focus strongly on how deadly the virus
It's not true that Obama sold the Viber
Vagina
It's not true there's proof that the viruses
Does man-made
Those are all just
Salvageable narrative pieces
He fell while he was trying to support his argument that Millions were gone
How to die
I need to buy a silver gargle in food buckets
Want to survive
Much like viruses themselves propaganda narratives mutate
In order to accommodate the propagandists
Meads
We saw the center breakdown of the Boston Bomber
Child was constantly shifting things around based on where you wanted it to go
He's doing that now and I kind of suspect there's Turi
Reasons why
The first is that he
Baby keeps going with his death
You put himself squarely at all.
With Trump
If you're screaming about how the virus is going to kill everyone in your hero present
Just calling it's a you know a
No big deal that's where all super prepared everything
It's good it's hard to maintain positive coverage
The second is the Jim Bakker f*****-up Alex's silver gargle sales plant
Which is really the main monetary reason for Alex.
Spread the medical side of the panel
Baker tried to sell his silver the same way Alex
By lying about it being proven to cure
Your Coronavirus
In response the New York attorney general sent a cease-and-desist
Baker went to public with
Damn and now there's a very explicit order from a state attorney general threatening to take action on someone selling his s***
That way
Alex obviously knows that and probably doesn't want to pay millions and fees
The food buckets sales
Are compatible
With a generalized Financial
However
So make some sense that you'd be able to play I Know Places narratives there and do
We can land
If that Anderson had to head
The state of Minnesota strip him of his gold sales lights
Bob Chapman weren't dead you could guarantee that this would be a long prophesied summer of rain
Selling gold
So damn hard you can guarantee of Trumps old trump-branded food bucket
This would be the biggest
Catastrophe in the history of the world
Yeah
So there's another part there
That I think we should
Pay attention
To the end of Alex's initial clip
For that Supercut
Earlier
His argument was the China would need to fake this virus outbreak in order to shut down their economy without angering the workers
But in that last clip you heard Alex use his standard line on
Economies completely faking
Control their workers are slaves in the state does whatever you want
He has these things
So down pat
It's like cruise control for him to spout the mop
She doesn't realize that if these things he's saying or true
He takes her legs out of this new conspiracies yeah
You just doesn't think things through very much and he's totally fine with internally
Consistency I think he's also probably feeling
Betrayal of
Man I've been out on the front here trying to do this and I turned and looked behind me and all of you guys are in the opposite direction
Motherfukers I've been trying
I've been fighting for you and I'm not getting the lines anymore
Now I want to be clear
This is how this show female this is how Sunday feel
This
Feeling
May not last
Odell
Jesus
Christ so anyway Alex believes that this
Viruses attack on Trump
Mostly what's going on but it's a primary thing
But not just Trump
A global problem needs a global solution
This is their answer
To follow sorrow in Brazil
Trump here into the brexit in the UK was having Europe this is yet
So I know it probably seems
Petty of me to keep playing these clips or Alex doesn't know bolsonaro's name there wasn't a bigger reason
It's been months and months that Alex has been boost
Bolsonaro for the first stretch was just calling in Brazil
Trump
You started mispronouncing it pretty wildly
At no point is anyone it enforced corrected
At no point is he realized he was f****** that up
It just seems like
He may not have a good grass
On the subject he's covering
And to make matters worse
Alex interviewed bolsonaro son at CPAC
Mere days before this episode that we're listening to here
Get me
If you listen to that
It seems like Alex is aware that he doesn't know this guy's dad's name he keeps referring to him as your father
Introduction to that interview
Here we are with the start of the Brazilian president who the real Maverick
Can't say his name
I definitely won't say at 2
His son
Space
Bolsonaro son pronounces it very Brazilian
So Alex is convinced one of the reasons
He's correct
What about this
The virus is just to attack Trump
Is because
The media
Media can't stop attacking Trump
You please one click
I don't know if I heard him play any others this is the only one I remember him playing
The demonstrates his claim
Elevator
And now that uses to the Health Emergency to attack the president
Well I think they're actually in for the president
At the CDC and the National Institutes of Health
Responsible
Donald Trump
Actually happened in China where you act like it's not a problem and then you respond
Vice president Pence and charges not a medical doctor
Pictures of total setup were proven right again
That's not the media salivating over the possibility of attacking Trump I did not hear us elevation
That's a very measured conversation about whether or not it's a good idea to point the finger at route for the administration is now
Sample of Public Health
Situation
Obviously there's a
Ton of issues surrounding Trump's response
Man you look pretty well laid out by that anchor
But I'm not really going to get into that water right now
I'm not really well-versed enough
Be able to really assess a lot of that stuff while this
Situation is ongoing
And there are a lot of other sources people can get information
Trump I will address that the sorts of things
If Alex makes a specific Claim about something I don't mind getting into it
Risk making it seem like my discussion of this virus situation comes from a desire to score points
Against Trump so I'm going to I'm going to err on the side of
Not dwelling on that too much
I'm going to go with
It's bad but I don't know how bad
Haha
So that clip is important for one major Reed
This is not the media salivating to attack Trump
It's a restrained articulated series of points about what appeared to be bad signs about the governor
Response to a Public Health crisis
Sure
But refrain does a rabbit attempt to smear Trump
Because Alex has predicted that would be what the globalist media does
On some level I'm convinced that Alex made to the prediction
But the globalist media would attack him for.
Because he knew that
I did never to believe the media would cover that
Derby stories about the
VC funding Garba voices of concern about putting pants in charge there be a lot of questions being asked about why
Certain things weren't done sooner
In order to inoculate the audience from hearing those questions as reporting
How much is established in advance that this sort of coverage is
Actually proof that the whole thing is a globalist plot to begin with
And the coverage is
Actually the payoff of that plan
They released the virus to synthesize doc Market to a tech Trump and now they get to attack him for not respond
The thing that
Kind of hilarious but Alex is underlying argument is that even his narrative include admission to Trump didn't handle the virus
Situation
Even he's not trying to deny that
He's just loudly yelling and pointing
Sing Somewhere Else
Only didn't respond well because the sea
CDC
Or something
It is weird I find the reality fascinating beds
As Long As Trump is doing an
Awful job
The media will criticize him for it
Which then makes
The white aggrievement conservative narrative
Function it's always an attack on
So that he can either do a really terrible
And the media
Call Somerset president
Or we can do a good job
And get praised
But if he gets praised by the media
Then that a grievance narrative doesn't really work
No
It's almost like the conservative
Propaganda machine is relying on Trump to be a shity president continued their Dairy
The long-standing pigs is talking about how like
Mikey would tell people in the media that if they wanted to destroy my grandpa
What they need to do is endorse him
Rite Aid in order for them to endorse him he'd have to not be a crazy wings
So it is kind of the same
Did you have to be not yourself in order for the media exactly
It's not a good way to to look at
No it's your ax
So we know that Alex is a humorless boob
And a weirdo
Yeah even though the right is getting better at
Who robbed
I've always thought that just because he's not funny
And is a dork
Turns out there's another
I tell you this
So he's about to Brazosport
Dialect
Bragging
Play seen the difference
They're going to do
They call that
Third-dimensional 4th dimensional chess
That's bragging
Not seeing things straight on one-dimensional
Tell me a joke
I just don't even get it
Because I'm in a mode of not
Being in the comedy
Literally
I'm taking in all the data
It's cuz you're not funny
No it's
It's mainly that
Jokes
Sister jobs you could almost say that they're three-dimensional.
So this is all synthetic
The virus situation naturally season dialectic
He's always knows what's going to happen next
Corsica
It's all totally
Concern
Australia
Tunisia the US
The globalist
It's all scripted
Attack
But
But my clock off
Get out of here in Austin
Or dead on folks I keep saying that we're done on
My spirit is not authorized to make out of here that is that is the like o you can verify what I'm saying
But the only guy you could verify with it is dead so unfortunately I just you just got to have to trust me on this one
Can we follow your spirit
Not authorized to release it by my
Spirit
I wonder what that means real people talk to you
I got nothing
So Alex
Realizes the Trump has been put in for the posture of like he's not really
Concerned right right right
About things a guy no big deal gofucker
Go fuc yourself
Alex is rationalization for this ends up being the Trump wants
To create confidence of the stock market is
Protected
And that kind of thing
Answer you rationalizes this
And
Advocates any responsibility
To tell the truth
Why Trump wants to play this town he sees the you and he sees a globalist
PCS I want to take down our economy you know Channel awesome
They launched against her own people lock stuff down and reset
It will show us that you do our economy they believe is fragile
Maybe the president tried to play it down
We shouldn't get caught up in that
Our job is the oracle
Infowars
Real Townsquare the brain
Unfiltered globulus academic giving his answers down off Mountain
Together
Yeah I mean like it
It's really important
When you have people
People calling in to be like don't pop bubbles
Got Chinese are no bubbles
Store
The high-level thing because obelisk
I'm stuck out here I was listening to that and the thing that I noticed
Is just how bad
Right right I just mean from like Google
How'd it go in in the beginning of that clap he had that like
Daughter daughter
Data.
Got it.
Saturday
You know that whole like
Perfect
Where it doesn't even matter what you're saying he's
Talkin musically their cigar
Going to hear that
And then if then at the second half is just like
Like he can't sustain
Well yeah he's cardio's not what it once was.
He's going to need to shave his head
Streamline aerodynamics
So throughout this it
It's been pretty clear that this episode at least Alex is putting forth
The idea that this is all about this
Supply chain
Disruption
And that intersects B2 makes it fairly clear that he
He thinks that maybe this is Eve
Soon as I saw China lockdown whole cities
Knowing it would devastate their economy
I said it was real
You could see the fee
People being builded the hospital for sake
The way they did it the cameras and all of it
What they were exacerbating at the order had gone out if create Global Hysteria
So that's a really interesting angle Alex's take
He's saying that immediately when he saw China lockdown cities he knew it was a fake of that than the global is ordered gone out
To try to create his theory
Please remember the China put Wuhan under lockdown on January 23rd
And for some context
Alex at Mike Adams is a guest to announce that it was over
Humanity on Hulu
Me check my notes
Phir January 24th
So I guess Alex is good buddy Mike Adams just spouted globalist line
You must be getting the globalist talking point that it was time to cause Hysteria
Innkeeper Alex facilitate
And that haven't like on his show every day and letting him guest host
What do you want to see pack
It's tiresome at this point for me to stress that all Alex has been doing this
Who's playing at the hysteria since late January at least
We don't need to believe her that point but there's another big lie here
And that is Alex
Claiming that he immediately knew this was all a charade
If it was real they would cover it up trying to cover it up
This is not true
In the early stages of Alex's coverage he was pitching a whole lot of theories
Like when you were saying
It's possible the trumpet release a bio-weapon on
Back for fentanyl
Or the entire it was stolen from a lab and Winnipeg narrative
But he would later call disinformation
He was all over the place
But his initial reaction was actually that this was a real thing
Unlike the outbreaks
Zika virus and Ebola which were all fake
It is January 24th interview with Mike Adams
This idea was laid out pretty explicitly and you something Alex signed off on and mirror.
In his later cover
One way that I believe that you know that this
She is a real pandemic is because the who
Is trying to downplay it
Whatever the whot
If the opposite of reality
When the bird
Flu virus was a non
They declared it a stage six pack
So the other ones in the past were fake
This one's real
He's not screaming and setting buildings on fire or something
I am sick
Proof being what they don't
Do well course that actually I think towards the end of this will get it clear that actually fully demonstrated
It's why they behaved
Really why Alex
And it almost broke my
Lays out his
Conspiracy
I bet and it's very sweet
I'm not even concerned or scared now because this is so real
She going through the bullies waiting for you you don't want to get in the fight
You're like you know what
McGraw
Email metaphysically no fear or no concern anymore
That tells me
My spiritual radar says this is the big moment shall we better start debating what the President should do
Speculating we know it's a weapon transfer to Obama to China in the future
As a martial law takeover of China to reset the global economy
Mobile crisis for the global solution Western open government
Open is a problem closed societies that run by the UN
What
Is the permutation analysis
At the end of Matt that guy
The guy on Blow
That's a bit much
We're all going to be closed
Nation
Run by the United Nations
Dad
Perfect
About the only thing I really find super interesting is is braggadocious bulshit there at the beginning of that how like I'm not scared
Heard anymore and I'm now my spirit knows this is the big one
Once again I'm a coward that's all I hear him say once again
I'm saying these things so you take me seriously
Yeah it's
It's it's repetitious to a point of
Offensive it reminds me to beware the earliest of March
Sure
What are the odds
So
Is downplaying this virus
Where is right and that's bad
Because the globalist Jose
That
Covering it up
Here
I really know how to setup his Club B convoluted a little bit in the beginning
Send
Alex says something
Deeply f*****-up
Answer for this
To try and understand the clip
But then also so you don't talk over
Accidentally Alex saying something
You should never say
My first
Breakin repeat this every segment is the
Summer
Any angle you look at this virus
Any angle you look at
When you watch China lockdown almost a billion people
You know that's going to kill the bubble top
Godzilla's in a movie
This is Godzilla all over the planet
Is in a Godzilla
Here he just wants to
Play it down and I understand that but see that's the Trap
When he plays it down the media is going to say covered up
Their only fear is he plays it up and uses it for control
Like GG
That's why Bill Maher said I
Declare martial law
Because that's what they want to do when Trump doesn't act
They're afraid Trump Maga rap
Plasma
And by the way
I don't want martial law
With all the bureaucrats
This is the world we Menard's do you want Nancy Pelosi
Martial law
Or do you want
Prompto
Because
The Wheelhouse
So the world that Alex is put in for this like
The situation that we find ourselves is Nancy Pelosi martial law
Aren't you the guy who claims you see-through dichotomy is a dialectic
What are you doing to your audience
You trying to make them
There's no other option than Trump martial law going to get martial law would you rather have Nancy Pelosi
Marshall Marshall
I mean
You know
Before I've been fighting
Non-stop against martial law
Obviously going to happen
There's only one choice
This would be like me
In a couple years on this show talking about a great w Cleon skousen is
I think Ted Anderson should get his gold lights
Ethan's back I think
Rob do is the best corporate representative
This country is ever see the definition
It's just like he's mr. anti martial law guy
Because of this crisis that he believes is a globalist manufactured crisis
We either need to have Trump martial law or
Losi martial law choose option
This is no fighting against both this could not be more like straight out of the girdle pants
Agnes is bad like
But here's the thing
I'm just going to take the worst option and get rid of all other possibilities so my ridiculous
Followers will of course
So Alex has Mike Adams on the show on Sunday and Mike has got a new theory about what this virus
This is really about
No
I have noticed he hasn't hasn't been going that far anymore scale does Great Heights
January 24th
What a bore
He's been a little bit like
I might have really over shot that one
So you have a new Theory and its various
Clearly
The media hype that the EU hype
They have done they're planning something big will this what do you think it is
What is a second
Trap
That they can initiate an all this
First trap was to allow the virus to spread deliberately
And the narrative has already been launched the second
They know that they're going to be quarantines of communities and perhaps cities across
America
Will most likely be liberal cities
You have the most filth the most homelessness
And the highest
Elation density
It will be the Democrat with the last one being
For suspending the election
In November
Democrats will be able to participate
Smart
Suspend the elections
Then
The Democrat
Is able to I mean you might have to have a lot of other
People going along with it
Supreme Court perhaps
But he's able to achieve that
Then the Democrats will say
Oh my gosh
He's a dictator now he's just a clear himself a dictator and they will use that to Launch
The violent revolution
And here is when we learn
Mike is a health Ranger. A political science ranking
If you follow his theory the real trap of the Coronavirus
Verses about making Democratic areas unable to vote which will prompt the Democrats to call for suspending the election
If Trump goes along with it'll be called the
Dictator all the violent leftist to take to the street and enact their violent revolution
Write this is a dumb theory for one major reason and that is absentee ballot
In 33 of the states in the country any registered voter
Request a mail-in ballot without
Even given a reason for their need for an absentee ballot
The other 17 states allow voters who meet certain qualify
Locations to vote remotely which I would assume Coronavirus
We're under quarantine well if you can't make it although that is what Georgia would do
Five states automatically send out ballots to everyone
But if if they prefer they can still go though
On the occasion that the coronavirus situation does escalate the United States there's literally no reason why we shouldn't have the infrastructure
Make sure that we needed to still carry out the elect
It would just require some slight tweak
And some coherent messaging
Participate
Absentee voting
For this reason
Even if Democratic areas are hit harder by an outbreak probably never hear Democrats calling for a suspension of the elect
They would call for sending out at
And given the fact that we're not even through the primaries yet there's every reason to believe that there is enough time to get that done
Should they have the political will
And like I said
The coherent messaging would really be the most
The only way the Democrats would call for
For suspending the election
Birdiebee
I don't think Adam case of you
I'm just making it a hyperbolic
Fair enough
People who would ever call for the suspension of intellect
Can our Trump authoritarian boosters like Alex
This sort of conversation Mike is having served the purpose of preemptively making it the Democrats fault
If Trump has decided to suspend the election do you want Pelosi or Trump
That's what you got it won't be a sign of authoritarianism and dictators leanings coming to the surface
It'll be just
Your response
Do an evil left-wing plot
I just wish the left-wing wouldn't
Make me punch them in the face all the time for standing there you stand there they're planning something
It's not my fault I have to
Punch them in the face
Yeah I'm just standing there
Like I said
Stress this because it is very
Key to understanding
Things are going
I'm trying to stress
A lot of
The talking point
A lot of the things that are brought up
AR
Intrinsically about the
Supply chain disruption
That is the primary narrative
Surrounding Coronavirus
March 1st
And that's why Alex will bring up things like this
Reuters guys
We can
German Auto industry Mike
Have 50% reduction in sales over Wuhan virus
Breakpoint
So this is a minor point but I wanted to call a tent
Demonstrate how little care Alex has represented
Information Act
You just grasping at straws to pull out
Some headlines here at a while back in order to reinforce
Mike Adams who's making
Complaints about the disruption of the global economy the viruses
Alex says there's a story and writers about the virus causing
The German Auto
To drop 50%
In reality this story is about how the virus might cut in half German automobile sales
Specifically in China
During the month of February
The German automobile industry is already in top shape
They've been hit hard by emission standards people transitioning to electric cars
And is caused by us China
Ozark
Tariff
Smart
The conversation that Mike and Alex are having it's about the
Disruption of supply chain
Companies are losing profits cuz they can't get the parts they need to make their Prada
The German car situation is
Completely different thing
It's all about the
Sales in the Asian market
BMW Daimler Volkswagen don't even have any factories in the affected areas of China
This is Adam and disruption not supply
But Alex and Michael care about that distinction
Also Alex is just spouting off s*** about German auto companies dropping 50% when it's a much more precise
Statistically
He doesn't care because it helps serve
The Narrative it's being pushed
That's annoying it is annoyed
I'm very annoyed
Alex
Still pushing the food pretty hard
Okay score still going hard on the food
Because I run out of
Exactly exactly
So you can use that
No I don't think so
I think you said in the past that none of this stuff comes
I don't know I don't know
I would be OD interest
Did you find out
I would bet that my Patriot Supply whether or not they do source
They do not I would imagine so
So they do that for a bit
It's not worth listening to. All the standard s*** chair
I found this really interests
Got the health Ranger on here
Ask how we can win
How can we protect ourselves
From any possible infection
How do we snatch Victory from the jaws of defeat
Outlook America can survive this but it
Requires people turning to
Antiviral molecules that exist right now
And they're only two sources where to get that number one there are some
Prescription
Medications that have antiviral
None of them are yet proven against the Coronavirus
The 2nd
And understand
Switch is a food superfoods herbs even just regular things like garlic and ginger and onions
Conspicuous sanitabs
Nano silver
Alex doesn't even bring it up after Mike's products
He says
When he gets sick
He eats a ton of onion
That's the trick
In the in the past
Couple weeks
The past month or so these sorts of conversations always be accompanied by
A plug for the oil in the gargle nothing is more antiviral than what the Pentagon has
Proven to be antiviral against this very virus
It is very weird it almost seems like somebody might have
Send him a letter
It seems like he might have got to warn it could be I don't know that to be the case and I would be
It's possible to speculate looks like I think he did
He's not he's not selling the gargle like used
Well get it ghetto Baker getting a letter is might as well be a baker getting a very public letter yet
It's definitely putting people on notice
Play Moana lose millions of dollars
Potentially advice
His behavior Whitney
Need to change it would be a smart idea
Out to I don't I don't know exactly their other possibilities but it is behavior is
Noticeably
So Mike
Start complaining about how the youth are lazy
How these Millennials and blood and drinking it yet
LOL that's good
We're lazy right now
The ocean
Does not allow you to do that to your employees
You complaining about how
This new generation
Just sucks they don't work hard
Ignore that
To Alex screaming about his account
I thought that was really funny mad about taxis
Younger Millennials and an even younger people in America today
They do not have a work ethic
There's this laziness it's real it's in the Youth of America today
Factory I buy brand names
Consumers
Producers
And this this is
Really
People then also just seen number that go
Even if CPA they go
Well there's this money in your bank account
That what you didn't change
We got to pay the vendors and I know you're right sorry
Colonic
Epa's man
Itsy bitsy me a man that is behind it all
Is this related
Don't understand
I just thought that was really funny Alex
How dare you my sister-in-law's a CPA you come at me when you come
What's CPA
I was an accountant for a little while but certified
How do I cook beer from the Sunday show
And it's Alex if you wants to scare the audience about the possibility of this quarantine
You coming to the United States
Answer yes to bike
To help
Will this pandemic is going to be the ultimate wake-up call
Global environment over for Humanity
A few minutes here
It is really deadly and everything locked down
The old lawn quarantine what will the average left us do you talk about
A group of psychotic piranhas
I suppose there will be no enforcement liberal city in America
Because the people that you would try to
To isolate
But not comply
Not at all
They will go insane normal day in many cases
I have no idea people in the last to be more or less likely than your average person to go along with a quarantine
Whatever Mike is f****** if he thinks his militia Patriot buddies. Don't tread on me type sore
Any any more likely to accept
The government mandated quarantine
These are people who threaten Insurrection over military training exercises in the landgrave
Fees
Do you think for one second that these same people
Standoff at the Wildlife Preserve
Tell them to stay indoors or whatever you got it
Farcical
Alex's said that like half the police in the country
Killed if background checks for gun
What does Works Bandit
How do you think the Sovereign citizens react
They don't think they need drivers license isn't a few quarts is invalid
They legitimately don't think the state has any Authority so they're not going to acquiesce to a quarantine
So really stupid
You can hear now it's his voice that he's rushing to the end of the show
He wants to scare the audience before he wraps up
I don't know why that's the
Believer
Scary
So we get to the SEC
Monday
Now to show open
Opens up
Very serious
Very
Very soon
Up-to-date
Broadcast I've ever done
You've said there's so many damn times
Do I need to open my car window and start screaming into block traffic
Yeah I need to this going to change the games
So it turns out
All of that stuff about
What I was talking about
At the coronavirus narrative shifting Supply
Throw that out
Get out of here
Fresh Start
Fresh start throwing out the f****** window cuz now we're back
F****** everyone's going to die
So turns out
Turn on a day-to-day basis it turns up
Alex has a couple of
Sources about this
Annie gets into it in this just next
Coming up here today
Bottom of the hour
Multiple experts one of these
Lieutenant colonel
Did Army Special Operations
That back
Who said the Pentagon
Believe
With the numbers they have
That they can have up to 3 million dead people
In the next 6 months here in the United States from the Coronavirus
Spell I learned this
A couple days ago
And then
There was a retired lieutenant
Colonel
And I had to go
Totally separate issue
And I watching the drinking coffee with him
He just retired like
A year ago
The word and he was with army Special Operations just so happened
Yeah the word is from the numbers is there looking at 3 million dead
Oh man you know what is really weird it's really weird at this 3 million dead figure that Alex is pretending that he has
Exactly the same estimate that Mike Adams made on Alex's show on Sunday
Wait oh my God I can't believe this I completely forgot to play you that clip
You mentioned rasulallah bring this up 2% mortality rate
Which is pretty typical for a flu
2% comes out roughly 3.3 million dead
Americans essentially just admitted there could be millions of deaths in America
Larger than the flu
Let's be clear we don't want that to happen it's terrible
So this is an offshoot of repeated
Sunday show referring to Rush Limbaugh is an expert on these
And Rush said on his show that there's a 98% recovery rate there for 2% mortality rate
The two percent fatality rate is an estimated by bike to be about 3 million.
It was really
Really remarkable 2
Show me how Monday Alex has multiple high-level sources telling him
They're preparing for 3 million dead
And yet when he's discussing this very topic on his show on Sunday
Didn't come up it is strange because he heard from the lieutenant colonel's
Write a couple days ago
He knows a lot of lieutenant colonel
Same thing as Mike clear day doesn't seem to know anyway Brigadier generals he doesn't really have much much
Other rankings to go by
There's another
Weird cork here and that is that
That clip of Mike making
Is 2%
And 3 million dead
That
He's talking about
He's responding to clip of Rush Limbaugh commentary
Now
Here is Alec
Explain Rush
Talking about the Coronavirus
On his Sunday show
The coronavirus is
Common cold by media
Type of this thing
Pandemic as The Andromeda Strain as all my God if you get it
I think the the
Survival rate is 98% 98% of people get the Coronavirus
Picture respiratory system virus
It's probably it is probably is a chai, laboratory experiments
That that is in the process of being weaponized
At a secret hearing last week when you cover it they know what it is
So here we see the 2% number being established which Alex and Mike Adams or later used as tomato 3 million
More interesting
Rush says that this virus created a Chinese
Strengthen that
Alex says that there were secret meetings in Congress and Rush knows about
This has the effect of implying that what Russia's saying is actually secret high-level information
Supposed to
Rush Limbaugh doing what you always do
Talk s***
Over the course of
Situation strength
By the next time Alex brings up Russia's comments
He's not very very strongly implying that Rush saying the virus might have been made in a lab in China
Raheem reporting on things
Trump and Pence tool
Everyday I mean
Limos totally hooked up
Media
Bio weapon got other lab it's not big
Fluted even kill wanted the 1% first
Limbaugh's getting it ready
And now let's Jump Ahead to the next time rush comes up on this Sunday show
Alex is talking about how he's been saying the coronavirus is man-made for a long time
You would think you would just brag about a Russian
Picking up
But Alex doesn't
Alex's actively can
Inflating Rush making stupid
Comment on his radio show
With information
It's coming from
It was Man made out of the Wuhan bioweapons lab
Intelligence committee meetings last week that's not Rush Limbaugh
He talked the president daily
Perfect bodies
Alex has absolutely no information about any real or imagined Senate intelligence
He's making that up because he believes for absolutely no reason that Rush was reporting on Senate intelligence
Materials
And stuff that comes from Trump when he was just talkingshit
This is one of the more clear-cut cases I've seen of Alex just blatantly laundering a source
Yeah but it's not
Fully laundered yet
Alex is still mentioning Rush when he's making
Disclaim in that last
This is technically still Justin
Embellishing Russia's s*** talk
However you don't have to look
Look too far to find this claim fully
Completely launder
It is something that is now
Levi's
I'm all set for over a month it's man-made
Major Indian universities other
Scientific
Facilities
Chicken vaccine
Within the span of his two-hour show Alex took a stray piece of b******* that Rush Limbaugh said on his show
Congratulate escalated into being super high-level inside information
It rushes report
Once Alex elevated that s*** talk to that level
He doesn't we rushed getting in the way
A brush is getting this from high-level Pentagon sources
Trump
As the commander-in-chief
And the Senate
Intelligence people
Alex can just cut out the middleman and report on the information that rust Rush
Must be reported
You can see these Fingerprints of the way Alex uses information if you pay attention
And honestly this
Scariest part for me is I don't even think that's a conscious process
I think Alex just started talking about Russia's comment and instinctually wanted to reinforce the parts of it that are most in line with
With his own narrative
Namely that the virus is man-made
So he started tying rush to Trump and secrets
Senate hearings
And as he's going
I have a feeling that he's lost track of where the starting
Point was
There is no secret information there's no Pentagon confirmation
There's nothing except a blowhard right-wing hack that Alex used to hate talkingshit
Add to loop back around Monday
Alex has three million estimate matches up mysteriously while with Mike Adams estimate that he was taken from Rush
I don't believe that Alex has any of these sources
I think this is all him working out
Branching paths
They're all traceback 3/32 clip
From Rush Limbaugh
Yeah I would accept
That this is just
Snowball situation where
Like even if you was taking it directly from Rush
He's just automatically going to say that there's a
Lieutenant V there's just always a lieutenant
He loves that rank so then it just kind of snowballed from there a lieutenant colonel goes to the Pentagon goes to the Presidents or
Right back to rush
There we go
I think it's very
Clear to me
Looking at
Looking at these little fingerprints
Looking at like why didn't you
Bring up any of these the first lieutenant
Colonel when you were talking
Mike
None of this makes sense at all but it does make
Make sense if you see it as
Alex losing
Tracker of his own
Escalating b******* about Rush Limbaugh
And now he's
Chosen to turn it into an
Active life
What was Justice
Conscious
Raising the stakes
On Sunday is now is
He gets in on Monday like
A very conscious
Decision to make up source
Absolutely
So Alex doesn't want to get into business
On the show
Working is deaf
He's just like
F******
Serendipity
Ridiculous things this morning I had to go to the bank
Double
Whataburger cheeseburger is my breakfast I'm going to be bad today
I don't know where there any good job there
Yoshino
Stressed out today
I already called ahead as we pull into the office
Pat Riley's waiting
At the office door with the double cheeseburger
Take
Serendipity
What do you call that
Gross
I'd I got to assume
There's something that the other people would know that I was in a bad mood first of all and then second
That the way to deal with that is giving cheeseburger
Yep both very weird personality keeps a little little baby quiet will give you will give you cheese
Put that in your mouth so you don't yell
These are very strange
Personality quirks
But I would find
Interesting
In like a screenplay but as Alex Jones
Features
In a bad place
Let's give him a GG
Cheeseburger for breakfast it is unfortunate when you're like oh a lot of places they bring in Donuts
And we all get to
The cherem
Here we just get the boss at
Cheeseburger
Appreciate
Eden Prairie
So Alex
Has these sources
And he wants you to know that
She's not waking up
Which makes me think he's making
And the way he
Acura this next clip made me very convinced this isn't true
That's a true story
I just told you
About to
One retired one currently serving
Specific
Sensitive area of the military
Not
I need to tell me this
Telling me this
You need to talk about
So obviously I am
At the bottom of the hour
Right now though
I got to talk about.
The cheeseburger in the belly really important to remember based on how this narrative starts the first
Is that a couple days ago you talked
The first lieutenant colonel
I meant Monday morning you talked to the second
Right
And in that clip
He says explicitly they weren't
To tell him
Rite Aid
Just told him
Those two things
Will be very important later I'm stressing this very hard
So these two
Independently of each other and their commanding officer
They both gave him the same information within a couple days of this Monday
This is this is two depositions this is a slam-dunk eyewitness case we're going to close it out everybody knows
So we get to this next clip and I honestly think that this is one of the points where I'm at
Close to like
Alright Alex FairPoint
Is we're going to
Trump comes out
When the stock market drops 15%
The media's
Asteria is a hoax
The super in the world
Is a hoax which which is true
Economy
I'm not saying I agree with Alex
Bye-bye I'd like to know if
Trump is saying that the media hysteria is a hoax
Where does
Calling it over for Humanity fall on that Spectrum
Trump
As far as Trump
Comment goes this was something that he said at a rally in South Carolina
When talking about the virus
That was on a fake conversation
They tried anything
I tried it over and over
Turning
His language was intentionally kind of unclear because he's an a****** dum dum who lectures
Talk s***
He was forced to clarify would met the next day because the first US citizen
Some died from the virus
Saying that he's not doing a good job by the hopes he's referring to
Quartz so cool
Critiquing his actions of the head of state are engaged
If what they say is not flattering
Could not be clear what point we're at as a site
Frustrated by the fact that it does seem like everybody in America has just decided to like
Skip over shut the Trump says
Like I'd like we just
You just like Zonk out whenever you said she'd cuz of any president said this out loud
The rest like we we'd all be like this is f****** insane
This is absolutely crazy obviously Biden's going to be doing this next year
Part that I sent like introducing clip I said it's close to being like a fair point to Alex
And that's because
There are bunch of people who took this comment that Trump made
And said that he was saying a virus it's a
Self was a hoax
And I think those people are doing terrible job
Like Joe Biden said quote the president of the United States says it's a hoax
It's hard to believe even for him it's hard to believe
Bloomberg said I find it incomprehensible that the president would do something as a name is calling it a hoax
Virginia governor Terry McAuliffe said the Trump quote said the coronavirus was a hoax
Politico's headline reads
Trump rallies his base
You Coronavirus
Which is really on the
Cusp of being off base
The article makes
Contacts
This day era
Do not be making
It's super appealing
Fun to jump on everything Trump says and dunk
If you act like this
He just creates ammunition
People like Alex to further insulate their size and kind of outside information
Yeah it would be hard to
Pace to the media with fake news if they weren't soci
But there are
Destructive
Absolutely and for people who are running
For president on the Democratic side to
Not be more precise with their language
I'm not saying it's the worst thing
That Alex is making
I can't really refuse if people did say
Vicki said the virus itself wasn't Rex
And that's a problem
On the other hand you know
It wouldn't be so believable if it weren't something that
You would
You could have said like Billy easily rehab
He's not paying attention
Attention to what he says ever so he might have
One word change any problems you know he would have
Nuggets
Yeah
Because Alex has
These things that he can point
As
Like examples
Right
Use that
To make other criticism
Media that are absurd
Making it
Between 0
Coronavirus
It's the end of the world
Mainstream Media Shack
This is cockamamie bulshit
Yep the media is not split into thing where you to believe that is a hoax or you think it's the end of the world
I want to just make that up
Because it works into his dum-dum Universal beware the globalist rank rate
Two opposing sides and control both
The dialectic that Alec mysteriously sees everything at
Alex sees the world like
The economy even work doesn't exist
Also it's good to know the people who say it is the end of the world
Considered mainstream media
Did not know that Mike Adams
What was the mainstream media but you learn something new everyday is a globalist
Mainstream media confirm now that Mike Adams is a globally
I think so every time he is on Alex's show
Perform
A globulin
You are everything
You have come to her
There is definitely Alex's fake sources saying that 3 million Americans are going to be dead
From this their projection
Camping this backup it is now like really deadly where is on Sunday it was so much about the supply chain
But
He is also still retaining
A lot of vets
Supply chain
Economy fear
So he gets into that and it's both and neither and everything all at the same
It's very convoluted
So now he has an argument that he's making that is that the Democrats admit that they want the economy
To fail in order for Trump to go out of course we
And I talked about
The globalist are Unified
Are making their move on the economy
To bring down Trump
And now the Democrats last week were admitting it
I hope this brings down from
And they're rooting for to bring down the economy that should bring them down
Interesting cuz I don't know if I've heard Democrats in office or major political commentators hoping for the economy to fail be
Because it would hurt Trump
How explain that CNN clip on Sunday but that's just analysis
Can use transfer
Response to the virus to their political advantage
Wasn't cheering
For the economy to stay or anyting
If you just heard Alex's show on Monday
Say the Democrats have admitted they want the economy to collapse because it'll take down
Trump and you'd assume he's talking about
Some pretty major figures maybe something he played
Previously the Mist
Because I listened to his show way more than anyone should I can tell you exactly who the Democrats are that Alex is referring to
It's one person
It's Bill Maher
Great here's a question not a Democrat by the way
Are you on my list you also on MSNBC CNN on this is great will finally getting
Play son of a
Bill Maher when he talks
Text Satan
Results it on lap
Little
What are those things been
This may come as a surprise to you but Alex never does play any other clips of Democrats salivating and cheering for the
Steak-Out
Because they're always lame is that Sienna
Bill Maher clip
Definitely Maura saying he wants a recession
Because it'll get rid of trump
Fairplay to Alex for not liking that
It's probably dishonest to call Mara Democrat
Carrying the past
Anybody for Bob Dole in 1996 and Nader in 2000
Also billboard also Bill Maher sucks
Stanley critique from the left for very valid reasons
It is it is funny
It's like that's how it
Internal consistency makes you immune to
Certain attacks because I like you criticize somebody and I like
Fire him into the sun to don't care
I've noticed a bit of a
Trend on Alex's show a claim that the whole liberal media saying something outrageous
The only evidence will end up resenting is a clip of Bill Maher talkingshit
How to use Bill Maher to be the Avatar the entirety of the media he's up again
I think the reason is you know because
Alex's show
F****** stupid if you just screaming bloody murder about what Bill Maher said on a
HBO
It makes Alex look like he's actually doing something if he pretends that Bill Maher really speak
For all the Democrats and all the globalist
And that's exactly why you see him expressing at the end of that
At what he does
Doumar's the ventriloquist doll for the global
Enough whenever Belmar says anyting
Alex is free to claim that the globalist and Democrats
Actually the one sing
Bill Barr may as well be the official corporate
Spokesman for globalist LLC
This is the same behavior we saw earlier earlier with Alex laundering source
He'll be totally fine for him to just yell his thick neck off about something Bill Barr said and how it
But how it made him angry
Dubious
Where becomes fundamentally dishonest is when he takes
Belmar himself has said
And that applies them to some other nebula Center
50 in response to the comments as if that other entity
Like the Democrats are the globalist
That actually said it
By assuming that Bill Maher speaks for the globalist
I meant to taking Bill Maher out of the equation stating the globalists
Save this thing that Bill Maher said
You're being a dick
Ultimately Alex has multiple high-level sources are predict 3 billion dead from
The coronavirus in the Pentagon said was in reality just heard a little bit of Russia's show the other day
The Democratic countries economy to collapse in order her truck but in reality I was just mad at
It shows very stupid when you pay attention
And you're able to trace these things to wear their actual profit
Bill Maher's a Democrat the way Bloomberg
F*** off
Fair enough
Navigate to little bit more from those does a lieutenant colonel's that Alex that has it is source
And all of it
All of the information
Dresser
No it's just the same thing
Okay Mike working off the
Maryland lighthouse
Once a year or something
Other business that I was doing it taken care of this about a year ago
He's there at leaving work
He's not having coffee with my wife
He called because I don't travel anymore he's saying
The Pentagon
With a 2% death rate
Has higher levels
Are saying in Army Special Operations
Isn't that weird
Hoverboard details Alex gets about this mysterious Lieutenant Colonel told him to prediction is 3 billion
Morrie talks about it the more it's exactly the same s*** that Mike Adams are saying on the show the day before
So weird
So f****** strange that coincidence
I was certain that this is just Alex laundry Mike Adams a ship through fake anonymous source
But now with the projection
Half the population
She is going to be infected which is exactly what Mike said
Chemical levels of transparent
There are two types of Lies
Their subconscious lies
That Alex doesn't even really realize he's engaging in
Which of the escalation of the rush clip turning into some kind of Secret Pentagon
Then there's this
Which is an obvious and
Channel I
I suspect the motive is
The same as for the bill bars
Alex know that I'm saying Mike Adams predicted 3 million. Soon I'm going to move the needle too much
Mike declared Humanity over like a month ago million death is not an escalation of that rhetoric at all in fact
Bike
That is reassuring
It's really going to happen is like to do
But is Alex presents this is information coming from a mysterious unknown figure was in the know
You can give it a credibility that he
Even he knows Mike Adams doesn't have
Mostly because he's
Humanity
And because Betty Bowl liqueur thing and pretty much the rest of my cat
These are clear Fingerprints of Ally
And I can't stress this enough Alex knows exactly what he's doing
That is
Unbelievable
Why would you even bother with both
An active and retired
Lieutenant colonel
That's so silly and made-up
Surely it's childish it's a childish
One of them was a couple days ago
And in the middle of them with my cat
Sure
So
I think this is really interesting I've noticed something in the past very reason
Alex has started to play the good guy
From Star Wars really real now into our number 245 days left of the
Election
He's also he's still playing The Imperial March sometime right but there is
A seating
Alright alright from Star Wars
He is with me
100% no baby there's no other way that you would do that seems weird and maybe there's a decent chance that maybe
Be at other times in the past he's thrown in the good guy be possible
It's overwhelmed it's stuck out alright if you are listening
Play the theme for Indiana
So Alex now
Okay what are the big things
The media at the mainstream media
One of them's a covered about Alex in the past week was that
He got to go to fight with
And here is where that begin
Ken's it turns out it's
Because of petty reasons
They ran into
Gorka
Tyranny the whale
Or just Gorka the gay well
Whoa
They just like a royal. He's a
The White House policy expert
He's got stolen valor
And
Or I am God I am
Gorka
It's all day but
You don't see Nigel farage coming over here and telling us
Turn on
Free speech
Really nailed the landing on this side
So here's our the feud with Gorka begins
Because I guess he had Owen
Thrown out of CPAP
I don't know if and I don't care if that happened
If it did it's an instance of a guy I dislike taking appropriate measures to
Lisa space
Which is fine
Owen had no reason to be at Sea back except
Disruption
Which has been known to lie about
Weirdly haven't heard much about that Bernie supporter attacking him recently
I thought they pressed charges because it was so obvious that the Bernie supporter at
Might actually be talking about it and I'm unaware of it is not to be
Central feature of Alex
It's weird for Alex to call Gorka of Britt
I mean he was born in the UK
But I think
Like most people more closely associated with hunger
Something's Hungarian
You live there
There was an advisor to Viktor Orban
Identifies with the Hungarian not the order of the test okay and supported
Beeper military Hungarian guard
Sounds like a brick
Because their activity was deemed to be quote
Based on racial conflict
Between the Hungarian majority and minority that's why brexit happened
Their fellow come
I think at least in terms of the present-day Sebastian Gorka is far more notable as a Hungarian than as a break even though he does
Citizenship
I would even go so far as to say he's far more notable just as a Nazi
BND
Got ya
Anyway Alex also called Gorka a gay whale I don't understand
I don't know
I've heard of use that it's on the past I'm sure the backstory is disappointing but I'm not
Sure exactly what it is later on he does
Explain that you just think sikorka sashays around
I don't know it's
Schoolyard homophobia
Ever since Trump came around with low energy Jeb been Little Marco
Husband tried to make playground insults stick to his enemy
He's just not very good at it
I suspect this
Just one of those
Alex goes on a jump into another topic
He spends a good bit of time on this March 2nd episode talking about Turkish president erdogan
Announcing that he would allow refugees and migrants
Cross the border
From Turkey
Europe
I would cover this but the
This situation is immensely complicated and I do not trust myself to handle it well
I wanted to mention it though just because it's
Huge International situation
It's something that should be paid attention to but I can talk about it too much
Mostly because Alex is only real analysis of it is that Muslims are basically animals
People in Greece should be able to shoot them
The Border
It's horrible stuff
Standard
Just with everyone's actions being protect for him to his normal anti-islam
Here's a little clip of Alex and his European reporter damn alignment
Just to give you a little bit of a
Clear the PS4
People don't know you live there
I mean most of the cities are now logos don't help it
Yes even some of the cities that you would never
They're starting to turn that way so I mean recommend if you come to
The really safe countries I always say this go to Poland go to Hungry they don't have any coronavirus either
Hungary the same country
As you
And is treated as
The promise
Especially
I'm not mistaken so that's that's cool
World population review compiles crime rates by countries for the World by simply divided by the total
Relation
Switzerland Estonia Austria Croatia Denmark Czech Republic Romanian the Netherlands all have crime rates
This measure than Poland
Germany is lower than hungry and I was Gales about Germany letting in immigrants all the time
It's clearly a secondary message
Should you being sad by Wyman's country wreck
Patience
It's just that Poland is the Arctic
Type of white nationalists
Yeah
Public Enemy of George Soros
So this
Section of The Fringe right-wing of adopted him as kind of a hero
I wish there was deeper analysis
Commence earbud
It's really kind of just
Yeah if I understand
Whatever edit gotten it's a massively complicated
It's a situation
A large
Part of it is basically Urdu on threatening
Government leaders
Stat
Eagle make
You're racist mad at you
Like that's a certain to a certain extent he's like I'm going to let immigrants into your country and then you're racist
They're going to be mad if you don't want that I think there is a reading
Situation that falls
Way more complicated than that but that is a big
If I would engage with it more probably
If Alex had more
To do then just be
You know like Islam's
Trying to make him bow and he's not going to
Any kind of losses
Thought in the middle which is
Always kind of fun
I don't want to go to their countries and blow them up
No you
There's a lot of things I can say about the high-quality storable food we sell them for
Commercial
Really fumbling
The ball at the end not good
He's not he's not closing
Not really
So you know with this idea that there's a lot of Muslims that are going to be coming into Europe
Alex gets really
Thinking about the
Crusades
She starts talking about her first of all
Christmas had to do
Ludacris Act
Had to lead the attack with the with the Normans in the French
Fandango
For 5000 3000 miles in in
Millions died books
Holding her up
Million
Millions
Do you know that Wars back then we're almost no men
Has the Muslims enslave kill the men
Bleed with the European women and soldiers
Western Europe
We've talked in the past about how off-base Alex's
The Crusades I don't want to really rehash a lot of that stuff in detail but I wanted to take a moment to talk about the claim me as their about Millions.
Dying and singles Crusades
Million
It's
Not estimated that Millions died in individual
There's no real historical consensus for the death toll
Generally speaking the accepted range Hmong Scholars is somewhere between one and three million for the entire span of the Crusades
I should remind you lasted from 1095
To 1291
That's 109
96 years
Something that happened over such a long period of time so long ago and
Such a wide area
Most serious Scholars don't even think it's worthwhile to try and nail down
Precise number
You're just being pause
With that being said there's no way out his numbers are even close to Accurate leaving aside the fact
53 million figure
Includes combating
Both sides
Not just Alex
It's beloved
Crusaders
But let's take that high-end estimated 3 million deaths from
The Crusades
Compared to other world
Then see how it Stacks up
If you look at the list of the most deadly Wars in human history you'll notice that most of them involve
China in the long-distance
25 million died in the Manchu Conquest
Between 1618 and 1683
Which led to the rise of the key machine Diner
Deeper in the past the Three Kingdoms
Conflict between 182 and 2
Left over 37 Million Dead
In China
JoJo fanboy
By the way
In the in the world
I like playing Dynasty Warriors
These were both Ariel King guys that would balupu guy
Both internal matters and didn't involve light
People's Alex into cancer
About those
So but also for comparison like maybe we should look at how many deaths were caused by the European colonization of the American con
None
A recent study from the University College London
Death toll of approximately 50
6 million people which was just a gigantic
That in the world it was so big actually did it caused a little icing
No because about 90% of the indigenous
This population
Was killed either by conflict or disease
This left quote
Vast
Attractive agricultural land being left unattended
Which quote sucked up enough carbon dioxide from the atmosphere
To actually cool the planet
The average temperature dropping by 15
Degreaser
Anyway my larger Point here is not that Europeans are so much worse
The Muslims or anything like that
I don't think that's a productive way to
My point is that history is full of atrocity
There's plenty to go round
And it's not good to imagine the people today are exactly the same as people you've decided are there historical analog
Is into the pasture be
Grappled with
Victims
Respected unless
Some should be learned
Selective finger-pointing but various things that happened like 800 years ago is not a path forward
And that seems to be with Alex
Too stuck in the thing that I immediately took away
That was
This is the beginning of your sentence
They had to March
Three 4,000 miles to protect their borders
And it's like
That's the thought process that is why we have
So many f*****
Warriors and
You is a up
Thereafter March
Three or four thousand miles
To protect the borders
Three or four thousand miles away from where they are
That does not
That's insane
That's a very minor
Piece of what's wrong about a lot of this absolutely immediacy of
Shut the fuk up
You're done
So we're selling food
We have you actually get
Checkbox taken care of
All the other products
Infowarsstore.com
We Dropship
Colorado other areas
Cross the country
Images of super silver wound gel
The strongest over-the-counter you can get
What is the Super Silver
Toothpaste that
Taking effect
Your mouth
Knoxville viruses and bacteria
It's it's close it's
Closeout
But it's Vader
Alex is dancing around it a little bit those viruses and bacteria
Well it's a nonspecific
Yep and it's also a kind of thing as opposed to where it be such a direct Focus
My God helps with
The food is now five to eight weeks
She's Elizabeth Escalade
Now another thing that's interesting is that Alex has to make a real serious point
Of our other product
Realize that I
I think some of his listeners think everything is
Write that backorder
I'm getting I'm getting
I'm stuck in a in a
Tulip situation where maybe my entire economy shouldn't be built around 1
Maybe maybe the food
Is
Is not going
To be a big seller after
A while so
So Alex take some calls
And I might have honestly
Ignore
Some of the
The stuff like the Crusades
Sure
Eccentric kind of inform
Who's the mindset that these callers
Appear to be at
Here is a guy
Sing something really f***** up
President Trump needs to do he needs to act like
Charles
The hammer
Martell
From France
And just went up whenever the Muslims Justin later
He said no you're not coming into Europe and went and Deuce
And just brought
And actually ordered his troops
Take no prisoners these people
Idiot
Wipe them out
It's all good well for this collared say to Trump
Should be like Charles Martel and repel an invasion
Maybe if you're lucky
Some ancient example of someone
Prince of the Franks
It's from 7
6:42 41 and reputation
Anybody good military leader with Wars against the Arabs
As well as the sax
This is not why
The color is red
History there's been some disagreement among historians
It's about a particular victory in Bartell's career
That is his defeat of an Arab Army advancing on tour
In 730
One side argues that it was martel's victory that saved the Western World from Muslim rule
The other side points out that the earliest account of the battle which was commissioned by martel's Uncle
Clearly lays out that this Arab Army has been enlisted by a Christian Duke named do you do of
AquaTech
To help win back some of that had been taken by Martell
Is a Spanish land that was taken by Martell and he had a partial why would they be mad at me
Why would
They're making me there's no indication from contemporary sources at that
Time that this was a battle between Islam and christened
That's something it was fabricated later
The Narrative begin a book called Decline and fall of the Roman Empire by Edward Gibbon released in 1776
In the book of giving argues that the Roman Empire fell due to embracing Christian
Which is not a position
That most historians
Leaving that Central thesis aside his book also serves as the jumping-off point for the retelling of the Battle of Tours
It is casting of Martell is a verb
Leader who stopped Islam
From overtaking the Western world
This was not a case of given reflect
Eating actual history
It was him using a historical event to craft a narrative
And it's a narrative
It's been widely attractive to ascertain
Subset of
The population
Today
In 2001 a multi-millionaire fascist heir to the regnery publishing
Fortune Williams
Saturday Charles Martel Society
This is a white nationalist outlet that runs
At the very races
Justin anti-semitic Occidental Observer
And was responsible for the founding of the national policy
Who's President is Richard Spencer
Through these Outlets are other Ventures regnery funds
With grants
A message of white nationalism and brutal
Do Muslim rhetoric has been spread quite effectively
He's far from the only spoke in that wheel but William regnery junior is a
The massive source of funding behind some of the early sources
Of what has
Become the alt right
In this modern cycle
This isn't just some kind of intellectual publishing
Though
You're like a we talk about ideas
This is real world,
I've received Argy Christchurch shooting
Where the killer had written the name Charles Martel on the barrel of the gun
Use the burger 51 innocent people
Is Twisted historical narrative about Martell began with given in 1917
Fascist
Using this narrative
Pantheon
That's why this caller know Sir Charles
Martellus
Not because he's a scholar of Frankish Dukes
Because he knows about him from
Christchurch shooter
Church shooter
Was reading about him
I was really trying not to
Stereotype
Cuz listening to The Voice
You're like
Okay I've heard I've heard
I get that
You know I'm not trying to be
That guy but when he drops
Martell in there as well
Something suspicious is going on here. Alright fascist anti-muslim
Blogs
Because of this
Distorted Narrative of this battle for
From 17 to 7:32
White Nationals have so many little coated things that
Yeah that you would
Dismiss immediately if you weren't in there
Next caller gives another one
He was Austrian Hungarian Empire royalty
Royals by Europe
When you hear somebody vocal the color keyplan you know absolutely without a doubt that person
Talking to is a white man
The clergy plan is a classic
White nationalist conspiracy theory deposit
It's that austro-hungarian intellectual Richard
Vaughn
Off-color Gates
Harry's secret plan
To replace the white people in Europe with non Europe non-white immigrants
And that the EU is a final expression
Basically as the theory goes these immigrants would have no intern
Relationship to the countries they were living at and thought they would be less likely to fight back
The formation of a One World Government
Usurp individual Khan
To support this Theory proponents 10 to pick
Can choose various things
Crafter white genocide
For instance you believe that the future will be of
This was a belief that he had based on the sense that prejudice will decrease over
Overtime of the people of different races will ultimately
In the future
This is not him saying that he wants
Does intermarry or that there's anything to fairies
Behind his beliefs at all
It sincerely just a sentiment that could only really be seen as scandalous
If you are a person who supposed to races intermarry
Like I don't know
Nick Fuentes
Miscegenation
The rub comes because clergy was also a big proponent of a United Europe
As he advanced in his work
Is it work
Tanjiro
It's probably important to recognize that this text was written and published between World War 1 and World War
So some of the utopian idealism
Some of a peaceful United Europe
Director
Response the horror
Of the first World War
The brief version of this
Conspiracy theories basically just white nationalist
Combining corgis
C4 United Europe with his belief
The future of man
It is a being mixed race
There are these are combined
To argue that he wanted to unite Europe in order
To bring in tons of non-white people who
Create this desire teachers
Are there be no more white people
Also proposing
This conspiracy believe clergy was doing
Behalf of the Jews
We got bingo
It is amazing
To me how bad the
The plans of the
Masterminds are
And their worldview it's almost like
They're the dumb
Making up the plan
Much like evoking Charles Martel this caller bring up the kalergi plan is a
Extreme
White nationalist being on the
That's what this is
These are subtle signifiers that people listening B
But indicate that the conversation that's being had he's not about current events
It's about a conspiracy theory that says Jews are trying to force
Integration on wifey
And it seems like Alex
Not only
Familiar with it
He is into it
So
You can see where Alex's heads
Can remember we
So long ago when we were like oh I'm not sure if I want to call him and out now waiting eyes
Yeah those were
You live and you learn
So Alex has complained about the the whale
Earlier in this episode
And that was
To set up
Towards the end of the Epic
You would have Harrison Smith come in
To talk about their experience being kicked out of Sea-Tac by Barca
We'll get to that in a second but before we do
Chose
He
The brilliant
It's political my okay
You makes a prediction
About the Democratic primaries at age well
Bloomberg hasn't dropped out of
Bloomberg
It is is the FrontRunner to me he's got
Got the money
He's not
Not going to go away
He's got the will
Anyone else has the wheel
Smash cut to Bloomberg.
Fairies
No matter what was it the next day
So
Apparently
Nancy pack
According to Alex
Workforce
Go out to break the short
CLEP I'm compilation replay of who we learned where everybody bags
Police dog
Remove them remove them
You think about a villain
Gorka the Titan
Workout the tighten up hearing
So the entire story is a Gorka came up
To the Infowars people were filming at CPAC and said they shouldn't be there since their loot
Conspiracy
Maybe you got them thrown out I have no idea but at least
Displays I don't I don't know if it's
Shows that
Anyway this spirals out of control it to Alex being convinced
Gorka was the neocon watchdog
Roaming the Halls throwing out anyone who dares the Neil
Anise cloves
Included three members of Trumps family SP
This is just Alex being Alex
He knows Gorka has a huge radio show that's indicated on Salem
Media in his own way way more stations in Alex
Courtesan who actually did work in the Trump
Administration
It is directly connected to power as opposed
Alex who just constantly shunned and kept
Far past an arm's distance
Just like Alex tried to bait Joe Rogan
Giving him Free Press by calling him
Sneaky Snake
And trying to start a one-sided Feud with him
Same thing with Gorka
Alex knows that if corkatoo
Takes the bait and star
Search respond to Alex on his own show
SS2
This stuff is just pathetically transparent and if you pay attention Alex doesn't
Seemed to start foods with people he doesn't have a possibility of getting
Free Press
Joe Rogan Sebastian Gorka Brian stelter
These are all people have platforms you can hope
This is one of his big strategies and I would tell him to ignore this
Does.
Top doesn't matter
I mean in this
Circumstance you giant troll don't
Yeah yeah
So Alex
Gorka wanted
To kick Infowars out because
Cuz they sell supplement
As opposed to them being crazy lunatic
Yeah you shouldn't be here
Did you sell supplements Gorka
TV
What that bad
Tell
Really supplements
You're making us Wayne
So I went and check gorkas website for his show America first
And the first thing that jumped out at me was the fact that he has ads for my pillow
On his site
Genesis Communications Networks
All right sounds like snake oil pillows
The man died on his site for supplements is for a company called balance of nature
This company legitimately just sells dietary
Like they have a product called fruit
Here's the product ingredient list for fruits
Apples
Aloe vera apple banana blueberry
Cherry cranberry grape grapefruit
Lemon mango
Pia
Pineapple raspberry strawberry
Tomato
Sounds like snake oil fruit in a blender
And then turn it into a gummy
There's another one called fiber and spices but honestly
Unless they're lying on their ingredient list
This is all just natural things ground up into a pill form
Another making health
Except the Fiber One
Which says it helps
I think is not an irresponsible thing
To suggest for a fiber pill
Yeah I think everybody knows
Is it fiber helps
Yeah
Alex's specifically referring here to another ad the Gorka has on his site I think the balance of nature is the one that he's like
It's pretty good that sounds that sounds
Kind of situation
So this other one
Is an ad to gorkha has for product
Which they claim can quote
Help your body reduce pain associated with aging exercise and everyday living
This is mostly attributed to the antioxidant anti-inflammatory properties of its ingredients which are ikran
Turmeric
Resveratrol
I decided to check out to Infowars store
And see if Alex old the same thing
And how he sold them
One thing that surprised me is that I knew that Alex oldest up
I called Icarus
But I went to look at it
The product doesn't care
It's spelled
Pickering is spelled icariin in Alex's product is
Misspelled icure
It's very weird
Okay it seems like people think of this product
Which is also sold in gas station bathrooms
I love it
I have no idea what Alex her name is product something so close
Do something that is the name before really well-known supplement
Confuse people but I have no idea product yesterday.
I don't know that's frustrated I assume there's something
Is it did you look up whether or not that was a
I think what
No not the the the one out that Alex
No it's just a name
It just an old the name is okay
I thought there was
Ed completely different herb name decorate.
Okay Alex's Bean turmeric product is body
And the write-up for body is it says the product
Contains things that are quote known for their
Anti-inflammatory properties to work synergistically with turmeric
Full body support
The write-up says it will help boost
Support your flexibility Mobility joint function even more
Honestly sounds pretty similar to the relief Factor marketing
Yeah that's
That's such the
That's a porta-potty copywriter who's like
What okay give me some specs on what this product does
F****** nothing
Alright I'll put synergistically in there and will nail it
DNA Forest
Contains Resveratrol support heart function cellular energy production
System boosting Mental Health
Promote energy production and more
They say the product can help
Fight against things
Causing cellular damage
Which could be painful so this again seems right in the ballpark
We know that Alex sells omega-3 Altima
Fish oil and weed
Because it gives Alex
The burpees
If you read the copy for Alta
Fish oil this line jumps out at you
Studies have suggested that fish oil and fish oil supplement Tatian can slightly lower blood pressure
Increase triglyceride levels decrease the growth rate of plaque
And provide a soothing reduction and inflammatory responses and joints
Reducing inflammatory responses in joint is the same thing as reducing joint pain
This is all pretty close
What you're getting close to
Snake-oil with a Gorka
But you know what would really suck for Alex
Really suck if I had a clip
From him from last Wednesday or tries to sell bodies
Is product by saying that some people think it's better than Advil for pain
Work as a snake oil salesman for selling things for pain relief
It's a good thing you don't have that clip
I have only I did
We have the ultimate turmeric formula bodies 95% of humanoid
That's amazing for immune system your whole body people
Pain see what that's for you personally
30% off go f*** yourself Gorka okay getting into snake-oil territory when you sell things for pain relief
The pot is screaming across the world to the kettle
Alex is really just trying to take swings at Gorka even when
Ends up hitting himself but his audience doesn't
Even though Gorka was in the Trump Administration
And it's been in that orbit
For a while
He's not a trump guy
You never Trump
Who broke through the criticism the attacks the black ball
What the Democrats
Cheap Alex Jones in the populist movement
Let them take the party completely over
The police dogs
In there hovering around literally spouting and pontificating an arrogant wedding
Gorka became a naturalized US citizen in 2012 so unless Alex
Naturalized citizens are really America
What are you just at the light
I think he thinks
I think I would go along with you
So we end this March 2nd episode with
UPS de resistance
Which of course is Alex
Threatening
And challenging Gorka to fight and of course
Everyone knew it was going to happen no matter what yeah we're going to
Do it for charity or whatever it is in the ring with five rounds
Enjoy that and that's always fun to your Alex want to fight somebody
No thing that I think is most notable about this is why
Shroyer's response
Everyone hates you now
Will you pose with guns
Everybody knows you don't know what she and the bullet comes out of
The Habit in Vegas I will get in that ring and I will be
Beat his brains out
To sign the form you big
I might go you got your cardiovascular do you want to challenge him
Charity boxing match because he's so big and powerful he wants to get in the ring
Oops
What is Gorka think about
Maybe I'm getting
Like really twisted on my perception about Owen Shroyer he seems to be acting more like an adult
He does I don't know what happened
Something's Happened
Has a confidence about him maybe wasn't there before
If you watch the video this cuz I had to go back and check cuz it sounded like it was an addict
After he says
It sounded like they cut out something
If you watch this you can see Owen kind of like rolling his eyes even a little bit
There is a feeling of elevation above
Alex's b*******
Yeah it's like when a twelve-year-old has to raise himself
As the parents are like
Very absent of the 12 year old
I guess I'm the adult I'm 13 but I guess I have to be an adult now
I don't know I'm it's very possible I'm reading way too much into it but Ellen's response they're impressed
Miata certain level up
Let's get lit
Focus let's get back in
Came to this as opposed to being like
Yeah it does
He seems to be making the choices that are
What are more adult
It used to be that Alex was like that
That playground bully and Owen was that Lackey where the bullied be like hey
You you go fighting
You go fight his own would be like
Is Owens identity was wrapped up in being the Destroyer
Exactly baby it's a situation where he went and yelled at Jerry Nadler interrupted the impeachment thing
And had to go do a hard bid of a couple minutes
Maybe that woke him up
Maybe then
Maybe he wrote a letter
He's got a
Maybe that woke
To be like possibilities of
Yeah something I don't know what it is
I'm interested to see where it goes
Daddy's been drunk too many times
Could be
But in the power rankings if I were making them now I think I am almost ready to adjust it
Like Paul Joseph Watson
Down the chart
Clearly in the num
Yeah yeah
He's taking over
Stone has started the war room power
He's ascendant
So we get to
And Alex
Is
No
Announcing
My kids coronavirus narrative is just completely
It ends so it
This is specifically tailored to rip
The argument
Did Trump has not done
And he's poorly prepared
President Trump about four and a half weeks ago
Pentagon and FEMA to emergency
Emergency
How to Coronavirus
That point and the Democrats taking the bait in saying that
You do not have any response
Launch to it
Measured response
Issa Vegas
About it
Tricom in the media
I have literally no idea what Alex is talking
Doesn't cite any sources on their ass and I don't believe is Pentagon ship based on a very strong
But now here Alex is reporting on his show the Trump secretly instituted a National Emergency over a
Month ago
As always he secretly instituted the thing that we needed just cuz we didn't hear about it doesn't mean he didn't
Do it this is super weird because on March 3rd Voice of America reported on Trump discussing the potential
National Emergency
I don't think you'll need that
Because I really
Think we're in extremely good shape we're prepared for anything
We can always do that at a later date if we need it
Definitely
Hasn't declared a national emergency
50 publicly or secretly Alex is making this s*** up
He's just working off of headline in the hill
FEMA preparing for Trump emergency
Declaration on Coronavirus
Report
This article is about how and tell the president declares a national emergency
FEMA is not allowed to
To do things like
Quote creating disaster
Medical assistance team
Mobile hospitals in military transport
There's a separate budget for FEMA they have for disaster situations
It's a full 34 billion dollars right now
And they're not they're literally not allowed to use it
Unless Trump declares an
National Emergency
These things aren't happy
Such as FEMA setting up mobile hospitals and cracking into that 34 Billy
So there's a strong indication that no secret emergency declaration
But Oz read that headline
Not the article
So he's using to Hadley
Great
Good work as a public health emergency
That was declared by Health and Human
Services secretary Alex Azar back on January 31st
This was primarily to quote give state
Tribal and local health
It's more flexibility to request
Fhhs authorized them to temporarily reassigned state
Local and tribal purse
Personnel to respond to 2019-novel coronavirus if their salaries normally or funded
In whole or in part by Public Health Service Act program
That's almost certainly with Alex's conflating with this hill ahead
You scammed
And now you turned that into a narrative the Trump secretly declared an emergency
Be back at the end of June
And he's got this whole thing under control
Houses not with you
Call Aditi
So now it's really important
Recognize that
This is now
A month ago
Because that'll come into
I know I'm asking you to
Keep in mind a number various things in a timeline there is a lot going on
Because it'll all come together
Okay
So Alex brings back up his fake lieutenant colonel
Apparently this specific again
A tired
They believe they believe how much
Play CDC Belize
That about half the public will get
The virus be exposed to it
Want to have 2%
Butt cheek
Specific well what percentage of America is what you call
So I guess it's very specific again
I thought Alex a drop that narrative
Now
3 million
Okay
I don't know what you say in response to this I would ask him to explain the 3800 or so cases
Is an Italy are those all Chinese Italian
I would ask about the 4700 or so cases in Iraq
But I'm sure he just make some weird race science argument about first and Chinese G there than similar
There's no there's no reason
This virus is racist
An expression of his
There's nothing
So Alex
It clearly is using this hill article
That is about how
FEMA has
Funding
But they can't use until there's an emergency
Declaration
Trump is already secretly done
Now
You didn't do anything with it you secretly
He hasn't done that
Okay because these things
Well you would say that
You see what you need to understand is it
It's what people don't do tells you what they are
Pentagon
The White House
They've declared a secret emergency the federal government
Agencies that would need to be deal with that
FEMA preparing for possible coronavirus emergency declaration no
It's already in place
Anyway
Mike Adams comes back in
Hooray
So I know from listen
The best that this entire narrative about these lieutenant colonel
Is just laundering
Stuff that Mike
I don't know bike is on and they discussed these fakes
It's adorable Rosecrans crazy
The song your show yesterday you
Person
Who told you they are preparing for the pasta
Millions decimal
Lieutenant colonel
Again over the weekend
Yeah couple days ago
And they're like no
Alright
Uggs the viruses real
We don't want to panic. But
We need people that obviously know this is real
Cuz I kind of want the hardcore
Patriots
Telephone
Operation
House with some business we were conducting
Mostly with that you were eating
Yeah right
Kelly saying that they are some people I think 33 million
Really thinks it's 3 million
I don't believe there's a real Alex whatever say was first
This is just a random nonsense
Yeah you see the first contradiction of the original form
This narrative
Now instead of it as being these people of their own volition
I'm telling Alex
They were commanded to because the higher-ups
Want to make sure that the hardcore Patriot people like Alex
Know what's up
Because I when it's coming down they're going to need them prepared or something
So now it's order
This is official chain of command stuff
Which is a direct contradiction
Section of the earlier attack.
I insisted
Keep I keep that in mind
Cuz it's it's just
The clear-cut case
Of this being b*******
Keep your writers room off
Your writers room shouldn't be the show
You shouldn't be workshopping your b*******
In front of me
It makes me angry
Yeah it makes this really
As long as you're paying attention over
A couple days
You'll notice the shift starts to happen
He's making all this up
So anyway
Alex is really mad about the media engaging in Hysteria
There's all this hysteria surrounding the virus again I would say that Mike Adam saying it's over
Humanity there's only going to be lone survivors is about as hysterical as you can get
Mike engages in a little more Asteria
Remember to early on I said that China would begin harvesting this and act
Actually trying to deposit
Into cities across America
I think we we've already been under attack
I think of some of these outbreaks that we're seeing are
Because
China
Try to export the virus
So you can say it
So how is that not Hysteria
We've always been under attack viruses are in the United States
Google that's not hysteria that's just that's just
Clear-eyed political analysis the sterical global political
Yeah
So we see another shift
In the narrative and the timeline
Hear this next clip with Mike and Alex talk
My concerns Alex that there may be so many cities under lockdown and quarantine
Election day
Democrat
To postpone
3 weeks ago
Now this week that's in the news already going I will this affect
Did he say that three weeks ago did he say that on Sunday
You're right
Okay alright
Three weeks ago you did say it was over for Lone Survivor now
So they get done 300 stupid
I want talk about this
But I don't want to get
Alex has Tommy Rob
Is it on the show
And we're not going to cover this interview because I'm not going to engage with the story
All good
On March 2nd Tommy was arrested for common assault after Witnesses say he punched a guy in
The face of the pub
Blackpool
Tommy claims that the man had assaulted his eight-year-old daughter
And he was restraining them
The reason I won't engage
The story is
Because
Generally speaking
I don't trust Tommy Robinson at all
He's been shown to be a very inconsistent untrustworthy source
The bad faith
But this is way too
Sensitive of a story
Position on or comment on
And in reality I do not know what have
Yeah and I refused
To be in
I'm good with that
Their interview
Alex and Tommy
Is disgust
And honestly it's one of the first times in recent memory today
Literally felt sick to my
My stomach listening
If Tommy is lying that's gross
If he's telling the truth
He's allowing his own child trauma to
To be used by Alex to attack Muslims and drag queen Story Hour and I can't handle either possible
No matter what the reality is it's gross exploit
Alex plays
The clip of Tommy interviewing his daughter will get it
8 years old on his show
It's disgusting
These people are
It's supremely a fan
Alex
Using this tutor
Try and sell his product
But you see why they want planetary control
The carry out their evil desires
It's not just the Muslims that want to do this if she stood level us every level
Evil incarnate on this planet so please remember
You're the only defense of the children
And when you
Supporting for by spreading the word and by praying for is my body products you're making all possible
Get the products we go
It's just unbelievable like it's one of the first time
A very long time that I have
Legitimate
Whitley Phelps
I feel like I might throw up list
To it it was
It was a level of like no matter what the reality is here this cannot be accepted
How
Does it keep happening
I tell you that there's nobody
And then this happens and I'm like yeah
The I thought I didn't even think that was a line
To cross
Yeah
There's no bottom no
So I don't I'm not I'm not
Matt at all out of
I do need to
Have pulled
You that this happened
Because it puts Alex in a
F*****-up heads
Because of this conversation
Buddy's had with Tommy
He is
This just in
A f****** mode where
He's talking about God
Yeah yeah
Deeply Disturbed
For a little bit
Episode
And he starts off that
Stretch by talking about how
Beloved
How attacked
I was thinking this morning
Thought right after I worked out took a shower
How much its baby stronger
Cow
Thank God for allowing that to happen
Will that make them persecute me even more
And I think the only way to tell the story is used to tell the story about the thought I don't know
But I haven't enjoyed the things that have happened but then I
I do enjoy the lighter
If your only way of feeling like
Validated or like you're doing a good job is
Buy attack
That happen against
Do you create a negative
Yeah you incentivize
Yourself to do things that will elicit
Negative responses
Some people because you look
Experience those negative responses
As if you're doing a good job you're on the right track
If you only way I get to open
Yeah it's a it's a real
F***** up childish system there people can get
I understand it sometimes.
Like a trapped in that without knowing
What is the feedback loop and often times it takes therapy to be able to recognize
And transcend them
I have a lot of empathy for people who
Maybe
Well-meaning
And in that mode
He is
Anita
Anyway Alex starts crying
Talk about God
As long as you
Crosman God
Center your Souls guide
There is no power
The enemy has
Chance
Well your thought you must
Totally trusting God
All I can say is
I've never asked
Presence of God
I've heard you ask God for things
You told God what to
On your shoulder
Comfort Shield so strong
Play God says
I really don't want to see heart
You see what they're doing other people
Are you ready to really get hurt bad
Dcra to be hurt
Alex Sims
Get a new God bro he's sitting there
On the verge of open
Tears on
Here
Talking about how God wants to hurt him for the greater good
This is f***** up hey man there's a look
I I know
Flagellation went out of went out of style a long time ago but he's leading the charge to bring him back
Get a f****** cata Ninetales and start whipping writing well exactly
Absolutely
These people
So it's not only Alex
It's really into Jesus.
You can break up
Did you know that it's true it's not hard
It's not just Alex though even if Alex broke up with God they would still be one person in the Infowars feared
Super into Jesus
And that
Is Rodger Stone
Sorry
I'm sorry I don't know if you know this but Alex actually converted Rogers
Give me more
Years ago
I pray the Rodger Stone in my office
I said give me your hand let's pray to Jesus for protecting a drink
Call please
From that
And he said it's just amazing you know I see the religious establishment of corruption and I don't think it's all Bs but
He saw the drag queen story times in the pedophile
Delia and just the email the Democrats he's like Gidget really real people
Rapture is like he watches it for they like
Man that is
Daddy I want inject that into my veins
You believe that then you can believe
She probably like me and you and anyone who thinks
I would say Rodger is flushed
Even if he is a religion
His older age or these
Crisis that he's in
Whatever I don't care I'm not going to judge
The notion that would Alex is fun
That it's just nonsense now that Rogers saw drag queen story time I was like
I got to get God I hope yeah that's
That's banana.
That's absolute bananas
People said oh it is Rodger Stone really taking Jesus's just
Personal savior
No
Bragging as I'd like to say we were at
I pray that
He wasn't manipulating ADP
Understand that nothing good thing
Celebrate that
You should accept Rodger
Would never hypocrite about going to Gay Pride parades
Wow.
But his wife
I've been wild nobody is judging anybody here
God judges the heart
So I got just welcomed Rodger publicly
Proclaiming his faith in Jesus Christ to that
We should all welcome him
Because there are no atheists in foxholes
Panic attack
Buddy you get Jesus
Are you bow to Satan
Stripe
There's nothing like having the devil on your ass to front get you to get over Jesus
They're doing all their evil stuff to you in person give you the minute you just call on Jesus in the middle of the night
I don't just tell Jesus what to do or don't I just take Jesus I need your help
Jesus
I'm not up here like some preacher man let me tell you
I mean I never bragged about it
People to death and things like that
I mean I missed her worldly
But I'm telling you
Jesus
Is the only thing that's going to fix
I think that being worldly is more like I like a cigar and I drink champagne.
I say it high-end hotels people to death
I've traveled the world that's so to Alex's point
Or not he has
About beating people to death or
F****** a lot somebody's got a Supercut
Heather Hills
Irresponsible
Not that I'll ever stop
Everybody's got shot
I tried a couple times not too nice
People long time to die if you start the guts up
I could have sex with the most beautiful women Hollywood
I never did it you know why
Every time they didn't have a soul
When I was 16
Games anymore
I grew up
The fights all the big rituals
Okay I mean he brags about f****** incitement killing all the time
A lot of people sent that
The Media Matters
I was just sitting there like
I'm
Good good
Jokers
I'm glad
Yeah I'm not
Talked about this
The last episode even like
It would be
Good it'll be a fuller coverage
If like
Once again Alex Bragg's
Danzig
Alex gets off this
Sort of weird God
The Jag he's been in
And he has a guest on
And I think it's the last time we will ever see her
I appreciate her holding
Well I got it at 1 to break a few minutes it's super Tuesday
Deanna Lorraine is amazing super smart and very beautiful woman
Sing I guess was beautiful
Creation
So I can't can't bring Indiana Lorraine's I'm talking about how she is
This'll likely be gentle rains last appearance on Infowars
Because she's only really well is it because you was trying to meme her way into running gives Nancy Pelosi for a seat in the house
And I didn't work
I didn't happen
Primary for California's 12th District was held on March 3rd
2653 votes
This was just
Pelosi's 89,000
460 South
So doesn't look too good for Deanna
All right that was that was the percentage of people who are going to die the coronavirus apparently she
It's also be by Republicans 1387 votes in democratic
Yeah I was rooting for
California is a very weird primary set of rules
It's an open primaries
The top two vote-getters end up in the general election
Even if they're from the same party
So do you want
Is out
The general election will be Nancy Pelosi being
Destin from
Five-star challenge
This episode is on the day of the primary so I guess Alex
This is some kind of a last pushed
Lorraine
That last mile that you needs to clinch the election
But it was not to be
I really don't want to make fun of her
We're getting involved in the political system since I would encourage anyone
Get involved if they feel like they can make a difference but
Chris on the way to Randall campaign
Feel too bad about it
Anybody who flies a plane around trying to make jokes about liberal tears deserved
Depressingly
She lost liberal tears we're getting those little girl tears for you
So anyway this might be the last time she was on his a guest
But
Which he's never done before she loses
She's offering her a job she lost so I guess
People CNN MSNBC
Infowars with a v
Get of the year
Yeah this is going to be
No
So Alex
Is there interference very stupid
Alex has something going on
They're using the crisis that is come with it
To take over and have power and control
He's not trying to do that
There's no doubt that
Everyone I talk to
I'm not trying to Coffee Ron are like Illustrated I can't stop
Lawyer
As ammonia is super sick right now
Back from d.c.
I know that's flown
Supersac
This is absolutely a performance thing like Alex's at a dry throat I imagined from Rambling too much
Well maybe it's not
On March 7th it was reported that attempt Coronavirus
The entire Infowars crew being a
Exposed to it
I pray that this isn't the
Since I don't wish illness on people even that I hate
And because I can't imagine the horrible effect this would have on Alex's
Is rhetoric
I can't imagine that making about you better but
Playing up this go off
I don't know man
Yeah I can call Steve pieczenik he can cure it
So we're running out of time on this March 3rd episode and Alex I think realized
But he hasn't done much
Touch
There's a lot of Alfred Lee Robinson there's a lot of rambling about God has
Interviewing Deanna Lorraine
Now it's time to get to work
Let me just tell you headlines
Don't
Hanover
Let me just do this without
Probably the best thing I can do here
No it's it's like doing nothing that's the best thing that he can do a ton of headlines
10% of these articles
Fully
Maybe 90% he's
Come over but he does read all those
Except
He doesn't know what reading mean
So he reads
He reads one article and it's
It's about how
The last
This is really depressing
I forgot to get this clip
What is the headline is that Liberals are having less male babies
And Alex says that it's on purpose
Of course
Party on purpose part is not in the
The headline is just making that up
This is about a study that was done
Specifically Ontario
They found it
Possible
Trump's election is thrown off normal sex ratios of newborn
There's a wired article that explains this really well and what it comes down to is that there's a documented relations
Between stressful event
And the sex ratio of babies
Which actually happened after 9/11 and the London bombings
In 2005
No one knows exactly why this is the case
It's still something that scientist trying to
Explore and understand
But there's
The pattern b b
Observe where highly stressful geopolitical event have a tendency to skew births
Tubing
More female
In this case specific to Ontario
They found a ratio of 1.0 to 17
Down from the normal figure of 1.06
This is certainly really into
And the more data points researchers have about the
This phenomenon
Because I'm a better chance of figuring out what's going on
However
This is not an instance of liberals
Choosing not to have boys
We can assume that this was not in the 10% of the articles that Alex
Yeah I would like chromosome is weaker to stress whatever
Just has been floated
Right now I'm just saying like
He doesn't give a s***
No he didn't read the article
Maybe that's why
So here's another one
Vegan
Cuz they smell bad
You stinking scum
Cool stories about an anonymous person in Berkeley California request
Another neighbor's not cook meat with the windows open because the smell is overpowering to them when they went jog
Even the worst interpretation of the story this is a neighborhood issue
Is literally no reason for Alex be wasting his time for taking
The politeness or lack thereof in a random neighborhood he's never been to
There's a decent chance this isn't even a real story
It's all based on someone posting an anonymous note they got making this request which could easily be faked
No matter what it doesn't married Alex calling anyone's, or even talking about the story at all
Definition of trivial
Also
That story has nothing to do with the government
The vegan did not demand any
It was a request
Any requests
We're not for them
To stop cooking
It was to close the windows
The dead South
Looks like that story was also not in The Temper set Alex red
I saw that story
I was so Furious that anybody like so many outlets picked up on that
And it just
Romantic
Neighbors
Hate each other
That's
It's so stupid
Just just stop it
Set beginning it was like this is going to be a trend
F*** off
Who complained about
Dogs next door is that okay
I hate that
Watch homeowner Propel Steve with motion-activated water sprinkler
Time to get to
How is this relevant to the show
This is just one of those fun videos you see someone from your office post
It's a sort of thing you see on the local news and they run it as a story when they need to fill 20 seconds if you have a show
Village
Buscemi's reading is Facebook
That is what
He's doing and he's like oh look at all my Facebook friends
Sharing articles I'm reading the f****** head lice
Okay coffee
And I'm sure that he's you've never found
I couldn't read the whole.
That's in the 10% he has not really a reader like I'm a visual learner
Very depressed
Very sad
So we get to the 4th
And
A lot of the beginning of
This episode
Is about Mike Bloomberg
A lot of it is
Are we still doing
What would
Bluebird
Can't we just not talk about him ever
It's it's I got really
Yeah cuz he I don't I didn't understand why you were spending so much time on Bloomberg
He was just a little little Tay
Taste of Abyss
Beginning
Body looks at that
Isle of dog Banner
And nose
But he will
Cloud Financial
Which makes me feel great
When a pile of dog feces like that doesn't like me
It means I'm doing really good
Bring It On
People have I not that Braden stature
But I mean hitting ships he thinks he's so big and so powerful
He definitely has a Napoleonic
Russian Roulette
And boy let me tell you that really sold the public all that
Sashay around
Well I say Mike Bloomberg
I'm just saying
Wagner cat somebody for a
Gay g******* video
He definitely be the main subject of lead deposits be made
So anyway that Bloomberg is funding the lawsuits against him and until he does I don't believe that's true
I guess Alex took the news the Bloomberg one that one primary pretty hard because he spends most of his first half-hour the show
Complaining
It's mostly about that video that came out of Bloomberg eating food with his hands pretty grossly
It's mostly just that
Hint
Always personal always physical
Appearance-based
Bulshit
There's so many reasons
To Hattiesburg there's so many
He can't make those critiques billions of real
Soda tax baby I don't know
Read that article
Offensively
Politically
Fuk fuk
It's very strange because Alex is definitely playing this
For comedy
But it comes off as Alex being really mad about a guys eating attic
Yeah like I think what happened is that like Carpe donktum made a meme and Alex really doesn't want to do any work so he just plays
Clip lick
Three times in the first half hour
And that was why I was not surprised to hear him say that
And I am really just
On my wheels apart
47 minutes
Do your job actually going to have to this part isn't in the show we're going to cut this part we're going to restart the show your f******
Job 37
We're supposed to be all the super important news always weirdly don't have time to get to
How do you spend over 1/6 of your broadcast day playing joyless memes and why is already dropped out of the race
Yep how he eats food he's
Are you this fight
Do your job
Grocery store cuz his daughter wanted some
Okay and people were not nice to him
And Alex didn't take that very well
Vogue's
Well I'm going to try to achieve this day was a wall of
Their souls aren't gone
Suspended animation are in carbonite
They
They've been putting a trans
But nowhere place and they
Don't have any power and they think they're desperate and they don't have a reason to live
And so they're just stewing
And self-loathing instead of a connection to God
Directions to Beauty Avenue just recognize Beauty
The painting knitting or power helping somebody or gardening then they would connect to the Earth because
They're all smartphones everything else they're just dying it's scary when I saw there's what I seen
Doing something
Whoa
Alright so we're not nice to him at the grocery store el-mel modern civilization is
Killing us
That is a bit of an Escalade shallow Unabomber yes
Great although you should count yourself lucky
You should be spat upon every time you go outside your door
Most likely getting bad looks
Yeah so Alex plays a clip of a video
That's
Supposed
To be out of a rock
And it's all four number of body bags in the hospital
And I
I want to play this clip I want to discuss
That's because I
What it does
Is really demonstrate
How there is a disconnect
Between what Alex does
And what's a proper
Hourly
If you just see it
I will tell you that I have no idea is that videos
Make maybe it's an old video that someone's reusing claiming it's for Risa
It happens all the time you do not know just immediate
Viewing of the video
I don't know any
Indeed
I'm less interested in that though because this Cliff clip offers a paper
Perfect opportunity to explain one of my main problems
With Alex Jones
It's very difficult to engage in his ideas a lot of the time because he and I have a very
Basic
Epistemological disc
Agreement
Fundamentally we don't agree on what it
Means to know some
How knowing something is achieved
Let's use this video isn't it
Hear something my prop
It starts with a question
In this case is this video
I can't possibly know that from the presentation on Alex's
There's just not enough information
So in order to reach that conclusion I need to seek out information
Through a little poking around I can find out that this video is said to have been published by BBC Persia and it's allegedly
All the number body bags in a hospital and calm
Then article in the New York Post says that it was a rich
Only shared on social media by a journalist named Bahamut
And.
Official account of fatalities
Seven opponents of the Ayatollah have claimed that they believe that his regime is covering up a real scope
The situation
There could be many more deaths
Short this video has been used as
Proof of that
An argument that there are way more deaths than 107
With this information I can entertain the possibility that this video is definitely real for a couple of reasons
The government of Iran is not the most open and train
Governments of the possibility that they've not been for
Coming is in the realm of
Possibility
But even if it doesn't
There aren't more than 100 body bags in that video
And the outbreak in Iran has been largely centered in
So it's also possible that this video to pick
People who have died
Which is very sad but not necessarily proof of any cover-up video
Has been used by some entirely possible
No matter what
Certainly can't
Jump to interpretation results
Conclusive
It's entirely possible and maybe even probable that this video is real and I feel okay with that because I've tried to figure out the
Source of the video
And nothing seems too suspicious
And places that generally engage in
Some form of editorial process
Have posted it
Some of them do say
For Alex
Even if he's correct I take issue with how he arrives it information
He sees this video and decides it is brain is a supercomputer and you just automatically knows when something is real
That obviously isn't
True documentation on the Shelf
That is his process
When I tell you my process is seeking out information about where this video came from who posted it initially what is
Report to show
That's a process
His process is
That's real I know it's real
Beyond this is dumb
If that's an acceptable way for him to
Come to his reporting
And he's just really talking about his feelings on his show like you said under that deposition
Information and actual knowledge
Mean nothing
I want that
Because
Helps me if they
That's true
Guess what
True
Beyond
Right and this is this is a very
Important
And that is whether or not the conclusion that this video is real
Whether or not he's right about
About that
Process
Nothing for
You need to be process-oriented
Not result Orion
As baseball just figured out in like
Five-year sure sure if you have a sound process you will generally Arise at the
Appropriate
Inclusion Auto auto automotive
Bassist whatever
You randomly be okay or close to write in some cases and then people
Biloxi intuition is so and I got there faster than all those number-crunching
All that s***
Now unfortunately
Nightly if you do engage in
This process and you have no standards
You'll end up doing some really f***** up things
Dislike
I don't know
Having Stewart Roads
The head of the oath
Keepers
Come on your show and
Like a coronavirus expert
Which does
No
You come roof you your come Stewart Road noted
Doctor
Militia guy
You bet
Domestic flights are now spreading it around
Cuz it is Airborne
It's not just that you get it when when someone coughs through you
Booker six feet away or safe
Relating to the air conditioning
And you're going to breathe it in just like smallpox
Or just like measles
What's what's different about this it's not the same as the flu
The house transmitted
It's also an aerosol
It could be airborne
See this is why it's a bad idea to have your militia leader gun weirdo buddy on your show to talk as if he's an expert in public
Because it'll say things like that
Currently no evidence that the coronavirus is transmittable in Airborne fast
It's been shown to transmit by human-to-human contact
Buy contact with some surfaces where the virus may have ended up on
And by respiratory droplets caused by coughs and sneezes
It's easy to say that if a sneeze can transmit the virus
It's not the same
Nothing
Diseases like measles can live in the air for long.
Hours after someone sneezes or coughs or
Which is not the
This case with the coronavirus as far as the current information on
Subject
This matter
Because the difference between being airborne and not is massive
In terms of the spread of the virus
Hwinstore roads what are you doing
Is line
To make them more scared
Which is why you shouldn't be speaking on these subjects
You have no idea what he's talking
Honestly Stuart should stick to whining about guns
Violent revolution
He's much better at that
I was thinking I was thinking maybe I f***** up
At the beginning of that
It's not a baba baba it's Airborne I was like
Oh he's going to he's going to Twisted
It's carried on playing
Get it is Airborne that's how it's getting around the world
And then he was like nope legit is in the f******
AC great Where Art Thou
Wow
Distinctions
That's f***** up talking about his lieutenant-colonel sources
This will be one of the reason
Why I made you
I really bring into sharp Focus that it was over the weekend
That the first one talked
Give us your expertise eating a lot of sources inside the female has all the answers the military has all the answer the loudest
We believe it kills about 2% of people and we're already having
Emergency going on
Because now Alex's added the secret emergency declaration that he's building from the hill have
Inflating the Azar announcement from the end of January
Now he needs one of his sources to have been among
So he's taking the first lieutenant colonel to talk to him over the weekend and moved it back
Month before because it's more
Convenient for the narrative
Nothing matters
Everything shifts
This is all bulshit you are missing one possibility
Alex controls time
Oh he's a Time Lord
Exactly
Artist took the lieutenant colonel they both went back to a month ago that Lieutenant Colonel told him
Against so technically he is correct when he says that a month ago
The lieutenant colonel told him
They were tired
Okay then
Okay if that's the case
Can't backtrack.
So you could
Matt Smith
So Alex
Has allowed Stewart
Denial say that is Airborne
Great
That's very good student no business talk about
Makes a claim hear that
Really kind of interesting
And I think also
Very response
Gut-level you really think this is a big
I think I think this is a serious threat
We had two more dangerous
You guys know what viruses are
So there was an article about people who had recovered from coronavirus testing positive afterwards was published in the New York Times
Times on March 6th
After this episode
If they don't know about that article in the patent less the time lord thing
Boston Store to Taco
There are not many cases of reinfect
Photo of looked into it already there are a couple explanations that are the most like
The first is that these people
Who got false negatives in the test
Redeem them recover
So it's not actually a reinfection as much as it is them still being sick but haven't gotten an accurate - 2
That doesn't sound possible
Possible but it's
Probably unlikely
Since to be discharged from these hospitals people have to test negative in two consecutive test
One day apart
It is unlikely but it's also not impossible since
False negatives are more common than
False positive
Possible that's one explanation
Well considering the kit rollout that we've seen like there's old there's all kinds of possibility of absolute absolute
And the other possibility is that they often bring up is that
The PCR test
It's being done that found them positive after recovering
Could be picking up remnants of the virus
It's because it's a super-sensitive test
Is New York Times article points out that PCR test still quote
The tech remnants of the measles virus
Months after people are no longer
So there are those possibilities
Other explanations than this
Virus
Keeps coming back
Journal of the American Medical Association found for patients in
China tested negative been discharged and then tested positive
18 days later
Do they tested positive later they were asymptomatic and none of the family members who live with them where
Indicate that they weren't contagious
Their study was inconclusive as to the cause of this phenomenon but sad
Further examination
It was recently
In China who died after discharge
From hospital
Presumably because he was
Clear the virus
Is it doesn't match what they're talking about
Since he died of respiratory
Failure
So it's more likely case where he was wrongly
He was one of the number of readmitted
Define Kang Hospital one of the new Leaf
Constructed facilities they put up
So odds are this was a hospital problem where they discharge page
To capricious
There was one case
Japan recovered then days later returned to the hospital with a sore throat
Chest pains
And tested positive again
So I kind of feeds into the
The heart stuff
Stewart was talking about
Some early indications that doctors are seeing
The body creates
In response to the Coronavirus
Do not persist for very long
I like chicken
Box where you get it you're immune to it afterwards
People may only have a very
Temporary immunity
And I am cases
Which is why we need
Vaccine for it
It's just
Survive it or like
Take your kids to f******
Chicken coronavirus party
Another cases in these but there are too few twice
Positive cases to conduct a study or Draw.
Conclusion
Ed Sheeran Lewis the director of the Peter Doherty
Institute for infection
Immunity in Melbourne
Before
I was able to find an article in Taiwan news.
It seems to match up a little closer was Alex
Stewardess
This article is about Taiwan news a message
Increased
I am peoples
At that leave instead the deadliness of the infection
D-sub headline of this article reads quote
Instead of creating immunity the virus can reportedly reinfect an individual in Hastings fatal heart attack
So if you just skim the headlines you might have
Doctor was telling Taiwan
Reinfection of Coronavirus
Stewardess
If you read the actual art
Here's what the doctor
A few people recovered
From the first time by their own immune system
Damaging their heart tissue
And when they get it a second time the antibody dozen
Help but makes it worse
And they died a sudden death
From heart failure
I can't find any data backing up this Anonymous claim but if you
You take it at face value is accurate
Even this is just saying that the meds that were being used to treat the virus are damaging people's hearts
That's not indicative of the virus
Attacking people's heart
This is an article from February 14th so it's not exactly breaking news
But I could see this possibly
It's possible there's something here
If it's true that the meds that were being used compromised patients fart it would put them at far greater risk
From the virus
But the infection has nothing to do with that
That's strictly a problem with these
Anyway the point is is this is the source that Stewart now it's are using
We're completely miss you
I wouldn't be surprised
Neither of them had actually even read the article
Just read the headline
Headline is in line in line with the narrative that they're putting for the article
Is not
At this stage even experts can't definitively say whether the relatively small phenomenon of people testing
Positive negative positive
Is the result
Human error fault
The test Horsham feature of this virus that is not yet understood
And I had The Oath Keepers
Playlist of the Expo
Possible
I'm still recovering from the
Oh it's Airborne now it's in your AC run run
Get outside
Go underground
It's probably underground it's in the ground now you're going to get sick again
And now your heart attack but God damn it we're all dead
So
Stewart Rhodes Alex Jones having a great
Yes got a hit that does seem like there and how do you make this even better
0ad Rochester
Close
Steeplechase
God dammit
Okay and
He does want to talk with the Democratic primary and I sense a little
December 10th
She was seeing right now
The end of the day
When you have a blunt
That's a hard day buddy
For the Democrats
Steve's whole point about Trump being a great person to happy presidents getting super rich
Why does it matter the Bloomberg Jewish
Steve
I do I do think that that is
One thing that I
Cuz I remember I've gotten a few people
Sing me a message
When Elizabeth Warren dropped out of the race
Disappointed because
Now we're back
The two white dude all over again
And that Nazi flag really should put into sharp relief that we are not back
Acta2 White
Well some people view it that way
Homicidal
No
Nope
Alex is very convinced the shifting Sands of his Coronavirus
Narrative
Easter but it's man-made
This isn't even Up For Debate
Unfortunately
Steve pieczenik doesn't buy that b*******
I don't think so and I'll tell you why
If you want to create a virus
Create a Coronavirus
They don't work
So I don't know what the Lysol part is about but I know that there was a conspiracy going around about like
I saw that somebody took a picture and it was like
All helps kill 9899 Coronavirus
What's Diva saying but it isn't
Thing that he's like knives
Yeah
Tough time with that
Now
I mean there's advice
Oh there's bad advice
And then there's pieczenik
Has category
He has a plan
I want to hear this blithering
Used
The CDC was way behind didn't have the proper test
Or funding
So is advice is get rid of it
Tony fauci
Alright
I'm going to here's my plan
Now a lot of people in a lot of movies evolved in about
Fighting the Zambian
Apocalypse
My plan is what if instead
We don't
What if we lead in what if we do not become a zombie you don't know if it's not better
Maybe they're having a great time it seems like there is it there
Right there populating more than white people are now that's your great replacement Theory
Jesus Christ I would say that advice is
C'mon man
We should only be treated by midwife
I think it's indicates two things
Steve is really committed to the terms of everybody in the government
And the second thing I hear from that is that Steve really doesn't
View this as
Concerned
The Coronavirus
No big deal
Which is run
Counter to every element of Alec
Except on Tuesday
Nowhere Monday
Which state was not a big deal
It'll all work out it's all fine
Okay
Stewart
Are not stupid still there
You still hanging out of court and Steve
There he knows that malicious very active in Montana
Research rambling about Montana
Okay
This has nothing to do with anything
Okay I'm definitely biketown in for this
It has nothing to do with any
I think they were talking about before this
It's very weird
Montana
And I had a lawyer
And came down a Florida is Montana a problem
Tana in and of itself
Who's really a democratic state
Because I can
We're back in 2 minutes
Number three with Stewart Roseanne
On Montana
Straight ahead stay weather
Steve what are you talkin about or did you even have
Time
Yeah
Give me the timeline
Let me know when you are in Montana I want to look that up and cross-reference that with Whitney
Whether or not you were in Korea
I do love that anytime anybody brings up anything Steve is like I absolutely we are
Together all this time from Montana
What
Alright thanks
Globetrotter
Forrest Gump
Sure
Talking about how like yeah he wants to get rid of all these government agencies and everything because he can't get integrated Intel
Absolutely
Alex is like
Well Papa Steve haven't I given you integrate
This is very f*****-up
16 inch
When I need an integrated intelligence predict
The CIA doesn't work
Hi I said that for the 18 years you've been ahead of the curve when it honestly little eyes
Scary
We saw Trump was going to win two years before he did
Is the globalist
Man
F*** out of here out of here
Bulshit
Six months before his elected you work
Calling of a goddamn Bob
That's not true
But it was less than a year
Started supporting Trump
December 2015
Trump wasn't even running two years before the election
Announce tonight was July
Pennywise
Stupid
So
They talked about another thing that Steve has been like consistent on for a long time is it the Democratic Party
Yeah they're all dying
And you talk about that a little bit is okay
You know whatever
Talking about that
50 indicates that he was
Not a good practicing therapist
Okay back when he was
This party and the
Cast of A system that really
It's no longer in the car
Constitutional system down
The balrog falls off the cliff against me with his whip
How do we stop them from taking us out with him
And I'll comes back buddy
A patient committing suicide
I will not become a psychiatrist
Listen
I am going to go out a limb here
And I'm going to say because it's your f****** job
I'm not sure that's best practices watch people cut their wrists
I I go to a psychiatrist and I have an appointment
This week and I'll tell you something
Not
Her she is not going to watch
Yeah if I were to go to my therapist did you like a what you think about this call the police
I would think he was the worst
Therapist in the world
He actually have a responsibility by law to call the police if they are self-harming in his office
Some sort of a guidance on that issue
Stunning Steve just indicated he's a f******
You have to call the police if you were planning to commit violence to others or yourself
I don't know yeah I don't I don't know what the line is on viola
But yeah I said I should have looked in
And that but I didn't
Anyway
Saigon he's been
Complete nut bag
I don't think it's Braxton
So Alex
Gets into like this idea of it
These people who are
Clearly contradicting
Each other on his show
People accused me of that
All the towels and emails and Thomas
How do you say one another and I'm always for the family in Jesus Christ
America but you're not always
Detectives on the different angles to challenge my mind
Alex wants to challenge his mind he should take up Sudoku
If you wants to get the perspectives of people he thinks are interesting that he should probably learn how to conduct
Interview
Problem with Alex's show is not that he has different people on with different ideas
The problem is that he doesn't engage with those ideas from a consistent position
He agrees with just about everything
John friends
You can see earlier how we
Turn something like Adam said about a Rush Limbaugh clip into two high-level sources telling him
The half the US was going to get coronavirus at 3
There really is only one responsible way to do a show like what Alex is trying to do
And that's for him to stay neutral
Teva consistent northward facing bearing
Which would be hard
Pair
You need to hear Stewart Road say the coronavirus is Airborne
And be able to correct
Which Alex would never do
For one who doesn't want to offend his gun buddy
Into
He's more than happy to say it so he can say it himself later
Because Alex refuses to do any work that he can't stop himself from believing basically anything is stupid friends tell him
You end up in a situation where the show ends up being super disorienting
Kind of abusive
For this episode of listen to Sunday through Wednesday of last week
And I don't know what Alex's real position
Not Coronavirus
On Sunday the virus isn't a big deal on the real issues.
The supply chain.
I even suggest that the whole thing is fake because of his real china would have covered it up
The whole thing as a plot to disrupt the economy
An attack Trump
But then on Monday Alex mysteriously has to fake high-level sources you predict
3 billion dead
One over the weekend and one that morning
Singing all of a sudden
This is a severe medical Panic again
And even though it's a major crisis he still has time to try and bake Gorka
Into a fight
Then on Tuesday
It's still the three billion Beth dire situation but it's cool cuz secretly declared a National Emergency a month ago
And unpreparedness you see all around you was actually just globalist
In the bureaucracy trying to f*** Trump over
Of course even though he's still in a gigantic pandemic mode
Alex still has time to spend it
Interviewing Tommy Robinson
Crying about God
Been on Wednesday one of these fake sources actually told Alex this stuff about the 2%
Even though I'm about to go out
How to speculate on this is a race specific
That maybe trumpet launched on China's pay back or front
And then he has super credible always right expert Steve pieczenik on to say that this isn't man-made
No big deal because
Yeah we got it and enjoyed himself
Get rid of the CDC in the 80s
I can't put it more simply than this
I pay attention to Alex and listen to his show Act
And I have no idea what is actual
He goes along with the whims of these gas
Contradictory things they say become part of his narratives in a way that creates
Generalized
Incoherent
This is really hard
To penetrate
I suspect that this is intense
Review operates this way Alex will have endorsed and played around
100 nonsense theories it is got to brought up
Turn on the off chance that one of them ends up being close to Accurate he can pretend those other 99 we're just wargaming things
Not really his position
Was the one that closed
I'm fairly convinced that this is a strategy consciously
You're not
Where is case it makes the show very hard to understand
If you're just passively listening to this and
You actually believe that Alex knows anything about what he's talking about
I can't imagine what you have to go through on a weekly basis
Everything Changes
Because nothing
Real
On Monday Alex A source told him the 2% figure that past weekend
Then on Wednesday was
Alex tell Steve that he knew Trump was going to get
Elected two years before the election
When Trump didn't even announce two years in advance
Can Alex caulk trumpisms
Broad
Until December 2015
Less than a year before
In the same way that Alex is not a consistent protagonist for the show
Past of his positions
40 States as fact
Or just a whim
People who listen to the show were tricked into thinking of what they were getting was researched
And hidden information
It's really just the emotional Outburst of a racist idiot
Can't even be bothered to read articles past headline
It's sad I mean it really bums me out
It's
It's it's
It's it's difficult for me because I know that a certain amount of Alex's audience didn't know what they were getting in
Get seduced and with this promise of like
Entertainment I know the truth behind the arrows
Who's today kind of b*******
And then before you know it you could get
Just load sleep on this idea that he's right
About everything
It's just
If you pay attention
Extinction
Yeah
Those two high-level sources the way that story changes
In the beginning of it the way it's so clearly based on
A conversation with Mike Adams about a Rush Limbaugh clip
Like
You wouldn't
Notice that unless you're paying a
I imagine that they treat
Him the same way
The news in Chipley
Where
It doesn't matter it really kind of doesn't matter what he says
What matters is what you choose
To think that he
He said you know so
He gives you a wide range of options
But if you're listening to him
You're really only looking
For what reinforces
You're already done believe
Yeah probably don't like easy
He's not a he's not a source
Easy A
You know some of that but whatever it is
Something like that
It's still around
And he has another militia buddy with him
And I don't really care to even remember the name of that guy
Virus
She's going to have
Other
Example
Crisis
The song I been in for the time of shutting down
The ability of people in Hong Kong for example
Protest
A lockdown in our country
.
The rise of these militia units for example in Virginia
No one's going to want to go to a mass muster of 500 guys that we just had
Oh no militia turnout will be down
Yeah we want to keep those 500 people from
Close to each
Now they're gone song
Women who
Get together and protest
What the government's really focusing
Izzo's 500 Gunn weird
At their big
So
Stewart doesn't like Mike
And you don't
Trust the idea that he's in charge
Of this Coronavirus
Response
Okay
Now Alex
Tries to defend Mike
That's about
The disco's weird
Grounded
Fully in favor of red flag
We use wind to send 7
Oh yeah
Is the model the whole country should follow
You remember a couple Clips back before I went on that Rance but I like shows abusively inconsistent
You were having that clip Alex said the people ask him why it says one thing 1 hour
Remember how we try to maintain that is
Consistency was Eddie's pro-gun Second Amendment
Like 10 minutes later he is trying to push back on Stewart Roads talking s*** about my
Mike Pence
When he's informed appearances in favor of red flag laws
Which two people extort and Alex are they
On August 28th 2019 pencil to Roundtable discussion
I held one in response to the Dayton and El Paso shooting
And Stewart
Is totally right
Mike Pence was arguing
But Indiana's
Existing red flag laws about guns
Remodel that the federal government could follow
This is a big deal in the friend's gun weirdo Circle
Alex's buddy Larry Pratt's group gunownersofamerica even launch 7th wheat bread
About the meeting saying
Mike Pence's again calling
For red flag gun grab
Citing that Indiana's gun confiscation law to be a model for the country
And in all caps
So they got him
Alex had no idea about
The shining example of his
Consistency is an issue that he knows basically nothing about except that he likes guns
The f****** vice-president is openly supported week
Considers a breach of the Second Amendment
And Alex's surprised to hear about it like
Six months after the rest of the Gunn weirdos lost their minds about it
How to sew reverse to work
Can't even handle his one Marquee issue well
And it shows when he's sitting here with an actually committed gun weirdo
What roads did The Real McCoy
But he actually doesn't insane person
And then Alex's he's even sort of role playing his gun support
Mike Pence
It wasn't
Look at my ignorance
Yeah
Which he is never ignorant
Never brag but he's never wrong or never an uninformed
It's fun
So we've decided that Mike Pence's bad
Evil Alex
With other guys
Now it's time to decide who should take over for pets
Okay we're fantasy
It has the feeling of them being like
All right who are we going to put in his place
Control Trump
And set him up
That's what I truly believe going to happen to him
He's a global as I don't care how many times you deals on the show who plays pants with
Question
We should replace a month
Congressman scalise
Jim Jordan
Rand Paul
Kansas
Go back
No the other one
He's the one that was attorney general is really good
Hurley Hurley
Missouri
No I wouldn't
Ohio
Yep
Patience gives me a bad feeling
Jim Jordan food be good
In my mind
Grandpa
I hate to be the bearer of bad news but Jordan is
Not a good guy Parts about his cover-up of the Doctor Who was sexually assaulting members of the Ohio State
Going to you when Jordan was the assistant coach
Oh well there is that
On February 12th The Daily Beast reported that the former
Team captain Adam disabato spoke before the
The house Civil Justice committee
And testified that quote
Jordan called him
Heatedly in 2018
After his brother Michael.
Sabato publicly claimed that the sexual abuse of
18 Doctor Richard Strauss was common knowledge to those in the wrestling
Program
Cluding Jordan
Adam told the committee quote
Jim Jordan called me crying groveling
Begging me to go again
Against my brother
That's the kind of cover-up
What's going on there
Investigation found that his Doctorate abused at least
177 kids Between 1979 and 1998
Air Jordan was the assistant coach
Between 1987 and 1995. Swear this doctor was there
As if things were already looking bad for Jordan
On March 6th
CNN reported are now six former OSU wrestlers who were willing to speak with them
And that
Quotes they were present when George
Heard or responded to sexual misconduct
Complained
About the team Doctor Richard
Strauss
According to the article 8
More former wrestler said that the doctors Behavior was
An Open Secret in the athletic
All this is really bad for Jim Jordan because his whole position
His doctor was abusing these students
Meanwhile
So cool Alex
That's who you're going to go to bat for the good guy just feel really good about that
I wonder if this sort of information is a kind of think Alex will magically become aware of if Jim Jordan ever turns on Trump
I wonder I wonder about that
Cuz I think it is
I just
Can't
Imagine
Especially with how often Alex
Screams about
Burger up how I tell her I'm the protector of the children
And then just all of
All of this
II
Jim Jones a good guy
Say it say it out loud
One last clip Year from
4th and it's talking about
To do
I imagined kill
Good Lord I Hope
Trump does not do this
What's a truly when he should stand in as the POTUS in the
Crisis
GattiTown said he must now do it
Almost there
In a constitutional matter in the way to do that is to call the militia
Veterans back on the border and lock it down
And stop all international flights
Kill the cartels in
Total exercise the power
Also stopped the further
Flying into
People that are infected with viruses
What
You know what he's talking about there
That goes back to the you can either have pillows
See martial law or martial law
I think
That underneath the underneath this all Alex on some level
Do not
Very open about it
Kind of think
This is an opera
Yeah
For job to enact martial law clean house
Arrest all this political enemies and all that
Secure the Republic back on Facebook for God's sake
So I think
Underneath
Some of this
Like you no matter what the narrative is even though we
We can see over the course of the span of a few days
It's shift dramatically
Play there's there's
Large
To what Alex
Maine driving point is
Even beneath that there's probably this
Underlying current of I hope Trump uses this
To enact martial law
The Trump martial law that I want
In order for all liberals
All the drag queens to BX
Executed or thrown in prison
Oh my
The Democratic party will be outlawed
All of this authoritarian rule
Play but it will be
White Christian straight male
Active martial law
I think the lot of that is underneath all of this
And that's why a lot of it
To be contradictory and shifting
It doesn't really matter to me
Yep he's just hoping the Trump polls
The trigger on this ship
Maybe when he says you know like all there's a lot of conflicting information but what I've always been about the same thing I've always been about guns
Jesus and all that s***
What we're really finding out is he's always been about whiteness
Just whiteness
Just white white face
So ever let's get the taste of all this out of her mouth
Another end of the show
Chimpanzees
Can whip
No problem
What person do you know today
Fair enough
Depression
Okay let's.
Okay they want to find out who
Should be vice-president
I want to find out who
Spaces
Do you know anyone who can rip a face
I mean I saw the movie face off
That's true
Although I do believe Nick Nicholas Cage
Good commitment
Probably he's a guy who's
How about Jason Momoa or The Rock The Rock
ShopRite
Maven kayfabe
Either way this episode is part 1
Back on Wednesday
For the
Blood Diamond thrilling conclusion of the next 8 hours
Yeah I got cited
If baldness gives him some sort of
Clarity of thought
What consistency any of these two keeping all of his bad ideas
That part
Alberta in Tilton
We do have a website it's not right. Com
Right
Dollar General Store fighting that go to bed George
That's correct we are also on Facebook we are reviewed
The Show by a shirt all of it
Thank you very much
Emilio and Leo I am a double cheeseburger for breakfast
Holding