Damn important
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Nike.com
Everybody was like
I know this one out of left field is about enchiladas
When
Did you get your first
My first microphone
For this type of bird
Purpose
Recording
I like this kind of
I'm not saying
Did you start your first podcast I'm saying like when did you first like
I'm going to do this
I would have been back in Missouri probably 2000
When I was a much younger man
Tudo radio
Like have my own radio show and that wasn't a possibility
Discover the park
Was a thing
I wanted to try and do it
Early so there wasn't like any kind of
Who had to buy a microphone because I was trying to crack into voiceover work
You have to record your own little
Addition
Descend to the clients
Some folks in
0 gig from a lot of time spent recording
Stuff about Brickstone Tire
What a waste of time
Whatever product product
Okay
Let's go with there's a car say
Car dealership
Come on down
The Brockman
I don't know about Micron about Alex Jones
Got a lot on our plates
Got a lot going on
Anybody listening may I assume right understand
On Tuesday the 10th
Salix
Got a DUI
We'll talk about that at the end of the episode because
Up until the point that didn't that news broke
I already had a whole episode plan
Alex buck
You didn't
Pictures of a server
Certainly more than a couple hours ago
Hey guys today we're going to be
And Alex had to go get a f****** to you I got to add March 10th to that a******
So anyway it's like that Steve Martin thing you know back when he would do a one movie for me one for the studios
I know that the people want to hear about allergies today
Alex's bulshit first
Alright thank you
Hooks
What's that make this possible
Warners sporting show
So first been thank you so much you're now a policy wonk
Next Benjamin thinking about you and how about you want
I'm a policy wonk
Nike Benjamin text Roxana and thank you so much and I'll probably walk
Text Kristen
Journal about what you want
Policy wonk
Are you ever actually Brenda Brenda
Thank you so much you are now probably won't
Thank you and then finally like say thank you to a couple people donated on elevated level appreciate that very much so first Lisa thank you so much you are
And Thomas thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Money off that heroin
Is freakishly large
Thank you so much and thank you so much Thomas
Knowledge fight.com
Sure we would appreciate be lovely
So Jordan on our last episode on Monday we were going over last week
Yeah now it's a show
We're going over the beginning of last week
Envy
Free shaving his head right and we made that division on purpose
New Alex New Life
Jumping on Thursday you're on March 5th because that is right when Alex
As shaved
Just head and
A big news
It is but he
He does not
Want to talk about it
He doesn't have to talk about it I bet he will
Bring it up for quite a while since there was big old ball pit
He does actually start the
Show on a very familiar note
Talking about the Coronavirus
Situation
In this out-of-context drop that we will play
He reveals that he meant to start the show talking about something out
Watercolor job interview out of a homeless person eating poop the drudgereport.com like to and I
I'm at the start the show other but I just ask
You meant to start the show with it
Cool I don't want to start my morning
Like that no
That's what I'm mad at 11 now that's
Like Tammy California
Maybe
I don't know time zone
I know a lot about Alex Jones
Jordan
Restart
So are we still here on the 5th
And this is how Alex actually does
Start off the show
Talking about how
Maybe Mass hysteria around an outbreak maybe it's inevitable
When things happen like that
Humans
You don't know where you are in some small town
Google what ubiquitous interviews
Believe
Google that you actually about downfall scam
Michigan or New York
See the restaurant
With lines out the door
Restaurants
The grand analysis
Restaurant
That's for cars and if I doubt there's a meth head running it and they're dealing drugs out the back
Creepy looking place there are so many great restaurants that are not crowded
Sometimes the greatest restaurants are the ones that you
Highway 22
Entirely sure what point he's trying to make it how can I
Next but
I just take issue with this is my my favorite Thai places
Always
I think about people get takeout
Delivery but
If you went there you'd siakam
Completely empty dining area
If that
Yeah so this is stupid
Anyway Alex
Talks about this that Lansing
Set study if you'll recall
Up to this point he's been using that that Lancet study that looked at just a couple of very extreme cases of folks
Already developed the virus into the pneumonia
Stage and they were looking
King at a small subset
Channel people
And they predicted
A 15%
Mortality rate
Excuse me not predicted
They said there was that a small sample size
Alex has been using that to say that Lancet was saying
Bet the whole world
We're having 15% mortality rate
Coronavirus
How it
It's interesting
He now knows what that study actually was about
Lancet had a limited thing 5 weeks ago
I'm just 47-8 at least 65 to get a decent reading
With the ones they had it was a
15% death rate yourself
Super sick and puts on a good Focus cribs
Robert
I made it was 50% I would be in a bunker
Alex no nose
That he was a month behind on our show did he just where we explain that song
Now he knows
Which is important
Because he has that information inside his head
Save this as a correct
Well I miss reported this I had that wrong sorry about that now you just now knows what that actually is
That's interesting
Hold on to that for later
Okay from the virus and he starts talking a little bit about the
The Democratic
A primary
ESPN
Songs about the Biden being the presumptive nominee
He's just holding the front for gabbard
The come-from-behind right nope
But he is holding
Confront for somebody
Hillary Rodham Clinton
What are they planning behind that you know
You do know that
Trying to sell Hilary Duff and then he
At the stroke
Presidents have had Woodrow Wilson
The Protestant world
An endorse Hillary because there's a
Hillary in the bureaucracy
She supposed to
I am taking over and everyone that he's left us Steel
Believe
In
Hillary so we'll discuss
All of that you still believe him because of Hillary
Every single person
Safe for Bernie
He has moozie's I go they're going
How to get in
He's all just
Just about Trojan horsing Hillary
Was going to make her the VP now Biden going to make a VP
Before when it was the impeachment stuff
Lucy's going to get in make Hillary the VP she's going to tap Town Hill
These the one
Those are playing along
The left
Really coalesced around Hillary Clinton after she failed miserably at that one
Stupid stuff to save it so there isn't any support for Hillary in awhile
This is outrageous
Stevie levels to it Alex wants to be fighting Hillary
You can't just be like all right
I'll critique her documentary or whatever
What's actually pretended to be
U-Hauls of power Eastside
So I could put a couple back you was talking about the
Recycle Atlanta
5% mortality rate
I'm getting out
Audi
Right
Insurance at Alex's Bates
Preparations
Personal
God said the time has come before this I said I just
Feeling that things are dangerous
Yet
A farmhouse
100 Balls around town
In the crappiest brush area where no one even knows where I'm at
You just loaded with horrible food
An underground safe with guns in it
So the unibody voxy got to check the Unabomber boxes in early March Alex doesn't have
Have that and a couple months ago he told a personal assistant to set this up for him
Which is weird because on January 31st this is what he said
I'm a father
Got to be in charge
Future
Outside town
In 45 Acres with a
Done saving food
Living in fear I'm living in powered
Do you have an armored out or do you not what is the deal
You know this situation I think it's
The good idea to save both
That's fair
Exactly
If you don't people knowing that you have a redoubt what's the best way to hide it
Tell them that you have a redoubt right
Sears online
Yeah you got to keep the mystery in the air
For sure Alex has word out you don't believe it
Maybe you'll leave him alone
Yeah
So I've made a bit of a point of the fact that Alex cannot pronounce the name of Brazilian president
Bolsonaro
I've made a little bit of a point of that
One thing I haven't made as much of a point of is how he also can't pronounce are.
You always pronounces it hurt again
Add so he gets a little self-conscious about the fact that he mispronounces erdogan's name
I offered
Play Islam assisted launch big invasions down face to in the euro
Oregon
Right behind it
Cause everytime whatever something Ready Gunner Sayre one
Autocorrect
House is incorrect as is his supposed linguist
Expert Daria
In Turkish the G is often pronounced with a soft W sound
Any correct way to pronounce the name of the turkey
The president is air Dewan
This actually was covered a bit in the news because when are lawn visited the White House in May 2017
Truck caps
Pronouncing it with
The G sound
And it cost a lot of folks to write articles
Consulting with linguist
The Turkish experts
Guess what all of them said his name is pronounced aw
Daria the Nets
True that's given them the wrong
Here's why she's not consulted all these matters
I think she knows
She's just like I'm not doing the bucket
Forget it's early
That that goes to the show like the level of who gives a shift your right out
Nothing ever gets checked and it just things just keep proceeding onward down the dump Athens
Roads giveaways through the show and he hasn't made note of the fact that he shaved his dumb had yet and
He brings it up
But he refuses to say that he's bald or that he shaved his head
He's trying to tease the audience
By mentioning that his appearance is different
But he wants you to go like to his
D-zone website so you could see it for your
If you haven't seen a friend for a month
And they just show up with a mustache
And don't tell you about
All you're looking
Adams just like
Dude what's with the mustache
Tell me about the mustache
What I think is going on with Alex
Just trying to use the idea that
That you look something like something
Different to tease anyone who might be listening on shortwave or on the radio to go to his website
Good going on
He just refuses to say the word balls cuz he's insecure or something
On this transmission
I wanted this morning and I said I kind of look like
A cute little Beluga
You could meet me do a cute little melodica
Things are so serious I got this morning and I said what can I do to note
Everybody
That
Pavarotti making jugs
Well it's what we've done here on are of your ready Alyssa you might want to go to Infowars.
Check it out this year then Lego something different here on the set
Other radio
My TV timer tonight imma leave it at that
Ready so
I want some bellwether
I must look like a beluga cuz I already thought of myself
Michael Greger
Okay let's get serious
Like
That sounded very serious
Yeah I think he's very seriously told the staff not to use them
Please don't make a big deal
Yes please
I hate to be fair I want to be clear
I think it doesn't look bad
I'm not going to be a dick about this be like I look you I mean I'm going to say this big dumb head
It'll take awhile to get used to but I don't think it'll
I could grow into it quite well
What you might be doing it
Puppies not cuz
The DUI is Amy
Call
Anyway Alex
Talking about the virus news
Coronavirus news
But it's too
It's absolutely too intense
How to get to Sol
He does what he does best
Just pretend he's going to go to
Coronavirus so horrible so scary for me
That
David
Not so hungry caterpillar
Not getting into it by
A lot of people around the world
I want to know your take on it
Zoe goes to the cause
And this is one of the things you really should
Do you do a show like Alex's
Like if you're like
There's big
Intense
Coronavirus news
That I need to cover
So I'm nibbling around like a caterpillar
Instead what I'm going to do is go to the cause
Because you know what happens when he goes to the calzone shoes like this very insightful and Powerful things
Loop it around APA
Is a very dumb things and he thinks they're really smart
As its first caller does
Right now
We've already had Alex establish that he thinks of his like a race
Specific bioweapon
And now it turns out
Might also be age-specific as a biome
Actually nervous
Vista are what
What I think about
The coronavirus even on this show
Directions
Lay it on me brother cuz I feel something
Joe
Day-Day keeps
Came that we shouldn't worry about it if we're young and healthy
The old p
People
Compromised
People that should worry right
What is our largest
Unfunded liability in this
Billion dollars in debt
And all I hear on the mainstream media
So yesterday
Fox News their data.
Doctor on meth
Hey aiyuk
Get this thing you should do
Unless your old don't worry about it
Joe what would he
Send it
Bigots
Answer of wealth in the
Going to occur as
The older Generation X
Generation pass
If the government was able to receive
Some of that money
We have a huge
Where this coronavirus Bang
And
You know I totally agree with you
Government
Bill Gates has set this
Dogs and other events
You better
Cooking up a vaccine for it and who owns
The Chimera virus subgroup Bill Gates fun wow you just can't make that up
Yeah you can
Have you heard anyone say
Say that yet and
Just to come out of my mouth
Disturbing Evan get up there
Closest is a video report
Corona
Specific bio-weapon
To kill the elderly before they
Coronavirus short response
Targeting the elderly
Mary
Reasonable statement because it's midnight thank you sir it's not man-made
This is how easy it is to get Alex to jump on something as like oh my God we're going to report this
There's a possibility
Oh God yeah
I guess
My my biggest feeling about that would be just like that is a demonstration
Tune of how loose
The gates are
Whatever done thought you have
Alex is going to treat it as like oh my God yes
This is probably a beta test of an age specific bio-weapon
Allegory
I haven't heard anybody talk about
Do you know
The first letter
Virus do you know what that is
The V for Vendetta
No for Virgin
Specific bio-weapon where can I post this on website at the headline
Go out there and Foxy don't get the virus
Did you watch
Belugas
So Alex gets to the trend that goes on throughout some of
This time is now
Descended into a place where he's threatened
Coming to murder people if any of his family members get Coronavirus
And it begins here and I
This is maybe an imp
Implicit or implied threat again
Obama
Kind of girl
You may recall Alex believes that Obama
Sold the virus
Do the Chinese back
Because he doesn't know how to read it makes Obama at fault for his family members
That's that's
That's how backtrack
Is it a coming back over and over again
This has an HIV delivery system but that wouldn't be enough
Got a whole bunch of different viruses together
But do different things
Yeah it's a nightmare virus
Hit you
But no one wants to discuss that no one's supposed to talk about that
That's why I am so pissed
It's not a threatening thing to say but
You saw the blind
It's time to start holding certain people
Possible.
Obama
That garbage in 2015 if I bring my coronavirus file place while three employees
I needed that
Leaving aside that I wasn't even at the most basic understanding of how HIV works I wanted
When he says it
Virus has an HIV deliveries
This is just him not understanding the difference between the furrion cleavage in the Ace to cleavage Scituate
In the past viruses like the Coronavirus
Those were taken in by the body through a stew
Sites
Weaving device
The Quirk of this one
According to that one report
That one study
I was at a to cleave with you if you're inside
Which is also true of hi
This is not the same thing as the coronavirus having HIV delivery system or anything like that
It's just a different way that things are absorbed
Into the body
There are many things that use furin cleavage other than h
From the normal flute
Ebola from dengue fever
The anthrax
I was just pretending that the coronavirus has something from HIV added to it
But in reality he just doesn't understand the topic
He's covering it all
Also there's literally zero evidence.
This coronavirus is man-made there's no evidence
Ton of different viruses in one
That's all just a product valances demented imagination
He's reporting as fact to his audience
The article uses to prove that Obama sold the virus
The China Cruise literally nothing of the sort
When he says there's a big sister when Obama did
Did that what he's lying about is the fact that he found an article about 11 in North Carolina
Experimenting with giving a Coronavirus
Function in terms of that Ace to cleavage
And how there was a debate in the scientific
Community by whether or not
Experiments like that were ethical
He can provide literally zero evidence
Support those claims that he makes
There was a big
About Obama selling the virus China because it never happened
It's a lie
That being said I think Alex is trying to threaten to kill Obama if one of his relatives dying of the coronavirus but he also doesn't want to say the
Is that might involve another conversation with a lawyer
Yeah I would definitely
I keep that one choir
Notes
Seems very easy to stick a uranium 12 some
Took zero time at all Friday like
Obama's uranium one let's move on it's his fault
Come on everybody look over here tingling and one of the things that you'll see over the course
These episodes
Is that there is a a crystallization of it down to just these blunt talking point
There's no debate about it
This is been determined this is
Decided
And just like eight a dogged
Distance in repetition of it
So the audience just
Gets the sound bite
And you'll see that over the course of the
Spots
He comes back
And
Happy music
Is it is
Feeling good
The course you belong to
To the city
And I've noticed a trend of the Alex
Can't not give a speech
Over that saxophone
How do you not give a speech over saxophone if you got the
I don't
Dispute that it's
Very humid
You just it's like the siren song
You can't not talk about space
And like human destiny
Supposed to do stuff.
Beat Deathstroke
List of all the cedar
AI machine
Nothing Hammer going to win and then
Next Level the transformation will be upon us
We belong the stars of God
From which we came
And that is where we'll go to camp
Star2star the universe
Before us is that wasn't Alex Jones
It looks like the racism and
Jesus everything that falls for that
Ramblin Rover saxophone about
Our destiny is to
To the Stars
Wake up really really ready to go every board
Could do some time on the treadmill
Really get me pumped up
So Alex thinks another call and I don't know how to tell you
What what's going on here other than
I think this dude is super rude
So yes I was in Costco
Getting ready I went by a bunch of
For the paper into things before
Crotch really hurts and
Read my phone had to show going on sitting on my pocket so I could hear it I wasn't even headphones
And I
Free listening to who's that talking
At first I thought
We might get some slack but
Alex Jones
Your eyes. Wide open and she says I'm really I thought he was off the air
Round
I told her I explained
Told her where to go she wrote down your band.
Wards.com
Alex Spence a knot
Insignificant portion of the show expounding on how the man and the globalist want everyone to think
Think he's off the air
How do you stop
Everyday you meet people think that he's off their but then he tells them they can
Can still find a mundane forwards website and they're so happy to hear
This caller is what Kik
Fix that off that whole rant have a few thoughts
First
Is it I don't care what you're playing
If you're walking around in the store listen
Things I headphones girl f****** a******
If it's music you're an a******
If the liberal talk show you're an a******
If it's Alex Jones
A man who's known to launch into rant about demons raping
Children with little warning
You're a bigger
A****** family show that you're walking right it's like I'm playing on your phone
As you walk through the store
G******** video on the last show
You can't play that in public
No matter what this guy's story is about if it start at if it starts them casually mentioning that he was losing to Alex's Schodack
Costco without headline
F*** this dude
Second there've been a lot of points made about her Panic buying with
Things you don't need to
Panic buy is probably one of the more damaging things people can do right now
It's the disruption of the demand chain they can have just as many negative consequences as the supply chain disruption
Can have
Based on this guy sent you stocking up on toilet paper I'm going to say that he was not engaging in responsible preparation
Sensibly stocking up on mountains upon Mountain
The toilet paper minuscule amount of stocking up on toilet paper
I don't know
Leaving just like
Where the toilet paper be just a few rolls
I have no idea how much was buying but it's
It's not it wasn't a good
Finally and most
Importantly if you've been on air for
26 years and you've built up a fan base that
Do you like the sides you must be completely off Erica's you get
Kicked off social media something
Even exist when your career began
Then I don't know what to tell you
Something is wrong with that fan base
Either they're so hopeless that they can
Can't find her s*** unless it's shoveled right in front of their faces
Or they didn't like you enough
Enough to seek you out once the YouTube algorithms work
Constantly pushing your videos on
Either way that's not a solid fan base
And I wouldn't blame the globe
For that that's just a byproduct of making a dumb show
It attracts a fickle
Type of crowd yeah it turns out info Warriors are very
Capricious in nature
Nobody would have
Came back of it now as I was listening around the time Alex got banned from social media and key
He knew it was coming
Right to prepare
He was promoting his newsletter
You trying to drive traffic to his own website and
I guess people just didn't follow
If all these people think that you were too
Just off air
Yeah
I'm not into it
I mean
Just removed from like the first page to the second page of Google will do
Destroy anybody but a fanbase
She's going to be
Like
If they over there
Absolutely
Anyway
Alex believe
That the CDC is doing so
Some sort of a cover
If I understand correctly
The things that they did
Is try to make
Is that the coronavirus situation not seem very bad by not rolling out
MBA providing test make the numbers of cases lower
And then Trump wouldn't take it seriously and then they would
Put out all the test there be a ton of people
A ton of cases
Trump look like a dick
Brilliant
Now in this neck I see no flaws
Alex
Kind of implies
I'm by Plies I mean directly says
The Trump is involved in this cover-up
Just not good
Killing members of Alex's family
He might be involved in the cover-up of the things that leads to Alex's notarized
Damn
But I think all this is beyond it
They're they're not sitting out there
Gas station
I know it's been really a smarty is tied into
A six-month-old a bunch of people
Steve pieczenik also the guy who said that he was patient zero of the Coronavirus
Himself himself. He's very good at
Suspiciously
Not sure that you're with anyone else biotic
What an idiot
So there's a cover-up going on in that Trump is complicit
Alex of course has historically been against government cover-up on account of you know how the government shouldn't cover things
To cover this up
People go crazy
You and I
Didn't know about
The cover-up butter regular
It's weird for him
To say make a statement like that like
The executive
Federal government
Engaged in a cover-up is putting people at risk
I understand why he's doing it it's totally cool
Hey Alex Jones 1995 Alex Jones
So we finally get to the point where Alex brings up that he has shaved his head
Inside it turns out
He does sort of give Ariza
I'm like ready to get in a fight
That's
Symbolizes
He said you had some people don't grab your hair
Image of this is not normal
We're not normal Waters here we're in a war
You all know that as well
Play Dan hysteria Nono
You're concerned
Because our gut know something big going on
What is it
How is that not Hysteria
I shaved my head to give a
Typo metaphorical symbols
Literally in
Trench warfare grab my hair while we're fighting
Did everybody knows that it's coming from his gut
Rest area
Comes from
We all know this heinous and there we go
Inconceivably why Alex shaved his head was to make him look like a soldier or something
Give another reason later in a white guy shaves
Because he's looking for a fight that usually doesn't go well
Yeah
Don't like it
It's not good he gives another reason later that I actually think it's probably more believable and we'll get to that in a minute
Before we do though
Alex is going to take another really stupid color
First of all
One of the
After he's out there
Mike
Concern is when the weather gets warm
Welcomes
Oh my gosh I can spread it it's awesome
What happens when you supercharge
Mosquitoes
What the Coronavirus
Hours
Malaria
Stella down I think
A race car
Call a******
Couple of assholes here
Get it so right now there's no evidence of mosquitoes
Can carry or transmit the coronavirus and there's a very good chance that it's
Just not even possible
There's actually a good tea
Teachable moment
Mosquitoes can transmit things like a bowl of malaria dengue fever
Primarily because those things can infect the mosquitoes themselves
The only thing that I'm a
Mosquito puts into a person when it bites them as their saliva
So no matter what
Blood they have ingested it doesn't matter
That's not what's going to get transmitted to the
The B person
This is because there's a 22 proboscis
It's the dopest keto uses
The feed on your blood
One tube is the intake tube that sucks your blood
And you don't get
Exposed to anything from that it's a one-way Street
The other tube is used to
Inject saliva that makes you like not feel the bite
The
Itchiness
Took this life of mosquitoes
The vector that you need to be
Concerned with for the potential of MS
Mosquito-borne
This is one of the reasons that HIV cannot be spread by mosquitoes
They don't possess
The correct cells in their body to serve as hosts
With HIV
I'm surviving mosquitoes
And can't be transmitted through their saliva
Historically diseases in the coronavirus family such as Mercy
Since ours
Those aren't things that are known to be spread by mosquitoes
At this point all experts I can find who have commented on the matter or uniform
The position that there's no evidence
Since right now that this is a vector of transmission
They were seen or are likely to see
Mosquito borne diseases are no joke though
And they're very serious threat ever live
Malaria is a lot of places very.
But this doesn't appear to be one of those Circle
Circumstances where mosquitoes are going to play a huge role
Obviously anything
Impossible but this caller what he's doing
He's just coming up with a horrible scenario thing what about that and Alex's there is like my God I love taking calls
Every time Alex
Scholars Khaled we get a nice little like Magic School Bus
Alright he came up with some terrible ideas now let's go inside the body and discover how it is that people actually
I knew this cuz I had a buddy of mine who's a doctor
You and I had a long conversation about it cuz I didn't know
Understand that whole thing of like why can't something be transmitted by mosquitoes
I'm grateful you explain it to me I had to come in here acting
My guy do whatever
But the issue here is
Coloring with Alex are doing is just like it's
Baseless fear
This is hysteria this is making a nightmare scenario
Acting like there's any reason to think that this is
I don't think to be concerned back
Hysterical
Alex
Hey Alex movies are predict
Programming have you ever seen the bird
Oh
Nothing
So this is a big one the Coronavirus
Earlier Alex said
That
Trump was involved
In the cover-up
And I kind of thought that that was just a straight thing he said
Clearly here
This is not just something he said he thinks
The Trump is probably covering this up
March 5th Thursday 2020 242
Coronavirus is the big one so far
11 man made pretty total for your government using it to create hysteria and lockdowns
Play it down I understand why I can't fault him for it
The testing they are covering it up that's even in the news now and the left is using it against the president just like
We predicted
In that clip
You can hear it absolutely incoherent message Alex is trying to spread to his listener
Let's break this down
Piece by piece
It starts with him saying that it's official the coronavirus has the big
It's a gigantic world event and the big one
Whatever that be
It's man-made
Which it's not and the government is using it to create a stereo
So the hysteria is bad
Except Alex is running the shower he's allowing its guests
Declare that the virus is Airborne
Alexa call or say that everyone's going to get it from mosquitoes
And let's not forget that he had his science expert Mike Adams
Come on his show and say
2/4 Humanity
There will only be lone survivors
So hysteria is bad but also the show is nothing but Hysteria
Yes then Alex says the Trump is engaged in in
Solicit with this government cover-up of the virus situation actually suppressing the countries testing capabilities
This is a literal government cover-up of a Public Health crisis that Alex is describing
He's as a canceled job for doing it
His idea is the Trump is trying to
Check the stock market
Apparently if that's
The justification anything can be done
Covering up a pandemic and allowing it to get worse putting the public at risk its okay
I was trying to protect money
That seems to be Alex's position important
Then Alex complains that the left is using this against Trump
Just like you predict
So apparently if Trump is engaged in a
Conspiracy cover up it could literally kill Americans because he knows the
It's a bad stock market would make him look bad jeopardize his chances in the election
And the media dares point out the ways it is
Is Administration
Has not responded well to the outbreak
The media is bad
This is a completely bootlicking authoritarian respect
In one Fell Swoop Alex is establishing the virus as a gigantic threat
He asserts
Trumpism
The American Health System for being able to deal with it appropriately
And if the media criticism criticizes him for it
They're bad
The cover-up
Is good
The criticism is bad
This is over out in the open dictatorship
This is not
The end
He's covering it up in order to stop master
Hysteria
Right correct
Because the reason the stock market will go down
Psistaria
And Alex
Appreciate
And understands why Trump
What is covering it up
Anything's mesentery is bad
And he is also spreading message
He doesn't seem to have a real consistent position or what
Hysteria at
The struggle
These words
So here on the 5th
Alex has
Francis Boyle
Come back on
His bio lab
So
Francis Boyle shows his Bona fides
And is
Resistance to reading
By indicating
But he believes that that North Carolina Lab at the UN
NC Chapel Hill created and then Obama sold
So that's great and then
Join Stewart Roads in the group of people who are erroneously saying that this is Airborne
Yes I do think
Like this was offensive
Logical
Warfare
Weapon
That was originally developed
Up there at the University of North Carolina lab
Using the
SARS coronavirus which was already weaponized
To begin with
And enduring it with game also
Ocean
Indeed it even travels through air
Alex is not just
The question
Droplets that's why
Human excrement
Read this all disease we had
Reports are that coming out of Hong Kong and China now
First of all it's embarrassing the Francis Boyle is still pushing this
Conspiracy about the lab at UNC Chapel Hill creating a Coronavirus
We've been over this in great detail but that
Sweetness reading of a study
From 2015
He's presenting himself as an expert he has every reason to know that said he has nothing to do with this current out
He also should know the difference between Airborne transmission and
Fecal-oral transmission of a virus
The possibility that the coronavirus can be transmitted by fecal-oral
Contact me and you should wash your hands after going to the bathroom or handling poo
There are some indications that this virus May transmit that way as was also the case with SARS
So it's appropriate to exercise caution on that front
However
This does not qualify as Airborne transmission
Just because the virus can be transmitted through
Feces doesn't mean that
Being around feces is going to transmit the virus
You still have to contact the feces
II
Feel so much like we're in the 15th
CenturyLink
Oh well of course
Because of the smell you know that this is unhealthy
If you stand next to poop
Done
Put him in a plague outfit I'm I'm done with him having a black plague doctor mask and get him the f*** out
Boyle's handling this is supremely irresponsible and if the media didn't already ignore him when he pretends to be an expert already there
To be a good reason for them to start
So they're your humors are out of proportion
That's why you got the virus you need
To pray more
Do boils going down this road
And Alex brings up something that he saw
Recently trying to indicate like this is
Proof that it's Airborne but I would argue it
Actually the opposite
Did you see where Merkel try to shake hands with her interior Minister he wouldn't think we were saying it doesn't sound like shaking hands in the air
Tristan Hemsworth
It's in the air you're exactly correct
If it's merkel's Minister didn't want to shake hands that isn't indication
Embedded
More like
Angela Merkel was trying to infect
Tim and when he
He didn't
Shake her hand she was like
And we breathed on him until 8.
That's stupid and that's very generous of you
Anyway Francis Boyle wants you to know
That you cannot trust
Any expert
On the matter of the Coronavirus
For Alex to be
Anyting 8110 Nazi scientist
Freak the f*** out we're all going to die
Look up your butthole
Believe
We can trust
This
Teams are in Washington DC this team of feds
Score up to their eyeballs in this
Tupac
We advised the American people
How to protect
Themselves and their families
Prominence
I would
Suggested what needs to be done is
The American people have
How to get organized
On a steak
A local basis
Even going down to the cities and communities and Villages and whatever
Put together a team of
Medical doctor
Microbiologist
Public Health
Official
Be sure to do your due diligence on them
And make sure
That they have not accepted one penny
Maxie B
Biological warfare work
From the United States governor
Good idea
Whatever
You're trying to do
Course we can't believe the whoe there we know they're up to their eyeballs here
That's pretty much everybody
Okay
Local a
It gets muddy when you start throwing in nobody who's ever been involved in it
Any research that has like a federal government grant
Even worked with the World Health Organization of the CDC
And none of those people
It's going to make things difficult. What you got to do is you got to get together with your
Small community get the
Family doctor
Who is of course an expert in coronavirus as we all know
The microbiologist that most small-town
Tabnak
Naturally along with public health officials
Better well paid for by Noma
This is very very dumb
You just need
100000 Francis boils all over the country
So we have this last clip
Hear from the
The fifth and what's going on here
Is
If you'll recall
Back at the end of January
When Alex was pitching Theory
About the virus
One of his theories was
That it was the Deep state or Trump
Release the bioweapon on China as payback for Fentanyl
Right yeah that was a good one this was stupid
Wow do stupid
But Alex stopped
Pursuit on that line
Until now
Could this be, sold it to China
Could this be a
You ask Global as base
Bioweapon to launch of China for their fentanyl attack
I'm not positive
What do you think
People are saying they like in the past
But I'm not surprised that was me in the past
I floated this. Couple months ago and that I just and then
People are talking on the street I'm not saying that I heard it on the radio a couple
Once again
Aha. Delivered
Is in the grocery store with no headphones in
Listening to himself
Like a dick
Yep so we jump to the six
And this is a Friday
Alex has
Big news
Stokin the show
All hell is breaking loose as we told you five weeks ago this
Virus is the big one
That the globalist we're going to
Was the end of the world
Oh-so Mike Adams
At school
Reminder to call blister promoting it is the end of the world that is exactly what like atoms
Did so centralized anime who does everything that you say you're against
If you change what your against
Then they are also changing with Eric
It's tough to keep track of
So
Alex is basing this starting to show off with a air raid siren and is the biggest
Thing in the world all hell breaking loose because he's gotten
Some news
Now the models are
Millions and millions dying or the new
Computer model out
The shallows
July
Again these are just models other lands at models
2% weight
Yesterday you understood with that 15% what
What I can't can't miss you without intentionally
Are you know
That awareness is in his head
Wow
This is meme
Yeah mean person
He's full of s***
Also this is not a professionally created computer model
This was done by Mike Adams
The news published on natural news
No one has reviewed his methodology no one is checked any of his work it's
As far as I know this is
Maybe not even the professional computer model it's just Mike Adams worked out any put numbers in a f****** see
Animated
The more and more you peel back the layers on this ship the more you see that Alex is just completely relying on Mike to supply
With information that then he can he can then launder
And set you know
Mike created this estimate official release
From a credible Source in new computer
Sure
And to be clear Alex does later clarify that this is Mike's
Model but he establishes it at the
Top of the show is just this new computer model with million
Cool
You want to know how unethical it is for Alex to use Mike's
Model like this
Mike Adams on article about the modeling he did on his website literally says quote
The bottle is not yet. Viewed and should not be cited as predictions or fat
Facts
Alex reposted this article on Infowars I guess you just forgot to read that part
Amazing levels of s******* Behavior here
Graph on an XY access with just going up and he's like yeah
Druid and crannies like
I know this isn't fact but you can see how bad it's going
It's also the article says
This model predictive scenario where nothing is done
To contain the virus
In reality this model is therefore not predicted for the real world over the long run for the simple reason that such strong and revenge
Engines are inevitable
It's almost like this bottle was created solely to give Alex a headline to cover its carries audience about while he ignores
The part about this not being predictive in the real world
And I just shows how many deaths Mike
Mike thinks will happen
Literally nothing is done
Do not going to happen
What years ago video of playing
You gave him simcity-2000 would like an alien Covenant
This isn't predictive of how the world would actually react to an alien I'm just showing you what would happen how cheap alien
You cover it
So this article Ends by shooting on the CDC FDA and NIH
Before signing off with quote
In essence you're on your own
Read pandemic. News if you want to live
Like legit
F*** the wild wow
But yeah that sounds
I was able to find an article from February 14th on Staten news about computer modeling of the virus outbreak
According to this article the most recent figures show the range of 550,000
24.4 million cases of the virus
In simulator
But it's important to know these are cases
She's not deaf
The article also points out that modeling is often accurate but so often not
Princeton c2040
CDC model for the Ebola outbreak in West Africa predicted
Between 550000 and 1.4 million case
But the actual number ended up being way lower
A 28600
That's whale
Is Wailord
I'm not going to engage too much with
Computer modeling side of things primarily because there's a wide range of numbers you can get on that front and I don't think it's useful to people who are
Positions
Where those models are useful for their work
For you and I and most people listening to
It's an abstract number without a greater contacts
I want the model is simulator
Way more important to me is that here on March 6th
Alex is back to using that 15% number for blansett is if it was a total mortality for
The day prior
He understood
But it was severe cases that were already demonia and a very small sample size
Alex has no idea what he's talking about
Using sources however he feels
Depending on what feeling is trying to evoke from his audience
You know that you chose an understanding of the limitations of the Lancet study on Thursday
Then he's using it to scare people on Friday
The factory showed that Awareness on Thursday leaves me convinced that on Friday he's consciously lying to his audience
It's about that what that number really mean
You consciously and intentionally lying to his audience
It's to scare them about the outbreak
Which is a normal humans call
Listeria
We learned on our last episode that Alex believes that Donald Trump
Secretly declared a national emergency
Didn't see a month ago the response
To him
Declaring National Emergency
I'm not even going to try
So Alex does still believe that
That although Alex
On the on the 50 did say the Trump was complicit
In this cover-up
CDC
President Cyrus emergency declaration today
That's what it is. It's emergency
Emergency declaration
We told you about that
On Monday
Eminem
National
Declaration
Quietly been doing a lot to deal with it
So that funding bill wasn't a declaration of an emergency
No matter how much Alex might want
A 10
That was a bill that was rushed through Congress
The Trump sign
It was not a declaration of anything it's
It's just authorization
To fund the billions of dollars to be used in developed
Open treatment
Al Public Health measures
The only person
Who voted against
Memphis Belle in the Senate was you guessed it
Alex's old buddy Rand Paul
Show themselves to be more and more of a dick
Everyday
Villanova's Ron shoes
Just f***
You knew everybody else was going to vote it you did it just to get attention you're at
Child
Trump is not declared a National Emergency neither public nor Secrets there was a public health emergency was declared back at the end of
January but that's a very different thing as we discussed in our last episode
I was just making this s*** up and lying to his audience about
Is emergency funding bill
In order to
Further his
Convoluted
And contradictory
Narrative
It's about what Trump is doing
It just doesn't get more authoritarian then
Then like
Blaming the media for criticize
Trump for doing a bad job
While at the same time
Insisting that he
Secretly
Doing a good job
Even though all evidence
Suggest that he's doing a bad job
And you yourself claimed that he
He's in a cover-up
Of him doing such a bad
Ja
And you're like
I don't call I don't understand that guy understand why you ever confused position
What I would I left out of there was obviously that Obama soda virus
Send it all his fault
So Mike Adams shows up cuz he's made this model
Cool right
Cool
Great
So whether they get to talkin about
This
The cover-up
ICDC
That Trump is in office
Mike has an interesting Theory
What's that real quick
This is a big question
How can you just be in on the cover-up
If you're the
President running the CDC
Deleting it right
We are
I want to talk about that he wants to talk about bikes
The new Theory
Sabotage
Left behind
Trap has been set up
To be blamed
What kind
DC has always hated
This is a revenge and love CDC just got to
That's right so now I guess Trump's not even on the cover-up
They're hurt feel like they're punching me in the face over and over and over again and I can't do it
This is violently
So far up to this point Alex has not acknowledged the whole thing about Trump in the cdc's budge
A lot of people have made accusations that Trump cut CDC budget
Something that Trump did to cut off their bioweapons
Production money
The CDC was furiously
City cut their budgets
They bungled the response to the Coronavirus
Payback
Superman narrative standpoint this is putting a hat on a
Alice already has the hole of the globalist released the bioweapon to crash the economy and embarrass Trump narrative
There's no reason to a subplot about scientist being mad about a decreased budget
Get personal you bring it back down to the personal this is disgruntled know
If this were part of the script that I was editing I would say cut it out
Just get rid of it it's not adding anything it's kind of confusing.
It's really them
I don't know it's go. Anymore
I hope this gets better I want there to be no love story in the CDC we're also Obama had a secret
That with up agent straw
Yeah that's what I want
I got
Problem here is the Trump didn't cut the CDC funding
That's a messy people keep repeating but it's not true
You'll be true to save it until he signed that emergency
The funding bill there wasn't enough money going to the right places
And until he declares a National Emergency a lot of the funds that could be used
For all this stuff
Unavailable
Because they can only be used in those
Kathy got their butt
It's not that he's cutting their budget it's that his actions are withholding
To an extent
It is proposed budget for the fiscal year 2021 there's apparently an app
Approximately 16% decrease in the cdc's budget
But this budget has not yet been approved by Congress
Send us is not act
Many folks including some Democratic presidential candidates
So got details wrong on this and dust
Lots of people think Trump actually cut funds
For the CDC
Including people like Alex and Mike Adams apparel
They're a bunch of other things in play here that are
Just more
Kind of stupidity and negligence
Then outright malicious action on Trump's part
Princeton to 2018 the capabilities of the cdc's global.
Disease outbreak
Prevention efforts were reduced by 80%
A lot of people interpreted that is Trump cutting 80 per-cent of their budget
But in reality was the result of the existing allotted funds for that program running out
And Trump and Congress
Not making sure that it was fully funded
That seems like a negligence thing yeah I could argue that it's
Symantec said that he's cutting the bud we're sure
But it's not
Quite the same
Also in 2018 rear Admiral Timothy ziemer
The senior director for Global Health security and bio-defense
The National Security Council was removed from his position
His whole team was
Expanded
According to Snopes
They are people who are quote
Responsible for coordinating response to a pandemic
Add after the firing
Zebra was not replaced
And the team remain disband
Okay it's hard to say exactly who is responsible for this though weather was Trump or the head of the
Security account
Audrey doing a reorganization
Zacian But ultimately
States where the buck stops so is responsible for that but how much is that is he didn't
No that is a possibility
Don't know absolutely that one could be a negligent thing and again right that comes down to is semantic thing did he
Decrease
The viability of that team
Operate
Or did he just
Not realize that team was gone
And failed to ree-ree
Appoint
Yeah I mean in this case though I also find it like the argument of whether or not this was do we have a militia
Isis leader or no
Incompetent leader is that
Kind of debate
Text to me
Nmd effect
Ultimately
Right on that level agree with you but
To saying his narrative about the
Angry CDC employees
I agree with
Ultimately the matter surrounding these things are far more
Complicated that sang the Trump cut
The CDC pot
That's a grotesque
Oversimplification
But you see the way it's the way that our understand
You know that he needs to spend
Because he believes the Trump straight-up cut the cdc's budget
Because if you do
Make Trump look bad and dumb
So he decided to pitch The Narrative of spiteful doctors in the CDC allowing an outbreak
Spread cuz they want their money
This is week
Yeah I week stuff I really I really think that that makes
Them the most
Evil people in history
Leica CDC well
I'm just going to let the world get f***** up by a virus because
Cuz I needed
2 billion more in funding for the
The fiscal year of 20
20 character motivations don't make sense
Good in this case
So Mike
Has
Yes Biz model
And it's Alex has pitched
At the start of the show as a like professional computer models not attach to Mike Adams
By now it's clear that it's Mike's and Mike is talking about his model
And even he has to tell Alex that you need to change the headline on the story
About this
Think that this is a
A prediction
That has no qualifiers
This is this is a model of 100
You're coming on
With alert projection model
U.s. Buy
July 4th
We need to make sure the sub-headline is there the sub-headline up there is
Okay awesome oh no what year so that line was
That's right even f****** Mike Adams realizes that the way Alex was reporting on this was
Sensational and
That's me
At sign
Yep that is
Bad I understand what you're saying but I want to make sure my listeners don't understand
You're really giving up the game fine we'll put that sub headline up there or whatever
Make it smaller
So that's a point of disagreement between him and Alex
How to use his
Models and as well as their globalist ideology sure Mike Mike Michael global
Globalist
So there's another thing
And that is this notion
The secret National Emergency that Trump declared
Mike doesn't believe that
National Emergency
100%
It will happen
They will be extreme severe restrictions on domestic air travel
Road travel
Toby cities under quarantine
There will be roadside check
Points in certain areas
There will be
Empty universities empty School
Campuses
Corporate
Corporations will send their employees home in massive numbers much larger than anything
We are about to experience a shutdown
Have American society beginning around
June
July
Going to be the summer of Rage
Hell in America
So close
You could almost taste it
Sommer Ray
Sprint.com
Autism slam dunk but some of the things that he saw that mean he's super Sensational in a
It's over for Humanity
But he's
These things that you say
Conceivable
In terms of if things
Things go down negative handled correctly there could be a massive disruption right
Things that are normal life
Yeah
It's over like that is
Time I'm I'm not I'm not playing that quip to necessarily mock like
Schools will be closed
So Mike has this model that is 2. something Million Dead if nothing is done
But nothing is done is not a conceivable thing to happen in reality so the model is
Useless
Except as a way to
Put a big number here to scare people for Alex
Mike actually believes that the numbers are way way
It's way worse than the numbers I've already
Because
I don't know what's wrong I don't know why it's being intentionally bought
Because they're covering it up from
President to blame him that when it explodes
No he's covering it up
Russia failed impeachment failed this is our next attempt to CDC is trying to take out Trump
That's what's happening
Mike Peggy so much wow well hopefully work repair
Help for the word Festival of oneself or I
For the worse to try to overthrow America
I just
Read this is
It's it's Madness
Did the way that this is James from proposition on the the cover-ups
Tonneau cover up aimed at Trump by Angry CDC scientists
Who want their money
I don't even I can't even
I can't even handle it
I would like to tell every sci-fi author whose like
The only thing that will bring Humanity together is a threat to all of us if
Sedalia comes or if a virus
F*** off
Half of humanity can be like
Does the president forever
It's sad
Saint Philip K Dick's did not predict this
So Alex
Get back to talking about this this whole situation he believes that the Chinese of course so the government released this
On purpose
This is f***** up
Try to do it on purpose
On accident now
This lets them clampdown their use control flies
Dependent
Our supply chain
Because
We're dependent on that
Viruses
So if I understand the narrative is being presented now
The Chinese government release the bioweapon on themselves in order to help further the goals of the CDC who are mad because their funding was cut
How many goddamn moving pieces does this stupid conspiracy have
Ocean's 11 of virus outbreak
Who let Tom Clancy
Bi-Rite reality now what
Insperity
Is overbooked
BBW
Yeah and some weird sex scene
Indigo.com without it looking
Also you'll hear there at the end Alex trying to explain. I think he's trying to explain the outbreak in Iran saying that Islam
Pharmacist infected themselves or possibly that's his explanation for how he just got to other
He's unclear about what he's talking about at this point
Again if I were an editor
And I was like this is a draft
Screenplay I would say go ahead and cut out the Islamic terrorists subplot you don't need that to explain the spread of a virus
What appropriate steps aren't taken
Also Alex wasn't told about quote islamists to we're going to
Infect themselves months ago by Army sources
Like he claims in that clip
He was told about it on February 8th
By Mike Adams
Any enemy Nations
Does Iran or no
North Korea
Can simply send
10 human volunteer
Here's to the Ohana
Don't get infected
They can bring it back
They can Harvest it from their saliva they can wrap a
Located in egg yolk
If you pay attention all of Alex's information is laundered
He pretends he has these sources in their their mysterious nature and their official
Status Cube he's playing some kind of credibility
But 10 times out of 9 it's just some dumb bulshit one of his friends said on the show
But Alex is pretending came from whistleblower
Really transparent
Pathetic
See-through a little bit
Very
So I was confused like
I initially thought that he was
Cindy's
Islamists
Is you trying to
Explain why there's an outbreak in a rod
And then you talk to your Lieutenant
And by that I mean I listen to little more okay well there's that
Explains what he means it turns out he's just a
F****** racist
This comes in
Where the stars looking for delivery
Sneeze on a few people now man
He was probably putting it into the food
So turns out out to talking about Italy when he decided to blame Muslim
Spreading the virus
He's just straight-up making things up
The first cases of coronavirus in Italy were Chinese couple from Wuhan who arrived in Italy on January
23rd
Alex is racist narrative is based on a misrepresentation of a story about a Pakistani man living in Italy who apparently did not
La quarantine himself after
Testing positive for the virus
The circumstance
Does a good story or not clear so I can't speak
Do that
Gigantic Lee
For someone to make that
Person's intention was to infect
The story was published first
Italian Outlet called
Chorus
On
It covered this Pakistani man but at no point did it claim that this man was the first person in the country with the Coronavirus
That story was that used as a source for historians
Quote pro-west blog
Free West
Media
With the headline quote
Italian Italy's patient zero
Migrant who delivered food at home
They completely add the patient zero thing to
The story which was not reflect
Didn't their initial source
Because this is a Blog dedicated to demonizing non-white immigrants
Funtrivia Alex's old buddy Paul Craig Roberts is a contributor to freewestmedia
Which of the prize no one
He was also a writer for the white nationalist publication vdare
From 2000
Wait a way to keep popping up guy you're doing you're doing good evil got to work
So from that point after this story was embellished it was picked up a game subtraction and white nationalist circles but honestly
Even the comments on freewestmedia don't seem to buy the story with one of them calling it
This is as
So often the case one more piece of evidence that Alex gets his news from
I'm completely racist sources
And then
Ones that don't engage in any kind of fact check
And also offense
Sometimes y
Bushel racist agenda
Also
I guess you know too
In order for Alex's narrative to make any sense
They have to be Pakistani as long as a sleeper cells employed his food delivery people in Italy
Thor working with the Chinese government in order to
Embarrass Trump
In the cdc's involved because they want their money
Thread on this one Global conspiracy
It's the big one
Working together
An inexplicable way
Yeah
If this wasn't about like a really serious topic this would be really fun
Yeah yeah
And it's very races
Alex is doing this stuff's Project Camelot
Aliens are real
Like this is exactly how you be like this is irresponsible Behavior
We actually have Xenomorphs outside of our home
He has these established
Pieces of
Right
You've got that it's man-made
Short you've got that they sold at the
The Chinese
He's mad
No one is to
Talking about it we're getting ready to clamp down on party are many parts of world using this phone
Virus is the pre-tax but nobody made by 11 Labs Obama
We are
This is where I get kind of personally offended
Is like Alex is up here complaining about on no one's talking about how the virus is man-made and how about them so China
Places like CNN and MSNBC
They're not talking about that stuff cuz it's all bulshit he created out of thin air using lunatic sources
And lying about various artists
There's no reason
For them to be covering that
But we are that's what we're here
Recovering the idea of the viruses man-made
Ground covering
You claim that Obama sold it to China
What is using Alex's own sources to show he's full of s***
I started to have like what I listen to this is her to do some like flight to Fancy's
Where is just me and says that he read his own sources on air and then you barked at him
I got caught up in my in my head about that
Dream dream dream
Take some calls now on the
Michelle and he gets a caller
That really really bummed me out
Here's my question
I want you and Mike Adams.
Rosanna Pansino
And I really plan my lifestyle around what you got
What a bummer I plan my lifestyle around with you and Mike Adams
Same
Caller wants to cuddle
Please the caller wants to know when is it
Time to bug out
When is it time to just hit the woods
And Alex has
And then this caller actually has an interesting follow-up question
That Alex does not answer well okay
Bugging out I don't want to use the term cell
Quarantine
Self-isolate
How do we know when it's getting
Take it on our own to just be
And get away from the world if I was retired and didn't have to be in Austin I would already be preparing the next E-Waste Ali
Fidget exponential
Then bombing as soon as possible
Okay well here's what I worry about when I watch your show
I try to take
Mikey from y'all
But I still see you sending Olin and Savannah and Millie and
Rally's in Canby
Inventions
And
They're not wearing masks and it doesn't look like they're very
We've actually had those discussions now
Are you watching very closely I mean I've already canceled one trip and tell people that
Okay
That's a pretty good rebuttal question
That was a very insightful follow-up yeah it's better follow up
The moderators of Seattle now time immediately to bug out about didn't
Have to leave
Try and protect his his staff without
Weiser are you eating that Grill if it's cuz
Not yet I love chicken fries
Weeks baby
I didn't eat Burger King yesterday nobody talked about that
Stop
So in the same way that Alex has been really preoccupied with really trivial matters
Reuters headlines that he read on the last episode
Mike Bloomberg
Eating habits
Homeless people
Asher Asher
He has another one here on this episode and here's a little Clippers
I'm talking about it
Go back to your call. Just a moment
On this last hour
I shouldn't have
But it just did really captured my attention
Beginner sickening wave
Williams
That's his only crime I never suggested American
51 million from Bloomberg
Million
Ad spend
Now let's just pull back from that for a mama
How's this going to go
You could give $1000000 to 500 people about a million dollars
327000000
Anybody knows that
Yep
Guess what the New York Times now doesn't come out defend themselves
Paul Joseph Watson article
Blah blah
Math blah blah
Pasquale
Watch Predator humiliating 1 million
For every American Sales everyone that first credit thing
500 million does not give 327 million people a million dollars that gives 500
Doubling down
They said he could easily afford to give everyone in America a million dollars that was their point she says
I knew that was what I said was
Knowing that would
Billion dollars
327 million
It's 327 trillion-dollar
I don't know what's going on here I don't like hearing Alexei numbers
What's up Alex
Two segments
It's on this and I don't think that's an accurate
I didn't cut clips of it earlier because as I was listening to it I just decided to ignore that nonsense
But when he brought it back up I realize this is important to Alex so I will honor him by Chaka
Episode Alex
Has been trying to score some points
Exxon
Fun of a segment Brian Williams did with Mara gay
Where they
Incorrectly asserted that instead of giving
Spending on ads
Bloomberg could have given everyone in the United
Midstates $1000000
It was a very embarrassing and pretty much everyone clowned on the segment but Alex is using it as some kind of proof that the media is evil and trying
Change math
Or something
Not entirely sure
I did not know Brian Williams was still on TV I really thought that he I thought that thing took him down still around
So what it really is is a high-profile example of someone in the media getting something wrong in a very Elementary
Freeway and Alex knows that he has to make the most of
Turn on the globalist
Might be as imaginary enemies but from a dollar store
Sandpoint is real rivals or any other thing people might watch
This gives the minutes
A chance to attack
So anyway this
Segment was Williams & gaydos cussing a tweet posted by Washington
Post writer
Mekita Rivas
Which got the math wrong which then they should have mirror
In the aftermath of the segment Rivas tweeted that she met Bloomberg could have given everyone a million dollars and not noticing
All of his money
Which is also in
Calling all this is just an embarrassed
Sing song for everyone involved
And that includes Paul Joseph Watson who swung in like a bold Brave journalist
To cover the story
He wrote an article about the gas
But Paul made a little error of his own in the Arctic
Dmu people
The Bloomberg spent 500 million on the campaign but you wouldn't know that if you read Paul's article
Quotes with math obviously not being Revis is strong point
It was immediately pointed out that Bloomberg's 500000000000 doled out to all 327 million Americans would mean
They got just $1 and 50
3 cents each
Whoops
Looks like old pjw f***** up the math of his own on that post was making fun of other
Packing up their math
500 billion / 327 million
1529 not one point
So now I'm going to rant about it for an hour we got two segments about this coming up
Obviously palmen 500 million but this should be a prime example of one
How trivial the b******* is that these guys spend their time yellow
What about how little editorial work is done by anyone in the Infowars orbit
Shape up Paul Owens on your heels
Yeah look right
Come on man
Bad
It's bad
Read when everybody embarrasses themselves on top of
It's a it's a
Vistaril
It's a head-on I had surgery The Three Stooges don't need
Need to be interrupted by The Three Stooges
While another pair of Three Stooges are coming
You like right
Insane it's insane
Just shut up everybody
So I just yeah
I don't know I just think it's funny that they didn't all sanctimonious about this nonsense and then still making
I mean if you take it at the five billion if you take that's what he
He meant to write ebony got a math are absolutely so
Anyway
Alex starts reading some headlines
Article
Baba Bean savagely beat 50 year old girl in New York
Portugal racial attack
Okay and the cover.
Story is talking about is about a big gang of youths attacking a fifteen-year-old in New York and stealing her shoes
I watched the video and it's horrifying
But you can't tell the race of the victim
I'm from the video
From the angle the surveillance footage for faces blocked by a binder that
She's using to protect yourself
I read a bunch of articles about the story and know where can I find any information
In about a racing form everything I can tell there's no reason to jump it
The conclusion
If it was a racial attack
The perpetrators have been arrested and questioned and as it turns out the victim went to school with
They jumped her because she'd beating up another girl who they were friends with
Earlier in the day
There's literally no reason to see this as a racially-motivated attack
Unless the only thing you see is at the
The perpetrators the young men were black in your huge racist
Galaxy
That'll do it
So even the small things
Reading of this headline
There they are demonstration
What is racism
So Alex
Screams about how he wants
People that the
National Institutes
Tongue
Because of how they're dealing with
Discovering everything up
Not anymore that was yesterday
Icons of the globalist
Some people
So
Don't want to talk about it
That's the elephant
So what so what he say
Is that if
The government
Has a man-made problem
Aha that kills 3 million people
Right people
Yeah
That's an established
The globalist
Chinese
Men are doing this
Extreme language
He seems very confident about himself which may
Make this next clip really weird
Communism horrible I know Satan worshipers real
I know the left
Love to kill babies and it's a religion for them I said 20 years ago
Rockstar
I don't know
Tell you what you should do okay
So.
Defer
For months now you've been saying things about this virus
Cop out like that
Bobby AutoZone
Able to I would right now
My God before guys
Man this is a lot of punches
And here comes another one Alex Gaston
And it's guy named Anthony Hall he's not been on the show
A Dalek
Gives him
About the worst
Possible
Intro
Given
What I know about the
He hasn't respond
To the end
Targeting
Delight deeper analysis
Story topics that his detractors have targeted him
That's why I always do
But I get targeted for
What they try to shut down
He's what I then
They don't want you to look at
Again Alex's mentality about the negative attention is virtue or is correct
Is a bad way to look at things
Because
I had to say
This cannot be worse than reduction
Anthony Hall
I guess this dude hole has been talking
Some s*** about the coronavirus lately so Alex is playing this game
I thought that whole thing where it's like is that you know what your detractors are targeting rule about that's you know
Holding
That he's trying to apply that to the Coronavirus
Targeting Anthony Hall because of that that is not correct
Payoff for Alex to research his guests
Just a little
Since when Alex brings up
Calls complaint
About academic
Freedom on campus it has nothing to do with the Coronavirus
In fact it's about a topic
It's become all too familiar on Alex's show these days
It's nice to say that Anthony Hall is a professor emeritus because that sounds a lot better than the reality
In August 2018 haul retired from his position
University of Lethbridge
This was after he was suspended without pay in October 26th
16/4
I'm just going to read do you hear from an article in the Lethbridge news quote
Comments he made on an online articles and videos suggesting that Israeli and US Jews stage the 9/11 attack
And that the events of the Holocaust should be up for debate
As it turns out Holly Bennett avedio produced by a group called the committee for open debate of the Holocaust
Which you might
Go ahead and gas in Utah
Be correct
The Holocaust denial do I assume that when they say open debate that means that they're willing to be proven wrong and when
They are they will shut down their group right
An article in the Alberta views quotes
Call as saying in the video
Quote we're living in a time of huge hate speech
Speech directed towards Germans collectively
Jeanette generically
With no real ability to consider Germany's place in the world outside of
Peculiar way that national socialism has been interpreted
Fat
The Rays
Using that you're going to get stopped the peculiar way that Nash particular
In that case
The people he was in the video with from the committee where Alfred and Monica Schaefer very explicit Holocaust
Alfred's
Open featured on a bunch of anti-Semitic shows are arguing things like there were no gas Chambers
Monica was arrested in 2018 in Germany because Holocaust denial is illegal there
Whole set of those siblings
Alfred and Monica are quite typical
Call as I am myself in a
Trajectory of looking at well
Is Israel could do 9/11
What about this other big religious fable
Concerning what is called the haluk
So cool
Alex's interviewing another Holocaust denier on his show
They seem to be popping up a bunch
Lately pretty serious if then
And statement
What was reinstated from a suspension in November 2017 but his real controversial return and apparently he was asked
To resign
So he retired and now here he is on Alex's show
That's why it's not a good look
To introduce Hall by saying things like they target you for the things
Want you talking about
Reduce that Hall that weighs basically to endorse helica
Cross the Nile Valley or not
The Lonesome place
Just having him on to talk about the Coronavirus
Because he's been talkin
Some s*** about right so I'm going to assume that he is going to have a
Measured and appropriate response to this that definitely will not scapegoat any non-white peoples at all
I didn't pick up
Too much
Like a blaming the Jews for it I'd say but I did pick up
Some sources that are
The first is that it seems like
A bunch of his information may just be coming from Alex Hoopes
When I saw it
Eclipse
Puyallup
Where you were saying while I initially
Saw this
Coronavirus thing is a kind of
Deep state
Diversion Anna Anna
Used to bring indifferent
But when you saw that the
HIV virus
Is
To be in this
It's been welded
What well did I made medicines cut into it just it just flopped
Flopped onto when they're treating the ill people they're using HIV
Remedies
And
Ebola remedies
So this
Is increasingly the evidence is increasing
This is a human made
BioWare
None of that is evidence of anything
I like your speech pattern Pro
Says it turns out this guy Anthony Hall is basically just an Alex Jones listener who happens to also be a disgraced former professor
All he's doing is regurgitating completely bogus narratives that Alex has disseminated on his show
Amplified by the adjacent media sources like zerohedge
He's not provide
Any other proof for any of this stuff outside of things like you set it on your show
I was just so desperate for anyone with
Any credentials do their name to come in and validate is Coronavirus bulshit
He's got to do do lost a tenured professorship over Holocaust denial
On his show and you know what
By treating this dude like an expert validating him because his views on the virus like because you're doing that
You're kind of giving a big thumbs up
To the other believes there is that
I'm surprised though I like holy s*** this show is drift
Take down this path
Bend
Real ugly.
Yeah yeah I don't think anybody did you know if you were at let's talk about checking the boxes I think we got the Holocaust denial box check
Worse
Because we learned of another source of information
That's Anthony Hall has about the coronavirus might as well be
And I've been listening to Trunews Rick Wiles
They do a very good report everyday on Coronavirus
So here we get another indication of the sort of place is that Anthony hogetsu
Snooze for
Trunews and Rick Wiles are
Perhaps the worst place anybody could hope to get real information
H-E-B noted that Rick Wiles is very no today
One thing that jumps out is how he called the Trump impeachment a quote Juku
Play the Jews work their deceivers they plot they lie they do whatever they have to do a cop
A the political agenda
He went on to say quote you have been taken over by a Jewish cabal
The Church of Jesus Christ you are next
Get it through your head they're coming for you there will be
The Purge
That's the next thing that happens when Jews take over a country
It killed millions of Christy
Naturally some people took offense to this kind of rhetoric
Particularly when it was announced that while
Given prestridge
Supposed to cover Trump
Trip to Davis
People were saying
Hey we're did they say
Credentials
Of course
Wild response was to claim this criticism was proof of the globe
Alright
Okay okay
Examples Rick Wiles being an outrageously over date December are plentiful over his career so it makes sense that this Holocaust
Tonight former Professor might gravitate towards
Lately Rick Wiles has been framing the coronavirus is
Plague sent by God as punishment for the world sin
He said on his show that this is a death angel
And that if you're Christian you have nothing to fear from the virus
The blood of Jesus Christ will protect you do not fear
Yeah if you were living right for God if the blood of Jesus Christ is our new you have no reason to fear this death ain't
But those of you who are opposing the Church of God
Mocking God attacking his servant
You better wise up
Because there's a death angel andaluz right now
And you're going to get an attitude adjustment
Did that dude just a attitude adjustment
You know what happens Jordan when someone says attitude
What happened
Anyway Rick Wiles said on his show at the end of February that the virus will end if China accept
Jesus
Do you have to understand that this dude Anthony Hall is viewing that guy is a good source of information
About the outbreak
And now he's just regurgitating things that he believes are Alex's show
As an expert it's a dama feedback loop it's going off based
I if I become
I will
Institute of policy
That there will always
Be somebody around
Everywhere 2
Escort you out
And he needs to be a score
I don't know what I don't know where he needs to go I don't know where he needs
To be escorted to but somebody needs to be
Excuse me sir
He's serving an important function on ALEKS
To show though
Because
It's around that
Time in a show where Alex needs someone else to do some talking
It stayed where I am I'm trying
Going to identify different
Scenario
Without
Thank you clothes
Sibley it's this
This one or that one
I was eating a sandwich over here
Before we leave this episode
Call Harry
No Alex needs to make some
Baseless
Insinuations and
And theories
There's lots of
On record of who you know
Experiments on human being
Place was the
Princess
Was that big yacht was that a human makes
Was that some kind of
Professor doing awesome job
Oh yeah great
Maybe that was human experimentation
Great job and you're doing awesome zombie movie rating let's we got it all this story has everything we got love
Storiesig
CDC is coming out for everybody love it
3 comeback
On March 9th
Yes on Monday
Yes Monday show
And Alex
Starts things off on real familiar tone Coronavirus
Bioweapon launched for the Deep State megalopolis
Regina thing at the United States and bring down the economy by Trump
Try to bring down Trump.
Help him and now he is being absolutely setup we have been dead on
Again
And we can stop
But it's up to you to get the word out there and lay it all out today in the most important broadcast ever
He does not really lay it all out but again
And it's most important broadcast our every single f****** day is the most aboard broadcast ever
I don't remember repetition of the same bullet points
Over and over again this show
On Monday is
Really
It's very not interest
It's a bad episode
But Alex does say
I called this
I called a bio attack
He called literally anyting
B b b that's true
This is the big
Enchilada
Not the impeachment
Probably just Luann thing
6 weeks ago
Probably this movie or so love Austin was at
The Oracle of Austin
I can't breathe
I cannot believe the lies are so heavy and so aggressively full
And I know from listening to Alex's show back when he was saying what comes next
He didn't say a bio attack that was one thing out of a million that he okay
The thing he kept pushing on
Was he thought that the globalist we're going to Nuke Chicago
That is what he kept saying
That was I just feel like
The big ones, they're going to do in Chicago
I called it did say a number of other cities possibly as well but it was largely a theory that there was going to be a nuke
And I was going to be
Probably Chicago
Chicago
Still open up in Duke
So there's another thing Central
I'm not I'm not going to
Play much
Watch for Monday
It's a very uninspired episode you take a lot of phone calls
It's very boring
But there are some things that are important
One of them
Is that Alex is clearly shifting
More and more towards
Any dissent from Trump
Is evil
And this is an attack on America
Anybody that blames Trump
Highland mornings the First Responders
Anybody that blames
Frontline medical workers
When the globalist of Tricom
To create a collapse of confidence in the dollar
One of those things
And this is Modern Warfare
The First Responders
The medical people
Cover that is fully in stupid from the fact that he's saying that anybody who's against
Trump is an enemy of your family
Right now admittedly that anybody who disagrees with dear leader should be assassinated
Killed immediately
But that's also if they
Complain about look
I support trumpet if I complain about first-responders I'm right there with him
I just so happen
That all of my political enemies don't do the other two
Sew in
So Alex also the other thing that's really important here on this Monday March
9th episode is that Alex is back on his b*******
About the silver
No
Because things have progressed with the Jim Bakker situation
Can I believe
That a lawsuit has been filed
Alex might want to watch out because he is
Percent back on saying it can knock out the Coronavirus
Patented bio silver
The czar's coronavirus family not that too
To do it
So
It is like I have to take these things myself cuz I know they're great
He's he's f****** around again to get himself involved
Open that lawsuit
Blah blah live blah blah
Does mention that his ratings are up
Hugh
I don't make sense
I mean
Driving
I don't see any reason why
Yeah you celebrating that quite a bit yeah
That's that's immoral
Very much so I'm going to go
I don't think God
No
Speaking of God
I would start stalking
A little bit
On this episode starts talking about Jesus
I think I always have a feel for it
Like it's been too long since we've talked about God and ramble about God
Yeah so Alex notes
That like when he's out
Public
The leftist
Talk with him anymore
Now yell at him like they used to the shop near me
First of all leads into him saying something
Not true
I don't do anymore and tell me a bunch of crap I get right back with your face now the words out
They don't sit there and run their fat mouth to me in public
Looking eyes look at them inside
Phone over
Prices on a mission to be crucified and died for our sins and he wasn't going to let anything get in the way of that when he turned it
Last thing he said was his disciples is
I weapons
What
Who wrote your Bible
Stewart Rhodes
They think about that
Jesus's last words to disciples were not get weapons
I'm coming back way while they were not they were. When Jesus returned after he was crucified
He came back a few before the disciples is like strapped up
Get your name
Yeah Alex is taking be coming back with fire thing from Isaiah 6650
Quote see the Lord is coming with fire in his chariots like a whirlwind
You'll bring down his anger with Fury and his rebuke
With flames and Fire
Isaiah is an Old Testament Prosthetics
So it's important to remember the
Historical context
If it's writing when you're interpreting it but
Whatever
The part about how the disciples need to get weapons is from Luke
B-29 takes place during the Last Supper
That part that people like Alex always quoted the Line quote
If you don't have a sword sell your cloak in
Can buy one
This is all very good and well to say that Jesus said that but it's taking away the surrounding context of the verse
No surrounded contacts doesn't have any effect on things especially in the Bible
Here's the Fuller Passage
Quote he said to them
But now if you have a purse take it
And also a bag
And if you don't have a sword sell your cloak and buy one
It is written
And he was numbered with the transgressors
And I will tell you this must be fulfilled in
Yes what is written about me is reaching its full film
The disciples said
See Lord here are two swords
And Jesus replied that's enough
There are the two parts there that the biblical Scholars note
A particular about the
This passage the two things are apart
He's talking about fulfilling his role
And the fact that he says that the
The end the two swords are enough
Two swords would not be enough to actually fight
People want
Crucified
So that interpretation doesn't
However if you understand the line that's enough in the context of the Fulfillment
Jesus's role
It starts to make a little more sense
When Jesus is talking about his fulfillment he's described it as involving him being quote numbered with the
Grassers
Which is to say that he would need to be considered and treated like a common Criminal by the state
As for this theory of the text
Jesus saying that's enough
You saying that because his disciples being armed would be enough
To create the perception
He was like a gangly
In the telling the disciples to get a sword Jesus was attempting to
To fill the prophecy that he would need to be seen as a criminal to non-believers
Other scholars believe that the swords themselves are a metaphor but with no serious biblical scholar believes it
The Jesus was telling his disciples they needed to get wet
Cuz it was about to
Time to kill people
Listen up
The twelve of you
F****** Mount up
Regulators are about to deal with some
Okay
Also of The Twelve of us
To sort
If you're in a fight ask
Paul to toss you the sword
I get it yesterday choreograph
That interpretation is you
Unique Boutique
Fascist types that Alex believes are the only true Christian
Leaving aside his completely flawed and violent
Misrepresentation
The text this was not the last thing that you said
The disciples
In fact later on when Jesus was arrested in
In The Garden of Gethsemane he told Peter that hold those who live by the sword die by the sword
Anyway
Alex has more biblical interpretation
Was
But you know
Was Gutenberg really on the right
You know
Were the priest doing a fairly good job reading the Bible why did Alex get to do it
I don't know what the priest should be the only one but someone should have stopped out
That's for sure he's not good at
That's right I'm anti Guttenberg I'm finally coming up on it
Has more thoughts
About killing
King and the Bible
Right
Maybe we can do better than ultegra New Testament
Can I come to your house at night to hurt you rise up
And tell them
Pull up the clothes
Bible verses rise up and kill them
Pasta shorts
This verse is Alex that we talked about his Exodus 22 2
Quote if the thief is found breaking in and he is struck so that he dies there shall be no guilt for his blood
That's a little different from if a guy breaks into your house rise up and kill it
Is it more or less just of ancient stand-your-ground law
Also the next verse literally says quote but if it happens after sunrise
Is the defender is guilty of bloodshed
Is loophole is only available at night
So if you kill someone breaking into your house during the day you're guilty of bloodshed
Be interesting to see Alex try and weave that Nuance into his dumb calls for religiously just
Justified Violence
We weird it's always funny when
In the past
Heather has
Rules and you look at who you're like oh
So just
Nighttime it's so we're living
A daily prayer
The moment the sun goes down
Are you put on someone breaks into your house
Like that idea of a in the morning everybody shakes hands
We try it all again tomorrow night it would be really fun really fun proud to try and incorporate that son
Sunup
The coronavirus is coming
Obama sold it
It's time to rise up
We're going to do it around
732 is sunset tonight everybody get ready sunrises it's 6:44 we got to be done
We got to be done
Dan check the Farmers Almanac will see what it's like tomorrow night everybody
We're going to have breakfast
Dobie Gray
So Alex is a big Point here on this Monday show is that like this is war we are at War virus
It is
Economic war is also biological War terrorism
Stop
And he
Makes a pretty bold claim
This is this is this is America
This is a greater threat than Hitler clouds
In in in in 1940
And the Japanese
God sakes
You're going to get you
So at
Japan today
Kabam pretty hard though
So Alex thinks it is a bigger thing than WWII we're already had
So that's great
So I would assume that he is certainly seems to hang out with an interview a lot of them
That's weird so last clip here from the 9th is just another in
Instant of Alex selling this coronavirus cure in a way that I think is going to get him
I'm in trouble from over 10 years ago
Torchy's Mueller Co American biotech labs
University
Security in here
Special Operations Command
Found with and receive on
It would take me out
The SARS virus was the coronavirus man-made
Silver
What's in our
Super Silver
Super Bowl and iodine
We also have it for children all fluoride-free
Still
A lot of the Super Silver
He has information that is about the wounded gel does not apply to the toothpaste
You going to get in trouble he's back on there say a4c
Some trouble from
Yeah all of this trouble mounting
You bums me out is
Is when he does that
Toothpaste
This is a proven.
How lonely must
Affair in the valley
You would
Genuinely believe
That if all we needed
To fight coronavirus with
Toothpaste
Everybody in the world would
Actively
Hide that in
Information
Except Alex
Thinking that the entire human race
Is garbage
So you might
Confused why they're not on team Coronavirus
So we jump now to whatever one is I'm sure waiting for which is March 10th
Tuesday
So Alex starts off the show by teasing
Talking about
He's very f*****-up night
Keys on a dick he does not get down to business for a while
Pick my David Knight show
Transmission
Not possible
No sleep last night I'll tell you about that Tuesday interesting story very informative
Bird's eye view
Very interesting place such a big transmission today you don't want to miss it
So that's how were teasing this interesting experience last night
And some stuff to her
AR got arrested for a DUI
But if you didn't know that yours is likewise
Something interesting happened
Start listening
At what you do
Extra extra Alex story
Bees get back from break
It's talking
It's enough to almost trick you into thinking that he's had a moment of real
Inspection and I started to get really
I started to care
Very accurate
Morning
I'm talking to one of the crew members of the building
He was like you know there's a rumor in the office cocaine
Because there's no way you can be so tired during a break and then explode
Don't you come back on air
What I do
And the reason
Adrenaline
And and and endorphins and focused anger
Is a drug
I mistook that for vulnerability
What I heard that
Because that is true
Alex does use this performative overblown excitement
And
Manufactured anger in order to trick people into
Anxiety passionately believes various things
That are just made up or just manipulation
Yep so I heard him
Say that you don't like I'm addicted to this
Sanger
And I need to get off that drug I thought like yeah
You do
You do if you want to get help
Then you should
That would be good
Place to start yet
I was lulled into thinking
Maybe he was
Sincere
Bye
Even more things
Is hatred of devil worshipers and pedophiles
But
At the same time
I got too much of it
It's in my family background
Alpha male super successful everything
The others were still out before then
So he realizes that they are health effects
Text to come from this unbridled anger
You know high blood pressure or whatever
And you know you you're listening to lose your
If you listen to this you thinking like
You are too angry you could learn maybe to go get
Some help with anger management
That be good
Be a good first step
Find the suspect that with really going
Going on is that
This was more a rationalization
For his Alka
Vuze
Be alive at Burns twice as bright
Banamine
That is never awake never cares never had passion that's why I talked about the man Irina
Alex
Jones the drug addict
And
Because
That type of passion
They don't have that drive so they can't imagine somebody
Broadcast today they need to and loved it and want to come back at night and do more
Don't have that spark
I know you
And that's far
You have that Focus
And that's what we need more of
Turn things around you that's why last year
W whole bunch of weight
Exercise Better Built some obscure than Christmas came around her drinking again a little bit
And I'm going to Mount Everest 100% quit forever
Because you can focus away but
Depressants
Natural depressant
Wow
Orchard kitchen
I'm at because I care too much
Take it to take the focus away to take
Clarity
Did you because I can't handle reality
Places like that
That's a very typical
Thank you here for
Some people
Who has
Unhealthy
I got this
Feeling
As I was listening
Going to dislike this is a guy rationalize
Quite a bit
But he doesn't get into talking about what act
Actually happen to him the night before until deep into the show
There is just the sort of app
Abstract
Conversation about the disease
I'm too passionate and I have this
This drug of anger that I use and I use alcohol in order to deal with how alive and patch
Did I am about to fight again
A global issue
And
I think there's a dolt a dual-layer to it but whatever
Alex gets mad though
Eleni starts ranting
About his
I really
And how people said that he was an actor during his cussed
City Cakes
And again I would remind you that was Alex's lawyer who said that
As a justification for some of the things he says on it
That's why the system constantly says Alex Jones is a fake
Joseph Kony
She says that he is a
None of that strip
They they they were trying to get it
Makeup
When I'm on the show being Alex Jones myself has a father in a man as a Christian
Human
Global integrated feeling bad it's not true about Humanity
Disagreeable not let them steal my identity
Quite so important for all of you to be vocal and all of you to be involved
You don't speak that
Your voice
As well
Don't let her slow take your voice like she did The Little Mermaid
Her name is Ariel thank you very much and Empower yourself
If you don't know what's going on
Clearly you can tell if you read
Between the lines to be in the papers and I'll
Trying to
We like well hey remember back when they tried to say that I was an actor
Look at my lawyer
Use that as a defense
It's going to be going to be like that again they want to take your identity
If you're just listening to this
Something
Preemptive lying about bulshit I got we're going to be
Yeah
Alex
Gets onto rambling about various things there's some soup
Like surface-level stuff about the coronavirus that
It's just all the same
Kind of
Phone calls are boring along the way a bike Adams shows up and
Talk about
Nothing
But before he gets to his actual
News
Of his DUI
He just start
Getting real weird
Well that sounds right this is Project Camelot
Listen to this
If you look at the architecture
Festival making the world
Uninhabitable for humans
Is the globalist plant that he's talking about
Battaglia
The Bible says there is a fallen
That is immortal
Does it say
That lives here
Prison
And hates us
Because we were made
By the dude
Maroon nahmir
That's the coolest science fiction book ever man
2000 years ago
3000 years ago
Don't you think the Jews just
Why don't you think that
Really nasty Nass
The really want hurt you
Alright
Humans that collaborate with him through a spiritual interface
Okay
Facebook
Canada Guatemala
Who built the pyramids
Tell me
Tell me who else.
Building a thing to kill everybody
Everybody I talk to you a little Silicon Valley allowed UFOs
Everyone in Silicon Valley's in UFO
Country brake
I love just the idea of the years of Alex being like I'm not into that UFO alien
To say that I am not on this alien guy I'm not into that stuff now. How
Now granted
Underneath all of my beliefs
Secretly I believe aliens are behind all of it obviously
Also true
Look just cuz I believe it doesn't mean I'm that got you know that
This guy
In the Bible is written they were referencing
Satan Satan was a metaphor for the giant evil alien that lives beneath us in his aboard
Who built the pyramids Alex tell me
You should send a
I want to know
So how it gets off also gallon about to drag queen story time
Tower and I've cut out all that stuff
But it leads to
An indication that Alex might be taking some time off
In the near future
A boy
Jiminy Cricket
I've been there man weekend next week I'm not going out of town
But everyone's insisted
Week off and somehow
How do you take a week off during this coronavirus in Saturday
When you're falling apart
I mean people are a
Asking him
Maybe even saying you have to take
Some time off
This is just bad I mean I don't want to make fun of it cuz
Deeply Rock territory
Know what sucks me up is that
The two of us
Maybe hate more Alex more than any other people on the
And how many how long have we been saying that
Long time
Talking Tom
Audience was tired of me
Just an hour and now we get here and there
F*** that
I'm so mad
I'm so mad at this
I feel personally betrayed
I hate him
So much and now he's
But I don't think he's going to get help
Of course not
I think
I think I'll be right back to hating and by the end of empathy
I do think it is like the rot
Situation that I'm describing is like
This isn't isolated this isn't a bubble Alex's Behavior affect other people around him
Yeah that is a really difficult situation to be in when you're like married to him or his
The kid and the keys
Behaving in these ways that are really destructive
It's not
It's not a situation where I want to make fun of Alec
What his behavior is other
Kind of tell by these things that are coming into it with
People are saying you got to take some time off
Those people
Are concerned for his well-being or his behavior is affecting
That man away
They need him to stop doing those
It's f***** up
And I think he's still drunk from the night before
Because
He says that
President
I'm serious
Donald Trump and get me Tucker Carlson
Tucker
Couple days later, I'm not saying he's copying swrve to their Macho's him anyway
He knows how to distill it
Yeah Tucker for president
I can't think of a board nightmarish
I've never had a boat I'd present maybe it's time
Bow-Tie guy
About
Before getting to his actual story Alex engages again on March 10th with selling this
Silver stuff in a really bad way
Time Warner
We're just your daily life in your gum in your teasing for regular viruses and bacteria
The patented nanosolar we have
The Pentagon has come out and documented and Homeland Security and said this stuff
I filled the whole starter on the Family
Don user the product we have
Probably having private label
Is about to be in Walmart coming up there they just massive
Not the one they have
I'm just saying we're always Cutting Edge thing to God
Be careful Alex
He also is talking about the food buckets of course food bucket
Good sales are still being
Pushed and we get an update on that it was a six to eight weeks
Now we're at 68 months I think 6-8 weeks maybe 12 weeks
I'm not entirely sure but there's other news
He has horrible food in stock but we have to package it and it's six to eight weeks behind shipping out to you other people lie to you
It's next week
So get your orders in only have a few radical 4 weeks before the real s*** goes down
You need to get this from if you order it today but also there's only a week left
10 time before the price goes up
We also don't want more orders cuz there are too many orders I am overloaded
I am going to try and encourage you to order now because prices are going up next week
Very very contradictory stock
This is
This is a gray
So Alex
Gets into
This is next week is along the same lines of these ideas of like stealing your identity
The globalist
Ain't you in a certain way and I might get a DUI
Immediately after getting
Not clear yet I was on the show but he's wrestling with these thoughts about how they'll paint you in certain ways
You eat
How do you wanna be
I want to be a sofa
Gator with the things they associate me with
I don't want my identity
Too late
Liberty and freedom cannot be Allstate
For me they think the Liberty Movement
Operation
Is relaunch
So they can destroy their champion
As long as you realize that my destruction is our empower
What am I asking for it
On this operation is a side of ARP
And our devastating successful truth
A operation
Again this consistent mentality that bad things and negative feedback
Is equivalent to
Proof of you doing a good job
Is just never never good it's
Just a really bad way to look at the
No it's a recipe for
Acting out like an ass
Bright
So Alex now teases
Poor
Can't believe that he's turning this into a full keg
Who shot j.r. scenario
Fuk up y'all
And then
I guess I'll just
And that and that you should know that
Here first
Before these men doctors another chance
That
There's no such thing as bad press
I'll take stuff to the artist people there on your Liars
Telangana corporate people just ignore whatever I say on topping knows about me
I just say they're live but you hear it and then you promulgated
Without you I am so dead the water but that's okay
The Alamo went down in flames as well Travis was a drunk too
So it might be appropriate
Whispering seeing is f***** up very weird a decision on his part
That's not what I would want a kid to the family
Costco very weird
Is exactly the sort of thing if you hadn't slept that kind of a
Arc of DBZ I'm just
F****** fight Freeze already I think of the goddamn recap episodes
Previously
God dammit
Alex likely saying there
Obviously like
I need to get ahead of the story use my words
Like I'm listening to you outside
Wasn't
You hear their the end
Without you without the audience
I'm dead
I think that's a recognition of Alex knows
This is a bigger issue than we even just a DUI
Yeah
So Alex gets back
He starts talking about the extra
True story
And of course
He dances around a little bit and
Can you talk about I really even
Of course of course
I want to
I'll just get ahead of something
I actually enjoy talking about this
Because it was quite the experience
To see what's going on in this country and and
To go through it myself
I talked about this on there quite a bit.
Just last year I bring it all
And I certainly got to the point where
I don't have more than a beer or glass of wine and drive a car because then I know that I will never blow above
0.8
I have no proof that he drove after that c-pack rally but he certainly had more than one beer or glass of wine
I will tell you that
So here is here comes the story
Alex was out to dinner
With his wife they went
Had to go get some sushi
That's where everything fell asleep probably
Well
Last night I've been out at
Japanese restaurant my wife
Bottle of sake
Holy shot glasses
60% alcohol
We go home
Later
Beats Apple Store
I'd rather
Turn on pull me over
Description of the black car with her some domestic dispute
Get out of the car
Alucard
Cuz you been drinking I said yeah about 2 hours ago I went native
Chinese restaurant
I want
Because all right thanks
Calling Mom
Where you stand on one foot and look at that he can't do it
And that's my wife that's my belt
Start laughing
Then I know I wasn't being mean that was just like
But I was wobbling
Alex isn't really telling the truth
According to this article about his arrest in the Austin american-statesman
The only reason the police were there
Is because Alex's wife
Show me article quote
An arrest affidavit for John says a sheriff's deputy responded at 10:10 p.m. Monday
To a western Travis County residences
Since for a disturbance
Reported by Jones
His wife
His wife told the
The dispatcher they were in a verbal fight that had been physical earlier in the day
The affidavit says
He said Jones was leaving the residence in a black Dodge Charger
And that he was possibly drinking
The affidavit
When Alex says that the cop pulled him over because his car looks like one that match the description
That's because it matched the description of
He's car
Which the police were looking
Looking for because his wife had called the police
He was the person the police were looking for
And he was going 45 in a 40 mph Zone
When the deputy pulled him over he quote
How do you strong odor of alcohol
Which is not surprised
According to the affidavit Alex's story on air is completely alive
On-air Alex says that he was going out to get the thing from the store share later says that it's Blue Bell ice cream
So that's when he got pulled over
That's what he was doing
But the affidavit tells a totally different story
According to the report Alex and his wife got into an argument at dinner over sushi
Do you think quote
Jones ended up walking
3 miles home from dinner
When he arrived home they continued arguing the affidavit says
Jones stated
He then proceeded
To drive to another residency owns downtown
To get away from his wife
That's what Alex
Told the cops
The night before
And now he's completely lying about that on
Alex wasn't going to get out
He just got into a drunken
Fight with his wife
Anyway the point is that Alex has a p
His ex-wife is said that he was abusive and now we have his current wife calling the police
Because of a perk
Attracted fight
That had been
At one point
Leading to him getting arrested for a DUI
And then of course Alex turns around and he's trying to play the victim here on his show
Is a narcissistic monster
Who takes things out on his own
The basic
Facts of the matter here they he got booked
The county jail in Travis County at 12:37 a.m. on Tuesday morning
And he was he was charged with suspicion
Of driving while intoxicated
Who do the Class B misdemeanor
He ended up getting released at 4:11 a.m.
So that's those of EU
The timestamp
On a lot of this
So after he fails this field sobriety
Task with the officer out on Airways
He's telling the story on Aaron he's already lost
Based on his own tellurian the everything so
He's a meat so he's got this
The situation
With the cop
Sobriety test
And then he has to go in
For a
That's it you're going to jail
And I said man I just told you I had
Hours ago album in my body
When
And they have a plumbing keep blowing
So I leave and they put me in a tank
You literally
Don't have any alcohol your blood in Lubbock
It was until I got out this morning that I actually got the paperwork and that's what's really weird
What is shock Alex has some fake Anonymous jailhouse snitches who are
Jailhouse snitches man
You got it you go you get locked up in County 45 seconds and all these jailhouse snitches running around telling you what
What the cops are secretly doing
Is
The Cornerstone of Alex's sort of like
Evidence
Narrative that they were trying to jam up basically
He's got to be one of his one of his jailhouse snitches
Was like
They're stitching you up
They're coming for you they're either called they're saying that you were drunk It's ludicrous
They're going to send you the paperwork and it's
Yeah
So he he gets back into talking more about these jail last night
That was until I got out this morning that I actually got the paperwork and that's what's really weird
Is that
There were two guys in there getting tested hearing that they say
Only show up and I'm not saying conspiracy here. In the police ride together
So
There you go
When you see the shipping news
Italy Jones arrested for DWI
You are
Sandy Hook
Wild ass stuff I wanted you to hear it upfront
With my version
A computer
Fictional retelling of this whole circle
Stand right
You
That's what I'm here
Q from the Liza
Liberal
PDF by telling you all kinds of
Fictional bulshit
About all of my life
Yep cool
So Alex
I'm certain his making up these people in jail
Where's alternative at the same time
Well the hot tub does come up
Knowing yeah they're talkin about Alex Jones is here and
Glowing glowing glowing glowing
Model y
In the hot tub
I did not have
0 bus
I'm sorry what did you just say I've been at the home at the hot tub blanket
Here is just that part again
Icymi
In the hot tub
I did not have
Right really quickly
The Whitney
0 Buzz with
That's what we call a towel I was drinking a lot of alcohol
Cool
So I am I should say I'm interested. I got a DUI when I was 9
And
I will say from Mike's
Experience if you're someone who hasn't had a breathalyzer test done
It does feel weird
Because you have to blow pretty hard and it's not a comfortable thing
Not like your natural breathing so often times they will have to have Ubi
You have to do it in such a way
Yeah so I think it would Alex's describe
They made me keep doing it right
Doing anyway
And so they weren't able to carry out the test
Alright whatever I don't hear anything here that in
Indicates any sort of
An appropriate procedure
Try to get a breath of
It's. Yeah and I
I don't know anything but Alex as a whole
Is it non-cooperative
It seems that way
We go back
The scene of a crime
Alex
Pulled over is innocently trying to get Blue Bell ice cream man
How to get ice cream after getting a degree
Just cuz he didn't put a shirt on after he left the hot tub
He got right in
He was going to get ice
Glass of whiskey with ice all melted
Because he was in the hot tub drinking
Sure those are honest
Innocent man
Who is trying to get some ice cream
Catches up
So when you're pulled over often times it'll be various different things that officers will do to try and assess whether or
Spell bee that you walk the line or try and stand on one leg or whatever
I want the main things they do is they flash a light in your eyes because the response that your eyes have
Are very indicative
When you've been to
Answer Alex discusses that big Don
And is next
We have this like my eyes to the crap
Volunteer for 1 minute
You're like that
Not cooperate
Morning
You got me the lowest level of arrest
In the country
Texas
I got all this
And so now
Yeah I had two beers couple hours ago
Does it matter it's legal
Working on the narrative that they're just trying to jam everyone up
Man Alex
I don't know if you know this
For the Cubs
Husband
Using quotes for a long time I've heard him care too much
Who those quotas
It doesn't seem like he's made a big mama
That's not entirely true if you go back like
A decade apologize
I don't believe these jailhouse sources who told him that the advert right they said he was sober or whatever
And I don't think he's Garza
Good theater I think this is just Alex trying to
So I would also argue that it
It's possible that Travis County
It's not so much a
Quota issue
It might be thing where they decided to take drunk driving more
Seriously because
The county saw a 70% increase in BWI related deaths compared to 26
It's possible they put rules
Someplace to get a closer to zero tolerance policy
We're officers discretion is used
To determine if someone is impaired whether or not they blow a point eight
A .08
Even if you only have one beer and you blow like a
.01 if you're impaired in such a way that you can't operate a vehicle you can still be arrested for driving while under a nymph
So this officer pulled over Alex had good cause to
Suspect that
There's no way that Alex
I didn't deserve to get arrested
Regardless of what
And he's obviously there's no reason that
Like somebody who's swerving all over the road drunk off of his ass driving around Camp blow-up .07
The cop is like
Well you got it this time but it will get you it don't you have another drink will get you next time we can has to be
About impairment not about that it actually
The police
For his car
Everything about this well
We started out looking
For the tank but when we realized it was still had to offer
We figured we'd look for your person
Certainly
The Travis County
Is Jim going to go on a crusade
I get to be in court
Sha
Arresting people
Michelle
And they're continuing prosecution to show zero alcohol
On that
He's going to get to the bottom of this man and until his court date passes
This will be
A major point
I still don't think he's going to talk about whether or not people should be used to show up at Rikers
I don't think he's going to care too much about that at all
Be very self sir
Reform is really about
So Alex gets
Talking about how like he stopped drinking for a while and now he's back
Drinking
We were very clear about from the c-pack episode but he didn't
I mean like
This is kind of gross and I don't want to make fun of it cuz it's
Just a Fool
Expression of somebody who's
Like struggle
Yeah
This will just be a huge nothing but you know what
I started back on New Year's drinking some more
I have that power over them that I'm
Hundred percent
Quit
So that they can never again
Restaurant
Cab
Bottle Shock he was this tall
What is Express in alcohol when I started drinking again and now I'm going to really quit
Just the sort of thing that is
Is very standard people with problem
Alcohol tolerance
Yeah and
Stand-up that's something that I've heard all this
I hate my life that you back I've heard all the
Everywhere that I go where peep
Seriously struggling with alcohol those are the
Same words that are said
Yep
And it's like
Man I am I hate him
Help
You need help somebody
So in order to prove his
Yes
Wait what were we doing
I was going to prove his innocence
To go about it is to show his alcohol test result
On air
Missouri
Play right here
Big Missouri out of this
Curious mind
Alcohol test right here
Two of them they put on there
0.076
What do I feel shades of Elizabeth
0 point
That's like one beer basically
There's no way that Alex's story about drinking a little sake at dinner then hours later getting pulled over can be true if you almost
Blew up
It's really hard to nail down the exact
Numbers because there's no things can vary from person to person and depending on their weight
But generally speaking
For a person over 220 lb to have a BAC of 08
It's absolutely categorically not one beer
Is Alex's story is to be true that it was ours after dinner then he definitely kept drinking after dinner
Maybe in that hot tub because otherwise he would not have blown 2.0 76
It's just not possible
Is Bollywood
Metabolize that alcohol by that point
There's no way he's being honest about this and it
It's just a desperate attempt to save face
There doesn't have to be open
Unreal about the consequences
His actions
And it's even worse
The map to cuz like
But there's the time
Different
Downstairs
Twi
And was
Below the legal limit
But when they put Avenues it will be the exact opposite Giant
Fiasco
Children and running around with sickle chopping people's heads off and
Canisters of gasoline in
Snorting
14 lines of Nina 14-foot lines of cocaine
Shoving bottle rockets up my rear end
I mean by the time they're done it's just
So he's just making a mockery with the straw man version
The things that people will say about it as opposed to
I I got arrested for DWI after getting into a fight with his wife that is I have been in that situation
Before talking with
Somebody saying
Almost
Word for word that
That same kind of
Not necessary immunosuppressed
Give me down but it's like
Do they
They call me such a bad person cuz all I had was a few drinks there going to say that I'm killing babe right now that's what they're going to do
And it's like
I want to grab her by the shoulders and
The deflection
So Alex drops one little bit of information
I hear they later found this in the article that is affidavit but
It was
It makes this way worse
It was 10:00 at night
I've been in a hot tub
Salata bar doesn't make anything better or worse
Npm
Because he said he just had sake at dinner
And in the affidavit at estimate
The time he was at dinner with eight
The two results of the BAC test for done 5 minutes
When you finally got props
One was it 11:55 p.m. almost two hours after he was pulled over
That was the one that had a .07 6
Where is the other way
Was done at 11
D9
But p.m.
5 minutes later
And that one was .07 9
Which tends to imply that
Kia and drink a bit of the booze pretty recently before he got pulled over
Sense8
Could be the fact based on those two reading that his BAC was on its way up
It was climate
As opposed to him sobering-up
In between those two tests
So
He was drunk
That's the bottom line
Anyway Alex takes this he has this mentality that's like
I am pretending
That I just had one beer
And that means
Didn't know one
Can have
A beer and then drive
Therefore all bars must be
Be closed
Restaurants should not be allowed to sell alcohol
You should be able to serve somebody up here
If they drink that 16 oz beer and walk out there going to go to jail
For all restaurant Berkeley shutdown
And not go to jail I like to remind everyone that Alex pretends to be a libertarian
What are Ikea seems to pretend that you go into a bar and have some drinks menu
The drive people are
About is how it's literally everybody else
Who's fault but mine
In fact I am so not at fault
I challenge you to close down all restaurants across this great nation
If you don't want me to drive drunk
You shouldn't own a restaurant
And that
It's very weird to
I know that he's not being literally he's trying to
Make some sort of a point with this thought experiment of chlorella bars
But the point is dumb
You made a decision now again
Yes
Something that you are very
Strong about is how people
Should make this
Decisions and take
Possibility
Now one thing that I need to make very
Clear is that I think is pretty Siri
And I think that Alex
Is
In a really bad
And
I think
Duii is obviously a piece of that
Details of it being like
He got into a fight with his wife at a sushi place walk
3 miles home
Kept fighting with her obviously drinking more than
Trying to drive to another property
To get away from her she calls the police
And then gets you know we get the rest
Like the circumstances surrounding that are really really f***** up
Yeah but I also a lot of it does fall under the heading of his personal life
Stant
I'm not
That's
Not in my purview
Yeah
But the thing that I need to
Make a point of is
Everybody posting tons
Tons of
Tweets
All this about his
DUI
He knows that that's exactly what he wants you to do
Attention
Lions Gump Travis County great folks in Florida it's okay I told you I only had
Alex knows there's not
A ton of consequences for his actions
Class B misdemeanor he's not going to prison
In for it
He'll be a fine of some sort of whatever he can pay that off from the food bucket money that he's made
So that's not a huge deal you knows his audience is perfectly manipulatable so he'll just lie to them about the circumcised
I just going to get some Blue Bell ice cream
All that's fine he's not going to suffer that much of a consequence
But
He's also told his audience that everyone talks about him is lying
So all of this
Everybody posting about his DUI is Free Press
For him
And he experiences that way and I think that that
Is going to be
The largest hurdle to him getting the help that he needed
Not that everyone posting about it is impeding his ability to get out makes. Sing that
As a positive right
If you get any negative reaction
From people that is how you know you're doing a good job
I mean if you recognize that he could get this much Free Press
It's out of a DUI yeah he probably have been
Oh yeah
Very well have been
Volkswagen
This may have been pre-planned
There's a whole thing
I think bush is behind all of this
Liquid
Cheney that's who's done it it's possible
So Alex
Comes back from the break
And he has some ground rules
He's going to be taking calls for the show but he has
Where what was the coveralls be alive today
Sold out last night again the clear fact that is a bioweapon
Alright college no talking about how I spent the night in jail
No talk about the one thing that all of you want to talk about right now ain't nobody bring up the details from that also
An American statesman article that
So we heard throughout the course of these days that we've been covering Alex
Sort of threatening
Murder if any of his family members right Coronavirus
The government of China on notice
He's coming for us
Rambo Style
I'm going to hold a serious possible
Just tell China
I just left
Showing up in China like where's the government
But I beat him up
Especially if the warning is just like a
Hey you tell two people and you tell two people in eventually it'll get back to the
So Alex is in this mode and if there's a bit of threat
Violent talk
Surround
Coronavirus like someone's gotta pay
Kind of thing
And we don't have the police and we don't have the military in the Civil War
We go around them if we ever get to that point
The king band
Card
We're running a show whenever they are
He'll be their own security people in New Zealand
Hawaii
And in Montana and in Canada
There's no conspiracy
They all
Global try to take America down
The first thing
These waffles are going to get is garroted they're all going to get a wire
They're going to get killed about 15 seconds
You're all dead
Okay
Go ahead and fill your hand
Go ahead and play your game your dead
Let's go
You know how it is and they're losing
It's not people but everybody knows what's happened so they're viruses successful
Globalist not by my hand
People know who you are
They're sick of you
Going to break
Your neck
So this is not the first time we've heard that fantasy being played out die Alex
No it seems like you just
Supplies that to whatever situation he's talking about like these your security people are going to go rock you
It's like he hasn't
You just looking for an excuse
To trigger
That fantasy
That's one of the things like
Thinking about this the reason that right
Now I want him off
Fair is not mainly
So he gets help
It's mainly because when Alex is in a bad shity mood and his life is in shambles
He tells people to start
F****** Civil War
That's the that's the inability of narcissism
Experience has his own personal troubles as being like
Devastating worldwide thing
Yep but even when things are going alright he still a little bit
That's fair
Easy the violent guy really violent
Yeah
So he
Kman
I'm not on drugs
I'm high on the holy
Holy Spirit you know you spent the night in jail
You you are hallucinating
You are not high on the Holy Spirit
Talking directly to a
Talking bunny that looks like a leaf
If you don't sleep
And you listen
The Tom Sawyer by Rush
You up
And listen to what happened this is
Nonsense
This is what that is
This week vessel cannot even begin to show you
God's power
But nevertheless
Do they sell crack in the video
Infowars
You
And see the spirit
Music for a minute cuz there's a lot of music out there but the way that
Synthesizer comes out of that Rush song
In the beginning of Tom Sawyer
Restaurant place
Yes
Yeah yeah yeah
I'm about you
I'll make sure I plan on that Hill that I got all the strings I've got I think every step just right
Go out and you know we beat them
That's not not a guy who didn't spend the night in jail
Pets in heaven all the time
Fantasy from Ewan McGregor in
Trainspotting
What is a habitat
Ridiculous
So Alex starts yelling
About
How
His products are good
Because
He sells them
And you know does he have a hangover cure
Probably
Probably brain Forest
He wouldn't be able to sell you something that wasn't good you understand I do for his products are good
Battle
Because you can't lose
Because you know Infowars delivers in the fight
It was just
Cardboard box you are getting
You're funny gimpel words win but
Add a stop
You think I'm going to produce at your mouth
We can dig it
Put my name on something and screw you metaphysically knowing I'd be in the
Cloud devil operation about that
Running around
The polar opposite of the liars
Below the legal limit
Nothing wrong
I've been Vindicated
Now you trying to hit him with a car
That's the issue. Me
Never made some of that rage
Seems to be off of
You go to a library and read a book by somebody that's exactly as dangerous as when I am
Drunkenly driving in the
Middle of the night in Austin
Is everybody else's fault everybody else's but
I mean it's
It's standard stuff for him for the most part but the context of it makes
Saturn
And I
Anyway we're One Last Cry. It's Alex
Kind of crying
Talk about courage
We were going to get some tears
My dude hasn't slept he's going to get to the point of Tears
Jumpoline
Let me tell you something right now we're going to win because of you
The school and working hard in God's all you need to do that's all the wealth of the world
Injustice
Just letting God you do that
Everything else is handle
You love God you want to be a good person you you just love goddess experience at relationships I love God
Alan Jackson
That's all the well that's all the powers of Gods
Do you have courage
But that's God
Courage is it
Something
We come up with
As well
And it's like I
Kairos power
Nursing big dams gates open when there's a big flood
God looking for people that can handle that level of power
Expand human consciousness
And a minute
You enter into that gate you are now the presence of God
You feel that presents
You don't fear the new world order for all the Slime bags or all the cowards anymore
You just want to be in alignment with God
Or you want to drink in your hot tub then died
Yep
It's good to know that
Well I'll tell you this
On the road to
Yeah
It's really difficult for me is it like
I get my empathy
Triggered at the beginning of that the 10th episode
He's talking about
How he's addicted to this anger
And it's a problem for him and he wants
Do better than you start to realize Maybe
That's only in service of trying to justify the drinking in order to
Udel
The the anchor righteous anger that he has a mcclarity
And then by the end when he's telling the story of the DUI and everything surrounding it
All of it is obfuscation
Deflection
Defensiveness
And the behaviors that you tend to see from people who have a problem
Who don't want to record
Acknowledge that they have a problem
Alex screaming I'm not the problem
Is kind of a Dead Ringer
For that
The only positive is that you
We bring up the hot tub
Every single one of these stories involve
I believe that I said you were going to show that Alex needs to stay the f*** away from hot tub
I've never heard her a lot of problems never heard them factor into a story of his that is a good story
This is this episode was basic
It was like watching
An episode of intervention
Button
It was reversed where it's just a bunch of
Addicts listing of Grievances and yelling them at the person trying
I'm helping the center
Yeah like
It's like an interview episode of intervention that doesn't have in an
Yeah
You may have the resources to not have any real consequence
I mean
Like honestly
I don't know why I can't pretend to understand
What is going on in his personal life
But I mean if his wife is calling the police
Regarding
A fight that
They had
Chance that you might be heading for a second divorce
Like that could be a huge problem in his life
But beyond that and that's just speculation had no f******
An idea about this
The real
World consequences of this
I mean
Boring
The possibility that he has some secret DUIs on
The past that we don't know about now it's like
Make that would make this an actual escalated to a felony or something
He's not going to have any consequences other than a fine
Some minor inconvenience in his life
And if he gets a better lawyer you could probably get out of
Half of that City
Even if there is a possibility that he would get his license
Since taken away which I don't think is the case
He can afford to have his his audience can pay for his lift
Or chauffeur
It's a it's a it's a
It's unfortunate
Because this is
It should be
A situation where he recognizes like
There's a larger thing going on in the world
And in his own life that
Right there
It should be some sort of a wake-up call but it's
Probably not going to
There's no real consequence here other than
Possible embarrassment in the eyes of his audience
And he can inoculate himself in that pretty easily
His own
Joe
If you're rich Rock Bottom is a
The long long long long long way down
At a DUI.
Close
It doesn't seem like like like what
Jim irsay if you if you own the cult
You can f****** kill people at
App
So anyway we get to the end of this and I mean obviously I think
That my intention
For this episode was
Sort of demonstrate the continuation of the nonsensical incoherent nature of the
The coronavirus Meredith yes
And we got
Well I mean almost hit by a drunk driver
We got T-boned by Alex's Tuesday show and it turned into what it is
I mean I know the people really tired Ward for Great Line sex is there that one
Podcast over
I know
The audience's incredibly tired as me
Expressing
Best Buy
80s still my firm
Conviction that Alex needs help
And
I hope that he gets it
As much as I hate him
And as much as I can
Think of you say
Toxic
Cancerous thing in the world he's clearly
Expressing
That is full of chaos and
Hurt
And can be helped
So
That's the feeling I have and
I don't know
I don't even know
Man
I really want to just reiterate real quick
Mike Adams
Except for that one Shining Moment where you told Alex to change the headline that
That is a nice job that was the one redeeming quality
I realize that I think I forgot to play that
Clip
Of Alex's second explanation
For why you shaved his head I didn't hear the second
Because he's jealous of Owen
Why should I have hair Superman I'll be Lex Luthor
So anyway we will be back
Another episode in the near future but until then we have wipes
Upgrade girls on Twitter
We are they going to be like to download the show please go to iTunes or wherever podcast years download
Believe review
The donate the whole thing
Emilio I'm dvx Clark
I'm out Jones's jailhouse snitch
Alexandra Thurston color