Damn important swetik
I have great respect for its knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as if
Knowledge vype.com
Everybody likes it around Bicknell to Beverages and take a little bit about Alex
Text Jones Jordan
Damn you know I've been trying to get you
What's that
Witcher 3
Oh have you talked about it
Is the hardest
Decision you've had to make so far
Deciding to play it
I found a cheap used copy of it
Review
I don't want to give anything 10/10
Score or whatever
I don't know I just I haven't been playing it that much
That long
Met any
Super
I don't know is that there are so many complicated moral decisions
That you have to make love to you that is being listened to Too Much Ali
Alex Jones but I don't know if I encounter too many
Pigs as pets notably morally dubious
Have you done the Bloody Baron quest line yet
Probably a man there's some boys
Maybe I look at that more is just like oh this is
Bucked up
We live in a post morality world
I don't know I think it's alright
I heard a lot of people say like this game should be kept awake
Drink it because of all the f***
Yeah there's a lot of
Seen any of that up till this point
I don't have any don't look forward
To finding out what
I mean by that is a lot of complicated
Don't know much about Witcher but I do know about Alex
I also don't like how it's our introductions attorney get to video game reviews
March 11th
Through March
Wednesday through Friday of last week it was a trip
Texas life
He had just done his show
Post
Not sleeping
Spent the night at
The little dual screen
That was on the 12th that was Tuesday the 12th
Happened
Answer Wednesday through Friday is every tumultuous. For Alex
He's still trying to push a lot of the coronavirus situation to trying to deal with the major news that's going on
Pain in the world
But you can tell that something is
Not right
Like
This is
A very
F***** up stretch
I'm not going to
Sugarcoat it at all
Okay this is
Trouble
You asked if I was okay when you came in by Forest recording
Any part of it was like
This is
Messed up stuff this ride is going to be as messed up as a couple of missions in The Witcher
No problem.
Okay
So I will get down to business on that before
Show
Michael thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Next
This is what I buy taurine
I don't know if that works in
Dafont
Thank you so much
Next dealer thank you so much
Next
Fox and Dylan thank you so much you and I'll probably walk
Dunkin Donuts in Dillon
Map 1106
Thank you so much you and I'll probably walk
Yep thank you Aunt finally looks
Technocrat
Heroin
Freakishly large
Kristen
So Jordan we start off today on March 11th
What you B note
Is 311
And we know one thing
Alex hates 3053
But
By this point
Other media
It started picking up on Alex's she'll Versailles
The way he was very inappropriately unethically possibly illegally
Is silver gargle in toothpaste
And So It Begins
New show
Dublin the f*** down
Jones
He claims protect you against Coronavirus
Play on this garbage
The truth is we showed you the documents
From the Pentagon and from A&M
Nanosilver of this type is known to kill viruses at the fact the hospital
Nanosilver products
So you were right
To sell your supplement as if it were a drug
Then
It should have been approved by the FDA
And this is going to be
System thread throughout
Somebody who has robbed is that corporate representative position is bad
Self-esteem goddamn
Yeah you it's unexpected
So I was get to talkin about the these documents from the Pentagon and all that and
I think that if you listen to this especially as it gets
It's further on and the attention gets
Larger
It's being put onto Alex about this
Sales issue
I think it becomes pretty clear that he knows damn well that those documents are only
We talkin about the wuzhou
Will you try to label this is a stronger silver you can get over the counter
The strongest American nanotech company puts it out please
Leftist are so anti-human
National holidays
They they literally don't want you to know about silver that goddamn these people are
I'm not positive that he does get back to that story about the holiday but
That's a classic methinks you do
The situation
That cadences
What they do what they don't like is what
Food delivery
Yeah
You're not talk about the issue
You don't think you can tell like about the
The gel it's like
That is the one that is approved for sales that way
So
Alex has been thinking that real deep
About this virus
And he wants you to know that
The main thing
Important to remember is that it's man-made
But also
He has people on the show
You really scare you
Because that's important to
4 a.m. this morning and I spent
Ed Sheeran
Bringing a cup of coffee
Answer the phone not reading news relief
Dwelling
Cogitating
Jitter
Information
Chili's
And I'm going to lay it out
Right now
Vision engineered man-made by 11
They don't discuss
Because after Achilles heel
It's been deployed it has a low kill rate
Supercenter Subway
The elderly that's Superman
Maybe quarter percent 4:30 Central Public still a big deal still want to get them
Horsham scenarios
What's going on
The world map
Open
No it's not
No that's not I need to have
Outrageous alarmist
Important part of us
Finding the right narrative
That's like having a writer's room or something along those lines
Not trying to format I elected
We're going to brainstorm all the reasons you're going to die on ER
Present them as if they are all
And then later we'll pretend
Just spitballing
That's very responsible kind of is aware of them
The really going to think he's
You know
Let me know she's not going to be many people to say I told
So a lot of the narrative is just over the maintenance kind of situation a lot of it's the same stuff that he's been
Observe building with
Obama sold it to China
The building blocks are really wet
Which is what keeps getting
Pushed
And
There's a few
Slight changes
Other special edition
Lot of spinach
Is Wheels though like Alex starts talking about this idea he has
There are a ton of different
Prince trains
About 3 weeks ago
I thought that the other strains of something bigger
And now I'm sure of it and now we see them saying that
Priming the pump
The only tell you what they're going to do before they do it
If you're not getting chills you're crazy
The media
You want to go out
Well I just got the biggest she'll ever had in life when I'm on target man always very sad
Target
Beyond the Veil spirit world.
That's it
To doing know what it is
Digitakt
What do you need to get not hysterical you need to get right with God you can tell everybody that it's a stage the man
The other so people understand
That
This is an attack on our markets attack on our confidence
Come back coronavirus and some other things
But I do just want to remind all of you that
Anything I promoted
Really believe is the best thing and needs to be done
Are there
Stream situation a little bit later
Is it more but for now just
Try and scare people getting lead him naturally
Into any local
So he's he's really defensive
About the silver sales tactics surrounding
Those tax
And so he
Deploys lot of straw man
You already heard earlier and saying they're saying I sell fake weed never
And now he brings out what is probably his largest
Strawman to play this pretty regularly
It's very
Let me just show TV viewers since Mother Jones just demonizing eyes
In a very deceptive formulaic piece where they show other people
Mets flames and violated
FDA regulations
Regulate supplements but then they'll come after you if
You say you need water delivery sunshines good for you or you got a vitamin C live
So Alex is only real defense he can have in terms of his be clearly unethical sales
Silver products
Is to create straw man argument
The FDA is not making
Here you see one of these regular formulation
Saying that the FDA won't let you save the humans need oxygen or water
So the basic point that he wants his audience
The thing is that the FDA doesn't allow you to say things that are
Completely established
Damn, knowledge
Because he's trying to make his claims appear to be established
Uncommon knowledge
He wants his audience to take
His claims about the silver product
Bienville legitimate as someone saying you need air to live
The problem is the what he saying about the f
True
The nutrition labeling and Education Act of 1990 establishes that there are certain
Types of claims that are solidly proven
Widely accepted
To the point where you can make the
About supplements in the FDA does not care
The FDA has a big list of these on their website including things like the relationship between calcium and osteoporosis
Or sodium in hyper
Pretension
If you sell a calcium supplement and you promoted by saying that
I can help you avoid osteoporosis
The FDA considers you to be in the clear
And they're not going to do anything
Think about it
Claims like you need water or you should breathe obviously things have to be ft8 does not care
This is a stupid thing
But I don't we know the 5G Cleaves to Ox
You never know what could
Sure
But Alex beads is audience to think
These ifta people are so aggressive and nitpicky that even the most obvious claims are too loud because he needs them to think
Egregious example of someone making it unfounded helpline
He also need them.
But he was defrosting them
Never gazette's
That's dangerous
Because he's getting a lot of heat
On this front
Decides to
Promote another product
And maybe
Maybe he doesn't do a good job
I want to show losartan viewers a couple things were going to break here
Percent
What does nitrous oxide
Look it up
What does boosting the entire
System
Agency
So Alex is getting really defensive about the other media picking up on his silver gargola
Toothpaste how are you selling them as Protections in
What kind of vaguely as cures for the Coronavirus
In an attempt to sound really research
In studies study besides to pull out a bunch of science to demonstrate
All this product is super good for you
And apparently he has too much of sob
In the warehouse because he decides to start pushing
Beats are really high in nitric oxide
Not nitrous oxide
And this product he's selling his very beat-heavy
Are you saying it's not going to get you high
No
So Alex is pulling out these studies about nitric oxide being helpful for immune response
However he clearly hasn't read any of these studies
They're just printed out pieces of paper that have had lines that are to show people that you know
Nitric oxide to human immune response
However
None of these Studies have anything to do with people taking nitric oxide
Having a better immune response
They're all just about how the actual compound nitric oxide plays a role in immunity
Usually studies to establish that you can sell a beat product to boost immunity
Probably not hold up in court because they're not relevant studies to the claims being made
Also I have
Distress Alex
Absolutely not read these studies
One of them is from the July 28th
18 journal of clinical and diagnostic research
With the headline
Nitric oxide its role in immune
Newspaper include the section
Entitled
Nitric oxide and immune regulation
Which begins quote
Exact function of nitric oxide in the immune regulation is on
Clear there is a roll but even this review is saying that it's not fully understood
Considering that the sales pitch is happening in the middle of a viral outbreak in Alex's clearly marked
Marketing is products in that context
He probably be good to check
Check the section about nitric oxide immunity and viruses
Which does say that nitric oxide helps with virus immunity but also that quote
During clearance of virus
High levels of nitric oxide can produce some undesirable effects on the house
Like hemorrhagic
Fever
It seems like
The point is that low levels of nitric oxide that's likely to be good in the body's natural immune response
But they do have really high levels of it
You can have some pretty naked
Consequences
You would know that if you just read the papers introduction
Nitric oxide is also implicated in the path of physiology of various cancers breast larynx
Cervix head in that
Doomer promoting role of nitric oxide is dependent on the tumor type
Nitric oxide
I concentration interact
Chicken with protein
Metals or free radicals
And the genetic makeup of the house
Lower concentration of nitric oxide is important for immune function
Well nitric oxide at higher levels are shown to be immunosuppressive
Suggesting a dual role the biomolecule
If you have too much nitric oxide in your system
According to the study that Alex was using as a citation on air
It can lead to tumor growth and immunosuppression
That seems Reckless of him
But it becomes even more Reckless when you hear this
Now they super concentrated bean extract
One of the strongest you're going to find out there
Vascular system is good
Michelle's is back in stock
Papa John's I'm getting my children
Give them a lot of it
Probably not a good idea to give your kids as much Nitric
Dockside supplement as you want while citing a study that literally says
Too much nitric oxide is really bad for you
An ungenerous reading of that behavior would be that Alex wants his audience
Have to
Immunosuppressed
That's the only
Conclusion you can come to you actually believe that Alex's read the study
Deciding
I'm far from a scientist
But from the studies Alex has provided
It seems clear that having too much nitric oxide in your system could be very bad for you
And here he is on there saying you can take as much of it as you want and that your kids
Can take a bunch
That's incredibly irresponsible Behavior
You're in from where I'm sitting that indicates that weird
Situation were Alex's refusal to do any work
Coupons
Doodle rescue his audience
Does help
Hey please understand
Alex has no f****** idea what he's talking to
Later in the show
He's promoting this beat
Product by saying
High in nitrous oxide again
Outside chemical compounds
Write down the blood increase nitrous oxide
Incredible
SOB's
Concentrated
Strongest concentrates
Beet extract
Outside its role in immunity
Let's get f***** up
Nitrous oxide is n2o and it's f****** laughing
Nitric oxide is an o
Are very different things and Alex doesn't even know was product well enough to
To know what's in the
This is not a good showing
For him trying to be defensive about how he sells a product I think this was a swing-and-miss
Just you just can't understand how you could
Could take the worst thing you could
Could do and really do worse with another Pro
It's impressive on a certain level
He's just lying
With the recipes
Borderline actively trying to kill people
I don't know about that I don't I don't know what level of
Nitric oxide those Vezzo Beats pills have
Be dangerous even if you take a bunch
But the mentality
Is irresponsible 34
So he keeps you know every now and again he'll bring up those
Those
We've already talked about that Rebecca silver
Toothpaste
To reconsider throughout this
Alex gets down to
Little bit of talking about
His DUI
My situation
Twi
You got arrested on Monday evening into Tuesday morning
And
He seems to think
That
The media
Is
Controlled by the CIA and they're attacking him
By people covering his DUI
Giant development
Ultraman coronavirus run
Not here at the moment but first
Look at the CNN headlines
Infowars Alex Jones accused
Twi
Haha
Got them
Thousands of the newspapers every TV channel that you randomly checked because it was typing then
CIA Mockingbird program
CIA operative
Mockingbird
And Obama is still in control of it
Everyone else is saying
Headlines
Accused of BWI
This is just a case of CNN initially run with the headline Alex Jones accused of DWI then later updating it
Alex Jones arrested on DWI charge
Those are accurate state
Both are fine to run as headlines
But the latter is probably more indicative of what the story is so I can understand why an editor might change
Change that later
It's fair to assume that I say that Alex was a
Accused of DWI by the state of Texas
It's the same thing you know where you presume someone's innocent
Until they've been to court
Alex allegedly was driving drunk
You can say that
It's also fair to say that he was arrested for DWI because he definitely was
Mark Richards was accused of both killing that guy as well as
Flying a plane and being off-planet has anyone accused him of the ladder now he is only guilty of
Whataburger
Claim the ladder
You can't say his wife has a
Accused him of being offline
He said okay that's
Just an instance of an editorial update that Alex is going to try and eat some kind of Nefarious plot to demonize him in the media
You don't talk about anything other than the reality
And his audiences Prime to believe him
People Janik says business
CIA Mockingbird stuff so nothing that you see about Alex in the media is real at all
Ignore it
There's a bit of a segment
Where Alex retells the story of being
We arrested for drunk driving
It is kind of sad
What you see is a complete
Refusal in any way except dangerous
And wrong
And he just is is
Blaming
Everybody
But himself
Import
Everybody who's writing these stories about his DWI
Propaganda fide propaganda
Of the media
Yeah
Yeah that
Every major Channel
Every major newspaper
Jones
Twi
70w
Because that's what that is
0.6
Oh you heard that
So it's not unify propaganda for media Outlets report that Alex got arrested for DWI
It would be bad recording
Play said that he'd been found guilty of it in court they said that he'd been
Convicted but to say that he got arrested or that he was charged
Those are accurate statement
Eastbound wonderly CNN Headline that has been up
Hate it that says he was accused of buwi
So what he's doing is claiming the only accurate headline where's the restaurant propaganda
Set
Alex drove drunk
Instead of taking responsibility for his actions
He needs the world to know that Not only was he the victim
In the arrest
He's also the victim in
Interglobal send
Because the media is accurately reporting
Also pretty much every state has a DWI limit of .08
With the exception of Utah
Utah as a limited .05 but it's also important
Keep in mind that Utah is the state
The country with the most restrictive alcohol laws
I only only state-regulated liquor stores can sell beer with higher than
5% alcohol
There's a bunch of cities in the state where you can
Can't even buy booze at all
Using Utah as an example of why you shouldn't
Have been arrested for drunk driving is not a good argument come on
Who cares
Some
I don't think that I'm going
To let it pass
So Alex decides
2 oz
At this point
He's taking the knee
He's getting out of Studio Beats from Wednesday to Friday and
The he'll be you'll be out all over the neck
Go and get behind the wheel of a car and have a high alcohol level
Yes
Before but certainly not
Not an argument
That's the case
I was already taking next week off I'll call the show something but
And I just happen to be so free of it
But I'm never going to drink again
I'm really conflicted about this because
It's that intersection of the personal life
An on-air Life of Alex
That I find really did
Difficult to navigate
I don't play this clip to mock Alex for his claims that he'll never drink
And again I'm playing this to demonstrate what Alex thinks is worthwhile spending time with
On his show
There's no standards or professionalism on the show at all
He's supposed to be getting into the big news about the
Coronavirus but it's about 40 minutes into the episode of this point
And so far it's mostly been
And being defensive about his sales practices and a big defensive about a Twi
I understand that in order for him to
To continue to operate as a business
He has to protect
After the scam from the natural consequences
Of the way he runs the sky
But it really feels like he's coming to the point where he's in over his
It's it
Feels it feels like especially
The way he
Do you need to respond to these things on air so much
Time with me
Opposition to other times things have happened he's really been much more deflection
Oriented
Stand to these accusations it away it's like
Buddy
You are going
Turn into Lenny Bruce
Like to do all your stand up shows about how you got to rest
Yeah yeah
Not its
Not as good
Strategy
You still got to give people a good show if you want to drive
Yeah only be like most devoted
Folk
Are going to put up with that kind of rayon
Entertaining Lotus
Is 4 hours long
But Alex only host
The first 3 hours
When that was the third of the way through his on-air time on this
Button episode
Restatement of his dumb virus stuff
You provided no,
Other than his own person
Issues
Bleeding into his
Professional life
He can't perform isn't effective propagandist
Because his narcissistic need
To protect his own self-image
Just getting in the way
Exactly like the band
Exactly
Look at you
The band 311
United's I have no idea about anything about him it's just the only name I can picnic
I know two people in 311
This week off but if he thinks
That that stuff with his silver sales
Just going to blow over in that time
He might be in for
A bit of a surprise
I don't say I don't know if that's
So Alex decides going to buckle down now
About to hit the latest on the coronavirus coronavirus and the response to it in a coordinated level
President-trump
I believe they probably already released until you should get ready
A whole line of products that are known and documented wow
Customer research and studies
Really good for your body boost your immune system and we have the DNA Force plus now back in stock
Looks like The infomercials not quite done yet the fake out
The old eyebrow fake we got to get to the coronavirus we're going to get to all that but
I just got to tell you about these amazing products that are back
Supergirl
It's amazing
So Alex Hawksmoor hear about that the
I think that this just
It's going to be
Almost exactly the same thing as a clip I already played
But I think it's important to stress that I believe there is an awareness that Alex knows
That the claims
In those
Bedford he has are just about the womb
We also have the super silver toothpaste
With a nano
And I'm not going to sit here and go into a long discussion about
The patented nanosilver but it is being approved over-the-counter in the super silver for topical
The strongest silver you're going to find over-the-counter
So I believe there is an awareness
Of what the actual things that he's been blurry
He specifically said this is been approved in the wound
Specifically
It's been approved yet
Angele
And I think this takes away a little bit of the plausible deniability about like him being can
Confused are not knowing what these
These things are
I don't I don't know
Yeah I mean
I'm sure you could office gator
Enough
Pastor the
Shittiness of the illegal
Possibly
This is definitely
He knows what
Yeah I've been wearing out-of-court what I can see from the indications of his
His words
Past 3 years
I don't think Alex
Getting away with it
Question
Tell Barnes to go home
Good work
Talking here about the surprise sale and I think Alex is back to
Canadian money
Nanosilver products get your ex to the rx-3
40% off right now infowarsstore.com
Do this next week
All the free right now and it's a free shipping for wide is implemented again right now stay with us
I suspect that Alex is facing
Sing some new legal
I plan for some fines in my near future
Stores ready for that
I have
A reasonable suspicion
But that might be the
Kcpa
GPS man
So
During the second hour of the show Alex Lee
Okay good
Do you just leave
Take care of The Assault reviews on there
Yes Owen Shroyer fill in with this guest named Gary Haven who Alex says is a pilot and a billionaire
Supposedly just met with Governor Abbott
I have no idea
Gary Haven is buddies on it forward so I do not trust him at face value
Maybe he met with Governor Abbott maybe you didn't I have no idea
Anyway Alex leave because he's dealing with things
He doesn't want the audience to know that
In the aftermath of his arrest Alex
Ex-wife filed a motion
To be granted custody of their children
Which ultimately led to a judge
Requiring Alec
Text to get drug and alcohol test
That news broke on Wednesday so I'm pretty certain that this is
Is what I was trying to dress off air
Wow he was
Decided to leave his show to get healthiest all
Again his personal troubles are bleeding heavily into his professional life in such a way that he's unable to do his job
And host then Mike Adams takes over for the rest of the show
Alex did nothing on this episode literally nothing outside of pretending he's a victim and his DWI
Anton's of expanded infobear
The show is
I I think I'm going to steal that and
And use that as
I've take care of yourself
Globalist
Globulin
Call Oliva party
Going to be there in the morning
I'm under heavy assault by the globalists talk to you guys later
My bad I mean you're out of boobs
I'm so weak
Get to the 12th
Already
And Alex
This is one of my favorite
F****** announcements to start a show that I've ever heard this is so good
I was locked
And loaded complaining
Focus with just
Come on air
Research and in the president
Start getting ready to speak again and I said well let me just start the show with that then of course the computer
Frieza shop in Manchester way works Nigeria
I want to lay it out I'm going to rebroadcast for a while to cool down
Anybody's fault
Laser focused again and come back
Gouache
Before I lay all this out
Just calm down
So what happened is Alex David hours and hours of research
Figured everything out he's got the globalist master plan that he's going to lay out for you then started watching
Trump give a speech
There's a glitch any lost everything. Please reset
Please I got to go to rebroadcast I don't
Know what is funnier
There's two possibilities really and that is that Alex's dresser to bluffing
And trying to be like I understand everything but I'm not ready to to lay it out
Because I don't really understand everything that's kind of funny that bluff
But it's also funny or to imagine
That he did
Prepare and got everything in order and then
Just got so mad because of a takeaway baby like
I don't
Remember what the globalist
Liquid Richard
F****** high school
You got your term paper
Oh s*** I forgot to save it
Yeah but Alex's that guy but he has no teacher it's just the audience kind of
And now let him do anything
You can just say that through the global state has homework every single time and damn globalist
I didn't do my book report don't care don't exist
So Alex does
Get back on track
And he has
Usher
Shocking
Okay
Very good chance that
Tom Hanks of the total Global to take the president
Alex is a Tom Hanks prison
Yep yep. Max is Tom Hanks and his wife making
Something positive
Coronavirus in order to take attention away from Trump speech
The globalist made bachelor party with this in mind and this was the plan from the very beginning
Absolutely
Kisho and now we're here
This is an interesting intersection of like qanon and Alex
They both hate
Very weird Cloud Atlas with Tom Hanks
I think everything makes a lot more so
Sure
So Alex I initially thought that that was kind of a throwaway thing and he's
Just mad that Tom Hanks and Izakaya Faking It
You going to bring it up again later
But Alex gets
How to
This is going to this is going to kill
Almost everybody everybody
You've either
Simultaneously as
Personal issues bleed into
His coverage in his inability to
Perform
Is job
And he started
On a pretty bad place
In terms of
Panicking
An escalating things
But it was Mike Adams who said that it's over for Humanity there long to be Lone Survivor
Alex is now himself getting into bit more fatalistic
Overview
Laser focused and just go to the main point of the night we come back
And that's where it came from who's behind it what the plan is
I'm going to give you the bad news when I come back
I figured it out
We can walk through all the background in the viruses
She's going to make AIDS and HIV down the road
Look like
Very mild problem
They have just introduced to you
Population program
We don't stop them
Most of you will die for this
Sears news today
Next decades news today
Living defense that takes care of
5 months each back in stock
What this behavior is really coming back in full force this
Most of you are going to die of this also
Listen your you've got maybe five six years left don't worry about it we got some good s*** back in stock
Bye bye bye
It's not like this it's not necessarily went away or anything but it is
Really ubiq
This. I know you think that just because my personal life is clearly falling down around me that maybe I'm exaggerating
What is happening in the world right now
He's going to die in the world
Probably just because I predict
A little bit that maybe the bed I'm going to die myself
I'm going to die I'm going to die we're all going to die
Anyways we got the other DNA Force back in addressing
How you feel by the end of it
So earlier Alex was saying that he sat down
Fertilized everything he got the globalist master plan in his mind that then he got mad and forgot it all
You're running we've got
The globalist masterful
In mind right ready to share it
You may think
How does Alex know these things do the globalist they're going to do and all those like how does he predict
Things ahead of time
Well thankfully
Alex decided to take a little hit his
Jake's Plano
People ask how I was able to do that
I did not get that information
Person
I was younger by Brian was
Better
Thousands of integrated point
I should be clear he's talking about predicting 911
That's what he's talking about I thought you made it
Explicit
Pre-programming
For the fact
And
That much data
Call the police
How does he know how to
Only kills every few months
Finally be there in the right Zone and catch him trying to kidnap a woman
There's a lots of cases
Con artist 1-800 numbers in 90
And it's the same thing you got all this real data
And then your conscious brain is 100 times begging
Or less
Powerful
Right
Is an arrowhead
Unable to understand why
So right off the bat Alex predicted 911 because he listen to Bill Cooper's hour of the time and just do the prediction wholesale format
That's all he did there it has nothing to do with this subconscious
His mind remember the constellation of datapoint
Whatever
You guys ripped off another dude
Hasbro Bill predicted it I mean
Bin Laden had attacked the World Trade Center previously and wasn't making a secret that he wanted to do it again so
Whatever kind of had a vendetta
While it is true that some police departments consult psychics on a very limited
Bases in some cases
And some mixed results what else is describing is not the real world version of this sort of thing he's describing
TV shows and movies
Yeah if you listen to that and you don't clearly hear a man that
Knows he's
Full of s***
You are probably a man that knows your full
So Alex
Describing that as like all these data points and whatever he can put it all together
Describe the sort of like
Almost enters a state
Where you can make predictions
And see things he goes into mint at mode
Right
Describe another dude
Oh I apologize
Describe that
And then he's like
But
With the Coronavirus
Tire setup is like
I have psychic powers
And I can see things
Has nothing to do with what I'm talking about right now
Not helpful
I don't work on the CIA
Contact me
How how does
How do you say
Music venue are rock concert
Night
Sunday show
Okay yeah we don't think you're involved
I mean how the hell do you do that
No
Really
Getting this place
That's that Easter level that I don't know how I do it okay
With the virus
It's not that
He is
Solutely documented and proven
Enrages me
That
It's so obvious and that we can stop these people
So I'm giving this a little bit of short shrift
As we're getting
Into this episode where you know he's talked about Saul proven
Because a little bit later this episode we will see Alex
Really formulate and uncompressed down into a
Digestible form
Pieces of the narrative standard model yet laid out
We were just on the episode that comes out today of cognitive dissonance
Cute snakes
But on that episode
We discussed Alex's coronavirus narratives is what does theories are
And my response was
Along the lines of
He's all over the
Say anything that's probably something
I believe that on this episode what we look at is
I really solidify
Of the the narrative
A Guinea
Ignoring and not worrying about
Some of the
External things
Anxiety disorder
Distractions just getting
Get down to what's important
So I'm saving a bit of discussion of that for that cuz all of its going to
So Alec
Let's get down to business talking about how Trump is doing great
And you got to really be you got to be really reaching for a positive Trump women
But Alex is hoping in this club but I think is really important
And I think it damaged
Straight
Other aware
That he has about what
He does for a
And if we fail this test
You're going to be ruled by the threat
Unending invisible bio
Weapons
Remote control for a long time and the globalist brags all these locations are going to use
The threat of mass
You know all that
It's obvious
But
Scale
And I'll tell you the only person I see is the world leader
That is not going along with this and that it's farted and it was shot through it is Trump
Emily knows exactly what's going on
Inside
Trichomes are linked up with another side
The Taiwan embarrassment
And then try to topwater economy that's all about that
Virus
Dragonball from when it's known to be man-made
Close
So I think there's something really teachable
Side vent clip
Like a lot of it is meaningless nonsense but I
I think you showed a little bit too much of his cards there when he says if we don't get the narrative out on a mass scale we're screwed
What's revealing about that is Alex he's what he does is putting out narrative
Just as I am
See what he does iic it exactly the same way
He's not putting out reality he's telling a story
Any needs that story to spread in order for people to fall into his marketing
At least on a regular level that's the case
Pino's
You know that he's pushing a narrative
It's just talk
But when Alex has something like if we don't get at this narrative we're screwed
It's important to consider what he's actually saying
The Nativity needs to get out of the idea that the globalist they're behind this release of a man-made biof
Which is designed to crash the US economy and get Trump out of office
That's the narrative that he needs to
Describe
Kind of obvious why
Alex is really saying here is that
Reality is going to look damning in hindsight some preemptive damage control
I have a narrative in place
Explains away all of
The things that Trump didn't do
All of the failures and response
That is
That's all he saying
If we don't get this narrative out realities going to look really f****** bad guys and our entire philosophy
The government not doing anything
And maybe the federal government not existing
That is going to look
Like
They're going to almost be in exact
Example of why that's a bad
Way to organize Society
And you can tell that he
He is like
I don't hear his heart
Like he not like
There's no way that you can
Straight faces
Dudley say that we
Trump is doing a good job like younger
World leader who's doing a great job what about boosie boo boo
So I don't know
It's it's weird
Anyway
He has said in the past we think a bit more now
And that is that this virus is a chimera
It was like Skype
The word
So he talks about that
It's a but it's secretly not a virus
This is a ton of viruses
Cuz get mutates into different chimeras
There's been a bunch of different versions ever released
Are texting right now our response to see they can lock us down
And we lock down properly then they're going to release the real Bayou version will then start wife
Global depopulation operation
Terminate you and your family get change
Dramatic
He says the virus
Is a bunch of different viruses
Susannah Kami Wright the real viruses virus
Get back to what he was talking about earlier we got chills talking about the
What is lying about it
Some preliminary studies out of China
According to the South China Morning Post
Researchers were finding that there were very
Stickley relevant drops
Send some of the early symptoms of the virus and patients who tested positive
Poster January 23rd
I suppose those who tested positive
What are the theories that's been put forth by the researchers is that early on the virus had to strain
One be more aggressive than the other
What symptoms showing up
Pretty noticeable
The quarantine that was placed on areas of China created very strong selective pressure
Against the spread of the more aggressive version
Send it would have been noticed much
Much more easily
If their numbers are correct
This makes
Some sense given that their samples reflect a drop from the aggressive strain being 96% of the samples
Collected prior to 2000 January 23rd
60% of the samples collect
Did actor
It should be pointed out though that their dissenting opinions about this research
And it's not even accepted as established fact that there are two strains of the virus
Even if the proposed 2strains hypothesis is
Correct according to an op-ed in
CNN
Professor in the department of
Epidemiology
And microbial diseases at Yale public school public health
Quote the two proposed S&L coronavirus strains
Only differ by two mutations
And are 99.99
3% identical
It's extremely likely that any vaccine
Design for one coronavirus will be protective of
Against the other
I hear that guy's expertise and
And it does seem comforting but I would like
Like to know what
Somebody and their guts
Feel about it
Well we already heard that
DJ guy in Texas
Does yelling
Well I'm going to listen to the gut
Chirped
Viruses mutate because they make mistakes and replication when they're copying their RNA
These mutations
Can have basically no effect on their characteristics or they can have
Effects that are either advantageous or disadvantageous to the virus
However some things that would appear advantageous to a virus
Might actually be detrimental to it
Mutation that makes a virus more aggressive can I have the effective
Debilitating The Host
It makes them less likely to spread the virus to others
It would be disadvantageous to
From the virus
Just like if you have laser eyes
Sure that's cool but you
You can never look at the
The people you love without wearing glasses very difficult about that
Cartoony drawing
There's a complicated interconnectedness when you look at virus mutation and in the case of the current outbreak there's just not enough in for
Formation to make a concrete assessment about any of it
Over Alex's headlines about these two strains and he's determined
But that's proof
Secretly a ton of different viruses in one
Is is right
He's just dumb
Interesting lead is very closely mirrors
Conspiracy theory that was promoted by Russian
Can scientists after the 2003 SARS outbreak
They claim that SARS is actually combination of measles and mumps Wichita
Definitely was not
This order theory is pretty common in propaganda circles whenever there's an outbreak
That's a very human impulse
Do I
Facebook
With uncertainty
There's a need to craft a narrative and a concrete villain out of the situation
Where
Might just be human failing
And we fall into that
The same issue it's with Avengers movies you know we already have measles that's not
Scary enough sir
We need measles is
You need the bad guy to be escalated
Also when Alex has at the end there it came out of Wuhan
That's a contradiction of his established
Conspiracy about this
It didn't come out of Wuhan according to Alex it came out of UNC
Chapel Hill and Obama sold it to the Chinese
He's just trying to say something you thought so too deep and
Profound
Contemplatively does whip
It did it did have a did have a tagline kind of feel to it though it came from
That's not bad
No movie on top is it at
Line on the back of one of the sci-fi novels he read and bases world you are awesome
It's contradictory
Position
Alex gets back to rambling about how he's the
The victim of driving drunk
I'm sure there's a concrete example.
CIA
Mockingbird operation is out to get it
I'll show you a photo that was sent to me by one of my friends his dad on a cruise
Cab off the coast of South Africa
Terrorist
Cruisers
Bass
They have a article about Alex Jones
Twi
There it is
Why would that
Be on a cruise ship out of South Africa
Published operation Mockingbird what it's called
In every newspaper in the world that's affiliated with it and every broadcast system
Every newspaper
System
Horse Eye blue under
Illegal lemon
I text you at the jail so I had to be taken to jail it's ridiculous
A will do that to you
Alex is so desperate to find another narrative here other than I got it
Vwi
And I guess the best I can come up with his people reporting on my DWI is proof the CIA is trying to get
Yeah I got a little lame and weak
But whatever he needs
To do not to face reality is what he's going
Going to do
So Alex flashes up on camera this picture that someone sent him and it's just a shot of like a
I printed out newsletter kind of thing
It doesn't say the name of the papers that introduced a little bit of difficulty in figuring out exactly who he was
Being a Mockingbird CIA Shields
But the picture did give me one
In the upper right-hand corner of the page and said kvh media
Who are clearly the producers of this newsletter
I thought kvh's filing with it
Security Exchange Commission
According to
The descriptions of busy
They are quote
A leading provider of commercially license
Entertainment including News sports
Music and movies
Commercial and Leisure customers
In the maritime hotel and Retail Market
This is a company that provides broadband
A cruise ships and resorts
And also news
One thing that confuses me though is that I'm not sure that they send
Physical newspapers
Cruise ships
That seems almost prohibitively expensive and difficult
Especially considering they say they primarily offer a quote
News from home digital newspaper
Paper service
That includes more than 100 daily newspapers and more than 20 languages
That at the end of 2015 was delivered more than
Commercial ships
Hotels
And cruise ships
Digital content can be printed on board or viewed on a tablet smartphone or left
I remember playing Paperboy on Game Boy you used to
To deliver paper
Do cruise ships all the
Hyman that
That was the last
Last level is very difficult
Dogs and then throw papers into the ocean was like the boss
So I took another look at that picture Alex as I noticed something peculiar
The blurb about Alex is just an AP article syndicated through this
Just kvh portal
The article right after it is cooked Coachella festival postponed
Also syndicated from the associated
Depress
There's another article about Harvey Weinstein Center
Something which appears to be syndicated from
Aafp
What's going on
Yes
This is a publication called news
And it's just an aggregation of news
From large newswires around the world
Newslink has a ton of options
And then what they have
How Works basically
Is it they have
Approximately
100 different option
Prepackaged newsletters
Should are just aggregation
Oceans of Lake if you want
What kind of focus do you want are you a cricket
Sports will give you Cricket award for
It's the one I'm using
Is like if you have
Accrue
A bunch of people who are from the Philippines
Score on this cruise ship
They will have news that Centric to the Filipino Audi
That's smart rights they have a ton of these options
But also
People on board the cruise ship can customize
So you can make
Make your own newsletter the Taylor's at
Itself to the audience
People that you have on the boat
I don't know what's going on here exactly where there anything a cruise can't turn into a buffet dad is there anything
Lockhart
So I don't know if this is necessarily it's got a Mockingbird operation
Associated Press story about Alex getting a DWI
Specific cruise ship decided to include in their newsletter
Or it was part of one of the package
Newsletters
I'm not entirely sure
Alex wants to make this a nefarious
Conspiracy the only bad guy I guess
Kvh
Which media if you want to say that or
Captain of this ship or whatever
Who's in charge of the
The newsletter on that ship
I don't know if this is a week
Wheat beers at the AP is run by the
That's really his only
I mean I guess if he wants to take that swing
Go for it
I'm fine with that whatever
Alex
But here's the problem
If the AP is run by
The CIA he should just say that
Instead he's using this bulletin on a South African
Cruise ship as his example
Right there's too many steps removed for the accusation to be that it's evil
Something about the cinder
Indication of this news Ryan
And the steps
So you have to go through either the captain or JV
Choose whoever you want to slander Alex girlfriend
Question
Was the
I don't know
It is not
His name was Phillips
So Alex gets back to being
Sensitive
About
Selling his silver
In terms of e virus
Pizza Town
On-air the fact that
Hospitals have nanosilver
You go to CVS now they got a whole section of silver
Everybody knows silver kills a virus a bacteria
Resale
Different
Silver's not alive
Nanotech
And in the media thinks everybody said during those old Jones claims he can cure the coronavirus not ever said that
You had the virus replicate
Personally gargle with it knocks it out on contact that's a good for
Okay well here's a little clip
Alex
It's over in ways that are probably not
That we sold out of the 16oz of your guard over the nanosilver the stock meditech
Coronavirus
I was if I was going to Taiwan
I'd be guzzling
Banana platinum silver weave
Sorry
Brush your teeth
Bio silver
From the Pentagon that knocks out
Thesaurus coronavirus family
Security in the air
Found with and receive on
The SARS virus was the coronavirus man-made others that 12
What's in our
Super Silver
Hardly ever get sex
Getting sick last week for me and Arlo
Dawn
So I think that what you have
Is
I guess Alex is main defense
Is like
What is a knockout mean
Take out Pirates I didn't say that it would take it out of your body I just said it would take it out on a nice
Little date
I think that you could make a pretty compelling case
That the way that wasn't
Intended to be heard by the audience
Because you can't really knock something out if it's not there
Right
Ethan Hawke took her out on a date in before midnight it was a
He took her out you know it wasn't the Killer
She was present
That's true
Find me spoilers
Some emotional troubles
So I don't
Compelling argument
He's make
Getting here and he tries to
Claim like
I've been selling this silver exactly the same way before the Opera
Which I know is not active big sweater this is
Really really layered
Oh no he just came Fly by Night
Really before this whole thing popped up
I showed you this
Tabs
Apopka right now sitting out season desist letter to the
Keith Mueller American biotech labs
And then we got their letters here from 13 years ago Texas A&M University
Symptoms Health Science Center
What they found was there
Nano silver
Taking out
The tsar's family family I don't know how one but that's kind of
Dancing like a pesticide kill cockroaches
Salinas fair for Alex to say that he was like selling his immune gargle and the toothpaste
Prior
That's true
But it was telling it the same way
Clippity brought out these studies and these
These letters vdi Pryor
To the
And that's not
Play Supercut of him selling it irresponsibly I assume that
Do you have a full suit
I'm not doing
I don't know what that would look like but here it is
Alex brought up
These studies about the effectiveness of the nanosilver Visa vie
Thesaurus family
That was on January 31st 2020
Even says on that app
So that he
Just been cleared
To discuss this stuff
Brutally cleared by his silver supplier
Yes
American biotech labs
And that makes some sense
You know how every time Alex pulls out the
This piece of evidence he begins with the name Doctor Keith Mueller as you heard In that clip right there course
That's because the top document his stack
Mysuu Versailles stack
Is an email from doctor
Keith Mueller who's the CEO
American biotech labs
The email reads quote
The report is the coronavirus is like the SARS virus and Homeland Security put out the data that our product could kill them
TV above lateral from the director of the Homeland Security
The secretary
Dr. Carlton is a brilliant man who came up with the Mobile hospital system
We only received a copy of it because our testimony before Congress on balearia and it was
Included as an
An addendum to that testimony
We never received a good copy but we did get a copy and it's worth the reading on the
The claims they make about our product
This should be pointed out is not an email address to Alex
It's addressed to someone named Ken and another person named
Kimball
Kimball is shown in the email to be Kimball Mueller
Who is listed as the Eastern Us sales rep for silver biotics there Silver Line
I'm not sure who can is but I would assume that it's someone else who work
Works with American biotech labs and the silver biotics
That email is about the silver
As you can tell from the attached
Letter that that email refers to
This is not the same as saying that the Homeland
Security found that the gargle
I said nef
Cassie against sars-like virus
Weather in Arden Hills
Same silver
This information cannot be used to justify those sorts of claims and if Alex tries to use this in court
You going to lose that case
Those imaginary cease-and-desist letters that he's going to send out are going to do s***
This is Alex threatening to sue the Associated Press all over it
Also you may notice that
The email from dr. Mueller starts quote the report is that the
The Coronavirus
Is like the Stars by
Witcher tell you that this information was
Was created
After the outbreak begin
You can
Clearly see a date
January 24th
20/20 on the
Email
Tracks with the timeline of Alex receiving this from someone a few days later
And then bring it on air on January 31st
It's important
I want to pretend that is sales tax
Predate the outbreak
Because if he's
Opportunistically selling the silver
Response to an outbreak that makes him look like what he is
Con man
Unfortunately I wasn't do this you and I know for a fact that he began in response to the outbreak
Behaving this way
And Alex is on document
Proof is that date on the email is
Pretty f****** thing
This email didn't exist
Prior to January 24th
How Alec
TxDOT the document
These quote-unquote cleared
To bring to the air
Time travel
His defense in court that's what I would
That's a better argument than what he always does
Family brings out his strawman friend he was off-planet
Department of the Army Headquarters United States
Where's the
Hm
30 years ago
The FDA says you're not supposed to say you need oxygen to live
Not said you need water to live
These are these standards, Anthony bring out whenever he's a you know a position where he looks really bad
Mike Adams
Comes on to help Ranger
Our good buddy
Not a good buddy
He comes on and what he does immediately out of the gate
Is defend Alex
About the criticism
But he's getting
For the silver sale
This f****** guy
Now you tell you
He is no help for it
Your comments on
Silver and copper I just want to mention new research
About how long coronavirus survive on surfaces
Real quick Altos not talk about copper only talk about silver together
Bring it all in there all precious metals copper surfaces
An hour's whereas the virus survivors from many days up to nine days on other services such as cardboard
Are plastic or others
And silver is known to it to kill
The viability of viruses and kill bacteria even more aggressively
Copper
Estimation as an elemental scientist
We deal with almonds all the time we run microbiology as well
Uber would probably kill this virus on surfaces
Copper
Anyone saying that silver doesn't work against the coronavirus is their minds or just a literate
And also I'm an alchemist
My friend Jack Parsons was an elemental scientist and you sir are no Jack Parson
Like is referring to a recent not yet. Viewed study that looked at how long coronavirus could survive in very good condition
Including on various surfaces
Here's where the first problem with Mike's comments pop up
Silver was not one of the surfaces they test
So this study does not really helping
That doesn't
In their testing they found that the viruses
Detectable for four hours or so on
Copper as opposed to 24 hours on cardboard
And 72 hours
Plastic and stainless steel
This is useful information to have four people
And if the results stand up the peer-review it'll be a good
To know about the virus
However the way mic is using this information
He's completely f***** up
He's coming on the show right after Alex gets super defensive about Hobbies
Being criticized for selling his ingestible silver ship
To make Alex feel better about the people rightly criticize and have bike pulls out their study that says it's
Silver Ingot silver kills viruses more aggressively than copper
Copper is in the sky
Mike is bringing silver into it for no reason
Here's where the major problem
The study Micah siding is about viruses on Surface
It's not inside the body
If Alex were selling silver countertops then maybe this would be relevant
Now there's literally no connection between the observed lifespan of a virus on copper
India Sudafed
Eating silver will do to it
But if Mike really does want to make this connection
Wisely advised in his listeners to
Copper
There's a Stephanie right there stating the copper kills virus faster than
Steel
Should start eating 1976 pennies
You can't sell pennies to people
There is a lot of dirty value
If Micah sings should seriously he needs to turn in his health ranging badge
Cuz this is pretty embarrassing to Elemental science
It's full-time
Elemental science
What kind of a****** would say as an element
Little scientist inferred from him so I'm going to let it slide
You come on
Jamaica some big news about the state of California
And he wants Trump
Nobody wants Trump
Some military
Sacramento County
Dropping all quarantines
No longer going to try to contain this there just releasing all high-risk patients right out to the public
Doesn't sound right
I called for Trump
To declare National Emergency and literally dispatch the military to take over Sacramento
County in order to re-establish basic medical principles
The modern era
They're deliberately want to bring down Trump
By spreading the disease and infections sabotage
The part of Sacramento County
It's not complacent
My curiously doesn't mention that YOLO in
Placer County's in California are also doing the same
Same thing the Sacramento County
I wonder if that's just because he's only read one headline on the story and decided to run with it is a narrative
Probably
So this is situation where Sacramento County has decided that they're not going to impose a 14-day corn
19 on everyone who's come in contact with someone who has the virus
If you're sick you're still to isolate
But if you came in contact with someone who ends up testing positive
The advice
Bi-County gibbet is giving now is
The full story here is at the head of Sacramento Sacramento County's Department of Health Services doctor
Peterbilt
Bailenson
He decided that we're at the point where they need to dry
Different approach
You determine that the county was past the point of reasonable can
Containment and it reached a point where mitigation was
The main priority
Have you told the Sacramento Bee
Once you get a certain number of cases
It's hard to continue contact Trace back the way that you tried initially
Originally
Do we move to mitigate
Which is basically trying to mitigate the risk to those who are most at
The elderly and those with chronic underlying
Conditions
An epidemiologist interviewed for that article in the bee said that this shift in approach May
Makes total sense
In early stages when you have a hope for
But it's good to quarantine as many high likelihood person
As you
You can't Raystown
Once there's enough cases that becomes prohibited from a resource Tamplin
You need to try a different
Approach which these counties in California
Cornea are doing
Whatever your thoughts on this are it's not an attempt to spread the virus
And disorders narrative hitmaka
Spreading is really just
Indicative
Desire to see Trump
A brutal authoritarian Crackdown
Ion people he doesn't
So you're telling me that
The city of Sacramento
Did not get together and hold us
Secret vote
To release all of their infected citizens
No in order to take down
That would be
However pretty amazing if Sacramento did
Successfully taken a while
That'd be pretty cool
In the United States California is the most
Heated state
It's two people like Mike and Alex
Pretext for Trump to place
The capital city on Durham
Military martial law
Those dudes Jack to
That's all that's really going on
Are you twisting
Some story into being like they're trying to take out Trump
Is the bad guy in
This is terrible
So I thought that Mike talk
Think about the copper and silver defense
Sprouts
The things I've heard him say in a long time but he one-ups
Another big factor in all this Alex
This is a question do mosquitoes
Parry this blood-borne disease mosquitoes spread this
That mosquitoes spread malaria plus diseases that are blood-borne
When mosquitoes bite you they actually suck some of your blood
That's how malaria spreads
Malaria is a virus of course I
Viruses are present in blood
Can bacteria
Can mosquitoes spread that we don't know the answer to that yet
If you needed any reason to doubt likes credentials as a health Ranger there you go
Illegitimately has no idea how mosquito borne illnesses are transmitted and yet here he is acting like an expert on the subject
What does indicates to me that he's never even looked into this
Because if he thinks while they're sucking your blood obviously little bit blood they drink earlier
You later you take a sip of wine maybe you spill a little bit it's the same thing
If you look see if he thinks that he can
You possibly have looked in
Because if he did he would understand the 22 proboscis
The mosquitoes used to suck your blood
You understand that mosquito borne illness
Are not spread by the blood that mosquitoes drink previously
But what that blood could have infected the mosquito with
Mosquitoes inject a little bit of their saliva into you when they bite you in this is how they transmit diseases like malaria
If a particular disease cannot infect them
Mosquito and replicate in the Mosquito Lake
Cannot transmit that disease no matter what blooded drank earlier
This is legitimately some basics
Stuff that Mike is 100% wrong about it's disqualifying
Being a helper
You can't be a health Ranger if you think
This is
Cambia Health Ranger if you have a first
First grade Anatomy textbook and then you just start make
Well actually mosquitoes spread Disease by a psycho
Link with other mosquitoes who have contract
Active diseases
From of course the diner
And that's how we were all going to go
Valtrex perfect
Totally clear
It may end up being the case but the virus will be able to
Transmitted by mosquitoes
That might
Be the case
But there is no indication that that is
The case currently
There there
People who
Understand this
Far better
They have sat there is no indications of present
Sometime if this is something they can be transmitted by mosquitoes but
That's another May later be a point when they're so we might find that out
Now this ship could get wild but
This is something that Mike would only be saying she was trying to scare people at this
And if you
Other possibilities
Literally knows nothing
Thing is just talkingshit
Dragon sound like
He knows what he's talking about
Does he have a personal
Grudge against
Yes he's been searching for a real California
So this virus
Is bad
To embarrass Trump
Mosquitoes are going to carry a tray
Bright copper copper if you want
But
It's really all just
Just about something
According to Mike
There's another stage
Used to this,
Okay it's not his other stage
Did he said before which was getting
Tricking Trump into canceling the Alexa
The Dictator
Not that it's not that there's something else
This is nowhere near over
China's hoping that America
Collapses in terms of its infrastructure
It's hospitals and its stock market
Once that happens China will unleash even more attacks
Possibly
In a worst-case scenario
An actual
Invasion
America via California
As realistic although it's it's pretty far down the road
Before they would even
I was I was very worried about
You know the thing about America that I've always
Concerned about is
Is Landon
That's one of those
Practical things that were always accept
There's a there's a number reason
Dump
And it'll be really dumb by the end of this episode when this narrative has taken
Re-emergence
Google
Sure
There's a lot of stuff that's going on
Right in the news
That doesn't look good for Alex
There's a lot of articles
At this point on March 12th that are flying around about
I'm selling it supplements badly
Unethical
There is
Lingering
Headlines and articles about him getting arrested
.0 s78
Irish people laughing about his
Defense of himself
Annoying
But look man
It's all not true all those headlights are true
The attacks the lies and propaganda you can't believe
Any other
Is deception telling the truth infowars.com
It's perfect and if you can get people to believe that your golden
Cult leaders
I always say the same s*** you know there's really only there's only a certain subset of things you can say if you're okay
That's because it works at clear pathway
Clarity to being a cult leader I think where it's just like that black and white
For Millennia I'll just do what those guys
Does did boo
So now Mike gets into
Oster
Rochelle
And eat reiterate
That he wants
Everyone
All the officials in Sacramento to be arrested
County
In California
Sacramento County deliberately engaging in criminal sabotage
To spread this virus across America
President Trump to declare National Emergency
Send the military into Sacramento County
Seize control of the public health
Official
March them out
Prosecute them
And re-establish basic modern medical common sense
That's exactly what I'm calling for you can quote me on that
It has to be done
That's
Not a good
Quote me on this I would like
President-trump
To burn Sacramento to the ground
Murder all of its citizens
Larrays the power ups
The heavens is a signal that modern metal
How we do things and then brighten
You're the rest of us
Kidnap Gavin Newsom and making a gesture
Yeah I don't know
I don't like
The trend is going
Mike is hurt
A lot of messaging
From
Call Moorhead
They're saying hey man you don't need to get by
All the toilet paper you don't need
To do all that
That's bad because then
It creates
Get toilet right there is an issue though
Marriott
Yes
It's not
And bikes
Things like hey man you all are hypocrites
And by the way wasn't the mainstream media telling us this whole time
Before all this
Everybody should buy more stuff
President Bush
Economy
You're always told to buy more stuff but then suddenly
What what
Where does that come from
Buy more stuff
Consumerism
Is the
Complaint he has
What's the weather for talking about like after 9/11 okay as a long time ago
What you're not understanding
Is that when
Someone says something in one circumstance
And then the circumstances change
And then they say something different
Bet hip-hop
Sedan
But I understand that you know hey
This situation in 911 or both large
Lifestyle altering foursome foremost
The circumstances that I can see how Mike would be like
Okay in the aftermath of the giant terrorist attack
President Bush
Came out and said everybody's got to buy stuff right so why are they saying that now because these are different
George Bush
Did come out and say after 9/11
Everyone
Should stockpile toilet paper
Incase
Terrorist
Fly another plane into Walmart
I guess that's what I guess that would be what
Has to be the case to make an analog
Caroline you just
Is that all
That is incredibly
Stupid stupid thinking and you should be
Ashamed of yourself for saying something happens when Alex just leaves
Like my grandpa on his own for a while
Stupid things
Who might Mike hosted on his own for a little bit
And then Alex comes back
And there's a real trend of
Him trying to make a joke
Out of his arrest
And you'll see that that starting
To begin here
Chinese restaurants around the Coronavirus
Japanese restaurant
This rights the first
Again
See you'll see a good bit more
I'm trying to I don't know if I want to call it reclaim
We're getting his if I did it here's how I would have done it
Well I mean I think there is a little bit of a I know that I've been I'm not going to get in any real trouble for
Glodan
And he's behaving
Fairly similarly about his silver
I'm saying topically
It makes contact with a virus
Silvers documented and understudies are solely gentle make your head spin and its back
Percent off
Infowars store
Dot-com
So you're using very similar techniques and tactics
Some things that he said
That are the things that are being criticized by like this
Is Mother Jones article
It's almost like a come at me
See what he
I don't give a s***
This is this
A huge bail
Here because all that is
It seems like
The
FDA
Attorney General
I'm sure sure but all that this is really serving
Need to do is
Kind of teach him how to skirt the
The rules the right way
Maybe maybe. Maybe maybe not back
Fine and let me know like it needs to be an immediate we will we will end up
See what happen
Okay I don't know
I don't know what's going to happen but like this point
It's important to remember that on March 12th
He's just responding to like Media Matters and Mother Jones putting out these articles
About in silver sale
He doesn't get that letter
The letter is dated March 12th
Okay so he when he's on air it doesn't really good
Chance he hasn't seen the New York attorney general's letter
So that is probably not in his awareness until the 3rd
Okay. This point there is a
Almost begging that letter to exist as presentation on the show which is
Really interesting
Sing dynamic
I think he feels a little bit Untouchable I think he feels a little bit
I'm on top of the world
I mean
Is there
It's hard to see anybody who is suffering
Let's count
Consequences for more terrifying crimes in then you've got out
There's a sliding scale for presidents and their own experts probably feel like I've been here before
People talked with me before
Yep I don't know if
Feeling stays around
You're doing smile because the other one on the 12th
Bye-bye
13th might be different
So on this clip here Alex
Is
Really
What it means it's really important is
Is when there is a lot of this barrage of
Outside attacks
Coming at him
Call Dakota
I might call it
Stories
Better accurate
He needs to make the audience feel
Like it's actually about
Them
Are they about to do without us on are they don't want you to have a voice they wanted
Your voice
So you need to stand together with Alex
And support his ability to whether this situation because if
If he goes away your voice
And that's what the
Really after they're after your voice
It's not
Alex
Got a DWI in there
There's consequences for his actions
It's not that he has been
Immorally
Fantastically possibly illegally selling or he's a something silver supplement as if it were a drug
It's not
That is
It's the globalist hate his audience
Right now it's very simple it's it's a simple tree of just like
Any criticism is an attack
Any attack on me is an attack on you
Please shut down any of your ability to think
Only react emotionally and violently and in defense
Now we get to the breakdown of the knee
This section takes place here on the
March 12th episode
This is where everything becomes more solidified
Alex hits
The beats
I don't mean to tell you
Divisible
No
No not the
Nitrous oxide
There's
This is no life
Can gas matter
Gives Abby the deformed
The Final Four
What I would describe as the
This is
Much more
Like this
This is what we're going
Okay and it's all
Bulshit
Break it down piece by piece
Says it goes along
Here's what we know
Chronicle dish with the author of the u.s. biological weapons law
Nauseam with the actual research papers of India and other major
Prestigious universities around the world
Coronavirus USA
Ridiculously man-made virus
Chimera with a bunch of different families of viruses
Splice together
With an HIV delivery system
Welded onto it as well
Not HIV
The HIV virus delivery system
None of that's true
Alex has not had great experts on the show he's smoking
Unhinged lunatics
Holocaust denier help him build up his narrative
But none of it even close to real
He constantly mentions that Indians
Study buddy
Never really
Discusses
Is the contents of it at all
He had waves away the fact that it was retract
By its own authors after their methods in
Conclusions
Play critique by the scientific community
Purchasing that they came from
Pressure from the globalist
Come down Dan
Truth can't get out also I thought that Alex's narratives about the Hy-Vee delivery
System thing we're just do not
Understanding the furrion verse
Is a stew cleavage
But I think they might have been giving him too much
Credit
Think that's just a bat Indian study
I think that's all that is and he didn't read it
In that study the authors found for nucleotide sequences they claimed were not present in other Coronavirus
Speculated were swapped with zika
Containers in HIV
One of the main reasons they're paper ended up
Tractor Disney Swift
Criticism they got
Particularly relating to
To the fact that
Two of those sequences are found in other coronavirus is
And only one of the sequences was even simpler to
1 Fountain HIV there's almost certainly
Coincidence
This is most likely all out
Just talkin about any claims there's an HIV deliver
It's all
Just Trace back to that
Retracted
Discredit
Indian study
None of this is real at all it's just a shotty collection of b******* that he's talked about for the last two months being pressed together
To make more
Impactful
In many ways
It is written
Diculous Lemay
Only the adverb just means that it's
I don't yet
So we get to the second piece of the narrative and it has to do with
Xenophobia
The day 16 weeks ago
Is China but when Trump talk about stopping flights and we said yeah that's great idea they went oh my God it's so
Susanna Baumann
Lenawee glider
South Korea Japan
Tasha all the other stoplight
When they freak out
Comedian said it was.
So did China something you in
Even responded shooting people checkpoint with good
Everybody else had
And that's when you see the agenda
So there's no good evidence that
Suggest that any country that
Suspended flights to Cenote
Decreased incidence of Coronavirus
Princeton's Alex list South Korea who stopped all flights
Today Google city with the most infections
Is on February 23rd
That country I had 700
63 cases
At that point and by March 1st they had
What are the reasons that generally people if you shutting down travel from
Specifically
Xenophobic
Is because it really doesn't have the effect that you would think it would have in terms
The disease containment
Experts on the subject agree that it's best to allow people to travel that way you can
Set up screening point
So people come
Coming in and out
Would you wouldn't be able to
To do with everything was shut down and only people
The only people who come
Again
Complete unknown quad
Given the lack of evidence of ism
Ineffective strategy
If someone is pushing for it to be used at usually means at Birth
Or they have a hidden agenda
Given how frequently the trumpet
Administration strike
Travel for bigoted reasons
The past
Kind of understand
Some commentators
Like it that
Alex is still not demonstrated his claims of people being shot at checkpoints but even the best
But he's acting as if it is
Employment with the UN
None of which is based
In reality
This is all just
Just b*******
So now we get to
53rd
Section of the gift
I was just thinking that the
Think about the
Travel ban
Story coming out of Italy
Philly where they
Somebody leaked it
That they were going to shut down
They were going to create a quarantine Zone
And they licked it about 24 hours before
And people
Ran away from the
Quarantine Zone that's certainly a risk
More people
You didn't wind up helping anybody
Can't ever really fully lockdown things even if there isn't
Leaks like that
Describing like that you can't
You can't have
Like a waterproof
Let's say our air proof
Something and so you'll inevitably end up
You can you can when you do things
Things like shutdown travel
Can slow things down
As we've discussed
In the past they can't slow spreads down
But it won't have the
The desired effect
Seem to be
The motivations and Alex
Or Trump
Would suggest oh yeah
Navigate to this third child
Secure and
More
Man-made virus so they can release him
In the lab they know
Human prisoners
They know how it's going to be
Replicate
Just Waxing pigs
Bass
It also can get it
There's no evidence of this is man-made
That anyone was doing any
Any testing on it but if they work this still makes no sense
No amount of testing would be able to predict what coding errors the virus of making RNA replication
Should lead to the mutation
That's random it's just a natural process that scientist
Could not control North Verde
With any kind of accuracy
Also there's no evidence
The pigs can get
Does Coronavirus
There are people born coronavirus is for sure like porcine respiratory Coronavirus
But there is currently no indication that
The current outbreak
Pigs
Dr. Jeff
Cindy manager of the
Canada West swine Health intelligence
It's not work said quote
There is very there is no very clear evidence
The pigs might be susceptible to
Specific strain
But I want to caution
Not that there is much
Research going on right now
That this could change within a week or two
Alex is making up this affect pigs
And it is that
Even if we eventually learned
The pigs are sup
Please just make
Take me to shut up
He has no idea
So we get to another line
Of this this is more or less just
Segmented chunk
Books of like a 3-minute disc
Installation of America
Yeah this is
And you watch
Play Disconnected
It's clear
They're already
For now 10 different strings
Some stranger more deadly than others there are 10 strains and exaggerating the
In that research that we discussed earlier that there are two S&L stay
Which isn't even something there's a consensus
It's about he's just
Embellishing
Exaggerating
Navigate to the next Beeson that's
The chimera
Show that he's got a whole family
A family
Where it came from
A family of families
Spider-Man
This is a
This is the Italian virus
So is that what we're calling it and we got a big family we got the virus
Free imprecise language
Describe the the situation I don't know
It's pretty bad like this is really truly trying to get
The concrete version that would make it even worse
Like fishes are the results of our extended investigation into this
And all of it
Just nonsense
I I just
I have a hard time
With this like it cuz it's still difficult to
Truly comprehend this
Scale of what's going on
Right like nobody
Has any
Clue
How big this
Micah
Sure and
For him to just
All the sudden start throwing this s*** around
This
At this level it's
II
I cannot
F****** handle that
Yeah it like this is
Genuinely terrifying
Pretty gross Behavior
Just because we're all trying to figure out what
The tone
Yeah we talked about that
It's even very difficult for me as someone who's covering this stuff cuz I will have Quiet Moments
Surreal self-doubt
I have made too little of
Of course of the situation
It's really tough because
Recovering Alex
Alex Wright says bulshit
Yeah we say this is bulshit yeah
Your heart I don't know the tone
I'm not an expert in
Yeah and
It's there's no way
There's no way yet to really kind of
Walk that fine line between
Worrying
Concern
And
Panic
Like there should absolutely be worried there's
Should be concealed
And there should be caution
There should be risk aversion
Pushing things into that full-on panic
You know
That's such a
Dumb things
To do
Toast
So hate
Well let's get back to this
This concreting of the the narrative
It would not be completely
If it didn't include
The idea that Obama song 2015
North Carolina University at Obama allowed to transfer
That's not true
I hope it's just that misrepresenting an article he didn't read
So you get back to North Carolina UNC Chapel Hill article that he's lying about
And that's where this
Began
You have the original virus Boston 2015
North Carolina University did Obama allow the transfer of it was a big National
They were able to get a functioning chimera
They could then be modified further
Now we know what's happening
So that's what's happening
Now we know what's happening I got this Chimera terrible to make a chimera right now
Please discuss
Any of that
Right
Watch Fullmetal Alchemist now we have pretty much the concrete version
Narrative
A Alex's have tons of
Very very legitimate expert to come in and we've decided that
This is a bunch of different
Viruses in one sure you know that the global is there behind it because they say it's xenophobic for
Trump to shut down travel wow
Praising China or something
Man-made they've tested it to they know the mutations that are going to happen there's 10 strains
It's a family of families family family
The blame because he sold it
The China 2015 is created in
This lab at UNC Chapel Hill
Extraneous stuff Beyond this is up for
It's not as important this is the narrative that Alex needs to get out or else he's screwed
That's why he's boiling it down like
There's so many parallels
To the way they
Treating this
From a person
Effective
Nothing anybody does nothing
Anything nothing is Trump Spa
Nothing he does is Trump's fault
With
Nothing I did to get the DWI is my
Nothing is a nobody
Look you're going to you can blame everybody but me
And you can blame everybody but him
Everybody else's fault it turns out
We're the best at everything all the
So now we got this
Down
We can take a look
What is this used
And here's Alex's Bazaar
They're using it to paralyze the economy
Hysteria like fear
This is the globalist plan to teach us to live under lockdown to teach us if there's this invisible in an even worse than terrorists
Give my rights up and take the person ovulation to do what they say
So after that laundry list
Completely fictional elements of the finalized version
This narrative Alex
Research that is being used to paralyze the economy and make us live under lockdown
Exactly
And that's why we should shut
Down Sacramento's borders send the military in
Close it off arrest everybody hang people little disjointed
My first suggestion is it if you see someone go 047 and their premises
Their conclusion is
Probably ship to
What Alex is doing is taking the natural consequences of something and then pretending those consequences are why the thing happened to begin with
Naturally A large-scale outbreak is going to have an effect on the economy
It's pretty inescapable in the modern world
Whether Market disruptions that happened
After an outbreak
You have in no way proving that the virus was released in order to
Precipitate
Disruption
You've got a good start on that Thriller novel you've always been meaning to write
And that's what Alex is doing
You taking a natural consequence and then
Claiming it's the motivation
The same goes for things like shutting down of the NBA and events with large attendance as you know that
That's a natural calm
That's the correct
To do when there's a concern about no brakes
If you pretend that
What is the motivation you can
Completely distort reality without ever having to
Promises
They wanted to shut down all this stuff in order to cause hysteria night that's why they were
It's it's
And everybody knows the real see
Situation here is that the
The Golden State Warriors release this virus in order to make sure that Steph Curry and Klay Thompson can get fully healthy for the end of the year
NBA season
They're going to sneak into the 8th seed in the west and they're going to wind up winning the whole thing
This is all Steph Curry plant been proven
This strategy
Pretending
Consequences are actually secret motivations
Conspiracy worldview
Generally what he does is yell about secret motivation
For consequences he's making up
Like in the case of him yelling about the globalist staging mass shootings
Pretty secret motivation
Is gone
The imagined consequence
I'm losing his gun
Never Comes
But expanded gun regulations and restrictions are the natural consequence you would have
Like to see from Tonto shootings
You imagined
The consequence
The result of the shooting
1/10
That go
Is what motivated the staging of the shootings
To begin with
The current situation is just kind of the envy
There are real-world consequences happen
From this virus
So Alex is just taking what's happening
The real world
I'm pretending it's what the globalist
We're trying to do by releasing this
Maybe race specific bioweapon which it's not and
So that's the game is being played
But it's the inverse situation
Yes when the consoles are all good
Right right but I mean when
The consequences are real and you're making up the motivation that's
Scapegoating and that's what her
Well yeah when the consequences aren't real that you haven't
But that's still good
I can't imagine Alex's underwear
Insane not today
So he starts talking about how like
Cuban talk
How they're going to do this
They're going to release his bioweapon started to bring it a world government
Can you pull back from this clear
This is the year 2020 and the UN and the Bilderberg Group of the day was probably said
We will use
Bayou
Happen
Events and pledged to bring in World ottoman that control
That's how you make country coordinate with each other
Taylors
While they take control of your life
You know what I realized when I heard that clip
Was that realize that I haven't heard
Complain about Bilderberg in a long time
Forgotten them is being the big bad guys in the world but LOL
Alex is in no way proven the Davos or the UN or Bilderberg
Has ever said any of these things
Is no citation you just sort of asserts this s***
He's built up his people as the arch villains on his show
Is Oriental just Prime 20
Unquestionably
Amcrest
Only accept
Yeah I've been following out
Pretty closely for years now including closely scrutinizing
Documentaries endgame and The Obama Deception
And I've no reason to believe he could actually prove anything you saying
Nightclub
Just be sure I went back and I reviewed Alex's bibliography for endgame
AMC 3rd something in there that
I did
I found a lot of Encarta Pages Planet articles but I didn't find any evidence of the globalist
They're trying to use bio-weapon
Are goals of a world government
Do you know what's fun
He presupposes that should there have been a world government
Or should there be a world governed
It would get us out of
Because he's saying that they will be our saviour's at our jailers but
Still saying because they
Created the problem would say almost evolution
Alex
Got to give it up
It's chugging a little bit about this idea that it's a bunch of viruses
Does put into want all splice together
I want you to pay close attention to this because
Listen to how
Incapable it he is a
Even discussing this
It's on any level
Headlines
Let It Go they were times all the conspiracy theorists in Russia and China
Brazil and Mexico
They are all saying it's man-made and then there's
Under electron microscope and you can see
Wow
A blob together
Sing
It was in miniaturize so we can be airborne
Your lungs every part of it made
But it was spread
So that everybody would end up learning they been infected weather
To the hysteria Lori's Fever Pitch
Once the test gets get out and that's why Trump says
Problem no big deal
Because the White House knows
So what thing I think is very important to recognize that may often just go to fade into the background is how unable Alex's
To talk about these issues
You can hear it so clearly hear he's a fumbling for words
Because he doesn't really even understand his own conspiracy narratives on any level deeper than some headlines
See the pieces of pizza
Damn right that's
Science
Right what's at the root of this whole misunderstanding Alex says about things
Splice together text back to that retracted Indian study
You're not study the authors discussed quote
Inserts
In the RNA of the virus which Alex is taken to mean that things were inserted in there
A berries with imagine designed as finding splice point and all that s***
In reality when discussing the RNA insert
Me with Alex
When already replicates
It can sometimes add or delete nucleotide sequences and what a sequence is added that wasn't there before it's called in
Insertion
It doesn't mean that human
Concerted anything
It's just a term that people used to do
Describe this natural
Phenomena you can see that use the sailor's knot to tie the RNA Dan there's only one possible explanation
God bless you sailor's knot
Chirp
I know that he's just making s*** up but if he's not I would like to challenge Alex to explain the quote slapping viruses together methodology
And after that I would ask him to walk us through the miniaturization process
Swirled around and then you get done you know you go inside a body and it's like
You got to take out a tumor you're not you're not
Baby my baby
Also apparently Trump is back into being involved in the cover-up
But he's involved might be one of the things he looks Shady in hindsight about this area that Alex
Number for
Whatever
So Alex is another gas
He's a man who likes to go to the woods
Tell others to do so as well no communist royalty Joel skousen
And he starts off his appearance
5 Maybe
Unethical selling Alex's home
You shouldn't be eating any junk food you got to be eating a lot of natural and organic food
And then you've got to be using some of the really good herbal and
Salesforce a nano silver
Very good
I'm getting all these types of Coronavirus
Medical studies
Sirius anecdotal evidence
You're going to f*** around and get a letter from the New York attorney general
I got some serious anecdotal studies on this don't get involved in this when you don't have feelings
Wait in there we need another
Night in the Army then
Joel is talking about the virus situation
And he has something
That he wants to bring
The table
Reassurances covid-19 is capable of Airborne transmission
Oldest for weeks now that you have to actually contact her sneezing or water droplets with a virus
Make this contagious absolutely false
Princeton University has come out
Great
Distinction that I need
In past episodes I've criticized Stewart Roads in France
Despoil for assert
The virus is Airborne nothing back in their claims up other than their opinion
There is new information out
Call some of this into question
Address
There was a study that came out after our last episode that's
Suggest that it's possible that the coronavirus can be transmitted in
In the air with the virus living up
Up to about 3 hours
Daenerys alive
Forum
There are many caveat
41 the paper is not pure reviewed yet has been no confirmation of the findings
But even if the study does hold up
It's not clear what
Conclusion you should
To draw from it
As one of the paper's co-authors Dylan Morris told
We still don't know how high concentration of viable coronavirus is needed to impact
Justin Factory
Human being
Though this is something we are looking
Cooking tomatoes in a few
Disqualifiers very important
Because the study just claimed to show that the viruses
Taxable in the air 3 hours after its
Very well may be that the amount that survives any relevant amount of time right now
I'll be enough to actually train
Is that the virus
Another issue is that the virus can survive 3 hours and air supplies form doesn't mean
The same thing as if you caught the virus will be in the air for
For 3 hours
There is a possibility here though
And undoubtedly more study will be done on this front wheel no more
In coming days
Surrounding
Another limitation of the study was they didn't even look how how far do you virus scan
Travel in the air
That's not to say that they were wrong
Isn't part of the scale.
Just because it's
Panda live in the air for long. Of time it doesn't mean that it'll travel travel really far like
It's been implied by a lot of
These decks
That's still an open question
The point here is that there is a study that indicates
The virus maybe transmittable in the air but I'm here
Still to tell you that Stuart roads
And Francis Boyle were wrong
You did not have any reason
You say that when they said it okay
Because this is an indication that
It's possible that there
Conclusion was correct
They arrived at it imprecise improperly
So I still take issue with them
Wisconsin
Little bit murkier
It's like a f******
Elrond walked out of the woods
You're not going to be like well obviously
Tolkien knew that elves were f******
King real he was making all that s*** up it doesn't matter that elrond
It said the point is that he was making it up when he said
It's a little bit Gray
Do you have no right to report this as solid fact since
Study is still incomplete at this point and isn't it
Pre Papi reviews
But here's a little bit more wiggle room to speculate than Alex's other friends did because at least the other source.
It's not a great source to be certain about just
Yeah but
The other dudes were just
That's just I wasn't claimed
Princeton put out the
The study of its kind of imprecise
The co-author is a grad student iprint
Distance I'll give him half
What are the larger points here to is it the co-author himself when speaking to livescience noted that quote
Even if aerosol transmission
I can occur it's unlikely to be the primary force driving the current pandemic
This is primarily because sneezing and coughing
Do not generally create aerosol size
It's particles which is what
The study was lucky
It doesn't it wouldn't
Exist according to this article outside generally
Outside of hospice
Still super relevant
It's not the same thing that people like Alex
And his friends are trying to create
Hysteria or what they're basically saying is that if one
If one small virus exist
Anywhere it can infect a human being
If it's in the air that can breathe it in and that's all it take that's what I don't want the message to be exact
Not at all
So I know something weird in this episode
First volley to loaded with
We already have Mike Adams of Joel skousen
There are two more people,
That alone
Me too weird
The show is super
How to improve the gas to talk to them for a little bit been dissing
Letting the other person basically host
The show
Mike Adams came in and out of brakes on his own
Mike Adams the show out of commercial breaks to without
Nowhere to be seen
In the same way that I look straight up left the show on Wednesday I think he's dipping in and out and letting
France take over
Because he's dealing with lawyer
It sure feels very disorganized
And like 18th
Trouble onto on this this Thursday show
And I will tell you this Jordan
Joel skousen on his own is boring is she
Know that old man monotone damn near put me
Need to sleep
His main point is basically
That the virus is the result of offensive bioweapons research is being done by China Inn
They wanted to take out the west and take over the United
States with a bioweapon
But the virus got out some
So Obama didn't
Well
I think you could make us compatible
Obama told them A Primitive form of it and then they experimented on it and then it got free and now we all have zombies
It's tough to say because that part of the narrative is definitely not Angels guys
I could see
Z-Wave
You could make it work
Jordan
I don't think you'll be that car but it also
Maybe a little silly
So the way Joel
Since the virus got out was that the lab as bad process for throwing things away
To the fish market
It's unclear who the trash band was
But
I would guess that they're not involve the Chinese government
Because
You know China was trying to create this project
He's not big on details pass
The broad conspiracy Strokes
Anyway he doesn't really
Get into the Obama selling it like I said
It just it
I don't know what I don't know
It's kind of like he doesn't believe any of Alex's s***
But you just wants to
To keep up his uncle's rabid Red Scare mentality keep that alive
I'm going to go with Luxembourg
Sandberg has been overlooked for
For far too long they made this virus to get themselves on the map that's what I'm saying right now
Maybe that's what I'm thinking
Alex comes back after
Skousen host
Rebet and he's coming in
Weird
I've been saying for 34 weeks when you see the celebrity get it
Shelby Drive
And I said I believe what I had the crew would go back and find it you all heard it
That is Soon As Trump acknowledges that it's deadly
But you'll see them
Make the weather now
Doubles
They had horrible.
American political activity
So-called ghetto good boy Tom Hanks
So-called costar
Are some movies are making a habit so he's out there all over the news
Transfer.com doctor claim
At a gut level
Especially because it came out
Why does Trump gave his speech
Calvary shadow that
Because of the weird narcissistic needle
Johnson world
The chicken crab Dimension world of evil
All they care about is being
1 oz not been saying for weeks that way you see a celebrity get the virus that's what the Asteria kicks in
I've been listening pretty consistently and it's definitely not something I would say he's made a point of
Honestly I don't even remember him saying it ever
I think he said that Forrest Gump would get the
The virus reset.com
It wasn't his co-star it's his wife
Tom Hanks
Free
Alex is probably going to be
Need that doctors can
Just come out and say whatever defense here pretty soon
Nothing as it seems like Trump
Just keeps getting in the room
The people who end up testing positive for Corona
Tom Hanks
How to overshadow Trump
The stupidest only one man more famous than Trump then five
Alex saying the people like Tom Hanks all they care about is being the top story is the
The clearest case of projection I've ever seen in my life
Alex
Stop talking about anytime he's in the Press
The singular Obsession for him
Conversely Tom Hanks seems to be a relatively humble person
As far as celebrities go
Come on man I think you could do way more attention-seeking Behavior
And totally get away with it
Refined living pretty quietly
Yeah
So earlier I mentioned that Alex theme
You trying to make a
A joke out of his arrest
And you'll see that trend
Continue here
And she says people aren't going
Chinese restaurants
Racism into I was in one last night was like no one in there
One of the limit but still it took me to jail do the desk
By the police department
Crazy
But this is all happening
Silence is trying to use that clip to say that the Democrats are trying to make this virus a situation about race
Really weird to hear from him because he
Keep calling you specifically there is that strange
Anyway you just
Hear this Lake
Deflection are you making a joke
Any continues
Honestly it sounds
So silly to say
Asian restaurant Coronavirus
They're dropping the charges
Laughing about this
We have another guest
Yeah Yeahs but Alex is trying to deal with the
The situation
This is
This is like
Such that office co-worker everybody knows the story about
Talk about it
We don't need all I think it's funny
No no we decided to talk about what happened to your wife it's if not really I know you're not
It's
It is a job. Yeah
I don't think it is
Steve bazan
Would be a Steve pieczenik
Cute coronavirus per hour
What is already cured
Himself that is not
Outrageous thing he asks a good time
This is this is more geopolitical
Liberation Army
Again
To me as a l
The people's Liberation Army
Veggie as a civilian is not
To be able to
Hold on to
Illusion of power
So Steve would lead a coup against
G-Man
I would not recommend that
Steve
Jeez acting incompetent
Particularly a virus outbreak
I got this interesting because so far in his appearances on the show Steve has been the least critical guest
As it relates to China that Alex has
Well Alex and his other friend
I've been running around like Chicken Little Things yet like I hate over
Free Humanity or only be Lone Survivor
Stephen tried to pretend that he was the first person to get the virus in the United States
Buddy cured itself with large doses of antibiotics
Not great
Viruses
But whatever
Steve has downplayed the significance of the outbreak
He's been
Coordinates of G's lockdown strategies
This man is leading a coup in China is real
Out-of-left-field
Steve then again
Almost everything he says is
Complete nonsense so I'm going to let it live in the air
So Steve
It's the talking about a trump doing a good job
And then he said something weird
The way Trump needs account
He's providing leadership
Story would be a pandemic
It's just a fancy word to say was
Interesting
Alexis Abril contradictory.
I want Andrea Francis Boyle decides the doctor fauci is a Nazi bioweapon research should be arrested
Spelling for Alex and Alex's picked up on a lot of them
Turning fauci
After pretending using Royce the administration
Alex went 180 on that
This is a hard to square with Steve
Fauci is doing a great job and not only that
Cream Steven med school
Steve knows this guy super well but also Francis Boyle says he's a Nazi scientist
If you're listening to this show and you think any of these people are credible
It seems like that would be
Hard to deal with
I
Are you just
Did just think
There's nowhere for Steve
You always room
Others claim that Tony fauci trained Steve Cornell
Possible
So I found Steve's medical license
Graduate from high school in 1960
Okay
This is a problem
Because
Cornell Med
School definitely not around that time
However
Fauci
Did graduate from Cornell med school in
2 years prior to Steve
All right it'll be easy for him to go immediately turned around
Teaching
He didn't
According to fauci bio
After graduating in 1966 fauci
Quote Pursuit house staff training
In Internal Medicine at the New York
Hospital
For 1970 1971 fauci was the chief resident at the New York Hospital Cornell
Medical Center
But by that point Steven already graduated from
From Cornell and according to his license
Steve did not do an internship or clinical rotations at the New York hospital where fauci would have been
I'm going to go out on a limb and just
Assume that Steve realize fauci went to the same bed school is Emily decided to build it into his backstory
Thought you was basically as mentor and teacher
I see no evidence
This is the case and the timeline
Does not really even possibly work
God dammit
Man
That's just good
That's just
Stuff from Steve
I swear to you I wouldn't even say that he
Newegg
Dora I mean like
I wouldn't say that he knew about you went to Cornell
I would totally believe that that was a lucky accident no no no
Be too surprised if Steve might have been acquainted with him
Not like the classes are probably gigantic
Who's ahead of him in the program
This is all both are
Christ
Actually I don't know if you know that but I'm adept
Well done
Steve
So it wouldn't be a steeplejack appearance if you didn't say crazy nonsense
And it also wouldn't be Steve if you didn't say something
Lake Ripley racist
Play what you hear
California dominated by Dairy
Waxman Berman machinery
Which literally
A what now
Google
Oh what now
F*** is this guy
Bandana
What I really think is so interesting is that it's so
Scattershot is it
Bigotry goes all over the place at these answer
Acquainted
Racist
Close
You just can't
You just keep waiting for him
Call Irish people mix
Like what are you coming
So Steve gets into talking about Trump
Good but in doing so he kind of describes trampas really
Yeah
The truth
The guy from here
California
Which president XI or food
We've never had
He understands the personality
Because
That's not that's not what I
I don't want a president who sees Mafia guys and he's like I like that guy I'd get along with Hank
That's not good
These people are in
That is that is incredible what do you think you wanting to l
I want to be mobbed up into really kind of just
Feel things out I wanted to be super mobbed-up
And also want to take over space
Increase
Is Space Warfare
Not just an asset
What does Facebook
And we don't want any more Connecticut action otherwise we don't eat
Tanks we don't need any Bazookas we don't need
Destroyer summary
These dudes are pushing for is a explicit breach of international law
There's a little thing called the outer space treaty that was signed back in 1966
She graduated
Jesus words known as space law
3D pretty clear that exploration of space is open to all country
And their purpose needs
To be peaceful
Only specifically bands the installation
The deployment of nuclear weapons and weapons
The master struction
I have to assume that a star destroyer that I was imagining would qualify as a wmd
My main point here and this might be the name of my book If I ever write one is that Alex Jones really just wants to be one of them
Bad guys in Star Wars
He constantly does impressions of emperor
He comes in from break with the Imperial March
Constantly almost never talks about the Jedi or the rebels
Alex is just a f******
Can Syfy dork who likes the bad guys
I'm surprised
Stevie B
Cvbz had been quicker you have been like oh yeah Star Destroyers you know I wrote the original Star Wars with George Lucas
He trained me at Cornell as well in screenwriting
So
You know the United States is setup is a
Non religious country connote the secular
Alex
It is weird weird extreme is Christianity
Country with the religion of America
If we had one religion it's not Christianity
Entrepreneur country
I can make any f******
To pay the penalty
Of disgrace as I would in Europe
China
Ornacia
So why don't you
Wild West
Self-sufficiency entrepreneur
And the ability to make
And everybody would buy into an idea
You're very bright man and underneath
They tend to be the best actors
Rata Tommy Levy come back to everybody calling me I'm getting constant streams
Real hard real hard right after Steve calls Alex and actor and
Yeah there is
I love this
Steve couldn't even keep like from lasting when he's like you're very good at getting your point
So Alex gets
To talk in here about
The silver
Again he's very
Kinds of about it
Beat a lot
And that's because it's
Comes up a lot
Let's go over the facts by lawyers
Technology
At the first line of defense in hospitals
Health clinics
Bacterial infection the Pentagon also uses
Call Keri Carlton
Science Center
Wunderground ridges
Retesting and has been found to kill Anthrax bubonic plague
Hospital staff in SARS
Years ago
Dial and have relied upon it making
Stationary
Cleared a double-blind human
Jackson studies
Over-the-counter sale
Do all the claims being made about the nano silver in this statement
The topical
If you were only two made these claims about the jail being effective against
I'm sorry I probably wouldn't be brought up weeks ago when he started selling
Toothpaste in cargo
Call the way he has
I'm not certain about all the particular details but he does seem to have some pieces to make claims about the topical gel
It's just these claims cannot be made about the
Completely
Product because
Dad some of the same ingredients
You talk to them about the other studies in the research
You go to the silver company's website at Silver biotics. Net
Dot-com
Where you'll find a sub page
Title research
The researchers split
2 second
The first is 9 studies about the wound gel
And it's used as an over-the-counter medication
The second section
Is where Alex gets in
The trouble is that about
Ingestion
Studies
That section is a collection of Six studies
Silver biotics
Text David involving whether or not it's safe
To ingest their silver
In the application
The gargle
None of these studies demonstrate that the
The same medicinal qualities apply to the ingested silver
Just their product is safe for humans
The consumed
You cannot take this compilation of research and conclude that it's Africa Laura Justified to sell the gargoyle the way that you
You might
Simply but Alex says no.
If he continues
Push the issue
And if the State Attorney General
Like their office follow through with their warning
Alex is going to be fine
Lot of money
Can't wait
Very bad I hope so
Defensive more
I didn't say you could
You're the virus with this
They're really pissed off right now folks
That that that people are getting this and protect themselves
Around tattletaling
Misrepresent what's going on and it's just not going to work
Know if you already have this David you are you're inside
Obviously taking silver is going to protect you buy me some Frontline
On your hands
Another buffer against a tech it out
Even if you ignore all the times that Alex very clearly implied that is toothpaste and gargle could knock out
The Coronavirus
He's still on the wrong side
At the end are you saying that the product being in your throat will have a protective
Facts against the virus and that's still not something you can back up with any evidence
It's just as illegal to promote this as a coronavirus cure as it is
Promoted ism
The prevention
Simply put
If things go the way they should
Is f*****
He's just digging himself deeper
Digging deeper
Speaking a digger
Let's dig in
Is Alex at his last gasp coming up
And guess what
You dumb
Either Catholic facts
Great it's Milo yiannopoulos
I've been spending
The last couple of weeks
Trying to avoid this history about coronavirus
It's not entirely clear to me that even exist
President thinks that I'll be know if you can
They just closed down hockey but I just now few minutes ago might not exist
What's going on but he has some theories
Stupid
There is some kind of flu
Antiseptic
Already
Has been existed
Is manafort
And clearly it is serving one particular
Side of the political aisle who all going in ham on it for like four reasons
I understand Bi-Lo being stupid enough
Just see that Clorox meme that was going around or someone pointed out that
Coronavirus
On the back of the bottle
Get into into it any further or whatever
Next total sense cuz he's a lazy fraud but I have a real problem with Alex
Disagreeing with this narrative the Milo's putting out
That's because
Alex knows damn well that coronavirus is the name of
The family
He talked about it a lot it's a family in Vancouver Lee when he's in the middle of a
Sales pitch for his silver
This is the piece of information that Alex cannot
So he's either completely checked out as a thinker and just you know whatever
Dumb guest says are presented as credible
Visible Changes
See the audience
There's no way around it
It continues they're pretending like they don't know that it
The family of virus
Stuff for year
Because it's because
Later it's
As far as I can tell it's a man-made thing everyone's known about for a while it's just you know who reads the back of these bottles right
Someone noticed somewhere
Somewhere somehow Dan
Against all available on somebody looked at the back of one of those things
This is just
Really stupid
So Alex gets into like
Talking about how like
Hey you know what
I would make more money
I said that this is like
End of the world
How to say that
More products
People need to the Morrigan and coil silver
Anyway sir live
Do you think there's a Supercut, I can't think of any time that he has said that it worked for him at home only be Lone Survivor
Alright well you got one
Collapse of civilization
Oh okay so that's
And so that's where all this is going
How do we know when it's getting kind
Take it on our own to just
Get away from the world I was retired and didn't have to be in Austin I would already be preparing the next few weeks to leave
Okay so that's
Then bombing as soon as
Possible
So I mean if I was saying I could have made more money if I tell people to head to tails
You literally are telling collars
Is 880 atleast
Exactly what you f******
Can say
Milo has a stupid narrative pitch bats New Jersey making it illegal
Ulta spread missing
About to Coronavirus
New Jersey
For spreading misinformation
Okay
So they're already existing laws on the books
The New Jersey that make it illegal to quote
Cause false public alarm
All the typing right now is
The Department of Public Safety in New Jersey is come out and said that they're going to
Enforce those already existing laws in the situation
Coronavirus
Directionality
Pretty simple
Individuals who make any false or basis reports about The coronavirus in Newark
Domino's
They can result in injury to Residents and visitors
And effect
Houses of worship businesses and entire neighborhoods
I think Milo will be in the clear unless he'd Start Spreading lies pacifically about Newark
Alex's show
There are people who've said that this is a violation of
The first event
But it's not really
It's more just an extension of the principle that says you can't yell fire in a crowded theater
Your free speech rights don't extend to being able to use them in ways
The cause real damage
The other people hence the laws against slander or extortion
Those are just the words you're using but they aren't protected
Things like this are real concerns for lazy propagandist
Like Milo and Alex
Because deep down they know that
When they're questioned when they're forced to defend their position
We cannot
We've seen Alex and his dumb Friends under deposition you see how they shrivel up and
Play dumb
Weather Astor Defender most Bass
Reporting
Cuz they're not facing
Any of the s*** they're saying on anything
The prospect of being questioned or investigated by causing a false Panic is really dangerous for them
Because all this it's man-made and Obama sold to China stuff that won't hold up
Under examination
Now it's knows that
Deep down he knows he's guilty of causing
I need desperately doesn't want to face that kind of music
300 behind this pathetic Shield that everything he does is protected by the first
And we'll see how long that holds up but for now
Whatever
Why they go to break
The comeback
And
This might be a little gross
Warning in advance
Infowars
Allowed
Take care of this right now
Thank you very much for this
There's quite a bit of
This kind of talk throughout the rest of their interview but I'd say that's a good enough sample
Pretty gross gross
Pretty goddamn gross do you guys not know you're on air
Does any is anybody
Hey babe
Just empty on baby
I feel like they're just a loan
Sitting in there like it does it.
Optical illusion like if you turn the cameras around is an entirely empty thing in this is The Truman Show
Well I mean if your theory but they don't know that they're on bikes
Is kind of supported when they start talking about Alex's appearance his new
Look
When is bald head man
The normal circumstances this combination I'm always wary of it cuz I think everybody looks kind of a rainy and dinner with the Vietnam
Bald head
How cool is there any sentence today today that doesn't have casual race
I'm dripping all over with Milo is like
He's trying to act like he's trying to get a rise out of people by being like racist funny
But he's not funny and he's a racist
Yeah
So yeah that's that's Bass
Sickly.
So the reason that Milo's on the show is because he's rich
Book about Rodger Stone
Trial in about how Rodger got set up care about any of this because
Milo have
Because it's a book about Rodger being set up
Can't imagine
A combination of two things interest
Sing me laugh
But they end up attending the show to talk about that a bit they end up ripping a bit about
The judge
Amy Berman
Jackson
Right now we're committing
Alex try some comedy out here
And this is
Bad
Berman
Well it's
Let's just say
Penis
Yeah it's not a good joke
First I mean
Beaches are
Typically female dog
This is the construction is bad on this joke the deliveries sloppy to the point where even Alex's douchey edgy comedy but
Buddy Milo tells him
Stop it
Eddie can't even keep up with what Alex is trying to get at
This like honestly is lower than open
My quality
When are you listen too much
Or any more of that
Will jump
The 13th
Friday the 13
Perhaps
Bad omen
Oh no I mean we're recording on the Ides of March
Stand this is the bad Omen right
I hear
Alex said starts the show with the big breaking news
I told you this 2 weeks ago I said FEMA has already declared secretly an actual emergency
And I said in two weeks being pulled off
Assemble into weeks
Just about
18 days ago
I said within two weeks
President Trump will declare
Financial emergency
Got it in place before they
Play roll it out
Two weeks ago Alex is trying to pick a fight with Sebastian Gorka
To be fair on March 3rd approximately 2 weeks prior to this episode Alex did say the trumpet secretly declared a national emergency
And see about about the prior
That wasn't
True that it's still not
Grudgingly declared an emergency
In no way proves that there was a secret emergency
She previously made
Nonsense
I just don't
There's just no way there's no way to break the propaganda firewall
Like if you probably not
If you can't look at what Trump is doing now and CA
An incompetent
Moronic
Huckster
But they're still
If you don't see it now that you're never coming
Two glaring
Yeah
To glare
Yeah it's tough
I got you can
Call the six-year-old be like
What is a better but I could make that argument about so many of the things
But Alex has done over
Over the course of his career
And equally valid
True absolutely true
Is bad day out
The world
Yeah that is that is the other
So Alex just ends up on the 30
You just making
You shut up about the public house
Situation
Airborne HIV
Just like HIV gives you pneumonia and cancer and heart attacks and and I forgot heavy doesn't
Obama and the US government
Create
They've released it is their big temper tantrum
Don't worry that got treatment for at all
Obama selling it
To China is not
Among other problems
Hysteria going on I would argue any of that Alex
Is involved with it
Is his own creation
But Alex thinks
The people are having
Fun
With the Hysteria
Like the idea
Beer of self isolating or that
Wingstop
Defensive driving
Fun with it
Where you can look on Twitter and see people making a lot of jokes
Some stuff and baby were trying to make the best of
A bad situation
But I don't think that what he's saying is
Is exactly true
And everybody gets into the Hysteria
Everybody has a bunch of fun with it
All the sudden Crossing at rush hour get there twice as fast
Restaurants are empty already
But now it'll be the new system with the new viruses weather report
Call this your first you will watch all this become real
The weather report like an allergy report
What
Allergy
You might notice a
Feeling
A little bit of Doom and Gloom
There's there's a
But there's a feeling of like
Optimistic Outlook
It doesn't seem that everybody's going to die all the restaurants are
Almost certain
Triggers a little bell in my mind but I was sitting and thinking I couldn't
Come up with it I am almost certain that I've read a short story
Or something
That involved
Like a virus weather report almost certain
I read too many things in my life I can't post
Specifics of a
I8
Definitely rings a bell
I'm almost certain that Alex is
Probably in Brazil
Alex gets to talking about the the Indian study that's
Retracted
And he's just ends up just making s*** up about that
Can I put out a man-made virus
Shut up the German and the
Russian and the Indian University the scanning the other six man-made
They just pulled it
So there's literally no evidence nor suggestion of evidence of the authors
Where's that Indian paper about the Coronavirus
Retracting to study
Because the paper was published before peer-review
Some pure started review
Their work
Was heavily criticized for being sloppy
Your response
One particularly scathing critique was made by Peking University's
Hey gang
Who commented on the papers allegation that the RNA samples mentioned
The paper a pieces of Art
Of HIV
Yang said that there was nothing unique about the
Small sample that is being said to be similar to
HIV
And if that's the only evidence of
Connection with HIV
In the same connection could be made between the coronavirus and quote fruit flies mold or even lentils
The paper was roundly criticized for jumping to unearned
Conclusions and making really baseless a sump
And upon receiving a criticism the author self retracted of their own well
His papers were not allowed to be publicly pre-picked
Never would have reached the second
Second stage of editorial oversight
Not because of a desire to cover up anything
But because the study is embarrassing
From a scientific
All the stuff about this study is just Alec
Text making up
Stuff it's just his imagination
There aren't shadowy forces trying to say
Suppressed that information
There were just other scientists saying that the study is s***
Weird
The Narrative is more fun
Josiah Bell
Fundamental basic
Lack of understanding
About science
And that is combined with a
Rabid desire to do
Discredited well you won't find Science in ahead
That's also going to be a title of an hour
You won't find signs in head
So now it's speaker
Melvin
Trump is going along with
The recommendations of scientist
Subway
It maybe Nowell
But now that he's doing
Alex needs to
To justify why that's
Because Alex
Distill encouraging
So here's how he does it and I think this is
Real dumb
Trump
This is Kylie doing
It's a paradox because if he doesn't buy into the hysteria that's impossible to defeat this level
Stampede
Run
But instead he's running like a wildebeest running from a lion with all the other wildebeest
That's what you got
It's not bragging
Okay
I don't know that doesn't make a whole lot of sense wow
So you're noble leader is running with wildebeest
I can't do anything
The fear of being run over by the other
Whatever man
I've been wanting to leader it is somebody who will blend into a crowd of other
That is the goal of a leader
Sorensen's bunch of Gaston this
Episode.
Decided to camp
The mall
I had several guest scheduled and they're great people but I cancelled them
No disrespect
Because I want to talk
To the oracle
Meet people
So he's going to take calls to take calls
Maybe
Alex's
Rhino declared that this is Airborne HIV
And he elaborates on this little bit
More or less where this episode takes
A real heart
Downturn
That vibe that we had of Doom and Gloom
Fatalism earlier is going
Taking up to a level
Born
2.0 Hy-Vee
Nobody
Everybody's already got
Six months from now when the kids are everywhere that's what Trump knows why
Dabbing
What
Everybody
Everyone's going to get this
You could go hide out in a basement somewhere you're not getting away from it because once it gets in the body
The human body
Virus
Last days even in the sunshine
And it's coming for you
Coming for you
This is
Funny if you went all doom and gloom
We are going
Jesus Soto
Panic.
Val Trump has been holding off on the kids
And I understand why and this is an
Anything for a human being to say out loud
Okay so Trump
Covering this up because he knows that a bedroom
90% of 3
So rather than
Do anything now
Even wait until everybody has it
And then we'll release
Alexandra think that's better
I don't know look
But also
He doesn't want you to panic
Watch Star Trek
Your Consciousness is being drained
Globalist are destroying our
Okay
Okay buddy
Respond
Stop it
Dead already
Already
Grow up man
Eclipse started with there's no reason to panic as you multiple times you're dead already
Sancerre
We're going to have to
I know I know I know I know your
Yes we are all dead already
I get you most of all
We're going to need you to
Wow
I'm not going anywhere do all this cuz they're not going to do it
They're going to kill you
Please
And most of us are already did
We'll all be sterile
It's over
But what matters is getting your spirit
Right with God
There is a very serious toenail ship
Is it Friday
Where Alex is deep in the place up to me
He's dead already
If you listen to show regularly like you can
Alex is in a very low place the beginning of the show
He's a gigantic narcissist
So I
Can't help but think that this had something to do with his personal issue
In the Fallout of his BWI is ex-wife is appealing for custody of
The children and a judge appears to be receptive
As a consequence of this petition
Arguing that Alex's home is unsafe for children
It also came up
Alex's current wife was arrested for DWI in August
Any arrest involved a private investigator that Alex heads
Following her
Calling the police
Information about his life
Paint them in a really
F*****-up light
Is coming to the surface including the you know
The fact that his dwy was the
It was the result of his wife calling the police
After a domestic
Incident between the two of us
Like these things are really pretty f***** up
Any probably is
Really worried
About the consequences
Isn't that I don't
Pretend to be a
You're calling a private
Probably time to
You're having one follow that would be time to like maybe it's not
A turkey
Kind of I don't know about that kind of just straight-up
Absolutely I'm hiring someone to
Spy on you because I love you so much it's not it's
It doesn't work
It does not pretend
Simultaneously Alex initially responded with Brash defiance
About the media covering him
With the silver sale
By Friday
The New York attorney general had sent him that letter
It's pretty clear this was not a problem you was going to be able to yell his way out of
The fact that he got on Aaron he continued to sell his silver on ethically.
Defensive about it on the 12th
That's a bad sign
We're not dead already
But the consequences of Alex's actions
Are catching up to him in a way that
He probably can't undo
When he says it's already too late most of us are already dead that sounds to me like
I'm trying to express that he feels like his ship has sailed
The New York attorney general isn't going to hear him do his blustery defiant speeches and then say oh I guess Alex was right
IDW I may not cause any direct consequences in
His life but it's looking like it
Probably cause some serious situations for him indirect
And neither of those things are things
He can do anything about
Automatic Farkle level those are the viruses
He's given himself
Yep
Not good and you can feel it
The deep deep
Yeah and I think that it has to do with
The fact that he has to go get
Alcohol and drug test
Because of the custody situation
And the fact that he's gotten this letter
From New York to General by Friday
It's just
His mood is
So
We're dead already
That is such Why cult leaders are so dangerous what the
Circling it on and they're like well we're all dead anyways
Who wants to get on the f******
Can spaceship
Let's go
So Alex believes that
The coronavirus is not only
All the stuff he says
Already
Attempt to kill Trump
And another guy whose name began pronounce
I'm going to lay out the evidence that they are
Me. I heard this weeks ago from proposing office and ignores intensified three days ago they were sick
Trump's got it at nnnn baldasaro
Burlington
Is it
I'm sure.
One of the worst thing is the bubbles can do they do
All right so it's finally accepted
Alex
Did something I didn't do
Expect on this episode
And that is
He directly addresses the fact that the New York
Attorney general has sent to me season 2
Head on baby
This
Might not be
And I'm going to show TV viewers that with an overhead shot
Headed to New York AG
Open it up
Just look at all those arguments as part of them hundreds of articles
What happened
New York attorney general who is not a fan of trump though she is a lovely lady
I don't know yet why you stopped selling and marketing products
As a treatment for cheering for Coronavirus website
I want us to take legal action and hold him accountable for the harm he's boss
But she went on to make even more
And then I got picked
Actually
From the attorney general doesn't say any of that
But see they're smart
They put out
Letter a PR statement that they said was her statement
And then in very few of the releases did they play
Actual
Are we
There's a letter
I said listen that's not a letter that's a PR firm
The legal letter says
There's a letter
Yeah I bet Alex was
You know saying is a cease-and-desist letter
Secret seconds
Cool Alex talks a little bit more about that
In the snakes
Isn't it about the process
What was with
To lawyer this morning
Sounds like you were getting mad
There's another official letter of letterhead it just run up the email letter
Like don't know if that's a PR letter
They put that out of propaganda
All just one-dimensional now so we see that
Everywhere like that
Alex flashes up on
Sunscreen the actual letter that secrets
Website
I'll read it to you in its entirety
Dear mr. Jones
Stop it
The New York State Office of the Attorney General is its
Extremely concerned by your representation during the March 7th 2020 screening of the Alex Jones Show about the Epic
Receive certain product
For sale on your website that you assert will cure or prevent
The 2019 novel Coronavirus
Included DNA Force plus supplements
Silver Seal products
I'm super Bluetooth
Notice
Not the will Joe
The 2019 novel coronavirus pose a serious consequences to Public Health and consumers are concerned
As to how they can best protect themselves and their families
Your representations May mislead consumers as to the effectiveness of the above-named product
And protecting
Against the current outbreak
Both the Centers for Disease Control and prevention and the World Health Organization and stated that there's no specific medicine
Prevent this disease
There for any misrepresentation
That the above-named products are effective
Combating and or treating covid-19 violates New York law
You're hereby advised to immediately cease and desist from making misleading claims
Is a violate New York's consumer protection statutes
Executive Lots
And general business law article 22 a349 and 350
Which prohibit fraudulent fraudulent and deceptive business practices in fallside for
Within 10 business
Wednesday's please contact the undersigned took
Confirm you have
Implied your failure
Comply with this directors may result in further action by this office
Please be advised that the Office of the Attorney General's office
Authorized pursuant to Executive lawsuits
12 in general business law article
7:40
To bring suit to enjoin any deceptive Acts
Open practices
And to seek restitution damages and penalties up to $5,000
Per violation
So there's also a little foot
That's when it it's
Talking
About the Air Force website
This is the hook
Weatherford
The infowarsstore.com
These products are not intended to diagnose treat cure prevent any disease
At the bottom of the product page in minuscule font size makes it unlikely that potential customers
Reader
Yeah so that's a footnote
They have on the other larger cease-and-desist
With the claims that you're making
About the Africa
Speed and effectiveness
That's the actual letter that the Attorney General sent to him
I don't I don't understand exactly what he
He's trying to say
About
They're being
Into Secret Letters
This is the letter that he showed on screen
It's a lighter the media covering
I don't know
These two letters but he's imagining are the same letter and you could tell here in this
Never shed
Is about tooth whitener
Security
Years ago talk about a property that's what I mean they're really crappy
Press release
Disclaimer
Only seen the front page saying letter they drink General
Think about it
Sovereign citizen
Sentai bulshit here
Know what he's done is
You taking the footnote
The font isn't big enough on your disclaimer and pretended that that's
Entire butter
Excellent letter is very clear that you're making misleading statements
So Alex
Good luck I mean I know you I know we can
Can pick his own audience with his foot this is
Like if the New York attorney general follows through with this
Business
Alex is a deepthroat
He's going to be find a lot of money
This is why
We were talking about this whenever the AG first sent the letter to Jim Bakker
It's just like
The NBA has a flagrant
Foul rule
Like this is not a you have 10 busy
Midstate situation
He's already spent two months
Freaking people out he didn't know about it up till that point might even be aware of the
Got the pattern of behavior as opposed to just this March 7th episode
This is a situation where it should be legit like
Hey
You f***** up I don't disagree with. I don't disagree but I don't want to tell them about their business
I do
Alright
You want to tell Alex to do his business I would like to do that too
Alex thinks that if he did do wrong
You should suffer Conte
I don't think they okay well then we're good I don't think you should suffer the same consequences for his actions
Can I take whatever consequences that the law
If I said I had a cure for Smiley's Coronavirus
I like
Stevi B's
Cuz I'm the one that says silver
It's not a silver bullet
I don't get it
Everybody knows that you think
What they say I did
See the issue is that Alex is going to really try and hang on to this I didn't say
Cure
The issue is also claims about prevent
So that is where he's
Claiming
To be reading the article real letter
You didn't read the part where it said
Prevention
Because he wants
He wants be perception
Be the ultimate he's attacking me saying I had a product
I said could
Cure it
Riddles about the prevention
So Alex tries to defend himself
I think he accidentally reoffend
While
My audience about real things
Maybe one goes in your mouth
You've already brush your teeth or something maybe it helped some
Doctors Coronavirus
Your honor my client said I'm speaking as myself
Oh well then clearly that
If he was he was using capital letters whenever he said
Now the fact that this is happening
After the AG sent the letter is really troubling
Going for allergies
He's just too stupid
Speaking stupid
He's just so stupid
This might be one of my favorite clips
I've ever
This is so funny
Funny
This is one of these clips
It's really like the disorganization disarray that's going on at the Inn for Studio
Alex trying to be super defensive but just
Everything
It's like he's trying to give like a really serious thing and then like a picture falls off the wall it's kind of a gas
I'm not saying the products we sell
Been selling for years
And watch these people do this cuz they took some clip out of context where I'm reading
Atlanta South
Cousin van around here
Here is the document
Hey Nikki.
The history of medical use
Sure
That's a big university report on it all the way
All bad
Car horn
They look professional operation
I never heard anything like that other snow
So weird
So great
So that's weird that was really fun
Can you talk about there at the end
That's not a study
That's a review of literature
It was published in the Journal of surgical impacted
Sorry there's a car
Is published back in 2009
The conclusion of that paper is that in ancient
Time silver had a lot of important antimicrobial function
But it wasn't really all that important
A weed
Got antibiotic
Figured that out
That study
And paper
In no way justifies out
It's not a clinical trial of the efficacy of silver as it relates to the prevention or cure any condition
It's a literature
If this is the best he's got he's straight.
Also super weirdly that whole stretch there when he's talking about his teeth being kicked in and when he accidentally sells
Closest toothpaste as a prevention the car horns going off
You know what
All that stuff was cut from the episode that was supposed to be banned. Video
I've seen that happen
10 minutes of the episode
Another weirdo so I noticed
Because I was going back and trying to find the video of Alex like having car
Because it's so good one thing I noticed is that the
Intro Bumper Music that he uses
A lot of the time isn't in the version that he puts
Sony's website
I suspect himself doesn't have the rights to use those
Communications Network
Had we can't play some of those songs without violating copyright streamsrus
Just wild wild stuff
In the car warranty like you running
This place is held together with duct tape what are you doing
That's 280
If there's a car horn outside
Power window
Fine
We're not a professional f******
Studio
So the car horns are hilarious
I think it's really funny
Is that maybe the best
That's the best
He couldn't stop
He was mad that you couldn't write that
So that's funny
But unfortunately they also had another unfortunate
They made it more depressed
I tried to take off about a month ago for first vacation in about a year and I'm not complaining
I need a vacation
Take off next week
Horns on the whole time so I'm saying that's it the way latest
5 minutes
Broadcast
Your phone calls now
So he is
Car horns have convinced him that this place can't run without account
Yeah yeah it's obviously cuz everybody else's incompetent Dan
Everyone else but
Bees bad at their job
God if I was a color I was just calling
Just turn my car horn absolutely
Well
Alex's
Pissed
Like I don't know if it's the car horns
New York AG sending in that letter
Not
Like he's not in the kind of mood you
You'd want to talk to him on the phone
Taking it you can hear my
Audio correct
We're all dead
Sure go ahead make appointment
You're dead
That's not
Good you got no time
Say what you want to say dumb dumb in let's go
So call her
Suggest that you know the kids are going to be out of school
Because the schools are closed
Curfew
Although this called does not go well
Believer
Releasing
School
Don't come up with
We don't want them to get
What do you think coming next
Confuse
Cool
This is
Wow
Alex's check
Not playing usn
Curfews
You got to bring something hot
Going to come today so another caller calls in and talks about a narrative that Alex
I already put out
A while back there was a job posting on jobs.gov or whatever
In November.
Beersy
Alex. Seems like yeah that's right that's right
Get off the phone with him and he is f******
Pissed off that you'd forgotten about that narrative
PS3
I want to get to all of you I want to shut up
I want to get to you but then I got like
Say that again
Can I wake you up early
Got you I'm just on here
I'm going to get myself in the face
Really
Man-made
He doesn't get the right amount of calls
Not under any stress
At all that you know he can't get the calls at all to raise the stakes you know you're not
What about
It's not enough
But he says he's a bunch of Self in the face
He has to make it even more
Do any cozy
That's like
Intermediate
Recalls in the segment
Just walk off the show
My fault don't get it done
Walk off the show
How many Costco
Why would a Kenwood WWII one call and then he has an
An emergency
Interview with France
Boil
An emergency interview with Francis Boyle is a sentence that nobody has ever see how he doesn't end up
Did you punch yourself in the face
Maybe metaphorically though because he does
Keep selling his solo
Don't want to tell you what nanosilver coil silver does fog
The studies don't
Don't buy my products
Go look at house nanosilver
Hotels
And how God knows viruses
No
You idiot the viruses and stuff too but you're unreal
It's like The Sylvers like no cells my
So I don't think a defense in court is going to be
I practiced it by saying don't by myself
That works
Precious they're just too dumb
How do we let fastest win
Every time there's a
So goddamn stupid
Depth
So Alex
Has Francis Boyle on and who cares
It's all the same
It's all it's all the same
There's one thing
It happened
It's interesting and that Alex has a new claim about why there's everyone ever on the covering
Is DWI and silver shed
You know obviously it's CIA machina
Actually but it gets only First Step but how it's actually has like
Reeling
Sure
But just having you and others on pissed them off
So somebody inside the CDC but the word out to try to shut us down I'm sure you've seen the news
Everywhere the converse
Doctor
That would not surprise me
So Alex is at Francis Boyle and Mike Adams on Cheeseheads
On for years and the EVPs
The last time there was an outbreak
Francis Boyle was on calling it a bio-weapon all this stuff is
Exactly sure happened this time that didn't happen last time
Twi
I was selling a silver this way
Maybe that's the variable
But no he's confirmed with lawyers that someone at the CDC got mad at him and so they're doing all this to him
DCS lawyers Alex has lawyers
Together they all Chad gossip and then
That's how you get all that information
Everybody knows
So Alex talked about how the coronavirus attacks
The testicles like this is about
It's not pure review yet
It's still preliminary
Anymore work
Needs to be done on that front
Alex should be reporting on it
Sure
Alex Jones get to this call
Takes more calls later but not in the segment where you said you was going
He does get you a couple calls looking for
Okay well then where
This caller
And also
Why are we not seeing any of these
Families
These people that
Guide
Doing interview
Shooting
Don't worry it's a giant Tower grab the whole thing synthetic
Body was dead
Body was cold
Maybe privacy issues maybe they're also quarantine number of reasons
Brick this woman Insider
Just just build a wall around this woman
She cannot be allowed out
It's not something that you would be wildly suspicious about the brexit I looked into it and a number of family
Members of people I have spoke
Places like the LA Times
You're not finding it doesn't mean it's not happen
So now Alex starts thinking about
One of his family members
Getting the vibe
Oh no he starts thinking about how he will kill
Casino that's probably not the right response
Yeah healthy human
We've heard him periodically brag about stopping people
Go to that right and what have you he said noted murderer
He takes it even further
Mike down for this
Because he said something
And then clearly stops himself in the middle of it I think it's important
Something tough guy Tang
Killing people is like taking a crap it's so easy
Like it's like eating food or having sex or taking a dump and it's like Were Meant to do
You know
Long
It's so easy
Right before he says I know how to do it he says
He was going to say I love it
He was going to say I look killing you was going to say I love killing people
Yeah Zodiac Killer what the f*** is going on
Alex Jones is Dad a famous serial killer and now we're some sort of like
Dexter situation where you trained to serial killer from when he was
The child and its whole f****** radio thing or a serious murderer I don't believe him
But neither hisses
What do you want people to think about
Yeah he wants his audience
To see him as somebody who maybe likes to kill
It's so f***** up Paddock if you are somebody like
I don't know his
Dad
Like you got to do it like you keep
What do you do when your son is
Admitting to murders and saying he likes to kill people on are also by the way I can't imagine this playing
Well in the motion that his ex-wife is filed in court
Playing for the judge I liked
They don't allow stuff that's on the show is the character
F******
This is how a nine-year-old thinks
People would think about like an eye
Find girls who was only ever watched
F******
Action movies and murder and violence over and over and over on screen
This is how you behave as a man
A real man loves killing
Well the other week people can't do it and all that
Sure
Stupid
So Alex brags about how his people
We're going to kill all the global Usher and this is where Alex gets even more depressed
I've already won
My
People who are
White people
Quite
I am there people
Quite going to kill you
We know you're I know there
And you're not going to rest
Well you did this and that's all
I'm not going to commit suicide
Been working really hard man and I just salad about it all like
I want to keep going forever
I'm not scared at all
I want to know
You're going to die
You're going to go to hell
I appreciate the call Janet
Call boy
Alex is really in this headspace
About like
I've completed my mission
There's a fatalistic in a
To this
I don't believe any of this
Things he says
Obviously he's full of s***
What I hear is a way of talking about
The consequences that are piling down on him
Without being real about
I would imagine that it's some point
Alex
Maybe had a lawyer talk to him
And said
This letter from the New York attorney general's office
No
I think maybe someone was able to get through to him
That like this isn't going
To go away just by yelling about this letter that you got
From your silver supplier
It is not you have breached
AG is
Coming down on Rob
Do buddy
Wright Do-it going to do is going to make it out fine
I think
I think that he realizes like there
Lose
It might be some s***
He gets into the head space where the waiter
That is
I've completed my mission
I'm ready to die
And
Let's reference
Rock song
The final equation
Iron Maiden song The Trooper
And we can go out to break
Let's try to kill the Tripper in a minute we got to do it
Because you'll fire musket but I'll run you through
And when you're waiting for the next attack
Better stand
Falling back
I'm Soldier
If it rhymes
True
Amanda farmer
And they don't know how to deal with someone like that
I'm so ready to die
But I want to make sure on the way down
And they're so scared of that
They don't know what to do when somebody's ready to die
Tell me what to do
The shifter
All night long
On their knees their God the devil begging for power
We Empower them to defeat us they will not defeat us they will burn in hell
Twisted Sister song
Just like that
You're not going to get victory
All your money how are we stopping this like
You know
You know how 24 hours prior Alex was joking about how the ladies love that voice with Milo
Now that he's being deployed
Very differently
So Alex has Mike Adams come in because he can't Bulldogs Gaston and I have to
It's so bright comes on and it's really interesting because
He's advising exactly with the mainstream media advisor
Bottom line Alex is the only thing that stops this now
Is social distancing extreme shutdown
Going to begin
And folks it it's not a conspiracy to try
Embarrassed
This is literally the only medical way to stop this
That's the opposite of a lot of
Alex
Read it like
I have genuinely gotten
Stuck in this like
So much stuff doesn't seem real
And this broadcast
Fields made of
It feels like
Real Beyond I like this either dream I think I could write it better this is really a joint tomorrow
All over the place
Even the best I can do is still a bit disjointed
Frazee
Yeah this is unreal
So Alex and Mike are talking
And I think that they make it
I think Mike's trying to keep
Keep the facade up a little bit
Is way too overt about the fact
Hey look
We've been line matter what the cases with
Virus
Could use it
Close the borders
And do all our authoritarian s*** that we want him to do
Closest way to
He's in he's pulling himself out of the trap now
For the military to the southern border
Block the Border block all illegal traffic
Today
Right now
Use the crisis to fix
You're a criminal and fluid rugs and stuff
Oh
We forget about how many years Alex has been screaming about Rahm Emanuel saying never let a good crisis go
Go to waste talking about Alex evil man
Cuz ramazan
So Alex earlier said that he wasn't telling people to you know flee the cities or anyting
That's what he has Mike for
He's there
To give the synthesis or be the dialectic or whatever
Cheers Mike fulfilling
His role
You're in much better shape
Right now if you're in the city
You might want to get out while you can
If you can't
You better be prepared to hunker down and survive
Becoming
So survivors get out of the city at the zombies
So how does zombies
The Mike is still on his b******* about how this is a prelude for a
Chinese land invasion
Now
He has added a wrinkle to this narrative Vic
Coexist
With Alex's narrative
I find that very interesting
Are not on the same page at all
America
Does first wave
China
Allowing
Fractions
Means that they have achieved immunity for
Charter internet create the narrative
That are not bad
And I may have the perfect bioweapon launchpoint that's how you would do this
Exactly
They're willing to sacrifice so many of their people and then
Achieve immunity
Quickly with a
A Draconian lockdown means
Mobile military force that is immune to the virus
Can literally invade and survive
If they choose to do that
Because their troops won't be effective
By the virus there already
So bike seems to not be up on the narrative virus keeps coming back
You don't have an immunity to it
So
Kind of is a problem this is
Completely like
Incompatible
As long as China
It takes out
Mike Adams
They can they can invade
How do you say wrong takeout in a I'm just saying
You know like it before midnight
You know they take out
Strong disagree if only because I don't think that's a fair trade
I think it's a fair
I'm not sure I'll take
So Alex in my crap up there in a few knocks doesn't even recognize how that is
Completely
Contradictory
No beliefs
He doesn't
This is such a sad
Burpee plug
At the break we have the Silver Seal products we have all the right to face
Leonardo back in stock but it's going to sell out
Crazy
But job
Show on the airless right products are needed
Feeling right now
Holyshit
A scene where a guy like Alex meltdown this is exactly what it would look like
I mean you could you could
Interpret what Alex is saying to
There's the way he wants you to interpret it which is I wish I wasn't selling these products because people need them in a terrible
Situation in there buying them that means
Stupid situations Tarot
Yeah that's
The most generous reading
King of that
Reality
Me probably feels a certain amount of guilt yet about knowing that is silver is going to do s***
For people and like
He's been pushing it so hard
He has to have some sort of guilt about what he's doing this is a real situation for people well now that he's depressed
He can't ward off the guilt with his massive ability to
Deny reality
Like that's the that's
The great equalizer of depression in Fort
Sometimes it does show you reality in it
It's a real bummer and now he is already said he's never drinking again yeah
Alex
Weed legal come on buddy calm it down
Grows out dreadlocks
August comes in with the wig at figure eight
I'm sorry one last clip I thought that was the end of the show but then
You came in for the 4th hour a little bit they were confrontational at best
But not all that
Interesting one guy calls in and is like hey you guys
Who went in like
You went down to Virginia for the gun rally
Yeah you know what you know what happened
The f****** Governor put up a wall you guys didn't do s***
Guy whose leg
No no
You why didn't you murderer everybody Governor is killing babies are you guys doing
You said you loved
Killer getting you didn't kill the one time you had the chance
Alex can't really handle it new just as like
That we're the Bad Guys not the governor over yet
Grow up
It's not Saturday
But there's one clip hear from that little M segment
This really makes me think that
What we're doing is
Preparing what we're doing is preparing the audience
It's that like consequences are mountain
Anna's Bistro
That
You won't be able to get his way out of it
It's like I've almost completed my mission
So exhausted
Megan bad about to happen
I think I may be taking out
Police officer Bryson
Say that let me dramatic I want to tell you I love you and I appreciate you
But
You want a big stuff going down
Charlie Clark
Sure it was
You just hear there a sense of like
Preparation
It's really difficult about this is like how much do you take seriously
But I don't I don't know what's going to happen
Like
When he was
Financially
Broke
Before all this stuff happened and he was able to move massive sales
Like before that he was in place or he was very clearly
Repairing the audio
For the eventual non-existent
Looking forward
He was saved at the last minute
And you know I think
He was feeling
Like the needs
To do that because of the circumstances
It's rabbit
Just because I didn't end up being the the reality in the eventuality
Makes it look like he was just being dramatic
But I don't think he was I think he was behaving in a way that made total
And I think here
Ucn
Expression of very similar feeling
On his Parts like
He's looking
At the surrounding
Context of his life and being like
I might be taking off here soon
This might
Teacher takes a week off
This is the moment that he
This is the crisis where it's like
Stop
Go to rehab
Get into counseling
F******
Do this s*** and then
There might be a show.
Back to
Keep going
There will no longer be a show
It feels like a kind of moment before you go off
You got one tone
There's no part of me that thinks that car's not going
There's no feeling that I have videos of any kind of
Ability
And I don't think he has a support structure in place
Clearly these
They can people around him or no
If they would allow him to
Cancel his week vacation because of car horns
Yep
Like that means that no one is going to check
Kim at all
And the fact that he's continuing to behave very similarly
In order to sell his silver even at
After getting his letter from the New York attorney general
Means that he's not even able or willing
To adjust his behavior when the consequences consequences are made clear tape
Yep that's a real sign
Of trouble
Now he's got a
You got to lose
So I'm not going to make a prediction about what's going to happen but I can I can
Steve from his behavior from the changing tone the sort of
Triumphant bombastic Glee of the 12th
When the media started covering
Is silver stop by yelling and being like I've got these studies
Mother Jones
To the 13th
I'm still going to be defiant but I'm really sucking
Depressed everyone's
Going to die
I'm I'm
I'm just so I'm so mad
Just because if
If you did have a
A support structure
They would just
Be like hey
F******
Quit
Go to rehab
Go to counseling I don't think we'd be here at the time
And then
Come back and run the Jordan Belfort
You know you can still run the Griff
Just do it from the other direction you're reformed
Mauer whatever
You'll be fine
Just live better later
LED TV
Exact same space
These are the Perils of going down this pathway and I live this life and I don't know
G-Eazy you got
Charisma
I don't know I don't know what the path
Forwarded I really I'm disappointed that he's not taking a week off for my sake and for his
Honestly I was looking forward
But now I'm not paying attention to the present
It's now gotten to the point where his narrative is
Packed it in and we can expect that largely those will be the
The pieces
That move forward
And he'll try to filter any news that happen
Through those
Episode
I think it'll be a little bit of stagnation I feel that even in these episode
A bit as there is tons of stuff happening in the real world
Surrounding the Coronavirus
Content
Seems to stagnate
Acted while the
The concrete was wet
He and I would solidified a little bit
Becomes a little bit less interesting
From a covering him perspective
Well not just that but
Real world
So much is going on and because Allie Hamilton
Darte Alex
Narcissist that don't show the only stuff
What is going on at stuff that
It's happening.
Yep and that's what the world is dealing with
The world is dealing with
I mean we'll see we'll see what happens
I'm a
I made peace out and do another sort of like a Wacky Wednesday.
This is like a
That's where he's out on Friday I don't know where he's going to be on Sunday
Maybe we back to normal
Maybe took a nap or maybe a taupe
But
Back we will be back
Until then we website
Twitter we are interest at knowledge underscore fight not go to bed Jordan
Attract
We are on Facebook if you'd like to go to iTunes download re-review leave a message
Deserve the donate to show you know the deal
I taught Anthony fauci at Cornell
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color