Damn important
I have great respect for its knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Everybody outside and Dad talked a little bit about Alex Jones
We are damn Jordan Jordan
We're all having a rough go so let me ask you a question is it about The Witcher
I started to play the card game
I do like the diversity of things to
To do in the game especially that that that is such an extreme example
Game inside the game
Really good
I was just saying a happy thought
St Pat's
Because here we are recording on Saint Pat
That's it that's an interesting question I don't know
I don't really remember Saint Patrick's day is finally
Childhood years it was just like a thing that you know maybe you don't go to school
And then as I got older it was
Just an excuse to drink
Cancel
You f****** bread
Yeah
The same time I was doing that almost every other day to it wasn't like
My early twenties of late teens it wasn't like a
You didn't need a reason it reminds me of a Paula Tompkins
I don't remember that it's Saint Patrick's Day mainly because
For me
Any old day could be Saint Patrick
Noon
Especially whenever I've driven out of
Yeah it wasn't today wasn't something that you know I'm not
I think I might be a little bit
It's a least one of my grandparents adopt
Then we don't really know a whole lot of family lineage
But I understand there may be a little bit but I can't really
They claim that
As being something really important
Specific
60 Patrick's memory was what
Groupon
But my office was right over the the river
Downtown
Chicago that's amazing view of them dying the river green
Viet dispersing and like you could see it be
Coming
Celebration
Saint Patrick's Day
They're becoming is very
And then a couple days later you know walking around Viking Wrigleyville and just seeing
The trash
The other side of the
Grace
Absolutely
Do Jordan today we have in it
Episode to go over
Before we get down to that
Thank you
Sporting show
So first of all Michael thank you so much you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Next 2813308004 thank you so much you are now if I was you on
Normally I wouldn't normally I would have said no it's a reference to a song
Otherwise I would not have the phone number on the show
It's a rap song
NextBus
Yes thank you so much you're an alcoholic
Nextag thank you so much and I'll probably walk
Text Chris
Thank you so much
Conspiracy grows
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you
Text Rosemary that goes I'm not sure now.
I'm a policy wonk
Are you very much Rosemary as well as
Donated on elevated level
Thank you so much you are now a technocrat
And the video thank you so much you are now attacking
Regret
Heroin
So good
Freakishly large
Thank you so much Kelly and thank you so much video
Do it like this
Does Brookshire weird
Appreciate it thank you very much
Jordan today where I'm in the world is going a little bit
How to control there's a lot of various ways you could
Describe it I think tensions are in
Incredibly High I think that there's a lot of trouble
But I don't know how to I don't know how to put this well
It's it's the most uncertain I think I've ever felt
I I think
So 24me unprecedented on many levels
The uncertainty surrounding
View at the house
Situation
In the country and all of it
The f****** world
In a situation like this
I don't
Want to talk about Alex
No I don't really want to I tweet
Did Arthur episode on Monday
They covered a lot of these solidify
Location of his
Conspiracies around the virus
Sans IV the outbreak
And I don't really have a whole lot of faith that it's going
Grow much
From there yet
That's doubtful
You ain't seen his own personal struggles
Bleeding into his show in a way that makes him incapable of covering it
I don't know I haven't actually listen to Like Mondays episode but I don't
It's going to be anything really all that interesting cover
Either we would be spinning our wheels and I don't know if that's necessarily a great thing
Things to do
And I feel like
In this climate of
I like there's a lot of information and I think that people should be getting that in
A better Source has been
In terms of health information what you should do
What's what's best
Practices I think there are tons of other outlets and I don't think that we can fill that hole absolute
Where is I would love to be able to be the show that does literally everything
Now what we can do
Jordan I find myself
And situation where
It's just a real bummer it is I don't know exactly what to do
There's a lot going on
And it's scary time for a lot of people
You're going through this unprecedented Health crisis
Any question of what
Going to happen
Is it impossible for
No clue
I feel like in times like this listen
To Alex and talking about is bulshit isn't the highest
Priority
He's going to do what he does
Pandora next episode we can get back to
Paying attention to that
But in this time
I think a lot of people you know their self quarantine again
Stress is really high
So maybe the best thing we can do is
Providing the sky
An amusing Escape
From the prison
In order to do this though I'm going to need to perform a magical rich
I need everyone to
Close their eyes
All of you listen
Jordan you included
Unless you're driving don't do that then
But close your eyes and take a deep breath
Breathing
Breathe out
Breathe in
Feel your breath taking you to a simpler time a simpler place
That sound you hear
Is that a breeze rustling a palm tree
Is that a songbird fluttering right outside the window
It feels so familiar
What is that sound
I know it's alright let's do that
So we got ourselves.
I felt like baby the best use of our time would be to do another episode about Lionel
If
Disney Junior
Subway now he's still going to be bitching about people
F****** backpacks on this goddamn Subway's I will say that I went I was going through a lot of his back Kat
I found that there is a lot more episodes about backpack
Complaints about it cover
People having backpacks on the subway
So in case anybody out there has not hurt the other Lionel episodes
What is a gentleman who
Used to be a pretty regular Gaston Alex's show
He is a former lawyer
I'm a beast
Practicing lawyer monetarily sure what his life is all about
Albany you come on Alex's show and be really dish about stuff and then it stopped
Because he went real far epecuen.
Qanon
You now currently does three livestreams a day can't be real
Three live streams a day
8 a.m.
2 p.m. and 8 p.m. I believe
For the workout
Ely calls him absolutely
Rough song called working
Yeah
So I hear you Super 8
Qanon now but you can before he would go on Alex's show
In the earlier days
You know 2000
Nintendo 2011/2012
Back in those days
He was a commentator on TV station did New York
You complained about the most trivial bulshit
Like like
Biggest deal in the world backpacks on the subway where is a real picadillos is
He also is mad at how words are pronounced are terrible
Beyond the thesaurus absolute
And
So. That guy erupted
A very dog-eared
Crumpled thesaurus
What's that has been rifled through 100 times
In order to help get us through this
I've got us this
Spiteful Brewery
Miss O'Leary's
Chocolate milk stout
Lovett Illinois product helping out these these Illinois companies hell yeah
So let's take some novelty beverage drinks
Cheers to you
To the end of the world my friend
Drink drink or smoke them if you got them
Eat drink and be merry
That's pretty good
So we start off
There's been some trouble surrounded with this public health
Emergence
Wickersham
Are we in the present-day this is all in like 20 1122
I was thinking about getting some of his current Day stuff about the qanon and all that like why ruin a good time
So we are there's a lot of trouble about the cruise
Diamond
Situation
There's
Little people saying
Hey don't go on cruises
Lionel was way ahead of the Curve
Of course you really did not like cruise ships
Way before anybody with the exception of maybe David Foster Wallace
Did David Foster Wallace we wouldn't be in this situation A supposedly fun thing is never going to do it again
Here is Lionel complaining about cruise ships
The story about the tragedy involving the
Stricken Italian cruise liner reminded me of
Forget
Let me see if I can get through this
Without becoming a medic
I mean throwing up for visitors
Thesaurus
I'd rather drink bleach
It going another Cruise will my friend
Your boys live
Should be 1700 stand
What the attraction is
The cruises
My wife and I been on our share radio and work-related pain promotional deals
And the only thing worse than going on a cruise
Is that being able to hide
Because you're obligated to a meet-and-greet
And you can't escape
You want to prison
Scout can find a quarters
Either referred to as
Cabin door
Stateroom
The height
Your mind
Touchdown
Do a cruel
So starved that you've
For stimulation
That you'll see anything
Fegley label
Bingo in Toledo.
Bad my Max ventriloquist
Broadway cavalcades karaoke
Charades
Staring at your hand in the crows that's loud
Anything
You'll do any
Look I need to I need to pause here
I can't tell if this is self-deprecate
I've no idea because Lionel already established that he's been on these Cruise as much as a media affairs
He is leader paper do the cruise ships look how could you how could you beat all this
Complaining about how anything
Appears to be entertained on a cruise ship
He is entertainment on a cruise ship they will do anything including listening to Lytle talk
Understand
I really can't
Figure out if that's trying to be self-effacing or not but
Okay alright
Because yes
I have an idea for a great reality show
How about
Entertainment
Not good enough for cruises
Imagine the horror of that
I do imagine that
And around
Catatonic
Seemingly endless death maze
White Guy rap
Change to spend the rest of his miserable life
Paralyzing Bart Amil
And the food
Jaundice
Scripter amazingly
Similar Cuisine motifs
What exotic
Bye-bye
Quality
Yoga have as much as yeah what
Great comedies
I'd rather
Soccer Hospital map
That go on another Cruise
You will get anywhere.
Are you can see the gradual
Destruction of your mind and will to live
In the series of
Pictures on
Sail no less
That Chronicle your Maritime equivalent of get MO
The first day
1000-yard
Stare
J-3
Facial paralysis
Stultifying Express
Conducted
Turkish president
Day 5
Embark boots
Scream
The people
People that have been in
I'm sure personally selected
CIA rendition
Hanging out of you
I'd rather lick a bar rag
Then go on another Cruise
Can't do two licks
The Gap near anyting
Anything even resembling a cruise
Have I made myself clear
Coming
Jesus
I love the guy saying no
That's good complaint is this
It sucks to be
Oh
Really related
Millennials are so terrible they're the worst people they complain about the smallish it anyways I'm rich enough
And popular enough to go on cruise
People pay me to go on
The food bad
Aldi
Oh my God
I'm so frustrated by the piece
People laughing at
Like I don't know where the B
What because
I think that some of that is uncomfortable laugh
A lot of the laughter was at the rather suck a hospital mom
Coronavirus
Go to line
He says that a lot he says he'd rather suck a lot of
Mostly Hospital
Bar rag the problem with that from a structural standpoint if you're writing a bit is that licking
A bar rag is less
Disgusting
Been sucking the hospital. You have to flip those two
Has to work at least as a little alcohol
Squatting over a bear trap is a good third one
Cuz that causes like bodily harm and what have you but
Backwards then forwards
In terms of the
The rule of Threes there at the end
That's a failure
Alphabet
So even if you're trying to do this hockey nonsense at least do it like with a little bit of joke structure
I'm at my notes.
You said, does he
I've been with enough Road
Text to know that if
Just get the rule of three
You can do fine
Yeah it's it's less disoriented you at least
Do I have the progression
Correct solutely
So Lionel in this next piece
It's found some news that you next
I like that I think is a little bit different from structural perspective from our show because these are a little bit longer than most
The clips of Alex someone trying to be funny
Where is Water Valley
Discomforting
Very upsetting dispatches
From the lower upper class
Yeah that's what the
Lionel here has found some new stories that he thinks
Are funny
So he's going
To cover these stories
Lennar funny see what Patty bulshit this year
I think this might be the
This is these are not funny
Just a headlight
Headlines ma'am
Watching Sparky
Space
New stories that are so great
Just in terms of their facts
Structure in fragments
That's for tonight
Pieces about it I don't trust you with my Graphics thank you because
Disgrace
And I've got three for you tonight now first please
The stories are not
Funny I in no way want to create the impression that I'm mocking anyway okay
Then don't do this
All right y'all ready you you give him the
Like the point where this is
Fluoride in conception
You're talking about funny headlines. I'm not trying to make
Make fun of these stories
Alright
Joe neuberger had her for Monk
Do you seize by state wildlife officials
Burger who.im not Burger
Claim has a form of autism claims The Chimps are
Service monkey
Here's where it gets interesting
It seems that said State officials were
Different claims as to the chimp
Statuses
Service monkeys
Because they were dressed in pirate
She was also
Decked Out
A Buccaneer togs
And charge
2buckz
For a picture with her and her
Swashbuckler primates
Your service monkey
What you charge $2
I want they want to take a picture what can I do I can't stop them
This
Is what I meant
The usual pirate pun okay
But I'm not ardmediathek.de
Justify
So this first story here is about a woman having some monkeys that you dressed up like Pirates
There's no joke in Lionel segmented bypass he just thinks
The very existence of this story is enough to be f****** hilarious
There's no need to do any more work monkey Pirates it's time to go to lunch
Don't even bother with the
Slightest of pun
You kind of accentuate you do the joke where it's like I would do this joke and that's supposed to be the joke that's Para
There is an explanation for the story
The monkeys were dressed like Pirates
Because it was New Orleans
During Mardi Gras
Also there's
Much more to the story that Lionel could have riffed on if you cared at all
So this is a piece from 2011
But if I do any work Pastor letting a headline be a joke
He could have found that this woman
Had one of her monkeys stolen
In 2007
Years prior
Who works on exotic
Pet store
Inform at allegedly came into the store and
Stole her monkey friend that was Named Destiny
The explanation for them being serviced monkeys as spelled out in an article from News 4 Jacksonville about this that
Where she says that she has seizures
And the monkeys are trained to help her in that
Situation
Whether or not that's true that is the explanation
An article in the Florida Times-Union points out that the store was the victim of a number of pet that
In a short span of time
A police major told them quote it was the second time in six months that this type of monkey was stolen from that busy
The store owners also found a leopard gecko kingsnake and ball python missing around the same time presumably stolen
Okay alright
Okay
People stealing monkeys robotics alright okay
Struggling older woman who has the monkeys who may or may not be trained to how
Helper in the event of a seizure
One of her monkeys was stolen
What a few years prior to having them taken in 2011 is
Probably re-traumatizing for her but then on the other side of this which is
The situation in July 2011 this woman was convicted of Cruelty to monkeys over this
That's trouble she didn't have permits to have the monkeys they're being used to street performers an issue Department of Wildlife and Fisheries
A spokesman said quote the monkeys were in
Import Health overall
With a diaper rash dehydration in
Piercing
There's a larger story here cuz they're Pirates
I got it what the diaper rash
Who is the larger story that on the one side deals with an unwell person who has a
The connection with these monkeys and on some emotional level probably does need them
On the other
And it also has a story that clearly deals with animals
Abuse both of these are serious issues headline about a crazy lady dresses monkeys up like
That's wild
Who's the best service
The story there was a
Rash of
Exotic animal theft
Yeah
That spray that was in 2007
Did they find her
I couldn't tell from the news reporting
I think
Did they move to Atlanta and you know where she
She's working she was a big fan of 2 Chainz all right
Magic City
I don't know I couldn't tell from the
The stories
That what happened
Became of Destin
It appears that maybe she got another monkey friend
Alright anyways
He's not done
Are the premise of the story marinate with your neck
This is just a great headline
News in Pennsylvania
What's wave Hearing in boob murder case
What about Kermit button mirinda boob
I'd love to hear our own Marvin Scott the great marvez got it on
Live from the courthouse
11 News
Neither do I
Yeah
What's a boob
Why the f***
So this is a story about a man named Ronald heichel who is romantically involved with a woman named mirinda boob
Problem was Miranda was married to Samuel
In order to take care of that inconvenience mirinda and Ronald decided to
The murder Samuel
And then Ronald paid Kermit butts $5,000 to help
Dispose of the body
Is a pretty f****** serious story was the murderer in all but the funny
This is so fascinating to me because I'm the one hand Lionel tries to play this game where he is 100 synonyms for every word he uses
Sound like a smart ass f****** dude in the world
The humor of a
F****** third-grader
But
This is great
All I need to do is read this headline
Love it
Great I'm finally
Please I'm not making this up
And I even got it okay ahead of time so don't email me I just want this is crude
Global time
Out of China
The headline read
I swear to God
A happy ending to Farmers anus woes
Let me just read part of the
The first sentence from the story okay quote
A farmer from ju county of
Who made Providence
Has live 55 years without an anus
Habersham reason she comes to mind I know it's not what you think
Why wait wait wait
Nobody talks about the Ouija
Do you know anyone in giu County
A special hello and a howdy-do when I get well soon to my favorite farmer with the
Hope you get better
So there you have it
Thank God for the internet and I have these stories link
In their entirety on my pixel Evan blog comment
If you're bored out of your mind
That took a dark turn out to be clear also when he says referring to the weatherman
Traffic
That's confusing now
Flip stories f****** horrifying
About 55 year-old Chinese farmer was bored of the
Congenital condition that left it without an anal open
Without getting too graphic
Epic prior to 2011 he had a surgical hole that he could use to s*** but he also had
Extruded manual
According to an article in pediatric clinical advisor there there's some degree of
Perforated anus in approximately one in five thousand
Live birth
But you can imagine this is usually not too big of a deal
For people with better health coverage pretty immediately upon
But it could be horrible for someone like a farmer living in
Absolutely
This story is just
Haha this guy didn't have a butthole to Lionel believe that you probably
It's like really edgy comedy stuff like he's out there working Blue Man
I never imagined missing Jay Leno
If you're going to read headlines
UCSF
I think that he thinks
He's kind of like a hipper
Edgier Andy Rooney
I believe that
The kids man
Divers have a butthole
Bored
Tragic
Reality but that guy lives with yeah this is just
Is Lytle mocking people with shity or lives that have the headline really should be like awareness that this is
Congenital condition
Exist
Choose your words better
Oh God damn it so that really wasn't it
Lionel is a mess
It would be wrong of
To sit here and say that
He is wrong about everything or doesn't have some good
Generally
B2B variant support of lgbtq Rights
Very in favor of legalizing sex work
He has some
Pretty decent Cosmopolitan ideas
And his next trip I got to say
I find no fault
Then this one take that he has
Why do we have presidential debates
Seriously
Have you ever heard something candidates
Something about anything that made you say
I think I look for that guy or gal
Yes
But that answer just now
That changes every
I'll save you the type no
If you like a cat
You'll love her debate performance if you hate
Someone shorter than the cure for
Real quick this is part I agree with now think that's a bad take a lot of color suede by
Wow
Can't say what it is
Bigot
Now if I had my druthers then I'm not so sure what druthers even are
Cool
Have you ever heard before
Of course I do
What
I had my
Here's how I do debate
Big the GOP snoozefest
One solid hour before the actual
Everybody Gibbons is drinking I mean hardcore
Alright he's playing me with this one
Then
Ties at half mast
Hair messed up
Cigarette dangling from your lips
Maybe an eyelid droop
We're just learned but the truth
Pours out
And exudes like a
Michele Bachmann today look
I'm hot
And you know it
I would really
Run hour
By the way for guys in Brooklyn
You think I like being me I know I know I'm bored
And I'm sick of the Romney jokes
Perry
A triplane cowpoke 24/7
Quiet business it's hard
Grandpa
Look at me
Secretly keep calling me a nut
I want to follow the Constitution
And they called me at 9
Wait that's what Ross
Need to get out of the country inn
It's bad for an amateur
He's just doing front
A psychiatrist
I'm crazy in the coconut
Unbelievable but that's your image of what Ron Paul would be like drunk
We talkin about how you tried to
Invade that Island
All right let's get real nobody would go
Let me tell you about my problem with O'Shucks
What's a loser
And thinking of medieval cut me some slack
Caden husband
You Got It Bad
Herman daddy neither sure why it was named
Yep
Herman white-cain
Why why
Because of all the times people have permit
Why
Note
Imelda
How old I look like
Chucky
About white brother have a million-dollar tablet Tiffany's so quit your bellyaching
Find me San Antonio
Why am I running again
Anybody
Help me
Now that
Comet
That is you
I like the idea of coming on to your platform and being like presidential debates
Fish beef
Conversation I think is
As room for that
Like
You floated
However as a comedy bit
Those are bad examples of what these candidates would say when they're drunk
Newt gingrich's just saying he's fat
Newt Gingrich is like I'm trying to get another wife right now I'm hot you can do better
Michele Bachmann is like I can see
Either side of my head but not straight
Final vote Tuesday to go with your drunk
You know they say they write drunk edit sober
Take a note take a note
Yep
And see what they would say if they were in your position
See now I'm going to I'm going to take his wake up in the morning
Polish it up a little bit on TV
Remove some prepositions shirt
Flowers for re-election
Do I go with the hard-r
Goodbye.
Okay so I'll take this idea all approved
Did you ever do there was a show out in the northwest suburbs where
They would get you a hotel
And you would do the first
Completely drunk
In the meantime I'd heard of that but I've not the guy that that is the perfect
Format for a debate
That would be interesting
I really I think those kind of shows are really irresponsible
I probably while I was doing stand-up would have done it
If asked
But I'm glad I didn't
I can't lie and say that I was sober every time I stand up
Absolutely
Yeah I don't know I did this is close to like
Alright
GPS doesn't work out
But yeah
You should die
Head back to the
So I'll say this relying on that last click he had a point and he made it
And that is the piece that needs to be better if everyone is
The message is
Yeah
Now I think
I thought I stumbled into
Do a couple of these these missives
F****** synonyms
Bet these couples
Yeah it's not bad
These next couple are muddy
I don't know what the point of the month
I want you to update from now on or we start these
I want you to try and guess what they're going to be about
Let's see this one we're talking
In 2011/12 tall of this is from the 2011/2012 win
You was gone from the station by about 2
Started doing like
Overly long boring
Going to cover those
I mean
We got to go with Obama
This one's got to be about
Right
It's not
My friends
I'd like to discuss something with you one of the best
Human Endeavors in fact
What makes us different and separate into
Distinct from the other animals
The pyramids are ability
We winning
Penguin
Pot of gold
Train
And you know what
Vibes that vehicle
Mega Millions Lotto ticket
Take a chance
Snipped whatever
So you're listening at this point you thinking always going to take the piss out of the lottery he's going to go after these either either
Either the exploitative nature of the lottery the dumb dumb
Supai Lottery
I could go either way
The punch down
Kratom benefits
This is best at this point
No idea where this is going
The cruises
It's your ticket to a dream
Nothing but exemplifies this
And the offer
Seaworks
That's one example.
Sensible of the group
Perhaps a tad Daft and dreaming
Decides that for reasons that
I can't quite Wrecking
Fathom
Give me a lottery jackpot
Significant enough to warrant
Pulling his
Coworkers harder
Shekels to buy a series of
Buechel fund of
He's mad about office pools for lottery
Borderline antisocial
But also he seems to be
Bike
This is
Kind of dumb
Nothing exemplifies this. This Dominus
I mean I guess
It feels like a negative how does he feel about March Madness bracket
She doesn't bring it up like
Point to like this this fool the simpleton who believes in that has all this hope he's
Play pointing to the guy working the board behind him
When you see like what do you hear laughter it's often because he's
Gesturing
To the the room
Alright
Hey guys let's just do a fun things
Together and we'll just eat that nobody wants to win but it'll be
Technical employee
The station
Habitual find a tendon
Find or derivative
White-eyed delusional and frankly insane Alpha member of the psych ward
Collect everyone's dollarin
Buy the series of
The photocopies.
He realizes them somehow he provides weird notation
Have you been
Childish
Psychotic
Scroll that an FBI profiler
Serial killer
I thought he had his dream
Sweet dreams
I'd hope
And pray
And wish
When
Divide 81
Money
Cats and say I'm a winner
I do look at this poor example of genetics run-amok
Slightest idea math probability or anything approximating
And you know
Knowing your heart
Manchild ever win
He certainly would be that Lottery victim
That pathetic Orchard
Mountain bikes
Pastime
German p*** but I say
I say let a man dream
But I'm groveling delusion so what
Way to pull off this now you're fine with confidence
Deliberately cobbled image of cool collected and together
Shut the main drain that noted
Better place for Charles Manson once noted as follows
Look down at me and you see a fool
Look up
And you said God
Looks traded me
And you see yourself
What does that have to do with anything
I haven't the foggiest idea
Of what that has to do with country what this
Brief
Winning
I'll bring something
Just one
For one moment
But the man
Dream
As you see fit
This is the kind of
Ginkgo are
You know like milk from a
From a standpoint of like what is
Is he saying it's like
He's abusing this guy is being crazy
At the beginning and like this is like all right
The point turn
Turns into let them Andre genetically inferior just
It's very strange
Picture how to decipher
AC Pro or against
Help
The end is definitely for it but it's
Is it stupid
Maybe it's just sort of thing or it's like the dumb raffle the crowd the rebel
Terrorize
Let them have their exactly I get paid to be on cruise ship
Let them have their stupid dreams of office poop
You just mad that no one invited him to the office.
There's one of those
Personal storage
Absolute mad at a guy
Generally speaking his topics
Might as well be like he looks over his balcony in his like
What's a billboard say I'll be bitching about that
But this is this does feel like there's a guy evolved
Yeah two important points one the German pornography thing
Is a running gag that's why everyone laughed at
He always right whenever you bring the pornography references German pornography
The second thing is that Charles Manson thing I think is actually the closest
He gets to like being pretty absurdist funny
It has nothing to do with what he's talking about
And the way he calls himself out for like
Nothing
Nuggets
It's close to work
But because of these surrounding to
Confusion about what the guy I think that it fails
I I think maybe my big ass
Issue here is
His complete and utter lack of
Timing wedding
He slows down
Yeah like he can get the ranch
Timing pretty well but once he starts trying to hit the the punchline
He wants a
F****** up
That is a problem now that. Just like
Charles Manson noted philosopher Charles Manson once noted
And then
It's terrible to go do some reps at open mic
Absolutely
Get some of this worked out workout there 5 at some shows long before they show up on The Tonight Show or anything like
Like that come on man workout your workout your five
My friend this is not the
The Tonight Show
So I thought was a little bit confusing a little bit muddy
What is actual point is
I think his next one is another example that what do you think is about
Let's see well we just had
Office pool
You bet
The genetically inferior getting everybody in the office
To give them $1 very important pressing issue in American culture
It's got to be back
Gabby backpack
That's a good guess but I will say that I didn't
Include any further
This week A friend of mine
What showing a young lady in her 20s
About 40 years ago
And he handed her the yellow
Photos
I can't handle bone-forming
And it hit me
She never held
Snapshot
Photos
Never before
Smartphone and iPhone
Pictures
Scream
Anime
Be printed for
Occasion
Rare
She knew nothing of
Polaroid Kodak
Kodachrome
One hour photo
I want chocolate
Home movies
The right now you can tell that the setup is
Kids these days exactly
Is Andy Rooney all the way
EB the johnra of these kids don't know anything about XYZ thing
They don't know about chasing the hoop down the road with a stick
Never worked in the coal mine
Jose's no way
Sounds like
Was when she asked
When were these photos taken
How old were they
And I said well
Turn the photo of
It was a printed Mountaineer
She never seen
Snapchat
You photos back
And every now and then threw something
Snafu
You get the wrong patch
I just Romo
Gordy's Fayetteville
How to remember taking these photos
Who are they
Remember
Before when
Photo books
Chloroplast
Black almost
Paper albums and you glue in his room
Triangles to hold
The pictures and play
Same pictures
And now the bike
Theoretically
On a phone or computer
Where's Creighton
Why
Because it's
Butter today that's
Comet
As juicy
I don't know what the point is this
Wait
Okay
All right so is
His point is
Look at these
He's dumb dumb young kids
Who don't know what a Snapchat is
Don't have a Polaroid in their in their bones
And
Cool
Well it's great it's
Try to set up as this like if you kids don't know from photographs
Kids
Vanellope and it's like
Because it's better
Yeah
I mean this is
I mean yeah
This is maybe a trade observation
These kids don't know anything about photographs and a good
Okay alright
Alright thanks for signing off on iPhone wide open
The TV used to turn off
9 p.m. and there was nothing
Until 6 a.m.
Bad
Now I appreciate late-night infomercial it's like the whole message
It is
You know
I haven't people remember and having a Avoca
Images of this bygone time
That sucks
Hours putting
Looking at the
The same photograph wondering
Who are they
And now I don't have to do that
Weird
I think baby that's an example of Lionel subverting the form
B b like it's poorly done
But you can't just
Throw the twist there in the last second
Of the of the
You kind of need to earn it a little more ripe
Overall Edge n***** pork
Pennywise
This next clip yard
Misses epistle letter
Post
Report
I'm out
The next one what you think
You going to be about
Okay
See
Young people again what are young people
Destroying
It's about IPA
The beer
Snow out there is not
It's actually about
It's about how there's a rash
Stupidity
That is a
Going around the country
I'd like to address the topic that isn't
Ever discussed it's a condition that someone you know
Suffers from
There's no cure the diagnosis can be tricky it's called
Stupid
No one talks about
Stupid it's not that we don't have a long
Standing
Series of
Aphorism
About how stupid people cannot be cured
Well
He seems to be like trying to
Set this
Stop with a
Like hey no one talks about how some people are dumb
The quiet problem again I would say go to another disabuse yourself of that notion
Pretty quick
The heartbreaks
The pain of stupid is responsible for more lost jobs and lost opportunities than you can imagine
It's wrecked political careers
Marriages
Costas Country Village
Use of dollars in Lost productivity more than any other individual pathology Factor
There isn't a person or family today who hasn't been personally touched by
Stupid
Four years medical Sciences both failed and refused to address and quantify this sometimes deadly diagnosis
Stupid I refer to is
Uncontaminated by either a substance abuse or sexual component
Hey Brett Favre
Penchant for obscene s****** and Ally
Is he stupid
Yes
But there's a c
Sexual component involved which renders
Megaman completely devoid of any rational thought
Potentiate
Stupid like
Alcohol
Angie
Certain medication
Barb was motivated by
You know
Weird men aren't responsible
Boehner aspects to it then it's not stupid stupid stupid
The stupid that he's talking about
You've made that clarification
He missed
The easiest
You missed the
Easiest joke that everybody is had a family member who does it and then the obvious joke there is
If you don't know who it is
It's you
Line on I-30
But don't pure and authentic stupid is different
Stupid enjoy the singularity on the boneheaded
Spectrum
Uncontaminated by any other Factor
Chemical emotional or homeowner
Case in point
Navy Captain owenby honors who enjoys the honor
I'm losing I get it here craft carrier USS Enterprise because of a series of profanity-laced sexually-explicit home
Homophobic
And inappropriate videos when he was their ship's executive officer translation
He was stupid
Yeah it wasn't drunk Jairo she did it for the heck of it on his own in a strict military regime
But doesn't Brook any of this nonsense
A man who clawed his way up the career ladder whose wartime command is pure gold
He gave it up for no reason whatsoever
Edward Mason
Stupid
Stop Text Aaron
Drawn by The Lure of the
Even an in-house closed-circuit
Camera
There's also the similarity of the case of General Stanley McChrystal
Who on his own
No particular reason disparages commander-in-chief in
I'll all places
Rolling Stone interview
Stupid
Stupid stupid
Only ignored nipple
Magnificently stupid
Colossal Cave
Brobdingnagian stupid
Medication will help anyone at any time
If you were someone you loved
Suffering from the Heartbreak of stupid there's no known cure
No medication no treatment
And don't be misled by milder forms of the disease foolish idiotic as a seemingly ubiquitous damn
Full no
Paraphrasing Justice Potter Stewart equipment
Seminole 90s
64 giacobello case was stupid
You know it
When you see it
Comment
Accordingly
So
I don't understand
Because the parameters as they were set up in the Brett Favre stupidity doesn't count cuz you was horny
Right so horny stupid doesn't
That's stupid
Stupid
Jets versus the example that used Owen honors
Like I was a Navy Captain until he got in trouble for those defensive videos
Cuz he was filming while he's on board his ship
The reason this should qualify as pure stupidity
Is because otters wasn't just making those videos for fun
He was screaming them on Saturday nights for the crew
In the same way that far ahead of secondary motivation to his action
Namely being horny
Soda Donner
He was driven by a desire for attention and some poor with localized celebrity on the ship
Is obviously doesn't meet the standard line was established for the store
Report supposed to be about
The situation with General McChrystal was rolling
Stone Peace by Michael Hastings
Wearable Crystal and his staff talked bunch of s***
Maybe this is closer to an example of just regular stupid
But I don't know if I would say
Speaking to a journalist
Quickly that's really stupid
This seems like you know
The problem isn't what
Crystal said it's so I'll be
Commander of the International Security assistance
Sports NFL
Stan
Give me the Beasley only two examples Lionel gives about this rash of stupidity he's worried about
It seems like maybe he was trying to talk about a lack of discipline in the military
Connect
Please do examples of military people who got out of pocket
Boggles my mind
Just because his
Problem with
Honors
Seems less about
The massive homophobia
And more
About that he recorded
Or with diagram giving you my peace
Is more correct or incorrect it's that he told somebody
Military discipline
Keep your house in order otherwise you're stupid
I don't think the military discipline is stupid
I think he's trying to Trojan Horse a complaint about military people not following orders and being like
Really regimented and all that stupid
Stupid and I
Two examples both of them
Exactly the same
Not bad
That clip
That report
Is really weird
To hear
Particularly after you hear this
If you think for a minute
Direct Perry's disastrous performance Wednesday night is going to affect
His chances of cinching the GOP nomination
You're out of your mind
Listen to Republic
Let me be brutal
The GOP and Republicans have
Some kind of immunity against
Before you think I'm being partisan
Perish the thought
Let me remind you that the Democrats were nuts
Over-the-counter
Pended Obama
Whose campaign transmission never got out of Hope and change
They love what they perceive as
Smart
No message
But Republic
La Bonita
Any Republican says
No matter how he says it
So long as it matches lowering taxes
I bet his eyes lovingly over the image and myth of Reagan
Vegan dispute Evolution darwinian mechanics
Gravity
He can't believe in intelligent design
And that beard to 6,000 years old
No problemo
I love or the supposed left-wing media laughing Jordan over Perris
Incredible
Inability
Remember
Three agencies
Who's rainbow boa
Represent
The sole basis of his campaign
No big whoop
Republican stage W have repackage wandering confused logo lately
Engram
I somehow Charming
These guys are good
They didn't realize their verbally an intellectually ambiguous candidates and politicians
Pretty critical analysis
By rebranding them as a new and improved departure
From the intellectual Elite
So you see what you have a pretty good diagnosis if it's okay
Republican
Immunized
Themselves against being seen as stupid
Cuz it's an opposition
Into some kind of idea of the
Intellectual Elite he's talking about intellectual is a month and the right-wing
From his local area
This is a fairly
Accurate take I would say
This is middle of the road she goes okay
They embraced being curious and load the functionally illiterate
Stupid uninformed and grossly under qualified
No no inclusion
And their political lexicon
But I must say something about Rick Barry
I get this guy checked out immediately
I'm not sure if he's got a drinking problem
A drug problem or a combination thereof
But something's wrong with this dude
If your parent or kid acted as goofy as he does
You'd watch them do a neurologist right away
I just think little mixtape
What the hell do I have to do to get ahead in this town
Herman Cain
I saw they women okay 40 years ago
Perris y'allywood
What about me
What oregano
Hey I can play Wall Street sell out
Come on people please
Remember
When it comes to Republican candidates from Bush
The bach Principe Linda Perry the cane
It's nice to know
If there exists not anyting
That they can say
That would be considered so stupid
And it would disqualify them
And in a way that's
Had a nice isn't it what's common
Jesus
Is something wrong with Rick Perry
And I think that's a good
I can be president
I'm not sure either and he's like a toothless Joe Pesci
Like you're just confused but you're not afraid of yeah there was a complicated sort of point he's trying to
I don't think it's complicated the point I think
It's it's
The follow-through
Write a whole piece about how there's a rash of stupidity going around the country as evidenced by to military guy
Can candidates got a lot to be as stupid as they want and that's great
Is my lovely
Don't you don't you want to live in the world where one half of the political system is
Completely stupid
Those two things are a little bit contradictory
Let's Straighten
So we're going to get to this next
Report
Back to our game
Your offer already.
Let's go with the left-field he's going to he's going to talk about Sammy Sosa that's
That's what's going to have to talk about
I should tell you this
In terms of sports references he makes it's almost always broke
It's always prowrestlingtees old school pro wrestling
Is that the only thing that I'm not sure if there's a baseball reference
As much as there is talking about like gorgeous
Just Jordan
Essentially
But heavily script
So maybe not
It's not about sports at all
You listen more to me you'll know that I believe I looking at the UK to see where globe
Insanity
He's heading
No disrespect to the britons but it's
Disrespectful
But to be honest the Brits are simply.
Quest Laboratory disease
What insanity
I'm sure by now you've heard of
Schools in our country prohibiting dodgeball tag hugging
Name is because
The fears of
Hahaha
They all started in the UK
I'm telling you if it's not
A penny UK
You know
How to make a good
The tourism
Anywho
Here's the latest
But you won't believe
Primary schools in the UK are Banning
School kids
Are you sitting down
Having best
Friends
That's right
Swear to God
You're burning kids
From having best friends why you ask good question
The first reason is because they want to encourage kids
Two-player large group
Versus focusing on one on one
Individualized
Amicability in socialism
Weird
Socialist message there I guess
Anime
Is it metal
They're doing it to save the child from the pain of splitting up from your best friend
When I guess the friendship ends
Kid moves
Give you the heave-ho
Predeceases you
Suppose
Tylenol
I just want that one
Kids and adults
Should I have pets because
They'll die
It shouldn't grow too attached
Grandparents or their own parents because
Advisor
They're All Dead
Perhaps
Self-loathing might be a demon's well because
You're going to die so don't get to it
Attached to yourself
I forgot matter
Yeah there's a
Before you know it
What's the real reason
Learned helper
Jazz
When you're subjected to overwhelming unrelenting negative stimuli
Without surcease
You learn to make
Become helpless
Stop
It's a guiding principle behind the abuse bowel syndrome and our world
I'm overwhelmed oversaturated with law after law
Limitations
You can't even
And now we're habituating kids
Clear
You can do nothing
We control what
Each month we're reading eventually
You'll become
Habituated and condition
And
When the feeling of helpless
Completely sets in
They will have
White
They will have capture
Hobbit
Add juice
So this is a story that Lionel's reporting on out of the sun to r i b a has thinned sourcing
Now that that rag is right on it every time
Specific schools are Educators who were said to be banning kids
From having best friends
In that piece
The entire article is based on to second-hand comments sing
Some schools are doing
Directional provided is basically
Close to it line was talking about
Avoiding the pain of losing your best friend if you move
But it's also supposed to be
Like the emphasis largely is on
Encouraging Group Play
Instead of children
Excluding each other
I have no idea if anyone is actually
Did you win that from this article though because
Is no one who's an actor
His policies mentioned
Or quoted in the article
What super weird isn't this article was published in March
12 then
In March
2013 there's an article on Fox News quote
Several schools in the UK issue best friend
Dammit
These people are all stupid
Weirdly this is just Fox news reporting on the story in the Sun
From a year prior
Yeah they've always been
Then in September 2017 there's an article on Business Insider
Quote schools are Banning best friend
Protect students feelings
This article is implying that UK schools are Banning best friends but the only source that has
Is a maryclaire article about a school that Prince
Georgia Tann
Which might be skewed sample set
Talk about the Royals
Then in January 2018 there's an article
On Fox with the headline
School band
Best friend
Which is just about the business
Insider story
Itself was just about to marry Claire story about the school to Prince George ghost
God this is that
No more September 2019 there was an article in the Sun
How about how princess Charlotte is going to school where she can't have a best friend
School that Prince George
Got these people
Just want something
Sing so bad
Give me a singular obsession
This is such that like
That rainbow lips
Stick party thing all over again
Do you remember the b****** party
Who are you people sure are you doing
Yeah you guys doing
It still seems a little bit more damaging does Urban myth
Don't like Lionel gets the message
Of what these stories are
Supposed to evoke
Yeah it's like
Socialist
Social planners
Not have friend rate learned helplessness
Nothing's more 1984 the new
Unsourced report about some Britain's maybe not wanting to have messenger
Did the Royals
The Royals are allowed to have best friend. I don't know if there is a movement in schools
Entirely in the United States or in the UK about not letting
Kids have best friends
Play wouldn't be surprised
There were some schools of the tri-tip
Emphasize
Communal group Lane it's healthier that way
Exclusionary behaviors are generally things you wanted discouraged
Is not in
Even if this is what
A hundred percent accurate
The the
Place behind all of this s*** is coming from is just like
Hey
Don't exclude people
Write a good idea
Why do we have to turn this into a f****** the government is
Monitoring you
I think it's so fascinating is like
For a neuro the span of seven years there's all these articles about the the UK Banning best friend
Does its catnip to right-wing media sources
It is it really is
Wanted yellow about something but there's nothing really big going on in the news today
I think I remember that story from like 10 years ago or
Breasts best friends were babybay
And it's always presented as like this new thing in 2012 was this new thing beside Sun article
The next year in
Fox News it was being presented as a
Even though it was a year old article that was the source
Godby
Out of control
So this next clip Lionel stupid might be an issue for
Maybe
So Lionel talks in this next clip about the
The collapse
That's coming in the world what do you think is going to
Precipitate
Some petty b*******
It's got to be some petty bulshit
I'm going to go with
Pet ownership
Egret
It's New Year's weekend
Television heaven for me luxuriating before the flats
Screen
Redskins from the couch
The wife watching
TV marathons in Moscow
We gave you the Honeymooners by gold standard
I watch Dallas
The show's time listen classic
I'm back
Wells flipping through the hundreds of channels
I came across the most frightening television show
That I have ever seen
What do you think
Hey New Year's well it's not the
The Twilight Zone
It's not Doctor Who
Let's go with
The Bachelor
Show was impacted import
Far beyond anything you could imagine
BB looked at by 7
Skip through the rubble of our once Pride proud culture
While many factors caused Rome 24-hour fall
Will be because of this program the show is called
My Strange Addiction on and this is the set
The warning
Chattel
Channel that has yet to apologize for Toddlers & Tiaras
I know what you're thinking
Why do you want to chat line Olympics
So bad why
Because it's my job that's why I I want it for you I've got
Not the problem
Associated with mental illness
In an effort to demystify
Andy stigmatize the subject
You're that last there it's cuz he pointed at the employer
Like a band leader
Hoarding buried alive
Not to be confused with the Animal Planet
Confessions Animal Hoarding
But they show
My Strange Addiction
Let me just tell you what a few of its episode in no particular order
There's a woman
Who has Pica syndrome
I was addicted to eating household cleanser you know like Ajax
She was 12
You're going to be
You're going to drink bleach buddy maybe not drinking
Another woman
Beige tile
Toilet paper
Cleanup course
Sleeping with her hair dryer
Right next to her
All night
Crazy
It also highlights
I won't stop talking to them
Someone who Tans up to three times a day
Cannarex Sia
Wake up
You see what's happening
Weird evolving dematerialize Augusta creative cultures iFunny Motors pick mandates
Mash
Even Seinfeld
Giveaway
My Strange
Pelican
Beautiful Barrel
Not to share or teach
Stand before a camera
Have you noticed
Look at me they scream
Look at me I'm as helpless
Yeah like that
It seemed to be that he was sort of
Dancing around a commentary about what art
Send media word yeah and like
I think there's a fair point to be made that the way
The exploitative way people engage with media like
What's a celebrity rehab or My Strange Addiction version of the Freakshow
Not
Exist on television if people didn't
What is there wasn't
The man the supply probably wouldn't be there
One season and then
Another season of Who Wants to Marry a Millionaire too far
Cover boss had two seasons or whatever which is
Is bananas
If that were the katiki was making
I guess
That's fine but then I don't know why you have to
Point fingers at the people with pie
I got like that's a real condition
Yeah it's not like something that people are just making up for attention or something
Cruel at the end when he's at he's desperate
People on the problem that I have is it
Because he's really bad at this
I don't know if that part at the end of supposed to be self-effacing
Like You shiting on these people on My Strange Addiction
For the desperation
Be in front of a camera but meanwhile he is so desperate to be in front of a camera that he thinks insulting
Countess worthwhile comment
Like I don't
No
I really don't know if that was meant to be a winking job in himself at the end or bruised just accrual outro
Punching these people who he is only heard about cuz they're open
His mother struggle and because of that
Because I can
Can't tell
It's a bad day
Yeah
I think why I think what would really undercut
His biggest
His biggest problem
Is I think in most of it
These clips
He has
Kind of
Gotten the point
That in each one
He's also kind of given a nod to that idea of like
Will be there about D stigmatizing mental illness and getting people more comfortable with it
And then incredibly up
Obtusely ghost
Hard against that is humanly
Like almost deliberately
Like he's he's literally like these are people who deal with stray
Strange addictions
And we're watching
But also it does help us
Kind of get more comfortable with the II
The idea of it
Spiga mental illness
And hey look at how dumb those Dum Dums are for going on TV
Desperate for attention
It's very weird
If you'd made it more
Clear
Like at the end if that was supposed to be like
Winking like
I am desperate for attention to
You should have laid that the the setup for that
Punchline
Throughout the rest of the
Some hints along the way
It stands now it really
Just feels mean
It feels like
Pointlessly mean
Because buddy
You're talking about 1
You're living through the f***
Golden age of television
With the Mad Men and Breaking Bad and so many of The Sopranos like this is the Golden Age
And then not only that but he's not going out
After
Reality TV shows that are based entirely around Gathering attention like f******
The Bachelor or Jersey Shore or any number of
He's going around reality TV shows
Biggest around people who are struggling
This is a meme
Criticism that could be made of
Of
That John ra of television
I just think Lionel is incapable of it certainly Within
2 minutes so he just goes this route
Keeping people who are in trouble or dealing with stuff
On the real world are looking
Retention
People who are on My Strange Addiction or sometimes people who just
Cannot afford to go
Any other way and those types of shows they do deal with
Like things that will be a problem
But there was a situation on the real world Road Rules challenge where a couple of dudes sexually assaulted a female contestants
And like of course they were never on the show again like they got sued and like that
Programming because of obvious like
There's an issue
Yep yep
There there is
The demand
Would be a problem if not
Activating address this thing
Same thing with the
I can't remember
What it was theirs that VH1
When they were trying to do all their their reality show stuff
There's a show called Megan wants a millionaire
Are the contestants
Choose like a gold digger lady and I'll have you
There was also the there version of real world Road Rules challenge it was called I love money
And to be like the people
Competing for Vermont
And there was a contestant who was on Megan wants a million
Who then ended up on the Isle of money
I am that guy after they had
Filmed the season of I Love Money
He murdered his wife okay well that's not good
It was a Grizzly Mart
Yeah they dismembered and like like put her in a suitcase
They're only able to
To determine it was her because
The serial number on her breast implant
Yeah the only way to Lionel would know about that is if her last name was but
Stroke
What ended up happening was
They just canceled That season
Even made it never came
People believe it's because he
He won
So it's like you can just get rid of the first couple episodes
What I'm saying I'm trying to get around 2 is that there is a
Weather is an actual demand or an applied demand element that will alter content that is Supply
So if people started engaging with
Content like
These rehab shows for
My Strange Addiction in ways that work Freakshow it
Yeah the treatment of it was
Vanderwood
The be less incentive for the shows
Created in that vein
Right and the way Lions behaving
Is actually part of the problem
So
Because he's there for the
Exploitative nature of
These programs
That's what he's there for
Let's bet he's the demand but it's his job
So why this next one
Alright
I would try and ask I would have drink
Give me a word
Yeah give me a give me a direction
Hard
It's a social criticism
Don't know if that helps
You got me
I'm going to go with walking okay
Some people are saying Sumer is
Battling
Some people are saying
X or Y
Wait some people are saying
Text people are why
Okay that's not
I mean that is as good of a Templars I can give you and you are never going
Alright I'm going to go with
Well obviously if I'm never going to get it I'm going to say young people are out
I'm going to go with
Complains about the used as much as it seems
Yeah
It seems like maybe does I'm going to go with some people think women are capable of holding public office
It says some people think women be shopping
Hero might be the most overused word of our Alexa
Next
Genius and love
Look
We all are thankfully nothing happened at Times Square and more thankful that the mad bomber turned out not to know diddly-squat
What about
Okay here we go leave that nothing happened
It's going to be a tag
Everyone was Vigilant and alerted the
The cops are the hero
But Statham
Laudanum
Appreciate them congratulate them but not automatically bespoke bestow
The Halo title of hero
Lionel gets a certain amount of time on air for these reports and he sat down it was like you know what I'm pissed
Stop that people reporting terrorist attacks are being called to your house
I don't think of
I wouldn't say that this take
Is heroic
Heroism involves an act of Bravery doing the right thing
Calling 911
Calling the cops is what's to be expected
Civilized people do
Suggest that is heroic
To alert the cops
Mom said something's wrong means that getting involved is not the norm
We want to thankful for being alert
We've seen the video of that poor man
Left to bleed to death a load of the sidewalk
A man who really was a hero
He showed bravery and stop the woman from being mugged
How about Wesley Audrey who in 2007
Lay on top of a complete stranger who had fallen on subway tracks
As the train passed over him
Psychologist now refer to the bystander effect
Where people see something
I do nothing
It conjures up Kitty Genovese
So we appreciate anyone who alerts
The cops what yes
Is that involved hero overuse is a verbal version of grade inflation
Is becoming an automatic reflex response
That's will be Mentor show thanks and well-deserved thanks it that
You know how many police dog what's your f****** point
Kind of Duty have received
Heroes tribute
But those jobs as Wonder Woman greater fantastic as they are
You're my hero
Harold M fine but I hear a whisper
Special and Hillman
Basic Congressional Medal of Honor
Which isn't even given to
Everyone actually demonstrating bravery give the Rush Limbaugh
Vacuous gallantry
And intrepidity at the risk of
One's life I've been through.
The word hero was almost holy and recognizes
Quintessential Valor
Gyro sandwiches
Guitar Hero and the worst
You know how is ear wax
Speaking the word for photocopying
It's yet state for all the teams of tape
Don't let that happen to Hero
Remember
The First Amendment doesn't protect someone from yelling fire in a crowded theater
Okay
And only if
There's really no fire
Because if there is
It's you dude
Write me
Read me in, did you see fit
So if I understand correctly it's your duty to yell fire if there is a fire
So if you don't
You are
It's Europe
You're going to be arrested for not yelling fire
It's against the law
First Amendment to not yell fire
This is a this is a weird
Point to that part of it is very weird
So there was a
People who they reported a suspected
Carrboro
Right here at least Amanda crisis was averted everything worked out okay
Bent out of shape about this
8 for a guy
Like Lionel
To argue about the sanctity of words
And their definition
While at the same time tossing out as many $10 worth of
Possibly can
Places that
Do not need them there
The only reason you would use those words as if you need to be incredibly in very specific
Not if you wanted to show off your f****** vocabulary hero word
And shut the
How to really good
Yeah I think I might respond to this if I were just like
I like to do is I like to imagine that every single thing I hear from Lionel is somebody saying this to me at a dinner party
Look up I'm hanging out like a cocktail a cocktail
This guy's telling me that people are here
I think my response to this be
Relax
Calm down
No people over use the word hero too much
Okay
I don't think there's a sort of a position that I
Turn the corner
I might have agreed with him
My younger years theater and the movie Coach Carter came out
And the movie was all about
Complete this coach
Yahoo
Close the
Jim
The gym
Because the students are there on the team we're failing in unless they got their grades up they couldn't
Play sports some reason
I recently watched
Coach Carter
I think it's I think
I can't remember I think
I want to watch it on Netflix with my partner there
I don't I don't remember if it's a good movie
You're not you just saw it so you might be able to have more insight on it but
You know what it's very paternalistic
Yeah I got that idea of the hard-nosed kochuri
Teaches people a lesson about
None
White people version of the blind
Like it's your IRA
Say nothing about the movie
Cuz I don't remember it well enough
I have a critique
My position on it back then and I remember telling a lot of people that
Was that
He's supposed
To do that
These kids are failing these supposed to not let them play sports if they're feeling
Is he being considered a hero movie
I think
Now is 35 year old man looking back on that position I hadn't think it's a little assholes
Because the
Not so much
Doing what you're supposed to do
That is considered a heroic
Text thing it's
The results
That comes from it that your celebrate
So
The ACT
Even a trivial
Tritech dry heroic
In the in the right circumstances
And I believe that Lionel's missing that Forest 4-3 but there's a certain amount of
What do you have to over
Overcome in order to
To do what your
Expected
You know it would be
Legitimately heroic
If somebody actually
Control of our current
Situation in
F****** do some s*** about this
Until like they're f****** supposed
It would be because the the insurmountable
Simple odds are there
Just doing
Your job is
Sometimes eroic
And taking
Take It Outside of that
Contacts
I mean like if you think about what you have sorry for putting a knife
Even even talking about like what do you
Have to overcome Lionel makes that clear
The psychological bystander effect
Exactly it is almost built into your human brain
Is there wouldn't be a name for it if it wasn't something that was studied and is a shortcoming of human reason
Something happening you soon someone will take care of it
Overcoming that
To the point where like I got to do something
It is
Is abnormal you should celebrate
Call The Gyro call it's the get her done guy
Call It Whatever
You f****** want it doesn't matter
I work is pedantic nonsense
The movie Boondocks
You think he's a bun. I think he's a Boondock Saints I think that's what's going on there
Absolutely
I think he's been fighting Willem Dafoe for
For years now
I did not
Open upon Master blackface
In Boondocks
No but there is a lot of racism
Well it's interesting there's a load to defend blackface
The good answer
Here here's where it's at
I don't know if I would say that Lionel is defending blackjack
There's an earthquake
I will say that this next missive of his
To work
Donkey story about blackface it seemed an Australian Cosmetics makeup brand was
Is running an ad that appeared as though the woman depicted was in
Blackface
Blackface but I'm not sure what
Blackberries as in Jolson or Minstrel show or they know that Cakewalk
Looking for a woman
Dressed in black
Dark-complected of the caption read
Not dreaming
Applewhite
I need to know why I'm describing is right here
Take note
It was very simple rule that you must learn
Especially
If you're in the communications World blackface
He's never without a
No one will ever ask you
Are they won't ask you
Spaces the message the theme that means
Action whether it's instructional historic houses all good
We Care not
What your intent was
Correct messaging strategy
You're nailing it inspires a meeting objection and time and without fail
It's almost
Jumble pavlovian
Don't like
There's a butt
Even if it looks like
I honestly don't think that's
Totally true
Like I on it I really don't
Don't think that's true I think there may be a conversation
That comes up around
Artistic
Uses of black slaves or whatever
Late but I don't
Has
The negative
Social stigma that Lionel's drink
To paint it to be
When it's used
In context
It is kind of like okay whatever
Like robertdowneyjr didn't suffer any consequences for doing it
Tropic Tropic Thunder
Because it's because of the parity in the movie
The boy on how that is
Real loud
In ways that let's say this austere
Yeah
Bureau. Org
Say Ralph northam's
Rdr2
Being prime minister
I should also say that this is not the only video
Of his that's about blacks
Would not be sunrise
You tried to point out that like
Hey with a Wayans brothers made white
Chicks
Oh man
A boy that is a man deliberately
Try not to get to the
Good pretending the people.
Say like it's f***** up
Right
Eagles
I remember
There are scores of people
Who thrive on being offended
Do they pour over the news
The Scottsboro boys
Remember
In November of that year my wife and I saw the production at the lights
I thought was a protest
Guess what was important to know
About the center
Okay I'll save you the time
Sex
Who heard about the
The blackface party
Hadn't seen the music
They heard about
The black actress
To perform really
The production
Didn't seem to take offense
Probably because of two major point
First
Do I recall it was
1999 the Brooklyn Museum of Art
I met a Rudy Giuliani
To the painting The Holy Virgin Mary
They contained
Inter-alia impudent
Prince is an elephant dung as a theme
Now
Let me remind you first
It was Rudy
And the story got a lot of traction
Second
He was offended
Offended and care not about the symbolism of imagery
I need love the warm glow of being a
Ended we all do
Violated our senses and Sensibility under attack
As Roman blasphemy and you are ready for
We loved
To be offended offended therefore I am
I definitely that cannot be missed is that because I am unable to appreciate your message
Because I'm unwilling or incapable of appreciating are grasping your message
So bad
For you I'm offended
You lose and that's it
No importance Auto idea is not
Capable of not offended or insulted or angry someone
If an idea or messaging is so bad that I didn't say
Nana. It's not worth even having
Watch lese
The marketplace a free-speech involve the marketplace of controversy I
Thrive
America
It who
We are
Trouble
As you say
This is
Weird contradictory thing where it's
It seems to be the entire report
Is about people are too offended by blacks
Yes but then by the end he's talking about how great it is that people are offended cuz
People thrive on controversy
So it's actually a good thing
No I don't get
I don't get what's going on
He's shiting on people who are offended by blackface
That's stupid you're right your weight
Too sensitive you shouldn't be offended by this
Beyond the guy we all love controversy roll-up to be offended
Is Brittany
Not presented as that being a bad thing
Being like in to being offended
It seems to be like that it's all good
This I think
What's going on is
He's fine
Is old version
I'm taking if a
Informative
And full of bulls
But I think he feels it but he's again
People taking
Actual offense
When something offensive
What is going on
You're supposed
To just perform
But you can't ask
He doesn't like valid criticism valid
Anything he just enjoys
22 and a half minute
Pieces
He's like that guy who just likes
To argue right when you're like f****** I don't have
Not today
So people are mad
Sometimes
About black
Well. According to let's just call it right it is overblown
Alright look through it and see what's going on
People really don't like talking about how racist white people
But something else is not
Whiteface Lodge
I'm going to try and make it through this commentary without soiling myself I
Tend to lose certain bodily functions when
I'm subject matter invades my
My soul and I
Speaker
I have to actually put into words and explain and explicating limb the
Basis of my contempt I feel
A rage that may be hard for you to understand what am I talking about first I hate hate I hate the word hate
I'd rather be bathing in
They're a bunch of videos online
YouTube page
About how much hate crimes are b*******
Sort of hearkening to those he has to hate crime designations are stupid
Just like Heroes but look dude
He's mad about something
He's about to unload
I will make an exception for
No word or concept
Come close to even describing the vast and incomprehensible disgust
That pathological
Rage that is inspired by
These people this one group of people that I will tell you I
I hate
Why are they
Is so sick
Selfish egocentric Eagle maniacal self
Centered self-absorbed look-at-me rude
Boris Starbucks
Get to the f****** point
Grinch who take over tables for hours and hours without newspaper
Laptops
Starbucks
Squatters
Their vile
Pickable waste
Subhuman flydubai talk to you
Psychotic hominids William rumored to share DNA with people who claim
Now it's reported
That sucks
Starbucks Maybe cover AC outlet
Blank face plates to
Forced these sick people to leave once their laptop batteries wear down
Daisies degenerate some of these sites
A store next hours a day
By the way I would assume that the Starbucks
If they are putting plates on their it
It's more to like not allow that say people who are
Experiencing homelessness
Do charge their phone
Sumitomo
Add vendakkai writing a screenplay it's been there buying a croissant
Put it all there
I can't say it but I can fake it you know all there
On the table in Musica
A separate chair for the laptop case or file some of these animals
Apps for free water all day
I think that their coffee is somehow rent
Do you know who my blame
Starbucks
You sick
Why what were you thinking
Wide report that cool Seattle spirit is that it
Does he think that this is unique to Starbucks
I guess if you ever been to any other Cloud coffee shops
Have these people other coffee shops have the f******
Moral
Necessary to keep these loiterers
I'm just sitting there and work
This is the horking dance the whole thing with a coffee shop
What is he bi how long is he spending in the coffee shop to know how long their spiders
Are you
Nobody's walking over be like hey have you read my screenplay lately why is this a problem
It's a huge
Hate
Gratitude is over there the episode with the human race
Demented art
Mindless Vero
And before laptops
Thanking in Newsies recording their deep by the most.
There was a god
And if she answered my prayers
Once I pray I could walk into us
Starbucks
Survey the room
Not my fingers
Or what
Checkwriters
New Starbucks
Water buffalo world map
Hell I would have to walk over to one of those journalists underwriting her deep thoughts for the past 10 hours
Apple
Screen with a blood curly the light I am the god of hell
Bedtime
That Hemingway
Welyn
Yes. I just
Soil mites
Comment as you see fit
Lionel wants to murder people who loiter at Starbucks
John Keats I saw you in a
Cafe
I will kill renier Maria rilke
We're going out to
Parking
I understand that he's trying to be funny you don't like it's an attempt at a bit
Right but it's a bit is I want to murder all these people to loiter at Starbucks
You compare that to his other material which is
People are too offended about blackface
I don't know where priority at the right area
People sit somewhere too long
People are offended by referencing the absolute exploitation and murder
Entire race but
Let me tell you something
If they were sitting in a Starbucks then
Cody angry
Is that is weird
Wolf Salina wants to ban something what do you think it is
I am guessing Cosmopolitan white man isn't the it's 52
Before I can hit play on
Alright what does he want to ban
This is the point where Isabel person
You're f****** with me it's going to be backpack
I would never do that to you I apologize if I've lived in such a way as to make you think I set you up
To be a good time to set me up should you we all know he wants
Superman backpack
This is something you don't know
Okay well
He's going to want to ban 2-ply toilet
Nope
I won't dance
I don't ask maybe you'll see the story about the couple who was arrested for allegedly dancing going to New York
Subway platform
Well after they were pinched for impeding something-or-other
And now they're showing
I wish them well
Play absolute
Advocate the prohibition of all dancing
I mean criminal incarcerated
As Cicero said
No sane man will dance
Ballroom dancing square dancing polka
I don't care
I am without that part of the brain or nervous system. Crave
Silly movement
Ostensibly set
Perceive
You old f****** white dude
Musician
I misplaced the neurology
There was this throughout our history
Ordinance
The artist that limited public
Dancing all together
Why
Is dancing a natural
Counter-revolutionary
Bill joke
Why do some stretch
And you can fill in the blank with your particular favorite conservative face system but
Why do they never make love standing up
Because I look too much like dancing
I'm being very serious
For some atavistic primordial reason why we loathe Nancy because remember
No sane man will do
Why we doing a lot of work there buddy
Better again atavistic and vestigial
Why do we not our heads
To indicate affirmation
Because it mimics
Cycling our mothers
Why do we shake her head no
To mimic the action
Spitting out something bitter
Why do we dance
A reason to base
To attract mating partners
Define embark
Territory
Two events dominance in for the most part in human Kaiser to create the illusion of hot
Sexy and attractive
Tell your weight down the structure and control
Proceed right
Total breakdown of civilization
Has nothing to do with ceremonies called The Rhythm of Life
Homicide
No sane man will
Comet
At juice
I mean that's all good fun and all that I don't know like obviously he doesn't want the government to ban dancing
I mean like
I'll be home soon love you
Kevin Bacon
Can shows up and go
Give him the people's elbow like there's no other way that this function he doesn't reference Footloose at all this is weird
Based on his political set
Possibly want
Dancing bear
Possibly want that
The only way
Dancing fire in a crowded theater
Right when there is no fire fire dance
You're still not here
If the fire walk with me out of DaVita
Yes
Dd2
He has to be making
Obviously doesn't want dancing bad
And it's clearly not the point he's making
This is satire element of it doesn't make sense
I do but it's all good fun whatever
The problem though is that Cicero quote that
He bases his whole thing audio staying man will dance
Translation of the actual quote
Sleep sounds
Quote Cicero
The quote is taken from Pro Marine
Which is the context of Kato accusing a dude of being a dance
Which apparently back then was a serious accusation
It's like a man who doesn't wear a hat in the death at that point yet
So in response to this Cicero says quote
No-Man
One may almost
Today ever dances when sober
Unless perhaps he be a mad mad mad
Nor in solitude nor in moderate or sober party
Dancing is the last companion to prolong feasting of luxurious situation
And many refinement
The basic argument he was making
Against this accusation was that no one
Other than a Madman dance
Sober
And he was being he wasn't bi
Accused of being drunk
So the accusation of being a dancer must
Be an accusation of being
You mad
Paraphrasing the quote as no sane man will dance
Fine I guess
But then attributing that quote
Cicero is really unfair
It essentially is putting words
Cicero's mouth or more accurately taking context a wave
What you was actually saying
Cicero weather
Singly insane people dance
Drunk people dancing
No sober not yet
Insane person
These guys got
Home all the time by myself
Are you drunk
No well somebody you're crazy
Anyway
I have a singular obsession with how all these people like you end up becoming fascist bootlicking cheerleaders
Inability to understand
No idea
I'm really getting
To the point where I'm starting to wonder if that commonality is significant
Among them
Like if there's actually a legitimate
Piece of
What informs their ability to
To deal with the world right they can't understand quotes within their proper Khan
I wonder if you want a chickadee eggs
Situation like that
I'm not sure
I'm going to buy the thought that I'm having is
Weather in Ogden
Be predictive
Like you see somebody who is unable to wrestle with what a quote
Where it comes from
If that makes them more likely
Into being a right-wing
Maybe even though right when you could break you the director
Computer Museum
These right-wing
But that might also be partially because
How ascendant that is
In the conspiracy world right over the last
The left wing
Conspiracy world has not been nearly as fertile
Overground
Particularly is Blaziken
Make money
The SV the right-wing were obviously see the results
I wonder I wonder about that is interesting is there a hike nearby with your grade school I might make it my feet
Coli idea like just give somebody like what do you think this quote from Thomas Jefferson mean
And then in small print
Are you sure it's from Thomas Jefferson 2 hours as real as hell
It's perfect
To skew the results
Have the knee-jerk
That's true.
There'll never be
Figure out what these quotes
Is the formulation of it they like
He's thrown around in memes of like
Using that is
Not a fair description
It's better than just saying
Nope no sane man will dance
Same time though it's very much
Schleich
That's
Controlled
Media
Because they don't want to
Expand beyond that
If a source they trust gives them a quote about some b******* that reinforces their beliefs
That's just a true quote regarding that you don't
It reinforces what I already buy
So for a lot of people
Maybe one of the issues is that
Real quotes
Reinforce what the left
And fake quotes reinforce what the right
I think this one's a politically neutral
Yeah that's true for almost more in
Interesting to me obviously these are weaponized by
Propaganda Outlets are all the French militia windows and stuff
This one is really just
Right
I want to complain about dancing behavior is similar
I have an old white man prejudices so I'm looking for a quote that reinforces my old white man fragile
That parallel there
So I should tell you
I got to go through Lionel's
YouTube page
Scroll through hit5
Everything good maybe watch the hundred other videos that are not talk about cuz they're so goddamn boring
Right
Almost all of these have
Like 300
These are old videos
But no one has ever watched
Stop of them only have 10 like these are longshoreman
Spelunking for both
This next
First one
Out of nowhere
Has 100,000 vehicles
What did the
Okay alright what could Lionel penetrate
The Consciousness with this video right before it
200 use
This one
Okay this is going to be Colin Kaepernick
No this is before it's too early
Damn it really for that it's got to be something like that right it's got to be something that can
Captured the zeitgeist
In 2012
Early 2012
Yammit
There's nothing to do with politics
Nothing to do with Paula. Going to do with like the 2012 election okay
Get that out of your mind all right there's no way you'll ever guess
I was going to go with like an American Idol or singing TV show
The Rock
Who are we or anyone to say what is and isn't a legitimate religion
Why would I know is I mean this has to be islamophobia
That's an interesting way you think now you're wrong
Judgment
Are the theological authenticity of one's faith
Psychologist precisely what this Intrepid young man wanted to know
His name
Nico Alma Lionel's hero of the week
Mr. almond Austrian
Please inspect these photographs
Got it seems that the time discussion
Provision of the European Union in Austria's recognition of quote
Confessional headgear in official photographs
You don't really even have the perennial caseware up
Muslim woman wants to appear in the driver's book
I think she like me wearing a hijab or
Are there various types of
Muslim headgear in Vail American as a burger
You you responded with a gas but like mocking yeah I should be clear at this point in his career he does
Does not seem to have like
It's that in Pryor
Atmosphere to Austrian motor vehicle authorities that he was up
Pastafarian
Remember
The Church of the Flying Spaghetti Monster as depicted here
And this holy painting
Its website states that the only Dogma
Allowed in the churches the reject
Action of Dogma
They also listen part as articles of faith
But they believe that pirate
The original pasta Burien
We're peaceful explorers that it was due to Christian misinformation
Are they have an image of outcasts criminal today
Explain that pursuant to his face he had to wear a plastic
Pasta strainer
As religious headgear
Play sideways of course in the photos display needless to say the Austrian officials
We're not amused by the pastafarian mr. Rime
Troy Baker prove his Bona fides
And eligibility to Tool about
Nico had to undergo
A psychiatric evaluation do establishes mental Fitness to drive
Now stop
Wouldn't that be great
A psych eval to get a driver's
Think about it
This city will look I got ghost
I'm guessing that it wasn't a psych evaluation
To see if he could drive and was more like
This guy says he worships the Flying Spaghetti Monster let's make
Sure cuz that sounds
Outside of the context of what pasta
Safari in ism
Not knowing any context yeah that might be something is like
Remind me to check in on
If you were familiar with the internet you be like
Well this month three years later I'm happy to announce that mr. Nicolas
Pastafarian and member in good standing
Of the Church of the Flying Spaghetti Monster
Find me received his laminated
Official driver's license
Seen here
For this posture straightener calendar chapeau firmly and can
Vacuously affixed
Stupid about mr. arms Nagin
Play sideways of course
Austrian officials certainly not to be accused of being
Antipasti
Haha remarked that as long as his face could be made on fuelly
Be good pretty much Google
Official acknowledgement
Apostrophe arianism
Or the church
The Flying Spaghetti Monster
To which I'm currently announced
That's neck
Coming
As you see fit
So I don't know I don't know what
Is it good
He seems like you should
You shouldn't tease open way religious
Yeah at this point is career
It's weird because he becomes
The Giant Killer
Max Coronavirus
Yeah
It's strange
But I think that's about as middle-of-the-road of a report
As you can do
It's just about this guy isn't it cool
But he did to this thing at school but also a little silly and so that's just kind of like hey let's reflect on this being
Cool in Philly yeah there's there's a like
Quirky interest to a knot
That's as close to a
Find Lionel report there's no real
Sister anything that goes along with it there's no like
He's
He's pointing out kind of the
Certainty of religion as a whole and this whole thing is
He's kind of threatened
I would have
I would imagine the defiance
Spaghetti monster doesn't want YouTube and dancing
Yeah
And it's so weird to me that I mean
I get over you interesting if it turned out the John Lithgow was
That would be weird
I just think it's strange that this got so many more views than any of these old
I guess I guess probably the pastafarian online community sent it around maybe there wasn't
Coverage of this story
Baby was early coverage
Something like that
But he probably
Just got meme
I didn't realize that there was that robust of a pastafarian community or maybe this was picked up by the reaction
Right wing
Kind of people who are like
We got to talk about this
I doubt it I think it was I think
If I would assume
My assumption would be it was more just these people who were into those articles any world
Bring it out so 100,000 views
Zapped
Which is
Shockingly Moore
All like this
The ceiling thousand times the ceiling for a lot of these
Videos like being very generous is like 15
Yeah like these are not
No one watches these again
There are decades they've been online for 9 a.m.
Gears
Alright alright well he knows
I'm surprised he didn't lean into the zeitgeist
I said I would make both spoiled up off the phone
Safarian that's what almost makes me think that possibly these views all can
Came like later
Yeah they came like 2 years after he posted
A f****** news.
I like your voice.
Tell me you guys talk
Mine even precious
Alright
So alright
It's really hard for me to
To try and
Lead you down the road
We have a chance without giving up
Call Total
But like I'm even to this next
Lionel thinks a president did something
What do you think it is and who's the president
Okay
Okay God there's
Think Project Camelot
Big project, okay I'm going to go with Eisenhower met aliens
Spindle
Like
The 34th POTUS and supreme commander of the United forces
Dede
Consummate badass
Akule was noticed that the benefits fruit salad in
Campaign ribbons I like the cut of his jib
Understated
You didn't have to impress you
You were thinking of going off
Trayizon us
Wait out Dave we know
Interloper
General of the army
Understood man with a tremendous leg
But what sets wde apart is that he's Christ
Smack
It's secret meetings with aliens
Dig
According to author Timothy good
I can the FBI scheduled
Sit down by sending out
Telepathic messages
Various installations including Holloman Air Force Base in New Mexico
The fact
I can whistle
I just got UFO sightings on many occasions remember
During WWII
Allied Pilots reported
Kissing balls
Fire
Mysterious glowing
Spears
Fire
Driver tell you when I was attacked by red bugs on a camping trip
What are we doing now
Story
But be serious until that store
I know
There's something out there
Always has been
They've been here plenty of times UFOs
Whatever you want to call them
Harvey
Demos
It's your government
Idea
Ivar being the lone planets
Supporting life
The Beyond
The age of our planet is four-and-a-half
Billion years old that's
100 million years
If another planet was just
1 million years old it will be a million years more advanced
Buckle
Fossil
Play 107
I could do it but music dance
Dumb bastard
What fossil record show of modern man first appeared in just a couple of hundred thousand years ago
German soldiers and thousands of
Honda's real time
All over the world by reputable
Lucian
Professional Witness
And not inclusive
The French comida report
Terraria
You bring this up
Invariably someone will say
But why do they want to make contact with us
They have
And do
Why would anyone want to speak with us
Have you ever gotten Down Under
Round
Face-to-face with ants
Real quick
It's really weird because this isn't a bit this is clearly he thinks
For sure that
First of all aliens are coming down and talking to us about
It's not a joke
Hipolito
Seemed to believe he's no joke
It doesn't seem like there's a joke the end
The gear he's talkin about the like
Why haven't they contacted us yet who answers to that one
Is
They have
I meant his second one is why would they want to
Contradict
Yes if you like you talking to an
But then the first answer was they have and they are
It would be like me talking to an end
Which I do
Talk to them
Why not
Why is going to communicate with them
Maybe because
They're Bonitas
Baby beagle
We are quite there beneath us
Observed
And not disturb them
You got the picture and look at me
Kermit
That is juice
I like her
Is an alien supremacist
You dumb bastard
Alien more than human
I do
I do like the root of a
Metairie Lodge
Betty's appliances
Well if our Earth is 4.5 billion years old and we are here
Then that means that if there is a planet
Methods for
Point six billion years old
Then they have a 4.6 billion year old mathematical mathematics
Million year
To do with win life might have been the progress of
Any pressures that might have caught that would lead towards
Branching right now
You don't have a billion year Head Start just because of this thing is old
Lionel dump
Lionel is buried
Next clip I think Ikea
Double D Eisenhower
I swear to God when he wrote that down he was
I might be the smarter
And he probably thought like this is Ribble.
This next Copa America ask you what you think
It's about guys
I just need to tell you that I think the only reason I kept this clip
Or I took it at all is
Because Lionel uses the word Sneaky Snake
Papa papa
Fear of
Snakes
Y'all
Phobia is unique in that the fear component isn't Park
Why should I
As some snakes are venomous
Bulshit man there's so many fears that are rational
Irrational
Anybody who's anybody is afraid of heights is crazy
Fear of dancing
Well I want to wish I knew the name of it there's got to be a name for it
Not local area that's certainly true
Completely rash
If you're allowing visits
Snake fear is rational
Fear of cars isn't rash
Probably kill more people
Vile
Behavioral
Experts believe that the fear of
Snakes Express
Hyper
Exaggerated
A company Man's Walk
Upright
She is believed that
Since he was now farther away from the ground
Where is snake
Head
More prominent
Likely to stumble
Upon are more venomous
Serpentine brother-in-law
Hybrid
Facebook
Preferred
Through retro selection and evolution
Wouldn't that be the same with all sorts of
Predator things that you're afraid of
Armchair 40in folks love to see the
Hidden subliminal representation
Nowthis Bronx Zoo cover story that beats instantly get it
Criminally unimaginative
Culturally shunted world
The dreaded mainstream media
MSN
Alex will complain that they're all
Snake media dad Aguilar Zoo complain that they're all Mockingbirds CIA
For his DWI
Tell you that no
They all want to talk about a snake escaping from the flu
Intellectual junk-food quickly did Justin with a high glycemic
Asemic distraction
Maybe like My Strange Addiction
Not not here
Wake up the dude in the video library and have them dig
Super Bowl
Call Jerrell
Harrison Ford in Rise of wrestling
Play Alice Cooper
YouTube
Features of some
Weird guy saying
He's a snake
Ouroboros of b******* like you
He
Brains and criminally vapid weathercaster
Screaming nonsensical nothing
Andy's
Angie and proud
How to say you're off the hook on that one my friend
The punsters in Brenham easy axle like using every conceivable play on
Serpentine imagery
Cobra
Islamophobia
Meet sophitia phobia
It was an Egypt
Home of the Muslim Brotherhood
Donald Trump wayson
I demand to see the cobras birth certificate
Shred some Muslims
As alleged by the comb over quiet
Bombast
By the color of tag
Whose account
The Escapist
So that's
Andre
Medicine serpent
Messenger of death
Marching down Broadway while fighting New Yorkers run for their lives
It wasn't
Escape
They found it in the reptile house
Outside of her
Which would have been my first place to look
Charles Manson fails
Escape from the
Even Bindi Irwin the lakefront cutters
12 year old daughter said
He's probably right by the case
Meanwhile Olivia
Comments
Has UCF
So
Here's what's great about this
First of all
I'm in the trade issue of a snake escaped that even within the report you like it was
The big deal
I don't know why we're doing this
I don't I don't know at all but
He does referencing his snakes
Most important thing though is that
Lionel
Is on a New York
TV show
He hates Trump
Yep he hates truck back in like
2011 yes Trump is a dick that's cuz he hadn't unsealed the indictments yet Dan Trump
Thousands of Secret at night
Lionel very regularly will make
Jabs at Trump for the birth
Get stuff for him being a birthday
And one of the things that I wanted to actually do was
I wanted to trace lynels
Towards
Supporting Trump
Because I think
It follows a very similar path is the people we've seen like Alex and Nick Flint
But actually his path is a little bit
Different
He's super
Against Trump
As the campaign begin
Yes and then
He gets to a point where he's like
Alright you had your phone
Cut it out
You're good you either need to stop what you're doing
Or just get out
Yeah you if you tell them to drop out in September 20th
Like he's just not into this
Anyting
At all
Then once
Trump becomes like really
Likely to be the candidate on the GOP side
He adores
And the reason is just Auntie Hillary
When he endorses Trump it's a
Dual endorsement
Trump and
Because it is a specifically anti-hillary
Anybody but Hillary is not super interesting to me in terms of the the right wing
Have towards Trump thing
Like the Nick Fuentes and Alex Jones
Seem to follow like a very similar trajectory of
Like real negative horrible things
Things about Trump win
Trump shouldn't be in their orbit or they shouldn't
Care about him all that much
And then right around very similar times they end up supporting him
With Lionel he's a New York media guys obviously he's been aware of trump for a really long time
It doesn't like him thinking
Is a piece of s***
New York and then when he starts running for office I got right we're tired of this act
Whatever
Potential drop has
Of like destroying the GOP
These are rhinos
Yeah whatever
Listen to that in the same way that he's into what Bernie Sanders could do to the Democratic right
A certain amount of
Just disruption of
It's a sports both of them
The system doesn't work so he's going for either
Candidate that is not the
Yeah I get that also primarily I got to listen to a bunch
Primarily it is surrounding like
The cab Jack's hatred of Hillary
So it his path is not that
Although
It is interesting
To hear this
This next
Report that he has
Lionel talks about what sort of President he would vote
It's interesting to hear this
With the awareness that later he would end up supporting Trump
Don't ask me who am I would endorse her
Vote for in the 2012 presidential elections because
I need an indoor senior voting for either mittens or hoping
But
But if I had to crap the ideal hypothetical candidate
But I might even consider is maybe already my vote
Bubba's have one characteristic
They must
Be crazy
Abby Flame
Is it what I would insist upon in a presidential candidate with necessarily mean they never have a chance
The Wynn
The platform that I would insist upon her so out of sync
Were the candidates the left and why
Paradigm offer so antithetical to the status
Do polar and antipodal do most of the brain dead in
Brainwashed electorate that the only candidate
Who'd even come close to passing my Electro master
Be the candidate everyone would call
Crazy
Just say you like Ron Paul over this dumb dumb you know who you like
Hanson hello Canada
People who want to revolutionize and undo the
Expected
Status quo in the usual
Reconstitute
The business really invade country
Brain-dead Washington
My guy
And for anyone to even think they had a chance
That would by definition make them
Crazy
I will never vote for a candidate for the left or right side of the identical coin the greatest and grandest of deceptions ever
Old in this country
Next to the neck
Tattoo
Is a myth
Truant
Actual political action
Significantly
The delusion that
That will
She'll always
Skip this great and Grand Country
From Africa
From the death grip of the globalist international
Stripping
And only someone
Crazy
Scared to go out today
Democrats again have Barack Obama
On the Gob
Is Mitt Romney is
The debates are a waste
Or has someone said
You're like watching McDonald's debate Burger King
Fry's
I called them The Identical duality of left their wife
Someone
Crazy
Give me a candidate who would demand that the FED be released
The drug called would be repealed
Defensive nothing will be done without Annex
I'm. Hocus
Spoke is an illusory virtually Reserve currency the best ERA
You
Another words
I want a candidate
Who is crazy
I never have a chance of winning
Someone who would be best
Describe as that great life
Chili's crazy
But what if he's right
Stop it
As you see
You're courting a
Comedy show
Also what if
Please do not write
Yeah that's real fun
F***** up to hear years prior to family supporting Trump is becoming a qanon guy
But yeah you know what I want somebody's crazy
And what it really doing else only three people pass the law to create the Federal Reserve
As useful as what a crazy person's brother would say
What's really fascinating to me about this is
Dat dere that essay that Webster
Tarpley Road
About like Winthrop
Started to become
Ascendant
Within the GOP
That essay that you wrote about how
The failures of the Ron Paul libertarianism
I have the implied
Cruelty of that worldview that went unexamined
Was aopa
The vestibule vet is fascism
Like I don't have any respect for Webster Tarpley appearances on that The Obama Deception or on Alex's show
But that essay was
Incredibly precious
It really was about the the ways in which
Like just sort of
This
This fanatical support for Ron Paul
And the deterioration of it
Because Ron Paul had no f****** chance Adele
The whole time
And then once Ron Paul stop running
Rand Paul comes into the more dis
Pointing option
Absolutely not going to do it
It leaves his vacuum
Where people are
Prime
To to go in that direction
And what I hear
Lionel talking about what I want is a crazy person
Yeah
Obviously you talkin about
Ron Paul in 2012
He's talking about the
The disappointment that Ron Paul didn't make it through the primaries
That's the subject
Of
He's getting at
And
When you hear that
And you know how things went
It's really easy to see on a certain level and Moshe
Going to leave it like
That is
Did Lionel walked
Yeah yeah absolutely
Disappointing
It is it is very much
Schleich
Sorry it made manifest publicly a lot of times as like
Everything is Whitey Bulger anything but Hillary
It is it is hard to
It's hard to read that web
Tarpley essay
Not be like
Oh I get it at
Takes one to know one
You know that kind of thing
Like the only the only voice that was really
Putting that together on that in that world
At the time was
Unfortunately
A bunch of dumb dumbs
Like what you know your own
Community better than
Times you can have the more critical eye on it
I love you and I would like if there's a
It's not like Ron Paul's policy set was all bad
There are a lot of reasons why you might support him
Yeah they aren't involved in the like
Rank cruelty and awful things
Things like getting out of foreign
Entanglement
The positive thing that ate that is something
That you could have gravity
Tulsi gabbard talks about wanting to not be in Wars
And it makes sense to gravitate towards her for that
Consol drug legalization
Those are things
Things that you can really get on board with
The Dead
Flip side of the coin with people like Ron Paul's all the like
Stripping away protections for vulnerable communities in the United
It stayed up
Getting rid of all foreign aid essentially committing
I think II genocide of people throughout the world
Our efforts
Are humanitarian
No it is
Specifically remember around this time because
Cuz I was
I was trying to make you
Someone
I'm not saying this
Webster Tarpley
But it is
Possible that someone
Of his his order
Could be like into the good stuff
Recognize
As it goes along oh no this is metastasize right
The negative things are
The things that are the focus
It's now
Call it a b b y
What you were saying
No I remember this time.
Like
I had just been maybe a year or two in
The stand up at the time and
There were plenty of comedians I remember
Talking about how much they supported Ron Paul
And in retrospect you look back in your life
You had no idea about the
Yeah you only knew about that cuz I cuz I've known these people for 10 years now and it's like they would never say
Support destroying divided protect
For all regulations
But
Put so much of the b*******
Rompope
Through it and
That was that was very Apple
Appetizing
And and
Just like
Yes somebody's finally saying this obvious thing and it galvanized a lot of you like populist feeling of
Suspicions about what are these Financial
Yeah tutions
He's doing like yeah absolutely also another like
Reasonable thing
To have concerned
Like with Ron Paul it almost always
Gets funneled into
A hard right
Conspiratorial version of
Yeah it's
The inverse of the coalition
Supported Obama
Ryan 2008
Of that like
We're here
Because we don't
Trust
Any of these people we've been f***** over
10 years
You have run on
Champagne of
Take care of all of this s***
And then instead of funneling us into the hard right
Vicente
And that's just not going to last
Yeah that's what Ed that's where we f*****
Obama head
Man it's hard not to look at 2008-2010
NSYNC
Those were the two years where we could
Anteverted
All of this
Look at that
It really is
Wow save that for a book
I can't do it.
Someone can write that book
What's the Unabomber
So I think
I think that Lionel being like I'll only vote for a crazy person
Is a representation of
Like the kind of mentality that went wrong
Because what he's talking about is
This can
Candidate that fulfills
These requirements that I want that Ron Paul
What are you saying
Necessarily all like
Destructive horrible things
You don't like auditing the Fed
Obviously there are audits that are done
Just don't you pretend there are
But that was like a demanding that be done
Alright I'm not really mad about
Legalizing
Drugs
Absolute
YouTube The Kings
That would be deemed Crazy by people right
That's what he wants in a candidate right
Fine but where it gets murky is when a real crazy person
Comes around
Henrico everyone's calling him crazy
That must mean that he's insane
That's where the thinking
Absolutely
She's one last Lionel report
And I'll just
Set this up I'm not going to ask you not going to quit
No I wish
Cuz he and I might find common ground
Suspicion of being
Then we could all find
We also
My girl
It'll kill you
So this
Last one
Is a real misogynist open
It's real
Colostrum it's real bad
He takes potshots at Gloria Allred
Hard like
She does nothing
Wolf
It's mostly about this woman who was working at bank
The bank but she was fired
And then she
Claimed that she was fired because she was to attract
Shorts
Like a media interest story but what's behind
Play Capitan
Sexual harassment
Situation
Lionel minimizes that and I don't want to
Get to bog down into it
Because the way this
Is
Gorgeous
Thisara is
Lionel maybe getting his comeuppance a little B motor light
For really trying to be a misogynist ass-whole
A work is a pro wrestling turnbuckle
Putting something over on the audience to believe that slow
The biggest work is that Abyss genius
BB lorenzana
Vandervoort alternate spellings than Kadafi
Now here's a story
Deborah doing that because she says they fired her because she was so darn sexy
Can you believe this I swear to God
I hear the story line
Beverly Electric
I can't help it if I'm a seductress
Olaf has a siren distracting Mad Men
Lyric Me
Living testament to the beauteous
Chromosome
Her allegation was actually that her boss said that she was
Too attractive
Distract
Thinking that's why she
Not her saying I'm too hot to work somewhere
The onus on the wrong parts.
Coronavirus
Olympics
Do it rain
And women jealous
Colossal
But wait there's more
Enter legal gadfly Gloria Allred whose names will be Gloria alright for the times are causes people to say alright Glory
Alright
Alright Lionel
Gloria
C02 defense lawyers are Riding Freedom in the midst of auto asphyxiation
Nobody knows exactly what Gloria Allred does that mean she's a lawyer but
She represents people who don't leave represent
Okay
She was injured or what you beating or what
Nothing
Murdered his wife there's a dozen the only reasons to get a lawyer where you injured
Call Peterson murder his wife in this
Amber was a mistress
You should she needs representation.
Maybe you're going to be
Characterized the media you do need somebody
So Glorious that were visiting one of Tiger Woods's shemales that he allegedly
For what
Why she hurt injured what
Holdout
Again it's the same situation you're somebody who's being brought in
Into a story
That you don't have the ability to handle Gloria Allred
It is
They're to be a guide
To help you with the
And by the way that term to ask there
Like that is out of character a Lionel
He is generally super
Did this person was trans or anything like that this woman that I don't know what that is that is
Just an insult
Being applied
Inaccurately inappropriately
I thought that was
Lionel
Gloria
I want to see an ad for her Gloria Allred
Yeah no problem I'll represent you for what I don't know
Bye-bye bye-bye
What or what is rye or the family of Nicole Brown.
What am I
Basically ended discrimination suit
You think this Latter-Day mr. Drysdale wants them
Breaking back are you kidding me
I Love The Nightlife I love that bug
Baby I'm acting a chupacabra
Two hearts baby Sara Lee or whatever her name is
We're jumping the gun
Picture from this victim of corporate terrorism
Coronavirus
How we doing
So Gone
Are you guys going to play the clip
Are there she is
No sound
Far too risky really show
Well let me tell you what she would have said but I can't
If you like to find out what you said call me after the show
In any event
She stands up to
Seek redress in the courts
Absolutely
Plans of mice and men
I would have bet this one
This is the award show
That doesn't for the pics news at 6:30 that's what we call a big fat ACU back here tonight at 10
That's a bit misleading
That's a gut punch
Misogynist b*******
F*** this dumb b****
I was all like tried to get this bag job back she doesn't want it and then the B doesn't Victor
Clifton play and then
Actually just talk
He doesn't know what she's
Can't carry it on his own
NES right
She deserves welcome
How to invalidate your in
Entire premise
The entire misogynist bulshit that you're you're
Confidence
Yeah Vickery
Batman
Brutal
Going for it
This will be
Be insurmountable I will
Stand atop Mount Everest
And I will scream from the heavens it's okay
Women
Again this is the thing where we
Fart sound
It would help
Because it's been a number of situations or things have gone
Very poor
In a live comedy stage setting
And I see that and I see
Guy who cannot roll up
That is not
Nope inability
Why are you letting
I don't know 10 seconds of dead air happen
Ativan
Well she should go to court I want to go to court
Time India
Gloria Allred.
Within two seconds of their being dead are you should be
Figure out what's up
Yep your life TV baby oh yeah
This is the whole thing
This is my big
Lionel had a great
God privilege
He had a great opportunity afforded to him
And that was he
He had a
Column
On a TV show
You have 3 minutes where you could do
Antifa
Whatever he wants to do
You wanted cuz
He's like David Brooks
If there was any goddamn editor
You think Banning dancing B
Does not mix
It's like this.
Like David
Yes if David Brooks was
Trying to be funny and it was audio we would cover it more as a podcast
I'm going to anyways short
This
He has this opportunity in front of them and he
Just
Fails
Constantly
But yeah like there's
Points that he's trying to make their kimchi
Stairs
A murky line of like is this
Supposed to be a joke
Or are you
Sincerely making this argument
And then the most of it
Waste of time
Absolutely
Amazing
I kind of love it because
It's exactly the thing you would have
Expect for like the
The previous career of a qanon
It's the kind of
Trivial
Right
Marginally reactionary bulshit yet
If they let him do it for a while that's what's crazy
It is one of those examples of
First
A white dude
Fill up
Anja second like
When the steak
Pixar this low
When the stakes are
I don't like backpacks in the
It's like
What are we going twice.
What's up
What will you do
Give me 3 minutes
Eventually he'll go out to pasture and drink bleach will call it a day
We don't know if you drink bleach it's just part of the thing that's associated with q and not have not heard Lionel actually saved your place I know
I'm saying that as a necktie
The key for the entirety of cumin
Tottenham synect
How about a Master P you want some of that s*** up in here trying to flex literary terms all day
So we reach the ends and Lionel has
Knocked it out of the park
I was going to say worn out his welcome
I think a lot of people have I get this alot
From listen
Like they want more line
Yeah and they questioned why has there not been enough 3rd Lionel
Install back which now there is
And what are the
Reason to like I can't stretch
It's hard
To get
Decent
Content out of
Even though he has a ton of videos
Little 3-minute burst if you got to go through tons of them to find ENT like
Anything interesting
Here's what I
I think people
Want
The
Correct amount
And that needs to
Be careful EQ
Nobody wants
Too much final is a line that has a very
Drop
To it's much like nitric oxide analysis beat pills
Too much danger ye men
CPA
App
It's not it's not something that they're there is an
Unlimited it's an unlimited resource to use it sparingly absolutely
Stances are exactly
What times would you need a goddamn little burst of Lionel
So
We can wait until we come to the end and
I guess we learned a lot yeah I think
Alarm ground fault
Lionel wants
The murder people at Starbucks
She allowed the
A fuk about
Blackface what is it
Okay
So no nuance
And if you report
And something that ends up
Stopping a bombing
You will be in a Solera call yourself
The f*** out of
Alienstock
Of course well yeah but that's just
And your dick
But also hey good for you if you like office Blues really confused about that one
Still I'm not sure what is playing on
Naked
I was
Fair enough actually
I took
So
Out there hope you're doing alright
Consensus that you're in
Absolutely I'll do as best we can to help each other
Anza
Listen to the advice of
People who are in much
Better position
Provides advice for you
And just
Just so everybody knows we're very very grateful to you for
Yeah those of you donate
Play grateful we wouldn't be able to survive without that
I mean
Especially now
Like all of this stuff
Is
Entirely because
People
Care
And I-80
Feels amazing
It overwhelmed
It's not good bro I appreciate it is well and I was missing about this
By yourselves cogitating on it as a contractor as Alex Republic
You dance
Motherfuker I see you
I was thinking about this
Like
Maybe the other night
About how
I left my job working
Coffee distribution
Company
To do this show
At a time when no one's
Almost nobody was listening
No one supported the show it was really tough
I did a lot of
Very bad work
Work-from-home type working
Sold my blood
In order to keep up
With this and you were very
Sported as well
I we were able to make
Make it work
It was a huge
Gamble
What is stupid
Did I win
Advise anybody to do ever
Thermostats
But we did that and it ended up
Leading to where we are now
And
It's overwhelming
Think about like well if I still worked at the
That coffee just
Distribution place
There's a real diesel
Some chance I would
Be out of a job
And
It's real it's real to be in in
In that sort of
Position yeah it is
It is amazing
That week
To do what we do
And
I understand
How difficult it is
For everyone
Willits
Let's stick together map
Be able to is best
And pay back a little bit
Through whatever evidence
We can and on the
The most basic
Lionel asked trivia level ride episode
About Lionel for you all to enjoy
And I will be back we may be back on Friday we might be back on Monday it's not entirely sure as we are
But take care of yourselves and each other
Amanda
Work we love you so much thank you very much for visiting now it's white.
Rosemont Twitter
We are on Twitter it's at we love you so much thank you very much for following it and I'll just go fight and I go to bed Jordan
We're also on Facebook very much and thank you so much for
Downloading knowledge and Unilever review
Thank you very much
We're back but until then I'm Neo I'm Leo
Ndzi
It's Clark I'm the guy sitting at a table that Lionel wants
Starbucks
Alexandra Thurston color