Alexandra Thurston color
Workout
Alexander Jones
Here's the thing about this makes it
An interesting
Conversation
It is super interesting
I like I like our hubris out of the gate today coming from me
The whitepaper that interest
Vietnam here's one way of putting
8012 the white
Do not know nothing about it you live a better life
I do
We're going to get into today's episode which is going to be
Same and all over the place
We're going to be covering
May
Quelf
That's the last Friday
Episode
The Alex Jones
Your apology walk now longtime listener I believe
Might have been onboard
I believe it.
On the team policy
Today is that we are drinking
Liberty school wine I'm glad you brought that up which is
On purpose very intentional I bought that bottle of wine for today
Liberty loving Alex Jones
To Liberty scooters
There is actually speaking at Liberty University
It's a double at the double wide
At least we're drinking but I'm not a single entendre there like multiple
Station
I like that
Poetry I don't like poetry
Alex Jones is in a weird mood
Friday
He got into the studio and I think he's started defense
Couple minutes to get into super defensive mode
Here's how we chose to start out on Friday
Do you want to right now
Laid in bed last night
IPad
6 a.m. this morning in research for a couple hours and then I got back to work and went over the latest news
My head is just spinning
Cuz of the Johnnie Walker
I got to be honest it isn't credit
In the way that Matt sent
Also
Throughout the course of this episode we're going to find it Alex Jones didn't know Reese
You might have been up till 3 reading Breitbart article
He didn't know Reese
Search at all
It is a good Beast
Digital crisis meltdown government
I'm just like yeah I know it's amazing
Amazing how good Trump is
Election fraud
Illegals to vote in Mass
Pants coming out and said many Christians hundreds of thousands a year been killed nobody
You are still coming
U.s. finished goods
Merced we are in the bathroom time
Broadcast
I watch the 7/2 minute by Keith Urban
I want you to very very careful.
You didn't you didn't do that
Job Corps job stories
Ostensibly wants to get too in depth
Look
None of them
Christians are
We're going to get into this thing goes along making the argument
The Christians of the most
Persecuted group in the world
I am that
Penske Moutain said that hundreds of thousands are killed a year is that true
I don't care if that's that it or not
100-percent not true
And
The premise that no one would have said it a year ago isn't true
Because there's like WorldNetDaily article for the past
5 years old horribly on source of Obama eventually got
Christians being persecuted all across the world
Christian
I looked into it a little bit actually found a pretty interesting article because he goes on to
I can't remember if it's the
In this clip or a little bit later
I think I think it's
But
So you eat talks about how the UN
Admit
The Christians are the most persecuted group in the world
I found on um. Org really interesting article
The talks about the first
Persecution
Christians
And I think that's the only thing that could be going on
Making that claim
And here all read the headline to you
So much credit for imagining that
He has red
Okay well then
Persecuted religious group in the world
Holy See tells um
That's a very different thing the end of the headline changes it if you read the first three
Three-quarters of it it backs him up
But
This guy from the world says organisation that would benefit off of
Christians being the most
Security in the world
Yeah yeah
Archbishop Dominique
The secretary for relations
States of the Holy See
I spoke at the UN
He went on to say that
The particular influence of a specific religion in a nation
Belongings
Should be discriminated against
In social life or even worth it
I like where you going so far I assume that means an all-inclusive thing
Where every religion should be protected in the
Exact same way as
Yeah that is the making
But
I don't like the butt that you
He also threw down this comment on the financial crisis going on in the world
World Stevens
To this day
The Archbishop stress
The economy cannot only function by market self-regulation
And even less in accordance with
What agreement
Limited too
Interest of the most powerful
Quote it needs an ethical basis in order to
The function for Humanity you said
Calling any other non ethical basis
Ingenuous or cynical
And always fatal
So
Absolutely correct he's almost as correct as Lionel
The only article that he could possibly be about the UN
Christianity being super persecuted
If you actually read the article goes on to
Say that Christians are persecuted but should not persecute there's also
Very important things to say at the same time that article
You got persecution in my economics
Right right
So then he goes also make me think of that like every religion always pulls that like
Persecuted
I am less interested in
How many people are getting persecuted
Finding that persecution rate
Sure Christians are person
Security Board
You don't get to
Don't you know
If it's the other way then everybody
It's an equilibrium we want all
Retro 10 persecute
The same time
You know
F*** you
So the other thing that you got into there was that like Steel
Steel Productions on the rise
Hanabi
Is true
Amorites
Trump's beneficence
Nothing to do with rope it's just like a nature of their high demand for steel consistently we need it
Literally everything everything
Has been going on for the past
20 years at army
All of the goods
Then finished good
Basically I think trying to insinuate the
What Trump tweeted out the other day about how China's going to start letting us elfing
What's the time again
I'd started to become finalized last year
The presidents have done for a long line
Always been enough
Blame the previous
Administration and then
Ministration scapegoating and Glory Hunter
Constant headaches
Absolutely nothing
But riding
Executive orders that will make
Everyone's life worse
And get halted in court
Ever ever
Blind
Why don't allowed to live wherever the f*** she wants
Millions and millions of dollars
Security detail
Why does she have no one gives a f*** about everyone knows this let's move on.
Get rid of her security
Think about this
If she gets kidnapped
Or threatened
Trump
Like nobody would care
I know I wouldn't care this is a good bit
But in truth I don't think that's a good idea
Well actually
50/50 disagree with you
Yeah
Get hurt someone could Target her and that's not fair
Every first lady gets
Security details
It would be wrong tonight
That's not like you
Alright
Security details and none of them
Most of them aren't monster
She might be great anyway.
Atlanta
What he really wants
Talk about
Keith
Bucking Oberman
Put out a video where you sort of says
All of the
Intelligence agencies around the world they were in a crisis
The time has come
There we need everything to come out in the open
Because
Eventually
You won't be able to
Write this
This is going to be
I'm not here to
Keith Olbermann
But at the same time you really opened yourself up to attack when you say
Hey foreign
Agencies
Spill the beans on our president
A goddamn president
You open yourself up to that exact argument and that's why I would never defend that
Well that's that's
The interesting thing
I do think about this
What if
You tweeted directly to the president
High hopes
Some Second Amendment people
Take care of you
Right you can imply that was a very direct
Sure but
If you go to court for
Can't you just be like
He said it
I'm quoting him exactly
So if you want to prosecute
He's on the pot
That's Mark Dice claymation right now
I'm telling you this is going to be alright
Here we go
I know body language
Twice
Last night this morning
Government is completely mentally ill
Is mentally ill
The dog off the leash
Widow Berman
He is completely out of control
Calling for to overthrow Trump
This is textbook
Sedition espionage
What is the president
I got some eclipse of professors today
Yesterday
Kill white people
And this is the climate changer
Not Libertarians not Christians
Not conservative
He doesn't have the eclipse
He doesn't get to those stories about that probably just grab some of the clips that I
Or he's at least
Okay with
Clips they could find would be on that border
I'm talking about
Buena Vista perience of
African American
This country
The idea that
Some light that has minimal
Compared to what
He's he's making this argument
That
F******
Obermann is committing treason and espionage
Dick most spies go on
G2
But after a minute long videos that seems like bad spy work
Navigation
Would let him on GQ
Snub gentleman
He should be drawn and quartered
Trying to figure out how to make that pain work
Conservatives and Libertarians aren't the ones
You should be afraid of
To differ
Journalist
Project Veritas
Truck wash
Hill doesn't real mad cuz
Trump is not going to uncover any voter fraud
There really is a
Insubstantial anyway
That James O'Keefe
Project Veritas
To come out and said
I was just I just wrote
Journalist yet
Which is like
The guy who
Doing like what seven years
No he's not in prison
Oh one of those guys is
Out it is
Out-and-out fraud
He is
Journalistic
Debauchery
We live in a world where I keep my
Be invited into that
It was incredibly scary
Voting rights
But absolutely is
Always about making sure the people who don't vote
For you
Put on
The on the ball
Department
The Census Bureau
The national Center
Like what you say is you resign
Quotes sign in
Protest I don't know enough of the details to say so I would want to speculate
The guy who's in charge of implementing
We're looking into these voter fraud issues
Has been sued over
Voter rights issues
4 * 4
Yep we're going to get some real good
Stuff out of this
I think we're going to get to the bottom of what's wrong with her voting sis
System we're going to fix it all absolutely
Remember
Yeah
Saturday schools windows
I don't look
Sour Jones introduced some of his narratives here
Mostly
But he's super mad to Keith Olbermann
That is important to remember for later
It's not just like
He has been
Stories he wants to talk about notes over prepared for the show
When he's over prepared
Suburb
I went into shops
A Starbucks
The pool supply place
Seven people to Starbucks three young Muslim girls with hoods over their heads
That's cool.
That are not tolerant that are the most oppressive
Call wife
People on earth
You bet I'm freaked out
Call wifey
Three daughters
$3
And I was like well
You're freaked out
Muslim women drinking coffee at a Starbucks
I don't know order pool supplies
Can't buy one of those noodles
I do like this could be a new stereotype of these Muslims
Muslims
You can't walk outside with them swimming
All that phone aside like
When you talk about islamophobia
Fear of Muslim
He's literally expressing that there's no other way around doing anything
Tolerance
Fairy tale
You like
You just said you wanted to
He is incredibly intolerant
Saudi Arabia
Definitely argue that his argument about
This is an incompatible group of people
Cool punch supply shop
Compatible three Muslim women are sitting around in a Starbucks drinking coffee
What will you do
Be more compatible unless they're open their own pinata
Exactly next door cat shelter under attack by the trendy's
I like the idea that the Detroit school is holding a Muslim girls only
Problem where you like wait
Sorry girls
Look into that plywood
I'm certain it's not true this is one of these things were sometimes Alex's lies you just like
There's too much going on in this episode of Too Many important things I had to research
Got left by the wayside cuz it's b*******
Research that did not
Dummy daughter Zagat
$8
No daughters
In this next clip Alex Jones
We're going to get through like
Probably six more Clips or so and then the episode Texas
Turn
That I
I'm going to give you a spoiler alert on
I think Alex Jones is mad that he is not the Press
Secretary
I can't okay
Look
Democracy that's background
He blasted
There's no way he would punch somebody in the Preston
Trendys in Folsom Collectibles and stuff like that
Alone on your show
You're only talking to people who have the same
Dumbass globalist mentality that you do or Eddie Bravo is your guest
But when you have to sit down
And have the scrutiny of the ink
Meticulous
Intelligent press
He would be
F*** they would tear him apart
Let's not give them
And also
What the Press pool is
Considering there
Being soundly defeated by the likes of
Huckabee
Sorrento's
What were the other one key
Keep spices it's an amazing
Next clip
See if there's an interesting things it starting
To come into the mainstream
I understand they talked about it before starting to understand
The idea of
Russian active measures
There are propaganda tools the Russians
These narratives
That are pushed out on
Sputnik
Nrt in particular both those Networks
Are state-run state-owned
All of the
Yes and they push out narratives
The idea that there are certain
Outlets
In the United States
Mirrors
What people are most
We concerned about
When people talk about fake news
Is that that's what they're talking
Someone who has been on
Infowars in the recent past
Former CIA agent
Discredited CIA
Let ever been on
Possibly
He is
Incredibly guilty
Appearing on
I meant taking talking
Point
That are
Jermaine
It originated on those Networks
And us
He have done so on Alex
The show gchq
British
Intelligence agency
Was spying on Trump
On behalf
Of Obama
Rat is a Russian
Did measure Naruto
Really
To spread these lies or buy by the Russian
Propaganda machine
You just like on board
He's being paid in his much but he's always been not beholden to
The truth but he's being in as much as
He is paid to appear on this network
Andy's band
From America
Right he is being paid
But why would you bring
Unless you were
Well if you
Consistently going on these shows then I assume part of his
None
Verbal contract
Is
Spread it everywhere
I'm not sure I have no evidence
Agent or anything like that
Documentation
Pastor
Let's go you might just believe dumb s***
That's
By this Russian propaganda
And brings it over to Alex
The reason I wanted to lay this out and
Explain it is in this neck
Alex
Is just straight-up repeating Russian profit
Really he's just laying out Russian propaganda
Really hard to accept
Well it's something that you realize he has been doing a lot of
He has no I know I know
The idea that you are.
You are so
Desperate
Nea
Information
Supports
You're both
That you will accept
Propaganda
Boggles my mind
Well I mean if you believe that Russia is one of the only countries that's not still in the grips of the globalist
It kind of makes sense
What does
Whatever their propaganda is as maybe the real truth as opposed to the fake news media here
I can see that was well if you if you believe that all Us Media is
Fake news propagate
Panda
Take me to propagate
Going right now
Admits that the Russian probe
What part of
He's been spot-on and staying present
If crazy Don Ford's come out he was being spied on
Hypnotic
With the Russians
Sports them
That's not true
It is hard to lose in the icebox
So the parts that are really important
That
I'm almost all of those points are just
Like regurgitated Russian
Yeah
Is Japan a word of the day
The idea that Russian probe
Stuff is just yet just because the Democrats lost in the
Sour grapes
The the idea
Trump was wiretapped
He was the idea that Susan Rice is responsible for leaks
Talking was the idea that call me
President was crazy he didn't
Say that
He was crazy
Well maybe even Beyond necessarily
Like a rushing record
Asian buffet
Comey was disgusted
Or nauseated
Could you help Trump
Is it horrible misrepresentation of his comments
What he was talking about was that he felt nauseous
He had had in a
Effect on the election because he is an a political figure
Supposed to be
What the office is apolitical and his axe
Cause
Nauseated
Not that you had help
Bulshit
Alex is being
But the rest of that stuff is just as effective measures
That's going
Going through the
Conservative propaganda me
Machine right now
Is the idea that
To fire him
Because
He should be subservient
Which is like
Saying it
Find for me to not be
Any laws what's
Course
That is the number one issue right now with a
The firing of
James Comey is that
If
That is like he's
And he said it like even Alex Jones like
He was being honest
About committing a crime investigation
Yeah exactly
If I was I would want to go
Should be independent FBI should be independent
It's like all of these
Things are again
Checks and balances that no longer exist like as long as there is a GOP
Controlled Congress
Absolutely willing to UPS
Every single
Possible Avenue
There is no check
Our system is
Broke
Create
The Safeguard of Freedom Alex
Liberty Liberty school but
Beyond that and we're going to get back to this cuz one of the big things that he started talking about there and it comes back up over and
And the path
That's just reducto
Good thinking it's both can be true at the
Of course they wanted him fired
In the past
Actually they didn't want
Every single example that he brings up
Is Democrat
Or Bernie Sanders
Becky probably should resign
They aren't
Not even if you even pretty f***** up
It would still be f***** up
Hillary fire
Because if they fired him
Then it looks like a complete like exactly
It's like retaliatory and that's not what you
You want from your president
Assistant
Flout
Spindles
Very very bizarre metaphor
Assure the point of
I think it's on
Bizarre metaphor
Either
Flip flop
Giving different stories
Bag of cash in Free bottles of whiskey
Liquor store
Not doing very good job
Idiotic
Why don't you investigate
Why don't you look at how they're involved with the Russian uranium deal
He just won't get off at
He's not looked into it's all he's got
Literally the Russians
Are laughing at us
On national TV
Is he fired
Locking us out wrong with the wife
It was if I was in his shoes
It's f****** hilarious
A constitutional crisis
Yeah that makes it even more scary is that clip
They don't care if we know they did
Do you think that because
If it does come out
That they tampered in our election
This severely
We have to f******
Kill all of them
That's an act of War
Which
Which is why I assume
The investigation
Ocean is take
Taking so long
Yeah because
Cosby evidence
Found
Because they need
Provide the evidence
In such a way
That we can acknowledge this
Corrected
And still maintain the Cold War instead of the
To be the only reason at all of this stuff
Is delayed because if you would there's no there's no other explanation because of any of it touches Trump
It's War
If you can if the
But you're probably right that's why it's taking so long it's because
Just was like manafort just Rodger Stone
Those investigations would not be that difficult to
You get to be like all right
This is f***** up your now a Sitting Duck president
Mustard is foreign agent Sandy more than enough
To be like
You probably committed a crime
Investigate it
It took us two seconds to find a crime because you needed it at that
Yeah PayPal
Like that's how they like you
Super specific simile of the guy being like
Liquor store you got whiskey
Something
Turnover liquor store
What did well I mean I just posted this the other day to the
The knowledge fight.com growing biography of Alex
Actually got kicked out of school for a year
Really
The ranch
Because he was fighting too much
So go check that out
The year on the ranch
Swan
Because
Tell me is Jeffrey directors Oliver
They're disgusting
Empower
Years of Democrats
And push with the goblins as well
Sure why not
That's what we call at the recall equivocation
Pets
Let's just call it
But you thought
What part of Russia now what
Cares yet
Exactly exactly it's that's
Superfudge
And then beyond
He's legitimately
Expressing
A desire
Unilaterally
Clean house
Which would be a culling of people who disagree with you
Which is a COO
No that's when you have a government clear separation
What you want
Is a single ideology in control of every single one of those acting in lockstep
You want you want Jordan disagreement how you get things done
Do you remember why this country was started to make more King exactly
First draft of the Constitution was
Realized recently
The actual idea of globalist being in charge of everything that Alex
Cells in order to
Do pictures b*******
That is literally a false flag
You know where the term comes from
No
Is a nautical term
Where you put up your enemies flag
On your ship
So people would think your enemy was approaching
Yourself
MC2.
Enemy was there
Sympathy
Or create
Did condition
That you're looking
The idea that he will think about it
The idea that he says
That a New York Federal Reserve Board member is suing him
When that guy is
Not a member of the New York Federal Reserve
Right that is a false flag
You putting that flag on hamdullah Kaya's
And that's not true
That is a really good point he's doing that to create sympathy in the people who already or like I ain't
Reserved
Yes using false flag sort of
Ideology
Operator is a false flag it's literally putting a
Even saying that all Democrats are
Russian agents as well or whatever
Just go into doing exactly
The opposite of what
He says
In this episode over islamophobia
Sarah Huckabee Sanders
Wow
What the
Home
We'll cuz he's an idiot
You like he thinks he's complimenting her by saying at the end she's really sharp
Compliment but you literally
Started
The first thing you said about her
Wow
That's f***
That is the patriarchy in a nutshell like that
Yourself she's at she's a woman
Did you know that and it's it's mindless and flipping
Throne chairs
And if you told him you would get mad at you and think that you're a p**** snowflake
In his mind
He was giving her
The Hyatt
If she was
And you're not even
Gorillaz
Is metaphor
He played a video of her on the show again
Listening
Yeah yeah
That officer
She related to Mike Huckabee
Hoboy
I don't know
She's actually the love child of Mike Huckabee in Bernie Sanders
I should have said Colonel Sanders I'll never forgive myself
Much better
Stroke conference
Situation
This is where we begin
The Alex wants to be in the Press Corps narrative or they
Via the Press
Secretary
Here is the beginning of his analysis
The press conference
Let's go ahead now
Sarah
Was fired this is from yesterday here it is
I asked you directly yesterday if the president already decided to fire James Comey when he met
With the attorney general attorney general
President of the United States said directly to the president
Remove the FBI director that directly it was all him
MP3 Channel
Call the consensus
Consensus
A consensus that the mainstream media are liars how consensus that their elitist
A consensus that your hat
A consensus that you're a cat
A consensus that you're a brat
A consensus the time or breath
It's a consensus that it's green
It's a consensus that it is
I was wondering how long I could keep going I was trying to find someone
You always got to go children's book
I know that's
For fun
The idea of him playing this clip
Is really too
The name of the article that
About
Sarah Huckabee Sanders
Kobe's daughter
Better
I play in the base
But be that if you don't know that that's not
Izzy's to demonstrate the cheese grater
Yeah but that's supposed to be a Ford we can even get to her response he's got to cut it off and he's got to respond
Reprimanded
Cuz she's not attractive
Is he at all understanding what this journalist question
The guy has asked
Alex
He's asking her
Why is there a discrepancy between what was said
Before
Presidents presidents that have multiple in
Census of people within the White House
Saying that it was all because
Right Deputy attorney-general is why is that the case
Right there under stand
Like this
Absolutely.
Well
Wellwood he's trying to what he's trying to do is get out
What Alex
They say that
Because they both
What
Wanted to do
It doesn't matter when Trump said or the light
Question though is
Why is it that everyone
Pointed
All the blame towards this guy
Said it was
The color that goes to
Existence
Kind of the question if you really wanted to still it down to like normal languages
What's going on
It's not
Why are you so bad at
Bread
How to do what state was his fault
Or why couldn't keep his goddamn mouth shut like why isn't someone advising him to just
Actually probably it's because the deputy Attorney General
Christine said he was going
Recommend
The idea
I think we all understand what's really going on
Sessions recused
F*** we going to do
Susan already
Is
Heavy scare quotes
He also I've been reading up on it
Turn the hopper by writing that letter
Really a memo about
The person who was
Conducting the Russia investigation means which is from
God
What are you putting yourself in jeopardy
What age
Rheem
Actually being
Attorney general is not allowed to
To practice law
Before The Supreme Court
Call
She's not answering her calls
So it goes on and will eventually have Trump
Only offer
Represent
Great writing a certified letter that you have nothing to do with Russia great
Doesn't get more boneface than this
It is all
Or
Or its next level trailer
Electricity red light
All right we have nothing to do with Russia
It would really drive people crazy if we use one of them offer
I don't think that would be hilarious
How are they sold
F******
Obviously
And we still because we know
Lewis congressman
A joke
Most of the elect
The go on in the
In there
Just putting their balls in our face
But anyway
Beavis clip goes on
The press conference
I don't think that Huckabee Sanders comes in
Ibis next quepe
Cuz you'll be wrong
Two atoms
Try to twist
Something you try to misrepresent
Warrior games
Opposite of a lawyer
So it like
What are you trying to do there is trying to say is just trying to
Trap
What's going on
What's going on here
We would like to be able to report this accurately but there is an inconsistency
We're trying to get to the bottom of it
Edina lawyer game
Lawyer games
Parcheesi
Seems like a high-class game right
Catan or abridged
Resource manager
That
Is
Very much a prisoner's dilemma
Like if I was gay
Investigating them like a
Straight up cop
Rights you have
Three different
Possible purpose
Different interrogation
But that's kind of the issue is there
Competing motivations
Like Paul Ryan
Just one
What is f******
Like he's willing to end America just so we can get rich
He wants to end Medicare
Okay that's that's his main goal
Right Trump
Just wants Trump to be richer and morphine
Just want to try
To be the Trump knighted states of America
Do you have
All of the other players
All of them just like
Trying to maintain some
Semblance
The massive wealth
You know if
The stuff that was in that. CA
That came out the dirty.
If some of the stuff that was in there is true
People like Paul manafort
People like Carter page
Rodger Stone
Stood to gain
Billions of dollars
From that tempers
Yeah it's like really in dollar deal
Holyshit may have like 20% of it or something like that
Yeah it wasn't
18% stake in the trillions of dollars
The embargoes on oil in Russia
Expensive
Oilfield but they're not using because
Sao opening that up with Santa make
People like red
Rex Tillerson
I am
Conspirators
Tons of money
So there
That makes sense of the motivation
Very simple you have all three of these different
Party
Giving completely
Stories
NordicTrack
Power-hungry
Hungry lust for money
Best game
He's trying them to
Turn on each other
And that's the prisoner's dilemma
There is the only way they all win
Is there a state
All temp
True none of them can do that and we're seeing an inability to tell the same story
Leeds
Meltdown in like not even
Similar story
Like legit
Yeah
Do not be still going on television
Trump's birthday
So this next week we finally get to Huckabee Sanders coming in
And giving her
Response to this question
Let's go back to her response
Fire James Comey we're so many people giving answers to just more correct
To report
Let you finish and read off every single one of those statements
Simple I hadn't had a chance to have the conversation directly with the president
I went off of the information that I had
I answered your question I sent had the conversation with him right before I walked on today
At this point
Good
It is not
We were misled I personally
Was ignorant
Because I just
Spicer
The death she's doing a great job as the press secretary
Is already
She's not
She's not said anything embarrassing like spider
I agree
Angry and run away like
He turned it into a quest
About her
Right question
That he asked
Perfect
Because
There's that minor little bit of taking responsibility for something that isn't really that bad
It deflects from the fact that the quest
That's a really good
But I respect the hell out of here answer at
And he waited up very clearly
I've been thinking about it for months which I did say yesterday and have said many times since
And then later he just had so much weird things like
Weird
And that he also
About
And then you think we're so stupid I don't have a memory
There's no collusion
Foreign minister and the ambassador to the United States from Russia
No one's saying the trumpet
Helping them
They they were just saying this is a dangerous situation
In the Oval Office
From a hostile State game
Even in his defense
She was like yeah
He set up meetings that legally wasn't allowed to do
No hit his argument
Kind of
Dicey
But his argument is that Mike Flynn whenever he was talkin to like kislyak
I was just saying
Cement 4S
Calling multiple times
We're still on for 5
Friday
Obama put sanctions
Poynette to call a couple times be like
Don't worry about it
I'm definitely not revealing foreign policy
I have not yet registered don't worry don't worry
We are so secretive
He might as well have had a
Next to his
Talk
I've soaked rain
But all of that all that s*** is
First of all
He interrupts her
Roots
I'm being petty
But I couldn't let the clip play out next week give her answer because he had to jump in with his aunt
I wish
I mean it's just
Of course he wants to be in the
What's being there so bad yelling at these journalist
It's Tricky
Hungry for the game
He wants to yell at them himself no one would ever let him there
I just didn't pick up on it right there but yeah
He wants to be there
Because he would answer them so much more harshly
Unattractive
Woman ever, I would defend
So much better than you
Pathetic
Building is old
Exactly the narrative
He wants to
Right
Around who know facts
Because you couldn't
You couldn't yell at people about how
The Washington Post
New York time
They reported
The Trump was wiretapped
They reported that Trump
Trump with wire tie
Tower Associates
Of his might have been wired
Right
Another body of the article felt it out
Yeah so
Everyone would just be like
Referencing headlines
Yeah
Physic
You don't read anything
You don't know
Eminence why you couldn't have
A job now
Because our dreams
Sobe still great
So is it next clip we get even further inside that Alex wants to
Like this just so clear
Yesterday and have said many times since Wednesday was the final straw
You were
Interview
He laid out the truth
The president
Little man
Contradicting statements
And people that were maybe in the dark about the Democrats was free too few of them
Nothing for the American people it's coming
Just goes on for a while that's that's what I'm talking about when I said it or answer doesn't stay good because
Like you said she's not answering
She's doing a really good job of removing the target
Basically
She's crushing
Look over here look up
Prepared
She came with all of those f****** Democrat quotes
Like she's on it
Yeah for sure showed up with
Like
Manila folders and just filled with
Black paper
Competency
I would love to be able to be there myself as a journalist
To be like give a rebuttal like
Not a hold on
Those
Are old
By and large
Their months old
In this context but
At the same time
She's being a press secretary
Because you asked questions like hey
Is this true and they're like well this is true
Hillary
You answer that
Hillary conversation
That hurt my throat
So Alex comes back after she gets done with her
And here is his summation
Wow she's good better than Spicer
Yep
Agreed
The brown daughter
The fox
Wow that's insane
What
Yeah what
God damn he's a pile of s***
With comments about how she's not hot enough
Put this very smart girls braids
Insomnia
Imagine
If you took Alex's
And put it into the brain case of a f****** dog a brace
The bridge
It wasn't a great movie I wish they'd chosen an Asian woman but what are you going to do gets done with this this break
I am
We now enter what will be the
This episode
She comes back from break
Start breaking down
This Keith Olbermann
I'm glad we got off of his
Rampit
Misogyny
No left dumb
Park
He skips break
And does 35 minutes straight
On a seven-minute clip
From Keith Olbermann
Wow he's our level of
But she's watching a little bit of information
Contacts
Any insight
Right just mad
He's just screaming
Trip out all of it
Hates keto bourbon
With
Well I would say that is
Is that is like like
Overman is definitely that
That's similar style of alpha male yelling
Trendy's light
It's kind of like Alex Jones
Is some sort of
Outkast
Epimedium High School
Keith Olbermann is the cool quarterback
Is exactly what it is
But at the same time
The f****** lineman he doesn't get it
Calculator
You can't move like a quarterback
Also like it's not even really fair that assessment
Might because like Jake Tapper is maybe the quarterback
There's something like that
If you want to go mainstream media but if you want to go mainstream
I don't I don't watch it
Is a highly rated show on the number one
Cable news
Anspach
No wonder I think he accurate
Alex Jones is an outcast
And there's a cooler Outkast
Still on The Fringe
That is not a good day at work
They put a lot of in-depth interview
Recently
Teen Vogue has been doing
Absolutely
We're entering the
Totally
But
You can't take aim at Keith Olbermann is being like a news Golden Boy when he's on Gentlemen's Quarterly
The fashion magazine photoshoot
So it's all good
Displacing
Mostly Isaac
We're going to explore throughout this
Maybe too thorough investigation of Alex's investigation
I like how we're going to do
Alex
Self
Okay he's yelling
Nokia
Alex is mad
Keith
Embodying
Things
Becky Fields Easley
Or things that you self-conscious
But he does
Like I said up top
No cuz he does have a fun fact
I'm not defending Keith Olbermann I think he has his issue
I think he's a way better journalist
And a better prison
Phenolic
In terms of being a professional
Haha
This guy is also off the chain
Lunacy
I'm not children
I'm not a boy
I'm not defending Keith Olbermann I am only in so much
As I side with him over Alex
Traduction here
All capital letters
This is just all projector
Ladies and gentlemen I don't know where to begin remember a few months ago and
Remember he said that
Video last night
Look at his eyes
He looks like he's completely mentally ill
Completely scared
Year old young boy who's afraid that
Killing
Sounds like someone we know
Shraddha Kapoor
Delivering
He's crazy
He's bad the whole world in danger
I don't know where I've heard things like that before
Could you think of anybody
Who is said something
Things similar to that
That prompted the Clown
Good point
One of his
Was the person who
Who's trying to kill exactly
Also
I like
He is mentally ill
You see it in his eyes he looks
Scared he looks like a five-year-old boy
Kicked off of
His mother's lap and told you don't love no more
Liquor store with
Two bottles of liquor store
His
Propensity for
Picking
Like
Parents
Totally
It's always got to be like
Look at him
Don't listen
Look at Trump look at house
Slick look at how his hair is always
Don't engage with his thoughts
Or his
Opinions or his research
No course
It's too it's too hard for him
I would say
Within
This 35-minute clip
Alex Jones hit the most of his greatest hits of Lies
Hahaha and also comes in with some new ones that I'm going to debunk along the way
And then also American Pie also right
I don't know how to put a finer point on this
Keystone
Please just mad at himself one of the arguments that he makes
Is so absurd
Italy
It undercuts
Alex Jones's entire philosophy
F****** Keith Olbermann
She's attacking himself yet when you punch your mirror your hands is fine
Go to the next web
So we can move this along cuz I
23 clip
This next one is about Trump
Many varied
Over delivered
Dominique koplo
You're tired of accomplishing things
Zika women
This is mental illness
That's more than that
It's called
Power
Criminal
Operations against your country it's called
As though you were
Sedition
Was really the sparring power
And he was screwing us over like
WorldStarHipHop
So in there he makes these
Desert of argue
Commence about Trump's Aqaba
None
Globalist are real
I'm sorry if aren't real accomplishment against them
That isn't real is real
It's like when he says that Trump is Rita Claire its offerings
What does that mean
Renewing your wedding vows
3 times before that any raped one of your former wife
Write a book about it anyway
Is really interesting because
The funding that actually is going to
Because it is a toy
Humanitarian
Organization
Like food
Organization and things like that
If you really look into
Specific cuts that are going to have to be made to make his budget
People who are involved
With those organizations
This will be
The barge
Humanitarian crisis that we've ever
Blueface
I believe
We're going to f*** porpoise
People
Ahca
The quote from
Have a name
It's kind of irrelevant
But like
This lack of funding we will not be able to make up from Individual donors
The amount of money
The US gives
Dive to keep people alive
Foreign countries
Third world countries
Medical release
Entirely shift
The nature of human
On funding of the UN is not going
To be some political game going
To be mad
People are going to die
Unreleased
That's what's being cut funding North Carolina's hurricane relief
It doesn't f****** matter if your worldwide
Look up
True but we got to keep it on the globalist
I don't know I have you ever come into North Carolina for disaster
F*** it the free market I'll take care of you
Listen to interviews It's Like Romeo Dallaire
The guy who is on the ground in Rwanda during Civil War
She wished that the UN gave them less funding
No
It's kind of the opposite
I was I was like wait
Do like that
Global corporations are they really just kind of
Screwed everybody over
And it was a temporary relief for a
The moment they left
All that s*** started up again
No it's not on
The the funding
Exactly what needed to be done
Cause
Countless deaths
Genocide
We're going to we're going to end up seeing in war-torn regions
Because of trump
Proposed lack of
And it's not
Like we want to imagine
But people like Alex one
You went to the money suck
Yeah just trying to keep
Consolidate business interests
Stuff like that
Usurp our sovereignty
Bright and in reality a lot of the money that you that we pitch into it goes to
People alive
It's and it's amazing that he
He kept Butler
That's not a story
Like you and I
Like most people
Do not know that those
Taking to the UN
So that
Basically means that
They can get away
This is no one's picking it up really don't it's not it's not carrying on as a narrative
Give a f***
It's the same thing with Americans are poor and brown
So if that's America
His philosophy
This next door I was really interested in it because
He keeps talking about how like in his short time in office
Trump is boosted
The stock market more than anyone ever
The massive rise
Like a bubble
Well that's one thing I have
Talk about how we're going to be okay for a little while
This will be the biggest crash that we've ever seen
Like
The sort of things everybody plays at no infrastructure
It's unsustainable it's
It's just on hubris
Yeah and I
Hot air
I wanted to look into specifics
Percentage of the
It's growth
Presidents
First
100 days in office
No I'm an
Delano Roosevelt
Oh yeah well
But he has of the single worst thing that ever happened to literally anything
33 came to office and raised
The stock market by 79 point
60%
What you got on
Call Totoro
Also just
Not having
Hoover in there
Who was active
Play f****** people over
The fact that you have somebody who espoused
Some socialist beliefs
The stock market
Was going to go up
And then the New Deal of course
LED 28.
Consistent growth for 40 years and then somebody
The New Deal
And somehow everything started going
F****** s***
Actually Hoover is first hundred days in office wasn't
Terribly bad
We only saw one point
2%
Decreasing the stock
Botanical Park
Hoover was elected
A 28
Number 5
On the list
Of the
Biggest growth
In stock market in the first hundred days
With a 5.3
2% train
How about
Junior number three
No
Bush
1980 97.9
3%
Obama Barack motherfuking Obama
In 2013 7.51 almost at 2%
Better growth of the stock market
In his first hundred days of his second term
How far is Dhaka dick Alex
Like your own stats there the guy who you hate
Is better than your guy
It's insane
Why doesn't anyone look this up
Why do outlets look this up
I know gives a
Goddamn f*** about whether or not something is true
I was I was talking my dad
And it was just literally like
Everything is fake news
That's that's abdicated your responsibility is a human being
Responsibility
It's not food
Media's responsibility right all the time
Responsibility
It's every
Citizens
Responsibility to engage with news that you get
Don't trust
Look into it
Who everyone is just giving up on that
There is there is something about
I will never remember the quote and I'm probably going
To paraphrase
Screw everything up
Without a name
Informed citizenry
Christy cannot fly
Shakespeare
It's one of the founding fathers
Where was Cooper
Clip
Just overall Alex not getting the point
Pokey toberman
Video
He is literally scared
These people are crazy they thought they ran America
Extra power strip
Calling to kill
Trump supporters
Pluto
Kill Everybody
The right there
Right there what happened
What happened
Hey
Auntie Fee
Kill everyone
But what happened there was like Alex DeLong
Was because Alex said that he reaches millions of people
I need to be like
OSHA
So he got into his headspace
Yeah I realize I don't know what
Saying
Twice
Material
So
If you keep probably did
Watch it twice
But I think our larger issue is
Is that
He met he doesn't have any comprehension
Information
Sympathy
Broca's area in his brain
Just damaged
Like the idea of like
You can't take in communication
Appropriately
It's possible that we could
Even really
Kind of speculate on because
I don't know enough about it to have any I'd like to start a Kickstarter to get a CT scan
And unlike many people in the
Commentary industry
I would prefer not to comment wildly on something I knows
0 about
Webster the Hallmark of our shows all of the stuff that you just said like a the different parts of that that brain
There's a certain parts of the brain that responsible for ingoing and outgoing
Absolutely agree with you
Is Brandon
One-to-many of putting some other dudes into a coma
Situation
So back to
Disagrees with it was a war with Russia in Russian
Shred
I'm a military apparatus of this country is about to be handed over
Russian
When people remain in this is the resistance
What is the weather
Entities
Entireties as
Gchq and MI6
That is the problem
Call David Hall
That makes me happy that's like I know I can suck on a lozenge we're going to break I'm going to come to f****** text thing
That's some classic Alex Jones right there
This the rest of this episode is classic
Wasp
Like he's media criticism
I don't want you to
I do want you to your stopwatch out
I don't want you to count out loud over the eclipse
How long it takes him to interrupt but it's
Buckwild and the reason I put my hand up
To play
Like Keith Olbermann intro
Right because he replays it
And interrupt the f*** out of it
And I wanted everyone to be able to
But hear what he was saying in a coherent sentence
Book
If you just take Alex's analysis you'll never know what he was actually saying
Like
Before I even thought about Alex listening to that alderman
Is
That is
Oberman
Barry Rec
Capricious about Russian
Scum take
Taking over the Alexa
Is very much a
Couple months back
Just getting it now
No he
I think we just didn't cover it.
He didn't tee off like he did
No I think
I think one of the things that
Get me about all of this
Debate
And all of the
Is that
Nobody is
Clearly delineate
That the Russian
People are
Not
Problem
It is
Very
A few people
In the Russian government
It is
Very few
In the United States
Like these are his f****** Alec
It is not
People
Well they are people I mean like
America is at war with Russia
What's
What's going on
Is the Russian
Pro-america
And nobody cares about all of the people living in America or you got it twisted
Neutral
You're not getting involved
So all of this is
Because guys like
Keith Olbermann
Always boiled it down
Nation yeah
And it is not
No that's why I don't
Defend Keith Olbermann
A bit wrong
If I had to side with one
I think the goals of Keith Olbermann
Better-than-expected
But I don't I still am absolutely his rhetoric is a little bit on him
But just like we were talking about earlier
That is that is the question
We all know that there's some in
How do we solve this problem
Without also
Sparking a war
Waterman's overman's goals
I get are the same as
The meats
Have to declare
War
Well I don't know I do
Yes
Weed
Don't have proof
That would justify a war
But there is active involvement
With
Foreign power
I think that we just have to suck it up
We have to go to
Like I think it's
Terrible outcome
Man that's a long conversation between you and maybe we'll do that all therapy
Is already shaping up to be a seven-and-a-half hour-long episode as it is
Snake salafi
Already called for a revolution Kevin murderer
The Justified
British mortified
Execution
Very different from America
I would say
If
We can't
Get undue influence out
Of all our body politic
Check without a war
We have to go to war
Because the alternative is the rosian of Art
Government
Believes everything
Problem is that we have no moral High Ground whatsoever
None will ever have we've done it
Exactly what Russia has done.
The real reason that we are angry is not be
Because of the
The doing of it it
It's that it happening
But that's human
No I know you understand that there isn't any
An internal logic to
To declare war
I don't want to make the argument of like America first
Cuz I'm not on that bandwagon
But like if someone punches me way more
Like us
Like I feel that more than someone punched you
I'd be empathic and I wouldn't
Enjoyed
Right
I wouldn't like that
I have to respond somehow
Probably by running away
Strangely enough
This is one area where I'm going to go
Full religion
Oh boy
There is a reason that Jesus
Has resonated
Throughout time
It sure is f*** isn't
The Bible like
Fully subscribed
The philosophy of
Look Russia did this
We correct
Look like
Here's here's my
It let me put it to you this way
All right here's my response to 9/11
We build the Tower
The exact
There's no record
Of their doing them doing nothing
But that's the point I don't know what they want
Is Oscar
To react in this
What I don't disagree with you in terms of 9/11 but we're getting off track is that
What I'm saying is
If there is no way to correct this
Without
Triggering a war
If there is a way to correct this with rabbit that's
The preferable
Bedford where you and I
We would like to
To be happen
Right but
Because of the exist
Doberman
It seems incredibly unlikely
Conversation for another time
Alex
Have some thoughts
The treasonous people
Covid-19
Absolute organized crime treason espionage
Organization
Three different things a lot of things
Squad
Years ago
Now hold on this is this is the foundation
Foundation Alex Belize but if you commit treason
If you trying
Induce
People to take over our government
Do you mean like saying that the Russians should info
Only implied that earlier
Nothing
Real
Costco
My my
Peacenik
Alex Jones
Very similar to
That I am but for a different guy
Yeah exactly that's
Headspace
Let's move on a little bit
TV shows
And he wants to sit here
Look at how sweet
Isn't running the government
We
World is country
This guy is not an American this is a dirtbag liar thinks he's better than you
Sagittarius
What part of the narrative but also I just want to point out that in the past episode
South
But this one particular
He also gave a speech at the Alamo couple years back
Diaper
Mark Dice
The narrative
The bitter clingers
He thinks he's better than you think he's better than
That's when people are going to latch onto a
He's yelling at you because he thinks he
He's better than you
I'm yelling at you because I love you
Right
The vets
Divorce stepdad situation going
I hate you I hate you because I love you
Now we're going to rain
The section of the show where
Every clip
Immediately
Hold on I'm going to let you talk real quick let me let me let you finish
Portcullis
I've been in this is the resistance
We are the resistance to use the globalist America
The resistance
The first instance of teleprompter
Threats teleprompting ask
So just remember that keep track that's one
But also like
Come on man
Resistance
You nobody's ever thought about it before
Well except Wilshire
Almost every piece
Insufficient funds
It was the result
Right now over minutes
And now we can
That sound
Don't say too much about that
K very
Okay
And very quick
A little bit threatened
Don't want to sell their country
You're appealing to people that just help
Election dumbass
Everything
Understand
So hold on
Helps
Trump get elected
Because they're sick
People like over
It's irrelevant
Only 85% of people don't want their kids to live in poverty
Very weird fairy ways to make sure the kids
15% of
The population knows that 85%
Want to make sure
That
School lunches
Our health
Contain
That's
Nobody
That's nobody in the GOP
Thrown around
That's a
Five percent Nation talk right there
You're a pile of steaming.
Okay
You better pray there's a civil war because I guarantee you you're the one calling for all this
You son
Alex Jones is really mad
Yeah
Someone is
To do with it has nothing to do with
Anything that he says it's all about
Very personal
Email to the left
Alex
Is a man doing a stick of
Yelling about
Throwing egg
Alpha male
Really doesn't yell that much
No but that's not that's not the point
Babe maybe everybody is yelling office
Betfair
Entirely
But the point is at 8
He's not yelling
Prius V
Forcefully
Direct
Aboard is left of the Free World
This next
Is Astoria
Two parts
The first
Is from the next
Thing he says when he comes back
Will be horribly embarrassing for Alec
Tweety
We the citizens of the United States of America
We need to release your information
Your conscience
Noreen the controller
Republic
He's from the Constitution
How
You can't just say it's a coup
Elected
Version of reality
Inversion of reality I think that Alex Jones
Really needs to stop
Saying
Cool cuz here is a clip
Text Alex Jones
What do you think is really going on here
You know Alex
You've been together
Was so obvious
You show
Ecstasy drug
Ouija
Intelligence community
It was done through emails
To Julian Assange I will not name individuals
Foreign Russia was
Respectful
Union
Anything they want
So can we do 2
1 billion
Alex will not interrupt but it's so funny cuz been for like the next five minutes there's
Just some like assistance
Scampering around trying to close
Kind of like a little bit of physical comedy 100% not intended when I loved
Just like this this guy tries on the Legacy
It's hilarious that fantastic
On this issue but the bottom line is freezing level three
Secretary of Defense
The White House
In the White House Homeland Security military
Department of interior
But you get what you saying
Yeah
Like I I don't
I don't necessarily
Believe
All of
Steve pieczenik stories
He's coming on Alex Jones Show
Is congratulating him
For hypothetically performing a coup
To take the presidency
And place people
In certain offices
Is Mike Flynn
I've sent
Registered as a foreign agent
Counter-coup how great could his wedding have been about the people
It that were involved in his coup
That he would not would he have not known
When was an employee of Turkey
What do you not know that
Level the level of ignorance
Could could
That's a good question
Shattuck have not known the plan was working for turkey
Is that possible
I don't know
I don't either
The fact that he says
And you're right he was mentioning working with Julian Assange
So like even there is a foreign interest Alex
I've always said Julian Assange
Not American citizen
Unduly influence
Based on
What we've already established about Alex's beliefs about what happens when you
Alex Jones
Mike Flynn
Kellogg
All should be hung in between.
Condescending
No you're exactly right
So they're fine with it if it's Julian Assange
Is leaking this ship that was clearly given to them by a
A foreign agent
But if Overman says
Foreign agent
Please leak this s***
Then
Also cockamamie and it's all an invertebrate
This is a complete inverter reality
It's Sonu
So weird to not have a team in this fight but hate both
Yeah like it's so f****** insane for me because I'm like
I don't
Fully support with Oberman say
So this is
The central question
My response
The Overman
Is it worth
While
Get rid of
Trump
By then devaluing
Like you see what I'm saying right there
Yeah
What is what is
Is it better to get rid of
By any means or is it
Is there a way to get rid of trump
The right
So we get rid of Trump by vissla
Right so then we put in the next
Which right now would be
But if there is a leak
We have to assume that it goes to
The speaker lighthouse
Oakley hats
There's some indications that he released was having conversations about money s*** with kislyak
Phuc yea
Strategic campaign
Group right
But that was in association with stuff that was happening
Sara Lee might be a bit of a Smokescreen
And I don't want to buy into
Conspiracy theories
Because even though we do a conspiracy theory
Yeah it is entirely possible
Timing is also very
Suspect and the fact
That the guy
He has connections to Rodger Stone and Paul manafort
Call used to work for their firm
Their firm
And on top of that
To campaign group
Has
I don't know if I can fully explain it necessarily
Jeep
Robert Mercer
Sartorius
That campaign the Strategic campaign group
Created
A political Act
Committee for
Bubba Bubba
Fake mustache
Un
Guy for
Bolton political action committee for John Bolton and the only person
You donated to it was
Mercer and it was consistent donation
The $500,000
Mercer is
One of the immerser got Trump elect
It looks
It's like
I had something
To do with Mercer and Cambridge Cambridge analytica
Watching us influences on the campaign
There's Russia stuff on the side
Dubious there Debbie wild research Cambridge analytica the memorial
Taking over
Earlier
To get rid of
Trump in a way that kills
Right maybe underway the wave
Just rotten
Yeah that's
But but
The problem therein lies
If Overman does
Then
If it is foreign agent
Enough
Full on
Chaos mode
I'd like
World War
That's not war with Russia War
With every intelligence agency
Who knows
Who's doing what
And when
Nym
When it's like
What will they do with this
I think
You who me
Here's what I'm trying to say
And frankly Alex Jones
Creon what it is
Or how did you mean
Sega framing this metaphor
There
Like there's a bottle does a glass bottle of ketchup that's falling off the counter and you know that it's going to break when
Haha so
Our response to it would be
Either try and catch it
And clean it up
You know Oberman might his response might be throw bottle of mustard at it
Let's just
Rebecca
Okay I understand what it is
We are
The fact that Alex Jones
Legitimately for the last
6 months
2 a year
Has been pitching
An entire narrative on his show
It has to do with a
A counter-coup
Hillary Clinton
George Soros
And broccoli
Against an imaginary
That is just
A regular Coupe
Now if you can
Steeplechase
Wants to come on podcast I'd love to talk to her
That's number one
Number two
The first question I would have is please prove that there was a coup going on
Cuz if there was
That makes things a little bit
Yeah that makes
Defensible and I think
I don't think I don't think there was the original coup
I think it was hatred of Hillary
Conservative
We got to do what we got to do
Right kind of mentality
I'm so
He is not a real great
God
Dammit
His ideas
We were just
That mean we were just doing our coup
Whatever you were doing
No matter how effective it is
No matter how much you're lying about it
You had
The intention
Of overthrowing our government
Agreed now just because you were overthrowing the government while the government was
Between Administration
Doesn't really matter
Think you were overthrown
Government for a good
That's the biggest
That's the biggest issue when you start throwing
Cool around
Is like
Well it's fine
Because we did the coup for the right reasons
Just validate
Anybody who wants to do is like that's vigilante justice
The same way like
We know he's guilty so that justifies us with doing anything
Becomes a purse
Everybody's everything
What they believe
And you know what that's why this entire rhetoric of inverting reality is so dangerous
Because if I just make the Arkham
You've inverted reality
Send
If I save it
You're completely wrong about everything regarding reality
Your
That it is
I call you a literal demon smells sulfur, coming off
I've heard reports it doesn't matter what I say doesn't matter what you say
You're a demon
Even on this like 40-something episodes into it now
Like we hate Alex
Put will give him credit when he makes a good point
Like he's not incapable of telling the truth now he just seems to lie all the time
And that's the difference
I would never accuse him of
Like all he does is invert reality I pray he lies all the f****** something
This is
Leads into the tree
Like interesting
Meaning meaning
Here is a
And he lies almost like a
F****** knife
Directly
Break any kind
Continuity
So so long as you can lie in this certain
Spot
You can never allow that
Kind of continuity
Agree with you
I've been trying to
The transition to a clip about inverting reality for about the last two minutes
Are not strong
Rihanna has saved
Inversion
Reality
Total inversion of reality
Father's Day
At least in theory
Investigation by the FBI
The second president
Rex Tillerson
Arise
Global expert
Who's working over 160 countries
More.
Bull
How does a guy openly calling for foreign government
Here's why that clip started with
The inversion of reality
And I cut it where I did
Rex Tillerson
Tillerson
Is it tillison or tillers
Biggie
Has been an oil CEO who's been through a lot been to a lot of country
That's not the same as
Diplomacy
It's not
Oil
It's the same thing as diploma so you understand if I said I was an oil man
The inversion of reality is that like
He's worked in these countries you've been there
The inversion of reality is out
Pretending that he's qualified to be the Secretary of State cuz he's
Talk to CEOs another country
That means nothing
Ambassador
Metaphorize wow
Maybe the worst thing anybody's ever said
I apologize
I'm so this next clip just get to the straight up
Elite Class
They are almost silent
Back it up
The only present 50-plus years
I really wanted it
Stuck up there
Is the only President in 50 years
To put plants in charge
Absolutely true
Get rid of all
A special interest
All of the lobbyists
Didn't do that
Chicken Alderman Ura
Speaker wires
Let's
How much
Goldman Sachs
If you really want to play this game first
We can
JPMorgan
$2000000
To Hillary Clinton
Fred Goldman Sachs
500 million dollars over a million dollars from
Write to Hillary Clinton
To Trump as far as I
I can tell
That's not that much money for a big Bank
To give to a presidential candidate
University of California almost gave $2000000
Words to her
Google alphabet Incorporated gave 1.5 million
EMILY's List
To get more
Women involved in politics
I have a list of them
They gave 1.3 million Emily Brown above JPMorgan Chase
Citigroup
Citigroup also gave
Yeah
Donators and this is
Through like
The Freedom of Information Act
All the stuff is public
His number-one donator is Renaissance Technologies
They gave 15501001
$600
That's a lot of money
Renaissance
What do they do
You want to know what they do
It's owned by Robert Mercer
Yeah we met
He's the guy who's responsible for the funding of Breitbart
There is not a left
He is the most
Right wing
Okay you got me scared that I said left-wing
Oh I apologize
Correct
He is
Curse of Steve Bannon is funded all kinds of things that he's been up to in the past
He's involved in Cambridge analytica
Technologies is a couple million dollars
The trumps campaign bit that holds self-funding
Canard
Of his campaign
Of his own will absolutely
He already he already has
He made he made a name
Investment
The Chinese
That alone will make him
Billions
Donator
Paid
Business administration
They gave 6 million
$700
So that
Might look like a little bit of pain
Also as much as
Understanding as I have
Of the pro wrestling business
Real reason why she would want to be in charge
Small businesses
Association
Yeah
Because there is
Trim
In pro wrestling towards the unionizing
The wrestler
They're not employees
They're free contract
Yeah they don't get insurance
Pay for their own transportation
Between events
And stuff like that their independent contractors
And the WWE has a vested
And them never becoming employees
Dollars
Ensure them
Sporteverywhere all the time right
For all of these people
You'd be insane
It is already in saying that they're not as a business practice
Obviously think it's
Worth it to pay trumpsta
6 million dollars
And then on the off-chance he gets in
She becomes
The head of a small business
Of course of course it's worth it
Six million dollars would be
What one year of their WWE travel
Target close
They have a roster that's like
How many they have
SmackDown and Raw
They do
Events on Mondays and Tuesdays for each of them
Right tonight
Insidious on other
Right
They have their pay-per-view people are in different cities
Everyday
Play Future roster is like 40 50
Does a hundreds of people you got to pay for transportation
Not including I mean I don't know what the
The situation is with their like
And the people who actually do the building of the
As it were
I don't know about that part
But like
Yeah took Millions
Nothing nothing
Oh there's a God damn
Global
People trying to
It's over so interesting
Thunder
Izakaya
Business called GHB
And they gave
5005000 + $400
The Trump campaign
That doesn't ring a bell necessarily.
That is no
That was a man who in 1991 paid a $30,000 fine for laundering campaign
The support of the Incorporation
California is a city
And the reason he did that
It's cuz he had a bunch of
Property
Taxes will go up if I became
Incorporated as a city
And there would be all sorts of
Registrations all kinds of
Things you have to follow also to rule
And so what are you doing
Is he at a big company
He had his employees donate
To this Thai
Incorporation cost
Now he is still active to the 3rd $1,000
F****** nothing
Giving money to
Nope
Curbed
Dot-com
About
Geoffrey Palmer
Is Biltmore apartments in downtown Los Angeles than anyone else
More than
And they're all f****** Tarot
His Squad nearly identical fortresses with embarrassing names like the
Visconti and the Medici
Aren't just ugly although they are very ugly
They're vacuum
Designed to suck the life out of a neighborhood that has worked so hard to become
The past decade
So basically what he does comes into makes cookie cutter
Remix project
That's very
Expensive project
Cheese that specifically are designed
To keep
Affordable housing
Course
So
This this article goes on to give some of his worst-hit
I hear a couple of
Palmer wrote in an email to Los Angeles mag
The buildings which are collectively referred to barf
Has the Renaissance collect
He is totally kind of italianate architecture style is
Actually historical
The Italians actually settled before the Spanish and Chinese
That of course is not true
Spanish 1700
Wow
Complete inversion of reality
There's the Man responsible for
Destroying the very last building
Downtown neighborhood of Bunker Hill
The city wiped out most of the neighborhood which it deemed a slum
Starting in the night
But there was one
1800 Queen Anne house left on
Cesar Chavez Avenue and Figueroa Street
In the late 1980s
When Plummer began
Work there on the Orsini
It was called the geese house
It was protected under preservation laws
Their plans in place
To move the house to Angelino Heights
A workers demolished
Lyrics
A bulldozer had accidentally backed into it
Making it unsafe
It gets even more screwed up
When the city suggested it might hold Palmer accountable for his actions
He sued the city
And he only had to pay $200,000
Provided some
Public mitigation
The public medication so we can find our that
All of his amenities are private
So basically his outward-facing home
Yeah but like if you walk down the street it's just the
The facade of a building
There will be like a pool in
In a courtyard and s*** like that
He has one building that has a fountain
Accessible to the public
His public mitigation
This is
We are living in
VX
Is the roaring
Robber Baron territory
A potentially hurt efforts throughout the state to build more affordable housing
He's 12 lawsuit
Affordable
Out of his building
Including one over the pro2
It pokes a hole in the city's ability to make zoning laws that require affordable housing
According to l.a. magazine
Affordable housing Advocates often blame that decision
The one
Yeah. Palmer was response
To the paucity
Of low-income housing downtown
So he's actively
Hurting the ability people
How to get Apartments
Palmer's properties are recorded
Rent range from about $2,000 to about $5,000
But the tenants don't actually seem to like
Quote therapy
Consistent complaints about trash
About the noise from other tenants
Nearest food
And about what people described as
Oversight
His company actually has its own management
Subsidiary that runs the building
So it's all his fault
Also someone had emailed
This article in the main update
I bet the Palmer's buildings are also magnets for breaking
Far more than any other downtown building
Plus they have security cameras that don't seem to stop any of that
I read the article that was linked
To about the break-ins and it's insane
The statistics in terms of like
What you should expect
For these buildings
8 time easy to break into apparently
Wow so that's his biggest
Donator Woo's a shity slumlord on a massive scale
Now the NFL
Team the Houston Texans
NFL is a slumlord operation if ever there
I have no idea
Houston I have no idea
So we can Houston the Texans
We got Robert Mercer
Linda McMahon this Plum Lord and then the Houston Texans
Stupid like the argument there
If you know more about the NFL
Business model
It's
More shock
All of the NFL did
Yeah Rodger Goodell can go
When you want to say that like
Hillary's evil cuz she took a million dollars from JPMorgan
Yeah we got five times that from this shity slumlord
Linda McMahon
Yeah there's no way
Love individual donations
Drive-thru
Super Pacs in
I tried to find breakdowns of like Donald Trump for president
I can't find
Publicly available
Very specifically
Public
Whole point of super
Like the idea of Goldman Sachs
Did not donate
Is f****** in
Because I guarantee
That end
Individuals
From Goldman Sachs
Absolutely donated
So now we've got to get back to the other b*******
That was in that cliff
Jesus there's so much bullshittin
Like that one is like
Alright
You can hang your hat on
Giving her money
The lobbying
Sad sad that people can't Lobby
I recall that
For that
Unfortunately
A little bit after that
It came out
But he was just giving people secret waivers
Oh what a surprise
He was giving lobbyist
In his campaign
Well he promised that he would cut when he was campaigning was the one thing
You could not argue
Shirt special inside
Get rid of
I'm saying
I'm going to get rid of
Is a good idea
And it's
It seems like it has
Open. Even in the slightest
I'm going to read
View from this New York Times article
6 officer is campaigns issuance of secret waivers that allow for
The handle matters they recently worked on
Setting up a confrontation between the ethics officer
President-trump
The move by Walter M shop jr.
The director of the office of governmental ethics
Mister shop
Mr Chavez tried several times to use his powers
Mr. Trump Federal ethics rules
As well as the Epic order that mr. Trump
That's a bad start to the article
Largest uphill battle there ever have been
Office
Is trying to force
The least ethical Administration in
Fairlife
To observe ethical Norm
0 navico stander
No just
Not even close
No constitutionally he's already violated the emoluments clause
10 million *
The most recent request came late Friday when Mister shop asked
Including the White House to give him
First a copy of
Any waivers issued to political employees of the executive branch
Saying in his letter that he was quote
Advancing the mission of the executive branch
Such waivers are typically issued when the administration
Wants to allow a new political
Employees
To work on an issue
Like Federal housing or
Environmental policy
That involves people
The new employee may work with previously
Ernest J Borden
The energy secretary in the Obama Administration
Matters that involve General
Even though mr. Moniz
As in nuclear physics
It's served on a General Electric
About 70 such waivers were issued during the Obama
Mister
It is several fundamental changes
Some of which
Mr. Shabbos challenge
First
Mr Trump eliminated the prohibition opposed by Barack Obama
On the hiring of staff
In the previous two years
Former lobbyist
Speaking jobs in mr. Trump's Administration Administration
Must get a waiver
From the attic
6 rules if they want to work on matters that overlap
With their lobbying
The previous two years
But
Mr. Trump is chosen to keep the waiver Secret
He dropped a practice in place during the Obama
Registration with the office of governmental ethics
And posted on the White House website or the ethics office website or on phone
The combined result
Eliminating the ban on hiring former lobbyist
Hey babe keeping secret any waivers granted to new hires
Means the public has no way of knowing if mr. Trump staff are complying with the rules
Terminator
Whether or not
Anybody
And so far publicly
Nobody
Nope
Coming close
Talk about how like the idea of terminating the release of the visitor logs to the White House
Plays into that even
Is broody
Show up
Like the nuclear
Detest
Aa've
Weaver
Even though he's worked with GE in the past year like
Dude
I don't even
Even Nuclear Physics like there's a part of me that's like always a nuclear physicist
Like Obama giving waivers to people
Is
I mean we don't like the idea of
Lobbyist to being involved in things that they
The same time if it's open
Officially
There are reasons for a nuclear physicist
In the field that he used to work it seemed like he was doing Lobby was like
You just worked for GE in the past
Yeah he's like
We know you worked
We want to be
Way above board
You you work for them and so if you were not
And if you just got the headline
Employee
Now working
For the Obama
Can you call Energy
Play you be like all there's something going on there
Instead of
Employee who was also a
Clear physicist
Clear Expo
As well as the
The Obama
Instead of just
This guy works for that Obama. His
Design
As it were
He crossed the t's and dotted his eyes
Little heart
Trump doesn't know how to write
What's going on
I think
Obama had to be a
Zacchaeus
Exact
That's what I'm saying
No matter what
And apparently
Nobody's going to stop
I'm at
All the evidence you need that we live in the
Profoundly races
The society
Absolutely
Anyways
This next clip is about coming
It's pathetic what you claim
Woodforest
They are almost silent
Special interest
Globalist
Precipitating a constitutional crisis
Alderman
Legos on television or tweet
Hillary Clinton
Husband
Nancy Pelosi to Maxine Waters to Michael Moore
Well we mailed everybody
Viewers are a bunch of idiots
Why you have notes
Teleprompter
Deception
Mister Baby
Select teleprompter
But also
We can move on to the next clip cuz that's all stuff
Yeah
Instead going to say what I want
Hey I'm going to pretend about a different situation
Or whatever we're doing but only to stop Democrats
We're doing Alex
Loses track of what's going on two hinges come off the door
See what's behind it we see what he's really mad about
Mister Baby
About timing
Calculating
Blue Bloods
Powers included
You're not people
Your time kicking Christian job that I know you'll be available again
1 minutes
Rock Lady Liberty
Very specific
East Coast
Wireless planet
Republican
The good news is that he's totally in control
What he lets
He's angry
He let his anger
Right right
Letting the dogs off
Elite of accidentally expose as you were saying that this is all about this warped version of
Conservatism that is all that gun
And
Christian fear
Like
Does
I I worry
That
Every single
Republican
Conservative
Throws the
Has never asked
Actually read
F******
Word one
Second Amendment
2014 I can tell you that every single order that from
Restore comes along with pocket Constitution
Very easy
That is the
Sing about
At no point in
Time do they ever
Anyting
And it's not
Second Amendment
Christian
That's f****** it
VM
Conservatives ideology
Regarding
It's not really about
Supporting those things
About fear
Yeah it's about this
Like it gets into that idea of like
You Liberals are in bed with Islam and its
Cuckolding off
Ryan
Warming the cockles of our heart
So
Was just nut
That was not
Do reveal
Thing about
The thing that we talked about last
He's always priming
For the argument
This is
There's they're like
F******
Okay
You support the Second Amendment
Name the 4th
What what
The 17th
What's the 21st like all of this s*** you go through all of these
These Constitutional Amendments
Unem
Again
Imagine imagine the world were these amendments
Happened like
It requires
Two-thirds of the states
It requires two
Two-thirds of
The Congress it requires two-thirds of
All of this s***
It is impossible never
Possible to imagine amendments
Happening to
Never
You can imagine one Amendment
The Constitution
In 6 months
An amendment very similar to a Simpson
Situation where it says
No Trump
Like that
No more reality show people
Clippers
I'm definitely
That would still Public School
Sporting event like I do
4th and 5th graders run over like you were a rockstar impressed wouldn't those kids don't know who you are
Overman
What is my IQ
Miniature Doberman
How f****** awesome is that
Alex is bragging about being huge with the 10-year old Market 9
211 year old Market of 3rd to 5th grade
They love me
At my kids school
The show I quit the show that's all I've ever wanted I wish that was the end
Have you ever been to my son
You're not a patriot
Because Mike Dunn
Now
When I was in high school I took broadcast production classes on local access
TV
Really nice guy
Ron Ron Whitman
Rod
Wrong
With Ben Ben
That's the super coolest dude the coolest dude you ever met in your life
Ron Ron
Windber Ron Whitby
I'm never going to remember this
And then he
There was a station called on TV
Todd's Channel 16
It was like School access
Talk kids how to use cameras
And create new story
Your stories would be on the public access years in high school
He was like a mentor to me
He was a really awesome dude
But I can tell you
They went he went to games that his kids play
But when he went
People would storm the s*** out of them
It's cuz he was kind of a local weather local in the same way that Alex there's not a lot of media in Austin
If you go to a game for kids who just know the idea this guy is famous
Right when you're 10
You're about the globalist
Your guy's a huge liar
They're like what are two bellwethers I know regarding popular
Knowledge of globalist how many shirts are being sold
Sure
10 year olds
Who like it's so pathetic too because even if you take the artificer waiver
Even if you take the part that there lies
Argument is that 10 year olds love
Jurist Merritt
Telling the truth
He is making an argument that I'm more popular than you
Which is at its base
Kind of is again
What he tries to argue
Well he always argues that it's
But it's about him being popular with 10 year olds
Well it is a
Alright alright
Like even if those kids agreed with you
On your b******* position
I don't believe that it's impressive that
People who are done
Informing their brains
Agree with you
They didn't have political positions
This begs the question
To you
How many of you are 10
And how do 10 year olds feel about
Jesus I don't want to know
For a while there was a there was a girl called in my old podcast she was like
X17
I like I can't talk to you I know you're just calling into my podcast but this is still so how is illegal if your
Stop listen to this podcast
I don't want you to have a
I don't want me to have a son
Congratulation
Who's on the
Fourth grade Market
Pretty thrilled with you
And if you thought that it was over
It's not
Meant it off
This
Next part
Is weird
That was super weird this is even weirder
We the citizens of the United States of America
Call Matthew Wilder
Whatever we in this country are too.
5:30 is all about winning and all about Never Letting himself get any trouble and being upright
He does is eat sweets
Every night
No alcohol
No drugs no cigarettes
Do nothing
That's why he's so successful
You got all the stuff give it to it
Organized
Floof let me ask you a
I'm listening
Scoops of ice cream
That that came out the news apparently the truck
Two scoops
And everybody else got one SKU
Which again I don't want to live in this
Right right
That's a pro
I guess
Active ice
Also assaulting women
There's only one Vice
Sweets
Sweet
He's got to fight tooth
He was the cleanest life
That's why he's a mentally degrate
Who's clearly on in phetamine
It is weirdo doctors vouch for him
Creeper
Look is that the craziest f****** thing I've asked f****** hilarious
Lunesta the same time
Okay
Come totally clean
I've been doing
Ice cream
You monster I had to ice cream bars one night to ice cream bars
So I've been doing a lot of listening
Call
COP stock
I've been listening
This
Invalidated our entire
Outback research
And I've started to realize
The key is an adaptable creature
From his past
Mistake
So in this
Well in this instance
Like you heard him do that speculation
About
You know koverman what if you're not you're not
Right in the past instead
Buy Chobani
He's very clear
Right
If this is exactly the same thing that happened
On
December 21st
He learned the lesson of Y2K
We've we went over the Y2K episode
I where he was causing panic
Everything
Concentration
Underwater
Yeah there was all kinds
When the next
Sort of big
Media hoax
End-of-the-world thing happened December 21st 2012 and I was like that just seems like a reggae
Either date and now I remember
That's when people thought the world
Yeah so on that episode first of all on the 21st
Do you have David Icke as a guest which is
Grateful
Put on the 20th
He is going on like
I got to be honest
That's like
Like really emphatically be like
Listen I got f****** crucified because of how f***** up I was
I'm not doing that
An adaptable creature
It's interesting
It's like
Camping chair
Kind of by the world
Now he eventually will end up for
Forgetting those
Right like you going to slander someone again
In the future
But
Yeah but for now it's it's recent enough
Next time he like
Oh f*** I'm closed
Supplanter
It's also like
My go-to is pedophilia
Because that's the worst crime you can
But
I know I can't do that as aggressive
Say it
To fraud
Exactly that Hillary stuff isn't
Look into it
10%
Most
Charities don't give nearly as much
Absolutely research
A charity before you give to
Cuz a lot of them
That's Wyler nonprofits they are also
They're still
A lot of them
Businesses
Giving to Independent charities
Ali Forney Center
Look
Clinton Foundation
But they were not running
Beholder money
That part is
F****** cockamamie bulshit
They just
Play by the same rules please do
God they're so goddamn many
But like
But also at the same
Time but you have to understand if you're running a global charity
There's massive overhead
Add to it
In terms of
Administration Employees things
By default going to be
According at all these usually the best way to go
They're more on the ground
The resources go more directly to the cause
That your age
Justin supporting
And what's the most effective
Charity
Bowlero
Federal funding
Well that too
Unfortunately
Yeah exactly
To get rid of
In terms of
Oversight
And the lights
If it is
A direct
121 Federal van
How many hours
We're at 3
More clips
Okay so this next clip listen up policy
Oolong
Uzbek-klip is a string of b******* and then
Our freedom
Is your shirt
Kill cops
Strawberries everywhere
Cuz he
A butt dial
Alex Jones
So now I want to be clear
All the things that he brought up our things that we have discussed in debunked
Black lives matter killing cops
Whole shebang
But
I've never heard back
TV show
Are you kidding me I'd love that
I don't think like that to me does not look
Think that's not like some sort of sign of a
Blueblood whatever
Gmail
Like is a contempt of place you're retreating you have a glass of white wine
The book that you just wondering about yourself what kind of hiding out
Does not land
Hahaha give me caviar in the tub right by CID Keith Overman
Just being like this
Super stressed out
I love Bab
I've got to be on set all the time I have to
Make this show
I can't read in the tub
The thing that relaxes me
What's wrong with it
If people started calling me back
I get that an insult from a lot of my friends that are like
Hey you know you never get
Clean the tub
Not primary function
I take showers also
But I like to sit in the tub
I like
Most of my life
I was a bubble bath guy
But then as I got older I transition to bath salts
Best alter amazing
The bathtub boys don't attack me out
Fighting in a f****** guaranteed Alex has a huge bathtub in his palatial mansion
The million-dollar home
This is not the
Toomey opulence
Is the double shower head
Oh yeah yeah
Oh I had a one-point back one from the front
I had a so when I was in college
What am I
Friend had a rich friend
And we stayed over it there'll
Penthouse
Apartment 12
3 shower head
And I swear to God
Beautifulest
I enjoyed it for all of
5 minutes
Before I was like
You know a lot of places
Just don't have freshwater
Dammit I can't enjoy it now you can enjoy the triple header
Amazing and I would encourage
Everyone
Burn the house down
Give your fresh
Water to people
Anus
AB Lux my way into my younger years that had that
Starting right now we're going to discuss
Rich
Some people who are not
And also Alex
Lying about them
You're sure
We need
Your help
Afford
Heartfelt Veterinary
Wings
He says the worlds in danger because of us
Since either
So the third part they were disabled eyes in the world totally turd
She threw the fact
About new clear history
Here's the thing that gets
Call Hema
Tool
Which is
Which is like that
It's similar to the races
But it's at like
He's not saying anything
Particularly
Intellectual
Clearly an
Directly
I want you to hold off on this criticism
Cuz I think he'll get too wide
He's going to insult his appearance real hard in a little bit
Alright
That's the quickest way to
To get that alt-right
On your side
He's an expert
Experts tell me what did you go to college
J I'm a proud boy
Former Chinese nuclear history
Yes so
We had the Korean War
20% of North Korea's Poppy
And here's a really f***** up thing I learned
During my research into this
General MacArthur wanted to shoot 34 nuclear bombs at China
The quote create a belt of radioactive Cobalt
Across the neck of Manchuria
So there could be no Korea from the north
60 years
That's crazy
I'm starting
America's not always
Nuts
I'm guessing that's not a widely published
Size Fat American history
High school they don't go over by the way our general
Have a case
Murder millions of people in make sure that there's a radio on
College history
Bestway
Like
I recommend reading Barbara
All day everyday
At no point in time did I ever hear about
This
The Soviet Union assist research
Peaceful uses of atomic energy
Hey 1956
University in Taiwan
Built its first
Research
Nuclear reactor
In 1960 nuclear energy research
A reactor from
Canada
Those are how China got their nuclear
Could you play Builder
The name of it was it
Xian
Space
GF
Eng Hua
All right come on man I'm sorry I just
Alright fine
But University in Taiwan
4front
Call Chinese nuclear research
Year it's theorize will create a meltdown proof
Nuclear real
Yeah they're they're doing some amazing research there and have been for the last time
60 years
Cuz that is
That's a really valuable just like other
Other alternative
It feels like solar power washer
If you actually
Get nuclear reactors
Yeah absolutely
Yeah because
Is it because when you talk about
I mean like
When you talk about
Pure pound-for-pound Energy
There isn't really much that
Compared with
Fusion invisibility
Borderline info
The f******
That's when we get the
Next phase of our
Cultural evolution
That's entirely pause
We had nothing
Really fundamental to do with Chinese nuclear
Expansion
Help
Of course it was just
Really
For really good research
And work being done by the Chinese themselves
I'm in a little bit later in like I said 1969
Canadians
Sold them a bunch of uranium
Even
They didn't really
Like
In-N-Out
You could buy Radioactive
Toothpaste
Like they didn't understand
Quite what
Fluoride toothpaste
Understand what
Radiation
Did two people that were missed
And then as far as as far as
Nuclear
. like
The moments
It was
Is discovered
Inevitable that
That possibility would be reach
Which by other countries
Pencil the myth of Pandora's Box
I am
The f*** with it
Absolutely right
When he quoted
Destroyer of worlds
Yeah I become death
So
North Korea
Haha
Shockingly similar
1956 the Soviet Union begin training North Korean scientist
Engineers enabling
The dprk
To acquire face
Acknowledge to initiate a nuclear program
North Korea and the USSR sign nuclear cooperation
Over the next 30 Years Moscow provides the north of phasic
Nuclear training
As well
The work doing s*** in 1959
Which end of course this makes
Robertson's considering the fact that immediately after WWII you have guys like
MacArthur and
And f******
Just saying all right now we defeated the
Let's go after Russia
Like that was there a media thought Churchill would like
Hey
Now we go into Russia
Because
It's super smart
Fight a land war in Russia
A little more about North Korea before the clintons were ever in power in any meaningful way
Hahaha in the midnight
1880s North Korea reach
Dangerous level of nuclear capacity
With it
Mensa due to increased
Support for their nuclear
In 1990s
North Korea completed construction of a 5 megawatt
I don't think that's correct
Mmw.
Mwe
Cooled graphite moderated nuclear reactor
For plutonium production
If our
For a majority of the year
Plutonium
There is still great disagreement as to just how much plutonium was produce
That was in 1984
Route 33 years ago
So
Alex's hold
Narrative
Dave Murray
Was already there
China and North Korea both had Soviet help
It was an offshoot of the
The Korean War
What the f***
This is such stupid
S*** this narrative doesn't hold any water in what
What year is the singer
Fertile ground because
Like I didn't know where the
Chinese or no
The clintons a liberalism
No of course not but if if I don't have any reference
Point for that
Then I am
I'm still susceptible to whatever it is
Because
You are always
Super diligent in your research papers from like nuclear organizations
Like I don't have any
Personal research
So if I
Have you
Who are you
Who's doing the
Very necessary
It would be fertile ground
For me if I already had a fear of
If I already have a fear of
North
I also North
These days
City Place
He's much more
Plausible B
Dream about you're not dumb you would look into it
You would find these same thing
Because I have
No frame
Reference for
I'm much
Empathic
Because if you're already
Predisposed to believing
Anything
About North
Thing about China
Like
Disregard
Well and nausea
I can't know every
And so if I get it at
Assertive
Authoritarian voice telling me this
8 much more likely
Play for me too
If I have
Especially if you've bought into a bunch of other b*******
Unfortunately a lot of my knowledge of the Korean War
Math
Like I don't know enough
It was it was an actor
Well I can tell
The movie of the show
Okay nevermind
So this next clip he gives them more b******* and I've got more facts
He's at least saying
Christian Christian
The last decade by Muslims against Christian
How Christians are being persecuted the world
That Muslims about killing all the Jews in Copenhagen Denmark
So that's complete bulshit the 80% military aged man of refugees numbers
Make an eagle
Physically based on the statistics
7%
Refugees are
Your number is already
Well here's the thing
At the refugee demographics
Syria in particular is a country with a large population of young people between
Especially in comparison
Europe
54 years old
It only 4.02%
The serious population
C5
Compared to the European Union
18 point
Refugee and migrant population
Balls are originating country
Is demographic
Then we should expect
Will be male and most of them will be young
To put the issue of agent
Perspective as of 2015
Sirius median age
Was 23.8
Arax was night
18.7
And Afghanistan
18.4
By comparison the median age in the United States
What's 37.7
Did the United Kingdom it was 40
In Germany was 40
Children from Syria and elsewhere makeup at least
The refugee
Children who whether a company or alone or looking
A chance to grow
That is not shredded by viola
Now
If you want to really break it down
The reason the population
Terrible
Help Healthcare
Is provided
In third world countries
And also then
And killed
Kilt
It just
The reason that population is so young is cuz everyone's eyes really young
That's
The equation is so simplistic it
Expensive
It's not specific
So f****** stupid
It's ignorant like that's like saying
You know the population
In medieval Europe
Was
Heavily skewed towards
Cuz most of them.
Well now the reality is a lot of those marauding
Is operating basically off
Because there have been memes that have come out that show I'm going to show them both to you
There is a picture of
Muslim men
And it's got the Getty Images
Tag 2
Getting off a bus
Really scary
Every will use that as an example of like book it's all young men coming
But what they didn't show
Is that another boss showed up the next
With all of the women and children
They travelled in separate buses because of cultural for
Yeah it's it's
What the f***
What is wrong because it's the other
It's the other so long as it's
The other it's ranked
Rank big
You will believe
Anything so long as
It's your auntie
The 80% military men
Statistic is
F****** horseshit
The spirit behind it that it's all young men coming cuz it's an invading
Force
Because women and children
They are coming along
Just don't
Which I mean we can have it we can have a conversation about how everyone
That's a different conversation two different conversations
Now there's also a bunch of reports of people
Like.
Showing up alone
Dudes
Pulling up alone who taken boats across the Aegean Sea
To die alone
And everyone who gets all the boat knows that's a possibility
So when they get on those boats
Oftentimes what they do is they go It Alone
And when they get to where they're going
Claim the refugee status establish themselves and send for their families
I don't know I know another place where that happen
What's it called
America remember when the Irish
Do you remember that
I do
What do all of those people have in common
They're fleeing something
Earthlings
I remember also how back then when the
Jews were
Fling
Some guy
I remember their I remember a guy
Right so they were fleeing from this horrific
Catastrophe
That was being
Visitor
Due to no fault of their own right
America
We can't let these people do it
It's bad
They're bringing the same brand of fascism from their world
I remember
It's interesting that
I remember that our memories we have reports
People who read denied Asylum to
Literally being murdered cuz they couldn't get over here
I mean I bet we don't have a
Many newspapers
A written word
There's like
I mean we didn't even have
Newspapers back
Oh wait America's erases f******
That's always been
Drive me up a
Walking wall
That Alex Jones is making these arguments
Based on
Lies
Based on facts that he's twisting
And the same episode
Where he's mad that Muslim women are at Starbucks
How old is he f****** not realize
What leaves within him
How does he not take a look in the mirror and realize
Maybe it's me
Maybe I have the problem
It's not to say that Muslims
Wide group of people don't include some people
How do you mean in
In his group of two billion people you might
I got to make it clear that I don't think that Muslims have never done anything bad in the world
That's about the argument I'm making the argument
Video
You don't want
You see them all is
You see them all is bad
You
Refuse to wrestle with it
Definition
Absolutely
That is the difference
Bill because all trance
People are bad
People get married because people are trying to destroy marriages inactivity
Yeah
F*** you
Alright big soapbox moment
I loved it
Yours
Probably
Coming in this next
Segment on the show right
I think because
Pink
Isabella climate
I'm not sure but I am not sure
Alright
Your surest guarantee
There any future at all
Future at all unless you are
Science Guy
Bill Nye saves the Earth or space the Earth
It's all lies lies why isn't another fake
Election
5 teleprompter
B o
How do you feel about this
Look
I am running out
I'm running out of gas
Gas on the climate
It's
So my my operating
Is
Very simple
Climate scientist
Have deliberately
Downplay
The dangerous
And they've done this week
Cuz they don't want
To look like
Yeah exactly
Need to do something about this
It's really important that we do something
It's not like I'm saying the skies
They're like the polite people who want you to leave their house in the morning
Get the f*** out of my house
This isn't just an old story about
Malcolm Gladwell
Airplane
So if you listen to the Black boxes
Of a bunch
Korean Air
At the time were the most
Dangerous
Airline
In the world
5 because they have
Had the
Number of planes
And you're like
Why
Does this one place
Such high
And they go through all these
See that
Pilot get tired
Copilot
Because of the
Culture of
Deference
Would be very Jen
Teal and they're like
Hey I think
I think there might be something
And then boom
Soda comes from not listening to other voices
Even when those voices
Deliberately
Lee trying to be as deferential
Nobody's going to get
The true scope of the emergency
Vista
And this is something that I
It's true and I'm
Probably right
All of the stuff they predicted
60 years in the
Will be 10 years
I've heard you make this claim before in a worried you're right
Absolute
Jones has claimed that whatever you see
Time elapsed things about polar ice caps melting
Is it summer
They don't show growing back up in the
Seasons
Siemens
Climate is just
Summer
Spring
Winter
Fireball
I remember that remember the fifth
Season
F****** song greener pastures
Who cares millions of people who are going to die
And the thing that kills me is that there is no other way to
Describe it
Then if you are a climate change
Change denier
You
Person
Ark
Of millions of
Million
You think
PG crisis is bad now right
Just a f****** imagine whenever sealine border
Which is my new favorite show on Fox
Just Florida
Just Florida a lot of territory in
In Florida is going to
Disappeared
Georgia and Louisiana
I'm unhappy that
Scared
That's only displacement has nothing to do with even like
Encroaching new deserts unlivable
Movie Crisis now is
Is about
People moving from
And you think
Terrorism
Imagine
Freshwater
Becomes the neck
Well that's how many millions of people
Fighting over
Just
Drinking water
Portable water
It's going to get ugly it's going to be
Roodle
And Alex Jones
That's all
Like it's gone from it's gone from me busy
Are you
I'm at the point
We're all going to die
It's over
Fort Lee
Billy's
I just
That I like I used to be like hey
Guys
If you're denying climate
You're killing your grin
Now I'm at the point where I'm like
OpenSnow so I can
I Told You So as we both
Let's get back
To modern-day not
Speculating about the future this is Alex Jones
Junior
Real fun
Big Lots
On that soapbox
About Trump and Russia
We need
Your help
Whatever there is
Review it
Issue is officially if you can
Whatever it is
Whatever it is you got
I did put Trump
My vision board absolutely
Also
Hey Alex go f*** yourself for
Getting shity at the secret
You believe in 12 dimensional demons
Don't f****** play that game
I'm going to get
Him get
I'm going to let him
So far in
And then I'm going to cut it off
Because there is a
That there is to be made by
Will be made
If you let
I love you listen
If you let him finish
There is like like the Fox news clip
I don't know if you saw this
But they went to a Small Town Diner
StarTalk
Come to this old dude right about Trump
Reliably old white dude
Even the old white dude is like
Well I think the timing of this whole thing is very subjective a fire
Interview over
Like if you allow them
Ruminate
On all of this circum
Stantial evidence
Even people who are predisposed to agree with you
It starts to look bad
Alex Jones claims
Fox News
He's not allowing on his own show any contacts
To develop
For this thing
Criticism over like
He's doing this
The show
Dobermans
10 words during that attack
Pilots like
42nd
But most of the time it's
Why what's the point
What do you mean what's the
The point is
Obvious
Know the point
The point is really simple it's to inoculate
All of this stuff
Sounds reasonable if
If you listen to it
All the way through
If you listen to it all the way through what Olbermann
Sounds reason
If you take
Word by word interruption
Your inoculating your list
I just had a revelation
So basic
What is it about the 7th
Know about the seventh Elion
They're attacking
The hitting Florida right now
So
460 years
You said
So I think
Okay so Alex is imagining a world where a bunch of people have watched
The old
Watch it all the way through
Making sure that his illicit
Can argue with them
Right
With point-by-point
Here's an objection you can make eggs
Exactly
Whooping
But everyone who's seen the old will just blindly accept whatever
And in that case
His listeners would win that
Cuz they're just
Noxious and bringing up stuff
That the Overman listeners
Like I don't know what you're talkin about
North Korea's nuclear program
If you were in a conversation with one of Alex Jones
I don't know about that doesn't sound good but I don't know about
They get aggressive with you doesn't go well if you go
I don't know about that
I need to Google this
Unfortunately
Rhetoric
A lot of it
Reality
Especially when it's super aggressive rhetoric
This next
Alex
F******
Completely take
Two words
Out of context
And pretends their bib
It's wild it's wild
Just listen to this closely
Don't talk over there
It's pretty quick
Pure and ask yourself
If there is any
Look to the last year
He's talking with the last
Few days
He's got to talk about apocalypse
So f***** up
It's it is
This is what I'm saying about this
This is very much
Alex
You're on
You are mine
This is where I
So don't f*** with me
Conspiracy territory in Utah
And Oldman is
Is doing that
Like
He might be
Right
And I definitely don't rule it out right now
But over it is definitely stepping into Russia
Conspiracy theory
Towers into let's not get into it
Just Auto very
Superficial
We do have to be super careful
Ourselves
And I think everyone else should as well about getting caught up
And momentum
With Conspiracy Theory on
Because we've seen what it's done to the right
It is this
But like
When we talk about Louise Mensch
Okay look
Right if I got you I got you I got you I'm not here to defend her she's wrong a lot of the time
But she is part of that
Hemisphere
Twitter
That has become
Bhldn
Rampant speculation
Maybe more right
Then the conservative side absolute but at the same time it's dangerous because there's a lot of things that are wrong to get forgot
Cotton when I write things
So
Well it's
Fortune teller
You remember when the fortune teller got it right
Don't remember all the
When we talk about Russian
I think
We're not
Saying we have any real secret knowledge
We're saying it looks bad
Based on the things that are concretely reported there is not nothing
I think
I think are our main
Summation
Insofar
Russian
Is
The architect
Something
We know these
People have
With a guy who is a
Front
So we know that there's
There's all kinds
Shabby chic
There's a lot of circumstantial
We don't have a Smoking Gun
But at least my operating
Is there is this
Through this that doesn't
Kill Millie
That's where we come from
So what if it's important
Become
And don't allow a left-wing Alex Jones
2xist
Yeah because if that person does exist
You're just going to get
It's just going to be an infinite psychotherapy
It's
If it's an eye-for-an-eye everybody's blah
Absolutely
He's putting his toe into
The water
Angling for
Again
Is it cuz she's not a demagogue
Sullivan Real McCoys
I'm saying that
Who is legitimately
Conversation cuz he is on
The internet as a as a video personality
As a newscaster
What let me put it in
In the way that I've already
Right
Trump facts
Executed
Judicially
I want him to be
Tried
And then because he
Committed that I want him
Punished
For treason in the way that it's
And if the fact that he
He didn't want him to
Right
That's how
But I really like
If if my stated goal is I want him to be
The way that you should be
Home from the neck till dead broke his watch
I don't want you forever
Fair enough
But I don't want him
Extra
So in the same way
I want
I don't want him
I'm gone because of a whole series
Conspiracy theory
True because that is the
The same narrative
Thursday right
FAQ
Above
Agenda and narrative
Yeah it's beyond that also I mean
Trump's already done is enough
Totally
Even just
Of course that you can't it's not
There's a
Institution early service
Insane the punishment should absolutely be
Commensurate with the
And I don't want
To get into
That same
Kangaroo court
Anime
Wiggle wiggle
Like we got some good
Policy wonks out there good heads on their shoulders
Because here's the thing
If you have people like Louise Mensch on this side
I meant also back to the other side
The thing that sort of Unites them as this idea of they have a savior
After is the I'm going to save everybody
And that is a dangerous thing
Like I said
Lunchtime
I would love for people who are beholden to Alex Jones asphalt narrative
Did recognize that he's lying.
Terrorist
I do it or they just
Breakthrough one day
Amazon idiot
We got it
Likes pain
Better than Alex Jones
Talk about it for a little bit
It is a
Pendulum
My transition game blew it again
We need it now
This country
Vincent Edwards
Blowhard
This makes me
Now I'm interrupting
Is playing by no rules
The Trump
This guy
This is
Over the top
Trump responds nicely anime
Freak out and go
Support office
Supposed to resist
Bulshit
Hakama
Sure
Dobermans Casino time
You know him
Him being like Oh you think you're the only person who can say
I'm the only person who can save the world from Goblin that's what was energized
That's why he has his
Is is
Is Israel
Is that expression hack
Hackles
He's rankle
That's why it is this like
Again you're on my turf
Yeah you're on my f****** turf
I think I think it really is that
I think you're absolutely right like
Alex
Getting to
Parallel
Liberal Alex Jones
A little bit
Not nearly as absolute
But but the point being Alex
To come at him from this like
Your
Left-wing proper
You know it's like Alex
Being off
Watching history
Except except except Alex
Still permeated
Repeat
But he's watching respect
So we kind of get a glimpse of what are podcasts would be if he was on it
Bother about the orbs
Is there anything along those lines
With is a f****** awesome
Again totally Patty
And it gets into that idea of what
Really
When he talks about like
Will share its appearance
Baisden
By reading a TV news
They have no rules
We can have no rules either
We will take the risk of re-establishing
Would you
In the Justice Department
We also
Mead
It may disappear
May disappear as well
What's up
Everything they claim Trump's doing
Had to pull it down
Celebrated and celebrate
Alright well that's
Take an absolutely attack
And then put always the same guys like Stephen Colbert and
Obermann and non-threatening
Argument
Nonthreatening picking up young college girls in high school girls
Where you going to break
He realizes he's losing
That's so much projection of the action of a
And he's panic
Alex
Mirror
Meanwhile
Alex
Sit down
With that bottle
Look in the mirror
There's a lot of people who used to wear a gray suit
Black tie
Nope
What were you saying
Ted Bundy
It's
Where at where at where at seven and a half hour it's so much not we've added about
3 hours of this lady
We're coming to the end of this but it's like
To when we've had a lot of stuff you can respond to
You are Trump
Donors who are we
Nuclear program
It's really tough for her to be like
This guy dresses to try and trick you don't know I don't I don't care
Appearances
Magazine article on how many people who dress like 60 but what about the
Percentage of the global population that dresses like that that is also a cereal
You're no good
Here's a stat that I can tell you I was Jones
100-percent again was doing that like
Cute dresses
I'm going to watch him until that I would have six months ago but I'm going to walk it back
That's good. Stay Harbor your phone
So that is nice
Is just Alex Jones f****** losing it
The temperature really hard
Flashing
The beginning of the episode
Him talking about how like
He's in control
Listen to this clip in
If he's in control of himself
Alright buddy
I forgot the milk as well and I
Throwing stuff during the breaks
I mean
Beckley wasn't like him screaming but
That's a horrible
Things to learn
He was throwing things during the break because
He had listened to an old woman
Alex Jones is my greatest
I disagree and can disprove most of his worldview
She makes me really mad
When I listen to it
To deal with that
Inger Stevens
And then I think about how fun it's going to be when I prove him wrong
That is how I deal with that I don't necessarily when I'm at work and I'm listening to him
Don't like
Throw my computer across the room or something like that
In his defense
Pretty much what
Like a physical manifestation of your anger the Alex
Laughing
I am
The screaming is mostly you just externalize and surprise
It's not really real
Embedded within it
Go home anyting but
Visibly shook by the reality that
Alex Jones
You can't control his temper
TF2 little baby
Yeah he's a baby man
If he could lift your baby if he were the Butt Boy from
Man
Maybe
You know what I meant
I don't
It's hard to say
I think if you
Visita
My bigger theory is
His life is being ruined by his own supper
Can Superman vitality
Testosterone, s***
And so he is wrapped himself up
Way too much.
He's experiencing all of this
Anguirus
Rate
Cause of death
Inability to control his behavior
PennyMac
Do not do that
Super Super Size Me thing where you take a lot of
Do not want to deal with aggressive dad
Listen never had to restrain you before
And throwing stuff
Can we listen to
That is a theory that I'm going to be working out over the course of a number of these
Time travel episode
I think that you can't
Attract a very different
The philosophy and terms
The globalist
Like that is absolutely
Yeah but the behavior the freak
Currency of outbursts
The inability to
Control
Is very much like he was as a child
Like we talked about
We've documented
The number of times
Ann Arbor
Give him all of these
Incredibly violent outbursts
Please fight that he get into
Camas
You don't see a ton of that necessarily and adult life
Until
Wave closer to that now
In terms of like you don't see it on the show
But you just admitted the last time
He was throwing shade
More than just when he listen
Colbert
If you will both of them
And if you
Exhibiting those sorts of behaviors
Adams being a b
Safeer
I don't think he is
To be around
Like if he has that kind of
Like hair-trigger disagrees with
We'll send him into a rave wear
He breaks things
That's not someone who can be trusted around
Growing
Humans
I think this
Is where we are out of our
That's why I think this is the one where
His kids are not living
With him full-time and I feel
If you listen to this podcast you know that's probably
For the best
And again I want it I want to stress
Don't buy his product
They are deteriorating
I think there are negative
Sequin tracking him
Tomorrow we're going to be doing an episode come out later in the week
About an episode 4
Haha
We'll see
Fresh
Market
So
Anyway
Finish this s*** out
We Are One More clip
This is the end of his analysis
And
It's dumb
Prevent this day
Others less so
Right now it doesn't matter
Lecture
You've got to be the Patriots now
Overtime
You got to do it okay
Okay
Account.
American
You need what you have and we need it now and we need it made public
Give us all your dark
There is
Obey the ones running around
It is more than just the fate of this sloppy but well-meaning
Flopping
I like it now
If our governments helped overthrow this evil president
So do you out
We cannot be left as a fascist Rogue
Enemies of freedom and international, t
The fate of all in your hands
And your willingness to not merely hint
What
You know
If we go under
The freedom you say will be
Your own I get a little blowhard
Yafo
Change change
As a Cooperative operation Black Ops is a psychiatrist
Play.
Wait though
F****** second 35 minutes we're going to go to a guy who has been in
With the regime changes that we do all the time
Play James on my own show that he was involved in a coup against our government
Hey
Nothing is real
Hey Dan I think I hear something at the door is it at let me open the store real quick
You're busted
Stupid
Gordon 4 hours
The punchline is
This regime
Yeah
I don't get it I don't get it. Damn it I thought we were going to
Thought we were going to book end it with the clip a couple of cups of this one
Actually I forgot
We are out of context a drop so might as well do it now
There's a book in for you
Good
Robots are evil all right you understand
Love chimeras
He said he doesn't
It's not
70 year old man who is spooked out by handheld devices
Mobile phone technology
He just doesn't
Island
Frankly based on his
Situation regarding leaks
Recording
He's probably smart and I wouldn't
We got to get out of here
We do how many hours a week
On Twitter at knowledge under
The score
Username is jacked
Kobe Achilles up with a direct message over
Also
At gmail.com
I was about to say something it's off
Dollartree.com website
You can
Unsubscribe
Little cast through there
Please leave a review
We love that
If you are still is making you haven't left a review
Rappaport still lives
On iTunes
Now also if you're still listening
Dude what the f*** anyway
RAV4 still live
Rubber bracelet
Also if you want to donate to the show become palsy walk you can there's a link on knowledge flights.com
If you would like us to do a time travel episode
Pacific dates
$10 a month
Yep and we'll be happy to do it
Until next time
Look at you soon
But
Rapoport still live
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work