Damn important I sweat it
I have great respect for its knowledge by now it's like I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
About Alex
Damn Jordan quick question
What's up everybody is now course
Working from home we you and I both working from home for a long time
Tips for I do it for
Because I really can't be all that helpful
I don't do work-from-home well I am
I'm very consumed with
You literally work-from-home fifth
The show
Any tips other than like
I think you should listen to someone else
I think other people have better.
What's that my question
Yes sir is Jordan what in this time
Newsome brights
What's up what up what's up
No solid ray of sunshine
I'd like to every episode
You and I try this one again
Smile let's see I mean
It's hard I can go first
Thinking about this. Not a ton
Popcorn
It's a popcorn
And therefore perhaps one of the best things I've ever had
Okay
Maybe the jalapeno cheddar PopCorners
To be fair even in a non crisis
I probably would be hoarding
If we're in the end times popcorn
Store running out of popcorn
And they will
StayWell
You know that feeling
Right now I usually don't like
These ones
Alright
Let's see mine
Steven Universe
Future this is the last last 10 episodes of Steven Universe
Which is
Shredabull show
About a young boy who is also a
So on and so forth
It's a really heartfelt and right now it is
Is dealing with a
Narrative that is purely based on
Recovery from PTSD
Finding yourself and doing all of these diff
Different things in
How he's dealing with it
Right now especially really comforting
That's what I was right
Great
Grapes bag of PopCorners
Absolutely
March
19th and 20th 2020
You know hey
Some of it's going to be
Even the point of doing our show as normal for a large stretch
Shove that since our last episode
Circumstances who would want to be listening to Alex
Not me not
And I can't imagine most of the audience wanting to listen to
Disaster
I've gotten messages
A bunch
From people
Who said things like
I don't know how you do it I don't know how you listen to him also
That
It's not that difficult to listen to it but I'm finding these circumstances
It's not ideal
I will take all those
Old sympathies the people sent me
Shift
Well we all think
Congregate
Turn around
The first Elliott
I'm a policy wonk
Next
Sweetie honey thank you so much you are now policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
James
I'm sure now but was wrong
Got you an alibi was wrong
I'm a policy wonk
DM Thompson 360
Anderson Cooper
36 Riverside
Journal policy wonk
Who donated
Technocrat
We got to go Full Tilt Boogie on this watch
Heroin
Freakishly large
Puppy love
Jordan
Little bit of
Preamble
Episode
I believe that
As its Public Health crisis continues and things
Get worse than a little bit more
Brightening and uncertain
I want to take a moment to address something that I've been wrestling with a little bit
It's a thought that's kind of natural to come up in these sorts of Circa
Stances that is was Alex
Jones Wright
It can be difficult because I think
Very important to recognize in situations like this even when some of Alex's vague prediction
Come true
He's still wrong
There's an important Dynamic to consider and that is the Alex's an alarmist by name
He has to elicit very intense emotions
The fear and anxiety from his audience in order to keep them in the full so every world event is presented with an amplifier
Fight level
Usually painting everything is a globalist plot
Hamburgers
In this case is alarmism feels warrant
Aw
Autumn alarm
Obviously his show win
Way past the line terms of being healthy alarm is
The drifted deeply into Chicken Little the sky is falling territory
Which is the first major strike that would have against him
Altitude alarm isn't was never also also never pointed in any productive Direction
Princeton you talk about the low number of tests being done
The United States
Disillusion wasn't to push for
Testing
He instead decided to yell about how he imagined the lack of testing was a globalist
Plot embarrassed
Trump and it's actually good
Because Trump needs keep the infection numbers artificially low to avoid
Panic
Glad it worked out perfect rake
The point that the government
Point they're making a
No feeling in terms of
Testing is a fair one
But the conclusion that
Cause of that
Is Luda
There were various things that you said
But you can't really do
Dispute have come
Past but it's important to recognize what sorts of things those are
There two major categories of let's call them
Predictions that appear to have come true
The first
Is completely obvious byproduct of
Things getting worse
The virus
In this category give predictions
Seems like the stock market is going to go
By the point this was a main talking point for Alex the city of Wuhan was already under a lockdown
So even
Anything's didn't spread much
Past that point
It's a pretty safe bet that there would be some
Economic implications
This is not the sort of prediction that you could really give someone a ton of credit for
It's also important
Recognize how this predict
Was used
This was never presented as Alex giving
Street Financial mark
Prediction
It was always delivered in the
Context of saying that
Rooting the market to embarrass
Where is Trump was the
Ultimate goal
Which is why the globalist
Release the virus to begin
This is important to remember that the stock market steak
It was not
Consequence of events happening in the real world
It was the
Secret motivation
Find it all
Alex has in no way proved
Further the idea that the global is to release the virus to try to attack the stock market
Trump is used
To justify Trump
Involvement in the delayed and bad response to the outbreak
Trump didn't put out adequate numbers of test because he
The globalist
Tank the economy
Already knew that if the real numbers were out there the public
Panic in the market would fall
Let's remember this
The good guy
Analysis definition
Not all that impressive prediction that the market would be affected by an outbreak is ultimately repackaged into
The imaginary motivation for the outbreak
Itself and then used to justify Trump's negligence in his response to it
The other type of prediction
Kind of right about is
Things that he predicted with
Actually the result of a negligent response
What are the big early ones of those categories how Alex that there be an outbreak around Seattle
Turn out to be correct
This was a pessimistic prediction
But it wasn't an outlandish there's already a
Confirmed case in the area
If you're an alarmist you will take that case and you will build on
Which is what Alec
It's important to recognize that Alex's behavior in this crisis isn't really all that out of the norm
For him
Back in 2014 he was saying that Obama was trying to bring Ebola
Into the country but you forget about that his stereo because the situation was handled with appropriate
Intensity there's International cooperation in Obama took care of that s***
Everybody else Roosevelt
There are hundreds of examples like
Even outside the medical
Every time Alex yells at his audience after the shooting about all the guns being take
All the times you would prophesy a total
To the economy and its number of Rage
Back when he was primarily a gold picture
Or the many many times Alex said that the globalists are going to try to kill Trump within the next week
Alex's business model largely relies on being wrong all the time
But insisting the audience
Forget about all those incorrect predictions
Can only focus on the stuff he was
Call Stu Wright
About
As a coronavirus situation
Gets worse he's able to play the game where you can say that he was right and everyone called him wrong
But it's important
Recognize
They even if he hits some of the
You still a liar and a fraud
It's also crucial not to lose sight of the main elements of his
Conspiracy
He believes that the Gates Foundation already has a treatment or vaccine for
Which is incorrect
He's just lying about a group that the gates have given some money too
The pure Brighton's
What is a patent for completely unrelated Coronavirus
Related to a vaccine
Meaning for chickens
He's asserted as fact of the viruses man-made is tons
Different viruses all lumped together
Aunt has Quotev
The Hy-Vee deliver
All this is from a non. Study that was self retracted by its authors
After the methodology
Conclusions began
Getting some review from their scientific peers
Who's on the work to be deeply flawed
Alex still believes every exaggeration he's made about that studytube
Profound
He believes without any evidence
The study was retracted
Because the authors were pressured by the global
Alex's claimed Atlantic said the virus had a 15% mortality rate
Not true
The study only looked at a handful of Asians
Developed
Severe symptoms like pneumonia
And it's not
Something you can extrapolate to the
General population
Even Alex
Understand
The study was about
But he's not
Stopped from making the claim Atlanta
10% mortality rate
That is implying
He believed in deserted as fact
The virus was stolen
China
This is not true
So not true in
Information
Sentence dum dum expert Francis Boyle came up with a better day
That Meredith was at the virus
Who created
C Chapel Hill
This is not
True
This narrative
On the term gay to function appearing in to study for UNC
As well as a recent study about the novel Coronavirus
The 2015 study has given a Coronavirus
Gain-of-function related
Ace2 cleavage
Where's the recent study was about the coronavirus it was noting that the virus
Naturally occurring K2 function related to
These are not the same thing at all
Button
The word gain-of-function in both studies
And that constitutes a closed case on Alec
What's a show
Alex's asserted as fact
Based on net study from 2015
So the virus
The China
This is just a lie based on the fact
There was some Chinese funding that went to the state
And it could also be explained
Very easily
Alex is assertiveness fact based on the headline
Profound about that 2015
C study
That there was a big public
This is an article on website the scientist
With the headline lab-made Coronavirus
I was just
Choose whether or not
Which is a complete fabrication
Just making it up it's a lie
Is a very short article and if you read it
Debate about whether gain-of-function studies
Themselves are ethical
Asserted as fact
And then walked back
Embrace the idea that
Coronavirus specific
Targeting Asian
Military age Spanish
Possibly
The Deep state
Attacking China for Fenton
He has no reason to believe it's at all it's
Completely made up
Yes it 110 bloated is that
Trump
Is the reason this has happened
Hope is that was a short-lived
But that was there
There are plenty more examples
But these are the very Foundation of Lies
Misinterpretations Alex's used to build up his Central conspiracy
This isn't saying anything
About the cities allowed is gay
He let Steve pieczenik claimed that he was the first person the United States
Get the virus itself with antibiotics
Even though antibiotics don't treat viruses
You let Mike Adams lie about Havasu
Tito's transmitted disease
Yes he's
Supporting colors making claims ranging from
The virus
Security to
Bubbles because
China could be infected
It high anxiety times
The work of alarmist
Some propaganda
Becomes more
Because we're all can
And probably
Scared
If you aren't paying close attention to the finer details of what Alex is doing Fade Into the background
And you just kind of remember him saying that the market was going to go down
And that martial law was going to come in
There isn't really martial law at this point there are cities and states
It's hard not to
I feel like that's the same
Will martial law
It it martial law
It's in the neighborhood
The issue though is it be
Things that Alex is right about where relatively
The quinces
Decisions.
He supports made
Spell tomato
If Obama had a handle the Ebola outbreak in 2014 the white
Trump has handled
This outbreak
Alex probably would have looked a lot closer to right back then too
Anyway my point is
Whatever soup
Superficial things Alex's vagina correct about our way way overshadowed by the
Completely and glaringly wrong about
Which happened
BV cornerstones of his
Conspiracy
Anyway I'm sorry about this big rant
To begin the episode but I really
Have this feeling of
Being a question in my head
To stop that question about
Well I mean
No no absolute and this is not like
Even if he's
Climbing onto some s*** this is something that the people is
Epidemiologist have been predicting an outbreak
Like this for 20 years
Of course
Of course but the point is not that he was right by it
As long as you're paying attention to what professional
Experts are saying
And then using that is kind of a basis
For prediction
You'll probably be right often enough
And then if you're
Conspiracy theorist you just say
It's part of the conspiracy
Predicting
Outbreak natural consequences
Such as the stock market going down
As the reason viruses
It's easy to
I want to call it missing
The forest for the trees
Tannerite
It's not
And it's also a little bit like
There's an arsonist in
Chicago and he's
Don't worry about the arsonist if it starts burning down buildings like okay well eventually it's going to burn down buildings
You don't need to worry about it and then the Great Chicago Fire happen
Sounds like there's going to be economic consequences
For this and you're like yeah.
You helped
So
Episode 1 start on the 19th
Is narcotics drop from
Today Show
I'll let you go to Cuba today and the most beautiful women you can imagine
Could you for a $2 little tube of wormer
How do you know that
Message board
So are we start on the 19th and it's actually kind of fitting because Alex is going
Feels like he's
Proven
That
The Democrats and the left
Call cheering for the economy to collapse
Because they want to her Trump we got to sort of the justification for why he believes that the virus was released
It's so obvious and is it going to be running
Brothers episode it's all just Bill Maher
Where to get into the public land by the globalist to you
Celebrated say
We want a recession or depression
To punish Trump voters
Economy so we submit
And it's worth it to take the hit
Said that 2 weeks ago again
And now you say
Economy targeted
It's all bilmar pretending that everybody saying
Exactly the same things as well
It's ludicrous
That's not fair
No that's not
When you recognize
Kind of the foundation
For his belief or is just
Application for
Claiming that the Democrats wanted to destroy the economy to attack Trump
Which is why they released the virus
Stop watching Bill Maher
Podcast about Gilmore what about you
Stop pretending in something bigger than this
That's such
Like
A perfect encapsulation of everybody's arguing like people are ready to vote for a socialist
Does not matter
Biden will be called a socialist
Ad nauseam in the same world that we are called
People who want the economy to collapse because Bill Maher's
But it's also because there's a little bit of
With socialist for people like Alex's social welfare programs
Anybody who has any kind of idea that the
The state should do things
Basically
You know you have them calling like Obama social as they other call John Kerry socialist
That it's like that doesn't make sense
What's butt in there
Very anti-communist
Cold War holdover mentality
It's okay
I guess
But up it doesn't matter
Is going to come
So Alex has figured out that
Today's going to be a
Not
A short-lived
Situation in America
Things out here first
Oops
The government looking at 18 months
18 months a lot
Nice
She only indictment
I noticed every couple days and restrictions
Or control
Until they get the depression they're looking for
Hold on to that thought that Alex doesn't like
Qanon
Admittedly I have no idea how long anything is going to actually last
Have no predictor
Disabilities on that front
You're next
Trying to predict that has
Difficulty because the whole lot outcome
Is based on individual action
Are people don't take this seriously the timeframe for things
Get back to what you might call normal
Nextstep
There's just almost know what you could
You'll see
The difference
Yeah outcomes
Depending on
Different
Considerate
Even those are
You know who.
The 18-month number that Alex is talking about his specifically related to the UK
Boris Johnson previously announced that their strategy was going to be
The virus is going on
Richie epidemiologists roundly said was he
Very bad idea
I really think that we shouldn't
Alexa
Lunatic reality TV show Stars
Magazine commentators do our highest
I think it's a bad idea
It's not
It's not productive only gets a good idea
According to an article in time
Healthcare System
Maximum capacity of many times over
Cuz there was an article about Boris Johnson
To Take Along
Still not 18 months
This
Wave
May laugh
Yeah that accept
So I thought that's what it was
Amber comes from
That's the estimated time it will take to develop and get approval for a vaccine
At which point
Social distancing
Similar measures
This is not a statement that anyone is going to be a lockdown for 18 months
It's merely a reflection that we have some sort of containment
Considerations probably until there's a vaccine
And that's the estimated time frame for that 12
It's also inaccurate to save these things will only last few weeks
That's a slight misunderstanding of statement
From Health officials about the lengths
Things likes
Stay-at-home rules
Spike we have here in Illinois
Which lasts until April 7th
There's a possibility that it'll extend after that
Maybe probably but that's
Superior things can be reassessed
Some experts will know a little bit more at that point
People singing the last 2 weeks or not
Right right
That's the. And then we'll reassess it no more
From that point
It's them all trying to be like
Can we please hit pause on this
We're going to try and test everybody and get a full idea of where exactly we are
And then we can move forward
Instead of being like
I guess we're just going to go for it
Let's see what happens
Beauty why not I wrote in the newspaper for a bit
It's probably pessimistic to assume that social dis
The measures will last 18 months
It's probably good idea to expect worse than the best-case scenario but if people take this seriously and we get lucky on the medical
The worst-case scenario doesn't have to come to pass
The other thing
This is based on is a post on Michael Snyder's economic collapse
Blog which Alex's reposted
The US government is preparing a
For an 18-month
Critical shortages
Sub headline is are you prepared for the
Nationwide shutdown to last 18
2 months
No
This blog post is based on a 100-page
U.s. government covid-19 response
The only place in this document that 18 months comes up is in the section that list
The assumption
His plan was based
The number to is 18 months or longer and could include multiple waves
Who be important to also point out that assumption number three is quote
The spread and severity of covid-19 will be difficult to forecast
And character
This is a document that
It's primarily about government responsibility
Consideration
It's an organizational document more than a
Anything else
And I think a real stretch
Document
To prove it even the government
Planning
42 month lockdown
I think it's important to remember is that this 18-month number is an assumption of how long the pandemic may have an effect on the country that work
Meijer's Appliance
But that doesn't mean the same thing as there's going to be a year-and-a-half lockdown
Key point is
The active
Phoenix time
The phase where would be returning to what they call a quote
Preamble epidemic posture
That's part of the 18-month lifespan
Of whatever there
Assuming
This doesn't say a team of lockdown
Considerations of the doctor
Revisions in the scenarios modeling in projection
Used to inform planning and consequent changes in planning should be made
Affecting the parameters
Used for this modeling
So even this
Appliances
Scenarios
As more information
No the future
Vyond
Yeah so using that to be like how you're going to be locked in your home for 8
So
Knox
Mithril
Okay
Alex is feeling a little bit
Sensitive
About
His behavior
Gets into that a little bit
What their tail between their legs and run home
Understanding you're going to get a big giant Great Depression now
Take that
Collapses Millions will starve to death
Star the deaths during the Great Depression United States
I'll definitely pressure
This is the middle of a discussion about Alex's
Kind of feels like a sales pitch
But he's also saying that my Patriot Supply is stopped taking New Order
I'm not sure if that's true because according to their website
I just checked it
In an update from March
20th
They're still taking orders
There's a 12-week
I'm not sure what the situation is here like maybe they said Alex
Yeah we don't want to be. I don't think that maybe it's like we can't
Handle the load from all of us
Salford tons
Right-wing media figures
Might just be a thing where it's like we're not taking
Discounted orders
From our Affiliates anymore
Yeah yeah going to do our own thing
We have a demand of Italian us that we don't need
A bit right now
Again that's just
I don't know that but I do know that their website
You still taking orders
This really just feels like
Because
He's saying that they're not taking orders anymore it doesn't feel like I say
Self-defense
That's why he's talking about the
I'm not a bad person for obviously exploiting this crisis that I didn't know
This bad until
Pretty much right f****** now and now I feel bad about it
We've heard Alex talk about that in the past
Tell million starve to death during the Great Depression
Discuss how it's absolutely not true
He keeps bringing it up though and in this case
It's in the context of talking about his food buckets
So curious about this claim comes from
One thing you can be certain of is anytime Alex says something come
Songs from major universities
It does not come from major university
It turns out the pissed at traces back to research done in 2008 by a Russian gentleman named Boris Boris
I know
Boris Boris
That is the guy's name
Okay
Providence
Nrt
Attraction outside of those places
Most likely because his work was very flawed
I've looked at his assumptions and found that the research is just
Not good
His basic point is that if you refuse Census Data there about 7 billion people unaccounted for during the Great Depression and their
For they must have all started
That doesn't sound right
Leaving aside how that's a gigantic leap to make and it's unclear and 7 billion are even unaccounted for during a.
There's a ton of other explanations for the Democrats
Numbers like people not filling out sensitive during the Great Depression or mass relocation caused by things like the Dust Bowl
Exactly
Without minimizing the hardships of people living in the depression-era there's just no good evidence
It's 7 million people died of starvation
That raises a question
What's behind this claim the Boris autism
Pretty explicit
And that Pravda article that the intention here was to frame the Great Depression
Is America's holy
Okay alright so the goal is whitewashing the ussr's band
Man-made famine in Ukraine billions of people starve to death but it was America
I didn't see
Where it's not we're not bad guys everybody was starving people for fun
That was adorable that he was doing it everybody
Way too complicated for us to get into on this episode
This is super
He is a huge anti-communist Auntie USSR guy
His entire world has grown out of the red-baiting hardliners
How to sync for him to be citing a statistic about us death during the Great Depression that was more or less produced
Used as a propaganda narrative
To minimize the case of
USSR causing
This is an imp
The message of the erroneous
Stat that 7 billion US citizen star vinaigrette
Is more important than the context
Where that's at
Because Alex's 70s
The erroneous that helps him
Further and justify that goal
So who cares if it comes from a pro USSR anti USA
Are you as a piece of propaganda
This is not it is really like we're in
Like
The abyss looking back
Kind of. Of
History all of these guys are born from a bleach
Anti-communist
Lunatic
Mill
But because the only people now who agree with them in terms of profit
Genda outfit are those
Former communist people that you've they have to become stories but it's just like
Radical Christian
It like radical Christians agree with radical Islam then they do with
Anything else you know
Like the these strange times makes strange bedfellows
Those kind of situations
Or you become what you hate the most
Like
It's just it's just weird
What's wants to sell more than he cares about these principles of hated usmri guess
You would think a guy you would think if you would like signed his article about 7 million Americans dying
Starvation during the Great Depression
Why is this person making this claim alright like I did
Alex's
It's not that easy
Boris Boris all sounds great I'm going to pretend I saw that from a major university
So
There's a thing is really good
Inappropriate
And that is
To release
People from
During this Coronavirus
Outbreak because
Over
Very detrimental to People's Health
Because I end up in a very bad situation
We should remove that we should really
Eastham Prison I mean we should do even if even if you don't
Want to this is even if you have no
Christened
Good part of it
Just a tap yourself in
If you do not release
People from prison then you keep them in the
Overcrowded
It's spaced the virus is going
Get in there and go
And then
More possible than absolutely
Jla's not release thousands
Since 2 days ago
View
Thought
To go out to walk your dog you're going to jail
They want you the producer to know we own your ass
Hey White
Hey
Get in there
So
The government website literally list
The acceptable reasons
To leave your home and one of them is quotes
For short trips close to your home link to physical individual activity
Before the needs of Doom
System where you need to fill out a form to have in your possession in case you're out your stop by patrolling office
You know
Super thrilled with
I don't know this for certain
But I have to think that if you're out walking your dog
Even if you don't have one of those forms
You're probably just going to get a warrant
Either way Frances is a 40 people in jail for violating the quarantine
Guidelines
You know what we have all of these people that we
Keep separate
So if one of them gets out we need to put them
With a whole bunch of other people
Perfect sense
That's a problem of the thinking
Anthony issue California releasing prisoners I can't find any evidence that the prisoners being released of the ones who were convicted of violent
Crimes until it's mostly people
Pretty short time left on their sentences to
To begin with
Prison overcrowding is a serious issue particularly in a Public Health crisis
Anything that can be done to minimize the risk that incarcerated persons face is something that should be
Considered
Does that mean releasing all murders
Not necessarily but it does mean possibly releasing non-violent drug of
Appropriate
The house the violent offenders in the
Responsibly
From everything I can tell from the Articles I've read that
Basically what time
For someone like Alex who allegedly has opposed
People being in jail for drugs and likes to pretend he's a f****** libertarian
Should be a good
But it's not
Weather.in the islamists The Immigrant
Producer producer they're going to jam you up
Do you have one like
In his mind physical characteristics
Sure I would say
Talk about that
Hilarious
All the compliant good slave
Starving nailed
A big supply of a lot of our supplements motherfuker
Wow Behavior
Parker
Types of about food sales
And then all the sudden be like well yeah
Obviously we need to get rid of all illegal immigrants in Muslims
And you should buy
Just so you know
We need to get rid of all of them about immigrants but you should
It's a bit it's a bit much
Position anybody who has any concerns about Alex being on the up-and-up and being
The bad stuff
Go check light on
Alex
And this episode is
Is mostly on vlive
The martial law is coming
It's here
Tip
It's not a whole lot of evolution in
In terms of
Narratives about the virus cause a lot of that's pretty solidify
Like the
It was made in that lab UNC Chapel Hill
Bio weapon
The whole thing but now he needs to build from
Do you know this is
Very obvious develop
That is the Bill Gates is
Is the big bad guy who is the villain behind.
Alex gets into that a little bit here
Here is just a short sampling
Bill Gates
Headed up the UN disease X operation cygnus mystery things coming in a few years ready World Government will save you
Tabletop exercise in November with 65 million die
Coronavirus
How They Roll the 20
He's got the patented vaccine ingredients
Then
Family TV shows that he finances
About how he's a hero
Vaccine stopping World pandemic
Get the bird flu
The swine flu
The wine flu
Of the big panda China
All that stuff about Bill Gates is nonsense and stuff we've gone over the past
But I wanted to check
In real quick
Who claimed that the ended all of these diseases
Bird flu is not one specific disease
Is there a lot of Avian Influenza
But obviously the one hour to talk about is H 5 n 1
Interesting Lee the first case of human h5n was found in Hong Kong which according to Alex's stated policy set
He doesn't believe that's part of China
That's but that's on the cost
He cute he would call that China for the purposes of this article
B2009 H1 N1 swine flu
Capri openly debated origin
My people weren't entirely clear
In 2016 researchers at the
The Icahn school of medicine at Mount Sinai
Genetic analysis
Trace back to Central Mexico
Sores in the current outbreak or fair to say that they started in China
Epidemiology
Kind of pointless
I was just really know anything about this topic as evidenced by his claim that all these outbreaks originated
Play the game of assigning blame to his chosen Target
In this case
China go go
Also if you saying that these are the
The four big pandemics then
Ebola
Coverage
Didn't see that left off his list
It doesn't comport with
What's today's narrative
So it doesn't
Yeah I can't
I cannot
It just it's so stupid
Like unless China literally made it
Which they did
Ben
You can't and it doesn't matter where it originated
Viruses can exist
And explode from literally a
Yes
They're older than
There's an element of Randomness Earth or not
Space
Viruses are
Just part of the game I'm done with that yeah I think it's space is full
It's entirely possible viruses
Seated all life on this planet that Trump is trying to create space force
In order to
Okay alright
Got to find that dark matter
Smoking
Is this Thursday
Coming up on Friday
Guess who you think
Big and usually promote the next day's interview in advance
Full-time
So
Disappointing
A big boys TV
Nope Nugent very smart lady, know her intended pretty good
Until all this is interview want to meet tomorrow at Thai Noon going to talk
Far is Depew moment Ted Nugent
He's going to have Ted Nugent's wife on to talk Coronavirus
She right
Books
Some of them about being married
Okay so that makes her well situated to talk about the Coronavirus
Instructor who get into her when she shows up
Today whatever she shows up on the show
Covid-19
So like I said
Certainly there is a
The theme that runs through this like I said when Alex talks about the Bringing Down the economy
It's just Bill Maher
Sickening people
You're not just trying to blame Trump with this until the economy as they said they would do to bring down Trump
Rollover bowel just it's it's such a Thor attarian
I don't like Bill Maher
Shorting the market
So you can see in that clip again
The only reference Alex can ever make
When he talks about the plants bring down the economy to get rid of trump
Look Bill Maher said on HBO
I don't want to believe that there's no globalist conspiracy afoot
But weirdly
The only proof is something that Bill Maher say
Great
So last week or a lot of stories that came out about people in Congress selling off stock weirdly right after they got a briefing
I'm about to Coronavirus
Situation
That was such a really
Interesting coincidence really like
This looks so bad
They need to prove their good name
According to the hill Republicans Kelly Loft loffler
James inhofe and Richard as well as Democrat Dianne Feinstein
Each sold 100,000
The dollars in stock
Classified briefing on January 24th
On the threat of the coronavirus outbreak
Newsflash four of the worst people in the world
Do the worst thing in the world everyone's got an excuse
But I'm not sure anyone cares
I don't know what the government should do about these individual cases but it's
Probably time to ban elected officials
We're having stocks
A conflict of interest is just something we apparently can't trust people to handle responsibly when they're supposed to be acting the public
I thought that's what Alex was talking about when he said people are shorting absolutely no
Of course not there's no way that he would criticize noted monsters senator inhofe
Exel stock
Presumably based on non-public in
Nation which might be accurately called insider trading
But that's not the same thing as short sell
Short-selling is a super risky Market play that goes like this
You have a hunch that a business
The stock is going to drop in price
So you borrow stocks
From someone willing to lend them to
Then you immediately selves
With the expectation that you can buy them
Them back later
40 substantially lower price
At that point you could have
Return to stock
Double ender in pocket
The prophets
You theoretically make a lot of money without any
Initial investment
Side is that if your hunch is wrong
And the stocks increase in value
So you can return them
The lender
It's literally gambling
Economy is built almost entirely upon Shameless
The bulk of markets
Know that there is a housing bubble
Very very very
Yeah
Potential gigantic downside most people don't advise anyone to
The f*** around with stuff like short selling
As MarketWatch explains
If you buy stocks
Is a hundred percent of your money
Conversely with short-selling the amount you lose is
Literally live at
You could lose
Any amount of money
Alex is not talking about these Congress people when you talk about short-selling but because there is a story that's going to be coming up about it
Explain what short-selling
Before
It's real f*****-up
But also
I don't know I read
I don't know my entire feeling on
I read some articles that say it's good idea read some articles it said
Stupid there's no need to ban it
Here's where Alex gets more into this
He's talking about this short selling conspiracy that he
But what they don't tell you when they're all up
Turn on television
Is it they're shorting it
10 weeks ago
Stop Trump
Bill Maher and CNN MSNBC
Economy to get Trump
So I know that he says that he has all these clips and they can't play them cuz it'll take the rest of the hour but
I never heard of compelling clip but he's played
Indicates that anyone is saying that we would like the mark
Get to go down to the drop
The only f******
Please talk about
Absolutely
So
He was talking about someone being on TV and trying
To cause the mark
To go down because they have been short selling
He's talking about until this
But I'll tell you the good news when I saw this video yesterday up on Imports.
Hi, Paul Joseph Watson article
YouTube
National Television
Almost every, nor was this is the guy that bought up that drug company increased prices 5000% this is the guy that
Constantly doing Insider stuff
Is go after nationalistic conservative operations he's a Harvard alum
Mafia
So apparently starting with this guy Bill Act
Who it just Donna
Strange and possibly
Segment on CNBC shutdown
I think it's quote was something along the lines of
Can't work with an 18-month shutdown
But it can survive a 30-day
Complete lock
Whatever
His position
Blame prediction
But he also said that he was buying stock
Which led to
As Business Insider put it there were accusations
But he was trying to scare investors into selling so he could buy at a discount or profit from short
Beyond those accusations I don't see any proof being provided that he actually did have those short positions
It's just something people were saying
Also Ackman is not involved with Soros in any meaningful
Most of the Articles you can find about the two of them but are they have opposite positions on some kompa
Overtime
Also doesn't hate Trump
Vanity Fair article from November
X-Men looks at President Trump and likes what he sees
A fortune article from the same time
Any comments about how the economy should shut down for a month to save itself
He was even complimentary toward Trump saying that he could have it if you could navigate
Disgrace
He could be re-elected in November
Is not an anti Trump guy
I don't know what Alex is doing
You can pick any billionaires
Right now
Also he isn't
The guy who bought the drug company increased prices of 5000 percent that was
Shkreli who's currently
A company called Valiant
I'm having
Control of 10% of the shares
And that company
Has had some dark
Drug price
2017 Acura
The process lost
4 billion dollars
You don't want to apologize for the investment in the company but mostly for losing it
His investors money
Not for the price gouging
Because he wasn't
The person who made that decision
Silver City
So anyway
I guess
Savella now
So Alex claims without providing any
Evidence
Any proof that
Bill Ackman is
You shorting key Industries
In the United States
You find out he's shorting
Aldi's
They will then go down to close to zero and then he will buy them
Turn the lights back on just like Rothschild did
When they beat the polygons hey
Lord Wellington defeated Napoleon in
Fast Corvette on a car
Until the stock market
Destroy the British Army's down
Dunno Vanquish by Napoleon stock market went to 1%
Lord Rothschild the richest man on earth and control the British Empire
That's on record
So this story about Nathan Rothschild is not true
It's not in my history
When using the key element of anti-Semitic
Gandapur decade
We covered this
Extended detail in our endgame coverage but the basic element
B Story game
Popularity first
In 1846
I was told in a pamphlet signed by a person calling themselves
Satan
Who's actually written by a very public
I thought is Boris Boris
The story is directly contradicted by historical evidence
DayZ settings
Like the 1940 Nazi
Propaganda film
The Rothschilds shares at Waterloo
This is pure and simple no two ways about it
Any pizzas line is either someone pushing
The sort of person who would uncritically accept narrative
Did find a good
Propaganda
I have no idea if Ackman is short selling any
Mysteries and Alex's provided
Proof of it on the show
I would suspect
Probably not seeing as
On April
16th 2019 he announced that he and his hedge fund
Pershing Square
Forsworn short-selling
Baby was lying
I don't know
So Alex
That they're kind of breakdown the economy that's what they said
Barbell bar set
The economy by Design and if you remember
Democrats MSNBC CNN HBO host
Bill Maher Bill Maher over and over and over again
Today we're going to plunge the economy that was worth it to stop
Donald Trump
I thought that went longer
That's
Buy likes
It is a it is
It's always got
Scream about a CNA
I would like to be fair to all
So I am going to play the Full Compilation of
But he plays on his show of proving this claim
Okay how much f****** Bill Maher is in this calculation
Here's a short
Compilation
Another
A woman asked me to you
Tonight
Get rid of Donald
I think that's most
When you see what's happened with the media coverage
13 days
The bottom half
And by the way I'm hoping for it
I think one way to get rid of trump
Crashing economy
Winning economy that the president
Nobody thought we would have a global financial crisis
Cannes 2018
20%
The house that then that.
3% GDP growth at this Administration been talking about that for years he's are all things that damage can run
Isn't that
Cutting rates
Going to make the next
Economic down
What's your prediction
Show me people hate me for it but it would get rid of me for it
We would see the global economy recession in 3/4
For that and I'm bring it on Sean if you're watching me I can't make it happen
Wishing it if it happened it'll be because of your lord and savior Donald J Trump
Policy with kind of frisky
So almost entire compilation is close to Belmar
One of them is just a pundit saying that the
Can run on economic issues at the stock market
Which is a little shy of rooting for the market
Circle App Store
Kind of like
Like political
Factso
But that also mean
Means that if the economy does
As well then Trump
Can run on that I'm sure they would say that as well so that kind of a part of the
Conversation
Very important part of any statement
The only clip in there other than
Bill Maher that's questionable at all is the first
That was took place in August 2019 on
Fox News
The person speaking to Stephen was an economic advisor to Trump
A writer for the Heritage Foundation and author of a book called trumponomics
Hardly a source I would consider unbiased
Trump actually nominated
That interview begins with a clip of Bill Maher
The whole premise of the interview is at
Stephen Morris recently run into a woman
Same thing as Bill Maher that's great
Just go back to right-wing assholes not being able to just admit that they're mad at Bill Barr
We want to talk about their anger but they also wanted
Dressing up as something more important than being mad at Bill Maher
This was one of the series of interview
About Democrats
It was posted on the heritage
Foundation's website
Interesting Lee that article begins quote
Last week I gave a talk
Too high with investors in San Francisco
Not exactly an audience of left-wing Act
Tourist
That's where he runs into this woman who wanted a recession to get rid of trump
I don't know
I'm not sure if I buy this apocryphal story from one of Trump's advisers about have
Opposition wants to destroy the economy
Seems like bulshit
That's all this is
Alice's mad at Bill Barr
Position
He's sober
Pathetic
These people
Now
Atlas have a little fun
Alex goes out to
Hey comes back from break
Yo
It's fun when he sings over country music
It's fun when he goes over the facts and You Belong To The City
This is so weird
He tries to hit the talk
Like that
Jelly roll
Bill Gates on that
Exercise for my co-workers Coronavirus
Protesting
9/11 laugh
Right about now
Brother God
The funk soul brother
That's so bad got to be just like I am
F****** the coolest
I can adapt to any musical genre
Crushed
Alex
I like
Scare you in the Coronavirus
Reveals a shocking lack of
Knowledge
About basic information
About the situation
All of that craziness
About 150 people of day if you average it out over a year in the United States alone
Sex
Put that up
You sort of known that
So on the 19th
Episode
So the United States related to Coronavirus
To be behaving the way he is on air it's deeply disgraceful for him to not be aware of basic information about
About the topic
For some context on March 7th there were 233 total deaths related to coronavirus in Italy
By March 20th they're going over 4000
That's a two-week
Progression and that's what we don't want to
What is the anti martial law guy
Except for the money time
Martial law
PCS severe measures
Being taken to stop a pandemic
It's kind of on praying for him to be against those measures measures and minimize I think
And that mentality is pervasive enough with impede our country's ability
Need to deal with this outbreak
Simply put if you listen to Alex
Got a lot of food and silver in your home
Situation like Italy
In the near future most likely
If you don't
Yeah they're saying the UK showing that's a group
Same two weeks
Double after Double after dub
The goal is
Do know what they keep saying
Flatten the Curve
Yeah make things
Manageable in a way that it doesn't
Become
Complete disaster
Alex is not in favor
Of that
The bell curve
Play answers not the Belton
The answer is never the Bella
When is facing out over
You know once you live without have your papers who outside your house and drones
You're never going back
Never going back
Never coming back
World government
Needs a bio weapon or a new plague
Get the public to accept surveillance and control station
Having a discussion about that but I know that's
So I think is a good time to plant a real problem with what I'm feeling right now which is
Pretty well suggest
Stood by that clip
I want to sing I want to go into lockdown type situations you never go by
This is an Essence the beginning of the Tyranny that he's long foretold if you believe what he say
And that's a problem
Because if I know anything at all it said Alex recommend
Fighting against that tyranny
So what form would that take
What it involves people not
Self-isolating and its expression of this mentality
Could get a lot of people hurt but what's for more scary is if you believe without you saying
It's time to kill people
What possible scenario is there that
Time to act
If you believe that this is a globalist plot to bring it martial law
They will never go away and kill freedom
This is a gigantic problem for Alex's rhetoric
His rhetoric relies on escalation
And what's wrong
Place of almost impossibly high tension
He can really only get people
As the virus situation gets worse
Need to scale is rhetoric to match
If things go as badly as they bite things could get really dark
Established a narrative blame for this
Can't really take that back now
Alex is already said many times that if anyone in his family get the virus is going to kill some globalist
Maybe Obama
If that isn't giving tacit permission to your audience to do the same
I don't know what is
It's really f***** up
He's trapped
Yeah they extremists bubble right now
That I don't know I don't know how you
You keep deescalate this while the crisis is still going
He's already shot his wad yeah I know it it does seem like you
You really should have called for armed
Insurrection like later on
You know like he's he's our
He's already
Took us to taking us to that place
I don't know if he has
Explicit
Implicitly
Play 887 bbnc agency
It's a very simple equation of the things
He's literally given a
Okay if these two things start
To happen
Then we have
To start
The hot War
And those things have started to
So
What's it going to say
Whoops my bad I had my pills
This one out
You're going to say
You need some DNA 42 sales
How they doing
Well you know we got that letter from the New York attorney general telling him that
He did read it correctly
G1 battle
Headlines last week about Alex Jones
Prevention
Laboratories
Stanford Hospital
Somebody found out
Regulators that Walmart sells this under another name
Maybe I'll has they certified
It all went away.
Other articles
Y'all just stop
Sunday dinner
Pointed out that Walmart sell silver products
Just like that everything went away
Is b*******
There weren't any other stories after March 14th
Because there wasn't a story
Story was at the New York attorney general's office
The whole story
Follow up
Letter
Still sent a couple of days ago
I mean that's that's okay
More stories unless the New York attorney general
Further action
That happened so quickly
It's perfect for Alex
So he gets to pretend that
The fact that there's no more story
Vindicate
Reality doesn't really mean
And I notice on this show is being
Farm
Yeah I don't know I think someone might sad about cuz he's certainly not saying the same things
For the most part about his silver
He's constantly saying like this
All right out you got your a b****
Someone somebody lawyer check
So it's there's a story going around
And apparently it's the mega banks that are doing it
I'm not entirely sure how that works
Here's Alex
Powerful Fortune 500
Exerting their will
Start a Stampede in nonessential areas they were running
Cancel some big public events and Annie will have have government declare martial law
China
Set the precedent and the fear to have that done here in front
Monkey see monkey do
Sure
Creating is unrest in the end
Place a drink Emily put a moron everyday
Following a balancing act that we really advise him to cover
Exact same pragmatic
System
Because
Regardless if they're going to hide every event like it's the end of the world
If I understand that clip I was just saying that the mega Bank
Asteria which involved
I'm going over to force Trump to do the same
So Trump is fighting against the plan by pretending
Because he's a political coward and it doesn't want people to play
And Alex thinks it's good leadership
This really feels like
Wheel spinning
Really decided
I was listening to that
I can't even really
Muster the energy to care
Such a week
Defender 90
I'm just amazed that even in his
Defenses
Trump is a
Like Trump is a giant baby and that's why Alex likes
He's smart enough to take
No blame for the things that he is responsible for is not an endorsement of a candidate
Pixel remember him like Patton
When he needed courage
He summoned
The will to live
So RoboCop's coming
Oh okay
DJ corporate strike
Gangsta people
Rising there
Our
Over you
The shutdown the economy to shutdown the infrastructure
And to drive you into total
Hysterical fear and submission
And if you pass the test and submit properly then you are never going to get out of the handcuffs
This is the new world order this is the technocracy this is robot drones everywhere
Now becoming autonomous with wannabe police controlling them Italy the ruling technocrat
Weather robot armies surveilling and controlling I remember the non-lethal weapons
Honestly that sounds like a libertarian
Tattoos on the scan microchip total tracking
Domination
Absolute Total Control
Because after all
Anydesk
Get rid of the swimming pool that are more than
We have to get rid of
Diving boards
We have to get rid of dodgeball and Chase at the school someone might hit their knees
Albany
The robots will bring us the food and the robots will enforce it like thx-1138
Plan
So that George Lucas movie
Real globalist
So
Alex's Basinger's just on movies
It does seem like he's basing it just on movie
Turns out also British Royals
Maybe even other European
Country
Princess
I've run the miles Elizabeth husband
Farmer
The planet with a bio-weapon
They're in a good place to do it
Albert of Monaco
Thank you
Probably of Monaco
Grace Kelly son
A few weeks ago when they said Tom Hanks had it on that weekend I went live on Sunday and I said I didn't either made up
Orange pr200 from Smyrna
Yes you did say that
Job
Okay
Is discharged from the hospital and went to self isolation back on the 7th
It's funded Alex's digging his heels in on this one doesn't like you test positive or Faking It
Is it is Aegis Elba Faking It
I only got some comments about KY want to know also what good is having the Prince of Monaco fake a Coronavirus
Percent of Alex's audience can't find Monaco on a map
It probably didn't even know it existed 5 minutes ago
Seems like it would be a weird play on the globalist
Spark
This one Bob sure
So Queen Elizabeth's husband is Prince Philip
Philip Was Eighteen and nineteen thirty-nine When The War Began so I have no idea how he could have
Open an SS officer
The prior to World War II
Make some he was the first SSI
Prince Bernhard on the other hand may have been a member of
The group in college
That was claimed in a book but I have a hard time finding concrete confirmation of it
Best possible
I don't need a reason to hate Royal
Prince Philip didn't run his mouth. Wanted to populate the world with iOS
I was just lying about it
The forward to 1987 book called if I were an animal
This was a book where a hundred or so celebrities answer the question of what animals they would like to be
Prince Philip said
I just wonder what it would like
Species
The numbers that it was at the danger of extinction
What would be its feeling
Destroyed the human species
Population
Explode explode
Denied it
Somewhere to exist
I must confess that I'm tempted to ask for reincarnation is a
Particularly deadly virus
That's a little different
Depopulate the world
Not a big fan of details
I would also like a horse
Thank you very much
And I want ice cream
I don't know what quotes Oz talking about with Prince Bernhard but I'm just guessing it's a reference to him funding
The creation of the World Wildlife
Also I don't think Bernhard and Philip are cousins and Bernard's been dead for
So
Slutever
The world
Martial law most people even Alex fans like listen to this
Just go
Man shut up will it will get back to you in better time
This is dumb
No because they don't think
It's very nice
And if you listen like
Why
Why doesn't anyone
Inconsiderate
Everything he talks about is a movie
Yeah the globalist plan is actually thx-1138 have this next clip
Two movies
French face fines and they leave home I'm in coronavirus lockdown as you're prepared to close
I thought you said they were going to go to jail now there's no
Before you know that why are you being like this young
News girl is
Getting home 5 minutes after dark the thugs come around her
Add to pay for this week or bodies
Vortex about
But you want to live like that like says
Wow
Scarface you want to spy on every corner
Alex can't deal with reality that through fiction
This fictional worldview in imaginary
I was expect
Clockwork Orange
Instapop in I was I was thinking we would get some drugs going on but
Honestly
Got got out of left field there
Got out of left field
Yeah these all these movies that are real
Andy talked a little bit here by THX
113 being reality
Eddie veers into how basically science is demon
He's telling people things
Around
Coronavirus can't get you
1138 George
Mukesh made his first come about
Robert Duvall
Amazing actors
World
Talk about the time what they wanted to build
Text Humanity underground to protect them from a bio
And generations later
Your world over by robots in a technotronic Ali
Andaman technotronic plan it's always been at the pointer
Since 1856
Dalton
Course
I had a hallucination going golfing free books
Are the secret government readings
Batesville police
Family
The Blair's revolver little bit that's George Orwell later
Started having hallucinations
And they were told by
How to build all this wow
Scientific
100 years later
Five years later 106 years later
Officially
Tronic scientifically
I do see
Perfect
Did see you again Spire daily indeed yes I am
That I did not know that was Mainline history did they shall train line history when I was going to bust
Mandela effects
Darwin's
They bred humans and aliens and
Stuff we covered in the end
Some of those claims
You can go back in
Hear that stuff you want to there but
This is the sort of stuff that I'm just not even going
Really engage with all too much
Enjoy
If you think that all science came about because
Demons
Contacted hallucinating writers
19th century
And that all makes perfect sense
You and I are just going to be
Charles Darwin do share a grandfather
Eugenicist
So I mean there's some kernels of reality behind so you saying
You know it 2015
Ben Carson told a crowd at a creationist conference
The Darwin's ideas
You know
Give me the real Isis I guess is all like laughable and stuff but this is pretty standard like
Extreme Christian
That's all
So
Alex talks a little bit more about the
These demons that are inspiring scientist
Listen to emails when you're 67 years old
Project
Okay
Yo
You want to tell me
Alex Jones Is Right
About things
You now must
Explain to me that he is right about aliens working
With the globalist
2 Cal
Okay
Alright here we go here we go New York Times just recently published that story saying that the
Maybe in the Pentagon all know about aliens going on right
So that's proof that aliens are real
Step one
Aliens are real
Step2 aliens are communicating with the globalist the globalists are also
Woohoo I have
To prove they are real before we can even go anywhere
So I made
Stock today
Obviously they take
Yeah
Alex
Clairol buddy
He says the Rogan's
Ducted into something
Any ytmp
Don't
Take it I want you to
I'll take the DMT
Believe me
Because if you're not deceive elavegan rough-hewn they're going to try to absolutely
When the guy goes in the other dimension for a second and then they get him for a minute and comes back crazy
They'll just put that Hollywood movies
Yes I do
That's how imaginations work
What's on Netflix
Actually I do that that's great movie dimension
It's like a hundred years at Orchard Road
That's what it's like
It is
You're going somewhere
Berry plays a long clip of Buckaroo Banzai
What's the name of the what's the name of
He was the Starbucks Robocop and in Buckaroo Banzai
Yeah Peter Weller
Yeah I think I'm going to have to watch Peter Weller movies
Also
Remember
That's a backup Matt ask-me-anything
Episode that me and Robert Evans recorded
Alex got one of his question was are you a fan of Buckaroo Banzai
No bulshit and I wanted to play that clip but he's so f***** up and it's really depressing to listen to
Yeah but
Motherfuker
Disgrace
Huge Peter Weller
This is martial law
There will be over
And then you're going to get it big fat depression but don't worry
You going to learn how to make the government
All big box stores stay open you can
In drones flying around already tell you what to do
We tried to stop it
He has no real suggestions for what
Should be done to the measures that
Goodbye States
Even if like
You know California it's
It's an extreme measure
No it's a governor
Martial law
There's no way
No
He gets wants to promote and game
I'm heavy quotes documentary
What is the end game.com what is the end game.com
Dot-com
Amazon ban the sale of it
Amazon banned the sale a few months ago they said it was a racist movie
Amazon just took a game off
Prime presumably because no one was there to begin with
Watch out
I just went over to amazon.com you can buy yourself a nice DVD copy of endgame for six bucks
So it's clearly not
Everybody
He's taking it down
And ourselves
Everywhere they don't want you to any of you seen endgame
You search for endgame Alex Jones on YouTube you'll find multiple channels that have the film poster
What was it 10 years ago
Another 6 years ago
There isn't a big rash people taking endgame.
Bulshit
Rhodes
Roads are coming to kill us all roads I did
Z1 Amazon comment that was like
How do people like
Having that happened by the possible problems like
That's weird
Call are going to call Amazon if you like what the f*** is this
That would be hilarious
Have been red pilled man wasn't
He's going to show up I heard you died
I think that Hulk is going to show up
Kind of looks like Hulk
Got a thick neck
Great
Business
Next caller says something is probably
To the goals
Of Public Health
And Alex does not push back on him at all
Another point
Cole Sprouse
Corona has really blast
Might actually have
I'm sort of Iris in there or
Thanks buddy
You should really share that information with people
Piano
A lot of people are getting hit harder than
And
Because they are
That could be nanotech
Batman
Everything is lining up right now
Those are just a few theories
Can't let people say s*** like that with
No evidence no back
You know what I think
Take the test actually is giving people the virus
Sat is great
You know because what this is going
Me too because he
He just moves on to the
Stop
So that's an irresponsible thing
Listen to this one Turtle as a message of I better not go get tested yet
Some sort of
Symptom
Like this is f******
Crazy
The test will kill you
Test itself
Will give you the virus is maybe the most damaging
Anything that anybody could
Possibly say it's super irresponsible
That is
Then it's just like everybody's trying to kill you dude
Stay inside
Course
You can see it right there it's a total economic takeover us corporations are really globalist allied with China
Using this
Show The Thousands to die every year a week or so
The lovings to get into a pity party the wanting to be a victim of wanting to get a welfare check that wanting to win the
Lottery not all Americans but it's the overall weakness
This situation is talking about weak America
Ken's wanting a pity party and playing the victim
He got a DUI a couple weeks back
I can claim that it
Mockingbird CIA that there articles about it go f*** you
Yourself
Goddamn
Embarrassing embarrassing levels of
Of lack of awareness
The cast comes up now it's
Tim Reames
This guy I guess he's ex-military was formerly employed by Blackwater
Probably as good a time as any to remember that Alex in 2009
They were this is what
Turn around
His career do you hate to Employment Security in heaven
Informer
Kimberly was also a contestant on a reality show called American Tarzan
Anyway this guy use along with Rob do
They recently went down to the border to see if it
It's really close
I have no interest in that segment assault
Just pure xenophobia
Alex tries to prove
To Tim the this virus is man-made
Not the timid disagree
But you just uses in his Elixir to sounding board
J'approve
So here's a just uses two pieces of information
Really nail down
Indian scientist discovered coronavirus engineer with hiv-like insurgent
True genes and proteins signatures
They know it was
It's like ridiculous if you could ask
Self retracted Indians
Where's the next
Lab-made rotavirus triggers debate this is a scientific journal
5 years ago was Obama giving a weaponized virus beside cam
That they cut into it
If you was forced to actually read that article
Do I have to admit that has nothing to do
The debate has nothing to do with Obama selling
Virus de China
Those are the pieces of information that he's able to
He's trying to demonstrate that
The viruses man-made which tells me he has no evidence of that at all
He's full of s***
Yeah this is really
Disheartening
30 tickets
More disheartening
In this last clip
From March 9th
That is Alex
Promoting tomorrow's show
If y'all Chattanooga's Wife on tomorrow really break her Silence about what she thinks is going on break
Freedom fighter
Exact words with za
Big Bowl
Alright
Ted Nugent's wife is finally going to break
The world is with
Clavering today
Ted Nugent's wife
Thinks about all this every morning I walk outside and into the sky ice cream
Lorde
Tell me
WhatsApp
Ted Nugent
White Fang
And we will learn
Once we get to the 20th and potential consequences
Of this fire
Puppies stuck in his office
He knows that they are hyping this up bigger than it is people
So
Terrible
You f***** up
Especially considering
Remember
The last time they a
Set up a story like that
Alex
I just keep thinking about the migrants
Caravan over and over and over again
Saying how dare that they would never
This kind of
It's like you guys win
What's people who did mean
Jade helm
Danger talking about other people engineering
Answer to the fact that he seems think of tens of thousands of deaths
Seems like nobody
That is a good point
Work from home
Sure
This is a globalist
This is teaching you to work from home teaching everybody try
My cell phone to go outside
We talked about China a month ago trying to hold their cell phones where they can leave their houses
Megan Donnelly
Well now
He broke on
Monday
Drudgereport.com pick it up that MIT and villamonte agates have a plan to make you wear a bracelet that changes colors
And a digital tattoo skin the shows you been oculate it
Cell phone
So there's really no resource
On this bill
Gate stuff other than Antarctica
Anonymous quotes
Cybersecurity
Contractor
Suffice it to say that
Literally
And I rejected
Security
That means he knows what Bill and Melinda Gates
Okay well there's a lieutenant colonel
Stuff about the invisible ink tattoo for vaccination records isn't related to
To the Coronavirus
That was a research project that was taking place at MIT previous to all this
Conclusions
Jumping to
This isn't something that's even ready for you
An article in futurism from December 2019 describes it as cool
Proof-of-concept
Human cadaver skin models
The patterns outlasted five years of simulated
Sun exposure
I would assume that it's a goal is maintaining some kind of vaccination record that that's not nearly good enough
To achieve that at
It just may be a ways off from being viable and it's not approved for you
Also it's not Bill Gates
Still wants to use cell phones
The track people
Reporting in the Washington Post
From the 19th
Quote in the United States the White House has been in negotiation with major tech companies
Including Google and Facebook about potentially using aggregated in an itemized location
The Washington Post reported on Tuesday
Is Everett open Kappa largely from
The public that sounds like something that you would want to keep from the
The public you know that
Mass scale surveillance program that you definitely haven't already run
That's something trumpet
Play all these games he wants we're Trump's employees and administration officials to do things
They're not supposed to do according to Alex
Secret deep state music
His hero is the villain in his career
You f****** loves
Yep
So Alex bracelets
Tattoos
Innovative
Viracid what's it say tell them the tracking bracelet digital tattoos
Domino's
So Alex is making up the digital tattoos part of that article about Asian use of innovative
Is an article from the
The Japan times
Yahoo news
Testing out
The medical term
The article is about an
An app that people can download on their smartphone which is
Connected to a bracelet
This is pretty extreme stuff but from the article that only references those bracelets being used it in the case of people who are subject
Compulsory quarantine
Because they had returned from overseas
That's not to say it
But it's not quite as horrendous Alex
They're not kicking down doors
Slamming bracelets
Read this article
That's not something that we can prove using this
Make sure people are
Breaching the quarantine the bear
It's a it's a
LoJack
It again
Turtle tattoos that's not in this article
They just love the market
So Alex gets
Really into Gavin Newsom
California governor
In this side
This episode on the 20th
AMC
He's talking
About how
Press conference where he said that there's martial arts in place right
He's trying to be smooth about it so you go along with it and then
Your dad
Gross kidnapping
Martial law
Socializing
You too hasty
So evil
Very soon
Because it is martial law
You're a kidnapper let's use the microcosm example in a sixteen-year-old girl
Like your Ted Bundy
Volkswagen
It's not the music I want for this
A lot of this patient feels that Dorothy goes I'm going to Portugal in 3 days
I'll get ready to get the hell out of you
So the first point and that should be probably obvious Alex
Governor Newsom setting
Press conference
He was saying the Barcelona is not necessary at this point
Actor people are stepping up
We'll play the clip that Alex plays
Text Colette
So that's all bulshit
But
I wanted to talk about Alex
Is kidnapping metaphor
He loves telling that little story
Like a legitimately does that bit all the time
Duxbury kidnapper threatening
Kill you
You put on handcuffs
If you put on handcuffs
8 Define metaphor in all
But I have a different one that might be more appropriate
Alex
I would suggest that this is more like taking your dog to the vet
Your dog is a stupid a******* that doesn't understand better soon
But it still suffers for medical issues and you know what that dogs medical issues are going to affect other people other than
And other dogs
You know whatever because you ignore dogs health and then problem
Expensive surgery
Or because the dog has it
A condition that can transmit to another dog
Dog has to be taken care of
And it's too f****** stupid to do it on its own
In case you don't get it so mean
Alex
You'll fight
Barking
Maybe even try to bite
But it's for his own good
And everyone else is on my dogs
Are not stupid
How dare you
Call me and say we got to go to the vet I seen your dog s*** on the wood floor
That is true forced into a FEMA camp Arizona
When the state isn't acting certain measures that are necessary to stop the spread
He's the dog in the backseat on the way to work
You just need to ignore his stupid meaning was barking
Then that's all the
Better metaphors
That's a pretty good
So here is that clip of
The owners of Illinois in Ohio
Exercise because we get caught up in
Because
Date we haven't needed to do that
We said our guidance those guidance
I just been mad and every circumstance
In the past if you want to establish
Martial law
Is Ultimate of
Portsmouth
Have the capacity to do that
We are not at this moment
Billy Madison cesta and assess Adidas
That people do not socialize
And support
It's very directed guidance
I would be surprised
And we have all the confidence it will be
That's not insane
At this point people are going along with the recommendations there is no need for us
Force things gas
So
That's pretty much the
Complete opposite of what Alex is trying to
That's it
If you are the globalist
Why wouldn't you take this opportunity to declare martial law win even the reporters like
Do you think you should
Declare martial law
Suggesting that it is on the table other states
Start taking
Slightly more drastic and Emporium
It measures not declaring martial law
Something is the exact
So Alex
March 20th episode
I think I've used
Discovered the Cure
Okay
A
Inexpensive malaria drug
Is having incredible effects on people
Debit card
Forwarded to like roll
I got a bunch of Articles and studies in
Porch
NCH Lora
Quien
Didn't even spell it right
Maybe highly effective against coronavirus that was
Days ago they're going to pay my waist again I will guess
What
When does according to the literature
Bushes
Do not
LaSalle's
Can there
The viruses replicate
Michelle's is it
Interesting
Just like nano silver
You insane persons security
Shell
Viruses can't get in
Also fries
Paige angry do York attorney general
Stupid to live
To eat can't control himself
Nuts app
Around over the weekend this episode
On September
On Saturday retweeted tweet that cited a French study claiming to show that hydroxychloroquine
Is it
Effective in treating
Covid-19
This led to some scientists driving in avoiding out that the
The study itself is
Very poorly
Constructed
Super very small to the point of being ink
You can close it
America works
Jared Holt pointed out that the account that Trump retweeted was actually a guy
Used to go by the name Mike toks
Baked Alaska
He was even covered in an article in the guardian about the Figures were putting together that alt right rally in Portland back
In 2017
Can't imagine why he would be in
In Trump's orbit
A number of doctors pointed out that advising people to take hydroxy
Could actually result in heart
Greg Connecticut worse why do we have this
Oh my God world
After Trump's tweet Bloomberg reported on how is Nigeria there were two cases of corquin poisoning
After United States
President Donald Trump Coronavirus
God
I was worried that Alex's talked about the drug predated trumps
S*** about chloroquine
On Thursday
When he lied about it being FDA-approved 23 Coronavirus
That's probably what Alex was gone
Anyway
It's all the way Reckless now
Amarillo
Describe the level of Despair I feel seeing this particular little chapter play out in
On the larger radar
The FDA approved in the medication for a panther
Twitter the guy who hangs out with Nazis
Turning an ink
Some study that led to spike
Medication
At least two overdoses in Nigeria
And it's not that big a story
I just
I just can't
Imagine if Obama
Did any
Did we would be arrested Federal Building can you blowing up
For murder
Wow
Order to sell his own s***
Listen to that further appointment
The alcohol
They are using a nano silver
Biotech Labs on the Wii U
Not advertising it
Something that is a treatment or defense it's it's sold as a tooth whitening toothpaste
You're doing it again
What are you doing
Stop
I'm saying I'm not silly
Cures Coronavirus
But it's just toothpaste that I'm selling for
Purpose
The ingredients
Defensive about people calling about for that and so like you can't show
The New York attorney general's office will take notice
It's Not Over
Silver
Alex now has the cork
Angle
How can I make money off of
Guess what has a whole bunch of zinc
The real red pill
Belviq stimulant in it
So Alex only brought up a cork one thing because you read the word zinc
Find about it
To pretend that the real red pill that has zinc in it
What foods have zinc
Go eat some beef or baked beans
No but the red pill will actually push
The zinc inside
Okay well it's eyrise
This opinion taxes as an ionosphere
Which allows extra zinc
To enter the cell
It doesn't have zinc itself so 4 oz promotion here to make sense you would really be needing to try to sell as audiences
The real red pill and also say
Chloroquine
That's really irresponsible stuff
And you can just see the levels
Layers of profiteering
That's that's
It's as soon as something becomes relevant
He tries to sell it
If you go to the website there's a big banner that says
Your daily routine
Advertising the real red pill
He knows no bottom to the scam
You will make whatever money can buy jeopardizing his audience
As well being
Because he doesn't give a single s***
Elizabeth
This is just stop
F******
Is sold out everywhere
Vitamin C
It's sold out everywhere
Portland
Guess what we've got in stock
Sellout just a few weeks
Now it's only 20% off
50% off
Right now I said I wouldn't ever send off in the new year I haven't done it yet
I'm doing it now 50% off on Railroad bill
You can find
NSYNC on Amazon
Pretty
Disgusting is that
Feather
I don't know I like
Group social shaving for this Behavior cuz
Maybe just everyone
One tomato that they have to throw it out
So I look as bad as that is
That's terrible and I believe that
Cuz
Right well I need to know somebody
Is breaking their
That's not yet
Because I don't actually has a
Pretty good position
RV insider trading
It's happening
It's bad yes
Good
Republican and Democrat
Office
What
Classified briefing on Coronavirus
Add
It was
Russian agent
Add
Every
Damn one of them
Yes I agree Republican or Democrat
You go dump your stock it's called in cider trade
Stick a fork in them
Don't you know those three Republicans vote for impeachment
Don't you know now there's going to be a new impeachment, that's all you know it's coming
4 months
That speaking
Ian
The top
Sure
Against President Trump
You can see how old is she
Alex lost me in the middle
Caught for insider trading will not be asked
Blackmailed into
Yes got you and it only takes three Republicans to successfully remove
Alex's Affion number
We're all these people in Congress to be treated equally resign
It's this is actually a case of insider trading
Appears to be
I don't think you'd have that position if one of them was
Jim Jordan that's that's of counterfactual I can't really prove that that's true but
However
Alex doesn't seem to know who the Republican ones are
And Dianne Feinstein's only name even brings up
You also doesn't even seem to know that it's
Old Republic
And then Diane
The only Democrat
He's trying to make it seem like it's equal it's all
Three Republicans also also Republicans
Look they're cheaters and Traders in their awful
Also has a Chinese
Also I know.
Trump narrative is so goddamn boring now because she has to leave
Do the endpoint of taking out Trump
It feels like a sitcom that's like an
Season 10 where the writing is just lazy
Come on can you just be
Interesting
Weird
Tennessee
Everything is just like yes secretly trying to
Trump is doing a bad job
Ross
Raw is terrible
He's the worst he's actually literally killing people
Great job
And your show is boring
Great job just not do this
Yeah it sucks but in this next book so I know it's
Anthony
Same ones that run the show
We're getting good guide
Fauci
Saddles up sidles up
And says
You're all dead you say that
Sterling today
This is so f****** funny
Stay focused on responding
In front of them and it's going great he's behaving like a responsible grown-up
That's really pissing off Alex
Because he wants to have fun y'all conspiracy
But because I listen to Alex's show I remember that Alex fauci was back on February
What Alex misread headline and decided to report to Anthony fauci
I'm coming out at Trump's fast and saying that they believe the virus was man made
Yes of course with a load of bulshit but it led to Alex saying which is really funny
Now it's
The president for his
Mulatto calls
I know he was
Legend
Looked into falchi made some calls
Nothing is real
Nothing is
It makes you more able to accept
They were about to listen to Ted Nugent's wife
Why not
I couldn't get anywhere but wouldn't I have to listen to Ted Nugent's wife
The coronavirus and what's going on
And I started
To do some research on the password
To find out what
What's really going on
Crap out of me
So
Miss Nugent
I've done some research
She has a Chrome browser than I assumed
You know
You would maybe assume that his wife isn't maybe the best
Source of research about
The Coronavirus
Has some.
From you on the medical field
What do you think it's coming from what do you think's going to happen
I don't know is shemane Nugent is a respected name of the field of research or anything like that
She's mostly relevant cuz she's Ted's
Your website into Zumba and some years back she got sick because
Encourage her to get into alternative medicine
Anthony fauci basically at the same resumes
Zumba instructor big red flag on her website for me was her educational record
She has a bachelor's in radio TV and film because she met Ted when she was working
Detroit radio
She also claims to have a masters in betta fish
Switch izibor problems metaphysics
Yeah okay I noticed that you didn't say where either of these degrees are from
Because probably you know
Metaphysics
Degrees from scammy diploma Bell
Real accredited universities do not offer degrees in Menifee
When someone has a degree in metaphysics on the resume
Other educational background
And isn't in some other solid form of philosophy or maybe theology
It's a major sign
Butterface
What is a real branch of philosophy but it's
Something universities give degrees
It's the same thing with most branches
Philosophy
If I pursued a philosophy major instead of a minor in college
I would have
A bachelor's degree in philosophy
Not in the lodge
Emphasis in logic
Degree in logic
She's written
Free books
What is gold
Which of the wild game cookbook she wrote with Ted
Very rich
Researcher Dan others called married to
What better research is there for a book like that then actually marrying a rockstar
Rock and roll your way to Happy
Being married to a famous rock and roll
4 minutes is all you need to do good research
She's also currently making a documentary called killer house
Switch about toxic mold
Also in 2013 she was arrested for having a 38 caliber handgun in a carry-on bag when she tried to board a plane and
Was loaded but shamaine claimed that you had no idea I was in her bag
Nothing says responsible gun ownership than not knowing where your loaded gun
That's the games that remain like to play with each other you know like
Oru leaving the country perhaps international travel allowed just going to speak a little loaded weapon in your luggage
I can find no evidence that you should be treated as an expert in anything nor should her Research into the Coronavirus
Alex's weird pervert hero Ted Nugent
Great
We live in strange times
So you know this
Theories going around
Cover
For Trump to
Mop up the
Why would those theories
Suggest
Use the virus against Trump
Deep State both sides
This is
Preordained
Evolution this is unlike
2 biblical
Proportion
Had to unravel the way
What's really weird is there's a lot of talk invagen simulations of this being sort of biblical and
WYD
Don't they bring up the local
Play clean never bring up the local seleucus Arturo
Victor trying to pitch this like this is revelation
Why not bring up
There's also Locust
Too real
Everytime I read that news I swear to God I've read
That same news like 30 times and every time I immediately forget it because of likes
No I just refuse to believe that there's
Locus I refuse to believe there's a plague of locusts
How old is a plague of locusts
Right now
You think
It fits right in with their rhetoric
Willits
Conspicuous
Too on the nose
Alex
Talking about the mopping up the Deep State thing that's a cute
Yeah yeah
Narratives it's put out by qanon
Guess what shamaine likes qanon
I do believe that there is an orchestrated group of individuals
Some people have called
Choo-Choo have been dropping breadcrumbs so to speak
For Those About to
My people to do the research
Themselves
Sequoia research qanon
You're Googling weird article
Due diligence
For themselves
No
Does try to get
Alex to do
Exercise
Never done before on your show
Voicemail
I want to take a deep breath
Okay
You know what you know what Alex Pearson
We don't really know for sure what
Piece of information
More qanon language
Yep she's super into qanon
Interviewee
And Alex until kind of like is it
Yes too many questions it's going to get into her promoting q and she hasn't stated position of hating Q earlier they had
The day before
Consistently so he doesn't want to yell and make
Fun of Ted Nugent's wife keep Ted Nugent his friend
So you keep surviving
To live in the woods
Okay anyway Alex Lorenz interview
It's like an hour
That can't be real
Say on Fox News
I want to I want to I want the world to know what the nuge thinks they might
So anyway Alex gets into weird head space after the interview
He starts talking about the movie Rollerball
Rollerball is real
Globalism was about being able to show countries off because everybody was interdependent
Tell they made an incredible movie back in the 70s with James Caan rollerblade
Rollerblade
Watch Amazon TV
Like the early 80s
My dad going to bring me brazinski but when you get on up son some movies about what they plan to shut
So
You got to get rid of that Dad get a new one
Get a new one call someone right now
Hey eight-year-old son rollerball is real
Your old son
I got a brazinski book for you to read
But this industry thought Alex really legitimately seems to think they in the same way thx-1138 is real so is real
Call
World famous superstar top roller baller
The Lord of old to take your wife or your daughter from
Trying to find files about other corporations over and there's this one big Mainframe liquid computer
He goes to the computer
They got rid of all the books that got
While everything was available on this worldwide computer system call the internet
AI computer
That sounds like a good plot of a boot
You guys yes he categorizes things and then he loses them
Cloud lost now
Volume
Telling you everything
Yeah God
So many movie
He's playing a clip
Rollerball
And he's asking them to back it up with audio
Just in case
The cloud loses it
We need a physical copy of this
Text Woody saying
Movie titles that I think might come up later I got I got Logan
Run going on their husband
Is it Logan's Run I can't remember I think Blade Runner Blade Runner okay
Probably is going to be real
I wrote down running man but I don't think he would reference that one
I thought he would just hate
Arnold Schwarzenegger Total Recall
Okay Total Recall the good ones talked about
Oh hell yeah
Hell yeah
Market
Ifucking can't wait for like
Him to run out of Philip K Dick's related movies
You're right
How far how far is Augusta
You see someone with a hat
Now
Give me a people have to go through doors in like the movie bright
Starring Will Smith butt
Hear me up
No but you were at the game
Supposed to be Filipino
So Alex wants to take some calls
Towards the end of the 20th episode
Call
Specific sort of caught
I know you're busy.
You have specific
Voicecomm
Space command
Central Command
Army Special Operations
State Police
What you been prepped and ready for
Also Ted Nugent's wife
I want you to call him we'll talk about it
Alex Trebek call for collars from height until areas
Because he wants
What they're hearing
That's great
But I highly doubt any one of those areas is likely to call even less likely
Somebody private information on Alex's dump show
This is
It's not actually a plea for intelligence people in the audience
Call Lynn
In function this is Alex signaling to the audience
If they call in and claim to be until the
You going to let them
He won't question them and is willing to take at face value all the information the audience
It's my present as appearing a fish
Basically what he's doing is establishing an improv
He's inviting people to Lark with
That is it
The first line in proxy
Anyway
It calls for a while
Not getting any calls
Or maybe he's just
Plenty of evidence
Sorry starts rambling
One is super deadly compared to the other Buddies
The other is not
The medical workers the police the military rest of the last episode
Strains of the virus start
Something you made up
Is rambling talkingshit
Bring talkingshit this stuff you saying about two strains
Is not something that is a scientific
There is preliminary research
It suggested there's what
Call the Estrella
What is the ancestral strain
The original one that jump
A human from animal to Human
What are some point mutated into
BL strain
Which appears to be better adapted
Jump from humor
Cuba
When's coldy more aggressive strain
This is a reference to its ability to
The transmitted from person
Person not because it causes a more severe
The guardian reported on March 11th that it is not yet clear whether the
The two strains cause different severity of
I was just heard a few words like more aggressive
Listen to strains
And he's just a story about his needs
Whether or not studies do eventually show that there are in fact 22
Distinct strains of the virus
And that one causes more severe illness
It doesn't matter
Right now Alex is just making sure.
It feels a little bit like
Our language
Itself is
At fault for so much
This information just like
When you say oh it's
Progressive
Epidemiologist that means one
And for people who are deaf
That seems to mean a completely
Different things
A perfect example is every single time out use that line
About the gain a function study on the Coronavirus
Causing
Right
Is perfect
We accurate also when I
Perfectly fits his propaganda Barrett it's almost like they should have
2 makeup
Sleep random nonsense
Since words in order to describe
Likes instead of calling it a gain of function it's a
Flip flop
Like that's the only way that people won't confuse it for both I don't feel like it's the X
Experts responsibility to
Adapt their behavior to propagandist
Wow theranos
So Alex
Tim selling his zinc
She's pushing a bit now
Alex is kind of bad
The media
It's saying there's going to be a lot of deaths
You just said there was going to be a lot of death you might believe that yes
Lost in the cloud
Play I didn't feel that clip
Rollerball
Everyone runs in fear
No evidence of
So the media isn't saying there's going to be three million deaths in the United States from Coronavirus
You're covering the March 16th
Report from Imperial College the estimated that is literally nothing was done
It could result in 2.2 million
In 510,000
And the United Kingdom
Practice is this prediction by saying
In the unlikely apps
Any control measures or spontaneous
Individual Behavior
So that's kind of a setup it's Bianna likely nothing is done
Alex and Mike Adams
Misused Imperial College estimates
The past
About 50,000 new cases a day and sign up
Felicia be totally on board for
Except now
Play the virus or something
Just the media's being hysterical
Fortunately I listen to Alex's show
Pentagon
With the numbers they have
That they could out of 23 million dead people
In the next 6 months here in the United States from the Coronavirus
Typical for a flu
2% comes out
3 million dead
Americans
I mean I might have a
Once a year or something
Other business
Tried to leave the work
My wife
She called because I don't travel anymore he's saying
The Pentagon
They're going to kill you and your family
Most of us are already dead
Will be getting cancer said we'll all be sterile soon it's over
Survivors
CPAs man
I decided that my new signature B
A supercar
Completely
Hysterical fruit bread and butter
Dick that
This is abuse
Yeah I feel
This show is f****** nuts
Nothing is real
Not even from day-to-day from
H h
Important to know Jordan
Lost a million
And don't worry about it it's sad and it was not good but
The Great Depression
7 million + 7 million
Death from malnutrition Great Depression
7 million people
In the 10-year Great Depression
11 year Great Depression ended up
So
That is not good and the food can run outside
And then fall down the stairs break your neck
What we're getting into it
And the fear
This is so wild
Starving
He has the operators try to find a citation for
It look what happened
There is famine field 7 million people in USA
That's
Pravda. Russia
Chicago
But
Chicago study
Maybe not but just some other sources
Sabores for assault
You know you know how people know
About how many people who starve to death
Russia
You know how late we know about it like a famous thing that we know right cuz it's historically
Now don't you think that is a similar number number of people had started out here we wouldn't
Just finding out about it from Alex Jones
Pretty sure that would be a
Thing that we are taught not cuz the globalist
Oh okay
Rollerball
Let's go to Segal's
And
He get the caller
That wants to give him a sizing strategy and how to how to
Alex I'd like to help you commit a crime
I'd like to help you Market your brand
So much for taking my call real quick I want to tell all your viewers to do what I've done and that's
$10
I got a yard sale
Spray paint
Covid-19
13841 sign
Infowars.com on the other
Hold you already have more time but I've been thinking about having callers
I don't have it
Covid-19 just nailed it
Another caller calls in later is IQ close on that one but it should be covid-19
1984 good punch at buddy good punch up
The answer to 1984 is
Covid-19 84
I hate to call pawn shop
A little less cuz at least that was a good suggestion
In the realm we were talking about that sign that is
That is a better say
So this collar because he's giving Alex a market
Opera opportunities
Please get to say something stupid
Hang on line until he gets
Give a completely baseless.
Makes no sense
One more major point
Do you remember the Las Vegas shooting
Back in October
Yes I do
Okay if you remember Trump
Expected March of 19
Me and we started learning
So it's all connected hours cuz they didn't want you to be able to get
Chip repair
The martial law
Why do this
Prince very future
Oh yes
Bump stocks
Crucial element of surviving
Going to urinate
Alex
I would love
For there just
Come like
A moment where Alex has a break and you just like
Stupid
We're trying to create panic and we're trying to
I love all this
Spear Gray
I love conspiracies
I would love anything
It gives a different narrative about the Las Vegas shooting
You are.
Yeah you wanted to have that happy Billy Madison MoMA
Wasted everybody's
Retirement may God have mercy on your soul
That kind of
Or even like I've listened to a number of episodes of Bill Cooper show where he talks to collars and he's like
Do you have no
Like if you will just push back on people I want Alex
I know that you never do it because
It would hurt his ability
Key people in the fold and tell them stupid
But like I would love it if you did
Tee-off on somebody's a******
I don't hate them cuz they're.
These things that they're saying
Some of them are like legitimately publicly dangerous
To be so good
That's what the government's after
So this guy obviously
Not a high-level intelligence
It doesn't seem
Have one on the phone
We had
Robert Cerrone
You're not giving out the secret information
We've already in a form of martial law
The corporation's by the Democrats Terraria
Took the driving point of Alex's coverage in
These couple of days is definitely that Barcelona is already
Globalist
Doing it
On the one hand this is a message for Alex
Because he's always been
I'm pretty clear than martial law is happening
Time start a Revolutionary War
But leaving that aside there's another really serious problem look what Alex
Beyblade suggest
Left is responsible for making these martial law
Explains new reporting
Politico reported on Saturday that Trump
Department of Justice run by his good buddy Bill Barr
We asked Congress for the ability to ask chief judge
Judges
Do detain people indefinitely without trial during a bird
It's really stag
Global control the.
Political politically
In what are the documents the department
Proposed the Congress Grant the attorney general power to
The chief
District Court
Pause Corp
Proceedings whenever the district court is full
We are partially closed by virtue of any natural disasters civil disobedience
Or other
Situation
Also from that article
Violation
Pre-arrest said Norman
The executive director of the National Association of criminal defense lawyers
So that means you'd be arrested and never brought before a judge
Until they decide that the emerging
You're the civil disobedience is over
I find it absolutely.
Especially in a time of emergency
We should be very careful about granting new powers to the government
Jones
The champion of civil liberties
Not likely
The story
He wants Trump to become a dictator
He's been very clear about
Alex's care about civil liberties for their own say
Means to an end
It was an issue that was Central to the popularity of people like Ron Paul
So we had to push it really hard
It's always been a trojan horse
In circumstances like these are really big
Just dropping the mass
If Alex doesn't come out in immediately
Wheatley reverse course
On Trump
Africa's Department of just
This is asking for the power to
Team people
Indefinitely without trial
He should f****** throw in the towel on everything
He's overprotective
The stand for
Because that s*** is
We'll see I'm in that happened on Saturday
Friday's episodes
But it's it's it's
Comical the idea that he's trying to say that the globalist in the left is doing all this stuff
Trump is a heretic
There's all of these instance
Exact thing
Normally would be scream
Yep
You haven't used the villain of Alex's story
Absolutely
It is
It is amazing to me exactly how much Trump is doing what
They said Obama was doing
And loss
Masterminds
I still don't think
That even if Trump does
All the negative things he may do
He automatically becomes king and all the Senators become Duke
That might be true that might beat Rodin you don't know you have a replica
Constitution it's too big
I do believe it's impossible to read the whole thing
What science
So Alex talks about Hobbies play backflip
Tanaka show
Eye clinics in California during lockdown the governor is basically under martial law
Annabelle
Honey
Yonder martial law honey time.
Yeah I mean he's played the clip but it doesn't say what
You say
He's misrepresenting
Newsom into a misogynist
Somehow as well
Yeah
So Mike Adams comes on
Mike Adams I think actually has a pretty interesting
Position at this
Almost anything
Thank you saying but he does believe that these quarantine things
Are necessary
So he is at least at
The point of
Like
He seems to have
A pushing
Pulga
I'm fine with
But I don't want to
The thing is
Prepare to fight
Civil liberties
The lockdown and isolation that is medically
Eeyore epidemiological
That is not what that is
Necessary
BNA really really bad situation about the virus which I appreciate
Now he's also saying that we need
To protect our civil liberties
Course of that
Response to that would be
Go talk to Trump
No stick
At the same time
That is a
Relevant conversation
The tension
And the
Maintaining civil liberties while at the
Same time
This necessary
Right right I will open
Except that conversation
The difficulties in finding a solution or conclusion
Maybe we can all feel comfortable with
From anybody
But anyone who's ever been on it for
Exactly do not have the credibility from the conversation
From the
Pulsed absolute
I do appreciate
Micah saying if this is necessary
Because
In the world of Infowars assholes
That is monumental
So I was going to say the one person that I really don't want to hear from
That's right now
More so than Alex
Is Mike Adams
And somehow he's the one who has
I mean I mean
This particular thing he says
Yeah
Eclipse today
From March 20th episode
Equally wrong
Ocala My Confession in my my
All of this
Is I have vastly understated the
The criticality
It's over for Humanity
Only be Lone Survivor
That's understated I'd say that's a shot
No Chaser understand
Alright okay
So we come to the end of this and I think that Alex is
I think the theme
You know it's not as painful as I expect
Subway
There's a lot of this stuff that is like
Sniff people
If you can listen to this as opposed to experts their run the risk of stymieing the efforts of
The country
Getting through this successfully
But
There's also a lot of stupid s*** along the way
Do you know I can always
Enjoy finding that Alex said that this 7 billion people start comes from
A Pravda trying to just
Notify Sylvia
I read about it from the University of
Appreciate little things like that
Overwhelming
Bottom line is the reason you think
The globalist
Just released this virus
Is too because they wanted to destroy the economy to Bears Trump
Only defense you can ever get for that
F****** Bill Maher
That's fun to think about
Alex thinks that every single goddamn movie is real
Especially
Rollerball
Death Race 2
Desperate
With adjacent
We got to do there are hard
Hitting questions that we need
Tweet about Jason Statham's entire career
But
I hope everyone out there is doing alright
Circumstances
I don't know
Style 2
Or anything but hope you take care of yourselves and each other
Appreciate all the messages that we received
Okay here in Chicago for the time being
Girls on Twitter
We are on Facebook
The whole thing
Leo
Dzx Clark
The juiciest Ice Cube
Holding