Damn important sweat it
I have great respect for its knowledge by now I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Dollartree.com
Hey everybody welcome back to the fight knowledge I'm Jordan
This is a podcast where I start making up nonsense about people and we see what
What happened okay
Hi Jordan
I got a question for you what's that
What is your thing for the day that is brightening your spirits in this trying time we all find ourselves
Are you I have been
It is
Good to spend time with my partner
I love her very much
Cheese
Kinda you know we're all kind of getting used to this
Circumstance by
Having her
Has really made this a lot
Lot easier
How about you happy for you
Emotionally resonant I stumbled across some videos on YouTube
Motocross videos
On YouTube by this this pro skateboarder from
Jonny Giger
Okay and what are you does is a series of videos where he he's a professional skateboarders
Okay he's trying to recreate the tricks that Rodney Mullen did these really gif
Difficult tricks
From my classic skate videos to do them himself
And I I find them so
Endearing
Seems like a pretty cool guy is good bright personality
And one of the things I really like about these videos is that
The really a celebration of process
Okay you see him fail like repeatedly
I like trying to figure out how to do the trick
It was like a long learning curve through it and then the eventual payoff of
Hard work
Love
You know winning out and he does the tricks right so it's going to be impossible to write
Right and perseverance pushing through when you fall over and over and over and over and over again
The other thing too
Is like through that failure you see the
The incremental progress
You see you like oh that little part of the trick he's figured out now how to do that still falling at the end
Brighton
Really I really enjoy it
Just posted the successful trip
He probably would have gotten a s*** ton of use out of that people watch all those little Clips at on your way better in the
Structure
And enjoyed it's been night it's like outdoors and Switzerland gorgeous it looks nice
Music
I've no idea who this dude is I never heard of him until a couple days ago but I can't stop watching these videos
We tried to recreate these tricks
That's really cool
Shout out to Jonny Giger do you know him
That's a different place. I don't know what that means
That's my bad
Yeah that's alright
Anyways
Dan I've taken over
Yep that's true doing a reverse fight knowledge episode
And I figured
That since we talked almost done I'm done with Marc Moreno by the way
Before you do we have to take a moment to say thank you supposed to sign up in
Spartacus show
Lot of nickel a lot of initials on this episode
The first Anthony G Thang as much here now probably want
Joe are thinking about you and I'll follow the walk
Journal policy wonk
Next AKA thank you so much
Chanel policy want
AK University
Next Michael G thank you so much you know about what they want
I'm a policy wonk
I just learned as a man posted that Rodger stone is on Cameo and
If you can pay him to record those messages
Very close
It's over for Humanity
I've been trying to think of what I would want Rodger Stone to say and it's
You know I feel like there's already a body of a lot of things I want to hear it
I think I would just want to have him read a list of words
Just like completely out of
Poopy pants
I just enjoy it I would love
I think I might end up
And I can't justify that furniture.
Thank you so much
Arbonne
You are now ecology walk
Website dollartree.com
Here we go
This is your third
Listen to of them have been complaining about Marc Martel
Expecting that that's what you're going to talk about and honestly name
I have no idea what you're about to tell me about
Here is here's what I want to talk about since we have talked to almost exclusively about people who
Who either
Don't believe in what they're saying
Maybe believe in what they're saying but either way are acting completely differently and then what the
I wanted to see what would happen if we talked about people who actually believe what they're taught
I also I see your name
And here and I hope it's who I think it is but I'm sure it's not
Might as well go ahead and play
Okay you know we're talkin about
I'm not entirely sure I'm a night that he has the voice of the televangelist he is a televangelist
I went the opposite direction with this day actually believe what they say I thought you meant it was someone who has a good
Absolutely no I thought this was going to be like an uplifting these people are
Not sure who this fella is
I know it's not Pat Robertson
I know it's not Jack Van Impe
I don't know
It is Robert Jeffers okay I heard that name of that guy
Baptist Church of Dallas
And I
I started looking into him because I wanted to talk about
Religion or something along those lines I was looking for something to talk about
And I have this idea of what if we
What are we talking about if we
We talked about somebody who believes weather
So when I talk about belief I don't know if dr. Robert Jeffers or any I'm going to talk about a few televangelists
I don't know if they actually in their heart of hearts believe this b*******
But the guys that I am going to talk about have all actually live
Their lives
According to these
So
All the time
Sort of like Bill Cooper
Dying the way he did
Kind of
Indication of living by the things I don't know if they believe it or not but they are
Professional believer
Walking the walk
Every single day they are paid to wake up
And acts as though they are
The most Christian people in the world and that's that's what they do
So as far as
Belief goes that's what I'm talkin
Talking about knots do they think that is
It's 104
All right and I'm talking about specifically dr. Robert Jeffers
Is a Fox News
He is the TV Guide that you go to if you want
Any defense of trump
From any religion any attack
He will defend Trump doing
There's a lot of religious folks has less toxicity to him then like Jim Bakker
Okay absolutely you can slot him in on a TV show
Color clean
I've researched this guy for like the past 2 days Non-Stop
And by all accounts
He is an incredibly sweet
Nice kind human being
Who has the most
Vicious awful
Thoughts and like
He has Charmed journalists after
The journalist was Gone with him
Like I'm going to work with a guy named Michael Muhney
A lot of his work and he's
Basically like lived with Jeffers for a while to see what's going on
Do you know where you get that sense from like what does Louis Theroux documentaries he goes in the
Like all these people are terrible but some of them are kind of nice to write
This guy is a
Sleep cycle
Like what these televangelists do is
TV
Like they do it
Cuz they're good at
You guys aren't like guys who love the Griff
They're like like Alex is like a kamikaze
Hustling all the
Trying to sneak onto gigs trying to find every possible way
Selling merch after the shows that kind of stuff
The televangelist that I'm talking about are more like
They're just really talented performers I didn't want the spotlight Zach
They're really good at and they're paid because they're talented performer
To your point though
I think the Alex
Primarily is only grinding and selling merch after the shows because he was pursuing the Limelight
Overextended himself to the point where he now has a giant Studio
That's probably true of a functional thing probably would be
As
Like attention grabby
As far as that goes that's it that's an interesting question except these guys are the ones who took the steps that get you there
Alex
So he was
That's probably true maybe I'll douching for a movie The Devil like
Mark Dice
Yeah I mean this guy is the guy who goes on Fox News and says Democrats worship Satan Mormonism is a cult
Got do a huge fight with Mitt Romney in 2008 because he said that Mormons were a cult and we could never vote for him
Jon Huntsman was a better Mormon exactly Steve song Steve
Vote for Mitt Romney
Is that car
And like all the televangelists he's written
A ridiculous number of book
Books that
I don't think anybody reads
Ever had one of those like a bulk purchases thing
Not clickbait titles like the most recent one is courageous
10 strategies for thriving in a hostile world
Then there's how can I know answers to Life's 7 most important question
Or God 7 secrets for success
Something like
Nobody's Renminbi Habits of Highly Effective People almost exactly I don't think anybody is ready
And all televangelists right this the exact same book
I bet I will have read it and I bet their Church small groups
I bet that certain groups
Churches like to get together and have a book study
Well and he's he's the pastor of a megachurch so he does have a captive audience there where it's like he can he owns the printing
Press the princess books
Sells them to the people who
Work at the printing press
That kind of thinks good good grip
Good
So I I wanted to find out where this dude comes
And as far as his early life there's really not much
Detail going on the biography that you keep getting his
Jeffrey's was Jeffers was raised in Dallas
At the age of seven who joined the First Baptist Church of Dallas
He was saved by
OT 64 now
So that puts us at
Houston Auto 7 years ago
So how long was he in Dallas
His whole career know not his whole career he was Raising Dallas up to Hills overlap with Alice
Either
He's raising Dallas he goes to Baylor
So he's either Waco guy
This dude is First Baptist
All the way
And he was saved by legendary televangelists
Benny Hinn wa Criswell
The guy who established
Turn to the First Baptist Church of Dallas into basically the 1st
Megachurch
And
I love you
Here's a little bit of crazy
We have a full program tonight
Shall We Begin
On the car
Liberalism
Sure that's how he starts
There you go
That's that's basically what we're talking about when you get down to it
And Criswell is
Like one of the biggest
Televangelists
And he's got that southern baptist tradition
That I absolutely
Mystify but I like I love it I really do I love listening to Southern Baptist preacher
As an energy to just just listen to him tell a story
Oklahoma and Texas play football
In the Cotton Bowl
I got it I got to stop already
Wear it in front of me
What's an Oklahoma fan
All about horse
Where he was
Didn't have any takers shutdown after
Nobody
He-Man
Ingeteam
Sounds like a little plumber sign became so sweet
That's very very Dusty Rhodes
Yeah is your name yelling about hard times
Daddy you putting up the road through some hard times
I'll times
Oh yeah but that is like
The good version of it
You do kind of scary preachers it's a bummer because it is a really infectious seductive
A manner of speaking
When is the pro wrestler who is the American dream
Perfect maybe his belly is a little too big maybe tiny little too big doesn't look like the athletes of the day but you know
No brother he's bad and they know he's bad and Ric Flair
Now you see why it's
Yeah it's so fun
It's almost in your DNA. Kind of like it's really
The Tent Revival in the world
I grew up in
Church background my family is a cult
Increase well was absolutely
In fact
Billy Graham was a member of Chris Wells Church
Like he brought Billy Graham into the fold and then I went to turn heel
I think Billy Graham might actually tried to put up the
Maybe try to get more watch
So yeah so griswell
Creates the modern maggots
Basically
And he's doing this
To build a
Compound
He is not building a megachurch he's building like 80
Sweet fertilization Baker's Morningside Zack
Jim Bakker
Is a fan of Criswell
But this is from
To give you an idea this guy is creating a Christian separatist
Compound essentially and this is from a sermon he gave in the
Christian education is education and environment of the mind and heart and will of our blessed
Lord it isn't inst
Tuschen it's a school where the faculty and the administration and the trustees and the classes in the environment and
Most of the student body are all Chris
I don't know why I said most
51 doll of Idaho Drive
Putting most in there seems so ridiculous to me in a couple non-christians in order for there to be game
Yeah like 5% non-Christian
End of the term
The 97%
Voted for me where you need
To keep things interesting that he's turning the school into a into a
The Most Dangerous Game
Spiritually I know from my time at a Baptist mega church that a lot of the
Thing that seem to animate
The faith
Folks within the church evangelism part of it really seemed
To give it meaning
So I would believe it if you wanted to create this
Christian only environment in your someone like this guy
You let in five 8% non-Christian
In order to give people
Convert you got to have somebody to chase feeding pets
Well I mean there's a certain section of the the student body that's probably going to need that I'll record dealers snakes
Until every now and then you got to throw a mouse in there for them to I got you
You're not wrong
And he basically created that
He created this and Robert Jeffers
Is the result
Of an education
Completely controlled by wa Chris
He I swear to you he is like an experiment
The more I've looked into him he was groomed by Criswell from the age of seven
He is an absolute.
Otamatone
He's not a human being he's a psychopath
And he is the most terrifying man alive
Cuz he believes
Everything
I bet he is told
Viagra's
So
He's raised by Creswell
Goes to Baylor
Immediately out of Baylor gets hired right back at First Baptist Church in Dallas
Works there for a few years then he goes to become the head pastor at First Baptist in East Windsor
Which course will help him get the job
Then after that he becomes head pastor at First Baptist Church in Wichita in Texas
Which he
God because of the grizzly
Wichita Falls
Yeah
And then in 2007
5 years after Criswell died
Jeffers became head pastor of First Baptist
Doesn't Dallas and took over like this was
The king coming home to this is f****** Simba
I'm in Baton Rouge
Yeah
And he is relentless
Andynsane
And I couldn't find any early sermons of his whenever he was
You know before
First Baptist
However
He did go on
Card sharks
I like that game in 1986
Have a great game and you wouldn't find it charts the one where it's just high low
It's absolutely just I love I love that no it's great but here's the thing that I forgot about car charger
Like survey questions like Family Feud
And
Everybody is I think incourage
To give a weird
Personal tidbit before they give their answer for the survey question
So
You find out a lot of weird information about people
People eyes were surveyed how many people eat tacos in the last month is it over 40% or
Thunder and then they put out like the playing cards and you have like a 7 on there
That's a whole game
Yep I
Love it
It is incredibly stupid
You can't go back and watch
Children behavior like that if you win you get like
I don't know
How do you get a beach ball Ono at the end of this he went on like a few episodes
Roundup winning about $4,500
Region 19
That's not bad
It's it's wild to go back and watch shows
From the 80s
Can't do it
They they wind up doing all kinds of weird cuz I can't watch any kind of stuff from like
Any any of those
It's like oh my gosh I absolutely
The the post of the show
Has kissing people
You got 10
And who knows them as such
10 college co-ed
Who are asked to sit up next to the stage like Price is Right
Oh yeah
All right that's why they're called college co-ed
The 80s that you knew what the
Never understood that co-educational means it's men and women I know but it's always
It always describes I think it's more like I think it was popularized Maybe by playboy because
It was women that you wouldn't actually went to school with and not Audible
Some like that
10 ladies and women
They were surveyed
How many of you would kiss on the 1st
Okay
The
The contestant against Jeffers
Says it is
66 women
Would actually kiss on the first date
The guy a Starboy Robert
Robert says the number is higher and then this
Everybody
Everyone of you
Everyone
I want to see one person
Backstage after
Sit down
Alright Robert
Chicago
I mean look that's terrible
Write it just like indictment of the show this happens all the
But
It is wild to me that
David Buster who would later on go on Fox News who would give a sermon about homosexual should be killed
This guy is on card shark
In the 1980s and he is
Adjust
Don't You Remember When
Pol Pot was on the $500,000 pyramid
Don't remember when I disagree with the
And he's
Seriously
He is a joy to watch on
I promise you go to go watch this episode of card show
This is joy is infectious and he is just a very genuine and real human being this is him introducing
Love to see you like a
The Reverend Manning
Are the
Eastland Texas
I swear I'm the pastor of
The First Baptist
Church of Eastland
Until my congregation finds out
Unnatural playing
Cards on National Television
You may have some extra
Repentance Backus
Nation praying for me
He's just leaving Brady Charming he's just TV ready this is him this is him winning this is a super
Kind of him winning whenever he gets questions
Comes
Definitely
What is going to play
He's going for
If he is correct
He's our new champion
Lower than a 9
Do you hear that
For the match
The Bevy and pulled it out.
Barry Goldwater
Kadabra babe I don't know if you could hear it well but all of those
All of that with him
I couldn't I don't know what I assumed that was how I didn't think of it
Everything he's jumping up and down he's
Flapping his arms back and forth clapping and it is he's screaming he's whooping
Jeffers
Is f****** loving attending people love him and he's
He's giving it like I said there's not much information about his early life but they're all these weird little things that he starts giving up
In the in the course of asking questions
They'll ask you like
We surveyed 100 people
One of them said how many do you think said they send you say well as it's 60 or more but you have to give a personal
Note to your tacos
We surveyed 100 people how many of you had tacos
Well are you tacos every single night and I've been doing that for 30 years so I'm going to go with for like it's
That kind of this is his biography As Told through two episodes of card shark
Did he
Champion he was on for like a week
Belie
To date a lot of college
I'm convinced they were in love
With more than one person
At that time
Navigation and they
I have
A lot of weddings
Tony's lately and I think
Thursday
Itransact
More traditional type of
Marriage
I'm married no children yet look
Another great day on car chart attaboy
I do a lot of ass
In counseling people and I think I'm a pretty good judge
Character
And I would think most psychiatry
Frisby doctor
Egotist
I do a lot of women watch
Soap operas
Today and some into and they tend to fantasize a lot
I used to live in an apartment
And things got pretty
Grungy there
The grungy the audio is
From YouTube there but I don't find anything
Weird about it I mean it's a little grandiose who like I'm basically a psychiatrist
Dated a lot of ladies and that's just Alex and you f***** all the satanic cheerleaders stuff
But
The only details that I can find from anybody about his young
Younger years
No I don't know I don't know how much of anything is true but this is this is all stuff that he believes that
Part of this end this entire time
He is TV ready
And you see it the moment he goes on the show because
He was trained
By the televangelist
He was raised to be on TV this is a guy who is up
Sast with TV
And he's like
Here he is just
Cracking jokes
Like he's killing
Congressman wash
And we asked
Do you think that alien creature
She's from another planet have ever landed on
The Earth
How many US
Congressman dothey
Alien creatures have landed on the Earth
Imagine a lot of
Converse
Look at that new TV The Killing
You're doing but
Probably not one
Want to admit it
Even if they did believe
Because of the wreck
Applications
Bi-Lo number of
22 out of 100
That's a pretty good that rationalization for your gas if he's TV ready he's Direct
He's got the timing down
The The Host
F****** love song
They are cracking jokes back and forth the entirety
Now he's he's got a person you'd want on their armies against type
He's charming and charismatic
Seems to be fine in that setting of no he's a preacher going to like it
Unique
Contestant absolutely
And while he's doing all of this he is preaching the most homophobic
Like HIV is gods
Plan for gay people like this is all going on in Macon on Karcher
All of this stuff is happening at the same time as this incredibly nice
Charming and funny guy is on TV doing what he is the best
And I like I said I
Read a lot from Michael Muhney about him and he's
This is one of the quotes that he gives from a 2012 Proto
Profile
This is me Monique
In the days I spent with him sometimes from sunrise to sunset
He convinced me that that bright-eyed Schoolboy Persona is not a nap
He decided very early on that he was a Christian
And though he's grown intellectually
Yes several postgraduate.
Degrees in theology
He has never changed his mind
On anything
Ever
That said he still enjoys the company of people who see the world
That guy
Very scary
We are so used to disingenuous people in this world
Specifically that you can see why it's easy to be Charmed by a guy like
Dr. Robert Jeffress
Because he's
He's getting
Like
This guy has spent this is a journalist who has worked with
He's a Dallas journalism
Been through the whole ringer with all of these f******
Liars in
Bulshit artist in that
Jeffers
Absolutely
Like without question
Because
He is
Genuinely genuinely believes all this s*** he is
Open-hearted and clear-eyed whenever he says
All of this awful stuff that he believes
And you can crack a joke while he's doing it
I'm only slightly exaggerating when I say that even though I know he is not committed a crime in his entire life
He is a dangerous society that needs to be quarantined like the f******
Joker this guy is
Terrified
And it's all because Criswell
Created him
Okay that's why I know he hasn't committed any crimes or done anything like that
He was created in criswell's lab
To do all
And the reason that I
Thought about Jeffers
Is not because
Of his appearances on Fox News where I mean I know you're a regular Watcher I know you love
Read I love threading
It's so funny the right is getting really good
He hit another reason that I'm talking about him
Is because he recently
Got into a disagreement
With a guy named
Randy Rhoads
Now
He's the guitarist
Quiet Riot right
5th episode
400 episode
Randy Robeson is also a television
But he is the son of maybe the best Southern Baptists
This preacher
I've ever heard
Benny Hinn James
Cuz I'm
This is
This is a this is
James Robertson this is not from too long ago
He is 40 years old and he has honed this into a f****** knife
The story is basically let me give you the story this is the entire store
There's a carpet cleaner
Named Milton Greene
Alright Milton green
Invites are boy James Robison to sit in a chair
He says
I
Think that you're in torment and I'm going to get rid of demons
He does that
Everything's fine
What a nice guy this is how the greatest Baptists
This preacher tells this story
Do you know who your
Do you know
So help me
How to lean it up against
Holiday Inn
If I ever seen some
I could see stuff
Anyone
I heard
What are the good things about that like the style of talk
King is just like
It's so awesome that they
Seem
Completely comfortable being out of breath
He's always always very appealing I don't know why
Because it seems unhealthy but there's something about it that Justice
What movie tickets
Add sincerity to attack
It's like this is
I'm digging down to try and tell you
No he's a runner from Marathon literally
I'm giving you this information to save your life
That is how important is it
Here is what he say what he saying is a guy address to sit him in a chair
And this is a Titanic life-or-death struggle
And it continued
If I had ever known
A map
Ever since
Would you come
All the king's horses and All the King's Men
Could not
Ashame how we intimidate people
Beaten-down people coming to church beaten down
Warring against the principalities and Powers
We Bangla
Is there something I don't understand about this chair
Okay
Of the kind you might imagine
I don't
Understand with aluminum
Don't notify
Cool
What was he what was he even talk
About right
Stopping principalities new song about demons
That's about all I got to share you want to run through a f****** brick wall
I'm not sure I'm having the same response to you
I think it's good in terms of like oratory okay
Eventually he sits in the chair
And now Milton green starts the X
Fart
Criminal
And he is screaming at ever found
Bondage
Rejection compulsion
I said that man is talking to them
Only one in the room
What is my friend finder
What is the preachers
What I did I guess I baby
Didn't realize that he's talking about an ex
I thought it was just sitting in a chair
There's a little bit of
Okay
Neither of them actually believe in you
That that is there is that the reviews they are b*******
Later on Milton green guess what he becomes
Televangelist
They are working together
And
Here is here's the way he's just killing with this
These people are eating it up
And then he ends it with this f****** kicker
Speaking
Amanda
And he walked over to the
Side of the room
Honey grab the chair
He walked right beside me
Pray for you
Might be some pay my way to come 600 miles to get here he said here's the care
Freak
He has the power of
Story is
Just him
Getting his demons exercise
Right and then later on he goes to a conference
And people all bring their own chair to
To him cuz now he has the power to X
Society
This whole thing is that long journey.
And it is
He f****** demolishes this real
So James Robison is a fascinating guy whose son Randy Rhoads drop by right
So I was looking
James Robison and either contemporary
Contemporary with the spiritual dad of
They got you forgotten the main person's name because
I'm talking about four guys the first generation on the second generation
I jumper is is the one that I am aware of already and that's the name I couldn't remember
Clogging my brain with
With card sharks pictures
Dusty Rhodes reference
Too much to juggle yeah I know tell me about it
The the inverse is also true
So Robinson
Tell me it's hard to get their information with somebody to write to you
Right
Robinson is coming up in the world of conservative charismatic
Okay this is way back
Criswell's older games coming up I got you
James has become a because James is the f******
Can preacher he's the preachers preacher
You know he's the guy that guy who's got like a multiple rags
Does mop his brow
Oh yeah somehow I imagine him being in o'brother Where Art Thou
Early career is
Just that like he's hustling
He's going from place to place getting
Finding little things to jump in and get more famous off on places where people have chairs
Stuff like that yet
Like
Then
Sometime in the mid-80s
He stopped
He doesn't stop preaching
But he stopped trying to climb the conservative
Christian rap
And he just kind of
Almost settled
In create a modest
TV Empire
He creates the life that Alex
Or do you like sort of the sustainable Jim Bakker absolutely
He's not he's not screwing anybody over he's trying he's not being a good guy in the sense of like
You know doing anyting
Two positive he's got a charity that by all accounts and purposes
Is it okay
You know it's not a scam but it's not like
But also might be
Well
Charity watching people like that is evaluated it and said it's not if I call Jose for casting aspersions
No problem and
He just kind of
Creates this
Stable
Modern
TV Empire
He's got multiple talk shows
He preaches he
He's not trying to get too big
I he's
He's got a
Everything that he wants any
Stays just like a little under-the-radar like you don't know about
I'm right
Not not to off the top my head now
Worldwide
People all over the world watch him he's got his own channel like all of this s*** and
He
Again since the 80s
For some for whatever reason has live this life that
Suggest he believes what he's
Just like Chiswell created Jeffers
You correctly noted it that James Robinson created his son Randy Rhoads
Literally
Randy is not
Randy is not a televangelist
Just like a like a guitarist for quiet
Everybody
Randy is
A bit of a doof
He's a nice guy I'm kind of obsessed
I really am
He has his own like internet talk show on James Robinson's Network and it feels exactly like
A televangelist giving his kind of a Duke's on a talk show
Okay it gets downright
Chris Farley Show at times like
Do you like it
Okay
Easy does mainly like
You know reformed born-again Christians that kind of sucks because he has that
Kind of interview and of course
If somebody famous becomes a born-again
Christian you get
Welcome to life today I'm Randy Robinson
Can I have the heart
Exactly
Sean Michael
Many years
Anybody
Is wrestling
You know who this
Faerun
That's it you know what you are a real son-of-a-b**** let me explain to you why
Did you watch this video because you
You have
Introduced Shawn Michaels to the proceedings
And you didn't include his theme song I'm sorry I'm sorry I did not listen to
Michaels
Alright
The girls
Attitude
You know who sings that
Randy Rhoads
Sean Michael
Noah schnapp
That's hilarious
No that's not my fault Randy should have been playing that theme song
Expulsion stone cold on your show
That class is got a break
For Showmanship
Down again Christian
His tag team match that he had with Vince McMahon
Hamburger what pay-per-view
No it was a long time ago in the you like maybe
Sometime it's
When Shawn Michaels became a born-again Christian it became sort of a thing in the storyline did Vince
Because events at this megalomaniacal I'm more important than God came to think
Who is tag team partner was Shawn Michaels
Add John Michaels tag team partner was God
Literal. Well they did it wasn't invisible you had to have a spotlight
I don't remember all the wrestling is great
One of the more goofy things that
I've definitely
Coming to the faith allowing it to be portrayed that way and television
Seems very weird hilarious
But yeah
Drug problems
It's one of those things like that so pretty good
Root for him to go down as close to dying
So of course he wrote a book and it goes on rant
Hey wrote a book it is all of eight
This interview is really boring but it has one of my
My favorite like I watch
All of Randy's interviews are incredibly boring
But even when they're interested
But he is a genuinely curious person who's also a bit of a dude like this is him asking Shawn Michaels
A big question
What is Sweet Chin Music
Remember the arena where you
I do it was in feet
The Phoenix Arena
You said so
Instruct me in
141 you obviously
Attached
You know
Out of your life
You made a statement
The only time
I like
You made me
What is what is
Well
Unfair
I love that it's a pretty decent I know that's what I'm saying I love this guy no
Just the way he
He probably could have framed it a little better
Yeah it is a little Direct
Chris Farley Show question
He seems really not I would have preferred to ask what it meant when Shawn Michaels lost his smile
He's not there not curiosity
Michaels
Super kicking people Sweet Chin Music
Shawn Michaels has
What are you do is you'd be like coming up
You get knocked down on the side of the Ring
Will you be getting up
Struggling to get up
And has your slowly getting up he be in the corner at the turnbuckle
Stop his foot
It's like a bullet to give like the audience so you know it's, okay
Tune up the band then hit you with the Sweet Chin Music and then right when you were finally standing up and that's when the cake would come right
It's a good theme song
I was younger I hesitate to give you my
I don't know you showed up at a WrestleMania a couple years back out of nowhere and
Boy I celebrated pretty cute even expect myself to
Michael's fan excited
Well
Just like like the reason that he has Shawn Michaels and and those types of gas
Probably about
Not that many wrestlers a lot of come around to like being
Create
Lex Luthor not Lex Luthor Lex Luger was on the 700 Club
Okay and I almost didn't episode
Think I might have done I got half episode
But
User
The million dollar man to Ted DiBiase
Robert
This guy
Cycle through wrestling I didn't see too many with wrestlers but that one was funny
Realize tugboat was a wrestler
Yeah is it not using cuz we might not even have used their stage names on his show so Darwin piche
Irwin R schyster IRS
Oh man use attacks guy
I think I got it
I think I guess that wrestler
I really do around you I apologize
It's
But the reason he has
Like guys like Shawn Michaels on is because he fancies himself something of a bad boy
He's a little bit
This is the type of s*** that he really wants to get in
In Green Bay Wisconsin
And now he's got a new book called
Battle
Over
Yes the battle over rules
And you can talk about that online today
Check it out at like today
Play. Org
But
For this
Particular interview
You're fortunate enough
To be watching the bonuses
Or we can go
Out of the bounds
We're going to discuss the topic that was rejected
For the broadcast
Show
Because it was
Just a little
Over The Line
And I've got
We're going to talk about
I did not tell him to
We're going to talk about the bead method this is your own visitor
This is your
I did all that
Yeah you did and then next time you know
They said no we're not going to discuss it
Is this anal beads
Really
So we thought I was going to say there's going to be a joke it's be like no it's crafting
Dude actually straight up onto okay that is a little bit
Intellivision
You you get away with saying
Well it's not quite a little beads it's it's a it's in a marriage this this pastor has this idea of like
Okay we all want it we all need to have sex
Sprite but it's tough to have sex when you're older
And sometimes we don't want to do it so we created this bead method which is like a barter C
Like
Here is some beads
Now we talked for awhile
Then you're done
I'm out exactly
Also not that rebuild anymore this isn't that exciting
What is controversial
This is just transactional
That subject was rejected
For the broadcast show at 2 from my own show
But he's just obsessed with being this like
Kind of a bad boy
Brightness in this world like
So he of course
Has written a s*** ton of books
Like everybody else in the
But
Unlike most people one of his books
It was fiction
It's called scavo or I don't know how to pronounce it is sceva
And here is the blurb for it that was
Let me see if you can find out
Who wrote this letter for her okay
In the Supernatural Thriller the seven deadly sins threatened to destroy the lives of seven Bible college students after
Ill-advised
Attempt
Cast a demon out of a man
Now you can read the book Praise by Publishers as quote intense
A great read
And quote strong writing
But rejected for being too edgy for Christian readers
Who wrote the review or do you think I've two guys
Okay sorry I don't
No dad
Yeah
I kind of love I also would have guessed the host of card sharks but I could remember who I was
I think it is
Oh man I can remember bill it's like a bill Mitchell
Something along those
Qanon
Rebuilding
This guy
And
Robert Jeffrey
Are both second generation televangel
And my
That's
That's so weird
Isn't it there's a legacy business
It makes sense
It just took me back for a second to pick like
Hearing about one of them
That is what
But like here
Multiple I can think about like
I mean to Baker's kids are exactly
Right that's
Yeah
Steph
Except weird
And it's in within Caesar wrestling
2nd generation on 3rd generation wrestlers
Write like
Any any or any comparison to TV is what these guys are all
TV creator
And their eyes are all for TV
And it's between these two second-generation televangelists
That I try and explain the question
Why does the religious right support Trump no matter what
Why is
Is that because I see that article written 300 million times over and over and over
Why are these supposedly moral upstanding people
Supporting a monster like
It doesn't make any sense
And I will give you these two characters
Is to second-generation televangelists to try Annex
Explain it away Randy Rhoads
And
Jeffers
Alright
One of them
The bad-boy it's one of them the pristine article
Exactly
You know what's one do you think is worse though
Probably the pristine article
Absolutely what do you what do you feel about Randy so far
Everybody was saying I was Shawn Michaels can't be all bad he's not a bad guy
I don't know why that's not actually true. Michael said some
Kitty friends
Of the wrestlers
I don't know why I can't really get a sense of him from the like a limited amount of information I have I mean I know like his dad seems
To be a guy who likes to have exorcisms on chairs and is a
Like a classic old-school lasek
Huckster type preacher but
I mean
Seems were formed the sins of the father are bestowed upon the son
In my my
My conception Center
Yeah I don't know I don't I don't
I need more information
Well as far as his
Vocal patterns and all that stuff goes gifted
Compared to these other guys in the same time he's talking like a person
Yes so there's a
You know
It's not as gifted in the genre
But there is more of a there's also relatability about someone who speaks like
Well what about this thing that you're not like people like
Like that real f****** stupid on podcast 2
People like
Yeah I know and I like him
I genuinely do I
I mean I don't know what he's like
Private life but
Everything that I see through all of this stuff is just him like
He's just a guy
He's a guy who believes in all of this crisp
And he's
Struggling within this
There's this like
Constant push and pull with him
Between what he is told by mainstream Conservative Christian
Like dr. Robert
And what he thinks is a moral stance
He doesn't he doesn't believe
In the same God
Then Richard Jeffrey
Not even
Close
They are of course friends and
Randy basically agrees with everything that Robert Jeffrey
Says
But anytime you get that little
Bright spot of him like
Well I don't think we should be evil too
Gay people but
You could like
It's that over and over and over again
And these little bits of him
Coming really close
To the saying like
I don't believe
What you believe
And then just being like you sound right
Let's go
This the reason that I'm talking about the
You guys have because It Came Upon
Randy
Putting out a live stream
Entitled does evil rain
Which is based on an interview he recently did with
Dr. Jeff
I thought it was with
Gangrel vampire demon
From
What you want
Literal vampire tamanrasset
People
Use a vampire.
You're the lights go out and then there be
I got candles
Complained
He I was hanging out with the original Hebrew
Zedge
Christian right there is to sort of enforcer later on when to have their own
Very successful
Tag team in both world champions in their own right
Amanda
And then
Where was Gangrel and then they laughed and then Matt and Jeff Hardy became the new brood
Hung out with Gangrel minute run
We shouldn't hang out
Lame ideas fixies of them
I wish wrestling would like that just suddenly started
They broke
Hey babe the moment that it was time to sleep
Just introduced that new wrinkle
That's like that's like an ocean swell when Julia Roberts plays a character that looks like Julia Roberts
You're f****** with me and I don't like the introduction of like half realities worse than
You tell me that you think he might not be a vampire we all know
Fun though
That would be fun only only in the world of kayfabe
If you were to disagree though
You would probably have a
A better conversation
Then
The way that Randy did
Oh yeah this is Randy introducing the idea of disagreeing with doctor
End
It's not real nice
When you invite people into your
Facility on your show and you just to argue with
It's kind of rude
Did the flip side of that is if they say something that I disagree with
And I don't say anything people assume that I'm in agreement with the
And so I'm always having to measure okay does that rise to the level that I need to say something
And
If you watch closely you'll
See sometimes
When I say something I might I might politely
Push back and say you know his
You know any
That sounds like an adult
Eva nice guy
This is him politely
Like
Going through this he's like I'm doing a show I don't want to be ungracious but
At the same time if I disagree with somebody I want to
Be polite and then I'm going to measure whether or not I need to say something if I don't say anything he's recognizing that there is like a tacit
Understanding the audience as they like while you must agree with that otherwise you would have said something absolutely that's like recognizing you respond
Possibilities listen to that
Refreshing
It's very
Yeah
Now this is him going out of his way
To even when he does this
Agree with Robert J
Point out that he's like I don't want to offend anybody
Just know
That I mean
To the doctor Jeffy
As I
Offer you an alternative view of
But I want to bring his view because it is
Probably the dominant view in
Evangelical
Churches right now
An n
The only thing is I'm not
Convinced that I'm 100
All the time I feel like
I'm constantly learning which is why I love having all this
People in here
I am getting too, tap the brain the same as I push
I'm more difficult issues because
I'm sitting there learning and I think that the
That's good for an audience
Just watch
And learn
That's pretty humble
Now
Who are we talking about in contrast with that guy
The guy who has never been wrong
Once in his entire life
Jackie babe
This is what Jeffrey's sounds like
On that
On the show
Ryan what you drive I don't know if
Stereotypical
Let's play
I'm guessing you don't have one of those coexist
Bumper stickers
My wife actually almost got
Me one is a joke
Vacation Thursday anything's
The opposite of my worldview it's that coexist so she almost put it on my
The Joker yeah
Yeah
His worldview is the opposite of
He is one hundred percent right about everything
And he has no interest in Europe in
And he has no in
Can anything you have to say
That is why he is so dangerous and
Evil and that is also why Randy is a different person
Randy is humble and
Curious
He wants to know
He has his own opinions but at the same time he's always trying to learn
Yeah that is the difference between these this is the the war in Christianity as far as
And it is being
1 by
Robert Jeff
Like An Enderman
Randy is 1 mi / like here's Randy talking about
There's a certain difference in philosophy he has with Robert
Okay so he starts with the c.s. Lewis
Twitch
I love c.s. Lewis
Any points out that we are in a battle well we
If you don't know this by now couldn't
I'll just tell you we are in a battle
Where am I
Spiritual bath
We don't wrestle against
Blood
Common mistake I think
People make
Even Christian
Thinking that though you over there you're my enemy
No
Spiritual
Okay
Make a lot of people take that to be like
Spiritual battle and I'm against
Your spirit absolutely feel like that's what he's saying
But that's
Delivered slightly differently yep exactly what you hear from Alex it doesn't have the same feeling
And also I want to say that
He doesn't like
Louis
I heard that so much background to church
Ever read Mere Christianity the problem of pain none of those m************ reading
Out of the Silent Planet once and they called it a day
Hey read a couple of bucket paragraphs and they're like good enough
Because it's
Understand it deeper because I read all this other l
I Christians love because
Appreciate
Tony from him
In there but I still don't
Alexia Lewis
Dentist Knoxville never know
Like non
Lion the Witch and the Wardrobe
I don't know I'm unaware of that
Oh man the the second book in that trailer G is essentially a retelling of
Genesis
But it's
Adam and Eve on Venus
Oh and it is essentially a retelling of Genesis and it is
So much longer
And so much more boring
It is incredibly amazed myself whenever I read it because I
It's so boring
And then the third book weird to it have space religion be more boring
Right
And then the third book is
Unreadable
Like even The Lion the Witch and the Wardrobe
It's like no one read
Past like
Maybe actually a really good book I Remember Loving that but no one read a horse in his
Boy Oliver I read I don't know man so terrible
Google didn't read all of them
Turkish delight
Church who loves c.s. Lewis
Because I've read all of
Is
Eyeliner Wichita
The order
Prince Caspian the second Silverchair
How to say it's 5
Last battle is
But yeah
Listen to the way this dude is is putting everything it is this
This idea of like
He is you
Hearing the same words that Jeffers is saying just like you put it you know
You say it a little bit differently and it's exactly what I like
That's right but he's he means it in the
I don't know I'm more genuine way I hear what he's saying when he's saying it's a spiritual battle meaning
Within your own
You are having a like it is a
If the test is within all of us and
You have a responsibility to fight this battle
Within yourself to rise to the occasion absolute that's the battle
When I hear Alex talk about we do not fight against flesh and blood it's a spiritual battle
I hear him saying kill that person cuz there's a demon in
You got ya
It's a big difference but it is the same intrinsic idea
Words being used
Express different thing absolutely
That's exactly it
I feel like I'm hearing this and maybe I have way too generous at opinion of this dude because it's the way you're
Presenting I worried about that but I'm trusting you
I mean I guess it's I guess it's easier
To have a negative opinion of somebody with very little information about them than to have a positive
Opinion with only
Disgaea
Could be a trap it could be as far as I can tell like he believes
Here's here's my
Here's my thing about him
And this is the thing that I
I was really struggling with while I was I was thinking of this idea which
She's like
I've known my parents
I know that they do not want people in cages at the border
But I don't understand how they can justify it
And I know that Randy
Is that
Same type of Christian
That I like
Hear it in everything he says and everything you've does I've watched all of those over and over again
He's your parents version of Christian
Exact
He is that person and I think I think the large majority of
I think the large majority of them
I do not want that
But they are trapped
They are trapped by guys like dr. Robert
And here's another that here's what's going to
India are you
To Randy I think a little bit more than he's live streaming this
So there are people in the twitch
Osher
That's weird yet there people in the twitch Jesse like playing Dark Souls
But
I got this is how this dude responds to trolls showing up in history
Welcome All You trolls on Twitch
I see you guys at
And
You're welcome to live
That's why I'm on
You're not going to
Also that
You know he wasn't a nice guy that's the right
Move exact
Trolls are going to come up more freaky
They're always going to existing
You know like if you just have that approach then like
People don't get a rise out of you they don't get what they want
Do you just
Yell at somebody and you're going to end up
Attracting
It's fun we could poke him
A knowing that
At least or even if it's just
Like instinctual he continues to deal with rolls her out the lights
And it is
It is very funny ho ho like
I just don't know how more
Just like
I kind of like
General
Doofy good dude could react
Then the way that he does
It's just like this General sense of a guy who's just like
I'm
Satisfied with my life
I'm trying to do what I think is right
And you guys are being mean and you know what
To right to be mean
I understand
Like he's doing that whole thing
Weather
Later on he gets
My favorite recurring bit on his show
Is
He writes book
Sure and no one knows about it and no one is read them and no one really believes that he write
So in so many of these interviews you wind up having a situation like this
That's where he does that
Interview when he when he gained
The idea of happiness
That
I said
Well you haven't read my book
Call God wants you to be happy and he laughed we thought I was joking but
I'm not joking or what the book called God wants you to be happy
You know be a great bet he had never written a book
Everything's alright
The rider
That'll be awesome this happens like
3 or 4
I watched
I am maybe 5 maybe 10 of these
Do you have any insight on why No One Believes you wrote a book I don't know I don't know if anybody's ever actually published
Physically
Nature a lot of people sell public and I definitely don't think anybody knows about this
So you probably probably
It's not good
But this happens if there's an interview with another woman who wrote that that's super weird as an act
Accusation or like
How much do you think of that is actually people thinking he hasn't written a book and how much is
Him being insecure
About his book sales
Think about that other people don't think he's written a book
It happens over and over and over very weird he brought it up on one interview this woman
Wrote a book
About how
Christian women need to understand that men like to look at with
And that it's not a bad thing
And that interview gets
Weird and horny and
Brandy's
I'm glad I'm not a teenager anymore like doing all kinds of weird stuff in there and then eventually he's like
Oh happiness I wrote about happiness in my book I want to be happy
I'm sorry what
You did know I wrote a book
Happen
Over and over and over again this happens in almost every issue it is
Very funny
So yeah the disagreement that
Randy and
Robert have
What is
On
Happiness
That's what Randy is saying
He wrote a book
Call God wants you to be happy
Robert
Did not even I don't even know Robert believes in
That's the fundamental
Right now Randy is
Is a doofy guy who just wants to Live and Let Live
And this is the type of stuff he does agree with this is how we deals with trolls in that
We've known this
Belinda said she takes pleasure in looking at
And you know
Something interesting
I started the Reformation
In a bit because
I didn't really get that at
School
And one thing that that
The Catholics and those who were protesting the Catholic Church
Didn't argue about because they agreed on
That was the god reveals
Self through nature
Belinda
I100
Agree with you
I take
In in the mountain
I love the snow ski
Stand up there
You're at the Keystone to Breckenridge
Continental Divide
And I'm like this is
Beautiful
Temple
In the world
God's creation
So yes
Percent Judy
He might have Red Sea as well as
Maybe I was not judge too harshly
That is true
Babies that is a belief of like if you've never heard the name of Christ and you'd recognize him
Through nature that is salvation
Good enough
What is a position
A lot of schools of Christianity you help getting a little bit trolled with like
I like to look at flowers
I think I think I think that
I think that
The reason I think that is I think Belinda pops up later on
Okay yeah I got another context art sorry my bad
This is before belindapop sitting but that's that's what he's
He's he's
Very simple
He's doing this is what we agree
And here's where we disagree and there are more trolls
So I'm getting trolled hard today
About time
Introllsive left me alone
So here's the part
Where
Dr. Jeffers
I have a disagreement
And this is where I want you
Your input
Constructed in
I'll just ignore it
Just trolling but
And this is
It kind of goes to
Eschatology
In other words
How we
View the future and
The dominant in the evangelico churches is a futuristic
Other words things are going to get worse and worse
Warriors before they
Better
And this
This is where
I actually just don't
Don't agree I was raised that way but I don't agree more and we're going to get into it
He doesn't he doesn't believe in the the progression towards
Good
The downward progression
Sharp
Exactly
Randy is a chill
Chill guy
He's pretty much like he sounds so much Bob Rossi to me like so much of that just like
I like to look at them
The grill Tampa
Yeah yeah it's a religious show Bob Ross
Basically
And
What he is getting to is that when he says that eschatology is
Fundamental disc
He's not even getting to the real
They have no shifts is the fundamental
And he thinks it's just them disagreeing about how
Allegedly wrote a book about
I have not read it
He may not ever
Not exactly might not exist I went to his website and it's there
You can buy it on Amazon but I don't know if I'm going to go through to the car
But he thinks they're talkin about happy
He thinks they're talking about happiness and whether or not
You're supposed to be happy or you're supposed to wait until God
You know replaces the world or whatever right
What they are actually talking about is
The literal replacement of the world like here is Doctor
Jeffers
This is what his
Is on the
The side of
This world is
Not the word
And this world
But until then
Who is going
Filter I mean that sounds like
Lot of the religious things ever
How does the imperfect
Meet world
The difference here
Is what.
We get back into the words can mean different
Dr. Jeffers
Is not talking about
How the you know eventually the world Satan going to rain and then God will replace the world in all of this
Yeah actually talk
Talking about how he wants to replace the world
He criswell's idea of a Christian separatist
Compound
The main goal of
Was to create a completely separate
Christian world that would eventually grow to be the world
He could not do that and what he realize
Was that that was not possible
And it wasn't going to be possible to be left
Delon
Unless
You are the only thing
So he created dr. Jeffers
And
This is
The reason that I find him so terrifying
And it goes back to Randall rail bomber wrote an article in Politico
About the creation of the Christian separatist
How people always talk about Roe v Wade as
Inciting factor to getting the Christian right
To mobilizing
Right
What
Was born out of though was the
Court decision in Greenville Kennedy
Which later became Greenville Connolly when Connolly became the Secretary of Treasury
This happened about five to 10 years before Roe v Wade
The situation boils down to
If you segregate your private school
You do not get tax-exempt
That's it
Bright.
And the goal for Criswell
Whether or not it was racial segregation
The goal has always been
To completely segregate
Christian's away from ever
So they took that idea of
They're going to make a
Has become public schools
And they turned that who is Jerry Falwell and Bob Jones and all of those guys
Into this and then they
Teamed up with away riches
Burgeoning heritage
All of these guys turned into what the right is
Today
All of it just like knee-jerk an awful reaction
When's two Notions of civil right
With one mangle
And that is creating a completely
White Christian vehicle
That is the purpose
Price of this and that is what Jeffers was raised
So when he starts talking about how
Reno
We we the this world is not the world of God
Like that kind of
And we need he's not about waiting
For God to come back with a world of God
He wants his world
Yeah absolutely
It is interesting
I don't know how much of it is
Just like
If i Kin trinsic suspicion of things
But like
Does field if
Even without your presentation
I think I would
Your him say those things
Jeffers say those the
Differently then
Randy Rhoads
Right
Robinson
Disagree
It is its interests
It's it's
It's
I think what it speaks to is the
Like
The inherent
Neutrality of religion
Itself
Because these people are both expressing
Like really religious ideas
And one of them is expressing
That man away that's like
Alright
And the other one thing
Billy similar kinds of things like that are 180 degrees
It's about what's packaged on it
Right it really is the the
What will becomes a problem
And Randy
Is a
Absolutely
They're both raised
Second generation
They both have this incredibly intense
A religious education both of them can toss out
Anytime they all have that
Televangelist way of talking words like
Say where's where's where's where where was Hebrews 918 where is where where where you know that that whole thing big quotes
From from memory
Neither one of them has any greater
Command of the Bible in the
And both of them say almost
Exactly the same thing
And both of them disagree on ever
Randy is the only one who does
That's the thing that fascinates
About all this
So basically
Disagreement there having
Is that dr. Jeffers
Wants to get rid of this one
Terry's got a dippy ology
Yeah yeah
I don't know I I go back and forth between just calling him
Robbery
Jeffers or. David
Big Bob
But yeah it to your point
I find him so terrifying because the guy who is trying to be the bad boy
Is calm quiet
Humble
Karen
And the guy who is the pristine
Never been in trouble always enthusiastic that guy waving around and
I'm so happy all the time
Is
A tool created by a guy who wants to build a
Christian theocracy
And so now he is that perfect tool for Trump
It is almost like Jeffers was
Created by Criswell
To be used by the first fascist
Dictator they could that could show up in order to solidify
The Christian right
And
Because Jeffers is
Genuine and Brilliant and real
And Trump is a lying piece of s***
Jeffers is going to trick Trump
Essentially into creating it
As a Christian
Fascist
Dictatorship
Instead of just a
He is
Terrifying
The history of Christianity is literally
The world is we need to end the world in order to create our world
And then on the other side you have
Randy Robinson
Dealing with trolls
Loving his life and this is this is just like I I listen to this clip and I was just like this
This is the guy that
I think of whenever I think of like
The Christianity that I
Someone admire a little bit like listen to this
Charlie
Charlie sister
The Staten rules
Because Charlie came out
Spell satan
He's telling me God doesn't exist
There's a problem Charlie
You might as well tell me my wife doesn't
Latin does rule
Satin rules cuz you don't know how to spell Saint doesn't have that like
He doesn't have that you don't know it's just
You don't know how to spell Satan
Yeah I know
You're trying to tell me God isn't real
Tell that to my wife like it's it's so much just this
Benign kind of this guy that like you were saying that is a z
He's just trying to say I got exist in the same way my wife does
Laurence Powell
He's he's just a nice guy
I think
To me like
In my experience cuz I've spent so much time in
In Christian world and say love you
I know Jeffers
I've seen that guy
Everywhere
But the large majority of people that I have met in so many
Is
Randy
I would agree with
That kind of depth
And so
Whenever people talk about
Why is it
That
You know
Christians follow Trump
I see it as
A function of this
Kind of
Scism yeah
And the guy who trained the faccia
Was
Baby the best
Televangelist
The time and the guy who trying to chill guy with Dad was just sort of kept a low-profile
Yep you're bothering me out I know right and it's not because
There
Jeffers is so good at using the same words
Is the Christians
Used to mean positive things and twisting them into something horrific
All the while believing it's good
Like that's why he's such a powerful tool
Is because Criswell got him
At such a young age
And controlled every aspect
Of his life
And I'm sure you know yeah whatever about his own motivate
But it's
Fairly clear
That if you were
If your
Captured
By Criswell
And taken under his wing personally at 7 years old
You're not going to be unaffected
Yeah it's going to be a tough
Course correct
Very least absolutely
And you're not fully developed in your being
You know bombarded with a lot of like
Really heavy stuff
Give me hard to process the stuff that's coming in in addition
Shinto
Adolescence growing up yep
Now that's a bummer
Yeah and it's from the guy who's
The best at it
Bike
Criswell is a brilliant cult
Dew point
The closest the closest like
Analog for Criswell and
Jeffers that I can think of
Is El Ron Hubbard and
Miscavige
Like that's the type
We're dealing with
Jeffers believes all of this
To the point where it's indistinguishable
From
From reality
Like its
It's amazing
But most people like and here's the here's what I'm saying again with Randy kind of having that sense of
I know something's not right
But I don't know
Why I'm fighting it like it in this in this club radio
In the futurist view we believe that
A new world's going Jesus will come and set up his
His kingdom on Earth
And then there will be no
Here's my question for you
In a
The
That I would have with
Futurist Buick
Which Doctor Jeffers
And in that is when I look at what
Jesus didn't his work on the
Across
I believe
He gave us every
Good thing we need to
To establish his
Okay
Is the kingdom here on Earth is already ready to go
Randy wants to make the world a better
Randy thinks we have the tools to make the world a better place
Huh well I mean I guess that is the difference in depth
The definition of like what
The promise of the Cross was
Is the promised already fulfilled
In the act
Of the crucifixion and Resurrection
Or is it contingent on some
Future of that
That does seem to be
A profound difference
Opinion
I know it at that stuff I'm always down for the religion that takes the shape of
Things that will create a better world for everybody
So
Without knowing any of the other stuff that he believes cuz I
I really feel like I might be stuff I don't know about this really f****** here's the thing though
That's again
That gets to my point exactly
I will guarantee enough I know
Randy believes in obviously
Like conservative right-wing bulge
He will say it he'll repeat it
And it's just so clear to me
That what underpins his beliefs
Have him saying that stuff in order to stay in lockstep
With the people that he thinks there is two
All of these all of these people
Goes into that kind of second generation
Televangelist the difference between them
Is
Randy is
Like
He was raised in this
He knows the language he knows what he's supposed to believe
And there's a part of him that is fighting again
There's a part of him somewhere that's like
I know it's bad to do this
But
I'm told by
Guys I respect guys who are the kings of the world
Leader of the biggest
Of the first megachurch
Right now
He's telling me that this is what we have to say is what we have to believe
That kind of s***
I mean was it Criswell or Jeffers who
Started their speech off by saying
The evils of liberals
Yeah so he taught Jeff
It wasn't necessarily the mentor for
Randy Rhoads so it makes I mean like
Did the rejection of liberalism in the rejection
Look like a humanistic perspective
Is
Going to ultimately leave
Towards
Not
Recognizing
United
Society
It's going to always are towards
Utopianism
The future of like weird
Create this this perfect thing
Once this liberalism
Where people have freedom
Game of choice and they can send
They're allowed to send once were free of that
Yeah it makes sense with that dude
The dude who is a sort of mentored by that guy
Tubi
Barbara down that site then
Then someone else
He's
Far more effective
Like this is this is what
What's amazing to me
Is that
Jeffers
Is
Trained
As a weapon
Jeffers was weaponized
From a young age
And it's very clear that Randy was just raised in the
Like that is so much the difference to me
A between the two of them
Jeffers is here
To remake
All of Chrissy
Unity increase Wells
Image
And Randy is here because
His dad is a
The televangelist
And he got a little guy he got a little gig
Shawn Michaels and here's the other thing like Randy's on Randy's website which is
Very cute it is essentially an Angel Fire page
It's very funny he has these little
Like devotional isn't stuff that he's written
Before there's like five things
Almost all of them are about
TV
He just loves TV
He's eat like here's how we can make Christian TV shows you watch TV shows and when they're Christian your life
TV shows suck
Here's what we can do to make them better and that kind of
This guy just wants to work in TV
You have no idea
He's like he just he just loves TV
Like that's what he was raised up
Loving
Jim Bakker absolutely I think Randy
Sums up my views on
Jeffers pretty easily right
Craigslist
Satan is a bully
Hundred percent
You got milk he's a liar
Before crap
That's cute the bad boy
Can I can I see that
God I know Randy I know so many Randy
Daisy McQueen
He's very cute
And he's going to get eaten alive by dr. Jeffers
Every f******
Probably yeah I mean if there's a if there ever is call for a head-to-head confrontation
Is this close to the call for a head-to-head
Confrontational
Can get this from
A couple weeks ago
Space
Might have to do a part 2 on that
This is interesting
I don't know what I think about this
I get criticized a lot for not being like more aggressively atheist
In my position
Like anti-religion oh my background
Suggest I should be
You heard me a very stringent anti-atheist
Slowly and gently very stringent atheist
Slowly and gently fall in love
With a Bob Ross a Christian
Like
This guy is is what I've always thought that Christianity
Like wants to be
And he is in thrall
That's what I think of
Absolutely
Not so boring
You so boring
That's what I'm saying that's why he lose
It's why he loses
Like any
Can we go back to the wrestling thing like that's why heels are often more like
Exciting than fat
And I like the good guys are often kind of Dopey and like
I am a little bit boring or his
Wii characters that are allowed in the bad guy
Arizona always a little bit more they have urged to them they're more interesting
But they're assholes and you want to see them get beat by the good guy eventually
That's how you make the money
Right but what if
You're the ass hoe
You're the Healer who says all the interesting things you get so much press attention all the
And yet when people want to look into you and find out where you're a liar
Find out where you're full of s***
And really explosion
And it turns out
You're the sweetest kind of human being
Alive
You're incredible
There's just nothing bad to say about you personally you live that life that you say that you you do like
Like that whole thing
I mean Marty come both Marty Underhill and the the hero
Party dresses
Was going to kick my ass but I'm sure there's a wrestling analogue for that
Character
I'm sure that is a character I can't think of it but that's that's the thing that I think is so attractive
To Chris
Shinto otherwise would never
Go along with
Such a moral bulshit
Is that the guy spouting amoral bulshit
Is living the moral life that most of the most Christians
Hitler
Like most Prosperity aspect of the lot of these like a
TV preachers who live these
Largely comfortable affluent lives and leaves create like
An image that there that it becomes aspirational almost to their to the light to the audience in congregation
What is the buttocks
That's what I'm saying
Jeffers is different even from that if I wanted to talk about that you know we could talk about Paula white-cain all day
Like this
Some of these people are those guys
Who are
Selling you something and trying to win money from the grill
And I genuinely don't think Jeffers is
Jeffers is not trying to Griffith
Political he is
Yours is working on a political project absolute
Jeffers is a
True Believer
And the one thing that he truly believes in
Is getting rid of the rest of us and creating a white Christian theocracy
And you will say anything
Defend anyting
Do anything
To make sure that that
Let's hope Randy Rhoads wins that I know right
Got your back Randy come on buddy
Man Randy Robinson
He's at most of his
Stuff has like a few hundred views he's just a nice guy
Mommy's trying to enter a space
It's not made for what
He's doing
You know like
It's
I like to s*** on
Like Dave daubenmire for having like 35 use
Would be fair like
YouTube streaming isn't the place for
It's not a huge popular place for
Christian extremism
Necessarily so it's got to be even
Vore
A waste
And or no man's land
Religious
Sitting around chatting
I mean good on him no because I mean
I mean again
Hey I'm hesitant
Say anything
To committal because
I don't know anything about the I guess
Like the idea that like he's carving out a space l on Twitch
It like no one is doing that
There is a place for it in terms of streaming Platforms in if it's
Him doing it
Genuine person then unfortunately
Monsters will gravitate towards a
And exploit the work he's done and then his kid will become the Antichrist
I think that's the only thing we can only think that we can say
Is for 100% going
You heard it here
Randy Robinson's kids
Will destroy here
I mean if it skips a generation
Alright
No I mean
If that's but that's the thing
All four of these televangelists
Absolutely hold of Horrid View
There's no doubt in my mind
To varying degrees
There is
But
James Robison
First
Started by like just going like I don't want to be part of this anymore for whatever reason
Pretty much
In the Christian televangelists world
He believes in Opelousas
Randy Robbins
Absolutely in the Christian televangelist world
He believes a lot of horrible ship
But when you listen to Randy talk
You can see that he is
He doesn't want to
I think there's so many people who just don't want to believe this horrible s*** but they are
Because part of the teachings of Christianity is like
Shut the f****** and listen to your pastor
You know it's that kind of thing
So
I don't know if I fully got my point across but I feel like I did all right
How big is a lot of points
Linda
Yeah it's it's at me thinking I think there's a lot of reflection
I don't know why I would I would say they would I see from this is like two
French ejector he's going through time. Like
The one that seems to be working towards a better outcome and one that seems to be working
Toward the worst you haven't both of them believing
That they're working for the better out
Yeah I think almost everybody does it even Alex
It's hard for me to say this
Cuz I'm not sure I believe it I know right that's why it's so refreshing for me to study people who do believe what they say
X I do think that he probably thinks he's doing what's right
There's at least a part of him
These guys probably fully think that what they're doing is 100%
Yeah
I'm fascinated by these guys
Or I think that you're always going to find that whenever
The
The genre is religious
Yeah you know that you're always going to find people who
Armoire
Believing that what they're doing is right
It's
You take the the framework
Of politics and replace it with
Religion
Grated Alex is a crypto
Religious religious beliefs
Behind political message
And also alien
And
Delano movie reference
There's there's still like
There's still the political veneer to it that allows do you like
Committed
Saint Paul and Rand Paul and then spark Trump God
If you're in a religion for
Where's your ears one of these televangelists you can't be like
My candidate is God and I'll hold on
Another another guy you know contenders showed up and God is not doing it for me so guys you should vote for
Yeah that does make it harder doesn't it
So yeah that's that's televangelists damn I think I like what I made her run
And this is this is what we talked about as far as me doing episodes is
After the last one with Mark Moreno
I never want to talk about Mark Marino a
I think the feeling is mutual same thing is true of Robert Jeffrey
Alright I never want to talk about Robert Jefferson baby we open up a whole new series where you start taking on some of these
Televangelist that I don't want to f****** tell her we got a lot of requests to people out of town.
Recover like Rick Wiles
Some of these
Maybe that's maybe
Maybe that's the new genre of Jordan Take the Wheel
Thanks for bringing this to my attention I'd still a little confused
Not by you but
Just buy some of these thoughts
The generations aspect is
Is f****** with
Yeah yeah yeah
Nuts
Anyway so we are
Acknowledge right.com
Ore-Ida at Dollar General store or it go to bed Jordan indeed and I we are on Facebook
That's right you want to rake reviews
Subscribe all that Dad be duboku
You do that for my katsoudas heard it
In the meantime
Neo
I'm Leo I am the juiciest role
Dzx Clark
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work