Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
We are the bad guys
MoneyGram
Stripe.com
Did we are Dan
Damn damn
Can I ask you a question
What's your
Right spot this been going on
This is going to be an iffy Brightspot
New Bright but it's also a little bit weird OK Google
About the time that the WWF put out an album or rappers did
The wrestler theme song rap version
I've listened to that in a long time so I can listen to it
That great but I started to think about other
Stuff that I haven't heard him here's the 69 Boyz
Do you remember this
69 Boyz I do not remember this
69 Boyz when I was in high school will you drive to lunch
And everybody liked that one way 69
The guy who drove us to lunch
I had an album called the wait is over by the 69 Boyz song on it called
Down to the base freaky down to the album play a little sample of it here it's so far down
You represent McDonald's
Free movie
Listen here's the problem you were talking over the part that's the most awesome about this I apologize
I see he's as a man ever made you buckle up at your knees
By the way you slowly ate your macaroni and cheese
This song is
Full of food metaphors
Everything is just about f****** but he's talking about like I'm going to drop my ham hocks in your mustard greens
Ridiculous until I listen to it was like that's just as fun as I remember it
Configure really ridiculous
Song
And then I realize that that came out in 1998 blue boy that's
22 years old
Years into Clinton's presidency
That's like when I was born that amount of time back would have been 1966
So what I was bored like the Beatles were putting out albums if he
It's been said to 69.
Prequel
The Beatles in the 69 Equinox
In time
Something like that
What about you I will tell you this if you ever heard of awesome games done
Stream kind of thing
Speed Run video game
Blind speed race
Super Mario maker
And watching these guys just slowly
Figure out how to get through this imp
Ausable Mario level is so
It's so fun to watch them learn and their little techniques get better each and every time at all so it's just mesmerizing
Everything moves around there
Jumping off a
The wall
It's very very fun and soothing
I hate to be this guy
Hate to be this guy recommended those
You repeatedly in the past
What does like really really hard Super Mario Maker levels
I think we've talked
Yeah they are very fun to watch
Children
To take it away from you
Thank you for the recommendation
Are the bright spot
So for the day
Episode to go over at today we're going to be going over March 24th and 25th 2020 Hyundai Genesis
So that would be Tuesday Wednesday of this week
And boy Everything Has Changed
Not only the real world but in the world of Alex's narrative
Okay
Well sorta
All right there is no coronavirus a lot of doubling back on stuff and we'll get down to business on that here
Second before we do got to take Mama to say thank you
Timbuk2 signed up and are starting to show
So first David is a deviant
Thank you so much you're now policy
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you dear David next Shawn take as much
Jesse thank you so much and I'll probably walk
Aaira
Thank you very much Sarah.
Bvnb
Valon same Floridian
And thank you so much you're on our policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thinking about thank you so much
Proof of residence
Thank you so much and I'll probably want
Thank you Max I'm finally a couple of special thank you
This book is donated on elevated level appreciate it very much
Superstore thank you oh so very much Charlotte
You are now a technocrat
And we play RPGs podcast
Thank you so much you are now a technocrat
What's the business
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
Play r p
DG's podcast
Alright
The two of you
The show I like sports
Bunzel's Workshop would appreciate it but also if you're feeling so inclined to spend some money
Perhaps I consider donating to charity in your area that supports people who are
Laid off service industry workers
Ivor caters to people experiencing homelessness food shelters
Food Bank
Excuse me stuff like that there
I'm probably are more severe.
Vanoss although
We do certainly appreciate
Organize your friends in
Angela rent strike
That's what I would
Alright then you can find more information about this by going to number 12 Cheesecake Factory and number two
To Jordan Square
That sounds like
So Jordan like I said today we have a very bizarre
Situation on Alex
The show and it starts
With him promising
To be right on the ball today
Alright right down the middle
Going to be good then
This time I believe it
Going to do a good job
But I'm going to be a really good boy today and I'm going to cover all the news and boy is it
Amazing
Billion-pound enchilada the sitting in the middle of the living room
I like enchiladas trillion pound elephant sitting on top of that
Knoxville
Where the hell are the bubbles going to take us sitting answer is right into chaos
Rack and ruin and destruction
So he's going to be good today and explain how the Lobos going to take us into rack and ruin
So that's a very exciting
That's a very positive message
But we've got going on here is that now
This is a hoax
Whole thing is a route know there is a real virus
Okay but being afraid of it is a hoax
In order for the gloves to take control by way of destroying
The economy by having people not go to work
Alex discusses have this hoax
But they're doing
Call Buster
Amazing
To watch
Flounder around like this
Try one big house after another
StairMaster stereo
But now everybody I talk to
It looks like it might kill 1% of people that are above 75 and sick
So Alex is definitely caught the right-wing talking
Points he is gotten a line with the people are at like the Tucker is in the
These were putting forth the Glenn Beck
And Hammer in there in sync.
The old people are willing to go and save the Economy Inn
The economy ticket
That's cool
It is interesting to think about these people being like you-know-who should
Fight in World War I
The Elder
Put them in the front line they're willing to sacrifice them
Themselves for the good of the country
They have less time left put them in the trench
Oh no million people died
They're going to die in 2 years anyways come on
It's really interesting considering the trajectory of the path that we seen Alex walk down
And
The way that this is
It seems out of Step
With the path we've been off lately feels like okay
This is the night this is the mood of the right-wing culture now and Alex
Is falling in line with his own animal
But he does believe he has
In the same way that whenever the going gets weird that we are turned Pro
Quotes about Hunter S Thompson
The
Be
If you're all doing that then Alex has to go a little bit beyond
That ain't so
Does Kai
Kind of get down
That's in the club
He insists that what's going on is
Go to channel that's going to be
Coronavirus
Well not the virus but the response to
Gotcha nobody bad
The force shutting down
Constitutional
Deadly dangerous
Where
Point operation immediate Warehouse
So it he wants to establish for your first of all.
Personality question and he wants to let you know
This is not because my business is effect
Absolutely but I do are completely exempt
From the shutdown orders a stay-at-home orders
I'm not worried about it at all
Let's see how the next
40 seconds ago
It makes me feel
Art supply shops in Annapolis
Today when Austin declares its
Stay open
Academy close in Dallas
Walmart
You're in Michigan are there a water filter Supply
Selling out
This morning and I literally got angle water filters aren't essential
Marijuana
Within 30 seconds of him saying that life
Is it shut down and I'm very mad about
And all gun stores are spiritually
His sponsor here so any gun stores not being open
Certainly a big slide
So yeah he's a probably a little bit misleading there about not to
Affected by news about the five-year-old out there who can't get his first a Kayana
His 5th birthday
They then what the f***
F*** are we doing
So these government-mandated shutdowns their death
Meladie not unconscious
Additional
This point we're really only seen state and local governments putting these kinds of shutdowns or
Call Motors in place
And these are well within the rights that states have to protect the community from infectious diseases unconstitutional
According to an article in Politico by UC Davis law professor Elizabeth
This is a part of the
States policing powers
Just reserved by the temperamental
Has been affirmed in case law pretty
The question of whether Trump could do that on a national level
That's an open question
It's not really having a good take on it because there isn't
A good president
Most thinking that he could do it
If he could do it it would take the form of an executive order
Using this National Emergency declaration is the groundwork
The court could try to challenge it but they might not be quick to
To do that while the virus situation is still intact
Kind of complicated
But
Even if Trump did this he probably would be unable to do much more than encourage every state
To just do what California New York and others are already doing
If you were to try to put a lockdown in place in that way that bypasses the state governors
Being the one
We were making
Precision and running their home state
There's a pretty decent chance
That would be on top
It seems like if you are a big
States rights
KUB
More in favor of the states choosing their own path forward
Or you could
Just called it all on
Use that as a buzzword
The general Point here is that nothing is happening right now is
In further there's really nothing
Kim happened it would be unconstitutional that would not be initiated by Trump
Congress does not ba32 lockdown the country but it could Grant Trump the authority to do that
Probably wouldn't do that unless he requests
He could release an executive order
Outside of that what we see is just
State Governors utilizing their temperament powers
Protective
And as you pointed out Alex should be totally fine with that yells about states rights all the fun
Nope unconstitutional under Clause 2 of Section 1
Where it says
The Constitution is whatever we say
Sure on whatever day
Napier right-wing propaganda
Otherwise you're not allowed to look at this
I'm pretty sure that
So Alex is really pushing
Pretty good on this people want to die
In order to make sure that the economy keeps coming along
Just great
And we start to
See the way that this narrative
It's going to take
Take shape over the course
This episode
Today from one of my lawyers who's I'm done about 6 years he's a good guy these big Democrat
Well
Means well.
Look at my 401k and I'm looking at my first grandchild coming in
Chameleon
No I didn't know that
Information
I do think we just can't shut everything down for
Indefinitely shut everything down
Does lawyer does not exist
This is just Alex doing a voice to repeat his own talking points in the guise of some big Democrat lawyer
Let me know
Yeah such b*******
You are in the Great Depression
Very common things to know for a lot of lawyers
Did you know that lawyers get
Get together on their off-hours and talk about the Great Depression and casual
You have to study
This sucks
Bulshit
But you're going to start to see over the course of this in terms of rationalizing that notion
We need to put everyone back to work now damn the torpedoes
Do care about the consequences
Or the
The dangers of
Virus the Coronavirus
Put everyone back to work cuz if the economy falls apart will have a Great Depression 7 million was starve to death
Cure is worse than the disease
Right so that fixed
Statistic is going to become a very important part of his rationalization
Statistics are a huge
And just like
Viruses
Mutate you know how they do that huh
Sales pitch
Okay
Alex is in a position now where a lot of his normal Avenue
For making money during this crisis have been cut off
He's got a very Stern warning from the New York attorney general's office
And he can't really
Selfing
Like it silver the way he was
He's artificially increase the demand so high on the supply of the food supplier
The Dave had to not allow him
To take orders
Anymore
He is in a position where like well I can't do that
But as we saw her last episode
He is now realize that this
Poor Quinn
The Trump was promoting
It involves ink
And he sells the real redpill which includes
And so he's going really
Into like
Well now it's time Selznick
With viruses.
Happen
The sink
What does chlorophyll do
Chloroquine
A medical version of what is in
Tonic that you get at the store
Wow
And their troops all over the equatorial World ago
One of their Jen
Can
Alex goes on a rant about gin and tonics
Repeatedly like
Many letters from Attorneys General that he can
Is he trying to build a collection there he seems to be like
The kite like a dog
Going up to an invisible electric fence getting shocked
And then like trying to go a little bit to the side
Is this okay
This fence
Is a giant Circle but what if I
I just go in
Eventually I'll find every part of this
Circle right now it's all about selling
And I was able to find some studies it seems
Suggested zinc supplementation could have an effect on preventing things like the common cold
I'm not going to get too bogged down and Alex's shamelessly transparent attempt to sell the real red pill
I think he's going a little bit overboard but whatever
Amore
Bridgeton the fact that you still pushing the clerk
Particularly considering
Call the quarter quell which
Which doesn't Inspire confidence that he has a good handle on it
By the time we'd recorded our last episode there been to non-fatal overdoses in Nigeria
People taking
The irresponsible advice to take or Quinta
To treat or prevent the Coronavirus
Virus but since then
68 year old man in Arizona died after taking chloroquine phosphate
And it's 61 year old wife was sent to the hospital and critical
Condition
She survived
Explain Direct
We saw Trump on TV every channel and all his buddies said that it was safe
Tom kept saying it was basically pretty much a
Secure
Alex has one of those Buddies
Play in the same games as Oliver
Yeah news broke about the couple at least a day before the episode that we're listening to right now
Advice has taken at least one life and send others to the hospital and Alex's comparing it to quinine being in tonic water
This is absolutely staggering levels of the responsibility that he has on display here it's just you couldn't do a worse job.
If you try
I think a lot of people are willing to sacrifice themselves so the Dow doesn't go down a percentage
Good point but what we don't know is that also Republicans are willing to kill them
To make sure that it doesn't go down to four
You didn't know that
Did not know
It's very
It's very crucial
Crucial
Yep
So this is a psyop
It's going on
Apparently according to Alex
And also Trump knows
But it's a Scion
Trump knows so much that doesn't seem to exist or
Yeah this is where we get into the other element of the viruses nobigdyl naira
President-trump
Weather in a balancing act
Where
Bonded
The virus has killed people and is a serious issue
Ignoring the virus over there they only lost about 4,000
Italy's over 5,000 now because they have the oldest population in Europe
Because they all lived
They lose 70,000 on average a year
From the flu there
Firstly this is not a psyop
And if the siop is supposed to be portraying the situation that it's the end of the world I only know one
Bucking person who said
It's over for Humanity
It will only be lone survivors
So I guess Infowars of the tip of the spear on the siop we've already established
Globulin
Foreshore and he's working for China and in the mainstream media
I wanted to take a moment to address Alex is dumb dumb idea that this is just like the flu which he is insinuating at the end of that clip
And he has he does say pretty
You consistently over these comparing
Flu deaths
To this
I talked to my aunt
I think that your aunt
And a lot of folks on Twitter have this narrative in their head and they can
I can't seem to get past
This thing
From what I can tell the only thing his argument is based on his a wrong number of deaths
The come from the flu each
This is a really incomplete way of looking at
The situation and there's a couple of really important consideration
Keep in mind to help understand why this coronavirus is definitely not like
Flu and if not taken seriously it will be much
The first and easiest to understand Alameda this
A very
Fatality rate
The two conditions
The flu has approximately 8.1% fatality rate
Estimates for the coronavirus art about 14
But some countries are showing significantly higher numbers than that
I'm just that level it's at least 10 times deadlier for people who getting
On top of that you have a higher estimated transmission rate from coronavirus then from the flu
Each person has the flu generally will give it to 1.3 people compared
To the at least two people
Both are infected
Each person who has
Has the Coronavirus
He person has the virus one average give it to two people and that's triple the number of cases
In each iteration
Yeah that's how I
Exponential growth
But that estimate might actually be really low
And part of what makes things really scary is that the coronavirus has an incubation. They can last up to 40
13 days
As opposed to the about 4-day window for the flu
Is incubation period is the. Where person
Can you be asymptomatic
Have no idea they have the virus but be contagious the entire time
Because of his longer incubation. The cases that were seeing arrive in the hospital today maybe people who have been
Sick and not doing it for two we
During that time it's possible that they spread the virus to a bunch of other people who we won't know we're sick until the week or two from now
It may already be too late to do anything about where we'll be in two weeks
But it's not too late
To make sure that three weeks or a month from now things are not
Continuing down that same portable Pat
And that's why we should get back to work
Next week makes up Hazmat
Right
One of the things that makes this past so bad that
You could be on
Is that people will coronavirus are approximately 10 times more likely to require hot
Hospitalization
And people who come down with
Flu
Because of this
If they suspect very fast as a potential to completely overwhelm the hospital system in the country
At which point things have the possibility of
Deteriorating dramatic
Especially considering that at the
Point the hospitals are overwhelmed
They're still going to be more patient
Come again and people who are coming into things
Aren't coronavirus related wrong
If there's anything I know about America's Healthcare System as it stands right now it is set up
Any challenge
Standings
Possibilities American spend more on Healthcare than anybody else in the world to make
Make sure that when
Outbreak
Like this happened we don't have to worry about it then
Now you can add on top of that the factor people with coronavirus require a longer and more intensive hospitalization then do most
Patience
I'm in for the flu
A limited sample study published in the Journal of the American Medical Association found a median length of stay for Coronavirus patient
Doobie 10 days
As compared to an average of 6.3 days for the flu
According to a 2015 2016 set of data from the
Healthcare cost and utilization project
The coronavirus spreads more incubates for longer that's giving a longer contagion window hospitalized as more and causes
Does longer hospital stays
In patients who do end up requiring Medical Care
All of these variables combined are unsustainable
At a certain point
And you can easily imagine how this will have all sorts of Ripple effects
Could end up being horrific
Not least among them
All of the
The other needs
Of the medical system that would be left
And 000 of the flu
People because it's not like this is replacing the flu
The Coronavirus
Flu this year there's also people getting influenza top of a coronavirus you can only have one
Unconstitutional to have more
So the flu is no joke and I'm not here to say it's not an issue
But anytime you hear someone compare our current situation to the flu there either a complete psychopath or there's no idea what they're talking about
Cowards like Alex hide behind a sort of b*******
About there being like 50,000 deaths from the flu a year in America
That statistic is inaccurate and even if it were do you think you would change his tune if like 55,000 people end up dead
From the Coronavirus
It's just a mask
Absolutely
So some of this information to little bit wrong
41 Tappan has a higher proportion of people over the age of
65 in Italy but that's not in Europe
If you haven't media if you're going by median age Germany and Monaco both have populations that are older than Italy so those are
Also Alex's dad about 70,000 flu deaths
2 year and Italy
Completely incorrect
It comes from him not knowing how to read
There's a study was published in November 2019 in the international Journal of infectious
Just diseases
2000 flu deaths
Italy during the time period study
I'm fairly certain that this is a source
But what he fails to point out that this study covered the period of winter 2013 through the end of flu season
27th
Every year
What
That's 4 years
Okay so that's that's
What 280,000 deaths per year
We don't know you're you're multiplying instead of
Striker dividing
Also it's really needs to be pointed out that this study wasn't
They took all-cause fatality data from the country and then combined it with the rates of people getting in
Influenza-like illnesses and estimated that there would be 68000 deaths attributable to the flu in that five years
The study literally says quote
The study should be validated using
Cause specific mortality data which however was not available
For the entire study.
No matter how you slice it Alex's number is
Completely false
Some contacts he's providing it in
Actually according to that very study
Jeep 2014
Flu season throwing that time
There were 7027 deaths in Italy attributable to the
The flu
As of the time that I Was preparing this episode
It's higher now but there were 7503 death
From the coronavirus in Italy
Already hired
Glad for the year
The signup is not the media saying that this is the end of the world
Because the media isn't so
Alex Jones and his friends were a couple of months
The song up his people like Alex and most of the right-wing media tried to convince their audio
Reality is reality
It's a game they play so often and generally they get away with it
Because they're yelling about stuff like the war on Christmas
Some other booty
Concerned it's completely made up
Absolutely this one is not
And no amount of yelling it's just
Like the flu go back to work
It's going to make things right
It's not the
Nope but doesn't play by the same rules as these other propaganda narratives really does feel like this
Like you
Like it's almost like
The culmination of all right-wing propaganda is to eventually get it
It's people too
Like it is
It's almost like Fox News was a false flag
To kill the elderly at the end of the day like they started at 20 years ago
And they're like okay
We're going to have too many old
It's just going to happen we got to do something about this
I have a new
We're going to get a black president
And we're going to lose people
Mines and then killing the payoff and kill
Yeah I mean like if we were on Infowars you be suggesting that is a serious thought
Alex
Because everything is so different now
On in his rhetoric
He's trying to underplay all this
Keep out has to sort of pretend like the pastor
Didn't realize
Say that stuff
So here's Warner
Was never about the virus
It was okay
Pandemonium are they are freaking out
Because of the economy and the breakdown and the global is trying to use it
Virus
Because
So I will grant
That Alex does always talk
About the economy
And now you should Panic about
Play music gold salesman cuz he had a board
Strong financial interest in the that narrative but
You know that isn't entirely inaccurate but
Yes it's viruses deadly it's not like SARS and things that were just a hype up and scare people
They were saying last week
On
Thousand confirmed we're locked in here a few minutes go 24,000
The internal Chinese numbers that leaked
Rocky publish in China by the people daily
Said 24000 dead
Yesterday
So what we think they're doing is they're just putting the number of dad is a number of infect
When your sources at the UN from your own research how bad is this
Computer game at
John's hot
Hopkinsville
That's the only figure I have seen
Seems to be
Route to be a 20
Percent
Mortality rate
The official numbers now show
Chinese government says 15%
They're just introducing us
New age of the new millennium
This isn't just going to be
The kills people that have anal sex or whatever or use needle
This is something that's going to kill you and your family and make you have a heart attack and make your lungs bleed out
And it
Stocks
It's true
That is very concerned.
But now the numbers are coming out we know that it is indeed
Killing healthy young people that is killing a high number of those
Coming out of places like an l
A beginning a swell
You can't believe a word
The comes out of tricon's mouth
Go back a month ago
Horrible Foods
Sponsors a lot of
You listen
Spreading all over the world and it's
Got a high kill rate
The world is kind of high kill
Wow
Right now but not the way I want to sell it
Poor guy
His narratives harder than rise of Skywalker this is brutal
Just because of
Part of the things you said before doesn't mean that he wasn't driving real hard
And some of those
Numbers might sound more close to Accurate now
But he was saying them as the reality
Two-and-a-half months ago so they were not true then
They might lead to a little bit of a like
Far off
Still
Civil
So Alex
You can just see an absolute
Desire to pretend the past
And his
His rhetoric has
And then what it has
We get through this a little bit more you'll start to understand exactly why that's the case
But Alex is thrilled with the idea that Trump is coming out saying that
Got to
Get back to work
Do that
Number of jobs almost 160 million
I think it's going to be wonderful to be tremendous repercussions it will be from that
Probably more death from that then anything to were talking about with respect
A2Z virus
So they're listening to
Obelisk d.c.
University studies
The Great Depression killed seven million people malnutrition
That 7 billion people I number
Is not true
That's an erroneous stat based on flawed research that was but advertised specifically as anti u.s. Pro Sophia propaganda
A real study to back up his claim
It's the best I can do is article and profit about the flawed research that has been widely discredited
Major universities major university studies
What an ass
The problem with Trump and Alex's argument about their desire to turn the economy back on as they put it is that it
It's Dom
The framing of that argument that they think that they're having is that the virus will cause X number of deaths
But to avoid those deaths you need to shut down the economy temporarily which could lead to wider number of deaths
According to them if x is lower than y
It's not worth it
Did the shutdown
Things in order to stop the virus we should
Need to take the hit
Keep moving
Their thinking is flawed because it's not a question
Of X number of deaths versus y number of death
If you don't take this
Seriously
And take some action now
We will get that X number of deaths from the virus which will lead to
Complete collapse of our medical system
According to many experts
Ultimately and even worse economic collapse
Then you would have had from a temporary shutdown
In effect
One of your leg your options
Ry or
X + y 2x option that's on the table that is realistic or feasible
Love's Edition they're not big
Hands of a single variable
Man you got to have
Two variables got a smashing together
Silly
Insane in circumstances like this you should always choose the option that's
Controllable
The amount of pain that could be caused by this economic shutdown is pretty high
But all that pain can be mitigated by government action
There could be relief provided that if properly handled could minimize the amount of death that would be caused by a shutdown
That's a problem that can solve itself
If we let
The same is not true of Legend
The consequences of coronavirus just run free through the workplace
And population
The effects and consequences of that are fairly
Unpredictable
Outside of being a we can probably predicted it would be really bad
The unspoken argument that's being made here is that the well-being of Corporations
Is more important than your life
Alex
Pretend that's not what he saying by citing his bogus stat about starvation of the Great Depression
But mainstream right-wing talking
Pinpoint the one that he's working off of is exactly what you see on Fox News
Glenn Beck
Glenn Beck said on his show on March 24th the same day as this episode that quote I would rather have my children stay home and all of us
Over 50 going
And keep this economy going and working
Even if we all get sick I would rather die than kill the country
Trump's advisor Larry Kudlow beard on Fox News and said quote
The Cure can't be worse than the disease
And we're going to have
Have to make some difficult trade-offs
The conversation that's happening on the right at this point is how if
It can help the stock market thousands of deaths are an acceptable price
To pay or at very worried
A quote difficult trade-offs
This is the talking point that Alex
Putting forth
The Cowardly mask is fake
Depression stat
Alex is arguing that the market is more important
Public Health
Which should be problem for him
Forgot who yelled about Obama Death panels for years for
Yahoo
Just as recently as a few days ago was ranting about Bill Gates and the quote
For killing granny
You would think that he would be against the idea of sacrifice of human lives
Serve the economic interests of the already very rich but
Whatever
It does feel like the rich
HR just convince
That America is
Is no longer capable of torches and pay
Like they're just like it's just never going to happen again so we can act with impunity
Huber it does seem like you
But I don't know maybe they're right
It does seem like they've convinced a large enough number of people to essentially acted ways that would kill
Hinderer anybody else from doing it I don't know maybe maybe it's just
Where We Are
Vassals were
Worser
I don't know
So Alex
Austin has put in place this
You know stay at home
Situation
And Alex's
Barry
Insistent
That you know
Infowars
What is not involved in that and they are exempt
Travis County Austin Texas shut down order
I just came out 1 hour ago
Home work safe order 20200
Forecast
By the mayor of the City of Austin
Listen to me because it's too much fun to get
It's over for Humanity
Last week
Was in place last week
I'm not sure why why Alex
Always get so defensive about the
The dumb people he talks to her wrong about things
But if his friends and associates. They had to stay indoors by government degree like a week ago that reflects poorly on them
More than anything else
He knows uninformed people
And I have no idea why you feel the need to insist that everyone is as dumb as his friends secret knowledge
Also I have no idea why he's making so
Such a huge production out of proving that is businesses
Probably technically considered an essential business according to the Austin
Stay-at-home order
It's a very weird
And I don't know what he's worth
Bonding to
And also those numbers of the bill the 2020-32
Board that's
Skip the date
No yeah
Don't you dare what I mean it is the title of the
Yeah it's just the date
So I
I was curious about this and I'm like why is he so defensive
About being exam
Well know he is but he gives a little bit of a clue here
Bleeding at the emergency wasn't place last week
Holding the federal laws
This is starting to come into focus with me
I have a strong suspicion that this may at least be a related to some members of Alex
The staff not wanting to come in during the outbreak
Which I completely understand
However what I find interesting
Sing about that clip is it a tells us a lot about what Alex's employees
Think about what he does
For one he claims as an authoritative fact
Don't even claim that
You know something
Biggest thing that we know where essential
And their responses that syrup
That tells me that his staff know that Alex is
Is full of s***
And they don't trust him to know any
The only reason you would ever respond to someone like that is
If you don't believe that I'm just biding
Yeah that's that has the sound of
Of them just being like
Buddy
We know you
Wework
Shut the fuk up
We don't care what you have to say because you're a f****** like you're wrong
All the time
Second this tells me that at least some of the enforced staff
Do not feel like what they do is
If Alex shows them disorder that says that news organizations are clearly exempt and they're still not convinced of
The point of show
Propaganda QVC
3rd and possibly most importantly
Alex's Alex's crew has a
No idea what's going on in the real world
If they thought there was a lockdown in place a week prior
Then they're completely lost
These are the sorts of people Alex has work
It is alleged news Operation
People have no idea what's happening around
And that does explain a lot
So thank you for giving me that glimpse
Into
Yeah that's that's a boy
That's a boss bitching
Employees lunch
Yeah I think
That's probably what the what's the
Emotion
Behind you
Send a text with Alex gives a big brag
That I think is
Incorrect going to start by saying he's not going to brag no
Just Brakes
The Constitution
I am full
Knowledge is power
Information is power
That's why they don't want you to
I want you to have
As so
Lamp
Husbad
I can recite
Most
Of the pillow protectors
Amendment 1
How many are in the Bill of Rights I just know the second one that's most of it's mainly the one
More words than I remember
I love to say whatever I want to say but then
That like
Knowledge is power
So that would suggest somebody who knows all of the Bill of Rights
I would love the idea of like just being a Gaston studio and being like I know most of the Bill of Rights
What are the
Name them right now right now right now
What's the 6th Amendment
Sixth amendment that much
Tell me what the six
He has
No idea
So I'm his next clip Alex gets to talking about how
You know
Media media
Trying to take people's right
Suppose the president said about not panicking
Cowards
Edsby
Onelife
Tattoo
Hear it
Stitches
Alright buddy
Clutch
The actual micro microchips in deerskin under the skin
I'm out
Are they made with Nana
China's doing and everybody doing and it's all here
The mark of the beast everything happening
Totally insane
DIY White House were the ones who are trying to request the ability to track Everyone by their cell phone data
I was not vmedia
His employees
Alex can pretend all David is heroism doing the exact same things he's claiming the villains are doing
But that doesn't make
True
Also that story about the vaccine tattoos is no more true than it was when it was a lie
A few days ago
There's Research into a possible invisible tattoo that could be used as a vaccine record
But it's nowhere near ready for implementation
The only citation Alex has about this is a headline that says quote Asia deploys Innovative if invasive Tech
Coronavirus
Which does not mention these tattoos at all
Kind of sounds like it might if you only read the headline
What if you were paying attention
There's so many things that
I could be in there
Oh my God just imagine what kind of innovative invasive technolite bacon that article
Probably shooting
Scott archery so much more interesting articles
Knives all day
So Alex is celebrating that the market is
Is going back up to drop the same people need to go to work
Jones
Industrial
Is today
Driving down
It's up
Wow one
730 three-point
That's not a reason to go up
The stock market went up
I've been suppressing China and India another area
Really that's what he said
Again
In the market even though the Democrats
Holding up
Stimulus package
Give me the latest on that
Alex should be in favor of these bailouts
Have a problem with Obama was supposed to be the stimulus package and how was
Fiscally irresponsible
Alex kinky was goddamn principal straight it's just disoriented this makes no sense
Also I would like to make a formal predict
I rarely make predictions on the show but I feel
A hundred percent confident
Alright let's see if Trump does Rush people back to work
Alex will celebrate
Then
If things get as bad as experts are suggesting that he could
Alex who pretend he wasn't in favor of that plan
And in fact it was the globalist like mnuchin
Before strop to sacrifice
The good people of this country
Deceive the international Bankers money in the stock market
Specially led by Bill Maher
King of the left Steve mnuchin
This will almost certainly be how he rewrites
I'm almost positive
Cause of disaster and then blame everybody else
It is
Like the stock market
Going up and down in the pass
Last few weeks has made me want to start
It's just pretend
Goes up because he says something that he probably won't do so there's 1,000
Boys that go up then tomorrow it's going to go down by 1,000 points doesn't
It's empty why are we still pretending it does
Very it's very strange it's kind of surreal to watch
It yeah
Yeah what are we doing here it does I don't know about starting fires I think that's irresponsible at someone's house
Burned out
Triggering me I apologize
I would say that it might be an indication that we need to rethink how that whole thing works
Settle down maybe we take a look at this whole thing about Market
Abby
Let's figure out how to do this better
That's why we got to elect Joe Biden for president and and make sure that I get a gyro tattoos
Never had stocks
I don't know if it's true. My thought on Twitter
Why not
Anyway this next clip I really I think
This
Is
Pure form of a
Pegasus really his Solon
Display
And he's reading a bunch of headlines
That are people who have warnings about the disastrous consequences that could come
Promos not taking a very response
Pulls right towards that this
The circumstance
That were in right now
And how bad things could be
DC closes businesses Louisiana
America
Dubliner clampdown even as president considers easing
Unemployment claims Parts delayed check Goldman buy gold
Anymore
Farewell
Pot shops
Liquor stores
An warning
India lockdown
Dow Jones Industrial Average
That right there is the image I want you to keep in your mind of Alex Jones
As this gets worse and the realization that this isn't a globalist Blatz that's in
Remember that f****** monster
Remember Alex Jones is the person who mockingly read headlines about the possibility of all doctors being infected with the Coronavirus
Remember Alex Jones was the person who mockingly read a headline about the possibility
The real
Opening businesses prematurely could have horrible
Remember him like that
Because that's who he is
Alex has made all the money he can offer
This crisis so he doesn't really give a s*** and
You stopped selling the food buckets most likely because he caused a run on his supplier who couldn't keep up with the artificially inflated demand
According to Infowars website as of March
25th are opening back up orders
Quote for a very limited time but it's also been called pre-orders and there's like a 12-week delay on delivery
So this is no longer going to be something to
Can push with the same intensity
If the whole idea is that the s*** is about to hit the fan so you need to act now to get this food
It's hard to balance that with buy this now you'll get the food and like
Three months
At the same time
The New York attorney general's letter
And he knows better than to try and insinuate that is product or
Protection from water solution to the virus
Which is how he was marketing them for a stretch where you know he was more interested in making the audience afraid of the virus
There's no Financial incentive and now it's making the audience afraid that way anymore
So he's not doing it
As it stands now he has nothing to gain
For making the audience
Afraid of the fire so he's moved the rhetoric to the
I have some people will get it there be some jazz
Looks like the flu talk
Cuz that's
Where it is
Like most of
Where is the money right
The money is in not losing money
In an economic shutdown
Autonomy
He can make the argument all day that his business is exempt from the shutdown and he might be right but in
In a time of difficulty and layoffs
How many was ridiculously price pills do you think is going to be selling
Do you want his listeners are choosing what essential do you think
Bone broth is going to make the cut
I think for a surprising number of people at will in that
That bums me out real I don't think so
He may not have always been
He's grown into
A vapid cruel profiteering mod
If you need any further evidence that Alex Jones is a piece of s*** and he's only driven by his own bottom line you can find it buried in that clip
You responded to it a little bit and it's this
Unemployment claims to Parts delayed checks Goldman buy gold now
Right there
You see a momentary flash of him remembering that he used to make a lot of money selling gold off yard is just like this
He remembers it
And there's a moment of
But there's no money in it from to pitch Cole to his audience now so he does
That's the
Hell that's how you know he doesn't mean what he sells
If he philosophically believed in buying gold that part of the show wouldn't have
Curiously ended when Teddy Anderson lost
Is precious metals license
If Alex believed the magical gold
Oldest oldest audience for years
In-N-Out
Answer to be imaginary Financial
Collapsi got prophesying
He would keep telling them to buy gold and you be telling people to buy gold now
Even though he wouldn't be
Beginning a cut
For the last month we would have been hearing and being like our everything's going to go to Hell by gold now
Hey look I don't have any
Sponsor but there's
Plenty of them go find yourself gold
He doesn't do that
Cuz he's a f****** fraud
Dick
Guy sucks can't believe that there
I can't believe how many people are buying the
So many people are buying the line by
The line is people are willing to die in a pandemic for you
Fred Wild
That is wildlife
The opportunity for the
Oh man
Yep
It's it's a mess
Yeah we need to end abortion so we can kill the old people
And then will restart
Make sense
Man
So Alex Goes to Carl's and I takes one call and then I don't I don't
Because guys
Went on
CDC website
Dc.gov
I was trying to
Find
Virus
In in the US
And I can
Or anyting
Honor
Hundreds of people that have it and nobody's died yet so
Why we working is Trump fauci get fired
I got to say there was a time when I would have said Trump would never fire the guy who's been the director of the national anthem
Attitude of allergy and infectious
Diseases of the 1984 in the middle of an active pandemic
Max
I hear Alex like that and
I don't think it would surprise me too much
Be fired fauci and replace them like Jared Kushner
Triple H
I don't know
Might as well
McMahon is free right
Also factories with the NIH
What are you
I'll go ahead and sign off on
Half of what they call her saying though it's much as the cdc's website is not the best suppository
Information
The information he's looking for is easily available though I just I don't I don't know why you insist he has to find it on the cdc's
Agree with him through website could be better
Also
If there are cities where they have confirmed cases but not deaths
That does not necessarily mean that they will all be recover
It's also possible that these cases are still active case
Something Alex
Doesn't
Doesn't happen
Anyway
This next clip
Staggering
Everything in it is
Just about everything in this
Listen very carefully because there's a bunch of points where Alex is just like
You can almost hear him
In a writers room
Yeah yeah bouncing ideas off of
Blue Sky
Lockdown so government can be a savior that's a big Jack and push a force inoculation
The virus is just now starting to explode
Other people as well
Just like
Coronavirus or flu virus does the greater numbers
And that's how people aren't scared
Viruses are scared of new one
It's a real problem
Older people go ahead video tape it put it on the internet
Locked up for that
Everything
The word out
To get the maximum fear then I went oh it's no problem now we're back to work
But then I pop an 18-month shutdown of the US
Psyop
Didn't respond properly
It is a cooked
Superfly
Ordering Chinese
Virus
So they would know the trajectory of it
This is wow
Almeda
Wow and what's amazing about it is
A lot of it directly contradict
His previous narrative
This is staggering
I want to I want to take this piece-by-piece or at least a lot of these pieces because they are
So a quote
They said people aren't scared of old viruses
Cuz they're scared of new one
Altos make that up
I'll be dead certain that if a new vac
Seen resistant widely transmittable polio showed up or like a vaccine resist
Version of measles came around cold virus
Bar Rescue the s*** out of me going to watch reruns of the match game to Dan
Card sharks
They're scared of things out of China so China took a real outbreak
So Alex thinks this is a real outbreak
I thought Obama sold
What's the China they released on themselves of the false flag or something
Outbreak
I don't know
China told their people go ahead and videotape that put it on the internet
Right there was no evidence supporting information at all Oz just decided to report that the Chinese government produced
Or facilitated all those videos
He's previously used to scare his audience which is like this
I saw a haunting video last night
Cecily was in
Chinese
And it was just a video
Wuhan
Of all the apartment buildings at night
Light in the background
And The Scream
The Haunting blood-curdling screams
People that mental
I want to see a nevermind
I will yeah we've got the link
February 24th I guess that was a China putting out proper
Mike Adams and Alex are disseminated
Even more infuriating because they
Tried to stop it
They put the man who leaked it into jail and then let him die of Coronavirus
It's the complete opposite he was like dude it's not even wrong it's
Demonstrable Eevee opposite
That's fake news
Space
Quote and so they did with GG and ping
The party said they put the word out to hype this up
I was just completely making that up he has no evidence of it it's
Completely pulled out of thin air as he's just riffing around
Quote
The numbers up
Hype the death numbers up now that's now Wall Street Journal
China lied about the numbers
But they were much higher
First things first
About who's Pacifica guilty of lying about inflated numbers out of China
UB wise
Consider that Alex spent multiple days on his show back in early February
Pretending that they'll probably a glitch on a website had revealed secretly that there were actually over
24000 deaths
From Coronavirus
In China
As of February
Coronavirus situation in Aldie
Biological weapons expert
And a top scientist scanning the virus and saying it's man-made
We've got to get ahead of this and if you notice
Virus numbers
Thousand confirm I walked in here few minutes ago 24,000
The internal Chinese numbers that leaked
Ratchet publish in China by the people daily
4000 dead
Yesterday
So what we think they're doing is they're just putting the number of dad is a number of insect
Think about that
So that wasn't an isolated incident
Alex reportedly suggested the China was Under reporting a number of sick and dead because at that point it was in his financial interest to make the viruses
Itself seems as bad as possible
In China is evil as
Like Donna is
Ridiculous he's saying
The China over-inflated their numbers he was the one who did that
Dan
He did it and he only has good ideas
But I guess if he thought
What's that that 24,000
Was actually China reporting that number as opposed to a propaganda narrative that him and his buddies cooked up
Claiming that China's right
I guess that's probably his own Supply
That's nonsense
I have literally no idea what Alex is talking about when he says that the Wall Street Journal admit it
The China lied about the numbers saying that they were higher than they actually were
I think he was just
So I can find plenty of articles that suggested there's a good chance
The China particularly in the early stages under-reported
But I legitimately can't find any credible Source that's
Suggested that they over
Now it's in Alex's financial interest to downplay the virus itself
Open focus on building a narrative the China intentionally built up some kind of
So he's completely fabricating a story about G commanding people to take videos and Wuhan to scare the American
If that was used plan though Alex did a great job of playing
Department
So then he goes on
It's a
Cooked up global
Ordering the Chinese to do this with a man-made virus
Which was a real outbreak
A man-made virus made the real outbreak
That the Chinese gots but it's all
Little chunk right here it's not
Possible for the Chinese to have
Taking a real outbreak
Well I mean I guess it depends on what you define as a real outbreak
I guess but then it's still just as overcomplicate things and make a manmade virus a real outbreak but
Soda viruses man-made and Alex is absolutely no evidence
That these unnamed Shadow be globalist
Told the Chinese government to do any
Also be bad news for Alex an article recently came out from the Scripps Research
Institute that
Completely ruined
The man-made virus Theory
Christian Anderson the author of the study said quote
By comparing the available genome sequence data for known coronavirus strains
We can firmly determined that stars coronavirus to originated through natural process
They found solid evidence of a natural origin
For the virus
Disqualifying evidence that it was made in a lab
One of the main pieces of evidence on that front was that he's had the virus has a unique backbone
Whereas if someone were trying to create this in a lab they would have to use an existing viruses backbone for the basic molecular
And then they would build the virus from there
They wouldn't be able to do the back going to be able to infect people
Yeah a massive amount of
Research necessary.
Bellevue Factoria
Beat this quote
The fact that coronavirus has its own backbone essentially disqualifies it as possibly being lab-created
And the fact
Is back on his very similar to related viruses known in the wild make
Responsibility
Of it being a product of Natural Evolution
Incredibly
Almost absolutely
Definitively like
Signify
I guess you can believe all these scientists whose articles published
The nature medicine
Journal or you can believe Alex
Extends up to see whatever mood he's in on a given day images
Whatever you choose whatever you want to do there
Cliff is all just made up
At all the little pieces of it and it's
You even like
I found two things
In there that are
Specifically like counter to reality
I certainly
You know
But their counter to Hughes reality
That's what's so abusive about that
It hurts me
I didn't run all of this made-up ship is in service
Justifying the death
So many people
Potential.
I mean in his mind
They're already done
Because that's what he's saying right there he said people are going to die some young people
They're going to die
And then he goes on
This whole thing so all of this is in justification for what he thinks is
Is already happened
Inevitable which is the deaths of
So many hundreds of
The people
But
That's because
You have to be more scared
About the Great Depression that will be coming
Because
7 million people starve to death during it
Built to shut down and cower in fear maybe we should rebuild
Yeah the food supply breakdown a depression
Watch The Grapes of Wrath
Major universities again Grapes of Wrath is a.
It sounds right
It's so much of the rhetoric is entirely based
Just on this image of the seven million dead in the Great Depression
Lazy lazy work
So Alex has read an article or
Headline
In foreign policy
That pissed him off
Shutdown
Must be total
Sorry America
Full lockdown is coming this was from a week ago
Pieology.com
Garrett
Council on Foreign Relations
And she talks about sorry America's over
Sorry again for months and months and months
And yes you're going to have a depression
They all are
That's prop up the Lost Lady
So I read that article that Alex is talking about and it's
Justice Rider posting an op-ed that has the position that people should start
Consider the fact that things make it worse
It'll be wise to observe the examples of countries a little further down the path like Italy to get a sense of what could become a
I grant that some of the stuff is pretty star
And may come off as a little bit extreme
Like y'all were having a saying goodbye to friends for awhile you know like that kind of thing
But where
But Lori Garrett is basically just writing
It's meant to offer some realistic
Concrete advice for people who might end up
In a similar position
Is people in Italy are in now
Alex didn't look up Garrett and find out that ucfr that's in her bio it's in the article
But Alex Mills to point out that she is a quote former senior fellow for Global health
At the Council on Foreign Relations
Former
Steve pieczenik
Former CSR
I was also left off a few relevant things about a resume
Like how she won the 1996
Pulitzer Prize for explanatory journalism
Covering the outbreak of Ebola
I don't think she has any relevance
Expertise.
Different things to poke Awards
Four books covering Public Health crises so I think that
She's a bit of talk to her on this
I was just making up issues investor
Absolutely no idea who she has Investments and even if she
If he even has any
He's just coming up with a fabricated accusation he could use to tarnish your credibility because that's the level of work that he does in his audience
And I'm going to be I will agree with him this one time
It is
I consider it to be far more liberal
To choose great
Depressions over Mass
I'm going to go with you
I'm fine with
I am going to
You say that you can paint me
That way if you want to because the opposite means
You would rather choose Mass Graves over a receipt
So
F*** off
Alex is really pushing
Main prongs that ice of his
I want to go back to work minimizing the virus
Narrative
Are the
These are billion people died of starvation in Detroit depression
That's one
Now that the other prong is
Everybody dies from the flu particularly people in Italy
Most Italians left
Haley was I guess
60 million people
60 70 thousand deaths a year from flu
We are three
We have 35,000
Because you made up
It's imaginary
So Alex is talking about
No big deal
The coronavirus right I think it made for a while then you sick for a little bit it's all good
If you're not
Super
10-14 Days Inn at exit 79 days while you're sick
And then after that you're not even communicable
People have respiratory issue people have flu they have
Let him die
So I mean Alex has the basic incubation. Correct here and there's some preliminary research showing that you know can laugh about
10 days of active illness
Alex is driving at here is absurd
Some Studies have suggested that you are the most contagious and that. When you don't know you have the virus
When you're asymptomatic
So if everybody follows his advice is only practicing
Some distancing if you feel really sick
There's a really good chance
Completely out of control
The bigger issue I have here is how this is
Complete betrayal of Alex's established narrative about the virus
He's saying that it's no big deal that incubates for about 2 weeks then you got about a week and a half a sickness and after that it's clear sky
Is a bad month
Call
What are the major consistent features of Alex's contact over the past weeks
But about how this
This is a secret new HIV that the globalist have Unleashed on the population
And part of that
His mind is the even
After you recover
The coronavirus keeps coming back
2.0 Hy-Vee
Everybody's already got it
6 months from now
Tablet
We told you
Probably half now
Everyone's going to get this
You could go hide out in a basement somewhere you're not getting away from it
Because once it gets in the body
The human body incubates
Bioweapon virus
Floats around
Last days even in the sunshine
And it's coming for you
I think this is a serious threat
Penske
If it comes back again and again the person
Wheelies
This is been a standard element of the story about the virus that Alex's used to create the fear in his audio
You can see now
It is no longer useful to him so you just discard it entirely
Which he's capable of doing because he was just making it up to begin with
He doesn't believe any of the shoot he's saying so want something
No longer in his interest f*** it
Hello maybe like a week from now if he wants to he can just be like to keep coming back
Then this what do you think now will be forgotten if you don't work couple weeks
You're it's incubating you're not even sick right then you're sick for a couple of weeks you know
No big deal then you're fine for a couple of weeks while the
Virus
Germinates inside you
And you're sick for a couple weeks
That gives you 50% of the year that's
Find an that's not bad you could be at the office to keep the economy going
So Alex Goes to cause any takes another call who's dumb
I mean
Article. I was just reading that they were
I have the worst flu season
1st of January
Are they more than normal are there hospitals
New York Times Washington Post Olen January said
In one year
2020 and now we're told
It's Coronavirus
Baba baba
I mean the Coronavirus
Been around forever
Flu and Corona every year of some others
Coronavirus
I have bad news for The Scholar
The article he's referring to about Italy having its worst flu season in 40
Seniors is from the local
And if you check the date on that article he would see that it's from January 19th
2018 do you don't have to check the dates on it
Approximately 3.8 million between September 2017 and January 14th 2018
This is about where the country hit the peak of a
Particularly bad flu season
North 14 years
And this gigantic number of flu cases resulted in 140 serious hospitalizations
30.
There's another article in the local about the 2019 2020 floozies
Report a slightly lower number of total cases
Switch it resulted in 200
40.
These numbers are much lower than expected
Did actual death toll from influenza-like diseases and related
Application featuring Italy but it's legitimately nowhere even
I'm close to where Alex and is dumb dumb call her suggest
This color has no idea what he's talking about and Alex doesn't either but it sounds good to this new framing
Who throws in his $70,000 a year in Italy from
At Stafford he's falling in love with and now we can
Can suggest to his audience that that Italy's was faking
Toss it into the bowl
Another mixture we're making Jungle Juice Dan right
With all of our Lives Musical bulshit
But
You got to consider Alex's resume
I don't
Thank you so much I have a question before that question I just want to let everyone out there know that there's a new
Infowars
Simple War into this country
Discovered in Garden Grove
The person that exposed iannarino in the Clinton
During the Waco Massacre with
American soil
Clinton Foundation
David gergen
Interview still on YouTube and if anyone wants to see something amazing it's
When is the Bohemian Grove and then use confronted David gergen and he was completely spooked amazing
We need to get all those famous reports that people don't know about that we're so so revealing and end in repo
Also supposed to go taking off YouTube and I'll get ago
This caller is so indicative of a person who just accepted everything Alex says is
Tristan reality
Alex didn't discover Bohemian Grove there plenty of people who talked about it prior to him
From the mainstream media to a 1989 peace and spy magazine
All well before Alex did his publicity stunt
Alex didn't expose Janet Reno or Hillary
Clinton during Waco
For one that's rewriting history a little bit with the lens of the Hillary obsession
I'm considering it was Bill who's President back then
Just forget about that
Second Alex
Did get a lot of attention for trying to help rebuild the branch
Davidian Church in Waco and it was a huge part of his early identity but even expose anything
Standoff happened in 1993 years
4 oz on the radio but
You know who was on the radio already
Builded punzel episodes about Waco and interviewed a lot of people who Alex uses as big sources
Linda Thompson
Senator pseudo-documentary the big lie
Alex hasn't broken any actual stories about the Clinton Foundation
A bunch though so there's that
Alex's interview with David gergen is kind
The funny but I don't know if it really achieved any
It's just Alex telling David gergen that he snuck in with a
The camera to Bohemian Grove and Gerke
Call you're supposed
Keep that stuff Secret
How to capture any footage that elicited a response
India Bialik
Wow that's weird
Maybe this would have been a got your moment but from everything
Alex hasn't his documentary
Care if people at the Grove keep what they do their secret
This caller is such a great example of someone who doesn't
Stand a chance
He's willing to believe that Alex Jones is fighting a completely unspecific
Totally real animated
It seems to change their plans based on Alex
Is William super super powerful
To the point of controlling pretty much all the world
Can't seem to handle a dumb radio host
You can't be bothered
Everything pass head
Is collars willing
Believe that because
He too cannot be bothered to re-patch headlines
A yard
It's a cyclical thing it is it is like sometimes you look
Maybe people are just too.
You know like like as a as a whole like
60% of people approve of how
Trump is handling this s***
Killing us
What is it
But I can't I don't who are these people
It's add stop
But
You know
To dump we're just too dumb or just too dumb
We got to Alex talking about Missouri
Congressman
Congressperson
Josh Hawley
Senator
TJ Maxx
One-sided deal
Josh Hawley sucks but I'll just still kind of lying about what he said
Corsi's Hollywood on Hannity on Tuesday
Moses call for a turtle investigation into China's actions related
The outbreak
Alex wants the audience to think of this matches up with his narratives about the globalist
Telling China for Elisa bioweapon or some s*** but
It doesn't
Holly's just talkin about the accusation to turn it in
Probably and tried to cover up the initial outbreak
This is basically just a young Republican senator saber-rattling a China
To keep the base happy
Wow also doing
Distract
The fact the party's president has handled this outbreak
Is poorly as one probably could
To be fair
There is
The fact that Trump
Secretly ordered an emergency
Before you actually did
I forgot about it also Alex's stop saying that cuz he's
Not really in
Interested not anymore it's really kind of falling away
I'll also be millions of deaths it is fake lieutenant-colonel friends told him
Okay there's that talk about that anymore
You know you say that
Weird
Crazy
These these These Times
You know people expect you to remember what happened two weeks ago two weeks ago 6 years ago
Yeah
Is doing is basically change in a whole bunch of like really Central things
15 kind of important
Because drop
That you'd stay in line
But he doesn't just want to defend Trump
Always lying about what's really going on just like they do
I'm going to tell listeners again
You shouldn't take this virus seriously I'm not saying you shouldn't kill some people
Who's telling us what to do
Chlamydia
Everybody
Once they have their dirty deep State fingerprints all over it
Yuck yuck yuck
Oh boy
Oh man
We have leaders
In this great
I do
True true
So Alex goes back
Break and take another caller and just call her man
If there is a bad idea this is a
What happened
Justin Washington DC with conservative
Side by side
The Grievances for the Liberty Seas bar on government
Washing down the road
We're going to have to have that March 4th to show we are not afraid we are not afraid
This is not America
America was founded we are not afraid we are not cowards
Event
And the police in military everybody else to join us because
This is a shy off it's all about fear the president said
The real bad idea but
I
Thought that it was a joke
Cuz I saw some people think that Facebook post
This is a joke I thought it was a joke
Cuz he's supposed like rallies for conservatives
I think that's a
Stupid yeah but this guy's not joke
Okay know which concerns me about that being a j
Yeah
Yep
But I mean it's exactly what you would expect it's just that the oppositional Defiance in the
The faces like
It's like someone yelling at a hurricane
Or something like that you know it says you can't Million Man March everybody arm-in-arm walking down
The f******
Straight
Another caller who is even
Whipping all over the place just like Coronavirus
I really see that they're trying to shut down Americana trying to shut down the other countries worldwide
And it makes me wonder like why are they
Releasing all these inmates
Christine has happened before
We should have a March
Ruckus
Chaos
Releasing hardened criminals
Not the stop the virus but the crate as much bad one
So this caller seems to think there's some kind of a supervillain plot going on like where the Joker Springs all the inmates from Arkham
Overwhelmed Gotham's Police Department
That's legitimately with
These idiots think is happening because their world was so based on fiction that reality in
Comic books are in distinguished
I'm going to help this Colorado
Here's the situation you end up with
When you have an active
In prison overcrowding
You can either release a ton of non-violent and parole eligibility vendors in order to create room for the responsible of ministration
Incarceration
And Health Services 45
Defenders Waunakee
Keep in jail or you can keep everyone in jail and risk horrific on
One possible outcome is an outbreak spreading in an overcrowded prison
Which attacks really happening right now on Rikers Island
According to slate
Currently 52 people at Rikers who have confirmed cases and 96 more under up
Conservation
There are 5,000 people
Incarcerated there
And there are the way the Jayla setup there's almost no way to stop the spread of
The spires in such Close Quarters
And the jail was not equipped
You sterilize with sufficient regularity to fight an outbreak
And this is the first time I've ever thought Riker
Bakers Island was a bad bright
Given the situation like that you end up in a position where you can
Can act either by releasing people incarcerated for minor offenses or dumping
A million
Is it the building new housing wings
Something like that or you can watch his prisoners die locked
Incels
You can tell yourself
Imprisoned and they matter less but if you do you're a piece of
18th Amendment does tell you that
3rd president
Now the other possible consequences an offshoot of this one
If you have a large incarcerated population are being held
Any sorts of conditions or everyone around them is sick and dying and there's a reasonable explanation
But they're going
Going to get sick too
What's the stop anyone from rioting
If guards get sick to the security staff could be run thin and you might put yourself in a position where there's
Sweet chaos
The prisons
If you care at all about people or
If you're just interested
Keeping dangerous offenders in jail and you're not a dumb dumb the only right choice you can make right now is to
Freeze many nonviolent offenders as you can
If Alex thinks drug should be legal and your other guy was in
In prison for selling weed
Why the f*** would Alex knots
Support letting him out no matter what the
Santa's or not
He doesn't want a
To appear weak
On the innocent
Dan doesn't want you
Everybody's like all we got to be mean to the guilty let me tell you something
The innocent you really got to take down you got to imprison them for life
Whatever
Also it's not just Bluetooth
Ohio Revised releasing inmates
From Cuyahoga County jail and their Governor Mike dewine
A lot around the world a lot of places are releasing in golf but not in a
Positive
Like there
Getting out
Through
Combining together their efforts and just breaking free of the f****** prison
Otherwise they're going to kill
So Alex
Do you watch the Hannity
Because he's got a lot of new ideas
And he's going to use a segment on Hannity in order to help him with a sales pitch
Coronavirus
That's right I'm tearing them
Guess what we've been saying on air
0-0 hospitalizations hero
What's on the list starts with a z
Sleep
Unbelievable
Typically route is only excited they're reporting on this because it's a way for him to help sell his real red pill supplement that has zinc in it
The other avenues for a scaremonger aren't as open to him anymore is asbestos
Protocol really overboard on the sink thing
And honestly like
He can't help us
He has this method of selling
Whatever is the Avenue that's going to be
No Tony General wrote me about the zinke
He might be in a much more defensible place there because there are like
Health benefits of
Taking zinc
Yeah they're not
Solving Coronavirus
97 to 99% effective in killing the viruses
Way overboard
He's going a lot safer to him that a lot of the other
The dick is going the problem is nobody knew what nanosilver was but now that they know exact they'll be like I have it
So the whole story here is the Sean Hannity claimed that he had a letter from a New York Doctor Who said that he had about 500 patients and he cured them
I'm always not just think but also Hydrox
Chloroquine
Azithromycin
Steve pieczenik work
Exit the New York Hospital
There's no proof that this is a real letter or a real doctor if there's no proof that this alleged doctor hasn't
In fact you would anyone
Legitimately all be bulshit
But even if it is a real doctor and he has as many patients recovered from this drug
Cocktail it's still not sufficient to claim that the drugs caused the recovery
There could be any number of reasons if they recover
Completely unrelated
The drugs did you need to have much more
Data tobacco
What's up you don't know how science works
Super Bowl better
Do not care at all
So
Methadone caller
And I regret to inform you that this
And other day
Wanted to throw out in this is us
A really radical idea that would drinking bleach
I felt like I would throw it out there because
Soccer Terry tiller
ODI l l
Aart
Fontana weather
Who is Paige on
On the 22nd
There is no virus there are no viruses
Experts weigh in
One of them being Jon rappoport
Well I'm not
He's one of the ones that was interviewed on this webinar
There's two important things
Alex does not tell her like this is Ludacris
You don't
Don't listen to people like that there are no viruses viruses don't exist
You didn't realize this virus denial is a thing
He is in a position where they
And he responds to work like well you know if you got to have the conversation looks like viruses
Alex wasn't sure if Jon rappoport does believe in virus
Viruses are fake
That does sound like something
Who's believe
Does not know
The beliefs of the people that he promotes his expert want to show up to work
That's not
Good now
I think that Jon rappoport Spartan that video I was going to watch it but it's really long is just very boring
I don't even know John Rapport is in it but I think he's used as an
An expert
For hiv-aids denial okay
So I better the section of the rapport
Involved
Speaking of experts who Alex doesn't know
What they're up to
Steve pieczenik
Is on
And his
Main point is
Basically just to be like him at business is all that matters in America
I agree with Trump
I'm always agreed with a notion that he has the instincts to bring us
Business
Business of America is business
Snot shot down
Coronavirus
We are the business
We are the economy in that
And the only thing we have
All of us
Collecting and finally just
Just being like
Oh I get with
Guys were doing the whole time
Man if you go back and you listen to Alex
Jones's
Peace in Richard linklater's Waking Life or he's driving around in the street yelling into a bullhorn about
Humanity is too good
Represent the human
Spirit
Start 2020
Dick all of those people who are going to create things out of the human
Spirits
Work
You got to deliver food
I was just
Talkin about
Corporations
The groceries
So
Amazon can make all the body
Jeff Bezos needs to feed
So Steve his position on this is not based on any science I can find
Particularly
He's giving out Sabaton
Cast of Community
I can go in and
December or January there's no
They go to work
I don't think that you should listen to that advice
I don't I don't believe that
Based on any studies already.
That's like
What is referencing is basically how cowpox
Was
Help you grant immunity to small paw
That was that's his concept there
Whatever he doesn't understand that viruses
A flu is it going to fix
He's going to provide immunity to that they'd influenza viruses a difference
Amansa same thing with Alex talking about like quinine being help
440 virus app
Because it solves malaria it's like malaria is not a virus virus
It's a yeah it is
They're playing real fast and loose
That's an unbeliever
Kill Steve
Looks like you just get a cold
You're cool now on
Define not going to get it
That means either.
With the
The world
Well surgery and public health officials
But that still won't matter
Because as you said in the past
Reiterates
He wants them all fire
Some of these people
Some point in 84 got to go
We don't need I don't need him in the uniform
County Fair
Bill Barr baby
Months ago
No
That French study is flawed
But
I love the idea of the first of all
Steve in the middle of all this
Just like fire all of them
We need chaos in the public health battle really Inspire confidence
A first of all the markets and in the population I want to love it
And then also like it was only a couple weeks ago that Steve was on the show and thought there wasn't a Surgeon General
Get fired
Absolutely
Surgeon General
He didn't deposit after
Steve is not to bring his best
Like I said
You can't help
He can't help himself in his sales practices
Is as The Show Goes On he starts to like really push
The idea that is zinc
It's in his real red pill
Is a preventative
Preventive effect
With the Coronavirus
Scared
What are you do to prevent
I don't know how much is that is
Illegal
But it feels
I mean if if making the claim
What do you think
Yeah I mean like that
Yeah because the issue is like you're not supposed to
Sell things
Except
Cures prevention
Or treatments
I don't know
Let her know it's iffy
Yeah.
This is the Beast guys
Like it has to be a thing where I left at the end of all of this we do have to like
Get Alex and Hannity and Tucker Carlson
Like put them on
Mariaville trial actually
Going to get people
Trump already got people
You know like Trump should be in jail I do think that if there is ever like a retard
Bit of sanity
They should be at least Bank
Absolutely
This cannot
Is unacceptable
So Alex ghost calls
Steve leaves
And I hear apps
The show talking to
Dum Dums
And this guy
Allegedly has a disc
Distant relation
Who's a nurse
And she's treated Corona patients successfully with tonic water
Map to see if you can keep track of
Who's this nurse is all right the guy
If you're giving me this Preamble that's a problem
Friends
Granddaughter boyfriend
The boyfriend's mother is a head nurse in a hospital in Austin
He told her son
Water
The Cure people with
Coronavirus
Tell us more what she said because that's what
Why not is the ending for it from the British army think of the trip drink though
Sorry forgot Steve was still there
So
This guy
I've written it down
Okay girlfriend guys lady friends
Granddaughter's boyfriend's mop
A game of telephone right there
Obviously he didn't talk to the mom
I would assume nope
To the grandson
New talk to the mall
Maybe
Birthday three daughters boyfriend
Her grandma
Daughter
But he might have talked directly to the boyfriend
Possible so that's still
Second hand to hand the third hand to Alec
Ridiculous boy that's how I want my information
Kumon my great grandfather's sister's daughter's friend
Who is a nurse but
She's been retired for 28 years
She has a second daughter
Husband
He's a doctor
And they were
Bright
So are we won last night from 24th here and it's another caller who has cured himself
Course she had
Kansas Coronavirus
Coronavirus facts
First of January
I told my mother at the
I got that Rona
Sober
And Goldenseal
Today's
I know that's what I do
Oh boy
Hellboy
Don't they have like a
What's the 5-second delay on
The thing that
It is probably okay about that is that's a testimonial
True
He probably believes it to be
Pedro
I don't know
Super misleading I do like the idea that
Look
After six or seven days of having this
Virus
Fats are I have been told by a large number of people
Can last six or seven days in many people get a minor version of it and then
It's over
I actually cured it
With coil silver elderberries
And it's not like it just ran its course
I cured it
That's what I do
I'm basically Jonas Salk
I pretty much invented medicine
So we can do the 25th
And boy I'll tell you what
There is a return
Much like John Cena coming back to the Royal Rumble
We all know
Roblox
Hey man you know what what better time to throw out some real racism
I'm real
Pointed pointless racism
It's okay rhyme when stopping at a time when asian-americans are reporting
Increased hostility and races
Just abuse being directed towards them
Kimberly grade is Alex taking the time to start his show with absurd
Race
Hey there's no crisis
You can't try and turn into a
So Alex transitions from that pre-recorded
Fentanyl the Chinese dragon
Segment into another impression
Eye of the Mask
Answer he's doing Bane impression
Only know
The bad thing
Stop me to wear one of these put
As BigNik
A Big Mac
His suit
So Alex leave the show off
Please finish the impression
Not f****** around
That one person that's the whole thing
It wasn't good
Was good
But no f****** around
And I refused
But has some headlines
Federal law was overturning of the second amendment that passed
Newswars.com imports.com you might want to raise the alarm
So these guys the tip of the spear
Didn't know 4:30
They live under Cinderella rules of of La like that it's midnight so it doesn't count
You talkin about
It didn't change bud
I wonder what the point of it was so this is just about a 2000
7 release from the national infrastructure advisory Council under George W bush which didn't
Include gun dealers as essential businesses that should be kept open
An emergency situation
I guess it must suck if you're a gun weirdo
For gun stores to possibly not be open but I don't think that counts as the Second Amendment
Being shut down
I don't think the second member requires that you be able to conveniently buy a gun at every moment of every day no matter what
It seems like an incredibly weak argument but it's
Good for Aloe
Because it helps him
Pivot the Coronavirus
Situation back
Familiar water
You've done the gun paranoia show a million times by now so you should be able to handle that kind of narrative in his sleep
That's the way you do this this s*** back in
Into the territory you know
Got to have a
You know every morning I wake up
Go check the front stoop and I see that the Milkman has
Customary two bottles of
I go down to my local gun
I'm sorry just to get my morning gun
It's like
A cup of coffee at Starbucks I get a gun at the gun store
And then I'm ready to start
And they really f***** it up when I can only drink coffee now
What am I
If
Can't
Buy a gun at literally every moment
Then you basically don't have the right
No he's about return the
Huh
At least though at this point the impressions are all
They're not
Let me tell you who we have for you on the runs yesterday
Call Joseph Watson
Majesty
Island
Dangers of the bottle
Rosegal
Mark randazza and
Michael Jones
We got the rest of that list I don't really care about
At all
I can't even say how little I care about anything
Don't care about skousen
Don't care about Paul Joseph Watson
Don't care about Mike Adams
Really don't care about Marco
Alex keeps talking about how like he's coming on because he's an Italian citizen
I do care
But you Michael Jones
Coming back on
In the middle of
This sort of situation
Responsible is a bad sign
There's a bad
Harbinger of
Not do so when I heard that I was like
The Impressions were
Retired
Their master plan
What is clear
As a clear blue sky
Sounds like him with a mask
95 masks
But I'm going to get serious
I bet you are
How do you get one
Hey you know empathizing with the the Medical
Call Stafford on the road
But it's okay if Medical
So Alex is now like
Here on the 25th I think you can really hear that he's pretty much fully on board with the idea that like
All this is just
Giant hoax
Play the shop today
The Democrats
Lapponian
Hold America hostage
They're at work with the corporations to do it
China's opening businesses is
The governors of the president and Democrats
Partisan movie shut things down
Have their own political fever as a Calderon chemotherapy their own radiation
Right now it's showing you my bankrupting you that they're the boss and they think
Still want something new we start asking that
Do you know Alex is so full of s***
What's the new hoax
He's already looking onto at the neck
Thing is going to be
That's
It's sad
It is a very sad
It's
It's kind of
It's kind of amazing
That this is
Just made it
So
It's like we've got the purest
Distillation
Of
The two parties
Like there's no more
There's no more
Dog whistling her or hiding
Purely
The Democrats are evil because they want people to
And they don't want to reopen
Two party system is now essentially
Human life versus
Business
And people are still going to vote for business
That's why
You need people like Alex in order to justify those
Those
LL place
Evil
Governors
Geragos
People
Die
For Kerrigan
People die
So Alex
Pointed that out and I didn't know what story he was talking about but he has an article that proves
Dim the whole states hostage
Coronavirus lockdown
Is Walter deep state to hold the people and the economy hostage
A depression in civil unrest
Driving Trump from Office that's
There
So that article that I'm exciting as proof that these Democratic Governors on ahold cities hostage isn't an article thing sources are near
Trail riding
Infowars.com
It doesn't embedded video of David Knights episode from that day
Stop proof of anything they get to give their articles whatever headlines they want
Pretty sad
Pretty sad here's what I'm going to do I'm going to
David Knighton
Sure
A name you can trust salute
So Alex
Has been
Periodically
Getting a b race
Yeah we saw there with the fentanyl the Chinese dragon
Staggeringly race we we see it a lot
Alex is very rare
But in terms of the outbreak
Like in terms of blaming Chinese people
Trying to identify
The virus itself
With
Chinese people
He's just so far beyond like the levels of acceptable
This is real scapegoating s***
And I don't believe
I don't believe
The facts of what he saying
And I
Strongly disagree with
Point of hoodies
For the breakout happen
Three months ago there were Chinese everywhere
In every part of Austin very wealthy
Very fancy cars wearing
Very expensive watches carrying $10,000
Does he do it
It was a bio-weapon pilgrimage they weren't running from it
It was their mission to bring it here
Embassy DC
The block
Chinese
Prove any of that and then also like all the like functional
Affected
That can really have
Is making people hurt you
He just wrote the protocols of the Elders of woohoo
Look at all those
Wealthy Chinese people
Giving you diseases of their evil overlords
Fatty's
F******
You can't you can't do worse
But it's kind of illogical
Like the place you'd expect this to go
But at the same time I was just trying to balance it with like it's not a big deal
I don't know
It's it's
So Alex has a carpenter friend who w
Understand
He doesn't seem to understand
That carpenters in building is essential
And it's not
In the lockdown or whatever little bit
Struggle about whether or not
This business is essential any other people were walking off
The job site
Then outside
Is this stupid
Houses
The time
Walked off
Trenholm
They don't care they're getting into it
Have quarantined
You see
Workers Unite
These people have Corey
19 Envy
I everybody longs to be quarantined at that Concepts
That that
The human being would say that out loud
Oh boy
That's how Alex Caesar cuz
Use
A boxer
So
I'm Last Days episode Alex talked about Josh Hawley
And his moves and Alex talked about it a little more here than
Josh Hawley
Calls for international probe
China's coronavirus cover up
Big story
Barry
Dot-com infowars.com
It's absolutely got to get out
Companion bill in the house
Yesterday
Proud to partner
For the other Congress people introduced
This
Camera resolution calling for China
Tommy's party
Unleashed would their Lodge deception
Enemies
Asurion
So how exactly would Josh Hawley get damages
From China
Sovereign country
Without the exist
Sense of some international governing body that could oversee
Sea dispute between sovereign country
Gentlemen's Agreement
Outside of international law that every country is subject to how does even work
The very thing that Alex is celebrating his congressperson demanding his legitimate
Impossible without the very system he's built his career
Fighting against or you would have to take it
Right well there's that
This very weird
Insistence on creating
Cause for war
Without
Without framing it that way
Late because it's Alex truly believe
I understand why
People die in War I don't understand
I'm scared
Viruses
Can hit anytime
You don't see them coming and I can't shoot it with a gun start a war Alex truly believe
That the Chinese
These government
Deployed this is a weapon
Sanitation
Active War it's over
It's over the Warriors already begun yeah China
And that's obviously not the conclusion that you want to reach but that'll The Logical
Conclusion
It's insane
But I mean that is what he believes he does believe that this is a weapon
And it's
I believe
Released himself
Do you know it's man-made
Obama transferred
Precursor virus
Without the Hy-Vee delivery system
That was a real out right now
Pontil
Nope
Which is The Narrative of success
Are you in my mind that last one might feel real to you but you got to stop saying narrative when you're Alex
I would prefer the non-narrative reality
For the part that's not a story
Interacting with we need to push
This talking
Point in order to save our own asses
So Alex now goes
To his interview with
Jesse Michael Jones
Noted anti-semites
What's fascist
He is on
Cuz he made a video about the Coronavirus
It's very measured
It's telling people
Nope
About to have segments Michael Jones
Michael Jones
I want a big bailout in him
As well. Taxpayer money to police everybody and
So weird are you got a weird
Antic anti-semite coming on your show do you start biking
Complaining about the ATL weird man for his stated goal of eliminating all juice
What
Is tolerance if I can't be until the
So
Be Michael Jones
Springs up
That professor at Harvard Charles liebler Lieber
Who was
Involved with the Chinese government
Subway
Professor and
I think that there's a lot.
Details about that story that I don't
Why I don't I don't know all the details of it's a little unclear I think more will come out over time
Call Jones bring this dude up
I think there's an interesting difference
Between how he talks about him on
This show
Talks about him on his own website
We've had
Exposure of certain groups
In the country
Send involved in espionage
In collaboration with the Chinese
UCI chairman of the chemistry department at Harvard
Dr. Charles Lieber who was arrested just has this virus started to take
So on Alex's show this is just a professor who is collaborating with the Chinese government
You Michael Jose
Makes it sound to possibly more salacious than the actual facts of the case might Merit
But the thrust of it is just that there's a guy who's collaborating with China
Maui from his article on his website culture wars
Lieber who is Jewish was considered a Flight Risk because he has ties to Israel
Call the authorities.
The man that both he and his wife surrender their passports
Libras one of the founders
Bio-tech firm non-cis which is
Affiliated with the Hebrew University in Jerusalem
Lieber being Jewish is very important that you Michael Jones on his website because that's what his work is all about
Is a gigantic anti-semite
However to disguise the true intention of his propaganda he leave some of that stuff out when he's talking to someone like Alex
You cast The Wynette then once
People come in
Hey see what it's really about once
They're already ready to hear it
Racism
Pops up real quick whenever there's a
Sure.
Joey Michael Jones is not on the same page is Alex
Exactly Buddies
Kind of on the page of the last iteration of the property
Francis Boyle who was
The man who wrote up the antibiotic
Protocol in 1970s
Also believes it was a bioweapon that he says that there was
Back and forth between Winnipeg there
Level 4 bio lab
As well
Indication
Bioweapon
Miss the memo that's disinformation according to Alex
Throw that out because we're more interested in the UNC North Carolina Chapel Hill lab
The pay cards come on man
The only council is incorrect because
That narrative might as well be true to we might as well throw it in there today why not
If this information but yeah we're going
And the only confirm people we have using covid as a bioweapon happened to be white supremacist
Sure
It's crazy that he Michael Jones also his big sources Francis Boyle who's the guy who comes on Alex's show
I'll be working for the same
Oh well
It seems like they get the same
Newsletter of
So these people like
Alex
Cody Michael Jones
Play just like
Deciem
Fairy
Very
Willing
To accuse people of things that cause
Dwarfs
The thing that's just occurring to me now is
If the Chinese government is saying
That
And that they have the right to respond
Maybe they have responded
This is what occurred to me maybe New York was a response
A bioweapon launched by China maybe that's what China did New York I mean it's just
Speculation that this
So why are you saying it
I mean
It look what am I not going to say that we have been fighting a secret
Biowar with
China how am I going to not say that
I know it's
Incredibly irresponsible for me to say this
Look
Baby
But you know what maybe Mexico secretly
Oh God damn that was a response for the Mexican-American War
Just speculation.
Make sense that's why we don't have Austin
They're on lockdown
Incredibly irresponsible
So Alex
And
Michael Jones
Are talking about
Miss Mexico
Course they are complaining about p****** giving
Do people in Italy free accounts
I
Don't
Understand how we got to where we are
Here's the thing that's really important
About this
Trump latest
The clip their conversation
You need to understand that there is a conversation
And then there was a crypto conversation
Simultaneously
P***
You know where these big you know
Relationship
The pleasure of real sex
It is absolutely not be highly motivated
It screws up culture
Pornography is a weapon
I just now being it was been used as a weapon for the pass
50 years
The main weapon keeping people inside and disoriented when they now her fur
There
Because of Marshalls
Do not have sex with your wife
So on the surface this appears to be just
Alex being postponed cuz it has negative influences on intimacy or whatever he's not a fuddy-duddy conservative
But don't beat off
Whatever who care
However
If you know what he Michael Jones believe
This is a deeply anti-semitic conversation
He believes that the Jews created and promoted pornography as an attack on the non-jewish family structure
It's a very large piece of his worldview and anyone who's familiar with his work knows this very well
If you're someone who knows e Michael Jones you hear this conversation I honestly couldn't blame you for thinking that Alex was a
Agreed with him that the Jews are attacking families with p****
I don't believe that Alex doesn't know this
I have a hard time believing you be so oblivious to the people he platform
Then he be having a conversation about you Michael Jones's exact talking point
But leaving out the Jewish paw
This reads to me as an intentional attempt to whitewash anti-semitic rhetoric on his show
But then again Alex may or may not know if Jon rappoport believes viruses are real so you might be the
That oblivious
Yeah which is bad because then he's doubling down and signing off on E Michael Jones
Anti-Semitic
Conspiracy theories about
I all I'm saying is that
Baby Italians have a hard time to find a
But they know p*** when they
App
Seen a lot
Alright
I really
Horse
They can't talk about pouring and it's abject
Certification of women
And the many women who are f******
Abused in the process
If it can't include that adult they can take care of they can talk about that stuff but only if the
The villain is somebody that they want
To Target
Can't talk about it
Its own
Being a bad thing in itself
It has to be used as a as a means
Yeah
Asia
So we talk about the stock market crash
In the falling
Stocks
Michael Jones
Can't quite figure out if it's
The result
The virus
Or the virus
Came around
Because they wanted to
Crash the stock
You know basically Alex's
An
Alex says it's both
They did the crash on purpose and released of the virus at the same time
Smokescreen
Which would be actually a martial law consolidation Drive
What's an office
I think there's a plausible EX
Explanation I think
Not the response I would have! That is nowhere near
The other assholes
Sabri have gotten around talking about this
The virus and
It's inattentional bio-weapon that or something right
It's muddy
My lady friend
Granddaughters boyfriend's mom
Mom told me that
It's not about you
17 and tonic
So
The last life we have because I'll be honest with you
Raftery Michael Jones was on Ozark
The show
Where this guy wasn't going to come on aboard for the s*** out of me
21 Mike Adams took over the show cuz I wanted to hear what he was bringing to the table economic
Talking like you're not the finance brain
Take all that
Michael Jones
It seems like he's saying that
The virus
This is an act of God
But at the same time I thought it was supposed to God
Bio weapon Chinese
There have been never been a time when the oligarchs have had more
Control
Maybe like that the real message of the coronavirus is it takes
God's hand to break
The hold of their hand over all of us are the ones that released
Using is in God's hands
Bluegrass is rising
That's good news
I don't understand what the position
Woodforest
Other than he does not
In the Jewish people
And everything is secretly a
Conspiracy
So here's
Play Take on our position
Insofar
The Chinese did it right
The Jews did it
God did it
Those three
Edsby
Like it can't just be
I don't know man that I am
Finding myself
Disoriented slightly by Alex's
Work
Disorienting
Yeah
I understand that there are some thrulines you know like I'm not I'm not going to sit here and pretend that Alex
Didn't earlier on talked about like
The
Causing a financial collapse
Absence
Intended a lot of the other elements weren't also major parts
Of his is rhetoric
Even stuff that he was talking about like
Weeks ago
I like the idea that he'd have Stewart Roads on the talk about
Virus keeps coming back
And now it's no big deal
Do you get over in the week or fine
I have a real difficult time with it because on the one hand
You should look at it and be like oh
F*** you
But the other hand of like
I wonder where this is going there's a little bit of curiosity about like
Red leaves Iran
You shouldn't be allowed to do that
You really shouldn't
He's causing
He hasn't
Potential to cause a lot of them
No absolutely
That study that they
They did showing
Pretty well.
Probably that's
The more money you have those the Richer you are the more
Psychopathic
Your behavior
This is
More like
To me there's something deeper beneath
That money provides
And that's insulation for
Yeah when you don't have consequences for your actions
This type of shi
You can this week
The stock market's up 1,000 points tomorrow it's down 1,000
Doesn't matter
No contest
This week the coronavirus is man-made last week it was
It's just
Nonsense
There's no consequences
For your actions and so you just keep doing b*******
And that gets people
Killed because they have to
Part of that that is the case but then I think there's also a part that like
I think Alex is keenly aware of the fact that like he knows he's been lying for years
Like all the stuff he talks about is like there's no Stakes to it cuz it's not real
He doesn't care if it's damaging to them
Don't care it's just like constant b*******
That just is to facilitate whatever
Growing
Narratives that he has out some sell stuff
And help them push
Reactionary extreme right-wing
Beliefs
So like
Keno's
On a certain level like every time he yells about school shootings being fake he knows that it's b******* so whatever comes of it
No big deal
We're in a situation right now where neither you nor I can
Predict what's going to happen
But
The experts
The people who
IR in the field
That irrelevant you should be listening to
And they all have dire warning
The countries that
Have gone down
The Pav's that
Alex
Would like
To recommend people going down
Even if they change their path
Too late
Are in bad places
That's not something that has narratives can really do anything
Think about
Like he can
Later
Try and create an explanation like I said like you can rewrite this to be like always mnuchin in the globalist
That wanted people to go back to work so
The get sick
No he can do that
This is not the same
As
Lying about a school shooting
Or
Any of the others
He just wanted to clear it is but it's
It's not yet I give it
I give it a week before
Trump holds a press conference
Did they beat foutch's head to
The death because f******
Severed Pig's head
I told him it's a good
It's
Like that's where is that they are
It's becoming
License place on like
Episode on Friday
We have some plans
To keep y'all company is best
We can through this trying time
Will at least be doing Monday Wednesday Friday episodes
Receivable
Time frame and there might be some little sneak
Sneaky other things
Along the way but we'll see about that
We'll see what happened but
Until we
See you again
We're on Twitter
We are also on Facebook to download the show please go to iTunes download review Maybe
Go to patreon throw some money maybe donate to a chiller charity we would love it all very
Thank you
Back button
Omniome Leo mdzs Clark I am the juiciest Ice Cube
Alexandra Thurston color