Damn important
I have great respect for Tenaya Lodge B
What's fight.com
Everybody was acknowledged
Alex Jones Jordan Jordan
Do you have a break
Spot Forest
Sure
That's a lot of fun
Actuate
This time that we are in
I've found that I feel like I will need to treat ourselves a little bit
You know isolating and
Self quarantining to Anna
Self quarantining might be like a really extreme
Sing a little bit trying to stay inside our houses more
We need to do little things
You got to stay sane yourself with little things
Maybe that you wouldn't normally give yourself
So I've you know
PopCorners
No I do have plenty still though I have a lot
Goodbye like a little mini freeze-dried marshmallows
Just to Put-in-Bay
You know like that you wouldn't have Lucky Charms
I haven't actually corrected that yet so not sure if that's a great tree
Things I did was I realized that I used to have or not used to it
A while back I had a big Klondike face
Mcbarge
And I like the variety of them
At the pet about
50 Cent
They have these great flavors you know like there was a mint chip
On the Reese's cup one is at the store and I noticed that
They had a new one that I've never seen before and it was called Klondike
Donut
Ono Boston cream against the law
What what it is
Is the Klondike bar but the center is cut out if it looks like a donut
It's alright it's alright it's just
It's not
That amazing
Whatever information myself
I liked it so I was curious
Because I was like okay Klondike Bar Donuts
They're not just going to make one
See any other flavors at the store sprinkles maybe yeah I had to look into it
And what I did
Is that what the klondike's
Website
The problem with being a brilliant
Even with Klondike Bars you have to look into it so I went to the website to see what other flavors there are
Important than the reviews
It turns out there is a community of people who are really mad at
I don't know
So here's a review
Austin Creed
Distance from mbb in Gaylord
Boston cream doughnuts don't have holes
I just bought a Boston cream six pack for same sale price $3 as the other bars and donuts
Boston cream doughnuts don't have holes so why does the ice-cream have holes the weight range on the bars and donuts range from six
C8 285g which is a 20% difference
For the Boston cream at 73 g at the 14%
Or 42 cents
Lesson 85 G bar also expected more flavor
Please send me a
Donut holes
You're stealing chocolate and ice cream for me that's his review
So I found the Boston cream was
Just about
I checked that they also have a triple chocolate donut
Variety this is they review their from
Malara 33
Don't don't
Doc's people
Screen name
Bought the triple chocolate donut by Klondike OMG
I had to go back and buy four more packs
I love chocolate and I love donuts
And I love klondike's
My first bite I was hooked
!
Dark chocolate milk chocolate and potato donuts out-of-this-world
I had to actually hide them for my daughter and husband LOL
We all love Klondike laborers but this one took...
No good donut
Great combo and they better
Keep them in stock for me thanks Klondike
How many stars out of five do you think that God
Nope I'm hiding them from my
That's that's five stars so down the other flavor is frosted strawberry donut alright
He was from an
Where's the strawberry
Ice cream
Ice cream looks
Play plain vanilla there's no strawberry swirl sprinkles on it has barely a hint of strawberry flavor
Will not buy this ever again
Five stars
You got a response
Klondike Klondike replies
Thanks for the review on Klondike frosted strawberry donut
We're very sorry to hear about your experience we would like to hear more about your feedback
Dude I would say I think she was pretty clear I think
Anyway I had a great time looking at reviews
Recognizing their customer base has a real difficult time expressing
What's wrong
The other pretty clear
Play understand
She's doing brighten my day quite but that's fun
Klondike reviews thinking about like what it would take for me to leave a review of a Klondike bar that disappointed
I love it the new album by Thundercat
Is amazing
Also it has a track did you ever watch Carolyn Tuesday
I don't think so
Play Stay by the same
Shinichiro Watanabe who did Cowboy Bebop
And it's about it's about two girls
Singer-songwriters
Becoming famous that's the whole thing
It's really really sweet and in it
Thundercat has a song called unrequited love
And he's a brilliant basis
The Beautiful song but it one point
In a fit of
Cleverness that I will never understand
He said he calls it unrequited love
Because they're no longer in
Okay it's spelled
The same way that's
The game changer
Let's BET The Game Change
I don't whole world is differ
I don't know if I experienced it as a game-changer but it sounds interesting I'll check it out and I put
Appreciate the recommendation
Alright so you recommend that I recommend
Repeat
Deco fine people being petty as hell
It'll very harmless way
This while you do it
So Jordan today we got the episode to go over we're going over that be
I got the date in front of major I don't know why
27th 2020
On the Alex Jones Show and it's really something that people are really excited about I know and that is because
Did last weekend and real bad
Yeah
A bit of bad news all on Friday
There was he the news broke about his
A PO for a bunch of sanctions and the Sandy Hook lawsuit
That he was at the appeal is denied
And also he got his ass kicked off the Android store
He had a lot going on around his mood
Happens to be
On this day
I'm he's he's living
He would describe his best life
Fat
So I will get signed up
So first
David thank you so much you're now policy walk
I'm a policy wonk
I am thinking about you and I was walk right
Peter thank you so much you're now call if you want
Sexy women
Thank you so much you are now apology walk
Spanky Simon next
Leaf versus snail thank you so much right now about was he walk
Probably snap
But leaves are kind of
After all
Spell walrus
On top of it who win
Is this a like Paper Rock Scissors thing
Not sure
Decide after 2
And finally likes I think you did somebody who donated on elevated level appreciate that very much so
Andrew but I wanted to stand out
Thank you so much you are now a technocrat
What's the business
Money off that heroin
Why you pimp so good
Freakishly large
Ida Claire
Thank you so much Andrew but I wanted to stand out
Standout Indy today
If you're out there doing the show and you like sports
Or funneling that money towards
Charitable causes in your area absolutely
Jordan
We have an out-of-context drop to start things off here at on the March 27th
Little bit long for an out-of-context drop my thought it was really funny
O+
Play supercalifragilisticexpialidocious I can say that
Easy supercalifragilisticexpialidocious as overheat can save
I don't know why but if I'm I really I really
So Alex astarte's
Michelle and he starts on what I would describe as a kind of grandiose.
The year 2020 on this Friday Global transmission are 220 days out from the
In the world
Responsibilities and I'm honored to be here and be your house if this be the people's Independent Media
Human
Globalist operation
What an absurd opening to this year
But you also noticed
Starting to use the good guy music from Star Wars a little bit more
It says seems to be coming up a bit more
Yep so he has the most researched
Most listened
2 by world leaders
The people in the industry I think he must mean
Radio Liars
We could be radio or it could be spies or regular grifters I don't know
But all that snow
Alex believes that the media is saying
Anyways saying that we all should be following these these guidelines for public health recommendation
Alex thinks that what they're saying is we will never be normal again
Station map
Virus run its course
I've not heard anybody say they were going to be bubble people
Jake Gyllenhaal is a bubble person
No
Don't know what media he's reading
If that's the vibe he's getting we will never shake hands again
You will never talk I mean I guess you could
You can exaggerate
But what's very normal which
Just pieces saying that the world is going to
To be different
Write this is going to change the world
Turn it into
We're never going to be normal again
I think people are just like well The New Normal is going to be normal
Bubbles
So Alex believes that there's going to be people in America put
In prison for not social distancing
Gets I get to that a little bit here
About medical tyranny surveillance
Six months in jail over your properly
Social distance that's what
Chicago
Mayor is saying
Stories up on newswars.com
Chicago mayor Lori Lightfoot she recently gave a press conference where she was very clearly a bit pissed
But the city's leadership and giving some pretty clear guidance
Hey y'all people shouldn't be getting out there in big groups
And people are still going to parks
Send Hangout
Nothing I'd like the walk
And what have you
She indicated the people if people continue to not take things seriously the city would be forced to act
Maxine quote not only will our police be deployed to shut them down if you are not abiding by these orders we will be forced
To shut down the parks in Lakefront
The situation is deadly serious and we need you to take a deadly seriously
Alex watches a lot of movies
So I'm going to put it to him in terms that he can understand
In Jaws people needed to stop going to
To the beach it was dangerous
And they didn't want to take
Seriously
The mayor needed to close all the beaches too
Protect the population from themselves but
He didn't do it which got a lot of people
Who killed
Mayor Vaughn is the bad guy in Jaws the shark is just a force of nature
Or something recently say that his hero was I don't know
Possibly
That's not the message of the movie
No no
The conversation about a rest
Sing people for not following Health guidelines was initiated by actually not by Lori Lightfoot but the superintendent of the
Police Charlie Beck
Who said quote
The public health order is not an advisory it is a mandate
If you violate you are subject to a fine of $500
If you continue to violate it you will be
Check to arrest
Clearview
The message that was being sent is it
Can be arrested as a last resort if your habitually engaging
Babe your counter to help guideline
I don't hear that as much as a
Threat of an arrest of people as it is a reminder that arrest
Is possible as an outcome
Obviously with the issues of prison
Overcrowding and health within prisons no one's eager to increase unnecessary incarcerations right now
Do you have to just kind of assume it'll be a misdemeanor arrest for you get released on you wouldn't be going
Write anybody who's doing that like
X probably should be
Some stores
Conversely Singapore he's actually threatening
People with six months
In jail for breaking Health guide
There's a couple of big caveat here though
The first is that people who violate their order to keep at least one meter apart from people or meeting groups
With more than 10
Their subject
Either 6 months
Imprisonment or a fine equivalent to 7000 US dollars
It's unclear which one is more likely
The second big caveat is that it
Never a good idea to use Singapore is your example when you're talkin about criminal night
They haven't notoriously Draconian just
You may recall back in 1990 for a team from the United States was arrest
Prison
A $3,500 fine and six Strokes from the
McCain
Bill Clinton appeal to clemency and in the shovers
Respect the leader of Singapore reduced it to for strokes
Yeah
Enoch being formally punished
With the state uses
They also have a very broad definition of what sort
Crimes will get you the death sentence
Importing exporting or possessing more than 500 G of marijuana 30 G
Cocaine 450
Grams of heroin heroin will get you a mandatory. Set
That seems excessive
If you hear the Singapore threat
Dangerous people for violating Health guidelines that might not be exciting news but it also shouldn't surprise anyone
It's honestly a pretty lacks punishment given
Some of the things we know about their justice system
The only reason to bring that up here in the context
Alex is is because he wants to imply that
Chicago is doing the same thing as Singapore is doing and that's not really fair
He's trying to create that that conflation in people's my horse
So Alex
Continuing down his path
I'm trying to say that this is just like
The flu
And how much worse
Fluids
And now they're saying the United States
Is the global
The whole country covered in Red by the model works
Less people died worldwide from the coronavirus this year then died
The flu last year
35000 / 1,000
Dad from the coronavirus supposedly
Denied
CDC
The worst
Ears
First of all Alex's completely lying about the cdc's numbers from
Talking about the number of people who die in a given year January through December isn't really useful way to frame things in this kind of conversation
Flu season begins in like October
It starts to wrap up in February or March so it overlaps years
If your
Think about just flu cases in 2018 you would end up talking about the cases of
The end of one season of the cases at the
The beginning of another
It could be different strains It generally not have these
Difficult Prescott
I definitely not how they're usually presented on the cdc's website
I'm not sure which flea floozies
He's trying to use since this would be either the 2017
2018 flu season or the 2018 2019 flu season
Either way you lie
When he says the 80,000
Directly from the sea
Cdc's website they have to make 61,000 bathroom the influenza-like illnesses
In the 2017 2018 season
It's 34200 in the 2018 2019
Team season
These are imprecise estimates but they're probably spiritually accurate which is to say that the 2017 28
Season was more deadly than the following
Alex is taking his information from news articles from late 2018
The cdc's director came out an estimated there than 80,000 deaths that's easy
Which would be the 27th
2018 C
However articles about this dew point out that quote
CDC officials called
The 80,000 figure preliminary
And that it might be revived
And it was
But if you just read the headline you probably wouldn't know that
We discussed on our last episode by flu comparisons are dumb but I wanted to try it here just to show that when does even when discussing something
Kind of irrelevant
But factually indisputable
Namely that worldwide deaths
From coronavirus are not yet up
Do the estimate of deaths from the US
I am from flu-like illnesses
In that 2017 2018 season
Even when he's talking about that Alex can't help
It's all for being wrong
Glad to know this is the most researched show in the world
Restart his shows like
It's parody it's it's what you do if you were making a joke
It's it's literally
Like
That
That clip of like I just can't pronounce
Red pill
But I can pronounce supercalifragilisticexpialidocious
It is like
That's exactly what's going on with this is really research
If you like me saying this is the least hairy broadcast
Is the podcast where the host has been released back hair
Gaslighted
Hey white Alex is started taking
Atone
And I've noticed it picking up more obviously he's blaming
China and what-have-you
But in the most
Recent episodes I've picked up a little bit of a trend
Where is
More blaming Chinese people
Less so than the Chinese government's decision
I don't want Alex to do it cuz I don't think you can handle the conversation
But I think that you know people have them conversation about whether or not China acted
The way that it
Should have a conversation that can be had
Maybe worldhealthorganization folks
Rather not have that conversation while the pain
Pandemic people in the media who were like did China cover up their numbers early on did they act
Quickly enough
I don't think that is necessarily
A toxic
Conversation
But conversations about Chinese people
And their actions
Particularly chinese-american
Real bad yeah and I believe that Alex is starting to get into that territory
Democrats didn't want
Stop
Chinese from flying on everybody else's band them
Few months ago
Also the Chinese that came here under government orders
M95 masks for the medicine
Stop shipments of Medicine
United States Australia
Celebrate
G2 has a story out
Because where the epicenter
So we are seeing Alex take this rhetoric in a very disturbing Direction
He's always been a huge racist and he's definitely engaged in narratives that blame immigrants
Bringing disease on the pass
Houston we've called that out when he has
What do you starting to do now is still an escalation though because the same behavior that he's had in
The past in different circumstances as the
The potential to cause
Different result
When he was yelling about refugees from the south border coming in from the southern border having it bololo
He was trying to demonize non-white immigrants
Completely clear and off
But there wasn't any Ebola
He was making up an imaginary threat to scapegoat on to those refugees which is bad but not nearly as bad that is
What he's doing now
There is a real outbreak now and Alex's beginning to act in ways where he's blaming Chinese people for being bad
Like making up with a k
Came here and bought up all the masks and Medicine
These are the sorts of claims
They did Believe by wide enough audience stands to get Chinese people
Kilt
The fact that there's a real outbreak elevates Alex's behavior from being absolutely unacceptable bigotry
To be an outright incitement
Many people in his audience may have a loved one who have gotten diagnosed
Stop the virus in
What Alex is trying to do is direct
Feelings of anger towards China
He's not talking about the Chinese government he's talking about some mysterious nonspecific Chinese people who got
Flown in and bought up medicine and math
Yep
So
What's going on here is Alex's working
Two different angles simultaneously
We also which is traveling
What are you literally saying currently is it the outbreak is no big deal it's basically the flu and everyone should go back to work
But what he's preparing for with his rhetoric is the exact
He knows that this
Is going to get worse and he knows the people who are affected by it and who maybe lose loved ones and family members
Unfriend
For someone to blame
All indications from reality show that the Trump Administration made some really bad early decisions that have led us to where we are now
So Alex needs to find a way to deflect four people recognizing
Ultimately he's a racist and he's lazy so the only path he can come up with to go down is to demonize minority group in
And scapegoat them
For his Heroes failing
Just kind of what a Nazi
My day
Pretty much exactly what
Just imagine being a nympho Warrior
Walking down the street
Your
A family member has just died and then you see a Chinese person wearing them
Sprite and maybe a nice watch
Anything
God damn it they stole it
From me and
Killed a family
You don't even need that level of a
Cognitive processing you're already seeing reports
Increased hostility towards Asian Americans
Because of these sorts of
You don't you don't need the
Concrete A2B but
Discussing it in terms like this
Allowed people to
Subconsciously make jumps in their brain
That they don't even realize they're making
This facilitates racism this facilitates
Nonspecific big
Get tree
Hostility
Potentially violent
Yep and it's
Really really f***** up
The exact Behavior you would not want to see any sort
This kind of racism leads
To internment
Wow
Not right now because that would be
Murder but
I mean they're already people
Tampa
So Alex is really defensive about how everyone says don't call it the Chinese virus
Which obviously videos call it the Chinese virus
Doing that
And he likes playing fentanyl the Chinese racist dragon
Character
So he needs
To make sure that everyone knows that this is okay
And yes
The Chinese virus
You always say
Where something came from
Rocky Mountain
Spanish flu
Almost always have the name of where
They
Originated
Alex is just a biggest idiot in the world man before I get into 90s I'd like to remind you that he claimed at the start of the show that he's has the most
Research
Show in the world
So as to be Rocky Mountain tick fever that's actually called Rocky Mountain spotted fever
The disease is a was initially called
Black measles
Because of the coloration of the rash that it caused
However eventually it was found that it wasn't a type of measles and it was associated with
Bike short
It's actually from everything I can tell it's named after the laboratory where most of the research
Diseases.
The Rocky Mountain Laboratory
It's a largely of misleading name so it's almost all of the cases of Rocky Mount
I'm Spotted Fever occur east of okay
Oklahoma with very few actually occurring in the Rocky
Do you think area
It's debatable if it's also named after the fact
Did somebody first identified cases were
I initially thought
Because by the Rocky Mountain wood
Exclusive
Which is native to The Rock
But even if that's the case
It's less geographical in nature and more about the tick
The disease vector
Which is still not great according to epidemiologist
Professional swine flu you end up with
Unnecessary slaughtering
Animals
Spanish Blues even worse as an
An example
You may recall that as a name that was given to the pandemic flu outbreak from 19
If you know your history you also know that
18 happens
To be at the tail end of World War 1
What you might not remember so easily is it Spain was neutral in World War 1
Which meant that they weren't living in
In the same wartime restrictions
As most of the other Allied or Central Power
Countries were
Due to the need to keep morale High almost every country that was involved in World War 1
Highly Center news publication
Sibley suppress reporting about the flu
This was not a consideration for the Spanish
Yahoo a relatively free to report on the reality the outbreaks going on
Beginning in May 1918 they were reporting more candidly
I've been anyone else
About what was actually happening
Which made it appear that they were these source of the out
Probably was
True
No one actually knows.
Definitively where the flu of 1918 came from but there are number theories
None of which are Spain
If you're going strictly by chronology the first
Known case of that flu happened on March
4th 1980
What is soldier at
Fort Riley in
Kansas the United States
Spell l
One theory is that soldiers going to war in Europe introduced that
Disease from therapy
It's hard to definitively know if that's the actual Ulta
The beginning point
These are shity examples
But Alex's using
But we've
We do have a bad history of naming
Diseases after places
For a long time
West Nile virus or Rift Valley fever definitely come to mind is better examples Alex could have used
These diseases were named
Prior to the World Health Organization
Ocean Institute
2015 about naming convention
Where was discouraged
Aziz's after groups of people places or animals
Because it was recognized there was a
Considerate
A considerable stigma
They came along with that practice
Wheatley are necessary and dangerous
There's a rich history of using illnesses
To demonize group
People like for instance according to stat news when syphilis first came around it quote was known as the Napoleon
Not at napolitan.
The Apollo
Neapolitan disease French the French disease among the Italian
Russians called it the Polish disease in the Polish called at the German dizzy
This other thing is counterproductive
Public health so in present-day it's
Heavily discouraged
The issue for Alex though is that demonizing Chinese me what is exactly what he wants to do so explaining to him that we'd
You don't name diseases that way so we don't
Pointlessly demonize people isn't going to help
No that's
The point
Yep
It's it's amazing how well human beings
You know
And it also how
Very very very very poorly and not at all we do
It's amazing
Yep it's
20 f***
Walking 20
You better than 20/20
So
I was mostly interested in listening to the show not because of whatever fun wise you was going to tell
How about the coronavirus what kind of deflections use go
Going to have a backdrop that's kind of standard stuff
I was really boring
Interested in tuning in to find out what are we going to do about the bad news
What are we going to do
Approaches is unexpected but also completely predictable
Do you start
A second
By bringing up how the media always lies about his court case
The media's fault
I want to be clear
The way he's setting this up
It's obvious that you stalking
About the stories that have come out about the Sandy Hook hair
Get to this
It's it's bizarre it's really bizarre
On New Year's Eve this year
TV channel
Program
Fox News
CVS
Ranch Acres
Jones Lost a lawsuit
Attacking Sandy Hook children
None of that was even true
On a routine basis on every channel
Please ships in South Africa
That's on the little hand out at your door every morning
Black people children
That's a South African
Open cruise ship newsletter wasn't about Alex's court case I was about his DUI and it wasn't on
The front page
Was just an aggregated ft of AP stories
Attempt to repurpose that narrative here
Answer the question of whether or not the media constantly lies about Alex's court cases I would say they do not
The New Year's Eve stuff those stories that came out on December 31st 2019 we're not
About Alex losing any case
The headlines were that Alex had to pay $100,000 in
Vines
Ridiculous Behavior
BBC reported this was because quote
Mr. Jones
His lawyer I'd intentionally disregarded in October court-ordered
Witnesses
And other materials
Plaintiffs in the lawsuit
Some of this
Is out Rob dudes fault
Oh yeah
The AP story about this from back then clearly says that quote
He weighed Jeffries and attorney for Jones said in an email Tuesday that they would appeal the decision not to
Dismiss Define
This is because they had
Previously requested that the fines be dismissed
Which was the
Declined the Alexander
Appealed the decision to dismiss
Fine
That gets us to the price
Because on March
26th it was reported that Alex lost that appeal
And that he was facing approximately $150,000 in fines and fees in this case even before the trial hasn't
Begun
He's going to end up with even more
Before this is all said and done
Because his strategy is clearly to stretch things out
And file frivolous motion a frivolous motion
He doesn't have any other shot
Because he probably knows
This trial is the
Potential to end his career
But even though the media is reporting on Alex losing this
This appeal in the Pres
The Austin american-statesman
Clearly says that Alex's lawyer plans to appeal this to the Texas Supreme Court
So Alex can get on his show here and pretend that he's definitely winning this thing when
All he's really doing is trying to run out the clock
Yep it's probably work pretty well in other cases you know hoping
To become such a hassle to the plaintiff they settle
But I don't think that's
Play is going to work here
I think he's just delaying the inevitable
Nope not this time
Bedtime it's going to be real concert
So he's saying that everybody the media always lies and the media said that he lost this case back
Then which obviously is meant to imply that these new stories that are coming out now are also the same lie
Liza's from New Year's
But he doesn't
Say that
That's just the implication
You would understand very clearly if you knew the news that had come out
But I was just bring up the news story
It's very weird it would hurt it
It's very weird
Anyways
Gulbis need maker
The billing out of Alec
Why do they do that
Because the order from the shadow government went out programmed in to the Mockingbird system
Operation Mockingbird
Make me a villain
Why are they doing that
Because when the Council on Foreign Relations
Atlantic Council
All of these other
Globalist organizations tune into this show
Organization of economic Cooperative element as the main corporation
I know I know about the XM Bank
They know that I really have done the research
Them out
None of that is private stuff
Grappa just appointed ahead of the
Exports in Portsmouth
It's not none of
Google start worried about this expialidocious
Conception don't exist
But if they did they would not be worried about what
They would be like all right
You just going to make a couple bucks
Alphaline pills and yelling
All right. So why would they
They make you a villain
Because you play the Imperial f****** March theme song like I've got that everybody you like his ability even if they
It's just not hard but also like you know who else would make you available
Anybody who cares about other
It's really the reality
The way you behave and the rhetoric
It comes forth in the world that you wish to
Create
Through your rhetoric
It's something that's offensive to most decent people
So I think
They would have a vested interest in
Portraying you as you are which is villainous
Yeah absolutely
No need for globalist for the equation
Why would they make
Like a Villain and then you just play the fentanyl clip and they're like oh yeah
So Alex said that is a busy the scourge of
Still in this
This rant
It was
Gunn by the
Introduction of they always lie about me losing Court
Eventually going
Get to this news
But instead he's just like
Man they're so scared of me
Do you have to understand
Broadcast
With the guests and the calls and myself and the crew
Man
When I take over the TV station are the tape
Elevation of the government's villainess
Criminals and it's game over
The globalist TuneIn and they go if people
Ever pay attention to this
It's over for us
I don't know about that I've been looking into his stuff for quite a while and
I do not have the same response that Alex thinks the people's would if they looked
I would say almost the Opera
Just just
Just disappointed couple episodes ago we were going through what type of movies are hot on there I am going
Across Alpha Running Man
We got that one
You got to get a bingo card going you really should get a bingo card
We really should
I think it would be it would be used up very quickly
I'm I'm positive of hurting
But maybe not on our show
So Alex knows that the globalist need to make him a villain
And they need to do that
Because once they have made him bad
Bad
Most people don't already
F****** hate up yeah
They've ruined his name that make him kill him
The populist nationalist Christian Patriot
Mahajan capital letters before they kill me but they do intend to kill me
What about me
Human evil
Let's eat
To literally sterilize
Every man child on the planet
Bi-Lo
Children of Men
Oh there we go
You be in the mail
But you see that the movie to see the scripture saying we should Outlaw male fetuses
This is
Brooks
What sounds horrific
It is Harissa
So this is a great moment that helps reveal how little Alex knows better
He's just
Mad that the stock Clinic has a wing dedicated to gender since 1989 called the gender identity
Development service
He thinks that a clinic focus on gender identity is equivalent to them wanting to eliminate males
This is the byproduct of his bigoted
The confusion comes because there's another entity called The Tavern
Tavistock
Institute of human relations
Which grew out of the Tavistock
But it's been a completely separate organization
Since September 9th
T47
The Tavistock Institute engages in education and advocacy surrounding issues related
The social science
New release the journal human relations
Alex thinks that the Tavistock clinic in the Tavistock Institute are the same
Same thing
I've heard him get the
Completely confused on many occasions
And honestly if this is the level of work he's bringing
I don't really think
IndyGo bus need to be too worried about him
Before over the years they've been plenty of think pieces written about how women could probably do a better job of ending Wars than that
Which kind of relates to what Alex was talking about
I can't find any of them that relate to suggest a good men should be gotten rid of
Maybe a tweak here and there he enjoys watching to find me all about
I found one that argue for higher representation of women
Peace negotiations
And there's plenty of articles that have restless references to lysistrata
But the sword thing that I was talking about doesn't seem like it
It's real outside of
Diculous conspiracy theories that basically just grow out of anti-lgbtq ideology
Yeah
So I don't know I don't I don't find a whole lot of Truth there but it's so fascinating to me how consist
This inability to understand like I really don't think he knows that the Tavistock answer
Student clinic or different
I absolutely agree with you
I ain't no way he's fascinated by that
Because
He has every reason
And if and if you told him he'd be like
No they're not
Just a blanket boats named after Tavistock
Square Where is the
Anyway
The Chinese tablets
Leftist
Again this is still part of the same segment that begins with the
Ramble about the lying about his court cases
They need to destroy my name I'm the Zeitgeist the globalist fear me
It's all sort of in the same theme
Yeah you know yeah
If you look at the CD Granda the Ivory Tower
Family of the University
Formerly of the last
Now they Revel in conformity
On some good mission
Such
Useful idiots
Smocks
Their own world and system they have submission to the tyranny
Definition of ally they're delusional
Becoming Dumber
Dime
They're not having children they're dead
Metric show
But still they delusionally believe
Quest
And pull down price
Somehow they're University degree
As a liberal
Position of power
Vision
They're all going to run something
But first
Submit
The model that they have for you which is an anti-human model
And you ask why do they keep trying
Because if you are following the real human model
By God
You'll be empowered
You want a relationship
The God and the universe gun created
You won't need them
He's what he chooses to
How he wants to cover losing his appeal
Rambling
About
Demons that left us then
Oh they're all dead already
Projecting
Exactly what
He's trying to do on to the leftist
Talk about Conformity the entire right-wing propaganda machine
Turn the right-wing into a cult of trump
More conforming then
A 35% of the country
No matter what believing the Trump is perfect
Yeah it
It's disgusting
Yeah I agree
So Alex is still like I died
I can't stress this enough there's all these does this whole segment and does not address
The actual news at all but you can tell that's what is behind what do I do
When you don't work when you don't build when you don't
Strive you become
Lackadaisical
Rough
Obsolete
And ready for the fire
That's why they're building this world where
Humans are needed
Progress
Understand
Going along with your post
So I think Alex is completely lost the thread of
Seems to be trying to talk about it
Can you just bring himself
I look again
Once again stories of my lost appeals are not true
I feel like he's like
I don't know
A child that
Just got in trouble and so now he's like smashing glasses over there just
I need to get something out of this deal with what
Glass smashing becomes like manifested is just
Trying to yell about how you're the target of an entire worldwide
Broc
Yep and you know within minutes he's about the races and is completely unrelated stuff
I will say however at this point he like I said he has
Not addressed
The new news at all
That you know
Having said that
It's nice to hear him say that what the US did to the native peoples wasn't attempted genocide next term
That seems like something you
Pretty consistently denies because he's pretty invested in the American exceptionalism line
We're all negative talk about the country and its history is just
The product of globalist meddling
Imagine if he was pressed on it
He probably saved
Globalist for trying to kill the natives
It was a noble Forest trying to defend them again
But whatever
Leaving that aside it should be pointed out that on Friday news broke
About the department of the Interior ordering that the reservation of the Mashpee
Wampanoag tribe e disestablished
The land was put into a trust in 2015 but Trump's Administration went back on that
September 2018
There have been ongoing legal just
It's about this but I don't think there's any way to look at it
I'm not come away at the conclusion.
The timing is almost
Comically villainess
Alex in the political world either part of do not give a f*** about native peoples absolutely
It's just convenient to sometimes pretend to care when their Slaughter can be used
To make a point about your own imaginary Vicky
Yeah that's all
Great Clips
Service to it I guess I mean if that's
If you really are saying that right now and you're not then
And following it up with
And so we should invest more in the Native America
Community instead of
Just being like
Be they did it and now I'm not going to do anything more
Like it's do it
It's exploitative
It is
So Alex gets on with this segment it wraps up and he doesn't bring up the case
Which is
I comes back from break
Andy's got Passage
From history
That's on his mind
Thomas Paine
What are the times
Try men's Souls
Summer Soldier and the Sunshine Patriot will in this crisis shrink
Service of their country
Buy It Now
Deserves the love and thanks of man and woman
Journey like hell
A passage from Thomas Paine's pamphlet The American crisis but I think he was
The date wrong
It wasn't published in 1775 who was first posted in the Pennsylvania journal on December 9th
Keep 1776
It was months after that
Declaration of a
Independence
The pamphlet was basically just War propaganda to get colonists on the side of the Revolutionary War
Painfully naive
Pain says quote
Highest
Sincerely wish that our next year's arms makes spell them
From the continent and the Congress appropriates their possession
For the relief of those who have suffered in well-doing
A single successful battle next year we'll settle the whole
Revolutionary War did not end
XTR infact lasted
Until 1783
Thomas Paine was the Dick Cheney of his time at this is his they'll greet us as liberators
However there is a passage that Alex
Doesn't read from that pamper
I think is pretty applicable to Alex himself
Pain is disgusting help
Panic effect
Panics in some cases have their uses
They produce as much good as hurt
Their duration is always short the Mind soon grows
Through them and acquires a firmer habit than before
But their peculiar advantages
That they are the
The touchstones
Sincerity
And hypocrites
And brings things and been to light which might otherwise have Lane forever undiscovered
I feel like the supplies pretty well
It's Alex and his behavior the past month or so
Granted the things we've all seen very clearly in the light of this Panic has Shameless
Mystic sales practices and
Please disregard
A consistency or accuracy in reporting
Those aren't necessarily things that would have lame forever undiscovered
But they take on a new level of importance
Context of this outbreak
And not to
Forget his complete and utter disregard for human
Well that Candlelight yet
I think we had a hint at that fire when we knew but this now that it's
Do you know you can you can have disregard for human life whenever it's imaginary and you're like that could be a thing but now that it
Real and you're actively advocating for thing
Things that will kill people yeah that's that's a little bit
Different story
Yeah also if Alex could read the rest of that pamphlet he would have gotten to the part where Thomas Paine was not so thrilled with my
Alicia's
Quote from an excessive tenderness we were unwilling to raise an army
Entrusted our cause the temporary defense of a well-meaning militia
Assemblers experiences naoto
Better
He goes on to say quote
I've always considered militia is the best troops in the world for a seven
Exertion but they will not do for a long campaign
I'm with that I think I agree with Thomas Paine
Militias are good for I don't know let's say domestic terrorism
What sort of insurgent
Don't have time for that
Standing army not so good at short-term terrorist verse
I don't know
Betty White
They tried my point is that Alex doesn't have a good handle on his Source material here putting those a couple of good passages you can put out the
Tend to complement his narratives every once in awhile so
According to him he has a PHD in history
And this is the most research show at
One thing that he can pack himself himself on the back about is that he did not claim this was her
So, so
That's true maybe maybe we missed three days reading the quote accurately gets at least a quote
I will hand it to him
For that there are low bar
It's like when you give a kid a cookie for tying a shoe
For you for you
We need to positively reinforce
Your behavior
There's a cookie out
Enochian
So now Paul Joseph Watson ends up coming on
And they talked a little bit I think most of it is surrounding the idea that you know Boris Johnson now has Coronavirus
And so they talked about that a tiny bit and then Alex's something real.
Paul Joseph Watson is in the UK where the Prime Minister has contracted
The dreaded
Wound on Tricom
Covid-19
Ramping up that race
Umbro
Without the sun which actually kills
Covid-19
Is there an attorney general
Killing the Coronavirus
Sunlamps
Two people
I was worried that he did.
Vitamin D
Super concentrated UV light kill virus
But that's not what you get for being outside
Even direct sunlight over a long time will not do any
Think about the Coronavirus
So there are three kinds of UV light
Abmc
Is the most prevalent kind that you get outside
Be the kind of damaging to your DNA and causes sunburn
I meant see is
Pretty cost
Six stuff that the
Destroys genetic
Material
Deal with it and nature because the ozone in the atmosphere blocks it out
And stops it from
Ryan you yeah that one
That one's pretty helpful for the
Continued survival of all life on
F*** you up in like a minute
Anyway uv-c is
The kind of light that can kill viruses
Places are using that kind of technology for disinfect
But it should never be
He suggested to be used
4 people
It will f*** you up really bad
And probably give you can
Anyway I was just continuing the string of erroneous statements about cures and prevention
For the Coronavirus
But again like you like you were worried at least he doesn't tell you he likes I'm telling you he is trying to get a letter for
From every Attorney General
Problem isn't necessarily like that a lot of people have with
I mean obviously the profiteering makes it worse
Way worse
Spite
From public health standpoint even if you're not making money off it saying
Things that are
Will be wrong and dangerous like you should drink bleach if you're not selling
Oh man
So Boris Johnson's got the covid-19 Paul Joseph Watson recognizes
Boris Johnson
Is real dumb
Now the prime minister
World leader
Indian
Coronavirus
Please something to do with it
Coronavirus victims in hospital 3 weeks ago
Pretty dumb
Yeah
That's why I voted for
The claim the Boris Johnson is the first world leader to
Contract coronavirus is
Just not true
Bolsonaro tested positive though he claims he took another test and it was negative but he's also a huge liar and an a****** so
So who knows cleaning it's a giant hoax on top of
That I know
Even real Munoz
What an a****** even if you leave bolsonaro off that list
Monaco tested positive for this virus and I only know that because
Alex f****** told me so
Justin Trudeau's wife tested positive so you kind of have to assume that he probably has it too
You shocked
Vice president of Iran tested positive
What about
Prince Charles
Also I know that he's technically not a world leader but Alex
Thinks he is so shouldn't Rand Paul be more important
This conversation Horace that's a good call
Some of these people aren't technically the heads of
They're all people I would call pretty relevant politically
Boris Johnson
The first V number one
Absolutely
Yeah
I can't believe
Suppose got an interesting perspective on this
I buy everything I mean
Flagrantly race
Real so
Cautious
Interesting
He believes
There are things we need to do
Call
But he also has an angle that seems really consistent that's like they're only going to make White's do this okay there we go
Not great
Alright KKK
We should have overreacted because then if we
We didn't we didn't take it seriously
Problem is it
Hospital beds
The UK and in London warm hospital already why
Problem of the rush of new patients
Been making it
People who are already here
But again please
Social distancing measures
Bull selectively enforced as you said
Alex
You going to the
Migrant
Alabama Avenue
Gangs of them still out on the streets Northlake
Wow
Text Mary maybe not even
Totally I bet
Muslims aren't
Sure why not come on out
So f****** clothes
To getting it everybody on the way
The the Dosey
Detailed like we should have overreacted more
Because now we're seeing the situation where
The running out of ventilators of people who could have been helped
Can't be helped you out and it's causing a real problem the overwhelming of the medical system is coming into being
So he gets back part right
And then what's the next step
Play Muslim
Blaming them conversation towards like
Let's not focus on that let's focus on the fact that Muslims get away with everything
If you were if your argument is we should have done something before
Suggest that the p
People who didn't do that
Should have done it and they made a mistake
They f***** up let's not
It's more important to focus on the back of the non-white
Urban Youth Muslim
Guitar going now
This story
Mike down for this
Because Paul Joseph Watson
I do not believe the story
1 bit
This story
Is
Fake
Meanwhile
London yesterday
A group of
Undecided to have Alex
On the street
Pissing in the street
A group of six of them
On the main road in London
But if you walk your dog
In a remote location
England
Camille
So I know that he does not specify the race of these youth
But he is very bad
Regeneron if you're on Infowars you know how the audio
To hear that there's coding in the way you telling the story
If we do accept the promise of Paul's Tale
I think there's another explanation for every
The police are not everywhere at all times
I can be able to respond to things that are brought to their attention in any case
Different places will have relatively different sensibilities in terms of what someone might report to the
It's basic print
Temple is why when I was young I would never smoke a joint in my car in a good neighborhood
There's too many well-to-do people with nothing better to do than look out the window and snitch
It's entirely possible that the probably imaginary dogwalker Paul is talking about
Unfortunate
Remove nose
Eneighbors
If any of this is true and Paul understands the need to react in ways that may seem like over-reaction in other
Circumstances
And he Witness
Is this rap battle fight
What did he call the Pooh
Boise wow I mean he's not a snitch
It's because it's made of
Or because he doesn't really care about this to begin with
He's only interested in them battling
And telling the story
Opportunity to build up a racist grievance
Also the story definitely
Definitely did not
Let's see let's see how you were
You should join that rap
Come on man what are you doing
Alex joins as they continue this theme in this trend of
Baja Muslims get away with whatever they want while the whites
Impact
Muslim you literally can rape kill pissed dedicate stab
You're a citizen you're in some super world
Remote area climbing a hill it is then
Drones
A weird drum
Set Alexa
Because they know that
Okay
Buddy a lot of people get off by being obedient
The message could not be more clear and they are trying to do
It's disgraceful I'm going to be is racist to everyone is
So Alex has a big announcement and it's only sort of mentioned on our last episode I believe and that is that
Food orders
Are back on
Thursday Thursday
Pre-order
Thing now
You can have
Alex talked about this a little bit
This is the most ludicrous thing I've ever heard
That's a good news
My Patriot Supply
They run our servers and
Take the orders when you ordered
You're right
Comes in
Two weeks ago that they didn't they had enough food to fulfill those orders but not more food going forward while they got a bunch of food Bots
And they got two more factories fired up so that six pack
Everything
They're making us apply you food and they haven't gone up in price
I don't know about that but I would say that this narrative is f*****
Because
Where to get their food
Great pic at this
This is Miss Teresa
Surprise you make it and it's about food
Do more factories and then you suck the food out from the ground like an oil was that everyone else
Without a food everybody without a food then
These suppliers specifically only willing to sell to my Patriot Supply
A relationship where they would have known like all week
Can get
Wavy way more food
Then this wouldn't this
This is a clog in the drain never would have happened latest this bottleneck
What happened that I was
I just don't believe any of that's not it
It's not
It's just not true
But it is one of those things that the food buckets are certainly something like I've mentioned are compatible to a bunch of
Two different conspiracy
Panic narrative
So if Alex is able to bring that back online
He can still push that even with the virus has no big
Ideal cities to burn
They're going to lock you down even if it's not a big deal you're going to be still need the food buckets
It's probably something that you was working
To get back
To be able to sell
Because it's so
Evergreen
Yeah it like I was going back and listening to episode The Bill Cooper show I'm like he's selling food buckets of the middle of the 90
You know like it's just always going
To be something
It works with every Panic week before food buck
Skier Corona
Do you remember back in the end of February Alex predicted that Rodger Stone
Would be back hosting the war room within a week
Don't hasn't happened
Diction dislodge that in my brain and I wanted to make a point of like how bad bad prediction
That was pretty brutal
So in this next Club Alex retells the timeline
Of what's happened
Over the last
While
And it's really sad
Because you're trying to make Trump look good
And it's
He doesn't even succeed at doing that you can hear him like
Really trying
To come up with
The next something yeah it's like him running across a little braids or whatever
Creek
And you're jumping from rock to rock boys see him trying to find the next Rock
Mike Adams on the show was the first got a really raised the alarm and I agree with him
Then they flipped and said it's all your fault
We knew that was coming Warren Trump
Did respond now that we understand if we over panic it'll be too far
This is been a very scripted setup whole
You can hear him just like trying to figure out how to
Complete a set
Better than this
All that all that's made of
How does that work with Alex
Is all idea about the secret emerge
Cincy declaration the Trump made way back
The secret emergency
Fauci
Everything is fauci
Chief Albright
I want to imagine for a second to what Alex is saying is
Okay even if all that's true
Trump is a horrible president
Alex is trying to whitewash away all of Trumps very clear f*** ups by insisting that it wasn't Trump
Trump is perfect in always does the right thing but his globalist
Lying to him and tricking him all the time
Even if that's true Wichita
Trump is a gullible idiot whose inability to understand the situation he's in
Is putting people's lives at risk right but he's also a genius
Because he's tricking them at
At the same time
Getting
Good luck
Even in Alex's best case scenario where Trump is this is aerobic figure
He's still
Wildly unfit to be president
Yeah this is if you're that easily influenced and you're the greater
This thing ever then what the
What are you talkin
About Alex
So Alex is still pushing the hydroxychloroquine can help everybody think sure
Still in service of the fact that it supposedly helps put
Zinc into cells and Alex cells think so
Words that ever
So he's mad
Because some governors
Come out
They're not thrilled
With people
Getting unnecessary prescription
Ordered all Democrats
Doctor prescribed
Hydroxychloroquine
There's no way the governor's would ever outright ban the prescribing of hydroxychloroquine
Because it's an important medication
Can four people at certain condition
It's not just
Appropriate
Prescribed for Coronavirus cases necessarily important
Certain
Alex is most likely just reporting on a meme that was circulating
Turning Point USA the claim that Nevada Governor Steve
Sisolak
Advanced views of hydroxychloroquine
In reality Governor sisolak head
Just issued an emergency regulation that made it so you can't get a prescription for it
Outpatient setting
If it's for Coronavirus
Michigan Governor Gretchen Whitmer who Trump doesn't like
Made a similar rule
Andrew Cuomo in New York
And Ohio Governor Mike dewine
Authorized the State Board of Pharmacy to file an emergency rule
Which made it so people could not fill hydroxychloroquine
Prescriptions unless they had a written diagnosis on them from the prescriber
And if that diagnosis with Coronavirus
It had to be king
Confirmed
I'm not sure what other states Alex is talking about and Mike dewine the Republican so he might just be make
The stuff up
The reason for these sorts of actions
Being necessary is that companies Dumb Friends
Pretending this drug was a miracle cure for an active
Pandemic
What they did is it
Tended to have a beta run on the medication we're just created a shortage
And this is a big problem
Because why the drug is used to treat
Prevent malaria
It's also used by people with rheumatoid arthritis and lupus
Those are chronic conditions
People are panicking and running around buying up all the medications that are used
To treat them leaves less medication for the people who actually need it
These Republicans both Republican and Democrat are doing the only responsible thing they can do
Which is restrict
The prescribing of this medication is best they can
To not do so would create a ridiculous amount of unnecessary suffering for people with arthritis and lupus
Which is a unattended consequences
Of the sort of irresponsible behavior that Alex and Trump were behaving
You don't care
Yeah it really
Like whenever he said that
If they weren't
That should have been an immediate
You're gone 25th Amendment
F*** out of here that's on except
Well that's literally
Unacceptable Shakedown
Let's, CLE
Evil
This sort of thing it's like what are you ask yourself the question of like why I haven't
Past presidents
Said things like
Hey this hydroxychloroquine is looks like it's going to be a cure
Why is that irresponsible
And you reckon
Nye's Auto because
People listen to people in leadership and Authority position
Yep they take them more seriously then
Maybe they should be
And so people who have no reason to get this medication will go out
And try and get the medication
It'll lead to shortages and people who need
Need the medication woo
Possibly be left without and like that is why
Be careful
I mean there's other reasons that dude died in Arizona
Considerations that like are just
Wheatley
Gone now
Mines
The people who are in positions
Powerline
Yeah they're all literally
Insane there is very clearly making a case for like
Why did those
Sort of norms and behaviors
It seems like unnecessary why do people act like that
That would make
So enter next clip here we find Alex being very mad
It Michael Rapaport Michael Rapaport is said some s***
Before
You know that
Ugly
That I'm evil
Alright
Imagine being a
Biological
Android like this guy
I mean look
Gutter worm
Wants Baron
Barron Trump
Emperor Palpatine
No no yo-yo
In full disclosure of Michael Rapaport is a guy was a long history of talkingshit
It's kind of his thing
Call Alex at saying are you saying that
Forget Coronavirus
Switch deal
Cuz he doesn't think it's a big deal most severely offensive
A person could say how dare you how dare you wish
Harm upon dear leader
The Trump wanting to open
When businesses backup
And the Fuller quote is
Why don't you send your f****** son dick stain Donald Trump jr. big tooth
Eric Trump little f****** Barron f****** Ivanka
Junkyard Jared
Let them go out there and test the f****** Waters let them see if this s*** is sweet
Let them take the cars the trains the buses
The Amtrak let them play in the park
And if everything is good after 5 days and then playing in the streets
We'll all go back
So it wasn't just Barren it was more of a point about how Trump wants to do this thing that he's largely insulated from
The consequences other than the rest of us will pay the price
Of course Alex is the business of selling
Griezmann to his audience
And what better way to say this
Ben is dumb actor wants to kill Trump
Innocent child
You even like
It's in my it's in my son's here
Pieces of deer leadership
Absolutely that
How dare you Greta
Or his son absolutely not any perceived attack
On the Family
Alex will present as an attack on the youngest
Most recent
Yeah
How dare you the children Dan won't somebody think of
Cheerleaders children not their own
Or anybody else's
So Alex gets into complaining more about Bill a
That's at investor who you think's is short selling
The market
Neusa come out that he made a bunch of money
So he's not mad at Jeff bezo selling 3.7 billion by the year
Albert
Alex is mad at Bill Ackman if people have responded
Probably the reason
That he hates Bill Ackman is because Ackman had a
Negative
Position on Herbalife
He believed it was a supplement.
He's kind of an enemy of those
That's sort of marketing Industries
He hates Bill Ackman
But Bill did make a bunch of money recent
And Alex believe that it's
Short Selling
He has not proved that in any way I read a bunch of articles about this
It turns out what actually happened is that Bill Ackman took out credit to
Folks WAP insurance
On some long position
Said his hedge fund
Amanda paying off pretty well gacha
It's not the same thing
Is short selling
And Alex doesn't know the difference
I have no idea if any of the things that people do
The markets are ethical
I do not
I'm really going to let you know
Err on the side of no
So I'm not defending Bill Ackman at all but the difference between
Default swap insurance
And short-selling
He's just like Baba blah in shorts on the market that people are at least aware
Yeah
So Alex
Skip back to selling his food a little bit
A lot of food
Turn on
Meg
Just getting out of the business
Volatile
Christian
Mission to do that s*** what they believe in
That's ridiculous
I know that
Most businesses like to get out with demand is through the roof
Possible now we got to get out of
Look I got into business
Hoping to build something and make profit but now there's the opportunity I got to get out of here
I
Kidding myself
What was I thinking
How dare I try and make money that's
Comical so they got a huge amount of storable food
While every other major food distributor
And they can't handle the heat got to go.
So my Patriot Supply had to shut
Down production for a couple of
In order to shut down the Alex and then
After that they caught up
And they were the only ones able to secure a giant shipment of food
They are good at business
There's probably probably
So Alex
In this next clip talks about how like hey you know
I predicted all this
What's happening now
I'm so I'm going to predict
More things are going to happen in the future
And you know I'm always right
Hey this is where we get introduced to a primary source
But I think it's actually really interesting
Three months ago bio-weapon
Today
London Guardian
World Government needed
Rockefeller Foundation 10 years ago
We're going to use a bayou released to bring in world government
Are on record with all of this ladies and gentlemen
F*** you
I was pretty
So Alex didn't necessarily predicted bioweapon release unless you consider literally every straight thing he says to be a prediction
He's way more focused on the globalist
Nuking the u.s. city most likely
Chicago
Also the coronavirus isn't a bioweapon so even if that was his prediction
At the.
Alex references there at the end the Rockefeller Foundation
And I was curious what the specific source
Every time I tried to trace down one of his primary sources on this we're going to release a bioweapon
To bring in world
I think it's been a huge disappointment
I never run out of the benefit of
The doubt
Maybe this one will finally be the one that I
Actually Alex read
Correctly
If I went to the video for this episode simply doesn't say with this
Report Hazard give any clue as to how to track it down
But there is a good shot of the piece of paper he's holding up
Which month is a bit of a dead
Luckily for me though this is a huge talk
Pinpoint the conspiracy
Community
Easy to
Figure out what this word
This is from a May 2010 report from the Rockefeller Foundation
Entitled quotes scenarios for the future of technology and International Development
It's 54 pages long which is outside of Alex's
Paragraph reading limit
Quit
Here's what this document is
The people who wrote the report were tasked with analyzing the technological and International Development related issues that could come up
In the world that could pose a challenge to philanthropic
Ization a tickly in the developing world
And the only way to solve those with a biome
Guys that there were certain things that were certainty
Such as population growth and entered energy
But what the report was most interested in was
Exploring with a cold
Critical uncertainty
Airport has a full list of the uncertainties in the appendix
And identified a bunch
Things like new innovation
Global economic perform
Those are things that can't really be predicted
Each has serious impact on what situation we will find ourselves in a
The future
However the report authors were tasked with the
Deciding which two critical uncertainties were most Central to how things
Play out
They determined that
Adaptive capacity was one
And that it could be a situation where we end up
Highly adaptive or with a low level
Of adaptability
The other uncertainty that they chose was political and
Economic alignment
Which they determine could either be strong or weak
You can see how the second one political and economic climate is of particular interest to people in
Philanthropic
Yeah organization
Particularly in developing countries
So with these two critical uncertainties selected the team created for scenarios which represented a drama
X version of what the world might look like in each combination of these outcomes
And specifically what role technological innovation
Would play in each of the Worlds
Play Imagine
Right
So they
They war games
Yeah yeah
Bhai adaptability week alignment scenario was called smart scramble
The high adaptability strong alignment scenarios called
Clever together
The low adaptability week alignment scenario with
Hack attack
And the low adaptability strong alignment scenario is named
Lockstep
Is named fascism
Absolutely
The 2nd or probably a hack attack doesn't have a positive
It's clear that the ideal solution is clever together or the world you would like
Toosii
Able to respond to challenges
That's the that's the one if you read the report is
Nothing and it is negative
Political science article by clever together they're trying to convince us
It Rhymes though
Clever together is described as quote a world in which
Highly coordinated entry
Successful strategies emerge for dressing
Urgent and entrenched worldwide issues
Hack attack is quote
An economically unstable and shock prone World in which governments weekend criminals Thrive and dangerous Innovations emerge
Smart scramble is quote and economically depressed World in which individuals and communities develop localized
Makeshift solutions to a growing set of problems
Lockstep is quote a world
Tighter top-down government
Control and more authoritarian leadership
With limited innovation
Ingrowing citizen pushp
The website
To push this document is being about the Rockefeller Foundation planning to use a bio-weapon
To bring in a world government are inherently full of s***
Because what they're doing is cherry-picking lines
From the four different scenarios and
Pretending it's all one
Plan
However most of it is from the locks
Because that's the one where there's a rise of top down
Authoritarian Sissy
The authors of this report imagine that an instigating event for that scenario could be a global pandemic
Where the need for greater social structure to fight an outbreak could be exploited by leaders who want that kind
Kind of power
It's presented as a
Not good outcome
DB like some sort of Department of Justice wanting to indefinitely
Detain people without worrying about them going to
Oh no no no no
Sorry I was just thinking that
Random out of the blue just like thoughts that could never possibly happen
It's like I said it's presented as a not good out
And you don't want that
And ultimately in that scenario
There's no world government
It's only dictator
In many countries and some uneasy Regional alliances
Is with uneasy populations at the point of uprising
That's where that scenario plays out to it doesn't end in a world government
The government in shambles I believe in rubble and Meyers
Conspiracy sites like that the scenario starts with a pandemic
But it doesn't end the way they wanted
It just doesn't make
The point they want
Pieces out of each of the scenarios to create collage of something
It kind of sounds like something they can work with
The clever together scenario involves Global Collective action about climate change
So they toss that in there
The problem is that literally none of these scenarios involved
Louisiana Bayou
My weapon and none of them resulted world government
The only way to reach that conclusion
Completely twist the words on the page of the point where you might as well just be rewriting the report to
Suit your purposes
What is what they're doing
I don't like what
Report says
But it does come from
A place that I hate so how about I just lie about
Close enough for Horseshoes and Hand Grenades
I read over the document and it in no way demonstrates that the Rockefeller Foundation admitted that they wanted to release by 11 to bring in the world
That's absolutely ludicrous
Something I definitely would not expect
Epicure on the most research show in the world
I guess this was
The time but Alex it actually read the doctor
Correctly but supercalifragilistic
Expedia
I will get my hopes up again
Good luck
Also
You know how I keep mentioning that is really popular on conspiracy theory sites
It's not that popular I was kind of lying
It's pop it's not that popular the contacts Alex's using
However the most prominent site pushing
Narrative
Is Jim Fetzer blog might be the case that Alex is using his old holocaust-denying buddy facts
There is a source again that in the Sandy Hook
Okay so you said you said
F****** dumb look like like like you say it's a bad thing people say the definition of insanity is doing
In the same thing over and over and over again expecting different results
But they haven't met Spencer
He's too good
He's not too good
I should be
Beef are you Michael Jones is also pushing this document new Holocaust denier
Canker sores
Hey anti-Semitism is a good fall back
Plan whenever anything is going bad
So as Alex is going out to break easy cited these this headline in this report
And he says this
Where is my article
Laid out scenario where virus outbreak Prime storage area Crackdown
I'll get more into this
Furniture phone call
So he's going out to break
You read that other headline
Mickey's meaning to suggest this globalist think tank is a different story than the one about the Rockefeller Foundation
What is the same headline he just read
Acceptance
Infowars write-up of nothing
This one is written by a dawn Salazar our former Twitter followers
Marks of intentional lion
The one here's the first paragraph of his article
Bible Eyre I lie all the time as well babe
Rockefeller Foundation report produced 10 years ago imagine to viral pandemic is
The perfect Catalyst Implement quote
Titer top down
God
It control it more authoritarian leadership
Eerily similar to what's on folding during our current coronavirus outbreak they also included that celeb
Havertys would all sing imagine
The report doesn't imagine a viral
Pandemic is a perfect
Catalyst Implement tighter top-down government
Controlling more authoritarian leadership
Physic incredibly unfair characterization
The document because that framing
Suggest they were trying to find a way to implement authoritarian leadership
And the virus was the perfect way to do it
Instead of actively looking for a way to stop the authoritarian leadership
That's just a complete misreading of the point of
I'm not sure necessarily that it is actually even about stopping authoritarian leadership
If that
He's the world that ends up coming into being what are the challenges that Alex
Exist
From of philanthropic developing world
Situation
Most importantly
What are the ways in which Tech
Technological innovation
Will be used
DMVs
Four different type of
Society we find ourselves in
Right so that's really
What
The report is by it's not about the authoritarian system
Trinity's also most definitely not about how do we bring it in to grab it right
It's easy to
Forget that the Rockefeller Rockefeller Foundation is a charity
Yeah not a evil organization
They shouldn't say it so many times it must be true
So the goal like like a touchdown there is discussing how technological progress would likely develop in these four.
Scenarios
And wanted on and all of the right-wing dum-dums of glommed onto is the one that happens to be about
How technology would possibly progressed in a world where we have a low level of adaptability
Any strong Alliance
Mint between politics and the economy the one that their act
If we trying to bring
The world the author's Invision Envision with those two qualities would be one with a more authoritarian bent
To a setup where they
Creative flourish
Of how they decided to
To give that scenario a backstory
These scenarios are meant to be stopped
Provoking and meant to prompt
The conversation
And as such there written hyper dramatically
Each one is giving a
Given a needlessly intense backstory about how the circumstances of the world
It depicts
Came into being
For instance we hack attack scenario starts like this
Devastating shocks like September
The Southeast Asian tsunami of 2000
For in the 2010 Haiti earthquake
It certainly Prime the world for sudden disaster
But no one was prepared for a world in which large scale
Catastrophes
Whitaker would suck
Breakup breathtaking
Frequency
The years 2010 to 2020 word of the Doom decade
For good reason
The 2012 Olympic bombing which killed 30
2000 was followed closely by an earthquake in
Indonesia killing
A tsunami that almost wiped out Nicaragua
And the onset of the West
China famine
Which caused a once in a Lenny and drought
Climate change
The goal of this scenario is to create a world that is
Full of Chaos
Where the power of government is weekend
And adaptability is low
This is the story they decided to use to launch into that
And it's built on some real thing
Like the disasters that happened
Prior to the report writing
Anime augmented with
Fictitious real-world events
Like the Olympics
Bombing the didn't happen in 2012
I was going to say I didn't remember
For that 10
The things that they're used as pieces the world they're building
Wingfield sort of real though
Because they're plausible
There was a bomb at the Olympics in 1996
Indonesia had a gigantic
9 + earthquake in 2004 left over 200,000 people dead
Nicaragua was the site of a notable tsunami in 1992
China does have a history of severe drought
All of these things are not real to the people who write in the report
But they're things
Could happen in the real world
Any of those things
Could happen
But if they did it would have no bearing on the intention
Or predictive nest of the writing of the report
The same is true of the virus pandemic that's the setup for the scenario that there
Conspiracy right-wing is obsessed
It is a viral outbreak which relies on the H1 N1
Pandemic from the previous year 2009
Re-establishing it is a detail
The report says that China would be successful in squashing the outbreak in their country by
Instituting a harsh locked
This isn't the
Can the president as much as it is a reflection of what they did in 2002 and 2000
Free during the summer
They didn't have to go
Didn't have to go as far in in the outbreak
In 2002-2003
According to Lancet quote
China best exemplified this large-scale quarantine by declaring epidemic Zone
Play some people under collector
To quarantine the villages cities in Institution
The stringent control measures
Included school closures and closures of all universities in public places
As well as the cancellation of a public holiday in May
In May 2003 China lockdown Beijing
Enclosed more than
3500 public places in an effort to
The curb Community spread
The reporters using things
That have happened in the
The past to give life to the scenarios they're creating
In order to discuss
The issues of technological innovation
And how it relates to the central question of the report
Which is literally quote
How might technology affect barriers to building resilience
An equitable growth in
In the developing world over the next 50
20 years
Clear
Where you Don Salazar is writing about this report makes
We think that he has read
Which means that he's intentionally lying about it
What are the excerpt
He uses
Spin the article really makes me feel
Confident that he's
BB's Reddit
In the article
He says quote
Governments have a
Quoting from the report
From the report not from his article quoting
From the varying degrees of success in policing internet traffic
But those efforts
Nevertheless fracture the World Wide Web
The scenario envision
Here's the full quote
From the report
Quote driven by protection
ISM in National Security
Concerned
Created their own independent regionally
Defined it Network
Mimicking China's firewall
Governments are varying degrees
Discuss in policing internet traffic but those efforts nevertheless
Fracture the World Wide Web
In the report this
Is not a good
The report is literally about hatch
How technology can be used to help the developing world
In this scenario one of the predict
To technological development is a destruction of the worldwide nature of the web
Occult countries
Creating their own isolated and
Insulated internet
Which is going to hurt
Innovation
Because they're not allowed to share it out
You got it
No one who's read this report could possibly read that description
Attack in this scenario and think
The authors of the report consider this a desirable out
Or something that they will be working towards
You legitimate
Really have to be lying
Conclusion
Which add-on is doing
And Alex's then repeat
Don't say Dan they have to release their plan and act like it's
Not there
Plan in order to make sure that you know that it's their plan which
Allows them to
To carry out the
Cuz as dark demons
They have to agree it
It's like you
You can't let a vampire in your house unless you invite them in its exact same thing with the globalist
If you can't enact a global pandemic if you don't first tell people
That you're going
I mean I think Alex probably does believe that fly
Are reaching from this
People like a dawn Salazar are clearly reading the document in order to cherry-pick these quotes
So he has to
Either
Unable to read
On a adult level
Ascertain
I don't think that's
But you'd have to be able to not
Engage with what
The point of this document is at all right
Or you have to intentionally be lying about it
Or both
But I think probably the latter I think it's all just completely
Especially when you're bossy
Is not in
Things that won't
Help him
His narrative
Easier not he's not going to be like oh read this and write me up something
And do it with whatever your conclusions are he's starting from a place of like
I need this to be an evil AI.
Can you cover this response for me
Can you do a good job on this one like where they don't
Don't go off the reservation and get to get real
Who are you
Who are you what did you do with Alex want you to go by the Buckeye
Alright if you need help call someone at the Washington Post okay never taking a journalism class before in your
Your life but this time this time again you got to step it up
Ridiculous
Bananas anyway Alex gets into talking about how Trump is real
MMS gets real weird
Why do you think they're so damn scared
Cuz he's insane
What does real
Rose's real
What
He really calls the shots
You know how past the Bob Lazar
That there's a dude in there that isn't
Out to get America
What
Russian
What happened
Russia
The globalist
That is as I was nowhere as itsy was like real life field
Do we have to give it up to the Somali pirates what has happened
It's not uncommon for Alex just a heap Praise on food
Get like it's a
Sing for me
For a while
That would still like
What
What are you doing what's going on what's the
Anyway I don't think Kohl's Trump calls the shots then he has to take responsibility.
Don't worry about it
Yeah but you can only call shots when Global start lying to you
Stop
Fair enough
I don't like being a real
Black widows are real
Rattlesnakes
So you're saying the Trump might kill us
Yes there are
I don't know I guess I would rather us like a
Slick fake politician who's good at policy and like
Means well then
A guy who 50 he's real but
50/50 chance he will kill all of us
And even with a rose you know like hey
Thorns will cut you but also it's beautiful on top there's a certain metaphor I don't crave authenticity
That badly
Okay
Guaranteed income and universal healthcare
But this guy
This guy
Bacon
Tends to like various things he doesn't really
Codon table
He said he was in the room
Radiohead showing that
Not true I was on the bandwagon with Radiohead before he was he's a faker
I mean authenticity in Friends
Bike Associates
I mean even maybe like artists
Do you like that is probably
Conversation
It's worth having
I'm not sure
It's the
It's not my top thing in a politician
When you when you say you know I don't want a full online
Well it's like the
When you're like oh man you know I got to be honest I like
This guy cuz I know where he's staying
You know
That is also a
I don't like this guy
Because I know where he
Just because I know where you stand doesn't mean that I don't want you to run as far away from me as you possibly can
Very strange
Disgusting so Alex is a philosophy
3 explained
In this next clip
That's very weird
Hollywood
Hate you
The left
The globalist want to dominate
They are psychic
Stan
Philosophy philosophy
The family I said knock it off
I am blessed
I want to listen to keep us in the fight
So it's I need your mind
I have a philosophy and it's simple
Whatever it is they're doing is bad and I want your money
Yeah
People go get it
And then he said somebody says all the f****** time because
That's not some kind of weird Vision plays close to the back
Philosophy
Alex starts freaking out about the devil
The more you do it the stronger you get in the more High
On the fight you get in a good way of love
Challenger X the power they could ever imagine but with
And then you realize he's nothing but a reflection of the creator
And then you feel the awesome presence of God and then the power doesn't matter anymore
You're on your knees
To be ready to fight
By those of us
You will be thrown against Satan and broken
God
Well you had long
The States Army
God helps me politically takeout
A million or two million of the globular
The number to
Eyeballs gouged
I'll buy a giant black spider
All I found was Victory on the other side
I don't think you made it to the other side buddy
Anime
All the temporal attacks against me
And in the name of Jesus
Dudley depart
Vanquishing this week
You have
The sword
Bring down the enemy
That pauses Nestor a better sort out of that that was like really all that interesting
And there's not a whole lot to even discuss about that but I wanted to play that to like
I hope the audience
Spheal
This episode has minutes more of that
Really weirdly
Just like
I have been thrown into the depths of evil
Thank you listen to my television last episode
You got the wrong lesson but I like
Also when he says he's been attacked in the real world and also spiritual world and all the spiritual thing
Things go away in the name of Jesus
Spiritual marriage to spiritual victory
Not going to be great victories are going to
So Alex will eventually be sucked dry by a giant spider
I think
Your cute family is probably good
His kids aren't going to school or homeschool there if they go to public school I've heard him say both in the past
Real situation is
But maybe the families around the house maybe they watch the Wild Wild West
Obsessed with a big giant spider thing
But
Spiders going to suck him dry and apparently all of his enemies
Sure they have already been sucked dry by the spider
There's a spider on the loose
Spider
Now they have no dramatic Enderman realize we shouldn't hate
Those are like little bugs in a
Spider's web that are just hot
The dad they were already sucked out
They're already gone
Spiders belly now forever
Play the spider with their mother was there to give the milk
Only ever was
Another slave
Taken away from God's light
Freewell like a child
Tricked out backyard again
3 taken away
Forever
Into the spider
Gather Souls Berlin forever good movie
Oblivion
Are we going to break, stop pontificating
Your phone calls with comeback in 2 minutes
I just so much more
Logan's Run
10 years ago Rockefeller Foundation
Stop on infowars.com so this is Sam Rockefeller report
And it really raises the question
Question of
Why are you just talking about this now
I mean if you've been talkin about the idea that the globalists you know
Did they going to attack everybody and blah blah blah
All this to bring it a marshall or whatever right
But he's not even talk about this specific document they were 10 years behind and it turns out they're not 10 years
Very obsessed with this document that's been around awhile
I think maybe
I found about it by reading Jim Fetters blog
Anyway it it's just like
This is sloppy ant-like
Even if
He been talking about this forever even even talked about this specific reference the source
Forever
It doesn't
Approve what do you saying it does
Sad
This is the most research
Show
The f****** spider
The thing that I despise about his theology
She is that he's always so up
Obsessed with physical appearance
But demons are always fizz
Physically ugly
Weather
Literally
It's just so much as like
You're going to be tempted by beautiful things
Well yeah they're the ones that are scary that theme does
Play out a lot of voltec
Cover big deal
So Alex hasn't read this
Rockefeller report uncertain
And the way he discusses some of the details like he's reading off
A little bit like it's so clear that he is unfamiliar with
Call Mocksville
Spider top-down government control
And more authoritarian leadership
Limited
Innovation and Rowing
Citizen pushback
That's a big towel to me that all Alex is done is scam dad on Salazar's article
Because if he'd read the actual report he would know that limited technological innovation and growing citizen pushback examples
Elements of the lockstep
Scenario
That they do not want
Make philanthropic work
Enveloping
World
Right
More difficult
It would be a situation where you wouldn't
Be able
To help
People in a way that is your mission
Help people in his estimate destroy the world
It makes a certain sense for him to believe that lockstep is their plan because they want
All of that
It's stupid
Actually helps Alex to have not read it because then he doesn't have to answer that question
Can you be very difficult that would be a hard one imagine how Alex would as a joke
But I've difficult time would be apart of it
So Alex gets back from break
Abl complain
Some calls I'm not entirely sure if this was in a
Call but I
Complaints about what's going on
No doubt the globalist banks
The globalist banks
Rationalizing
So Alex is mad about global as Banks trying to nationalize companies in the midst of a crisis I have some bad news about what is Buddy
Trump said the Associated Press reported on March 19th about
Trump press conference where is discussing the bailouts for Industries like hotels and Airlines
Asked if his
If you supported the federal government moving to take in
An equity stake in some companies
Trump said quote I do I really do
Also in that article that discuss how it tourney General Bill Barr had commented that the US should
Consider taking a controlling stake in Nokia or Ericsson
To be able to compete with China's Huawei
I'm not really sure I necessarily opposed so nationalization of Industries but Alex definitely should be against
Yeah you think he was
Furious went by the Obama government took a stake in General Motors after bailing out the Auto industry
So I've no idea why you
Just as upset about Trump indicating that he wants to do the same thing
Except I do
Is because Alex is a principal list hack
His hero does all the thing
Things he says the villains
Do in order to continue
Pretending is racist ass idiot hero is a gyro
You just pretend someone else is doing it
Trump says he wants the government to take a controlling stake in Airlines Alex reported as Global everything
Very simple it's not hard
You just
It's like you goddamn dumb on all the stuff that he hates
About Trump is doing and then just
Crosses out Trump
Alright what are we going to do we going to Madlibs in here this time
Let me go with fauci did it
Get a call from Australia
And this dude is
Maybe my hero and not because
I'll agree with what he saying
But this guy knows how to use
Whatever window of time you have on Infowars
Using product
You're not helping out
Absolutely
Direct contact with mayo
You can contact me at
So he is in the MLS
Haha he's not promoting Alex's product I was there with you trying to drive the traffic to his yeah
Distribution
Tendril of the MLS
That's very clever
I like that how is that not what all the other MLM people have been doing
What do you mean I mean why aren't they
Calling in and being like hey promoting Alex's MLM
By virtue of funneling them to themselves
Not only does this
Got me being in the MLS
Strategy
Make a note
It's what they call in wrestling getting all your s*** in
We got to get all the moves and everything. It's going to be
Just do the most animals
You getting his shity
Listen to this this is also what you manages to get in
Find bottle of wine
Too good too good too good at least happy mad cuz he plugged and gave it again
Because of that
He gets away with plugged his friends haha
He had
Like I love it
5D at 5 Seconds
That in there to buy himself another 25 second
Basically the podcast
I know it I know it's going to be up and end game is
Incredible and now I'm going to promote something else of mine
That's that's good
So Alec
Let's get another color and this caller actually is a really interesting thing because it gets disrupted in the middle and like you
Forget that he has this guy on hold
I guarantee
Call her
Is terrified
I live in the
Nowhere Montana
The Sanders
County
Election
Administrator
Did my father is 93 years old he is a World War
Last 14 years of my life taking care of them
Tumi
Polling place election
Option
Mail
Miscanthus
Tips
Your guys
Whistleblower stop we get in lot of the times he's really johnny-on-the-spot
This is a whistle-blower
You're also a
If you listen to his story
It's an option
Mail-in ballot
Whistleblower
That's insane
I heard that is like
What's
What were you ready for you just wasn't ready for it
Male involving he wasn't ready for what
Is the story wait until there's an election day holiday
Man can you imagine how unready this guy's going to be for that
Can be real bad so Alex are you saying I don't have to work and I can vote
Go to break
So they get cut off and when he comes back from break
He is now learned
That he's been kicked off the Android
App store and it turns out that that is breaking
In the middle of the show
But because of that
He now has to pretend that that stuff earlier wasn't in response to
Him losing its appeal
You have to sort of pretend that this update his narrative mint
It's more like he now has that awareness of the obvious
Responding to it early to bring it up now
Because he's going to eat CertaPro
Pretending that they're all piling on a shirt in the middle of his show
You want to talk about Twilight Zone
Announced their monthly thing and I'm losing lawsuits cuz I followed like
Active
Battling all the appeals court before it ever even gets
If I were there kangaroos quartz injuries
Not that it's always
Lawsuit
Washington talking about Savannah
Lawyers habits
Just has a lawsuit
Nope
I'm a loser not a winner
That's the truth
So now he's able to respond to this a little bit because there's another story and I was pretty mad
And so
Egypt's two talkin about getting kicked off the Android
And I got to be honest with you Jordan
There is no better way he could have played this okay this is a work of art alright I'll buy it
Coronavirus Killeen
Quotes video I got man for
Yesterday
Chad
And under the Georgia Guidestones underworld
You're being deceived
Whatever this
Quotes
That is Coronavirus disinformation
My religious beliefs the devil's real
They actually say isn't allowed
You gotta read this man
This is great wow
That's awesome that is f******
Stupid
The best way to get into a religious freedom
Yeah that's what you got to do that's
I mean it's not true but that is the right
Man
That is so
And the article is just
As a little
Anthony's presenting
In fairness it does discuss his weird alien / devil beliefs thing
In the video in question Jones says that quote everybody dies under the new world order except maybe one-tenth of one percent that believe
Leave it there going to merge
Machines that deals with this interdimensional thing that gave them all the technology
You can't make a deal with these aliens okay that the Bible tells you about and you can get off
Planet
Alex wants to put down his concrete
It is a religious belief is that there's evil aliens that serve an interdimensional thing
The giveaway technology
Either way
The very next sentence in the article is quote
Elsewhere in the video Jones claims that natural antivirals exist 232 novel Coronavirus
The one that they're interested in buddy
Where the headline is about hubby coronavirus misinformation was what caused the band
That's really important part of the article which is why Alex
Pretend skier that it doesn't
Exist about being afraid of demon aliens is really just in that article to make fun of Alan
But again I have to say this is great play for Alex
It's completely baseless and he's just making stuff up but it's
Almost certainly believe that he's being persecuted for his deeply Christian
Believe in aliens
Give you technology
Also Alex is have never went to number one on iTunes
Briefly
So that this isn't going to work
Because I was accidentally read the rest of the article
Why did he do that doesn't read the whole thing at this point eventually
Realizes that's not
What they're saying
What is a really good initial thing and he probably should have stuck with it
Why would you do that no that was it was a mistake. Your deflection
So he eventually is like they're just mad cuz I said quinine in tonic
Good for you like okay
Much worse
It's boring as lame
My My Religion
Right to believe in aliens
Video suppressant before
The stuff that's the better one cut around all kinds of logical thinking
You get that in front of religious people and they'll be like I can't think any active no rationality
So Alex
Before he accidentally read the rest of this
Peace
Touches back on the Sandy Hook sanctions
Situation
Appeal-Democrat
Best friends
Whitney Vann
Some legal fees or something
They just recycle that story again and go Jones
Pappyland
Andalusia
You're the one
The
Popular five-star rated
Call Wars
That wasn't in the article
And then you read
Material
And it says
Because Jones
Deal with extraterrestrials
The Shadow Children take out Humanity
Somebody for that
Cuz you did
But it's still at still what he's presenting at
But he even
Has to realize it
It's too much b******* and
Which is which sucks
I want the Alex that I actually like
F*** it
I said it taken with it yet but like I said he accidentally starts reading the article and it's like
Yeah I could deal with these aliens
Let the Bible tells you about
Call the planet
Stop
And deflated
Bump bump bump
Yelling
7 C
What
Zinc
Now you're defensive
You lose sap
All the tonic
Is so boring now
Beginning really defensive about how his religion is based on alien demons and they give away technology people
Will take DMT to
To commune with the demons like
If you wanted to really go hard in that lane go in but that's
Good alternative f****** Project Camelot in no time
But
Now you're retreating back to these Waters of like
Quinine is actually good
I like Thomas it's so boring and standard and it gets into like
General
As a whole
Not interested
Though there is one
Angle that Alex takes that I think is pretty good
And that is
All these people
Out there that are trying to tell you
Chloroquine
Is not the miracle cure
Extinguisher hope
It's a really interesting angle
Say
Prescribed
Hydroxy
Because they don't want you to have help the Democrats
Okay don't want it now
It's not going to help in
There's a chance
Could approve the medication
And people here because of
Blind baseless hope Juris hope perhaps white lights
It's not Democrats Mike dewine
The Republican grow up
Secret Democrat damn sure Alex
Would say that I specifically want to do
Are my enemies so this is how Alex responses news of the Android thing anti Keats
Promising with the religious freedom angle
How many Justice
Layton's boring
You can feel him deflate to me a little bit
He went
And it's so clear that like you hadn't read it before he did on air
God just do better he's not confident reader
Certainly not
Nor do I have confidence in his reading
So he Rambles
The bed about this sort of around the same themes like
Fake stories about my my sanctions ranked
I like quinine
I don't sell it
Who cares
Bow is a long ramble
There was a guy on hold holy s*** I did forget
I'm going to keep this in my mind
There's a guy on hold
Literally
I hate you
So Dave
Still on hold
And I will get back to you
WWII vet father he gets this thing and something
Yeah
This is an envelope
Dated
We got him
What
Middle of
Nowhere Man
Fontana
Okay
Is he mad that the Postal Service works
No
He just think
That there is a
Spirits
Short about offering mail-in ballot
Options to people
That is how they're going to steal the 2020 election
Gotcha it's inevitable
But here he talks about that a little bit more and then I'll explain why this is dumb
I get to open his mail
They didn't send one to me by the way
Is that cuz he
Basically it's
Mail-in ballot
I'm scared of
Corona
Yeah
But there's a huge
Demand for that
So they can get it passed
Mail-in voting
Shein
So you are no fun fact
In 2008 when Obama won the presidency 2.4 million absentee ballots
Forecast
In 2016 when Trump won
8.2 million
Forecast
The number word
In those years and yet somehow the votes weren't all secretly stolen by damn
As Alex seem to think mail-in ballots are set up to
These f****** idiots are talking like
Today was the first day they heard about ads
How many fix
Troops Wagner overseas
97% of troops overseas
Please vote for
I don't know about that a long time and work totally fine with that
Any kind of fraud
Suggested
We use mail-in voting to help keep the election on Pace is a very good idea that would
Every indication
From States like Oregon Washington and Colorado bear this out
This caller lives in Montana
And guess what
In the 2016 election
64.6% of all vote
Forecast by absentee mail-in or early voting
Trump won Montana was just over 50
6% of the vote
The conspiracy here is
Incredibly stupid
But it's important to remember that it doesn't matter if it's
Conspiracy
There's needed to feel good in order for it to
The goal here is to invalidate the result of
The 2020 election
In case Trump loser
There's a very good chance they will see
Increasing right in absentee ballots which is a good angle to build a narrative on
Feels like mail-in ballots
Would be easier to steal and fake
Because neither this collar nor Alex
Know anything about the absentee voting
Because it feels that way they
I can convey that feeling
People who are into this kind of prophet
Ganda aren't looking into things so they won't ever ask themselves
These feelings are based on any kind of reality
Epic riddle of Dowling
Grow
This is legitimately just a wholesale repeat of the ten million undocumented documented immigrants voted in
I was just about to bring that up that's why I didn't win the popular vote
Siri won the electoral college but he also would have won the popular vote
Probably by the largest margin in history if it weren't for those undocumented immigrants voting
There always needs to be an angle
And these are two narratives are
If Trump loses you now have an excuse why you actually want and you don't have to feel bad
If Trump wins you get to pretend that not only he want he overcame a billion write-in votes or whatever there's no downside
Side playing a strategy like this except
Anyone who knows anything
Easily recognize what you're doing
But it doesn't matter
Because
It'll work with your audience
Them guys
It's amazing they are both
Like
No matter what is going on including if they are the ones
And actively carrying out voter suppression
To steal an election
That is
Them
Like
We're stealing the people who are working at polling stations who deposits
Concerns here are
Pretty legit
Yeah no I when I I went to vote
And there were hundreds of people
Crammed into a small
Are we still hanging out it's it's unclear what sort of consequences could come or could have come from
They're already done
So Alex now gets down to talking to the other gas to run the gun shop and Austin or in Texas somewhere
He's not happy
About the
Guns not being considered essential businesses
During the shutdown
Many years ago and he hasn't
Great gun shop and training center here in Austin
Dot-com
Liquor Stores stay open
Everybody else basically submitted
And
He's got a letter
Attorney General
So the way Alex wants this narrative to sounds that they're targeting gun shops
Close them down but that's not true
You can do this with any type of store if you wanted to you could like
You to play games
If you're like a big car guy you can
You complain the dealerships are closed
You're a gambler
Play abacus
Beano's
And no matter what you
You choose to complain about you can always say what about liquor stores they're keeping the liquor stores in pot shops open
Marijuana shops are being kept open
Because for a lot of people that's straight-up medicine
You can pretend all you want that
It's just kids going to get high but what a main reasons
It's become legal in a number of states is there people with compelling medical reason
I have weed
Close and pop shops be bad for these people
And the way pot shop or setup lends himself
Easily incorporating social
It's required to operate safely
They're allowing pharmacies to remain open Dan.
That's disgusting what is a better prescription than a gun
As for liquor stores
If you close all the shops that were considered liquor stores you would seriously cut off of
A lot of people's access to their food
Fermentation
Not everyone lives
The place is worth
Convenient to go to a full-on grocery store
And taking public
Transit is not encouraged in these circumstances
You have a situation where it's even less
Accessible
Why do people in the country rely on corner stores and liquor stores that they also sell food items
Satisfy their shopping
The clothing that would be a
A f****** disaster
Are very much
Necessary so
Give me some really work
African
No one's forcing States or even cities to DM
Gun shops
Essential or on essential businesses
That's a decision that's left of these specific areas
Question
Even the notoriously left-wing California governor Gavin Newsom said that the decision about keeping gun shops open with
Local sheriff's
Feats of discretion
Now they want to deal with
Expensive Texas gun stores are being targeted than the only person
Complain about his old friend Governor Abbott
It doesn't matter though since I'm the same Davis episode came out Texas Attorney General
Ken Paxton release a statement
The gunshots were considered essential
From a shutdown
Ultimately the segment is pointless
And
The f****** dude he's talking to Michael Cargill even brings up
Ken Paxton
You can't
To their complaining that gunshot unreal essential while discussing how
The Attorney General said that they are
Cool great workout
Yeah nonsense
Not but it's just artificial grieve man it's
Nonsense
Three-point last clip in italics
Complaining about getting kicked off the app
Her and I really wish you was still talking about his religious beliefs in Aliens
What
Father on entrance form
Come on mother and father
Helpless people that go get college degrees
Building the posthuman worlds
Sabotaging everything
Airhorn sound effect
The show but
Yeah man I mean that's really just
Purest version of Alex
Weird
Secondary narrative about being
Kicked off the app that he's not even eat nothing but you're not into it I would much rather complain about the
The demons an alien spider
That seems to have fallen off his radar after the middle of the show
Butter at all just isn't service
Selling a ship
I have a I have
Like I can't imagine
Being
Able to read
Is a wired article with a
A quote that I gave that fly
Their intervention interdimensional demon
Alien demon I apologize servant interdimensional thing
Horse
Quote interdimensional thinking out loud
That's the thing I said I nailed it and you know what that's my religion
A new read that allowed in
Research
Betty White
Nothing he's jealous
So I guess I'm kind of satisfied in some ways
Because
This episode was not as coronavirus heavy which I can appreciate
And we got
Experience
Like what a really said
Floating exist
Just Treading Water kind of guy have you responds to these really negative things in their life
I do I think it's almost at the point where he's not even angry about these things
He's probably pretty angry but also looks so burnt out on being angry at them they just like f******
I was lackadaisical responses chili the well runs
Yeah I just got
And also we got to here
The sweet sounds of a saxophone which is
And I got to find a primary source that Alex is misusing which is always a very special day
It is
I hope you all are doing all right out there
We will be back on Wednesday like we said we're doing
Monday Wednesday Friday episodes
For the foreseeable future during the
This time thank you to everybody
You're in there perhaps
Thank you to everybody who sent the nice messages about
How much they appreciate it
Until then we website
That's right we also are on
We are on Twitter at that knowledge underscore fight not go to bed Jordan wallpaper
The download iTunes leave a review at that building donate yay
K I'm Neo I'm Leo I'm dzx Clark I'm a big old
Alexandra first in color with your Japan I love your work