I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
College vype.com
Acknowledge
Novelties as we do before we might as well
Update it for our specific
Indeed we are
Hi
What up
Okay
Well interesting you should bring that up
Let It Go and I try not to go on it
Too much because it seems
Mabel gazy is Shindaiwa a little uncomfortable but I think it's really cool and I want to give a shout out to it
Created a Reddit subreddit about the show.com
Okay conversation
Too much
I can only imagine that they frequent Source conversation
People coming up and talking about the very thing to come up in the show
That is really cool I also I don't think it was from this but someone did send me a message
We also ask actually
Predicted the
Coronavirus
Of course we did that might be something that has come up on the board I'm not sure but
Episode that we did where dude
Who's mad at Kerry Cassidy interviews of time traveler he talks about how
That wasn't Martin Luther King's granddaughter or great-granddaughter is going to be president but you wouldn't be the right age
We discussed how the political realignment would need to happen for that to happen and one
One of the things was a massive outbreak of a disease B mostly kills older people
I've got multiple messages
Do people who are like you guys predicted this and also the time travelers are right
Rosary
So
Vide0 these Time Travelers in the policy
Of course we would accidentally Alex
Try so hard to predict everything he's always wrong and naturally he was joking of course
About what the surrounding context of this like nineteen-year-old becoming president would be
I bet she's going to be great at the job
They had stuff
But we'll see
Hey what's your bright spot and I don't mean this to be to blanket but
Batteries dead
Love documentaries
I might be two blankets
Everyone
Did you didn't
No I don't have a password
Tyrese they looked
Into that story a while back like when it was making the round unblocked
Send stuff remember a lot of the details of it already know but
Mighty about by get around to it
You're not going to worry about the national
No not really like really
Really specific
Really specific documentary
One of them is a fastball
Which is just a documentary about tires.
Not the band
No
Who sang stairway
Where are they going without ever knowing
The Beltway
God that song with every way
I don't know
I don't know I have heard that song long time I don't remember hating it
Make a dam I love that
Specific books
The book just about salt
This one that history
Of course were fascinated with micro history
I know there's one that was just released on YouTube made by this guy up just about how
One guy
Had all of the record high score fast
This times for Mike Tyson Punch-Out
And it's a story about any the entire community of
Tyson Punch-Out fans yeah that's like real nice going going
Hard and like we're going to find a way to beat this guy scores
At the end of this documentary I'm like
I need Sports back in my life I want baseball
Tell recently you were talking about getting really excited watching people like place
Mario I need Sports clearly
For my amusement
One day soon Jordan thank you to everybody involved over there at the
Documentary
Episode going to talk about some
Jones related
Before we get to that good thank you so folks who signed up and recording the show
The first Mike W thank you so much you're now policy walk
Next
What's your nail polish
Text Anthony
San Bruno
Thank you Alicia
Thank you Claudia The Nomad
Much so first of all you are now a technocrat
Next Sarah a
Dinosaur Sheriff
Thank you so much you are now attacking
Congrat
Business heroin
Why you pimp so good
Freakishly large
Take as much Sarah and
Dinosaur Sheriff the highest Lord and Country
Channel
The lord giveth and taketh away and I respect that
I like this.
You could find a nice local charity or something like that
Would appreciate that
Inspira
So Jordan today
Got an interesting thing to talk about
We're going to talk a little bit about Bill Cooper
We've talked a little bit about Bill Cooper on the show in the past
And how he's clearly one of Alex's Gyros
Awesome. Where Alex is just getting started in Media
I'm very strong drive through a lot more coverage about Bill since I find him fast
But one of the problems they've run into is that bill show is often
Really f****** dry
A lot of it is inbreeding a long drawn-out passages from his own book
Or a letter from one of his listeners is a member of his dumb intelligence-gathering operation
Apache
You combine that dryness with how come
Completely out of line Alex's show has been in the past few months
You have a recipe for me not having the kind of time I need to create the kind of Bill Cooper content
I think our audience desserts
Rest assured that those episodes will come hopefully soon
You're my exploration of bill there's a whole lot of exactly what you would
There's a whole lot of old
School conspiracy theory
Is a lot of pretty extreme right-wing militia sensibilities
There's an overwhelming sense of distrust of
Most of the other people in the militia media landscape
What'd you expect
I've noticed that one of the things that I resonate most with in terms of doing the show is not the expected but the paqui
The ways in which Alex is similar to Bill Cooper are largely uninteresting
They both love guns they hate taxes they have shockingly low standards of evidence for absurd things they want to believe
And report is true
What interests me far more is a ways in which Alex is a worse version
Of the person he's emulator
Our last episode about Bill we experience how much
More competent
Bill is it presenting information
He actually played the roles
Someone trying to prove something as opposed to Alex or just yells about nonsense and it's insist it's been proven already
Go look it up
But without saying
Further we saw how much better bill was it broadcast
Very clearly plan to show that advanced Incorporated music
Come to the show to reinforce theme
Today we're going to look at another dip
That I found
Between Alex and Bill
This difference is a strategic difference
It's one that makes me think that bill is pretty sincere about his relief beliefs regardless of how dumb they are and
It is ideas are
The difference begins in a similarity
Starting out their careers both Bill Cooper and Alex Jones
Had to know
The odds were not in their favor
They both interviews and politics that are not really welcome
And mainstream conversation
So the odds of them getting a widely syndicated radio show like Rush Limbaugh or getting a TV show on an actual Network
Incredibly Slim
We seen the Alex responded to this difficulty by trying to create his own Empire
He got a little bit of a foothold
He started in going to the local acts of TV show and then you got a radio show cuz his dad agreed to pay for
Advertising and then from there
From there he found a crazy dude in inside Anderson who had a gold sales
Operation that needed a pitchman Alex
Rose through the ranks through that
Publicity stunt after publicity stunt along the way
He managed
To create a cottage industry for himself
No point
Would you ever get
The science that he's not what's important
Right Alex use
Infowars Alex
Use
The head of the Liberty moved
Alex Hughes
The man who
Mainstream did 9/11 truth Alex caused brexit
Alex is like it's all about him he's a megalomaniac
And all the things all the
The trappings everything around it is in service of building up this
Greater
Sing Infowars
Monetized
Delusions of grandeur
True
The strategy is
Born out of that megalomania
And
Strategy is specifically
Create your
He knows that he has no place in mainstream World he's never going to have a column in the New York to
He's never going to be on Salem broadcast
Syndicated all these other
Sort of Mainline conservative talkers
He's never going
To be on Fox News
He's never going to have a job in a place
Of
Cultural legitimacy
I have to create my own thing
I believe
The Bill Cooper is really interesting
Because
He saw a broader picture than I
He had to create his own thing
In the same way that Alex
So he wrote
Behold a Pale Horse
And it became an underground class
He started his own radio show that ended up becoming the shortwave
Hour of the time
And by October 1993
He was at a point
Where he realized
There are other ways
To do this
I'm never going to get my own show somewhere else
Maybe
I have a limitation in terms of how big I can make
Without turning into what Alex's assuming that's what he thought I don't know entirely
But
On October 5th
Teeth 1993
Bill Cooper launched
Initiative
On his show
But I think is one of the most interesting things
That a conservative
Right-wing militia weirdo would ever think to do
Tonight
Taco Bell
Media
But you
And I
Listeners and
Cohere
Who produced the OurTime
Are going to
Purchase
Here we are
Going
To do that
The Bill Cooper has his realize
Correctly that he has no place in mainstream s***
He's built his thing
It is audio
It's up to a certain point
Best strategy
By the media
That's the trick
You if you're the boss
You are on your own show
Alex is proof of Alex would never think
To do this or it wouldn't be something that he would
To do
Bill Cooper is like alright look
I don't like the
The media
We can change that
All we have to do
Inspired
Which
So he's saying that he wants a large group of people to pool their money together in order to a
Achieve a goal that's not possible by himself
Well look the
Well sure there is that
But the interesting thing is it's very unclear what his plan is as he launches this initiative
But it is
Very clearly
Ambitious
Let's go
NADA just a major conglomerate
He starts out here on the 15th of 1993 in October
By talking about why
You would want to do this because the media has destroyed
So you must reclaim it
To rebuild
It is absolutely
Necessary
For us too
Take back the sky
The media has been
Destruction
Then it also appears
YouTube
Control
The only way to do that
Capitalistic
Republic
The media
The wrong
Exactly
Working gear
That was wrong
God we find a theme attic song but used
Open the show
In this case it's winners track from the Bill and Ted soundtrack
Battlestations
Lyrics from that song
Take a note prisoners open fire Battle Stations
Someone's trying to brainwash me Battlestations
It's the season to resist pre-programmed morons computer sleeves
It's not nearly as fun of a song is make it big but it's definitely unintentional choice of the bill is make
Like this is f****** someone's trying to brainwash me battleship
Yougov course
It's great he's he's doing what he does bills interesting
Seems like a real lyrics
You know like it doesn't physically have a genre of music
Deep cut from The Beach Boys and that Winger
I think he might actually like like Dead Prez
Turn off the radio turn off that b******* will never know
I want that no one asked him back then but
So Bill gets back to talk about it in this episode here on October 15th
Bill doesn't know which company he wants to buy him and his audience
To buy a
Giant Cup starts by talking about Paramount
Arrt
Kxta
Dallas
Txga
Eatv
Washington
Wlfl
Riley Durham
A Carolina
WT
Philadelphia
Madison Square Garden
New York knickerbockers
Basketball Club
The New York Rangers hockey
Motorsports
5%
And Publishing mail
Allyn & bacon
Incorporating
Linden press
Pocketbook
Poseidon trailer
Princess call
Silver Burdett
Simon
Is
Purchasing
Really have to confer
Dollars
Today
Paramount
Communications Incorporated
Close
New York stock
$7
4share
They have 108
Cher's outfit
To be effective
Call the policy
Every output
Incorporate
Mom of 10
I'll be out soon
Stock
So Paramount Pictures
Frasier
In
The realm
Hope our
Doing I think there might be some faulty assumptions are
So I don't know I didn't I didn't go back and check like stock prices or anything becomes consumed those numbers are accurate
Sure I could still don't think if you have 10% of the shares have controlling interest in a company like Paramount
10% of the business of Paramount you now control the Knicks
Absurd
The purchased 10% of the shares in Paramount using his figures you would need to scare up
847 million dollars
An 1919 $93
So if everybody gives a dollar it only takes 108 847 million people to come together and
That's over 1.5 billion in today's money
How do you fix this is something that's an option within the realm of possibility
He's still not clear what
You suggested like is it everyone sending money and that I can buy 10% of the shares
It's unclear is one option
But there's one company that is not an option
Mario Kart
Incorporated
And I suppose.
Today
Chairs
Outstanding
According to
2 hour
Report
Back burner
But it is
Viacom
Viacom not on Bill Cooper's right hotter
Dubai
Tooth ball
Mancino that's where he was wrong what you got to do to buy them down on the ground floor you know whenever Viacom
Tom only has 120 million
Now look where we are Viacom owns everything on his part
But I will give
Bill credit
To an extent
Amatis he does know his limitations
General Electric
Corporation
That's too big
$6
At the close
Today they have 800
54 million shares
Is out of RV
Yes yes yeah can I buy General Electric
A rare instance where hubris isn't complete
His limitations are like
50 share with 120 million
90 + share with 800 million that's too hot it's not about 7 ish are at 118 building
That's why I think it is about the money with General Electric a outstanding or whatever his
Math doesn't work out electric it wasn't it wasn't about the money
It was about two small potatoes
Bill's plan which he still hasn't really spelled out exactly yet
The problem is that once he starts putting this into action
And once
They take
Control of a media entity
What's going to happen
Is that the establishment is going to sabotage them
NBA established
Figured out what
We are about what
Are doing
There will be effort
Shania
Union may go on
Strike
Corporation
Coronavirus
International corporation
2 hour
Papers
If we have
But once we take control of the vomer it's their own newspapers we will dictate all the terms
What goes in those May 4th
NFL
Way of fighting back the people who
Put Supply the supplies to create newspapers will probably not give us
Unions might strike
I would say maybe they would if you're just trying to force them to print militia propaganda
I don't know this is silly
20 minutes into this episode and I'm already realizing like
This is nonsense
One I would say
A worrying about the establishment reaction
Is putting the cart before the before the horse
Yeah I'm going to go with that one we need to focus on the early planning stages
That's what I'm saying to you right now
Spurs playing
Especially since at this point in the episode he hasn't really made clear what the plan and I think he's declared himself
King of
Sitting here on this episode like really looking over these gigantic companies
It seems like a guy talking about like we could own all this kid
Looking at a catalog order any
Treating American companies like Skywalker feels like that doesn't seem to recognize that just because this
This is the parent company it doesn't mean that all of the decisions of the
Constituent companies are dictated by the board of the parent company
They're still like they're more interested in just only thing they would run
Or let's say like X company is owned by y company company is incredibly /
Profitable and doing well why company is not going to change what x company does and risk it be coming out
Profitable dish of propaganda
It's a problem with the New York Times has always been not enough militia propaganda
Wall-to-wall
I do appreciate it
The blind idealism
It's aspirational these times we find ourselves in here in 2020 of Dan has 120
The thing where that kind of thing could be very refreshing and I appreciate a little bit
Give that guy in San Francisco who just declared himself king of America
Words just like
Man you took such a big swing that people are around you just going like
You're crazy but you know what
I'm all for you I know a guy that Columbia Missouri who is
Drunk guy on the street
I think it was kind of an a****** but
Anyway it is next Club Bill suggest another company that they might buy
And I think this is where he starts to get into the nuts and bolts of how this would work
And this is
Job
PDS Incorporated
Close today
York Stock Exchange
32 dollars and five
Dollar Tree
Prepare
Millionaire
That is all
Outstanding
Million 3
American
To buy one
70 to dollars
Heartache
We would
Incorporated
With the rest of America
I found out what
We were doing I can guarantee
This is outrageous
Yep So the plan is everybody in the audience go ahead and buy one share and then we will
Collectively
Prohibitive
Page
In terms of
Making decisions
It all 1.3 million Americans have an equal share together
And their opinions are all equally valid but you would assume they would all act as one
Conspiracy theorists agree about everything
Conspiracies are crazy because it's act it's pretending like 10,000 people like the globalists are so many people and it's so
So implausible
The number of people would act as one without anybody sharing the details down he's like
Okay let's ramp it up to 1.3%
What an incredible
That is great so there's that and then there's the assumption that once people figure out what we're doing
The other stockholders I'll get on board as I was thinking the complete opposite of
Why would they
Also just said that like there are laws
Companies do does
You know what I mean
Understand things like this can happen
Like this coming in and buying up a bunch of stock hostile takeover
They can offer more stock
They cannot have stock BuyBacks
Their processes that
Do the defensive mechanism
The business is going to have to avoid
Corporate piracy
Can you imagine
The headlines
Batman if he did
Right-wing militia
1.3 million people together and motive business immediately
All the audience spent all their money on stockx
Holy s*** it's
Just baby that's a big swing that's a big swing I love Bill Cooper so much
Dennis surprises like use these things
He is not an idiot but this is dumb
This is f****** dumb
It's the kind of thing that I used to think when I was
When I was a kid and I am legitimately thought I can
Viscerally thinking
I'm going to make a business out of this
Is going to make me thousands of dollars
Iodine
Printed out sheet of paper with prices for like sizes of lawn trimming Hedges and stuff
Like Ike
I have the ability of the labor people haven't need
Why wouldn't they pay me to do mow their yards
I was like looking at people's Lawns and I was like alright
20 Lawns on this block
Couple hundred bucks
Every week do they need lawn mowed every week absolutely
Plan made total sense because there was a f******
This is how it feels to me this idea that I had
A million people sign my petition
If those million people all buy $250 worth of stock
I'd somehow all coordinated CVS it reminds me
More of when I had the idea to talk to a few of my friends and I was like okay
None of us can afford
A Nintendo
On around but if we pool our money together we can share it
And that's between like five people in the more I thought about it the more I was like
Who gets it when
Endust Begins the troubles you know like you're going to f****** a couple will be resolved
Later
Poorly
Idem
Whatever the case both of those examples we have our when we were kids
Because this is not adult fidget
A party in the sky thought
Is fun and it's filled with her
And as we all know the governors are trying to get rid of
It's also providing us with this later so I appreciate that
So CBS is in the running General Electric is out viacom's out not enough not enough
Paramount is in play possible
And also you brought this up earlier Turner Broadcasting is what play
Our
Gender is
Dorchester
System
Practice for all of us
Wellwood
25 + 7
Dollars per share
Insurance
Don't let the hundred
25 + 7
Pretty flowers
4share
There's no one
Who could not
Report to buy
Disagree
Do it today
We do it
You're going to
He doesn't even bring up the Ted Turner's crazy
I know I was I was one of you when he said TBS Turner Broadcasting is like
Ted might be crazy enough to be sold on this idea politically the other direction
Bring up that they own the WCW
Which is great but 93 is before like the Newton
New World Order
Thinking 93 Hogan was in WWF
Yeah I bet bill was a old school Hulk Hogan guy
Woohoo is it going to root for a foreigner
I would think Sergeant Slaughter but then he turned his back on America during the Iraq War
Who's the who's the most who's the character probably
So Turner Broadcasting in play also another entity that you may not have heard of before but is a big
Anthony
USA Today Gannett
Is also in play
Garrett Tokyo
Incorporate
Janet is the largest newspaper group
The United States
Headquartered in
In Arlington Virginia
Jennifer owns and operates
One daily and more than 50
Inundated
Newspapers
Robert Davi
Companies USA
Today is
Second only
The Wall Street
So weird
Possibly too big
You know what's crazy now that I'm thinking about it
Beaches
Shockingly similar to Sinclair media
What do you mean I mean the way that Sinclair media has bought up all of these local news stations it slowly
Gradually over time and now from the top is directing them
Two opposite
Is bill was like alright
For $85 I can get this station in the middle of nowhere and then kept doing that
That would be like Sinclair
Buck
I guess that bills not an idiot this is. This is very.
So we got Gannett is in the in the running
Turner Broadcasting needs that held him out
Well you have intelligence
It's like I'm looking
This sounds like he has a clear-eyed plan
All of the information he's just reading off something that one of his listener sentence like I
Edgy did all the all the
Figuring out what these conglomerates own and all that so he's recording off the
Okay I got
So we got another entity that's in the running we got another plan haha
Time Warner
Incorporated
Butterfly
Even better better
Love it
3/8 hours
For sale
You say that again
Dollars per
Well I was entertained
How many shells are outstanding
Insert Time Warner
Inside
Well within our reach has never been stretched to the breaking
Keypoint Moore
F*** is wrong with you I'm with you
Thing that gets me is the well within
Like within our reach is
Suggest you like
You know what we can do this but it's going to be a struggle
Well within our reach is like guys we could do this tomorrow if we want to do no big deal like I'm not trying to be a dick
And say like no one listens to bill cuz he's very popular at this point he's a hero for his book and like
He is
Baby
It's too strong to say the king of shortwave
But he's a pretty busy yes pretty big name
Conspiracy right-wing
Militia shortwave radio
He does not have an unsubstantial audio
Bye
He's what he's
Way too big for his britches
Like this is a situation where like
Time Warner buying it is 10% of the companies within our reach
Is just like you are
You think
Way higher than you are you you are out-of-pocket
This is the first time that it's like I'm really like
There's Alex
That like idea of like
Oh I'm not I look I have a grill on L have a big audience but know my audience is
Billions
The people
I think that's one of the reasons why I wanted to do this episode is because as you go along you see a little
Lil bit more of our
In this
And it's not
It's it's interesting Lee not on a Content level
It's
Very much on a on a megalomaniac level
Differently and I think one of them was really interesting about this is
Bills
Basic idea
He's smart
Yes
Did is it like okay
I might have a limitation in this Empire that I can build myself right but
The problem that I see is that the media doesn't report things
In a way that I view is accurate how can I change the media
That
Is good think absolutely
When he decides to go about it
Alex young dumb
But the thought is it is a smart thought
I mean how would you if you diagnose the problem as the media is lying all the time
Why wouldn't you want to do something to change it right my misguided but whatever
Is that
As far as I understand his principles
The idea of 1.3 million people coming together and pooling their money collectively is anathema to them
That's a union
There is a problem there and I would
Caution you to ignore that
You'll get bogged down too easily also considered like okay so just use the Paramount example
That was a 847 million dollars
That would be needed to buy 10 right right
Like any big Union
If you're able
2 mode immobilized that level of money
You shouldn't
Do it that way
Because
Like
Listen clear examples perfect
These entities are already too big
You're not going to get the bang for your buck that you want there yet if you can mobilize
847 billion dollars
You could do devastating
Things you use that money wiser
Trickle-up as
Bottom-up movements always do
We were we were I think he might have had a better
Strategy possibly if it wasn't 1993
Do you know what you have
You do have to consider the state of
Technology at that point
Prior to social media
So there is
There is a certain amount of like
What could be done
To disseminate information cheaply
Different
But still write still a bad plan
I thought though
Good know he does it is something where it's like
If you are
Meditating on your problem
The media
Then this is something this is an idea
That appear in a writers room
Somebody floats
Yeah somebody float this more like and then you guys start talking to you like
Weekend
Obviously
You're next
The problem though
You still stay with the proper
The problem is that the writers room is catch it
Probably there all till 10 so I don't think
That if you buy 10%
Accompany you now
Control it I don't think that's true
From everything I can tell and I remember my economics classes generally to have a controlling interest in a business you fifty one percent
Sevenstock
Typical that's where you're stupid and there's different
Kind of stock to
But anyway
Bill thinks
That if you have 10% of time War
This listen to this s***
He's
Absurd I want to hear it
Turner broadcast
In other words if we
Purchase time
Corporated
Wii with on
Turner broadcast
So
So why even talk about buying Turner
If Time Warner owned 19% of Turner Broadcasting if you buy 10
A set of Time Warner use that have double what you need to control Turner
So in that case
Isn't Time Warner the parent company of
And then if anybody
What if you have a company worth more
One guy on 10% one guy owns 11% one guy owns another 10%
They're all controlling interview
What is going on
It's funny that he's accident like
Incorrectly correctly diagnosing a big problem
Which is that all of these media conglomerates
Own parts of other media can do is
Double-check a lot of this but if bills accurate then it is a problem
He's he's even pointing to it there's so much as stuff where
Bill always seems like
He points at the problem
And then his solution
Exacerbates the problem
Unlike most of the right which is like I don't look at that problem just don't even don't even worry about it he's not real
And what I think we should do
Is gather an army of llamas
And then we will be able to defeat them on the battlefield like sense man you're like okay just make sense
We've already touched on the fact that
You know it's unwieldy to have
One point something billion people all have to agree on equal to agree on
And so in this next clip Bill explains the solution to that problem which I think is a problem
You were going to
Future All-Star
You are
You have a tissue
With your name
Why
I'm telling you to
That's why
You don't buy gold
Have somebody else
Stuart for you
All we want you to do
Eproxy
Giving
The voting
Right
If we don't do this
R v
Movie fractured and we will not
Have control
No s***
Anybody object to that
You don't want to do it you better let me
Me know now because I don't want to put my heart in
Penis work I don't want to build the organization
And follow it through
Make it work
All we can see
A bunch of idiots
Walgreens
Wilbur Who
Going to hold the vote
I want to know about it right now in the beginning
Because I don't want any part of it
I don't want this going to happen I don't want you squabbling about who's going to hold the vote cuz it's f****** me I am go
Going to control Time Warner
Hi Bill Cooper
Are you all side where your voting rights
Gigantic project charge
I guess you could pretend but like whatever decision I make is in the best interest of my audience
I mean you can tell yourself that but
I want to control I want
Control and I want you to give it to me
I don't like the media and I would like all of your money to buy me a controlling stake or what I believe to be a controlling stake
The gigantic Media Company
I love that he's already resenting people
So what's up the thing that is impossible to do
It's so much like
And in here's the thing
After we on this and I've I've established my business running the entire media world for the
For about five years
And I hate those people in
Don't worry about it yet
That's a good problem to have your walk before you run bill
So Bill goes to calls at the end of the show
And system is really interesting because he just has a phone number
People can call in
And supper baby pheasant
No call screen has a guest they have to call in
But
Everyone knows the phone number so is other people call in
The gas can't get on the line
I've heard a number of episodes
He's checking in to see if a guest is there and it'll be a caller is like I told you I'm not to call in tonight
If you guys keep calling in and my guests can't get through we're not taking calls anymore
It's childlike
It is it has a childlike innocence to it
I think what it is is like a guy doing the best he can with no
Competence right in the world of like production
No one outside of like maybe a couple of like ideological associate
Were there to legore radio professionals who were making this slick
And somebody can't afford to pay anybody
And let's be honest you can't trust
That could be an FBI informant
If evil f******
Bill's world
I think his wife
Was probably a snitch
We're on our way he comes up to me there were a number of people that he targets even over the course of these couple episodes real
Listen to the eclipse
You hate this guy named Todd Valentine who's another radio guy insists he's a mason
Is proved by handshakes that catchy members did with him he knew the Masonic handshakes
It's way too complicated to get into tell good he has a weird intelligence-gathering Network
He's what he's got a Scientology group like
It's spying on everybody it's so funny
Roof guy who's like in the right-wing sphere until like Bill
Kind of thinks he's controlled opposition or something
Anyway bill goes to cause any gets this caller who I think has a pretty good piece of advice for Bell
Streaming Romeo
Hi Siri how are you
Alright
You're bad
Okay
Sometimes I need a conscience
Well I don't have to get my hopes too high on their CGI nomos America
For anyone to really
The Martian Watch
This is something they can hold in their hands
This is something they can really do
And maybe right about that problem
That's fun
Voice of
Hey Beltline buddy you're talking to people who bury their money
Well I support you I got your back
But don't get your hopes up you know your audience
Notoriously suspicious and
Yeah
I appreciate that color that is really color is like a real
Positive
Yeah
Yeah and he's not all these calls are going to end up being
Episode episode
Who hates the Jews
Not so uplifted
Doesn't surprise me
So
At this point
We on the 5th
And bill hasn't decided what company
He's going to buy
Is this episode was really just feeling it out it was supposed to decide
It wasn't supposed to be
Take whatever there was
He hasn't decided which company to buy it like that is millions and millions of dollars at his disposal and
Discuss the possibility
So on the 21st of October 1993 Bill comes back on air
I mean granted he has other shows before that
He has
He comes back and it's been decided
Okay Arcadia
He knows what he's doing he's feeling on top of the world like everything is going pretty well
We are
We're doing it
A lot of calls
Stock
Intermedia venture
Not Incorporated
Give you the clothes
Close today
Was
50 and 1/4 dollar
After 4
Today
The damn party
Today's high was 51 1/8 today's low was pissed
One quarter
Are open this morning at $51 per share
Yesterday's clothes what's 50 +
7th
So
Downhill hope so
When all of us begin
Antibiotics
And other people get in on this venture
It's going to go up
If your
Your Fork restaurant eating on there you're making a big big big mistake
Because we're going to own this company
And we're going to tell
America
Latruth
About what
Happening
Hot on this country
But in the world
So he's decided on goodnight
The owners of USA Today among other papers around the
Country this is probably a function of the time that this was created in
That you think that the singular Focus like
I want to prioritize on somebody who owns a ton of paper as opposed to newer media
Slowly gobbling up
That's that it's
Itsfunneh
Sounded like a great plan in 93
When did the decimal point get invented was that about 20
So I think it's a problem
If I check him now they're listed with not the paper though
Oh that might be tracking the days of the News-Press
I mean I was joking but also I wasn't sure if it's
Cuz it's now it's out to like the fourth decimal point to
Yeah I feel like back I don't think that doesn't seem all that foreign to me
I feel like back in the day
Fractions
Are foreign
Feel like fractions were used on stock
Ticker is good enough for Dewey it's good enough for you
So we're good we're going with Jeanette
Now the theme that bill uses on this episode
I don't have any clips of it
We're going with
I don't even I don't even eclipse of the musically plays but it's just from Disney
When You Wish Upon a
God that's so funny
He has no interest in music and
He reads music
He doesn't
Listen to me there's no lyrics
Dislike
Idealistic metaphor
So most of this is dedicated to taking calls
From people about the plan to buy Gannett
And here is one caller
Claims he's Bots
Compares
Not sure basic I detail
I'm here
Fantastic
What brokerage
Well you don't have to look it up
What Christ
Oh okay
Did you tell him you wanted to voting shares
There's nothing else lifted
Are using else really how you feel about it
I don't think I got about chairs
Oh it's just me an Old Prospector from 1949
The guy
I'm not sure.
That's a guy's bacon shut up
Only
Yeah I don't know if that's the time you can put on the board or not but here's another
Call her to give you a little bit of
The temperature
Hello
Cheyenne
Good any of you to put your Receiver right in front of your mouth
Talk a little louder
That's a little better
Turn it off
Starting to work
Leave excited and he spread the word
Also Bill might be
Dead Prez turn off the radio
So you got a guy who
Stroop
I do believe
Bots.
Another guy who's excited but hasn't bought any
So so far so good for 2
Bill
Start you know ruminating about what's going to happen
Whenever he takes over again that the cart before the horse
Yeah so
What he's going to do is he says I'm not going to
The firing
This isn't going to be a situation where I take over Gannett and then I fire everybody at all of the underlying business
Although
He turns out a lot of people would end up getting f*****
The purchase
Corporation
Fire everybody
Call the big
Calamity
What we going to do you're going to tell him what we want
If we own the corporation
The mirror
For you
They're going to have to do what we
Like their job they will
Play don't do it
We worked in
We're well within our rights
We're firing you
M4 review
To change the policy
With the page of ownership
So you got a situation where it's like
Okay
Bill your first episode
Of your broadcast
Was about that silent weapons for quiet Wars right just fake f****** document
It's easy to figure out is fake
Now let's assume that you take over Gannett and you want USA Today too
Publish that document on the front page
As true
Now let's assume some editor does little bit of leg work and fixtures
Exactly
Complete breakdown of like any kind of standards
You turn it into the Inquirer in a week now this is me USA Today isn't even
Like I'm listening to this going like is this guy Jim spanfeller did did Bill Cooper fake his death and then bye
Gizmodo is that what happened here
This is insane maybe you finally figured out New Media
So another caller calls in this dude is
I think he
Maybe more into buying shares
He has a
Well
We're going to do it
And with the help of people like you
Really need it
4 year
I'm okay
Well I think we're getting for the year
We may not have fun
This president
I'm glad you called your brother
Real greathorn and I don't normally like to
You know one person
This pregnant
Who's president
Is going to be deeper
Destroyer
Discovery
That's Bill Clinton that would be built
How did how did that go
What year are we
So
Here is Bill's Cohoes whenever he goes on vacation
The UK a little while back in the timeline
She has her that I can't remember her name
60 year old lady
Schizo
You know we might not have five
Wait.
We might not make it to 1998
When you said that I immediately thought
That he thinks that the world will end
In five years
If they don't purchase the country
The country
Right
So I'm assuming that he doesn't mean we can't hold out for five years
Monetarily but no no no we don't do this now the world
The country won't survive because I needed the truth that badly
Right right
Yeah I mean videos with the other things
That that demonstrates the one of the reasons I wanted to
Keypad clip in
Is it like this is such an intrinsic element of this kind of media
Is that that
That immediate crisis of
Every single time there's something that they don't like
It's This Will Destroy Everything
Think about it that I noticed is
Has to be a
Apocalyptic because that's the only way
That you can get people to unquestioningly unquestioningly believe something and unquestioningly
Disbeliefs
So that guy is literally like
I don't trust a thing the media says
Everything you say anybody
Possible that were buying Gannett
What one he's part of the media whether or not you like it
Yeah like that's just how it is
So at this point bill goes to another caller it is where everything breaks really bad because this guy believes that the Jews control
The media
Yeah well enough
Carvel
Go ahead
Feed bill is the kind of guy who's open to whatever
Even if you're saying something that is maybe offensives and outside of
What he wants to
But talk about
He takes
Conversation
Which on one level I can
Now the other level
There's
There's a real interesting situation happening here with the
The question of do Jews control the media I feel like that question should already be answer
Well here's the thing
Bill is pushing back against this color because it's very clear that he's coming from an anti-semitic place
But at the same time
I think
The bill is pushing back
The wrong way
Because what he's doing is essentially ceding the point
That Jews run the media
And then pushing back on
Wow
What oh what are you going to do about it
No no
No no no no
Nothing against
You
I am really angry with the Americans
People as a whole
For being
People
Another word
This is a
Capitalistic
Republic
That we live in
Why is everybody sitting around complaining because somebody else was smarter than them and
The media
You're really care by it back everything in this country for sale
Everybody was complaining and railing against the Japanese
For buying property and business is over here cool sold it to
Greedy Americans
Sure
Wow disagreeing with this guy who lives here
Falling into anti-Semitic
Archetypes and believes himself it is
It is a little bit like
I mean
It's
It's very fascinating his his idea of like well yeah why wouldn't the Jews buy up the media that's a good investment
What are you buying up the media
I guess that's
I guess it's more Progressive than
Out note anti-Semitism but it is like well obviously the Jews control
If that's the problem
But that's because we sold it to them it's your fault that the Jews control the media that's a weird
Way to have this rebuttal that's not still playing into anti-semitic trope
And that would be to respond to him like
Look you're wrong but let's entertain the possibility conception
Do you know Jews control the media
What's stopping you
You from buying it back in a couple of smokes
Exact
Like rebuttal he's making
Pfriem slightly differently
To make clear that you don't believe the truth control for me
Start with
No the fact that you bought on the premises a problem
That's weird. Weird
At the end of this conversation bill is like
Hey
You hate the Jews
Your real big anti-cellulite
But how about you help us by Gannett
You want to get on the bandwagon
Help us we're going to buy a major
Media Corporation
And make sure they print
The truth
Whatever the truth may do
30 parkour liberal
Are meteor
Corporation is NACA
Media Corporation is going to be Armenia Corporation
There are others but okay
The truth murders on radio television
Parma newspaper
If you want to get on board and do something
River
Will welcome your help
If all you want to do is
Complain about the Jews
I am running tell you something
The Jews have not done anything illegal
They have exercised their right
Under the system.
Smart
They're smart enough to stop
To buy something in
Controller
And everybody else sits back and wine you're flying that plane towards the mountains deserve to
Everybody else that wise
Christ
Deserve whatever they get
That just happened
The fruit oh God
Oh God bill
Control the media but that's cuz you're a coward
Because you're a coward or Bill stupid ass
Bell
God
It's so weird that these terrible beliefs are there
With the wherewithal to recognize legitly
Anti-semitism
It's
While
I don't understand your note for the wrong reason with him bill but it's one of the reasons
Booty fascinates
Because like
There's stupid stupid beliefs that he has like the silent weapons for quiet Wars
But at the same time whenever caller will call in and say something
Absurd he'll be like
Where'd you get that information or push back on
On people who have fun
Proven Theory to sell them things in a way that Alex doesn't
When Alex get the caller who's like
Hey don't
Pop air bubbles cuz there's Chinese are there Eva Coronavirus
He's like oh my God amazing
Bill would never do that
But Bill's
Still believe things like silent weapon
Opposed
Too big
Like you. He gives speeches sometimes about like
White racism black racism Asian racism
Anti-semitism
All of these are inappropriate they don't have any place in society
And yet
You just have him eat that here to this guys complain about the Jews under the media together juice on the way because they're smart
Boo are you mean
I think well
I suppose you're the only argument he could survive on is that
The people who own the media
Are Jewish
And because they own the media they are smart
Therefore
The Jewish people are smart I guess that's what he's trying to say one of the problems with that
Yeah
Is a compound noun
Struggle
The phone because anti-semite I don't think he's buying
But you got another guy I don't know who's
This guy is doing the Lord's work in terms of buying
Okay
Absolutely
That's the best argument
That anyone
Including bill is given so far
Is it like we might make money
Crazy chairs
What it means dick
It means nothing
Terms of control of Gannett
That's funny too because it
It's like a stubborn it's a sovereign citizen
Broker
Play the market
Naturally I've signed everything with capital letters because otherwise the government won't know it's fake
I'm not going to leave money on the table Dan
I'm not going to leave money on the table just because
I think I don't need a driver's license doesn't mean I'm not going to get rich
Well I mean like there if you know if if
Being that you see this is a good opportunity to make some money involved
Bill's not going to be able to buy this company but I'll join in your makeup bucks off it or whatever
That's
Fine. Can I make money there's no downside
Why not anyway
Spirits are high
On October 21st
I don't think it's going to go as well
Futurewise
Do you know how he gets this call with a 2400 shares he's had a couple other people who said they've bought shares
Maybe they have maybe they haven't
Spoiler alert things he does not end up buying yes
I really hoped you had a chance
Empire January 13th
Bill gets back on
And
His mood
NACA entirely different level
What is Happy sound
What you just heard
Is a warning
If we're not successful
And working for people with this program
In concert with many others who are attempting
To do the same
You will hear those sounds
Marking
Copa America
Nice
Cooper Nelson
Because
Again alright like 3 months later and plan is not gone
Well
Struck a dent in the in the GoFundMe campaign
Boxer
So what you have is the siren
Happy sounds
I know that that's not uncommon
But either this is what's going to happen
What what's going on here is this really just about the fact that you don't own can that yet
Because you don't
It turns out it's not
Quite
Partially that
But also
Bill is
Curious
I'm holding
Cambrian newspaper
The newspaper lady
In my life
Same story
On every page
Newspapers dated
December 29th
I want you to make sure that you have a pad of paper and a pen or pencil by your side because we're
Going to talk about something
Tonight I'm going to give you
Information
I'm going to ask
Legends juice
Something
Don't do it
Well
You'll find out
The front page
Brother smoking
Pistol
6 gun
Smoke coming out of the barrel
Pointed right at the reader
Headline
Guns
Our laws
To the right
Homicide records
Stopped in 22 cities
At the bottom of the page
Cover story 200 million guns
Hand-speak
Ignored why are people able to shoot
Someone in the face
And walk away
Good question
Joey buttafuco
Correct side
A few
And all for sex
Today's Hamilton
Afghan Bible
Second Amendment
Is the right to bear arms as fundamental as free speech
Ours out dated has been
Private home
The next paragraph Barber Shop murders
Dying Young
Crime Pays independency conclusion Haven
Sudden death
Last Hope today's debate
Gatling guns under control
Creek guns
Cars
Hooters as drivers in
The blackness
Begin to lift tonight
So you try to touch one gun
You breakdown
America's doors
Began confiscating weapons
The blood will run
SuperAmerica
Now or something like Alex
There we are
So we had
A newspaper has done a special issue about gun violence and Bill is
Bucking Furious
About this
Because
She loves go
What we have here is a very Alex Jones evolve
Here in January 1994
Where Bill is saying you touch one gun streets will run red with the blood of
You know whatever
Listen to this I noticed a lot of very very familiar themes with Alex
So some of this is a little bit content
At one of the things is that bill is of the mind that all this gun crime and all this crime
It's going on
It being manufactured
In order to create a problem that the
Public will demand a solution for which is more government control dialectic
Crime list
Have you heard from Crete
It's simply for the purpose
Obtaining Americans
Conflict
Resolution
Scream for more control
So
Voluntary
Just a hundred percent does he think Reagan introduced crack in the black community
Maybe I don't know
It's Foster Reagan introduced
I have no idea if bill has a position on that more episodes May shed light
So they have that same sort of
Yeah boy
I know it's sort of trivial differences but what I really think is going on is more just bill is mad
He's channeling a little bit of this
Is this anger that he has with
And
I mean like I could beat around the bush all day but the reason that he's mad is that no one's buying stock
And you talk about that here
And gets
F****** so bad
What is audience
Grandmother car race
Tonight I cannot stand
Stupidity like
Scrabble
That's what I see
I gave you all the answer on this
Program
Several months ago
The answer
A few Noble coals went out
Followed
Mark Lamb
Ellen Rucker
The newspaper that I'm quoting from iPhone with every page
Topeka bear arms is USA Today owned by Gannett company
Proposed
That is Juicy as a narrative and ironic twist that is just perfect
That is perfect
I have warned you guys that we need to purchase Gannett and then three months later we haven't
Purchase Gannett and they have done the exact opposite of what it is I would have asked so let's imagine a scenario Pearl
Emerald where you buy Gannett
Give me the three months able to completely control the editorial editorial
Great Imaginext
Man somehow here's the weirdest
Somehow I
I kind of
I would prefer
Bill's reaction to
Calling people super predators
It didn't it didn't go well
For
The early night
I wouldn't suggest
Recommend
Screenshot
So what you end up with AIDS Village Furious
Because
You see this gun
Control gun
Issue gun violence issue of USA Today
He's recognized
I tried to buy USA Today didn't work out
Listeners have to pay
It's so fascinating to me that what he's mad at me he's mad at the Articles and he's mad at USA
Today obviously
Play please really mad at his audience
Because he seems to feel like they have failed him
And being able to stop that issue from existing
It gets into that a little bit here
You followed my advice if you have done this
But that you could never have
Never happen
It's good to have an article
A large particle
Wayne the real purpose
The second article
And amendments and why it is
Nefertari
Never relinquish their rights
Bear arms
Because we
What is the articles in the paper are Acura
What if he's articles about.
So you would just like sensor
Things about the negative parts of God
In service of pushing your pro-gun agenda and have you never heard what justifies the means
Why is it not possible to have a publication
In your idealized world where you do talk about the fact there is gun violence in
Something needs to be done about it but also the Second Amendment is important
Why is it impossible never works that way even in Bill sort of like weird idealized
A version of we have control over a net
Doesn't come into like a new w
Gone absolutely
Let's say an authoritarian type of rule over the editorial
Going through that we we spent so much time talking about Alex and
It wasn't it was for awhile before I was like oh this guy's out now fascist
But if we listen to this clip right here and be like oh
So the hard right wing
Wants complete control over what people
Here
Google jit patches and
Bill Watts
He's audience to pay for it and have no saying and give it to him
This isn't this is a fascist dictator old people for not making him a fascist dictator
Plain about communism and like
These deserve like pineapples
Revolution communism
Millions of people that come together and give me their money right and I say take
Sole control think about what happened with the b*******
Civic sedan see that's the thing is they talk about these like negative historical events
Exactly he's trying to recreate it
It's not even it's a one-to-one dictator in a certain scent
Through the work of false populism
This nonsense and you tell funny
God damn mad
I would assume a large part of it is a people wanted to or would have
Supported him but didn't have the financial means to or unfamiliarity with the stock market it's something that
If you're not
A stock person it's easy
The
Border of Entry is tough already involved
First one
Trying to talk you don't know exactly who to talk to you don't know
The process of it I think it's probably a lot of his audience
And of course they're the type of people who hide their money under a match
What are you going to do give them out there to paper that says it's money
He's mad at them for not getting over that hurdle without realizing that like
Most of them can't yeah you're asking them to do something that is outside of the programming
You offer that bike
Even earlier in this episode was talking about buying gold inside don't let someone else hold your gold yet are you
Hold it yourself
How do stocks work
Imaginarium holding
Hard money of the hard right
He's asking people to
Go against what they're inclined to do right now these mad at them for not doing it
Because he wanted the power to stop this anti-gun an anti-gun put the
He perceives to be Antigone
It's it's very weird it is
It is so
Applicable because it is
Him saying
I want you my audience to abandon your principles
Order
That I
In order for me to then Institute your principal
Like it is absolutely it's literally the Bolshevik Revolution it's incredible it's big brother
Bananas
This is like if Don Quixote was pissed at horses for not helping him by a windmill
Like it's insane
That works
So surprised
So earlier
In the beginning of this back in October
He needs 10%
Of a company to have control of it
Yeah
When we begin
Gannett Company Incorporated stock was selling at $50 per share
We only need to Garner 15% of the stock to
Effectively control the corporation
Uh-oh
The girl throwing it 50
7 and 1/4 / share
Sovereign citizen broker made from Bank
At 4 p.m.
New York time
So now you need 15% it seems like these numbers are arbitrary
But the other thing to Zack if you look at this
The stock is up $7 the only thing they've done is GameStop
I'm so mad at you
The only functional thing that this has achieved is Bill is angry and Cadet stock
That is exactly how that would go that's exactly how that would go
Physicist Bill himself in the face like it's
Goldberg
All these Byzantine Roots the ball goes down and then at the end he just gets slapped
It's so funny to me that if you would talk to an economic advisor who was it with Severance it isn't hard to catch you they would have been like
Here's what's going to happen
And then 86
Exactly what would happen
You're gorgeous
Some people who are going to join up with you to end up buying a bit of stock value of
Woodstock
And that's going to price out people who otherwise would have joined to possibly
Make more money and you are going to do nothing you're just doing free work for Dano fun it's all yours
What
You have to do it now just made more money for USA Today
You funded Sagano
Now Bill I'm going to say this to you right now
And this is my pee
Get all 1.3 million people together
Before
Don't have people
Trickle into the bags.
Work buddy that would be difficult to do because then you know that
Possible to do Dan and that's why he shouldn't have tried
Number one would be impossible
Also when you have 1.3 billion people all gathered together
And they're like
Let's give control to one guy
It becomes more,
What's the reality of a we could buy
Also
While we're here
The people who are going to be in that 1.3 million
Are people who listen to Bill Cooper probably take
One and a half second before they like
FBI informant even if they trust Bill implicitly they don't
Trust
30% is that 1.3 million
0% seems low so bill is mad but he wants to start over
He wants to he wants to speak out again
Everybody sell your stock no no you had to hold it but we're going to do it
Alright okay and if you don't
Bill is going to
F******
Destroyer
I'm going to tell you about this Corporation
I'm going to tell you that if we don't do it.
Carmen if you don't get off your butts
To your churches in your organization's and everybody else who's sitting around in this country
Dream about the media
Bitching about what they did on television bitching about what's in the news
Papers
Everytime I hear you b**** I'm going to
Laugh Loudoun
Loud and clear white in your face
Because you would have proven to me answer the world into our enemies but you are not
You are not worthy
To be treated as people
Parkland High School
Bruce Arians
Affairs of running
Your country
Are you will prove that the Illuminati are correct
Use their intelligence are no better than animals who do not have in Telugu
Such people are Straits on the table and be
Of Burden by choice
That's what they think of you everyday you prove them right
That's a quote from silent weapons for quiet Wars that's not a real Illuminati thing but builds dumb
This is where Bill starts to feel a lot like Ally
This is the guy
But what it is is like a guy who feels betrayed his own psychodrama that's playing
Now he feels like his audience has let him down
Now we're going to do this again
We're going to try
Forgot to buy Gannett
If you don't buy shares
You'll get every one of your church.
Buy shares
Then you aren't human
And you don't give a f*** about America
That might be an overreaction if you don't
Worried about a woman president
I mean
This is this is narcissism
Let me run this by you
I actually think I could
Make this a workable plan
Still impossible but far more workable
Here's what we do
Okay alright
We get a sufficient number of people not to be 1.3 million but it's going to be less 100,000
Right we buy plenty of stock
Then all at once
We sell
Because of the way the algorithms run the market now that's going to artificially deflate
The price then we get a slightly larger number of people to buy more stock at a lower price that's
Making it more affordable then we do that at
Over and over again later we do the same thing goes down its Market makes
Call Wilder
All the sudden is yes I am
Describe a Bitcoin
This is really real
This is this is the point at which I like really in this Saga felt like this is so
If I were Alex and I had the same issues that Alex
I was listening to this guy I would really identify with
Totally right
He should be mad why didn't people join up with his exotic Quest
It just feels so Alex
If you ever call us and complain about anything
I'm going to ask you first
Do you own shares and going to
Incorporated
Do we have your puppy to both your stuff
If you say no we're going to hang up on you because we don't
Even want to talk to stupid fool
#neverbiden
You could save this nation
Are you a fortune
OK Google
Somebody making you
You do it and I don't care if you hate my guts I love my country
Show me the most hated man in the world if I have to
The Constitution
The Bill of Rights
That feels so much like Alex
Yep that martyrdom essay said false martyrdom welcome your hate
And I do not care for those who are not true believers
I will have this in
Incredibly artificial cross that I'm bearing
And I will make sure you make a note of it
Because otherwise you're a f****** a******
It's
Pizza it's ludicrous
That's something that I
Listen to and I recognize so much of that like
Bernie or bust thought process
That I'm seeing.
There where it's just like
If you guys do your b******* then f*** you I don't have any
But I know that the difference between that and bills version
Good words like I'm going to hang up on you until you go fuc
Because you weren't part of their true believers
The difference for me is like
I know for a fact that
The when Biden gets his ass kicked or whatever happens
Though Bernie people are going to be like
Haha I Told You So now how can we help
The stakes are also the stakes are also quite different
Imagine world
There's no outcome
Of this that
Positive
Right really
Well
There's no outcome
So a bill is just f****** mad
Most of the show is just being like
The f****** if you don't buy the stock in the company and sign over your rights to this to me
Shut up a default righteousness
Is on May 4th night
And whether you know it or not you're going to purchase
Soccer
Incorporated
The American stockholders what's that mean
And we are going
Garner control events company
And we are going to the real truth and the real news
And the newspapers and on the television sets and on the radio station
Coconut Company Incorporated
Across this country and we're going to use those billboards
For construct
Purposes
And we are going to turn this
Country around are we are going to shut our
And put the things around our ankles
So far
You all have been
Daddy's disappointed you
The Constitution with Bill of Rights you profess to want to do something you don't ever do a damn thing
If you don't like the language
You change the station
I'm angry
I'm tired of listen to your thigh and kitchen mon
I'm tired of just stop calling me
Took all your problems and save your country for you
I'm sick of it
You're going to get off your butt and you're going to help are you going to shut up and put
Change run your ankle
One of the two
Going to bring this to a head right now
Peter gets bergner help save this country
Shut up
I become a good little
Play
Bill Gates Twitter
This is the thing that's another like real emotional commonality and
God I can't even imagine like
Let's imagine some weird scenario wherein like literally everybody who supports
Donate to knowledge fight right now you are you know you're a coward At You song
Call Valic
That would be the equivalent 141 take to be like
The act like that
I don't know I can't even comprehend that
It's horrifying
Now that I really do have that corollary of that
Literally what it would be it would be us
Yelling at every listener who does not donate
Even a dollar or whatever it is
And just be like
You guys
Love Alex Jones fight against Alex
Ratatata if you don't don't if you're not human don't subscribe
Dead to me you're a cattle your Sheep, Co
That is ridiculous I can't imagine how you get there
Well I mean I think
Gradual
Cut I do
About now 10 years from now somebody's doing knowledge fight knowledge fight like and this is where they started to go downhill
Really don't think it comes on overnight but I think that by degrees you and out like sort of
Buying your own s***
To such an extent
That
What bill is talked it up in his head obviously
From the conception the germination of this idea in October 93 to the point where it now in
Weary where it's like this is the
Answer
And it's the answer because I have decided it's B
He answered up and anybody who doesn't agree with me
Is
Cattle
The well is
Do a subversive person
But that's a thing
I know you probably like the militias you agree on right-wing stuff and all that
You call in and you didn't buy it
Call fuckyourself good night with your chat yet
Yep it's it's
And you know what it's ludicrous because bills on the air until he dies in 2001
Did he know
First of all no
Also bill doesn't keep being like answering every call would like to do by Gannett stock
Yeah of course it is embarrassing
Answer lashing out then and that's another
That big
Commonality between him and Alex
They lash out
Their individual personal
Problem
Am feeling
Need to be vented out
And
The audience needs to feel those things
Or else they can't handle whatever you're going through
Like as much as Bill appears to be more of an adult in
You read long passages he's literate
Yeah it's still like
He's a baby
He comes up with these ideas like I would have by this media thing because a bunch of people signed a petition to of something I
I was going to do
And that means that I can
Raise 800 million dollars
The anything when it doesn't happen he lashes out like a like a child yeah it's
It's still the emotional intelligence of
Somebody who
Needs to grow the f****** absolutely that's that's such a that's such a good point just because that that
Veneer of literacy and
Consistency at all that's like legit service like he was in that he was in Vietnam
Bitter respect about that certainly
And all of that can
Cloud U2 the rest
You know like it's
It's like
Somebody doing a profile on Richard Spencer where you're like
Look at the new alt right or whatever and it's like see he's literate and he's got all this s***
And that
Tricks you into accepting that
This is a
Fine human being
And a lot of things and a lot of the information about what a what a whiny races baby he is behind the scene
Maybe isn't available when you're writing that piece
In the same way that like with Bill IQ of course I
You should assume
That this guy
Is the guy who would act like this
You know it
But if he doesn't for long enough you're like
Yeah cuz you're the type
Type of person who wants to believe other people
And I still think he's interesting and I still think there's a lot of worthwhile things in terms of
Discussing some of the beliefs
That he has
Yes but like don't get it
This is this is part of a real Bilko
All of it
Three months
Arc over his career like
So we have one last night but it's basically I'm saying that if you don't buy stocks
To get him control of goodnight your dad
You must make a choice at this moment
You must
Destroyer arguments Tuesday
Stand up and take whatever risk you need to
You take
Your fight on the side
Right
Mark Gaynor
Company Incorporated
Rock the first thing tomorrow morning Joe
Anybody ever call us
Communicate with us unless you have done that because we don't
Good morning
We don't need money
That was
Sad that we don't even want to hear from you
Sad
You don't even I don't even believe it now like as as delivered I don't believe that
But it's so lashing out
It's so
Yeah petulant
Absolutely
And I think that's that's part of what underlies a lot of these these folks
In therapy Indianola Catholic I have a little better handle on some of my emotional response
I'm not like some sort of paragon of maturity
I wouldn't ever pretend
You see this and I think I think that a lot of these people who dwell in these world
Have just
Incredible unexamined
And undealt with
About Shameless cause a certain amount of delay
Develop
I certainly don't have any expertise in the field or
Enough information to really figure this out but I would suspect based on
Somebody the information I can find about Bill
And Alex
That maybe that's a commonality maybe maybe folks who are drawn towards this megalomaniacal
Individualistic
Conspiracy theory
Are Shiba maybe it's a product of unresolved
Yeah I have it maybe it is a function of
Being stuck
Ena
You're alright emotional
Yeah no I didn't I
Genuinely understand
His his
Feelings on that like
That's
That like
If you're not doing this
Then you are
Also responsible for what happens to
You might as well be a
There are so many times where I am
Like looking around them like
There are people in still in cages
Why are we doing
And if you're not actively fighting if you're not doing something if you're not trying
What the f*** are you for
Why are you involved in this
And then you stop for one second and is an adult you're like
F******
It's a struggle
It's a struggle for people
People who want
To do something
Sometimes they just f***
Well that catalog for this
Is Bill realizing
Find 10% stock is not going to give me control of all of the child companies
What am I doing
It's weird
So I think these weird emotional commonalities and sort of spiritual commonalities you can find
Find it
Yeah
But at the same time this is such an intrinsic difference
That like
Again as much as we've laughed
Abell is a dumb idea
It's very ill-fated
That's what I'm saying exactly
The way that he responded to the question
Did both him and Alex had to answer the question is
Media doesn't want you what are you going to do
You want to be a voice in Media
In a certain
Genre companies
Don't want anything to do with you because
You're lying
Or your job
And also saw the ideas you have our date
They don't want to publicize your promote you
What are you going to do
Alex
It seems like most of his career
Is entirely been individualistic
And like
Just I'm going to create my Empire it will be my Empire
Build seems to want to co-op
Which is the other option I which is a better option
Sort of misguided the way he applies it yeah
As he blames more about what his actual plan is
It's really just I want my Empire to be good that
That differ
But no Alex wanted to build an Empire and Bill kind of was like What if we
Concord and Empire you guys ever consider that Jefferson consider Conquest what if I use what if I use my audiences real
Resources in order to hostile takeover Empire
Ensign collectively it'll be ours but I'm the only one who will be able to do anything
Never heard of a situation where collectively people all got together but only one guy wound up being able to make the decision they noise
Heard these guys complain a lot about Collective
Anyway
I just thought this was one of the more interesting things that I've stumbled across in terms of like listening to Bill
I think there's a lot more like
Compelling and important things to talk about in terms of like
His actual believes in his worldview but this was like really a thorn
In my in my back unit like
I got to talk about him trying to buy them
Like 4 months ago
This is amazing Bill Cooper
Literally
Thought it was a good idea to buy a media Outlet that's fantastic
This is great stuff
You mean like I forgot all kinds of it
On Friday folks
We are also on Twitter
Yep we're on Facebook we are always looking to be like $2 open iTunes or pack astrolabs or wherever there's also donate
Jordan
Mdzs Clark Ione Gannett
Alexandra Thurston color