Air Jordan swetik
I have great respect for its knowledge by I'm sick of imposing a good guy
Dot-com
About Alex Jones
Indeed we are Dan Jordan Jordan
What do you got for brakes
Shows how stupid I am
I didn't know that
Frozen hash brown patties existed and could be sold at the store and
Discovered that and they're fantastic
Really nice for breakfast item
Potatoes no I didn't realize
How many different shapes of potato they sell it before
Food section
I like that I like the way you put that
Shapes of
A lot of presentations and
It's pretty wild I thought it was just like
We got crinkle fries you have chicken fries steak fries
Acquired so much more
Tots
Tots you got tots curly fries
Waffle fries at the hash brown patties
Except a pack of 10 of them cost like 4 bucks
You don't have to go to McDonald's
Browns mr. McDonald
Exactly your name maybe
A crock yeah that's a whole cracker s*** is what I'm
I will tell him
A book
Book series by Anne McCaffrey
Dragonsong and dragon singer and then there's a third one but
Play I love it so much
Because it's like that kind of magical girl story where
She's in a you know quiet remote place in
She's got a magical
Sure
Entirely about
Her wanting to become a music
And going to the school that doesn't allow women musician
And it's amazing is beautiful and it shows
A true and deep passion
A music that
I I care about bear
That sounds lovely
Recommendation
Souderton today we are going over
A little bit of an episode of Alex Jones Show for outside a we got
April Fool's Day episode
April 1st 2020
DMX
I'm so we're going to go over that it's really interesting there's some weird stuff
And then there's weirder stuff
Okay
I'm almost
Half of this episode is taken up with a
Source of conversation that is meaningless
Okay I like it so I'm thrilled to get into that
The first Dan with two ends
Great name one-to-many and thank you so much and I'll probably walk
Keep that in text Nicole P thank you so much and I apologize
Text Brian thinking about you and I'll probably walk
Thank you so much right now
I just want to thank you so much
Thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk donated on elevated level
Appreciate it very much the first Brett thank you so much
And old man house phone thank you so much you are now a technocrat
Heroin
Why you pimp so good
Is freakishly large
I declare
I like the show would like support these gents to do that
Finding a local charity in your area to help those who are in need
Please do one of the other they would be loved
So Jordan today like I said April 1st
April Fools
Alex starts off the show talking about a little bit of April Fool's business
Well ladies and gentlemen it is April Fool's Day and we got to April Fools
What
80000 in 2018
We have a total lockdown Society
No-sew first like
What's the
What's April Fools
Virus but it's not
Is Fairy real
Is the April Fool's Day joke pretending like Adams original estimate was 80 tonight
Original estimate
So Alex is flu numbers are inaccurate there but you and sofu comparisons are by definition stupid some of that aside
What I want to focus on here is the claim that Mike Adams estimates
Are being shown to be
April Fools
This that's fair enough. Okay to say they so nice appearance has on Alex's show
Is it possible to say Witcher bikes estimates
Alex was talking about
Michael's change projection
Quite a bit over the course of this. Very suspiciously in ways that seem to
Metacarpal Metallica's editorial tone
It's really helpful
On the day after China lockdown Wuhan
On January 24th
Famously get gastodon Alex's show and declare that it was over for Humanity and there would only be lone survivors
On that same show he literally said that most
People would not survive
Human race will not survive
I have this now there can be lone survivors or small groups
Survivors
We have to get to
Specific
But pretty high
On February 8th Mike returned to the show to misuse an estimate put up by Professor Neil Ferguson
Estimate that we would be seeing 7500 deaths a day in China from the virus
The death rate
Is
6:45
10%
Valet out here in a minute
Anna has admitted it
Accidentally admitted it
Neil Ferguson
Estimate
Professor Ferguson
His estimates
50000 noon
Directions a day
Translate
500 death
A day
Tryna over the neck
At the point of the writing of this episode China had experienced 3312 deaths from the virus a little more than
Of Mike Staley prediction
You take China's numbers with a grain of salt is still nowhere near what my
Mike's talking about
Then on March 1st Mike and Alex been a considerable amount of time discussing Rush Limbaugh's comments about the virus having a
2% mortality rate
And how half the population
Iff population got infected
That would translate to approximately
3 million deaths
You mentioned rush so I'll bring this up okay rush says there's only a 2% mortality rate
Map of America which is
Pretty typical for a flu
2% comes out
3.3 million dead
Americans
Essentially just admitted there could be millions of deaths in America
The flu
Let's be clear we don't want that to happen it's terrible times larger than the flu
Blue comparison
Did did Alex say that his projections were right
Meaning that there would only be 80 to 90 thousand people left on the planet or no
According to the universal one
By March 2nd Alex are completely fabricated to lieutenant-colonel sources who told him that
The Pentagon was predict
Approximately 3 million deaths
Exactly what you and Mike
We could discuss when they were talking about Rush Limbaugh
Alex playing with the military have been ordered to contact him to let him know this because they needed hardcore Patriots to be prepared
Weirdly Alex is completely drop this 100% made-up story line now because it's not useful to him anymore
On March 6th
Mike return to the show with Anouk
Computer model that showed a possibility of about two million deaths
By July
Which Alex
Proceeded
To use incorrectly
Donna models
Millions and millions dying or zanu
Computer model out
The shallows
Bye
July
Again these are just models
Other lands at models
Alex was so out of line that Mike had to interrupt their interview to tell him to change the headline about his model on enforced reflect
The model is showing would happen in the unlikely
Possibly impossible scenario that literally nothing was done to slow down the virus
So it was a very good computer model yeah
There is no narrative you can make out of this that says the Mike Adams was accurate
Michael's all over
Over the place and generally airing strongly in the direction of Hysteria or Lyon
What Alex just did to start his show is
Textbook gaslighting
Britannica Mike Adams has been
Super accurate
And his models they've always shown 80 to 90,000 and that's how I reported it
Straight down the middle complete Vindication for his prey
Complete Vindication it's abusive
It's so good to know when you're right
You know and I have a beacon
So there's a lot of rewriting of things in life
Creating this new episode
More solidified narrative and in this case
Alex lays it out here
It's essentially
You know what you need to know is that early on
The globalist said it was no big deal
In order to lure Trump
You know we've been down this road before but course
Here's how Alex explained
March 1st
I want to go
Because we're so they run the world
Alex's narrative his nonsensical about the progression through this matter really even care that much about how he decided to read
History
The story of his choosing
I'll just stick to
The claims that he's making
Alex claims that the US is engaging in more testing of the rest of the world combined and 100 times that of China
He further claims the China stop testing 2 weeks ago
On record that sounds like something China would do during the middle of the largest outbreak in their history
The claim the China stop texting people for Coronavirus is something that was making the rounds and some right-wing blogs
At which is undoubtedly where Alex got it from
So based on an article out of the Daily Apple which is a strongly anti-china tabloid from Hong Kong
Hasn't been
Substantiated by any other source and it seems unlikely that the case in China is still reporting new cases
No substantial questions about China's reporting about those things will be clearer in the future but this point
I wouldn't stake my credibility on this unfounded report
Unconfirmed report which Alex's just decided
Is on record totally accurate
A hundred percent
You got it
The u.s. is now done over 1.1 million coronavirus test and from what I can tell that is the most of any country in
However it's not more than all the countries combined
Italy's done more than 450,000 and South Korea is about 400
Issues that the vast majority of these tests
In America haven't done research
Where is it would have been way more effective to have dumped him
Earlier
Widespread testing is always helpful but
The point that they could have had the most impact has
Well testing now he's great but
Complaint is more the testing wasn't done when it was needed
But now it's real you just didn't notice that it turned from a hoax to react guess that's the way you explained it but
The other issue is that 1.1 billion test is good but
Per capita we're still far behind countries like Italy
In an article on NPR they they put the per capita testing at the United States at about 1 and 360
66 people compared to 1 and 130
3 + Italy
So when you know what do you adjust
For Countryside you can see the difference is a little bit more clearly
The numbers are kind of artist
To an extent
Father stuff
Nonsensical
Ways to try and defend Trump
Nonsense
Big numbers
Quoting from places
It's always
Is always conveniently getting rid of the per capita
Part of that you know
Chicago has the worst murders in the reservoir
Yeah that difference is is always
Start something he struggles with
Yeah
So one of the things that I found particularly interesting about this an April Fool's joke
But turns out it's not
Is that Alex is very insistent that the
And like the Pentagon
They now all are sure that this was a bioweapon released
Which
Getting to that from but okay
Senate intelligence and the Pentagon and again
People that are
Is it as he is a globalist
Because America was
New World Order
Americanizing it's 1776
Jerk plan that I have
Forward
A thesis
Where you been so that's what you mean by mdcclxxvi worldwide
Is not getting rid of the new world order but americanizing
And it's your version of America I don't want that
It's a global One World Government that is
Is created by the oh no that's not good
Okay let's
See it's a good idea to have a one world
No I don't think Alex can save that
Right bro
So Trump and his his goons were taking over the
Discover Bank
And that was too bad
So there was a globalist biotech that's why
Absurd
The Senate is it a consensus in the in the intelligence Committee in the Pentagon
The f*** out of here in half and find seen in Loeffler all sold out of their sex right away week
Cuz they found out it was a bioweapon
And so they had to save their money for the future
It's not unethical Dan
I don't know I don't know that ain't going to work. It's picking it up now
So the
The globalist
Because they're doing this bio attack in
In all this
They need people to be hurt by it
Or something
And so they don't want you to know that this Hydrochloric win
Is Bass
Squeaky
The Game Change
Bright
Really feel like it
We had all these these Governors like we talked about on the last episode of we're putting
Restrictions and regulations in place about frivolous prescription
Right because there's a concern about you know running into a complete
Shortage right customer
Enlisted everybody in a panic by other medication that could be otherwise very very helpful
Yeah so Alex has now learned that some of these
Senators and a senator's Governors are are requesting
Hydroxychloroquine
Decided that they flip
I have fought like the devil
To tell you there is no internet connection
Telling you that
Sunshine and
Things like that that is very hard to get it
Medical doctors
Hydroxychloroquine was illegal or now begging for it
Blocking the medicine to the people that it shows they are psychotic
So Alex is implying that mission Michigan Governor Gretchen Whitmer
Did assist did request a hydroxychloroquine
But he's lying about
She did it at the request of the Michigan Senate Majority Leader Mike Shirkey who explained his actions to the Detroit news
Who is Vasily
We needed something to prevent prevent chloroquine from becoming the next toilet
Prescribing hydroxychloroquine or Corcoran without further proof of efficacy for treating covid-19
With the intent to stockpile the drug May create a shortage
For patients with lupus
Rheumatoid arthritis or other ailments for which
Chloroquine
And hydrochloric Wayne are proven
Treatments
Again
These are drugs that have not been proven scientifically or medically to treat covid-19
This is exactly the situation we're discussing to recent episode
People like Alex a romper
Pretending they found a miracle cure and because people look up to them they're making a run on this medication
Which is leading to scarcity
To continue to serve the patients who have these conditions that this is actually used for people like the leadership in Michigan have had to try to get
More of it
Give the appearance
But they're on board with
Being a coronavirus cure
When in reality they're just trying to mitigate the danger caused by Trump's Reckless
It makes me so mad
I'm just home
Tired of that
We are
Forcing people to act like this because we've been trapped them in this
Cult-like Behavior
They're doing all this stuff that's causing a shortage at the rest
To deal with the rest of us deal with their b*******
They cited as proof that they
Succeed
Yeah
Yep
Yeah I don't have a rebuttal
Just so f******
Infuriated
That makes a little more interesting Lee is it simultaneously over the weekend the FDA issued an emergency
Usafa relation for Hydrox
Cork went to be used for Coronavirus
A couple of very important things to point out about this are they in their declaration the FDA makes it clear that the main reason for this
Emergency authorization
Is 1
There's no available alternative
Into the sent that the
Possible benefits outweigh the
Expected risks
By which
You know our
They're trying to get rid of
Hope Dan
That's what they're trying to
Yeah it's it
A very clear that this is not an approved drug out of the science does not reach the non-emergency standard
For approval but
Where is an emergency situation today
Try it it probably won't kill as many people as it
Might help
?
That's
Glenda being really bad news but it also might not be
It's really hard to say
But it's important to remember that there's a big difference
This declaration
And the rest of the ship we've been seeing
A health official saying you know like this is improving but we're in an emergency and it might do more to help than hurt so doctors should use their tusks
Gretchen giving it to patients that do test positive
That's super different than Alex and Trump
Promoting it is accurate
99% effective in the studies they're suppressing it
Cfda going Trump won't f****** shut up so far
Fine
Will do that
Yeah
Well but I don't think it's entirely that if you read the Declaration there is like
If you did if you look at the science
Under
Appropriate care
Odds of you dying
Are probably
Low
From the from the hydroxychloroquine appropriately with the assist
The doctor
There is
Not as unsafe as just everyone taking it or people doing it on their own
So trying to
Prove it
In that context
Makes more sense than running the risk
Of people trying to self Medicaid
So I think that their production Factor there
To the point that you're making it still is all all roads lead back to
Trumpets
Fit like a
Hyper-inflated expectations that are being created by Trump and his allies
That is still the root of where all of the impetus to trying
Self-medicate with it
Coming from but
It's like
It's like we're all sharing a car with
Toddlers And every now and again the toddlers get to
To drive and we just
Like I don't know where this is going to go there's a toddler driving it
Good luck
Well if you're a toddler and do you hate the United Nation
You might say things like Alex says I'm his next clip about the 1992 Agenda 21
Oh here we go
And I'll say I need citation
On pretty much all of this
Ewan said back in 1992
Rio de Janeiro
You're going to bring in total
Single parents
I want
What I want
Public
On the UN website
IGoodbye now do you want to bite
I couldn't find it I will play with creative post Human Society is on the UN website
Doubt was the human psyche
Sacrifice part
I don't even care anymore they didn't say that
So Alex gets to playing a clip of trump talking about Trump Stone did take a pretty big chain
Over the last like couple days where he's like
Baby Alive
Right right are the areas we get 100,000 deaths that'll be a victory that kind of tone
Yeah let me recontextualizing from this is an entire hoax to
Don't you realize that I mean not doing anything up
Up until now and then doing so
Something means that I have saved probably millions of lives and I'm the hero
Outbreak that I definitely did not call a hoax a month
So in terms of
Alex talking about
That in leading leading into the club
He
He kind of ends up admitting that Mike Adams
Predictions
Work 8090 thousand
This is this is ridiculous
Let's hear from the president
Are for hard days ahead
As many as 250,000 dead by
Middle of July
Mike Adams projector
About
Lockdown
So do he didn't he said to point something Million by July and is model that Alex was misusing the bottle was
If nobody does anything
If nobody does anything to something million
Right
Even so
This is this is Dante
Incubus stories
This is this is
So Alex is apparently a big Dow Jones guy now
He doesn't sell gold anymore he's got to buy stocks in Raytheon or whatever it is he does not leave the market is
Is like really important
Now Andy's you wants to check in
Finds out
Markets down
Uh-oh
That creates more inflation on the road but
Depression-era things happening so
Stimulus
Why
Cost of Praise from
Last night
We said okay we got to close two more weeks they went
My account
This is this is
While these
Did the gymnastics
It's required in order to make his make even something close to send
II
There's a mean there's no point
Again in pointing out Hip Hop
It's over with
The fact that piece
People on the right are saying like
This to trillion-dollar stimulus might not be enough
Makes me want to throw rocks
Speaker
When we hit the f****** last one there like all 101.5 trillion-dollar stimulus
We don't have the money to will never find it this is a bailout we need to it's definitely because of the balance.
That's why we're so mad
Package obviously 2-point trillion
Particularly with Alex
Berkeley surrounding the bailout was so
A lot of his coverage that like
Immediately and their money should go towards the civil
Like I realized that we can't do anything criminal
All of their assets
It's kind of a crime use civil asset for
I don't care
So Alex is really in a strange
Place that the beginning
In the first hour of the show
He's talking a bit about
Still the downplaying but also a trump saying
Like 100,000
A couple years ago there's still that sort of thing but he's also getting
I'm pretty deep into
Conspiracy s*** and like
It's a lot of stuff that we've gone over in the past like a lot of it is stuff that you'd find in our endgame coverage
Like he's just recycling a lot of weird
Old
Serta political conspiracy
It gets into talking about like the CIA man
I have a like
Really
Screwed over Shanghai shek
The Nationalist mean okay
And it takes a really interesting road cuz he's trying to relate that
To the present day with China being the
Tools of the global
Does it work
Shadow organization
The CIA
Around two years of the time
Track down and murdered hundreds of army officers
Fighting with shang-chi Shack in China
And the CIA sabotage d
Thousands of rifles and weapons
By removing the explosive grenades
Watch from
Long Beach
I was always read this
John Birch Society Congressional hearings when I was
Clamored
22 years ago
Watching History Channel
Yeah a lot of us thought I was going to really help shining so
The Rockefeller Foundation
Mechanic like a money on there
Yes
Congress you know
Was great
It's a week
I'm sitting here on History Channel
Show Mouse a tongue
Alex goes down the road on this episode of rewriting history of the Chinese Civil War
World's I really need him to do better than
I can find no citations with the globalist sabotage weapons being sent to Shanghai Shaq nor any evidence
The CIA was hunting down prosec soldiers
That's how you know they did it cuz there's no evidence of the CIA
I can find plenty of evidence of the US assess
The Chiang Kai-shek was doomed to lose that war because he was very terribly
TJ
I need to terminate a full-on US
Involvement would lead to a gigantic War likely involving a bunch of other countries
You just couldn't be justified
That's that's not hard
Conclusion
I was going through the cia's for you Archive of documents about my land Shanghai Shack and none of the stuff Alex
Thanks squares
Any of the doctor
Confine
However I did find an August 4th 1958 letter that Allen Dulles sent Shane kai-shek's wife thanking her for sending
A box of tea
It seems like they were on friendly relations
In 1958 was running the CIA that was drying
Kill people working with him and put now into power but whatever the jobs the job
Man it's not personal.
Cafe B Civil Wars
You would somebody but when it comes down to it
Depressed
I even thought of May 24th 1962 memo the details quote a result of a check with the old
China Han
Ants in the agency and the Department of State
They found that quote
The US has always held that the GRC the government
The Nationalist
Represents the legitimate government of China
However it also does saving in 1949 to 1950
Quote we did inform Chiang Kai-shek
Did the US did not intend to become
I'm further involved in the Chinese Civil War
Alex is making claims that I need to see more proof of any basti has is claiming it's in the books it's been Declassified and that's not good
I've heard him say 100 times
Is that kind of thing is just making those
Things up
I do believe that he read the stuff and John Birch Society text
No
What gives me no faith
And this whole thing
Is it foggy memory of some CIA section
Chief on an unnamed show on either the Discovery Channel or History Channel that Alex up 22 years ago
Hey you
Remember something whenever it's
True Dan that's how it works I have no idea if this alleged documentary exist
If it says
Thanks it does or anything
This is as good as providing no evidence quite frankly
All the information I can find about the CIA in the period around this time has to do with them doing covert actions
The train destabilize Mouse cover
I really need Alex to cite some sources
A couple things that are concerning about his memory is that there's no such thing as a CIA section
What's not real title
Is that Justin FB I think know the title whatever title is station cheese
Know that
There's only one
CIA station chief
In China at that time
Now it should be really fun
Renton know that person's name and information about their careers some corroborating evidence anything
But he doesn't
All Alex has is probably completely false memory about something
He claims he saw on the Discovery Channel or History Channel two decades ago
This is what literally
Indistinguishable from not trying
He might as well just say that he saw this like history in a dream
And that would be hold as much weight as the document that he's making here
Michelle
The section nine agency
There are sections in the Japanese law enforcement section 19
Chief aramaki done
Stop it that's where you got the idea
It's a great at the great movie
Scrape series
I'm sure
Okay
Until here's what I think is going on with this kind of narrative
Check was going to lose that war against Mal
And the US knew that there were only two options
In front of them
One was letting the war play out and probably allow the communist government to take power in
The other was becoming directly involved in the conflict
Risking a wider war in a best-case scenario installing Chiang Kai-shek and the Nationalist
The power
By virtue of our military support
Alex wants the u.s. of the past to do the ladder
But he's also invested in the hole
A whole lot of his career and beatley anti intervention guy
What are the only position
Never held that made people think
He's not a total lunatic as a strong aversion to
The Iraq War
In all these wars of regime
I suspect that he knows that it would be impossible for him to argue against regime change Wars
They claim that the US should have gotten directly involved in a country's Civil War in order to pick a winner
In order to avoid that cognitive dissonance
Netzkino is Extreme right-wing age
Communist types of created an entirely new story of what happened in that war
Look like they wish they were
Yeah what would have happened is exactly what they pretend to be against in the present
Instead of them retroactively calling for a war of regime change
They're really just against the secret regime-change that actually was going on where the globalist or sporting now
That seems like what it's going on but honestly I have no idea
This could all just be something Alex's dad told him when he was a
I don't really
It's
You really that right wing
Play book of
What I want to have I have no
Historical
Consistency whatsoever
So I am 100% against vaccines
And then you're like what what about
The polio vaccine
Welbeck
Then polio vaccines were great
They solved everything I have to stop you later in this episode
He might not
A certain Health Ranger
Alright well then I guess I'll have to give it up to him like the Somali pirates for some sort of consist
Even your parody examples unfortunately
Unfortunately
You know he saw this stuff in the John Birch Society and I do believe
Sharks a little bit
About that
What is the John Birch Society
It wasn't Lobster
The Tricom captioning
Death
Secrets
So to be fair
Alex's dad was in the John Birch Society we don't know that 100%
That there were birchers around
Right and it seems very likely that his dad was a virtue
It seems it seems incredibly likely we don't have confirmation that it could have been that he had like
Uncle's or his grandfather or
Friends of his dad to basically uncles
He have a lot of influence
And his dad seems to have a lot of
Similar ideas as the transverse
I'm just saying that if you
Give your son John Bircher reading
Yeah regardless of whether or not you
Something like that when you're without the proper
Maturity
It's so funny to hear Alex's
Is clip there though he's talking about these birchers always being right
Just a few years ago I was just trying to pretend that he wasn't into the jumper Society
You know the saying that he was into their s*** would prove that he was
Completely insane right-wing agent, is lunatic
Which would have hurt the crossover appeal that he was trying to cultivate and all those years and he's pretending he was above the left-right paradigm
I'm worried about that
All that time he was lying
He was a Bircher the whole time
I'm trying to push extreme right-wing s*** under the banner of pretending to be above this
The right-left it's just a lie man it's about freedom
In that sense
A lot of people really owe their careers to Alex Jones
Pave the way of that b*******
Horse and right-wing stuff
However it's hilarious to hear Alex say that everything the John Birch Society has put out
Is true
I've read a lot of the JBS materials and spice it's safe that almost none of it is true
I guess what I don't even have to get into any of their Publications to demonstrate
The John Birch Society was named they named themselves after John Birch
Who they claimed was the first US casualty of the Cold War
How to sing that he was tortured and he didn't give up and seek
And that part
Definitely isn't true
He was shot by a
Polar me
Chapcare contingent
On August 25th 1945 after refusing to disarm
He wasn't captured wasn't tortured
Ain't giving up his seat
Play the funniest part about that
Zimsec John burchett
What it's like
You didn't even get the truth of your own f****** name right
Nothing is true
Jumpers was definitely working in intelligence
China 1945
Which doesn't that make kind of mess up Alex's narrative at us intelligence working to install mount
The guy the John Birch Society was named after was plotting to
To portray shang-chi Shack hold on once
I encourage you not to think about it because Alex certainly has not you just hurt my brain
Lieutenant Colonel James Doolittle serve with Birch in China and I should tell you he's an actual lieutenant-colonel unlike the ones out
It is 2009 Memoir entitled I could never be so lucky again
He has this to say about John Birch who he knew personally
He had no way of knowing that the John Birch Society a highly vocal post-war anti-communist organization
Would be named after him because of
Its founders believed
To be the first casualty
Of world World War 3
I feel sure he would not have approved
John Birch is a
Ping to the John Birch Society not a purse
He's taken out of their patron saint while you had no say in the matter and according to someone who knew him
Probably would not be into it
And then what Alex is doing is even worse
You created a fictional fictional story about torture to apply to birth to make a narrative better
These people are cool
They are awful
The LIE is
Bacon
You don't even need to get into any of their their publication
The Blue Book
Are any of that s*** so
No absolutely I'm starting a group called The Mary Poppins
In society because
Mary Poppins
The first woman to murder
6000 people in World War II
I knew her and I don't think she'd approve
Murder
She's the basis for the penguin
Okay
CIA put now into power and also John Birch
Buzz
The hero
Silence is talking a bit about the CIA ship
And he seems to
Think that
The problem in the world and all
The Troubles of the Trump Administration
Are basically about
Trying to
To get his people
Into the leadership
Boy
Creating chaos
And this is
Stupid
CIA
He's just the biggest intelligence agency
You can see here again then Alex doesn't
Not like
The Deep state
You just wanted to be his
Saturday
Gina's time and time again minions uptalk
Too Loosely ends up revealing that the New World Order is probably good as long as Trump
He wants a One World Government like
We should all
Buy Greenland and all that s***
Just as long as
Victor one world government is in place
Is
Why bother you asked
And Trump is a jar until Pro as long as they're targeting right-wing Act
What if they're killing not a problem
Yelling about
The institutional rot of intelligence agencies being in control of the government means nothing
Because he wants the intelligence agencies to control the government
But only if his weirdos run the
Agency
This is exactly why political project
To the sort that Alex and his ilk engaging will never lead to real change
They scream about
Structural change but all they want
Is the kind of puts them in charge of the structure
The Superficial change online
Absolutely that way they can destroy the straw
Pictures and live I assume they become Duke
Call Larry
Also since Trump has been in office there been
Free heads up
The CIA appointed
Menlo Park was the actor
Sing head for 3 days at the beginning of the term Gina haspel has been in since May 2018
Previous the hospital who Trump appointed Trump
Appointed Mike
Pompeo is a headed
CIA for a good fifteen months
For making him that the Secretary of State
Will you have so much good practice
Practice is the head of CIA
Clearly ready for the promotion
The point is the Trump has clearly been able to put people in charge
Okay what about that Director of National Intelligence he's been killed for 30 years
Dempsey who's the acting head after Trump got rid of Clapper
And then Trump appointed Dan coats
Who was in the position for about two-and-a-half years
And then we got to act
There was Joseph Maguire who Trump appointed when Dan coats left
He was appointed because Trump didn't want the
The deputy director to take over probably cuz you didn't trust her
And then about five months later Trump fired Maguire because one of his subordinates
It's brief the house
Intel committee
About Russia's preference for Trump to win in 2020 which anger drop because drop is a baby
Pretty sure Trump said
You had me at good
Goodbye Trump replaced him with the former ambassador to Germany Richard grenell
It is time is Ambassador used
Describe a ABC News as quoted viewed as one of President Donald Trump's closest envoys in Europe
Which explains why he was involved in the negotiations to arrest Julian Assange
Alex should not be thrilled with but whatever
Grinnell was literally the person who made a verbal pledge that if Assange was handed over
He wouldn't get the death
And this is one closer Trump's closest allies we appointed Director of National Intelligence
What cost
That's all I got dropped has been dominating and appointing people to leadership position
Intelligence
Community
Any president would
Yeah but to be appointing bad people but that tends to create chaos
On that picture that Alex wants to pay here
Play bulshit the tries to rewrite why the chaos is happening
It's not sad
AutoZone
How do I get
There's no intelligence head that isn't a
Bad person
Like everybody else
Bad person like
It's just how it is
That's a fair conversation but also
There are grades
I100 centigrade
I'm just not going to argue
Sherlock
Someone like Alex should recognize like
I got really drunk at my CPAC speech and try to lead the people at a pitchfork rally
Julian Assange no problem every guy who literally negotiated the arrest of Julie massage Trump rewarded with making
Okay
Now you're
Saying one thing
But let me counter with this
No and a different thing
But my point is that Alex doesn't know anything
Also the Office of Naval intelligence still exists and there's been to riches
Appointed the time since Trump has been in office
These aren't actually positions that the President appoints
But they are nominated by the defense secretary who is appointed by the president
Also Army intelligence still exist
It's a much wider entity
But generally speaking
Be US Army deputy chief
Chief of Staff G2
Is considered the head of Army intelligence
Oxymoron
F****** bad joke in that position and he's been
Been there since January 2018 within the time
Trump has been in office
These things like Naval intelligence in Army intelligence still exist
His head no problem appoint
People into positions
If you wanted to what are we doing
Love is made of b******* Alex
Who started the Trump is doing a terrible job and he needs a justification
It can't just be the Trump is profoundly stupid and abolition
This person who's not equipped being office
It has to be the everyone else is working again
In fact the only good
Again Tamara things I said in Wednesday's Bill Cooper episode
This is childish
Very
F****** childish
It's it's just
It's amazing
It really is amazing
How
How f*****-up the human brain
Can be how many
Twisted
Can take to get
Had to wear it once
To go speak
If you are if you're even an uninformed
Person
Can't look at what Trump has done and go
That's a good humor
It's just not possible
And I'm not even talking this present I'm talking to
Human it just a human being if you know Trump store you're like oh that's
Retired after the like apprenticeship
Is your fire sucks in Home Alone 2 what else do you want he wasn't even Richie Rich
Which I hate
You never really a chain
Cancel
You suck at WrestleMania Hitler
It's a really good a meaty roll
In Home Alone 2 we wouldn't be
You really sucked
App
Stone cold stunner and he took
Very far
The Rock
Greater taking a stoner
I really don't like you reminding me that the president is in the world
Play Hall of Fame really don't like you're reminding me of that
When Vince McMahon and his family went to the White House
So what there was a beam that was like
Stone cold has stunned 60% of the people in this photo
God
So f***** up giving a stutter to Vince McMahon
It's not the children
That's a grim f****** hot alligator in f****** reality
Nation that we should stop wearing
Alex believes that the issue is
What Trump needs to do is he needs to come out very strongly endorse that everybody take
Hydroxychloroquine
Anthramycin
A z-pack
And everything will be cool
Counter that's a bad idea
Well
Or not
Mexico everywhere
I want to sing through these studies out of Europe China and Mexico claiming super high recovery rates
It's from hydroxychloroquine being used
Tree Coronavirus
And he needs to be more careful
The study from Europe he's talking about was that French study
And this study should absolutely not be seen as conclusive.
For one and only included 42 patients in the trials and 6 of them did not complete
Study with one dying in the middle of treatment
Of the 42 patients 26 were given hydroxychloroquine
Six were given hydroxychloroquine and azithromycin and 10 where the control group
All six of the patients who could not complete the trials were in the group that were given hydroxychloroquine
But only one was thought to have been unable to
Completed because of
The drug
So maybe some of that is just circumstantial
Because the samples so small
And the controls are good
Yeah you don't know
It doesn't mean
The six patients who were given the combined drugs
Girl said to have recovered in 5 days
Sunny study super dicey
412 small number of participants
Does not great and the fact they don't address that
6 patients
Complete the trial is unnerving
They just don't address
Well they don't give specifics into like what was going on
It's not really factored in
Well to the explanation of
Wow this it should screw up their number
Yeah the fact that they only provided data on the patient
For seven days when the trial was supposed to have been 40
Teen is also a huge problem
Four people have looked into it
There were a lot of problems with this study and it became even more troubling when the peer-review status was examined
It was accepted by the Journal the register the day after the study was supposed to have ended
Which is very suspicious
As it turns out
1800 authors of the study is the editor-in-chief of that damn what happened is with Rush
Through the process and published as peer-reviewed
Possibly prematurely
This study may be
Repeat with more rigorous standards and a larger randomized set of participants
But from everything I can tell you should not take this Pacific finding too seriously
Are way too many unanswered question
Since about the study for it to be like okay
So info
Creating why would you do that
Why would you release
To study with only
Samad page
I think it's worthless
Of
Like
Actual people in the medical field it is worth wild data
I get that
I get there
And I don't know enough about
The person who did the
This study tried to say that they were using it
Like wrong
Maybe their intention was just to give this information
Possibly hastily gathered together as it was
Create the experiments
Possibly
It does serve that function as one of the downsides of the interconnectedness of the internet and the
Free
Quick flow of information is a lot of stuff that's not meant for your eyes and
Can only be a problem for you to see what other people make you
It's just that the
The editor-in-chief
Also
Alps right
The study it ended a week early
The day after might not have anybody thoroughly positive it's provided on threat
The write-up
And then it was rushed
Through it just seems like that's
Two glaring
Anything to allowed
To happen
With that like I don't need the
Contact you are the results of the study
I just need to know that I'm like
I can't trust you
Well you know
Yeah
The way that I think is most appropriate to look at it is there's a lot of questions
It's not necessarily evidence of malfeasance
From the things that I've been able to tell questions that need to be addressed
Before you know you want to really
Look at the
Gospel is really troubling
For sure and I'm not arguing it like again maybe the results of the study are right on and maybe everything was followed to a tee
There's too many different
Turn things around there that's a
I can't
And so it's not
That I'm going to dismiss the findings out of hand
Buy but it's like
I'm not even going to
Pretendo
Matter until I have something
Weather interesting and you should
They are data points that are worthwhile
But I think when we get to the end of this
Little chunk
That I have to present for you
You understand a little bit why some of this information might come out
In the way that it does
So answer the study from China at the worst exam
This is the study was published by the Journal of Beijing University in China and the conclusion it reached was that hydroxychloroquine
Was as effective as note
Who was a really small study of only 30 patients
15 were given the drug and after a week 13
Team tested negative
Of the 15 who work given the drug
14 tested negative after a week
The conclusion in the paper was Deez Nuts
Statistically significant
And further studies were required to
Determine if there was any real benefit then
Another
Not yet. You'd study
Out of China of
62 patients did fine Daddy
Time of recovery
In patients treated with
But this is unreviewed
And it should not be taken as definitive as of yet
So I can find no study
Aeromexico
As I was explaining that hydroxychloroquine
Nqr Coronavirus
However if you just Google those words
You'll find a posting on clinicaltrials.gov which is recruiting patients for a double-blind study being put on
By the National Institute of respiratory diseases in Mexico
According to the posting the study is supposed to begin on March
23rd 2020
But would not
Complete until March 21st
I'm sorry March 22nd 2021
The results of these trials will likely be far more Illuminating
Even the small-scale studies we have access to at this point but the results are always off in the future
There's no way Alex can know the results of the study
If you was just reading headlines you might see something about a study about hydroxychloroquine
Mexico and just make up the rest
Is it in there yeah
Now but this Mexico study is actually kind of
Like the demonstrative of what I was saying
It's like
To do a real trial like this would take
That long
So the data would never really
You never have
The preliminary data
People are
Maybe needing
In order to like for mother trials
To do if you did it
This rigorous standards
With a large group of participants in
And randomization double-blind all the all the standards
The only started coming out of Mexico right now
How long it take
Coronavirus
That guy's
Nothing interesting
Study are you conducting that well we're all just were all conducting
It's like he's just not
He's not doing good
Like
Emma was still traveling around flying commercially
As much as possible denying that the situation is happening
Shaking hands doing the whole thing like it's amazing Arthur Boris about the handshake
Insane
These 3 countries are against Europe's not a country but the three places that he said their studies from
These are the specifics things
Nvidia stock
What is a French study that
It's dubious but possible there needs to be more work done on that
Before you can throw any kind
Conclusion
Chinese study the first one
Said
It is good as nothing
I meant the other one that more recently came out from China is not pure reviewed and is unclear
And at this point
We have no results from
Alex doesn't
Have anything
Things back any of this up
Anyway but Trump needs to say I won't take this
Course absolutely
So Alex has Mike Adams on because his projections have always been Acura
Okay
Regional protection with everyone
The latest and why they're starting to up and numbers after lowering them before
They're following the mathematics of where this goes
This is deeply gaslighting
This is a
Like Mike should have been
Like you know what no
I was off
Early I said I said most of the human race would not survive
Just being just walking back a little bit you don't have to walk it back at unjust be like
I was a little bit out of line at first
I was panicking like everybody else
And so I went back and I checked the numbers and I think it's more in line with what the
Okay.
I'm more than willing to admit that I didn't
Does the situation nearly as seriously in liquid say January as
I am now and that's because I had blind faith in the system
Matter how often we are disabused enough
Someday there will be adults in the room
Are not misguided belief
This this could be pretty bad but I have faith in the public health officials and everyone
Will make the right decisions and
So that's fine
You can bet that some of your assumptions
Were turned out to not be accurate and that's okay then like refuses to do that
It's a good thing that leads to growth
Perhaps
So Mike's projection is now 45 to 90,000
Sure
My projections are currently between
5 and 90000 deaths
The end of July
The White House is currently estimating 100,000 to 240,000 but look
Solution is
What solution I am convinced now
Is more masks
More zinc for everybody vitamin D3
More testing
Those
Four elements in place I mean Nationwide emergency production of zinc
Give it out for free to everybody flood the country
Recommendations
America
Back to work
By the end of
It's going to go f*** around and give people heavy metal poison
I would prefer it if you stuck with it
The end of humanity
Because now that he's going on this trip I'm more afraid that it's the end of humanity
Like when he's like I think it'll be between 45 and 90000
If we get all these testing in all these masks
The thing that I said 2 weeks ago we don't need to do and then that we're all going to die but now we're going to be fine and all that
Legit now I'm worried
That's an interesting reaction that you're having to the health Ranger
I also want to put him in the stocks and have people throw tomatoes at him
Forever that's not an interesting reaction is very normal
Queensryche so you got to get all the zinc
Sing to me about this is that Mike is
Presenting this is a very just like
This is
My
Research
Scholarly opinion
As if Alex hadn't been doing recently a bad pitch
Constantly about zinc
In the real red pill
What are the products didn't even know if it's in quiz in Port
Dammit
How did they how did they come to that conclusion independently of each
It's just
So constantly like
Just
Zinc zinc zinc is the answer
They're not talking about it being in Alex's prod
And I think that's intense
Oh you think so are they sick of getting letters from attorneys
The real issue is the doctor
You know those doctors that are doctors who have degrees totally real doctors who are also Lieutenant Colonels in the military
Doctor doctor doctor
Meet at hospital
Problem with their education Jordan
They don't know
Teachers you know medical doctors
More than a few weeks on nutrition not talk about nutrition as I'm getting different numbers.
Are you doing
And and eating healthy foods
Really I mean
There's a chronic Zone population
Covid-19 disease
Is really a chronic zinc.
Deficiency disease that is
Virus which
Otherwise would not be very harmful to people
Big swing wow that is a big swing
Looking think isn't it everything but there's a lot of f****** foods that have zinc in it
This is this
Like I can't stress this enough
What's interesting there is
Mi Cocina
What I do is I take this
That's a testimonial
Stats
Fine
Illegally
This really feels like they're trying to sell zinc it really feels like hold on tight because they are
It's insane
Cold essential you don't have
Some people don't get any robot him and see
Galesburg.com
As far as curvy goes
Don't call it a comeback
Scooby's not a comeback disease it's just a people who stuffy thing vitamin seed
You can find headlines like one that I found for
2018 quotes
Read the article on 2.2
There are people with malnutrition that may come down with scurvy but the numbers aren't nearly would Alex want you to think with a scurvy
He's making a comeback
A solution is always eat an orange
Zinc deficiency can definitely be bad for
People but also most people get enough zinc
As long as their diets include red meat and poultry
If you're a vegetarian
Keys almonds and baked beans will give you plenty of zinc or you can take a multivitamin many of which
Zinc
The more these dudes talk
The more I think that this is
Basically an unspoken sales pitch
For the real red pill Alex's supplement the sink
I think that Alex knows that if he makes it to overt
He's going to get another letter
So he's just hyper promoting zinc is the answer to the coronavirus and trusting that his listeners will put two and two together
I did the sales pitch for the fact that real red pill has zinc in it in the past
Yeah that was a different episode
Attorney general to make an argument that I'm doing this
They need use multiple episodes and I can argue that Accord
Haha feels like that's the logic
It's going really happened a few times and now I've changed up my primary sales method to strongly win
Thinking at the
The crowd also keep using testimonial
Thanks Alex keeps saying like
It good good for plants
Intentional
King shity honestly I wouldn't even be that suspicious about it
Except for this thing that Mike's
You have anything to sell
Infowars has Incan in their slow for fucksake
Minor ingredient in it
Multi-vitamin mineral formula
Really
Is
Zinc is the
The key
Beginning America.
Back to work
What can save the economy
A free Society
Liberty
We need to embrace nutrition which means we need knowledge
End the big Pharma
Stranglehold
4r systems
Big Pharma runs the media
Big Pharma runs
Washington d.c.
Shurfine
Homemakers
Big Pharma runs the medical schools in a doctors and universities
Bad as possible
Imposition
The drug companies and the vaccine companies
In the end
Fighting medical doctors
Old Jeep drugs at work right
Good news is they failed to suppress that treatment
Okay
Alright Health Ranger I don't even sell the product with zinc in it
I've never even seen The Matrix so I wouldn't know that if there was a product with zinc in it they would be referencing the make
Matrix and I definitely don't know if you Alex Jones the Infowars host
I wish with also the red pill
Did I even see my pillow
It's a red pill you said red pill
I wish
Listen
Come to the episodes like where Mike host
I guarantee I could have found some audio of him selling the real redneck
I believe it he doesn't sell isn't product but I don't believe that he's oblivious
The fact that Alex
Has been really trying to push the real red pill because of it having
Aesthetic
So
They're really
Ghetto the angle is very strongly in the pushing
Hydroxychloroquine
Which is an unproven
Now it what makes
This really difficult
Has a pill to swallow
Pun intended
Is that Alex is also trying to pair this
Narrative
News about when they make a vaccine
It will hurt you
It'll be an unproven Max
Right
It's it's almost like two narratives that should not exist within the same
Bran
Virologist
Do you have the warnings about Unruh
I like
Medical applications Withings that are
Thoroughly tested and aren't ready to
To go meanwhile
Strong promotion of
IPA
Only emergency approved medication
When was Alex
Be promoting this if it's a prescription coil
Score score
He should be saying constantly talk to your doctor
Confusing
Ideologically I want
Testing available for everyone I want
The eventual vaccine available available for everyone I want Treatment available for everyone
But when I listen to Alex Jones sometimes I'm like
What is the rest of us just covered our eyes for a little bit and then a few months they're gone
Like it's that kind of
Fury that I have at this liar
I want
To save his life
And he is actively trying to kill himself in his
Blisters dad
It's infuriating
It is infuriating it's it's it's
Trial of empathy
Really isn't pointless understanding
Yes and it gets worse because of his next
Is where Mike
Gets into polio truth or ism
It's it's pretty bad
The way to beat the vaccine industry Alex is to get the word out about zinc
I'm get America healthy and back to work again before the vaccine even comes into existence
The vaccine
Cause
The virus
It was all a lie
You know the vaccine didn't do anything
The vaccine actually introduced more polio
The number one cause of the polio vaccine
Do the same thing with coronavirus if we give them a chance
The word out about zinc
Vitamin D3
Parkland and masks
Master the key
Different from now on anybody riding on public transportation for the next few years
I know it's fashion masks coming out is going to be cool looking mask
All kinds of stuff
Your bicycle be like okay
It's over
So it's really f****** easy for the health Ranger Mike Adams to sit here in 2020 and save it
Polio vaccine
She didn't do anything
I think it's going to be a little f****** different if you were over 70 years old
And live through the. Prior to the Advent That vaccine
It's hard to remember this because most of us have lived our entire lives
Anthony post-polio era
Herbivore straight up
Terrified of polio for good reason
In 1894 the first outbreak of polio occurred in Vermont
And call dr. The world but recorded in the United States
And it called doctor
Completely flat-footed
18 people died in 132 were left permanently paralyzed
At the time people work
Fairly clueless about the origin of the disease and concluded based on preliminary information
Play things like observing
Family members not getting sick when
Bunbuzz
That they decided it was
Contagious
Omart
11 years later Swedish scientist
Ivar Wickman the Discover the polio wasn't that communicate
Couple and their people could have it without developing these severe version
Which often lead to death
Paralysis
In 1962 major outbreak struck New York leaving over 2,000 dead in New York City
Cases spread across
The country with the death toll reach
About 6,000
And also leaving thousands more paralyzed
Permanently
For decades scientists are trying to figure out if x
To no avail
It was just think that people lived with
The weariness of a terrifying disease that could kill you leave you paralyzed or put you into an iron lung
The March of Dimes was created as a way of funding Medical Research into a cure or vaccine
And through contributions
The millions of folks
They did
Makes progress
In 1952 there were over 57,000 polio cases in the United States
With over 21,000 of them results
Chicken paralysis
Naturally with those kinds of numbers we were pretty anxious for a cure
And a few years later Jonas Salk would include
Is Trials
Leaving to the introduction
The first polio vaccine
Immediately from 1955 to 1957
No
United States drop between 85 and 90%
Albert Sabin will come along a few years later with an improved vaccine can be taken orally and then phobia was essentially
Eradicated
In the country
The last naturally occurring case was said to happen
The 1979 but it wasn't
An Amish community
I don't mean that to say that Amish
Are more likely to be Auntie vaccinated right because of these
Secluded nature communities are
More under
Vaccinated
Knock-Knock position to vaccine grinder sir
Isolated
Yeah many of the people who had Polio but survived they come down with post-polio syndrome
CPS make up one of the largest blocks
Pics of persons
Living with disability in the world
The landscape of disability rights
Would be a lot different
Without a lot of the activists in the polio Survivor community
From Ed Robert
The founder of the world in
Institute on disability
Who got polio at 14
Had to be in an iron lung
Do Judith human
Zoo live basically her whole life of polio eventually becoming Bill Clinton's assistant secretary for education and
Potato service
What bike is engaging here in at 8 here is a shocking inoffensive Erasure of
Millions of people's
Experience
His whole the polio vaccine created more cases
Sapolio
Is just him misrepresenting
What stone is the Qatar in
In 1955 a number of recently vaccinated children were coming down with polio and paralysis of the arm
Where the vaccine was given to
Where the cases were investigated they were found at these they trace back to Qatar Liebert
It was awful and I'm not minimizing the experiences of the hundreds
The people who were affected by the fuk up
But this was a lavish
Do not have X
People were producing the vaccine they were not correctly preparing it
And in the process the virus itself was not being fully inactivate
This hurt public confidence
The vaccine itself
And it's used to this day by anti-vax weirdos like bike
The drying
Claim that the vaccine
Gives you the disease
Yeah it was
A function of
Bad business
Being done
The people have been more careful and actually that led to a lot of conversations about regulation of
Production of medical stuff if you want to try and rewrite FDR's Legacy on the New Deal
Naturally have to rewrite
FDR's Legacy on
Having polio
So there's one other thing that might could be referencing
But it also be lying about it
I don't know if you know this
But there's a condition that's called circulating vaccine-derived poliovirus
That's the thing that I
Folio
Sounds like you're not
It's super fascinating
And honestly
The more you know about it the better an argument is to vaccinate your children
So in 2017 mostly because the number of naturally occurring polio cases was
Very small
There were actually more cases of vaccine-derived poliovirus
When you get a vaccine you're getting a Wii conversion to that
Disease put into your body so you can
Can create an immune response to it which will give you an immunity sometime
Spinato's
Well yeah
Fine this is the case with his polio vaccine
But if you get the vaccine it's not you who could get back
Derive poliovirus
Unvaccinated people around you
So in the time that the weakened viruses inside you creating the immune response you can end up excreting
Desire ateez communic
In the in the case
But yeah
In the case that you're in a population that is under vaccinated
That virus could end up getting picked up by someone who hasn't been back since
This person will likely be fine
Because it's just a weekend version of the poliovirus and ultimately end up creating an immunity to it as well most of
However
If the population Uranus super under vaccinate
It just might be that this virus can jump
From person to person for a long time
In the process mutate back into the form of polio virus that can cause serious problems like a paralysis
The World Health Organization estimates that this process takes at least 12 months
And
Between 2000 and 2017 in that seven
19 year span
This occurred
24 * in the entire world
And it led to 760 cases of vaccine-derived poliovirus
Notion
But that's compared to the estimated 13 million cases
Did vaccination programs had prevented
I don't understand that
That's not a trade-off
I'm not willing to make that trade-off
Also this is only an issue with the orally-administered vaccine
It's not the case which is what's used in the United States so it's not even relevant to our lives
Here necessarily
What do vaccine-derived
Bentley poliovirus
It can only really
Be a problem
Vaccinated
Contrave the of the harmless virus right
To each other to the point where I can
Yeah that's that is
Like
That is that herd immunity Concept in
God
I just don't understand people who can honestly argue again
It has to be
Look I mean
Not honestly I mean I get that people believe
The anti-vax
I get that they believe it
The arguing of it
Seems
If you believe it just say that you think it
It causes autism or whatever it is your b******* is
And stop there
The idea of arguing with me
He's insane
Yeah
It seems especially when you're the health right
Yeah it's Sovereign citizen bulshit looking for help
I got big argue with a disease
Mike says that there are more cases of polio to comfort
Vaccine
He's talking
He wants you to imagine a doctor giving you a shot
That's going to give you Polly over the claim it's medicine
Ultimately what I want to say is a big f*** you too Mike Adams
Polio wasn't Israel
And the vaccine is safe
How was people in this country and around the world
Paralysis and death
Infinite
People who survived
I would beg
Anyone who's interested go watch
Some documentaries about polio survivors
Like hear their stories
It's what Mike is doing is
Outrageous
Avery had all that motherfuker Mike Adams has ever given the world
Is a dumbass Ebola cure that would definitely give you ebola
A couple of embarrassing rap song and this s***
It's over for Humanity
It will only be Lone Survivor
Go fuc yourself McAdam serious
He's he's got to be stopped
Strongly
Making an argument for himself as
Feel like being
The worst
He is like
He really is
Alex will always have the
Grandfathered position of the worst
Write that number two spot is it
It's constantly really close
Yeah it is a holocaust denier
And Steve
Might always be in the number to stop it
Might make a great case for a cell
We're past
It's like obviously the log can't help us
But if we
We had somebody
Need to take Mike
Arkham Asylum it would be okay
Do you know what I mean
Vigilante
But Arkham Asylum is a different situation a lot of downtime
I feel like you're good at
Your girlfriend's condo is going to have a cave and it soon
If only we had a butler
I'm free
You would be a great outfit
I think I could be off
You give me all kinds
Targets in all the stuff in you be like Jordan don't
Techno revered sensibilities to
Mike is pushing really hard that everybody's going to get these masks
And
Great I get online I guess nothing else though
They only people we need math
Well unfortunately
Keep talk
Discussing how like
Snopes
The government
Take basketball
Because the Surgeon General
Because the government
Agencies had this information about
And teach people know math
Our good master
What's on record
We're fighting the disinformation Agents of the world which are most
Do you think of Mike Adams is mad that the Surgeon General is take
Technically a health Ranger named Adams
I think he's mad that cbp's doesn't know that we have a Surgeon General
I mean that was only like a month
That Alex is fever like
Trump
We're all going to die
I guess they're learning
You know
You got to give it up for that for that
If it is true that the Surgeon General is putting out this information about whether or not masks
They're helpful for people who don't have the virus
It was only one person you should talk to you about that and it's the person who appointed him and
Play some it anytime and that's
On March 2nd Surgeon General Jerome Adams Twitter
Seriously people stop buying masks they're not effective in preventing general public from Catching Coronavirus
But if Healthcare Providers can't get them to care for sick patients
What's them
In our communities at risk
Then on April 2nd there was a headline from CNBC
Quotes
In a U-turn US Surgeon General asks CDC to see a face mask and prevent coronavirus spread after all
No matter what the reality of the situation is
You kind of see how inept the people Trump surrounds himself with our
And how you can't
Really rely on them for
Good messaging
Just it's just such an
Obvious thing
That we're living through right now
When we get past
And we're all again capable of
Congregate
These people need to face charges
They just need to face chart like
It Is by their bungling of the system
Directly
Many more people are going to die
Specifically and their actions
Have killed
That is I don't know how other to describe that then as a
Prime
A murder
And they should face charges
That's that
It's not hard if you were truly I don't disagree with you functionally I don't know what that look
But it's just
Should happen
So the big issue that I leaving that aside yes of course I don't know what to do with it
Will ever be able to like sit here be like all right here is here's a step one
Several million people together in the same place
The issue that I have with
Mike is that he's framing the situation with the masks
Incorrectly
There's a whole lot of debate about whether or not normal surgical masks are going to be helpful in stopping you from being exposed to the virus
Particularly if you're in close proximity with someone who's sick
And coughing
Do not create an airtight seal on your face
So if the virus is admitted in a way that could be transmitted through the air
It was come around the side of the mat
It's not yet cleared this is the means by which the virus is primarily or even the largely transmitted but if it is
The master won't really help
With that
However they are very helpful
If you're already sick
As they will be pretty effective than catching droplets on the way out of your
People who are sick should wear
Sister out in public that is definitely true
And if it's the case that people can be contagious when they are asymptomatic which looks like it may be the case
Then it would make sense for people to wear masks
Just in case
The focus of Mike's angle is wrong
If you're promoting people wearing masks for their own scent like as a self-defense mechanism
Sensical
It really only makes sense
Is a public health measure
Which seems
Public Health
I don't know he's a pencil but it seems to not be at all the way he's presenting
You should wear mask because it'll make it less likely you give something to someone else
Write what his messaging is is the same as the f****** chloroquine Scituate
Nation where it's like
All you're going to do right now
Because we don't have enough
Is dry large number of people who
Who have a large
Amount of resources
Into buying masks
Keeping them out of the hands of people who don't have the
And then we wind up in a worse off switch
Situation
Quite quite likely
F****** infuriated an idiot
And I see this
So there's a great piece in the Atlantic by Ed Yong that just came out about the mask issue and there's a lot of new one
The medical record
Invoice creator
The medical necessity of Grandmasters not really Atkins
Consensus but there are a lot of side issues
They're positive
It's to the unit like the idea of universal mask-wearing like
Increasing the stigma that someone would feel wearing a mask if they are sick
Take the disease seriously
But they're also downside
Like the fact that most people don't know how to wear
And they often end up sconce
Bentley adjusting InTouch
No masks
Which leads them
To touch their face more which is one of the main things you're trying not to do
It's more complicated as a picture
Then just saying everyone should wear masks
I'm being like I'm the help Ranger I did a great job Alex give me a check
Prairie
What's less up for discussion is that there are
Aren't Enough masks
To go around right now
Is there any advice that involves essential
If medical workers are having a difficult time finding
Masks
Then it's not a great idea to
Encourage everyone to continue buying up masks
Unless you're also able to simultaneously
Seriously boothby immediate supply of said mask
One thing that I find very interesting is that there's no part of Infowars model they can really thrive in the
The context of rational
Everything needs to be pitched in a way that
It's likely to create runs on product
Alex else's food bucket
By saying everyone's out of food which is meant to cause a hyperinflation
Demand
Alex's reported on chloroquine as a documented miracle cure Lucy no shortages of the drug
Locked up
In this episode alone Micah saying that the country needs to be flooded with zing
But everybody needs to be running
Richard everyone took his gospel would absolutely lead to runs on both product
I'm not saying that these dudes are causing these runs
But their business model is really only Built to be profitable when they're able to exploit and ride those way
And I think that's something that's worth
Maybe isn't all that clear except when you're in
Situation
Yeah it does
That is a really really good point
Because yeah it seems like they exist only
To prop up Bubba
And then float to the next
Like they sit on top of the bubble it explodes and by the time it explodes they've already jumped onto the next
They're they're the credit default
Flops of human be
Like they're disgusting and awful in their kill
Yeah it's like it's like the wrong interpretation of that quote like a comes
The Affairs of man that
The tired I don't know exactly how it goes I know Shakespeare quote but I only know it from Woodhouse no I don't
T Jefferson said
About what
So also Snopes didn't
Say don't wear masks they were just reporting on what statement
Since we're being made by officials
One of the sources cited in the article is
Not yet the biking
Alex's hero Donald Trump
Who said quote
I'm sorry this really article quote
Said Tuesday that his scientific advisers may clear the general public shouldn't be competing with hospitals and health worker
Crews were scarce masks of any type
His solution
Use a scarf if you want
Trump said at the daily White House briefing
I don't know what was the twist
25th Amendment
This it was for this right I can't find any Snopes articles about hydroxychloroquine being bad
Never say that because they are idiots and they realize the drug
Has other real uses
The only real article I could find to cover the subject is about Hannity and Rudy giuliani's claim that this mysterious.
Doctor it successfully treated all of his coronavirus patients with hydroxychloroquine and z-pack and zinc
Ncvps
Google doesn't say that the
The claim is not
True
Just that it's unproven
Which is exactly what the doctor at the center of this claim dr. zelenko said
In an interview with forward zelinka acknowledged that his regiment was new and untested
It was too soon to assess its long-term effect
So cool awesome great work man these guys
Snopes isn't saying the word masks are bad
Or that hydroxychloroquine
His Bat just these are not
Settled Quest
And a new one
We know Alex
Fucken hates nuance
It's really bad at it
And this is how he behaves
Concept of
Anyone reporting something with
Out making something up or
Using it
Is so horrific
To him that he he
Eat it like
It's so off
That he has this Burning hatred like
The idea of Snopes
Feeling like we're just going to quote people who say something in response
That's all we're going
We're not going to make up anything we're not even going to
How to give a point of view or
Like that
I mean that's one part of it and then he's
Constantly on the wrong side of it
Yeah that's true
His the scourge of his
Existence is fact-checkers obviously
They're always going
Go to be animes
Whatever the case we're done now with this sex
We're going to get him something
Completely different
And as a transition
We have Alex
Coming back in from break
And I'm going to apologize in advance for this because I think this
It's going to traumatize some of our listeners because of the music choice
Study hard using
Cuz it's usually we've seen a lot of him doing the over
The sax You Belong To The City doing a little speech
This time he uses Policy of Truth
RealFlight for the
But
Mike down for this
Because Alex gets into a weird fantasy
It makes me think that maybe he's been playing Castlevania
Policy of Truth
I love it I love it
What you said
Welcome back ladies and gentlemen welcome back.
Like this stupid
Stuckey's jerking off just mumbling to himself about fighting a vampire
Oh my God I just watched The Ninth Gate
How did The Policy of Truth
I think he did just watch The Ninth Gate
It could I was that girl who's the devil
Yeah I had red eyes
Are there are the castle at night
He's not scared
That movie is about books
Castlevania the game
The Netflix anime
Based on the video cuz I totally end
Absolutely
That's just
Castle in Highlander I'm going to mark that off on our big
No not yet I just like the vibe there is like someone I wouldn't
Want to hang out
Baby
Anyway
We get into Alex
Doing a part two of the
And it's much
Sillier
Yes it is what's Billy because I see an overall
Atar baby
What the f*** I'm studying it
No you don't
The whole thing's bad
Maine
What it does is destructive in the end
They're really into it
Videos p***
Because it's not what we doing
Personally talked to a lot of other people and got love for you have amazing Sports
And for
Pee tape is real
There's something about
Fortune
Treasure
Y'all call it a fortune.
Because it makes the air in this magic entry
Always thought we just wake everybody up
And
It just sucks
The energy and end the immediacy of everything
What's the plan
And as one goes we all go and all this stuff you'd imagine I'm called
You'd be chanting
So it's clearly queuing
F****** funny
Alex's apparently now mad
And I checked in with the guys over qanon Anonymous to see if something that happened recently
They had no idea
It's really funny to be about this is how trance
Paradis
Alex wants his audience to think that the reason he's buys because
Asiop it's working against these political goals but that's absurd
I'm listen to Alex's show the whole stretch of time that you anons existed
And it's very obvious that he hates qanon because he was unable to funnel them into his Revenue stream
Starting a fight
Like this right now or being like I'm going to start cover in this
It leads me to believe
That he wants
Alphabets
Yeah he wants he's looking
For some attention out of this
And he's going to try in
Metaphorically cut a chip out of a homeless person's arm
About this
The feeling that I get
This is a stock
It seems a little bit like
He's trying to start a fight
Feud with Joe Rogan in order to get back on the podcast but
He just ate like he's trying to call out whoever says they're cute and see
We will get on it
You need to hold on to those thoughts
But what's interesting is like I've listened to the show like
The forever and I know that back on January 6th
Alex literally told his good buddy Joel skousen
But he attempted to and wanted to co-op
Qanon I remember didn't work
Has ever come true
This is a pure disinformation expert
And
Sammy a lot of trump supporters including mices with some of my subscribers
Publicly
Because before chapatis it's definitely a delusional
Sucking up so many good people
Yes
Here is my Play
I was going to take over Cuba
Who is Kyo and then
Until all of qanon dum-dum followers
That it's my
Yes I was just going to use the name that's very popular to put out by own things
Straightforward
Straight-shooting
For sure
Absolutely historically Alex has been able to piggyback and monetize all of the hard right
Fringe movie
That have come along because he's always been the biggest game in town
And prior to social media he was able to be very secure in that position
He situated himself as we head to the 9/11
Truth folks
He's able to use the Oath Keepers and
Connection to them to co-op much of
The Tea Party enthusiasm that bubbled up
The 2009. And then purchase
Top of it
Who's able to frame himself
The king of all sorts of reality defying
Conspiracy theories that were popular online
Like Sandy Hook
In the Boston bombing
But now
Alex is not needed
Do not exist
Entirely outside of Alex's world
And they don't like him
Is there was a diamond it for Alex
To support or play along with this s***
You probably be doing that but since they're hostile to him
He knows that this is not a fertile market so f******
This is so funny to me
I think it's probably mostly just a result of Alex's interview with Ted Nugent's wife
I think there's Fallout do you think she got mad at him or he got mad
So funny I think maybe
Animals are real
Wife is Super 8
Might be
Oh man
What can you imagine
Look this is the first time that I'm really feeling a lot of empathy for Ted
Stuck between his wife and qanon on one side
And Alex Jones in
That's brutal
What what relationship do you choose dad
Neither is a Alien versus Predator situation
Whoever
Predator By the Light song
Where you talk about Hobbies Frederick
He is a sexual predator
Accident care about that though
No not important
So Alex is
Pretty mattock you and
Good things about you
Like it that you know people who are into it like to do research
Which is laughable
The whole cute thing cuz I know and it
Don't give an
Example
Don't do it
It's going to be bad
Don't
Stop
Lockstep Rockefeller
Billboard 200
Population
These are real things you going to Library read online
Eco science
You actually can
Sterilization
35 years later
37 years later
What else you got
Me and
So again it's the same sort of things like
Yeah I looked this lot of enthusiasm among these people but they're not
Pushing my you talkin
Points
Makes me angry
Yes and there's a lot of meat and potatoes on that like there's a lot of meat and potatoes on the bowls and f***
Pinhook 80's in their bank account
Becoming a potato bowl and I'm pissed off
I would like meat and potatoes
But obviously that's one
Very very clear piece of this thing
It really piss
But there's a second piece of this and I think it might actually be more what's driving him
I think
One of the reasons why I suspect
But this has to do with Ted Nugent's wife
Is that this seems
Kind of personal okay
Okay it seems like
As we go through Alex's grievances with qanon
A lot of it
Seems to revolve around the idea that people think you anons real but Alex doesn't get enough respect
It seems to be like
Do it likes me as much as that
The number one thing I hate about qanon is that they're trying to
Co-op cat scratch
Fever and I can't have that in my house look accused Stranglehold
Doesn't Rock
I cannot meet up with her
It seems very Petty
It's just
Insanely Patty
Reviews of Patti speech
Satisfied on the street whatever
Knowing that what I write when I say gets taken and put in the present speeches
President called my wife
Your husband's a real man got a lot of currently going through down
For real I'm real men like us know the truth identity of America press the attack remember your name right now
And it's Tylenol
Hanging out
Play one America News Network
So
At what
Call Patty Tucker
Whatever man I don't give a s*** like
The whole thing is all just like
Comparing himself
The qanon
Crazy about it is the way
That's start
Is Alex being like I have people that I know come up to
Tumi who are into
You are not like you're not cute level
These are your friends man
Sure is your friend group better
He's not capable of curating a
Don't get mad that you're not as cool as Q with your friends
Fridge
Whole God
But it's worse
Oh no
Asian people
Are you still at Alex Jones but now I'm with the president
90 Jones the hell does that mean
Embassy to Jerusalem
Exactly
Criticism of Israel
What two of them
For Israel
Proud of the fact that I am totally independent
Modern Talking Points that were adopted
President and his speech writers
America
Doc my house yesterday and called it a fake police
Your address was in your DUI report
Border
Metro
Audience of America
Freedom like 50 dudes
Give It Up
We've changed the world 1776
Bohemian Grove
Information
L.a. local
Austin original
Instructive but that does seem to be
So I would
Translate that entire thing by like
Qanon says
My dick small
My dick
Large
Very much
Trump and I talk all the time
About how big my dog is
This is just
This is so personal there's something so personal to it
Besides
One complaint
Gets into a petty grievance begins with like
Friends around me are in 2 Q
Cousin comes up to me
Who knows
Man who's just pursuing his dream
One can only hope he's somewhere in Chicago by the way
Buckley
I swear in this quarantine workout
You're listening
Scott hope you are
Confused
The fact that it's like so presented as like people in his immediate vicinity
We think that he's really just mad
At people around him not giving him the respect that
He feels he deserves
In comparison to this
Internet
Hoax yeah
No does my note and let me let me
Just read this for you
This is just sad
Double underline
Sad
Pathetic
And I wish it was an April Fool's Day
And I'm not positive it's
Not
By the way it is positive
The feeling isn't right
That's 100%
Yeah
He uses his Petty voice I love it when he gets that stick
Mikado to him
What he's with people
So don't
Man
What people tell her
Is that Alex's real
Don't respect him enough not truly believe in you are being tricked by trolls
In many of the same
Internet message boards Alex gets tricked by trolls at
Somebody could get hurt
My biggest problem the two people isn't always you know
Crazy
Manipulative
Mental illness
Manipulate
With a Q on his DeLand
Father telling you not to this year and last year
Robert
Nothing
Walking the president
On your wife up telling her how great you are
I am not God to a master of the universe but he's so mad
Dan
These people are all out here with these internet trolls they're all doing this for fun
I do it for money
I just
Here
Like it's always bad
I guess what's really in
Sing to me about this is like obviously there is a headline
It's easy to write on this story and that is that Alex takes
I am at 2 or not
Alex is a loser little titty baby
That's should be the headline headline explanation
Take me to Alex feel slighted by internet conspiracy
Alex
Completely refused Paul Joseph Watson
Buy something that he can't control
This is outside of his ability and he's dealt with it okay to fact that you can't control it over the course of
As long as you hear
Seems like right now he
Is coming up against something there's some sort of a crisis Maybe
He needs a flashing attention-grabbing publicity stunt and
Trying to get into a fight with a
The fake
Thing yeah
Is probably
Way to do it
I don't know it is
It seems death
It seems attention
Grabby
In all rooted in
I'm at
It does it does get
The feel of like the
The young at the old
Like it like
Isn't it in Nevada
If you are a conspiracy theorist
Famous enough
For long enough
That eventually you will be
The subject
Checked of the very
Conspiracy
That you are pretending
I'm not sure if ever later are going to be like
You're nothing you're
Part of the thing that arkan
Yeah I'm not right is that Alex has ever turned Bill Cooper into like
A villain it is
Conspiracy narrative
Yeah yeah and lied about their relation
For sure it we talked about that in one of our past episode
Yeah maybe maybe Alex have
Used to have the class
To not do that. Turn bill into like
A villain
But he's not getting that treatment
Woman qanon like I said like it one of the most important
Things about it is it
Exist outside of Alex it doesn't need Alex
And it has the freedom to be like
Open Shelf
That guy
Pay
Naive
Actually the most accurate think you is ever done distressing Alex
So as we get further through this when we went to commercial break their I thought like well he said his
He's done
Holyshit he's not even close to done
He is so mad at Q
You know I had the founders of cute at my house about two years ago I mean to you
And
Started out just as some guys having some fun that were authorized to engage show
Us intelligence
I'm just going to call him and ask him to come on it's on the song
Yeah okay yes
So Alex is here saying that the founder of Q on his
He almost hired him reveal to anyone
Alex has already claimed many times has fake intelligence whistleblowers act as part of
Fatimid started Cuban.
He's already solved this mystery according to the in-world reality
Unless he's just trying to get
Zack back on the show this doesn't make any sense
Me too hard
This is not an open question I've already done this with Zach
Of course but don't worry about that
Woop woop exacticide I'm writing down people who could have been
I'm I'm going to go with
Rodger Stone
Could be the only person that I think that Alex Wood
If I can call him and get him on the ship
But he's not going to actually call whomever fake
The Q is now that's true
So I think
Who has the like
I wouldn't be surprised if
Steve pieczenik had the balls to
Did you take that swing a bit
You know Alex I started
Soulmate
Steve is one of those two guys
Maybe it's time that we need to call inaara our friends over qanon anonymous
Did they have an expertise in like who might be hated
By qanon
Who could possibly be the the people who started it right
You know but then had it taken away three days
The 3D
Is very specific
I don't have the kind of expertise that someone like Travis does we may need help
You know why you don't have the
Because Travis is cute that's what happened Travis went to Alex's house three days later to Worcester
Stolen from him he started qanon anonymous
Done I've solved it this Travis call it out this could be truthful it out Travis
Baby we'll check in with them and see what happens
Miss you here
Is there
Alex knows who started qanon and
Weird
Gets job offer
From him or something
Who is wrong all the time now but work for those 3 days or something
About to go off this week for 3 days
The power go off in one town I can always go there
No matter how many times I still plan
Promoters going to come out and arrest everybody
I started it
Inside the White House on Air Force One
What do you think about a tweet about you today
Traffic
Go ahead
Dan scavino
Why did you do that as well yeah
Oh man
From them
Why
The very person.
The devil
Can't stand it
I tip my hand a little bit early
That I revealed that the person who created it now is attacks concert
Play by Q
Which is a clue to who it is and I don't f****** know who that I don't know cute excuse
Just about everybody
But anybody who's not to onboard with the quote Uncle plan
Yeah I have to act
It is so sad to
Send to a man described his business
This model angrily when somebody else is using
Nothing that you say comes
All of this stuff is a hoax perpetrated
Pulpit
Look at you
Talking Mirror
I think that's why he's mad
That is because like they're just doing what I do and everyone liked is
So into it they don't
Respect me and I'm kicked off social media you have speculum
But a dick
It is
It is so much like the the older brother that
Gets in trouble
And what did he does stuff to he does stuff to why isn't he getting in trouble
In my experience with the older brother that works
Alex is not going to work
Stickman Q lies
Saul eyes
Yeah but sometimes
DJ clock
I understand that it's not okay just information is sometimes necessary
Exactly
But you know what it turns out Alex's
Not capable of that
That's
Physically incapable of lying
He is just
What naked balls walls
We're on I mean it's just you know
Cool swords artifact
I see through fog
Because I live in
Sometimes I'll try to shelter TJ Clive for a counterintelligence
What are you doing
Nobody kurupt
Even
Say things now
That that that that that
Filter or manipulate
That's what a liar would say wow
I can't I can't I can't
Magic
Alex thinking that he's on
Honest about everything
But whatever
Proposed
The news
Police force
People who love war
I'll get together
Me like me and a bunch of my library and fat friends
A couple lips
Professor is in Willow just go around me like
If you don't
Mean what were the Mets
Get to use those word that it
All Alex gets
Are definite article
Call Steven have a
Ann and the Bee
I feel like a king
Feel like your fantasy is sort of out of The Phantom Tollbooth
One of the Kingdom
Alright okay
The weather bu B
I want have some bad words
So Alex knows the secret of Q he knows
He knows who's behind it
He knows all this
It's all good
And
In this clip Alex says something ends up saying something that I think is like shockingly
Spiritually true
What's so
Stupid
More than most people ever know
Do you think Pentagon the CIA
Almost everybody else couches what they're going to say
People are scared
Sting's and
They think about think that's called preparing
Yeah
Work
I mean I guess
I was just saying that he's not afraid to not prepare
I mean not to go even further
That it you know I mean when
I think I think of the the old that the adage
Compassion cruelty
Honesty without
Compassion is cruelty
Describing a lot of people
Think about how this is going to make people feel
And I'm a truth-teller I don't give a s***
No you're a piece of s*** you're an a****** honesty
Church was honesty without Grace
Yeah
Cruelty absolutely
On one level you're absolutely right that is manifesting
Concrete level
He's just trying to rationalize why he doesn't prepare
I agree people come in and they think about what they're going to say now I just shoot from the hip cuz I'm not scared
Like no you just
Can't do work
You can't
If you did you'd have no excuse for why you're wrong all the time
It's just nonsense
Do you work if he wanted to be a
Armor maybe he
Could learn how to
Hill
I don't think he can do journalism
Yeah sure every skateboard
Manual labor
Capable of the brain labor to just is unwilling
Heidelberg
You just unwilling I think maybe there was a time when he was
I still think he's perfectly capable of it now we just
Far more profitable to function the way he does
Totally that this boy
So Alex talks more about how he knows the creators of cues about
Two people we know that they're they hate what it's
Become an are demonized
Hillary by qanon
And
Is Realtors real trouble
Two people that
Created it
Political operative one
Zach
Spanish
Both of them
Oh wow
Imagine being the creator of it and watching it
I feel like that is something Alex is very smelly
Said right there eating a fan for you Alex
Add stop
I think if there's a lot of specifics there and
We're not in a position to really know who who this is
Hinting at but it's definitely him to get somebody that probably is very
Well
Determinable like if you weren't really into qanon I bet that you know almost exactly who Alex
Probably talk
I think it's
Yeah
I wish I had that kind of awareness
But I don't have to call the boys
So anyway
F*** dude thing is that
Trump doesn't like
Right
I could not
Think of anything Trump cares less about
He doesn't like
I don't think he has an opinion about
WhatsApp
You love
Enforce these operations
Authorized to do it they were authorized to engage encounter operation
Quickly
3 days
But people still go
Looking for the magic moment that they're finally
So and Alex's veritiv Q is real for 3 days and then it was co-opted and since then
Trump is not supported
Makes no sense
As recently as March 8th trampas retweeting qanon related
Content something is
Really consistent habit of doing
On January 2nd The Daily Beast reported on how in the
The evening of December 27th 2019 Trump retweeted or quote
Tweeted approximately 20 accounts
Who promote qanon
Conspiracies
Trump invited qanon people to his social media Summit
He invited Lionel to the White House and he's done basically everything he could
Possibly do to amplify and encourage qanon followers
Short of directly saying it
True
In terms of the things that drop is publicly signal
He's giving away more tacit and direct support
Do not then Alex
And that's probably because Alex isn't useful
Anymore
If I were Alex I'd be pissed
But I probably wouldn't have ever gotten into the stupid situation
Ramekin
Competing with Aiken
Sweetly lunatic decentralized
Conspiracy theory
For the president's respect and attention
That's a bad place to be even if you win that
That's not a good time right now
You know there's
Just like
There's no way to know there's no way for Alex to have known Trump
Would just abandon people
Play stop
Yasser. Just no wait
This is out of left
It is not his catchphrase catchphrase
This has been a
Years-long
Decades-long commitment to lying and f****** over peep
No not at all
You know what this feels like to me
As I as we go through this instructor realizes a little more
This feels a lot like
Someone asking for a raise when they don't know if they're going to get
You know like you should never go into your boss's office
And ask for a raise if you're not confident enough that like they value you as an employee
DM
Do you know anybody who might have asked for a ring
I was also fire
Fired for asking
Can you ask for raise for a co-worker of yours
I was a little bit different
For a union Ash 30 in my situation it was like you realize
Is it like
If you get into that position where if you don't think
Like if you don't have a reasonable expectation that you have leverage
To get that right
You deserve
If you ask for it
And the answer is no
Then you got to quit
Or you got to accept it if you accept it
You can ask again without them having
That like
Your sanity that's a no
Cuz you're there but yeah there's that expectation
You don't want to get yourself into that situation because
The outcome
Other than getting the raise
Me and that you better be prepared
And Alex
Getting into a fight with Cuban on like this
Which
Is pointless
Stupid number
Situation where you're not going to
To come out ahead
Here cuz there is no coming out ahead
You better be ready to quit
Cuz you're going to end up looking like a dick
It is it is very erotic than Alex
For sure it's a running to me that Alex
You don't have any organic side, he doesn't have the fake side cover
Sorry I keep it
I find interrupt
Sing to be on except
No it's a Ratatouille that for somebody who's
Professed ideology is almost entirely about decentralized conflict
And the way that those
Types of groups can resist
Yeah leaderless resistance he has no concept of how to battle against
A leaderless resistance
He still thinks that there's a cute guy
He still thinks that there's somebody
To have a feud with
Do you know what I mean hypothetically there is
Cuz there's still someone posting
Askew
Really
Still like a hypothetical
Nothing but like
The point at which were at now like that the reality of qanon is so insane
Diverse
That like
You can't really take issue with like
Cuz you could be like a you guys are a bunch of idiots who believe the j.f.k. jr. alive
You still alive you got the wrong idea
He's basically become libertarian
It's not real cute libertarianism
Big EQ a bad name
Start a fight with that end up like
You're basically playing my God what if
Qanon became its own political party and we got to watch the
The primary qanon
The primary debates of just
Qanon people like we did with the Liberty
During debates I want the
Qanon
I can't imagine anything being more wild than
The most Libertarian debate driver's license
You just saying that like hey I think it's some people may be old people who can't see maybe they shouldn't
We want McAfee
Who are off track a little bit how you can imagine how that
Alex's just like
Like this
Losing gamble no matter what happened
Also
I don't believe him
I don't believe the premise that
He's
Yeah absolutely
But I feel like we haven't really been clear enough about that but I don't believe that he had the person who started
He could have hired
But anyway
Tissue is the Q started
Who is first 3 days
As a really good
Call up the guys
Created
Disability
Wrong
Like missed connections
Club America
And then
When out of the globalist
Tell you
The Alex Jones the enemy
Things like that
Forget it
It's just about how he doesn't like they don't like
Here's the easiest way
Here's the easiest way for me
Sure if you did know
Who actually created Q
That name would be all over the
While he's in a feud
That's exactly what
He would put the name out as soon as possible
And try and start a few there
Wow
Maybe
Baby
I think I think that's the only way for it's the only way for him to
Pruitt I cannot prove but like
Win in this circumstance
Have you been there
Is 2
Play that car
That's an interesting Theory and we'll see how this plays out alright
Alex
I mean he ends up spending
More than
Half of his'n
Entire show complaining about Q
That's kind of why I think it's an April Fools
That's it
It's a ridiculous amount of time he spends
Play Rio by Kia
To the point where he ends up going
Nicole's
And this caller that
This first one did you get
Kind of needs to reassure him that like
Alex you were the real cute
How old is if he take that definition therapy
Patriot with two level
Hey you're not far that is
If anything you're the real q and you have been for 24 years
Anonymous
You're lucky said you need to take this over you're the one that's
Okay
I believe you want to retire
Yeah no I mean he did
Now this
Bucket you need to destroy it
Yeah that's true
It's not it's not something
That is
Necessarily salvageable
Well for you it's not something that's Co-op
It has to be destroyed
Wright Senior Spear and it hates
It makes your a shell right maybe for Israel or maybe your intelligence or whatever
You know you're something that is naked you're a patriot
You know you have to destroy it you don't take that over now
You can't I don't know
It's too late
I'm trying to think of a way for him I guess if he tried to reveal that he was the True Q but nobody
Leave that
That it's too late for that now
Well I mean you already tried was that and don't cares
It's probably going to pretend that didn't never happen
But
So we know that recently Alex put out a series of bumper stickers
And one of them said I m q
Go to infowars.com
And
You talked about that a little bit here
A imq
Bored.com
Is it exposed in hydroxychloroquine really great didn't want you to know and make about real stuff that's awesome
Dungeons & Dragons
Live action role play for everybody
Kind of
And the people that created it are Big Star Wars fans
And they're real people
Did you create it
I like the idea that he sang this isn't live-action role-playing but
I put up bumper stickers that said imq and if people went around it just used my narratives
And apply them
To this fictional character
Richard kind of you live action role play
That would be great and it's not live action role play
So you suggested that the only way this should play out is that Alex just says the name of the person
If he knew it
It turns out there's another way that you can
Play this
Especially if you're really just trying to get attention
You know what
I'll just expose it
Deadline
What are we doing
Come out with it all or I'm going to expose the next Wednesday
It's a homeless man with a chip in his arm
Documents
What an apple pie released
Obama ran
Torture facilities inside China
And that
Blackwater
The time
Who you hired services
Secret information
No one reported in
Obama to prison for that
This is the real world right here
I think there was a five-second delay they
No idea what story Alex is talking about about Obama using Blackwater to torture
Cleveland China mostly because there is no story about this on infowars.com and I can find
80 corroborating information anywhere
Whoever assuming it's true why is Alex so into Erik prince who ran black
Why does Alex brag about employing ex Blackwater security
Everybody's got to work there were involved in clandestine torture sites
Shouldn't Alex be opposed to the people who are involved in that company blah blah blah who cares doesn't matter
So you noticed that bleep
And I went and found the video this here's what he actually
I've heard of that
This is the real world right here
Iris my life doing this
Breadcrumbs in horseshit
This is a real world
So eat the bread crumbs part is like a real
Specific you reference I think it's all just a big cuz he said horseshit
The thing is like
He can't
Swear
Radio feed
Right
He can't do that
Things like that
That will cause a real problem
And the fact that like
It doesn't really matter
Means he's not on that
How many station
I get the audio feeds to like pull these episodes from Genesis communication
Network
It is the fee that goes out on the radio
Whatever there are things that are blurred like blind
Like this
I check
On his own
A course
Nothing like this every now and again but like
There is also like the look on his face after he says wash it where it's like someone said in his ear
Lights out dude
Or something like that there is a look
That is kind of like
Cuz then he immediately jumps back
Calls
Go get office.
So he goes to a call
And this caller has a dumb Theory
About why the Chinese would release this virus
I like it
It's no secret
The China does not
President-trump
I need to be president
Successful way at
Stopping
From holding success
O'Reilly's
Mail-in ballots
Mail-in ballots are fine in Most states of the country
I don't
Look if your theory is that this virus was released in order to
Stop Trump's rallies man
Dear gone man you are far gone
I realize that we didn't even really take much of a moment to even talk about the fact that our
What's gave a week
For the
I thought you were I thought you were your calendar
Of course
This is the homeless guy in the computer chip we're going to be listening to
I guess
We might be able to livestream it as a text
This is my WrestleMania
Alex
Next Wednesday this is this is Wimbledon the French
Open and f******
Things that aren't going to happen
Wimbledon
Maybe three things
The person who started qanon coming out and being like well Alex force my hand I must reveal myself that's not how
Second thing that's not happening is Alex
Having a big thing on next Wednesday show
The reality and the truth
About the first 3 days of cute and absolutely
Good God that's so funny
It's pretty amazing
You're going to do it this
I believe I believe what he says that he's finally going to take down Q
And it's really nice of him
To give you a week
It's it's it's the exact same thing that you were you sore to touch down a bit earlier
And that is the thing with Rogan
And he even brings that up
Cuz I gave Logan a chance
Because you were trying to get
A media stunt out of this
The reason that you give that window as opposed to being like
F*** it here's the reality is because
To get coverage from
I mean you want to get coverage from Media Matters you want to get covers coverage from rightwingwatch and when I get people tweeting about it
You want to get people making
Fun of the fact
That you're doing this
Organic
Even if it's make
In front of you it's still
Free Press people going to do it in such a desperate position right now
I mean the position that we're in
Because of the lives we live at this show
I
I've made peace with the fact that I'm very excite
Mostly because I know it's going to be a duck
It's going to be Geraldo opening that to Forever
That says that's the perfect microcosm of Alex's
Career
We've got this big story coming up
Alright hey we're on to the next thing nothing
The last example of that was the microchips
In the people experiencing homelessness
And that leads us nicely into this next
Call
This caller asks about how we got how are we going to fight back
Against the microchipping
Agenda
Id2020
You know with microchips and digital tattoos they want to put them in
Is it anyway you can
Thomas Jefferson was asked
Virginia Commonwealth
He said my dear fellow dear fellow
Pacious
Repine
Psychotic
Make them feel good
Dum dum dum dum
He's editorializing on my court quite a bit and also that the Frederick Douglass quote
Because all the time we can't allow black
I'm stolen
So now you
Try to co-op my catchphrase
Is there
I didn't call out
I'm changing my catchphrase
I've danced
Is 20
Because I think
Alex might give given me a better version
We're now in the New World Order in the AI take over in the robot
Clone world.
Emerge
Apologies
Get rid of us to save the Earth
Transmission
Advanced knowledge
Sheriff
It's the oldest trick in the book
Immortality
It's the oldest trick in the book how old is Troy Coronavirus
Jesus
Alright
Alchemist Dan at the oldest trick in the book
The oldest trick in the book
Book is like easy scam
Selling something called
A miracle cure Dan
Wow
There is that
Also I think Reed 2020 baby
Maybe maybe better
I like it I won't say a word
It's up in the air I'm not sure how I'm going to go with it
B I feel like Alex's I like to let him guide me over and over again
Was prompted by my belief that Alex was going to
Which is evident
Blister
Putting something he did not do
So
Hello
I have the demons
Got to kill you
Immortality which is the oldest
But apparently it turns out
Cuz we're wrinkled
Cuz the demons don't need to just kill you or they
You know the people who were working for the demon
They could kill
Great
Get them all the way where they need to be
There's another step they got to torture you first course
Coming to kill you and your family today must kill you in a blood sacrifice
There's a lot of rules
About how this have to go down
Translate
Actual process by which you take a soul
I call that has to
What happened in order for this immortality to be achieved
Right but then you wind up in hell
Anyways
File
So here's my biggest
Demons aren't real
No
That's easy
Obviously there's a little pedestrian I apologize
Las Vegas
Is
If These people aren't amore
Then by definition
That means that these people who have worked for
Who are demons
In the past have died
So if you are working for the globalist
Now
And you are where the
People who have previously worked for the demon
Then you have to know that you are not going to
Get immortality
So why work for
For the globe
The problem with this
Conspiracy living more than a life
Cuz you have all those examples of all the
Rothschild's who have died
If you work for the glove us cuz you want immortality so
If you are now we're having I guess the way around it is
They believe that their go get this immortality from the demon
But it's all
Ally
I was like what's been around
I would like to say that that's an unreasonable response but knowing that we sees you
Believe Alex Jones
I have to say that there would be enough people to believe that they would
Ghetto immortality regardless
Given all this information that we have
Access
Very easy
B2
You know I talked to a demon
Then the demon be like hey
I got
Got 5 On It
You know I got you
I got you covered
You could be like
I don't believe you I don't think you're good for it. I think it'd be pretty easy at this point
Can't do it
You still holding five
Speaking about of people you shouldn't
AmTrust yes
Francis Boyle
Shows up here at the end of the episode
Cuz he has big breaking news right Sir Arthur Fry
Does not really have big breaking
What is it
He does really have much
But they're talking about
The
Alex wants to start off a conversation asking about these various strains of
Coronavirus
Francis Boyle
All of his information comes
From that Chapel Hill study from 2050
And he's so f****** out of line
What about how it now
Attack the testicles I mean they're learning more more
I'll let you know I've read at least 5 or so right but if you go back and read that ritual you are
Wuhan
So what
It has been weaponized
Francis Boyle straight up making this up about the 2015 study from UNC Chapel Hill
Title of that study is quote
A sars-like cluster of circulating back coronavirus shows potential for human emerge
You can easily find it on the website for the journal Nature medicine if you'd like to look at it yourself and Rita
Boil is claiming that the study says that they admit they put HIV in the fire
Pleat lie
The only time HIV comes up at all in the text
Is in this sense
Pseudo type
Experiments were similar to those used
It's those using an HIV based pseudo-virus
This is a section about the methodology of the study where they describe how they use pseudo typing to create a pseudo-virus
Which is to say that using exist
Backbone of a virus a new could affect human
And then combined it with a circulating coronavirus to see if the viral material could infect humans
If it was in a package that was known
Humans were able to take in
The reference to HIV even has a footnote
The boil could have followed if he was interested in under
Understanding the study
It goes to a 2014
Teen study titled quote reversion in advanced Ebola disease in non-human primates
With eczema
This is a study about if you both look it be reversed in monkeys with
The use of Z map
A similarly pseudo typed combination of
Antibiotics
The 2015 Chapel Hill study in no way says they combined Hy-Vee into this coronavirus that's a complete fabrication
Part of oil who should be stripped of his 10
This Behavior like
Really seriously reflect Horeb
On the University of Illinois
Who's still employees
Francis Boyle
Tenured man it's really hard to get rid of 10 years I'm pretty sure if you do this s*** it's not hard
Darrell hamamoto that it's possible
So you're saying that if he was playing a pink guitar we'd be better off than if he's lying about coronavirus
Memoto might have like agitated a lot more low-key
Equally against
Like I think he might have caused more trouble for the University
Yeah then like
Francis Boyle doing is
F****** embarrassing
Because he is an employee of the University
But it doesn't necessarily cause as much
The local tension Cher has
Whatever
Darryl was up to calling for a an honorary degree from the University of Illinois
For information leading to the loss
Francis Boyle
I think that you're qualified to give out that
Kyrie Freddy sure yeah
I didn't graduate from school myself butter
Also this virus is not the same
Is the current Coronavirus
Cyrus the virus
Study virus called shc014 Dash ma50
And if the current virus was similar to that one
Painfully obvious
Which is probably a good reason why no supervillain would do this
Only imaginary evildoers dreamt up by Childish weirdos
Whatever crap to plan this stupid
Which is
Yeah it's Sean Connery in the event
So Francis Boyle he seems to believe
That the United States
Always knew that this was a Biomat
Of course they did and they get into that a little bit in Spokane
Knox
Did Mario Kenyon RI believe
The National Security Agency and US military intelligence
Do right away
That
Offensive biological warfare agent
I came out of that all mouhon
Bsl-4
Fauci do it right away
All he had to do was crawling up on his computer
To find that UNC contract
Because he funded
98 his organization funded this along with NIH and FDA
No problem
Alex
That's over
Dumb
Poorly constructed poorly defended conspiracy that they're bitching
But
I mean
It's not news though to this is this isn't like
This isn't fresh
Right right it's just that today
There were reports
Fauci had to ramp up his
Security sure
Because of threats from weirdos
Yeah I mean
To be fair Francis boils be calling him a Nazi bio-weapon
How to say we live in the world now where it's like
Look if fauci came out and he was like look
I want all my critics to beef up bears
Security cuz I'm
Coming for you
That makes
More sense to me
That we're living in professional wrestling world
Call out France
Boil
Beefed-up you
Security boil boil how about you and I deleting the rent have a celebrity box
We live in what we have
Incredibly celebrated expert epidemiology
And we have Francis
F****** Boyle
You shouldn't even have teddy ready
Greyhound is a weirdo
The thing is
They like
I was really
Struggling
At this point in the episode
Figure out why Francis Boyle is back on that is a good because there isn't new information he just keeps
AccuWeather UNC Chapel Hill study another Cruise everything that it doesn't prove
And I kind of realize that
He's a prop
Alex
Terrorism
He's on record as the author of that he's
The whole nine yards so you want him inside her
Bad system you've got it you're not some foggy thing on a 410 board
This is almost like he's bringing them out to be like
This is what we got not like you're cute and all bulshit
It's it it really feels like he's
Look like
The prop in this play that Alex is putting honorees
Mad about
Still mad about you or not
Extension of Alex's anger Hakuna how long is boiled
Not that long
See this being like a five-minute interview and just being like hey
We've got the guy who wrote The Thing
Guys
Q has a
Brought you nothing
And then you don't have to worry about
Too long of course I'm sure
Loyalty
They talked longer than 2 like the like
You'd you'd wanted to just be like a little smashed like a little
Yeah
Feels like that
Because none of the information is really new
And some of it
F****** embarrassing
Like how
Boil
And Alex
Clearly understand the difference
Correlation
And causation can't reveal that information
When you're discussing
The Chinese military's assertion
That maybe the United States military when they came over
For exercises
Introduce the virus here
They understand the
NIH
Now they've committed these crimes
Another facing life in prison that's that's why they don't want the public to know the big No-No is that is man-made
The Chinese
Just for your viewers might have your viewers ask me about
US Army meet her over there and fed we discussing
Alex
Correlation is not
Zacian
So far I have not seen a direct
New York City
Interesting
This is so interesting
Because
No
These dudes are capable of this kind of thought if they want to
If I were If I Were One if I were one of their
Don't admit
Anyway you like Rob do in a deposition
Pretend you have
Have no idea what's going on
There's this Chinese assertion that the US Army brought the virus over when they were
Is there for an exercise Alex and Francis understand that the fact that the army people wear their dozen
Prove that they started the Opera
They realize it further proof is necessary because
Claim
That they're opposed
Terms of Obama selling
China the virus
7 proof is weiwei f****** lower
It's weird how that works out these Dum Dums are capable of critical thinking when they want to be and look
There's a pretty good example of
Like this is
Minutes later
Engineer interview them just being like no correlation causation fuk it
Said years ago Lookout Bill Gates
They releasing they admitted
Killing a bunch of people
Messed up and kills people I mean obvious
Operation
Certainly that.
Biowarfare
Mosquitoes
We coming out of
Fort Collins they special in u.s.
Labyrinth
To be fair there's more than a
Correlation causation problem with what they're putting
Unfortunate
You see you see that they're capable of that kind of critical thought when it
Comes to like
Rebuffing
Arguments
But they're opposed to but when it's
Trying to sell a week
F****** narrative
They're on board with
It doesn't matter there's no need for evidence
It's all bulshit
Yeah it is it is so much like
A very obvious
Asymmetrical Warfare game
Being played against people who care about real
And they just don't
So they get to they get to win
Because we're on their battle
Field not ours
And we just pretend that we're not well I think that most people aren't
On their Battlefield we are
A little baby got into
Dwell in this
Ugly Siri
I just mean in the far larger Outreach of right-wing
Is that it is
Never
Fully kind of comprehended by so many people that it is
Your liege
You are not like
When CNN has somebody on parenting
Trump talking
Climate denialism or whatever it is
You are not on equal footing
Doesn't matter if you're on single sure the matter of your on Fox
Snooze
They are going
To say Amy
Doesn't matter
It doesn't matter and is you try and pretend the fact check
King is important
They are going to rape
How it is
You know
I think it we can all
All agree
That the evidence is overwhelming
Bad sign about a bioweapon
From Barack Obama
You're a little bit after Francis is left
This is stupid
Economy has killed people it does
For not telling you the answer
We don't have these things
Thank
Americans are among children elderly people on the planet
The Democrats deep State attempt to suppress
Fresh these facts especially with the approved drug for
70 something years
Hydroxychloroquine
Still feels like a sales pitch
Search for the
I felt
Zink sales paper
Yeah it is has the same tenor in the same delivery that I was usually uses
But it's just like
It's like he's learning
Yeah the boundary
I can't actually sell my product
But I can do everything short of mention my product
I don't know if
Can
Its internal be interesting to see if anyone cares
I think would what fascinates me about
One of the great joys
We had early on in the podcast
You would play for me these things that I didn't know we're going to be at
Yeah and now what I'm enjoying
Is not knowing that there
Not going
To be at pivot
Yeah this is the this is the ad pivot that
Two years ago out of been like
And now he's not doing it he's answering me
Yeah a little bit
Scorpio from our April Fool's episode
Which I mean
I wish this was all a joke but it's not
So we had this
Last clip
Alex is earlier in the show said we're at war with China
It turns out we're also at war with Saudi Arabia I didn't know about
Amor Amor amor
Production
Our oldest Ally in the world
When I say
It's possible you can cancel the election civil unrest
Did not catch you off-guard
Never know what it's going to come
Almost exactly after you're talking about not being being able to see the activities, there's one
He snuck it in god dammit
Anyway we come to the end of April Fool's Day episode and whatever the f*** they have
The stupid
Coronavirus rationalizations
Incredibly
Nonsensical rewriting of trump
Oh yeah
Annie
F****** Cuban odd stuff
Is really where it's at
This is this is what I'm excited about
I don't know
That he was accused by doing the show sucks
I got really excited
Like a month ago
When Alex
It's for no reason decided he was going to start getting back into Seth rich
Yeah that was one day
Alex decided
We're get back in
And then
Oh I know who you are restarted qanon
Of course I'm worried about that but I want it
To be like the next chapter
Because I
Definitely don't want to just talk about coronavirus lifetime
Make about it
Interesting to talk of
About you
I also don't want to talk about all the same sort of
Arcade conspiracies
We talked about
In past episodes I got to watch
Just keep retreating old territory
Starting a feud
With a ghost
Is
F******
Awesome yeah I like that
What is
The kind of thing I want to see from Alex religious freedom angle on
Pills all over again
Kenworth like that's the
Fun thing to do right and he's going to fail you
Well failed you
Everyday
For three years
Standings
I made clear
Discussion
But I will never give up hope next time will be
The right time because otherwise it doesn't work
He ends this episode still like
Without
Negating
Ruining the whole idea that he's going to fight
The other episodes
That one
He blew it 5 minutes in it
It still seems like a Live question when the show ended
So hopefully
Fingers crossed we got a chance
Turns into a falcon fight
And it gets so stupid
Alex yelling it
Nonexistent robot
Twitter accounts
It turns into thing where they start f****** trolling him earlier
God
Can you imagine
Now I just want him to do a ghost
I just wanted to fight
Inna
What do you like
West Coast
I don't understand how you fight him
See that's what Alex
Busting ghost disease
Can bus go spell Marie
Bosco's
But they didn't fight
You know they didn't get into the ring with
Didn't really see what they were made
Going up against ghost in a fair fight
I would like to see you Alec see if you could stop
Could do it
We'll see
I guess we'll find out what happens with this
Amman
Next Friday's episode
Will cover his Wednesday episode
Going to be a mess
Disappointment
It just did this is like
Christmas for me
I want to speed up talking
I'm excited
The problem is I am excited
Even though I know it's going to be a disappointment
I love The Pretty Reckless
Really great if he pulled a computer chip out of a homeless man's arm
She does
I will retire I pray
I will retire but I will definitely give it up to my smelly pirate friend Alex Jones
So we'll be back
On Monday boo and we'll see what happens
With his show
Where you at it's okay
It's okay
Knocking at the window like Jiminy Cricket website
Girls on Twitter
We are Facebook view rate
Donate the patron I do the whole thing we love you we will be back button
Until then I'm Neo I'm Leo mdzs Clark I'm a guy who went to a castle and felt really cool listening
Depeche Mode and I thought someone with red eyes but I wasn't
Scared
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work