Damn important
I have great respect but knowledge babe I'm sick of them posing
MoneyGram
Knowledge vype.com
Everybody was making outside of death fix it around novelty Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex
Jones Jordan
I guess maybe I don't know if you want but Sunday is
Any weekends
I'm not sure
Thoroughly enjoyed the first it's still fun you know I don't know I was telling you about the Boneyard
Before we started recording I thought it was horrible watching it baby I'm out of the mainstream and that opinion but
It was fun to tell you about it
I guess there's that
I texted you was telling me that he loved it
I just thought it was cool.
Record against maybe so maybe I'm a little jaded
Get another crack
Maybe maybe I always go into Alex's attempt
To prove things with the highest of hopes
I will ask your night to WrestleMania also with like better what I'm going to enjoy watching a little bit of nut
Absolutely for me
King of the Raptor princesses John got me a very very
Generous generous gift
Aura trick me into giving her address
Is the BTK Killer
It could be that the abbreviation correctly there
It was an incredible gift
It came at a time when just blindsided me and hers is very very
Super cool food is not a gift for me but I'll still say thank you John
Slightly
Little more disappointing I will take
WrestleMania
The bright spot fight that's the challenge
Today we are going over April 2nd
2020 babies
I don't know didn't feel quite right by Felicity
April 2nd episode That's Thursday of last week
And I intended to do Thursday and Friday for this up
Episode but Thursday is just too
F****** insane
This is one of the weirdo rides we're going to go on
There's a lot of emotional ups and downs
Alex trying to prove stuff
Stairs
Factually inaccurate claim as theirs
Casus belli
Oh okay
Alright so we're just taking territory now that's all
DFI mean it gets that by the end of it
So get ready strap it in okay we will see
We make it through but before we get to that
Thank you so much you're now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Next
This could be
Zoetrope
Or Zoe
Propzy
Propst
Not entirely sure but either way thank you so much
Thank you very much thank you so much you and I hope all is well
Dallas
But style Evian thank you so much
Rachel
Thank you so much you're an alcoholic
Who donated an elevated level appreciate that very much
Google Andy thank you so much
You're now a technocrat and Sean thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
Declare
The showed like the sport with these Gents
Contour website
Sports people who are
Dunedin these drying difficult times we find ourselves in
Yes we would like
How are you there hello
But also
Okay let's not forget the real charity come on now
Play we're going to start on April 2nd at the beginning of Alex's episode this is a little bit of a longer
Clip for a first
Quit but I wanted to
Alex is insisting that this clip you plays of Anthony fauci
Is
Play me something
Okay and it's going to be like a guiding thesis for the episode moving forward
And it's not
It's it's pretty it's pretty lame
Yes this is at the world government bio attack we always knew was coming from the very Medical
Mad scientists led by dr. Faust
Are we looking at wedding with some sort of social distancing guidelines
Baseball games
Political conventions over the summer
Possible or safe
I think if we get to the part of the curve that
Berkshire
Yesterday when it goes down
Down to essentially no new cases Note
Had a. Of time
I think it makes
Since that you're going to have to relax
Social distancing
Thing we hopefully would have in
Place and I believe we will have in place for robust system to be able to identify
Play Summer disinfect
Isolate
Play them and then do contact tracing
Program of can
Payment
Prevents you from ever having to get into mitigation mitigation right now that's what they say
Distancing is the
Ultimate
The ultimate solution
To a virus
Might keep coming back
Would be a taxi
The weekly conference call with the
Who sponsored group
All the health leaders in the world
Dealing with this and we all came to the agreement
That we may have
Cycling with another season
Would be much better prepared we likely will have interventions
The ultimate game-changer in this will be a vaccine
The same way
Other diseases that was Sturgis of the past
Now we don't even worry about
Say 1 minute 21 seconds clip that you're going to hear me play probably 10 more times today on air because
Confirmation
It's all absolutely
So I don't think that proves
I did
Didn't get that first react not your take away that wasn't the thing that I was thinking about
Where this goes
I think you could predict where it go
I mean the clip of thought you was explaining makes perfect sense to an adult
But it's interesting
Because you know you listened to enough Alex Jones that
I think you can hear that and see the points where he's going
To take things well contact tracing I heard that and I was like nobody
You should be allowed to tell Alex
About contact
Have to wait from him
Certainly that's one thing you can point to like okay
Bunch of little things in there's like
Oh I see how he's going to manipulate this
That's a fun little game
At home
If you're listening
What is UNIX going to go on and we'll we'll see how you do and your prize
So Alex
Gets down into talking about how it psychology
Talk to you saying if there's going to be forced vaccinations that end up coming any sort of brambles
We got a divorce
Irises
Yearly injection of Coors
Yearly or monthly shot
Well and you criticize it anyway you're not allowed to travel you're not allowed to live
So Alex is severely misunderstanding what was being said about the future reaction to the coronavirus ND post distancing
The pre-vaccine landscape
Dr. fauci was saying in the in the clip that we listen to up top is it there are two distinct phases of response to an outbreak wear different style
Allergies or affect
When there are not many new cases of no real Community spreading of the
The disease you can isolate individuals who get sick
I can track down the people who they been in contact with
And have them also self-quarantine
Imperial for the disease of Pat
This strategy can work well in those circumstances but once there as many new cases and as much Community transmission is
Is happening now you have to adjust a mitigation Tech
Fix like what we're seeing now with social distance
Alex seems to imagine a world where self-quarantine will be used
Does punishment against anti-vaxxers or sub
Dumb s***
I don't know how he got that for
Southeast comments but I would bet that when this is all over the country is gone through this deeply traumatic
Experience together
If you're actively trying
To get people not to be vaccinated and risk all of this happening again I bet a lot of people will distance themselves from you Sophie
I don't think
Anyone will need to force anyone to I think we will tell you to f*** right off I don't think anybody saying hi.
Melissa McCarthy
April that mutations thing Alex has no evidence of reason to suggest that the coronavirus mutates more than fluids do
Just making that up but even if it were true it's not necessarily a good argument
Against vaccinations
You should have mutations and vaccines are not a clear-cut black-and-white issue
Alex wants you to think it's a thing where you make a vaccine against the coronavirus and then mutates them the vaccine doesn't work
Anymore but of course
Issues more complicated than that
For one just because of vaccine or a virus has undergone a mutation that doesn't mean that existing vaccine won't be effect
This isn't really a cure
Mutations that happen with viruses are random events
Send all the mutations that occur aren't really relevant to the immunity the vaccine will
Create
It's entirely possible they could be multiple
What strains of the coronavirus that are all prevented by the same vaccine
On March 24th the New York Magazine Intelligencer reported on how the coronavirus actually has very low error rate
We just say that it's mutating
Very slow leak
Considering how many times it's been transmitting a triplicate
Peter thielen a
Johns Hopkins molecular geneticists said quote
That's a relatively small number of mutations for having passed through a large number of people
At this point the mutation rate of the virus would suggest
The vaccine developed for SARS coronavirus to would be a single vaccine
Rather than a new vaccine every year like the flu
What Alex is really doing here is just some basic ass anti-vax stuff
Send it
Pretty uninspiring off
Yeah I hear slow
Anti-vaxxers stuff is a far more palatable whenever there's no massive global
And it going on right now anti-vaxxer stuff
Kind of feels a little bit more murderer
You know a little bit more on the side of like
Maybe unintentional manslaughter area steaks are becoming a little bit to avert yet
This is uninspired level levels of
The ship that Alex is doing well.
I want him to be a little bit more creative or crazy with his ideas but he's bringing
His basic ass s***
So what are the big things that everyone
Of course is being
Bombarded with it probably for good reason then
And well
You know
Justifiably
I is washing hands everybody and others
There's messaging
Wash your hands
Write a message that we're still struggling
To Grapple with
So Alex is mad
That they played a video
Elmo
Telling people to wash their hands
You can't say that to on Fox Business on speak those aren't words
It's very weird
Dave
Talking to adults about how to wash their hands
Thank you
Go ahead and go to this clip
Palomo
Call boy oh boy here and I think Alex just committed slander
There have been accusations backlash in the past and I'm not entirely sure what the reality of that situation is
But Alex isn't saying that there were accusations
Is a convicted pedophile which is not true
Demonstrable a false statement and Alex is reporting it as fact
Even if the puppeteer of a particular character were to be a criminal that doesn't make the puppet
Is the Puppeteer dad ventriloquist dummy is really rude
Play give you learned of the person who played Big Bird is a fence for stolen goods that doesn't affect the character of Biggby
Ridiculous
Alex is mad at the elbow positive
That's all we're all in
I'm not positive that video being played on Fox Business is trying to convince
Adults to wash their hands based on an elbow it might be reporting on that video is
Existing
I don't know anyway I don't really care
Who's going to be playing Elmo videos
Probably
His next move is where I got really excited cuz this opening today episode is not
Strong but
Like whenever he says he's going to
To prove something
I get pop and Alex
Excuse me
At ease
For the minutes coming up late
In the last hour we put together an extremely informative
Powerful report
That is going to Premiere here
But lays out
Admission
By The Establishment technocrats that by 2020 they would launch the biotech
F*** yes absolutely Alex is going to prove it
Of course he's giving himself an artificial deadline of I have a report that I'm going
Play it's already
Oh my God
You're doing the thing that makes me think he's not going to play
Play a dog no you can play okay but you should be making me think that he's not going to prove it
I never considered that as a possibility.
He doesn't up playing
But it's really disappointing but I always get really excited cuz it's like
You're trying now
Yeah you're trying
You have you have stated on your own without anyone for some
That you are
Ryan
You think this proves something
Therefore I can take it more seriously and oh boy
You have entered my
Right
So here is this isn't the actual report but it is another like sort of factual claim that Alex makes about
The bring in the world
We will have
No matter how much money and how much blood if
We will have world government
With money and blood
Fun Alex's nose
This is a little bit of a lie
Which inspires anyone because it's Alex Jones talking about a quote
One thing it's important to point out is that it doesn't mean anything for someone to say that something's in the Congressional Record
If they're saying that to say it
Proof that the real or proven
There are countless examples of weird editorials and opinion pieces that Congress people have just read into the record over the years
Not as hard to become a Converse
Yeah this doesn't make the things that they read into the record officially accurate it just means that someone in Congress decided to read them on the floor
My point is that if someone says to you it's in the Congressional Record record
Odds are very strong they're trying to pull a fast one on you
That is not a good like
Argument
Do you know what else is in the Congressional Record
Quotes from f****** Elmo
Sure
As for the actual quote Alex's referencing he appears to actually be mixing up
2 quotes
The first is a comment by James Warburg in front of the senate in 1950 which was quote
We shall have World Government whether we like it or not or whether or not we like it
The only question
Weather World Government will be achieved by conquest or consent
This is in the context of a speech about the need to create peace with the Soviet Union and about how international law and relations needs every positive ask
Aspirational goal
Because if that wasn't the focus
Things will remain the same
Say they will tend towards War
Yeah so we talked about this in the endgame episode I'm about to Greater Tampa that that that
Completely out of
Text somebody really close to
Post-war situation
Watching the
Korean War about
What's a breakout all over it
Was probably like
Baby let's War would be a good eye
Yeah yeah
The other quote is quote
We are not going to achieve a new world order without paying for it in blood as well as in words into money
Isn't that to come from an article by Arthur Schlesinger Jr in the Foreign Affairs a journal
The citation that's listed with it says that the article is called quote back to the womb
Isolationism new threat
From volume 74 number
Virtu of the journal
Jstor has the full catalog of Foreign Affairs available to you to read if you'd like
You find yourself like I don't know quarantine but whole lot of time to kill
So if you pull up volume 74 issue number to the journal one thing you'll find is that there is no article by that name
In it there's no article by Schlessinger Eve
That's because most conspiracy sites give the wrong citation
It's actually from volume 74 Issue 4 of the journal
And the title is actually back to the womb isolation isolationism is renewed
Fret very bad citation work here but
Anyway
First I will say that the quote is actually in the tech
That is fair
That's a good sign but we're off to a good start of course it's taken out of
The article is about the push and pull
In the United States between isolationism in internationalism
And how it seems like
Except when we're in a crisis that appears to
The directly affect us interest
We forget about International matters or any responsibility we may have to help
Facilitate worlds
Stability
Crazy thing for somebody
Well to be fair license or even
He said that makes total sense
From the piece
How to persuade the housewife in Xenia Ohio that her husband brother or son should die in Bosnia or Somalia
Or some other place where vital us interests are not involved
Nor is it just the Zenia housewife who must be persuaded
How many stalwart internationalist
In the Council on Foreign Relations
Would send their own Sons to die in Bosnia or Somalia
Dying for World Order when there's no concrete threat to one's own nation is a hard argument to make
For understandable reasons our leaders are not making it
Yeah he's saying it's like a it's a good dream but doesn't seem like we're doing it
You can't
Send people to die for strangers.
Despite the humanitarian reality
So here's the wider context of the quote about paying for paying in Blood and Money from this paragraph
Despite two Grievous hot Wars a draining Cold War and a multitude of smaller conflict
It will soon Envision is as far from realization today as it was three-quarters of a century ago
In the United States neo-isolationism promises to prevent the most powerful nation in the planet
From playing any role in enforcing the peace system
If we refuse a role we can't
Expect smaller weaker and poorer Nations to ensure world order for us
We're not going to achieve a new world order without paying for it and blood as well as words
Send Bonnie
The point he's making his at the dream of the peacekeeping system
Detached from material and concrete interest is possible for the United States but it's probably unlikely
Do.
Detroit isolationism
What was on the rise back when this was written in 1995
Pleasanton wraps up his Essay with this thought
Perhaps our leaders should put the question to the people
What do we want the United Nations to be
Do we want it to avert more Killing Fields around the planet
Or do we want it to dwindle into impetus
Leaving the world to the Anarchy of nation-states
Robinson's you might draw the conclusion that he superposed
Nation-states
But if you read a little further he says quote
If we cannot find ways of implementing collective security we must be realistic about the alternative
A chaotic violent and ever more dangerous planet
Maybe the cost of military enforcement are too great
National interest narrowly can
Extrude maybe the safer rule in an anarchic world
But let us recognize as we return to that womb we are surrendering magnificent dream
I would say that
He was way wrong they should say to the best I haven't seen any negative
Are you saying that there's been some intervention
Resume is that the world is
Violent conflicts where is it we are humanitarian they're fine what
If you just take the original quote I paying for the New World Order and Blood and Money
You do make it sound like the author's talking about the villainess s***
But if you read the full editorial you understand the
Text Maurice.
Alex's never read this article
He doesn't even know who wrote it
Is just seen a quote on some dumb blog he's pretending like this is from the Congressional Record this is just all a lie
Alex is just lying liar
I mean it's not really
Oh no I mean yeah absolutely I mean this is that hole
Yeah
Sure
So we've heard of the pass Alex comparing
Heavy coronavirus to the flu
Certainly I've noticed a little new thing
I'm here on the 2nd
Seems to want to compare to the common cold
A bunch
Doubedeesarai
Is ramping up on a comparison
Big World healthier
All these systems
I want to learn from you
Analogy
Here we go
You understand that the coronavirus is the most common virus on terra firma
Alright well that's out
Common cold you always heard you in my 11th manuals and studied
Call Nicole.
Fifty million people year globally
Stop.
Disabled
It is true that
The cold can be caused by viruses that are part of the coronavirus family but that's a severe over-simplification
Listen to try and pretend that this 2019 novel Coronavirus
Isn't it anyway really similar to the cold
It is a specific virus in that umbrella group
But that doesn't mean they're the same
Also the cold is caused by many other thing
Things like rhinovirus
Too humid Republican in name only viruses I expose
Talk to human coronavirus oc43 and 229e
Are responsible for the common cold or are ones that are responsible, code
Coronavirus nl63 is also thought to cause
Some cold symptoms but it's a slightly different situation
Hku1 is another virus that causes mild
Incentive the generally
How many of the big one
SARS MERS
I'm covid-19
That is it in terms of known coronavirus has that can affect humans
It's a big family of viruses but there were only seven that we know of
They can affect people
This isn't a science show so getting into the nitty-gritty details over to probably beyond my capabilities but there is no attacks on
Coronavirus
And this is just one family
They sure distinctive characteristics like the fact that they have single stranded DNA
But Pastor similarities there's a pretty substantial differences between the just like the Huxtable
One of the problems with Alex's claimed that about the deaths from a common cold is it there's no way he can have a good stat on that
Cold and flu symptoms are often in almost indistinguishable
You're not going to be able to find isolated numbers of deaths caused by the
Common cold
From sources I was able to find it appears that those numbers would most likely be lumped in with quote
Influenza-like illnesses
Stats that Alex already uses
Report regularly
What at least three viruses that can contribute to
Common cold like symptoms even more
You could die of the common cold that's like saying
You could die of any virus that exhibits
That's causes humans to exhibit common cold likes
And just say that that's
The common cold symptoms
Yeah that's a problem for Alex's
Bulshit
So Alex gets back into talking about the virus
It's killing men
What else would it be
I think he's
Getting back into like scepter and sell his in
Specific
Set of Chinese man
Asian man
Race specific
Statistics today
You forget that
Weapon
You have to be deficient
Get the f*** out
Vitamin D
Vitamin C
Some of the data is tending to show a higher incidence of men being folks have died from this virus
Burly for anyone
Glue myself
Alex to definitively say they know why that's
McKay's
The earliest numbers morning this Direction came from China where they showed a 2.8 fatality rate among men compared to a 1.7
Rate among women
The first hypothesis that was offered was that men smoke way more in China
So this might be the cause
An article in the guardian site to stat
50% of men in China smoke compared to only 2% of women
Whoever is data is coming from other countries this loses some of its
Potential explanatory power
And Italy more men than women smoke but the Divide isn't nearly as
Because it is in China at the trend of more men dying of coronavirus still hold
Numbers are showing the people who smoke are at a higher risk of having severe cases if they could check the virus but it doesn't look like a
Good explanation
For the difference
The death rates
An article in the independent quotes Angela rasmuson the virologist at Columbia University who pointed out that this differ
Death rates was also observed in the case of SARS and MERS
Might be a distinct feature of coronavirus is in general
Right now no one has a good answer about
But in time or information will come out
Hopefully he'll be better understood
The answer is just a y chromosome
Boo you could there might be a chromosomal I don't know
Yeah
For Alex to come on his show and pretended he knows what's up here is basically I'm saying the understand science better than literally all of the
Scientist in the world which is
A little bit full of
Humorous as he pronounces it here is my pet
But then again
I don't know of any scientist for the cogitate like a couch
That's true
They are they generally cogitate differ
Currently been through
I think here's where we go
Here's what you bring back now that you
You got the men die more
Bring black the fluoride in the water Dan
That's where you go with it fluoride turns with the frogs gay
That's why men are weird
Men for years now Dan and he's right all along like a little fluoride gassed up
Appearance later but
Yeah I don't know I don't know he had to lean into it could make that work
A little complicated
So the rest of the clip I think he's just trying to sell his ink
It's an interesting strategy and I wonder if you can get in trouble for aggressively selling one of your product
Because there's ink in it
Then stopping doing that and pivoting to just presenting the zinc is a proven prevention for the virus
I wonder if that's
Trouble
All I heard there was
4 people in a room
And two lawyers
Is and them coming up with different strategy
No
Worse
Maybe that'll work I don't know give us
I'm done here
Anyways I'll just get more billable hours who cares
So his next step is bad science
My favorite 80s movie
And then a weird ramble
It's on record
Manufacturer of virus
30 40 50 60 replications down
That's not possible
Even between Syfy
Don't be silly
I said
At least
Drop your weapon
It doesn't matter it's here to take your rights
Officially
Coronavirus coronavirus Alpharetta
Government would just say somebody died from
You're a hero
They didn't jump out they jump
Victory to the side
Clear lag
Make sure the local pool and they got rid of the diving board and all the king's horses and all the king's
I don't know why that's the analogies do them to make because many pools still have died from Florida
They're diverting don't understand
I don't understand the Lincoln is brain even shut down the government didn't make anyone stop having diving board
The government suing anybody decide to sue whoever
Like the pool
This has led to some people choosing that it's not worth the risk to have a diving board or not wanting to pay for liability insurance for diving
What related injuries
That's a factor
Publican at home pools
Like but it's a choice you can still make if you want to this I don't understand
Pennywise
Scientists can't predict what mutations viruses are going to have that's absurd
These mutations are caused by random errors in RNA replication which isn't necessarily A predictable process
To be clear there are a certain number of replication errors that can possibly do you know it is
There's only so many
Play suspicious replication errors
In one cycle of replication is possible one out of eight
Honda of possible areas could be made
What is a giant number of possible mutations in any number of them
Possible so I don't know how helpful
It is
Incredibly stupid for one very
If you know what
Mutations that
I could make 50
Replications down the line
Yeah
Suggest that when you create the virus
You knew how it's going to Beauty
Giving you a depth of knowledge that would give you the ability to
To keep it from you today
Well
Deem the correct
If your goal is to get it to where it is 50 mutations later you would just release the 50th you thinking
Later or if you wanted it to achieve a goal you wouldn't want to commute
And do some
Write the strategy is stupid and it doesn't make sense
There are there are some caveats just because like me saying scientists can't predict these things
It gets into like
Complexity
And I don't want to just make that blanket statement
The scientists can use the principles of natural selection to guess what sorts of mutations would be favored by nature to be more
Successful
Have you tasted that would make a virus less debilitating for example and make it more likely to be passed onto new hose
Do you expect that in the case of that kind of a mutation happening
It would be, more prevalent strain of a virus
What I want to talk about is the idea that scientist engineer this virus because they knew how it would end up you dating which is just not within the
Arrange wood signs
Can do in the real world
They can take an existing virus and with some accuracy predict what sorts
The medications would be the most success
It's just not even close to what I was saying
Because he's just making s*** up
Most importantly In that clip Alex is saying that the virus is very bad and
It keeps coming back
This is a direct contradiction to his narrative from March 24th
This year where he was saying that it wasn't a big deal
If you get any dinner just could be sick for 9 days in your gut that was forever
It's really important to recognize that Alex's narrative make no sense when combined with each other
You simultaneously telling his audience of his no big deal he getting sick for a little bit
Please go back to work
And he's also saying it's a horrible bio-weapon that affects your body and keeps coming back
These are incompatible and Alex should be able to do stuff like
This to his listeners
And nobody's going to stop him
Sure
So a given textbook we learn that Anthony fauci
Is bad news
Someone might die
Coronavirus
So we will
Head officer
Running this
Oprah
Operative
Jumpman
Amazon
Conduction Beyond
Cloud
I'm somebody else's
Freedom
I mean
Okay so Trump is
Trump is a globalist
Trump is officially working
Trump is no longer the strongman powerful their leader that he wanted my man my man
Nothing matters
I'm honestly shocked at the accusation that fauci works for Bill Gates hasn't come up yet
I'm shocked it took this long to
That seems like a real no-brainer considering is the head of the National Institute of allergy and infectious disease and a ton of the Gates Foundation
Philanthropies around issues of infectious disease
But I think Alex is getting things a little twisted
The National Institute of allergy and infectious disease is a government agent
It's funded by tax dollars
It's not grants for Bill Gates
It's one of the Institute of the National Institutes of Health which is contained within the Department of Health and Human Services
The National Institute of allergy and infectious
Disease is really the same kind of lame as the Gates Foundation in that they both fun to research
That's pretty easy to connect fauci and Gates that way
A simple Google search will pull up articles about joint ventures between the niaid and Gates but
It doesn't prove it
Thought you got money from gate so that he works for him
I looked into it a little bit and I don't really see what so suspicious about their connection so I consulted right-wing blogs to see if I can get
The better sense of what the proof was
Payroll first shift
Wauconda post on Alex's buddy top Hertz website National file tote
Titled quote
Talk to you in Berks both have big money Bill Gates come
Conflict of interest
The pap smear if I ever
Something I thought was really interesting was that the image they chose for this post was just a Bill Gates
When it's super
Super easy to find a picture of how she and Gates
Together
No idea why they didn't use that for heightened effect
That is kind of
Or lazy
Lazy was the word I was
To hear that this blog entry sets
Gates has a lot of pull in the medical world he has a multibillion-dollar relationship with dr. fauci
Fauci originally took the gates line supporting vaccines
And casting doubt on chloroquine
So there's a claim with you there's any proof
Lied
This is as close as the article gets to prove
They are co-funding the Cambridge Massachusetts biotech company Moderne Inc
Vaccine against the Wuhan novel coronavirus now called SARS coronavirus 2
Moderna's other partner is the US National Institute of allergy and infectious disease
The part of the national in
Head of niaid is dr. Anthony fauci the person at the center of the Trump Administration by Richard Burgess
Response
I guess my response to be that this would be so what
Smoking Gun
Funky Music co-funding anything
The NIH
Stop smoking got the and I hate you providing
Funding for crucial medical research that Bill Gates also provides
What is the conspiracy
What the buck
Stops
Everywhere else dad
That's where that's all I know
Doesn't go
The only other evidence provided is that in 2019 it was reported the gates in the NIH or also both providing funding
Initiative to develop Gene therapies for HIV and sickle cell
Again what's the conspiracy
Out there this article is legitimately so pathetic that It Ends by trying to smear fauci by showing a picture of him with
Hillary Clinton
And a screenshot of someone tweeting an email released by Wikileaks get the f*** out of shows that quote fauci is a Hillary Clinton
Admirer
This article is nothing it's a complete zero but the headline
Ouchie has Bill Gates related conflict of interest
And that allows Alex to spin it and say that he's on Gates payroll and now we're off to the races
I reckon this work I really feel like these guys are doing
Because you're going about it all wrong somehow I feel like they're still trying too hard
Because it seems like you could write a program
That looks all you need to do here's what you need to work on if you're in a right-wing
The headlight
Programmed
Copies and pastes. You've had lines
Onion infuriated Alex
Never tell if it was real or not
So I'm also
I know you were laughing and scoffing about this
But I'm sad to hear that Alex is not realizing the Trump is not cool
Trump work with Bill Gates to get
That buck whatever
I don't know what the newest information about the Pentagon Cloud deal with Microsoft is but the last update I saw was for March 3rd
And it was about the Pentagon
It was a bunch of stories about how Microsoft had been awarded this contract
But the Pentagon was asking courts to give them time to reconsider it
This is because Amazon was claiming that there were irregularities with the contract awarding process so they wanted time to sort it all out
Either way it's really strange dear Alexei the Trump giving a contract to Microsoft instead of Jeff Bezos is bad
Reply that it should have gone to Bezos who Alex also hate
I don't know man this is a good times I need to remind you that nothing Alex says me in something
Nothing
No
So
Alex teases his big report again
In this next clip
And
Based on the way he describes it
I'm like this is not going to be good
Robin
Any problems they want to shut down
Document
Premier
Know what were the two big strikes there
Alex and he's proud of it
Not good
Great at peak hours
You've got great I can't imagine how bad is working late at night
Red Bulls and vodka
Katana kitten that is a guy who will put out some good chips
Hell yeah this is like
Trailer for a movie you didn't like you two had no hope
Woody Guthrie
You know what
Alright I already thought that was going to be bad that trailer is disappointed that's how I feel
In in his nightclub Alex talks about like these
Sort of distancing measures and how like it's polite
If you're walking down the street
Not to walk next to somebody
That is helping you know
Alex
Vintage bad to be polite hug strength or something
He keeps doing this weird condescending voice
About I whenever you talk about the bike
And then everyone gets into it and it's like a new form of hospitality
Origin
I'm sorry
We we we we we
Says I'm essential
I get to go out
Voicemail
Wachowski says
And
I called their chin throttle it
CC eating multiple things that he's completely twisting from fauci satcom at there
Exactly what you were
It's very productive
It's kind of rude
But he sounds like a whiny baby while pretending to make
Make fun of other people
Wait until we get through this
Go outside where I want to go
Some of this towards the middle and end of this episode is
As babyish as I've ever seen this
F****** the 46 year-old man
Is so pathetic
Oh my God I can't go out for
Two months ago but I want to go places
I don't
I don't know what to save life
Shut up I don't know exact
Entirely what's behind his internship but there's a there's a strain of it
So Alex believes the people love corn
Emptying and self isolate
The reality is
That's that's what that's fair
This gets into like this is the first point of the show where I was like
Like I really felt like untethered
I'll be this point
I think it would stoop
Alex Jones Show stupid
This is where I was like
Here we go
Get that feeling of like
I don't know I would relate it to like
Maybe when you're a kid
And you're in the pool and you don't really know how to swim but you
Consumed a little bit
And you like you know you
You're walking towards the deeper end it get to that point where you realize your feet
You can't touch
Yeah that little moment of panic
Of like oh no no no
That's
But I felt about that happened to me and I went down
Untethered it feels
Domesticated so soft
People are getting into it
Because they don't want to go to work and those people at most jobs aren't even working anyway
Most surgeries are elective
Mozart
People get surgeries every month
I was like oh oh I just felt like a what are we doing what are we doing
Odell
Did somebody give him a buck before the break
What happened
I don't know where he's getting any of that information
Feel like you need some
It doesn't cause brain damage
Unless something goes wrong
That's sad that seems like something the health Ranger must have told Alex and now he's just repeating on are without looking it up
There are some caveats of course
A 2019 article in the Journal of anesthetics does point out that Studies have shown that quote multiple rounds of anesthetic
Exposure in children under 2 to 4 years of age are associated with learning difficulty
In academic underachieving
Childhood and Adolescence
That sounds right
The same was not true single exposure
And generally a doctor would not anesthetize someone whose brain was still developing
Multiple times unless there was very good reason to do so
Even so this article makes a really good point about the limitation of retrospective studies that could be done about the effects
Of anesthetic
And that is that no one just takes anesthetics
There's another variable that
Always in place which is the surgery
It's pretty difficult
Ignore that when you're looking
Bodega
Just why both of these studies will not talk about
Defective anesthetics on
Like development of rain
The anesthetic and surgery right almost
Impossible to uncouple
Nobody's getting a
No
Note 2 year old is getting an elective surgery
12 year olds looking over in like selective surgery is a surgery
But yeah that's what I'm saying you don't work right
Know what it was
Nobody uses
Square
Well I think anybody who is is dead
They're very difficult
So that article there's there's an elderly patients who undergo Anderson
Cesar called postoperative delirium and postoperative cognitive
Dysfunction
The prior is a short-lived condition that we usually pass within days where the ladder can linger for a long time
However quote
Clinical evidence attributing pocd surgery and anesthesia exposure
Inconclusive
As long-term follow-up study found only 1% of elderly patients suffer from persistent
Pocd with preoperative cognitive performance
Which is to say
Mild cognitive decline
Possible or probable Alzheimer's disease
That's a better predictor of postoperative cognitive
Doctor
Anyway the point is here that that they're obviously some people who can be negatively affected by anesthesia
The surgery is mishandled
Absolutely no right to say that
Every time
Nonsense
Is weird
Me too
My name is beat the the waking up part was I
It was yeah
So also the sort of surgery Alex is describing where people are getting a little surgery on their fingers can pain pills that doesn't work
Require general anesthetic
That would a hundred percent just be a localized anesthetic situation where you don't go under
If I understand the conspiracy here Alex is saying that these doctors are in on the scam and they're performing these trivial pointless finger surgery
Used to justify their patient
Pain pill prescription
If that's the case there is literally zero chance they would use General
Aesthetic another person there who specially-trained anesthesiology
I have a ridiculously high liability
Are these doctors not in on it
If that's the case then most of these doctors are probably do an x-ray or look at the first medical charts the other recent surgery
Reason probably report them
Drug-seeking Behavior
One thing they probably would not do if you never give them
Generalized anesthetic for finger surgery
That's insane
You not learned about the opioid at
Epidemic and how you don't
Need to get Circle
Jesus has so many doctor
Or just like
Paid by pharmaceutical companies
Give them away you don't even have to pretend I usually get a fake finger surgery
Prescribing 10 million pills every year
Not enough
Finger surgery
Also according to a 2008 analysis by the American College of Surgeons using data from Colorado Florida New Jersey
It was estimated that the average American will receive 9.2 surgeries in their lifetime
But this number is based on an assumption that a person lives to 85
And obviously there are way more surgeries that will happen in the elderly portion
Of your life
Also the range workout to the surgery in that study is pretty wide so it's kind of silly to be talking about this
My point is that I was just making s*** up about people getting 15 surgery by the time they're 50 and that anesthesia gives you brain damage
Like legitimately that was where I was like we are
In Cuckoo Land out this makes no sense
It's barely connected to anything
That we were talking about
It was it made me feel worried here we go
And the speed with which he is speaking
So anyway is brain-damaged
Dementia
Fluoride
And now it's going to be
Yearly coronavirus vaccines
A bunch of articles about anaesthesia and brain damn
Damage but I realized after they closed that I didn't Google the exact words
Anesthesia causes major brain damage
So I did that
And I found an article on the website
Play Patience. Org
I'm sorry patient info
And here's what this says
Brain damage as a result of having an anesthetic is so rare that the risk has not been put into numbers
Alex should stop telling me to look fat
Has not been put into numbers
Yep that's such a small risk
Every time
Get the f*** out of here
So Alex is her story about a surfer getting arrested for surfing on a video about it
By themselves
Quarter mile office
Fornia
While you're still serving that be cool
New York
Boy we catch you
Hand sanitizer
The general public being criminals
The criminals are taking over the government
Your guys
And they get it all
What is going wrong with it
That's not good
Price gouging is okay with Alex now he's falling in line with the nice Institute
Did the stories that the Alex is talking about with that murderer who was released in New York is a bit of sticky situation
This is a story about Pedro then Aunt Marcia and the issue is that he's been charged with the murder but he hasn't been tried
Convicted
So he doesn't have a sentence
At the same time he almost certain
He killed his girlfriend
I don't know about the daughter that Alex is talking
About that was
In the story bud
The New York Post reports quote
The gruesome attack was captured on surveillance video and Witness by numerous bystanders
According to court papers
A cops nabbed him he allegedly asked
Quote is she dead I hope so
We as non-state actors can see this information say that did that murder
You'll be completely different thing for the state to do that without first having a trial
To treat him as a convicted murderer prior to trial would go against some of the very basic rights that the
Alex
Professes to love all the time protect never heard of it
Second Amendment
To make matters slightly more complicated this dude is 63 years old
And quotes
Cardiovascular disease pulmonary disease
Type 2 diabetes
Which basically put them in realtor the danger zone in terms of being exposed
The virus
Here's a real high likelihood that if he gets it it could kill him
And certain level putting him in prison where he could be exposed to it would
When he's not been to trial
Obviously this
Is Messi
Bartolotta option
He would have gone to Rikers
Square 231 incarcerated persons and 223 staff have tested positive for the virus
According to an April 2nd article in slate
He hasn't been tried but seems like the only thing the steak
I can do is put them on some kind of a supervised release program or house arrest
Or something like that
It's a mess
Listen.
Be in favor of
Aruba kind of cruel and unusual
Body weave
We haven't gone to try
With this coronavirus going around
We just don't want
Put you in Rikers
I'm going to have you sit in this chair over here at the
The very
Quietroom it's all empty
Well I mean yeah there's straps on it and no don't even worry about that thing that it's hooked up
Oh okay so it does look like a franken's a doctor Frankenstein handle don't worry
And it's not like they're letting him free of being like have fun
It's like there
It's still murder trial that you've going
To have everybody what I'd like you to do is leave the state
You you have a good day
Another case of that Surfer got arrested was a situation where all the beaches have been closed in Los Angeles County so people are essentially
Trespassing if they go to
Guy in Malibu goes episode of anyway and gets arrested
Little harsh just get a ticket
Yes
And you probably would have
If you had to put a total a****** to the officers
Score, declarative
Terry go
According to an article in the Mercury News it says that he was out surfing and was quote seemingly teasing the cops in life
Cards like he was going to get out of the water only just been back out towards the ocean and ride more waves
He was doing it like
Pictures
I honestly I'm going to be honest I think that might be worth a little truly you're wasting the cops time
First we have better things to do than most likely
But I'm still sure he just got like a
Ticket and got released on his own recognizance
Nonsense nonsense stories
So
There's this weird tension that Alex is describing where and he's talking to people a bunch in his daily life who are they
Like that we don't want to shake and but they also know that it's b******* and everybody should still be doing all the same stuff
But they are just trying to be like they just think
Alex doesn't want to shake
It's weird
Everyone seems to be doing it for each other or something and Alex's can
Confused
I know I just thought maybe
Everyone
I think I was a bit of a
You go along with it and so
Going to take everything you've got
Coronavirus vaccine
And coronavirus vaccines
And they're going to beg for them
I think
The people are already
Bacon for the 4th I think they would have been out already
And if that were the case that they're like there's wait until you beg for it
Could pass that fly
Isaac
If we're this the globalist plan
They have missed IMDb
Installing
The only people who are not begging for a vaccine right now are zealots
With regardless of like a religion or political ideology there's a certain zealotry
That goes along with that anti-vax
Are you people
F****** crazy
Yeah
Let's go
Is the last one before we get to that
Amazing report
That Rob do stayed up late working on a book report you wasn't ready for
This is just all so stupid
Because it's always changing
It's got to be exact
They don't care
You and your mommy they're going to block your ass now it'll kill you slow
Officers military
I was quite a pivot that was literally that was impressive
That's Alex playing at top
That's the stuff I be in your body whatever you do don't buy my product
Still got that cold vaccine
The reason there is no vaccine for the common cold is because the virus is constant it's not because the virus is constantly changing
There's a bunch of different viruses that cause what we call the cold already talked about this a little bit but
Cold is really just a collector
Can have symptoms not a specific condition
And because it could be caused by so many different things
He'll be really unwieldy to try and vaccinated
Against all of them
The CDC says the quote more than 200 viruses
Can cause a cold and many of them are from different virus families
Something that would prevent them all
Would probably be impossible
Frost plus most goals are pretty mild so the demand for cold vaccine is pretty low compared to other pressing that
Medical research
Although there are people who are working on
It's some similar things in there may be a breakthrough at something
But it's like
There are other things that most of the funding goes to
See they haven't cured every disease in the world yet so obviously that they dates
Too complicated or whatever
Yeah something like that
So anyway Alex goes out to break with that abrasive
Bill Cooper ask siren here-we-go announcing
Time
Infowars.com
Mission is to get this report out here it is
Okay should I accept it
Alright I don't don't don't don't don't
Don't
Bingo burlesque
Okay that's right
Miss it
Virus that was terrifying virus you can do what you love
Best to use
Power
Population
Vendetta's Realty
The heaviest this report the Rob do stayed up all night hallucinating
Together we're starting off with
IMovie
As always
Bingo
So our sort a little bit more about this about how there's real-world inspiration in V for Vendetta than you
Is that
#trumpcare
Monsters
Hugo Chavez
The other slaves
So is true that the government in V for Vendetta is inspired a bit by some real-world fascist and authoritarian States
Weather
Stories intended to be more specific on that
V for Vendetta was based on the graphic novel by Alan Moore who's been pretty clear that he wrote it with a strongly aunt
Anti Margaret Thatcher message
He felt that the government depicted in his book was The Logical extension of where British conservative
Six were heading
Also Alex if he's so concerned about how the movie is reality
I'm certainly am excited for him to get to the part about how the government scapegoats vulnerable population
For the problems in society that should be fun
It was Chinese people who wrote
Also a big part of the vibe of the graphic novel is about the national front the rise of the
Which incidentally is a group that was associated with the English Defence League which was founded by Alex's friend Tom
Bobby Robinson
I was literally friends with someone who Pals around with the information for the feelings at this graphic novel
Yeah but the villains are always the good guys
I guess
Also this is the reporter Alex is supposed to layout globalist admissions
And it's about V for Vendetta should have expected that
Of course it's about V for Vendetta
So anyway
Stupid it's just
Art imitating life
4 something
Are timid
Life imitate
Art Munoz
Baby
This
This is clearly and off
Call Francisco
Biological
Warfare
Egypt the top scientist Boyle
Scientist
Around the world
Play that clip one more time
Scientist isn't true and the Clippers playing to demonstrate it is Francis Boyle on
Top Southwest
That's a huge
Clip from his own show do you know how much that cost had to
Dick for that one
So anyway he goes on
He probably got it from us
Choreograph
Permanently erase
So in March 2018 the World Health Organization did lift disease access one of the on their list
The top concerns
It wasn't them scraping out eventual release of a bioweapon it was an attempt to focus
Attention on the fact that the next big problem that we will likely face
From a public health standpoint was something that was
Completely unknown to us before it happens
They were they weren't saying we need to go blibber teas because of the
Disease X
Central air brakes are handled correctly they don't become big outbreaks
You know there were multiple cases of Ebola in the United States in 2014 and it didn't spread because appropriate steps were taken
To contain it
That's what the World Health Organization was advocating in the discussion
Zach's not letting an outbreak it bad and then trying to play catch-up so you can take people's rights away
Is all nonsense Alex's a match
So It Goes On
I'm just playing basically
Caught a whole cut-up little part where he's just
Rambling whenever there's like a specific piece of information
That's that I've just taken all of these specific
Pre-taped segments
Ran at a time
Late at night time
Robot drone enforcement
Of course
So Alice is making s*** up there about the event 201 to make a better fit his narrative
Exercise wasn't related to this coronavirus outbreak you just happen to use a mock coronavirus as it's hypothetical
Because they're easily transmittable and because the world is already seen is SARS and MERS outbreak in the recent past there by May
Making the scenario more realistic
Do the participants who were in it as an extra
I was just making up the recommendations that the exercise arrived at
There's literally a webpage
Page dedicated
The recommendations
Which are as follows
One government's International organizations and businesses should plan now for how essential corporate capabilities can be
I will be utilized during
Large-scale pandemic
Good thing they did that
To Industry National governments and international organizations should work together to enhance internationally held stockpile
House of medical countermeasures
To enable rapid and equitable distribution during the severe pandemic
Okay Counterpoint what they should do is
Have a fireball the medical so
Supplies
Enforce governor
Stupid for them and then do them out as
His personal that wasn't on their list
Are you sure I'm positive
Three countries International organizations and Global Transport company should work together to maintain travel and trade during severe
Pandemics
Essential to the global economy as well as to National and even local
Economies and they should be maintained even in the face of a pandemic steal supplies from other
And keep them in your eye
Ford
Government should provide more resources and support to the development
Manufacturing a vaccine
Therapeutics and Diagnostics that will be needed during severe pain
Five Global business should recognize the economic burden
Pandemics
Sandpiper stronger preparedness
International organizations should prioritize reducing economic impact of epidemics
Pandemics
Government
And the private sector should assign a greater response
Greater priority to developing methods
To combat Miss
And disinformation
Prior
The next pandemic.
It's so funny whenever people do with
And then all wrong and you're like
What who could have known who could possibly have ever figured this one
Recommendations do they have everyone gets locked
A panel of experts go to the simulation in order to brainstorm actionable advice
They could help better prepare for an epidemic
I think a point we're seeing
As a camp with an alright list
I was just make
Yeah well you got a smear people who kind of predicted where
We should have gone and are watching us go the opposite
Manuel
When we back to this dumb report
The Rob did
True
Are you not going to reference
The graphic novel
Brothers
Graphic novel
True but it's on the white paper
He's not going to reference it was based on a graphic novel they made it up and wrote the script.
Bring up Alan Moore at all
You know
Besides it's from these white papers because I'm being specific about any of them but
What kind of work he's doing here
They see it in white papers officially
So let's see where it goes I mean I need I need meteor
These ideas
50 years ago
For the elite believe
He did it himself
The population
Good morning
Text cities
As far as I can tell Mathis didn't say that was really is a bioweapon to get rid of people
He was most closely identified with what's known as the malthusian catch a catastrophe
Hypothetical event that happens when population growth outpaces the supply of resource
It was his belief that after that point people being really terrible shape and so we should avoid it
He also had a feeling that population was going to be kept in check one way or another
Either we could do it ourselves with birth
Control and Family Planning Coordinator would end up doing it with famines and resource Wars that would come after this
Pathetical
Catastrophe
A lot of folks are not a fan of Malthus is work
Eventually if Alex is a Critic of his but he'll find himself standing side-by-side
With Carl barks and all the Communists he likes to yell about all the time who also hate Malthus
Honestly I could get into the Play-Doh stuff but I don't think Alex has read it and it seems stupid to try and even engage with him
When he's talking about philosophy
Not doing it all of Plato's
Socratic dialogues are written as debates that Socrates is having
With some other person
So if you want to cherry-pick lines as being the point of the text itself it's really easy to do that
So far Alex's talked about V for Vendetta a bunch of nothing and proved and then vaguely pointed at
Malthus
And Play-Doh
He made an airtight case.
Sure that's how I
The club of Rome
Calling for Global
Prince Charles
Constantly
In the event that I am
I would like to return it
Reported by Deutsche presse-agentur DPA 1988
Prince Philip quote
He didn't constantly say it it was just include in the foreword of a book called if I were an animal
That voice over here reading the quote is from the movie and the game
Caesar cut that out of endgame
It's actually misattribution and
And incorrect quotes
I can find no primary source from the Dutch
Press Argent or from 1988 that book
About what you would like to be if you were an animal
Unless Alex is a primary source on this I have to assume this is a bad game of telephone and maybe there was some German press
Set reported on the forward to that book
And it got mixed up in Translation or something
But all of it traces back to the foreword of that book
Mandu had to do some real work to
Oh yeah
The club of Rome that specific text Alex is obviously referring to their publication
The limit
Growth
Which came out not in the sixties but in 1972
Howard should know that
Because the club of Rome wasn't founded until 1968
And limits to growth was their first release
They did not put out anything
In the 60s
I've read limits
Growth and it doesn't recommend or support for
Global depopulation
It's more of an analysis of how continuing unrestricted growth would be unsustainable past proximately 2070
After which point we're in for disaster
The authors have released multiple follow-ups like the 2004 limits to growth 30-year update
And in 2012 they put out 2052 a global forecast for the next forty years
None of them say that we should have forced Global depopulation but do recommend people have less children
Totally up to you to decide if that's good or bad advice but it's soup
Reedley dishonest to pretend that these texts
In some way proof
But the authors wanted to
To populate the world
Their main point was the population growing itself limit
Buy all of its own it will limited cell
Well we've never seen evidence of that in the wild
Under the assumption that there are finite resources population has its own limit
The goal is not
To find a way to kill people off
Find a way to
Continue some kind of growth that averts the disastrous consequences that they foresee coming from unbridled growth path
That's the points that the resources
You cannot trust people who spend all of their time analyzing past event
Ants and synthesizing current information together in order to create a forecast
As for what could happen
Obviously as we saw with all these Bill and Melinda Gates things
I have no idea what the f*** their talk
Talking about listen to those recommendations we're not doing any of those things then we're fine
So far I would say this report is not going well
And it continues
Population
Have more money
Panel
And you're not
Pretty near the cereal
ICloud
Let's take a look
Following
Alex has some f****** brass balls complaining about that Newsweek article the case for killing granny after you spent
Considerable time on his own show advocating the people go back to work and risk a ton of
Because they're not do so I would hurt the economy
Also Alex is taking those comments from Bill Gates while they are contacts
We just got to the past but those
Clips of Alex uses there are tiny slivers of Gates making
Sweetly different point
Alex is playing
Alex knows what he's doing
He complains about being taken out of
All the time
Most likely because he knows that's what he does to people
If if there was a good
Democratic op
Episode
Easy to
Put side-by-side
Now being like
Go back to work
We need the economy goat look
Several people are going to die that's just something that we have to accept
Juxtaposed with
Going to kill grandma
Everyone take 02
Somehow we're not do
Also what is the Rockefeller Foundation Carnegie endowment plan
Alex can't claim that this is a report that
Approves all this s*** and then randomly pull names out of a hat he needs to use
Lifx
He wants this to mean anything which
It does not so far
Maybe this is what he's talking about
Rockefeller Carnegie endowment plan
Hugo Reid
Caldwell
World government
Will redic
Starbucks
That is just embarrassing that is embarrassed because he's only red
Little dumb blurbs about it on stupid blogs
So he only knows about one scenario in the report
That's cringe level stuff
Particularly when he says ice
Suggest you go read it
I suggest you read it
Actually called scenarios for the future of technology and International Development we covered it in-depth on a recent episode
Has nothing to do with the plan to bring an authoritarian Rule and crush the public
That's all just a paranoid delusions that Alex has picked up most likely from its coverage on Jim's that's a Blog
So great
So far not proving anything no that's not that's not very good but I was going to go with my
My scary plan is be
Kardashian Cuban
Watch out for bees play
That was Mark Cuban and Kim Kardashian got together and they created a simulation where and we all get to eat
Eaten by bees
So that's one to watch out for
Or they're going to implement
That real Sarah believe is they say watch that space
See what else is coming in this stupid report
World
Visual saying
We should get rid of the old p
What you're the one saying that you'd come back to work so they can die for us
I don't know
I was getting a lot of mileage out of the phrase
Former British prime ministers and others
There's one all he's referring to is a comment from a singular former British prime minister Gordon Brown
Gordon's not talking so much about calling for world government is he's calling for an emergency International task force
To deal with the medical and economic crises that are popping up
Largely because they are issues
They don't have concern for National boundaries
These are Global problems that could be much more easily solved if
Now heavy International cooperation
If that's World Government I guess fine I'll let Alex have that but isn't pretty weak stuff for him to hang his hat on
It fast this is a tappet call for World Government from a guy who hasn't been prime minister in a decade so
Nation-states in constant conflict
Actually agree
That's all I'm saying
Alright
Interesting
Perhaps
But if Alex could use a report
And he uses a quote
Actually gets right
Are you still wrong
Aaron Franklin
No no
Those
Ford security
You always
Who's running
Cliche
World population
So Alex is largely quoting that Benjamin Franklin saying correct
Play however it's kind of interesting to understand the original context of the quote
Benjamin wittes
The editor of warfare explained the context in a 2015 interview with NPR like this
He was writing about a tax dispute between the Pennsylvania general assembly in the family of the pens
The proprietary family the Pennsylvania colony
Who ruled it
From afar
And the legislature was trying to tax the pain family land
Pay for Frontier defense during the French and Indian War
Depends family kept instructing the governor
DeVito
Franklin felt that this was a great affront to the ability of the legislature to govern
And so he actually meant purchase a little temporary safety very literally
The pain family was trying to
To give a lump sum of money in exchange for the general assembly's acknowledging that it didn't have the authority
To tax it
Which goes on to say quote
It's a quotation that defends the authority of the legislature to govern in the interest of
Collective security
It means in context not quite the opposite of what it's always quoted as saying
Much closer to the opposite than the thing people think
It's fine to use this quotation in the way Alex's people do it all the time and it seems to resonate
With people
He just shouldn't
Quote Ben Franklin when they do because he was arguing
Please Lee different position
And you can really tell from Oz analysis of the quote
Like you. He drives a
Lele different meaning from within Franklin intended which tells me he's never read the original Source material
But just read the quote on some dumb blog which is basically all he ever does
Also that part about reducing population to 500 million
It's just Alex referencing the Georgia Guidestones
Come on so sad
So sad cuz you reference the Georgia Guidestones a 100%
Reliable thing to rap
Now I got enough
What else you got
Nothing
Microsystem
Word world
That is not true based on the article in Wired Magazine by Bill Joy that is
Alex
Only reading
A part of the article where Bill Joy quotes
The Unabomber
Alright is all that's going on there
Passage
From the Unabomber is the
The point of the article
It is not
Just make it hard
It does have it does make it hard to have a conversation at a party
Subway
Alex is using that Source their he's not proven
Anyting in a lot of this isn't even like
The pic it's not
The suddenly there is a lot of V for Vendetta and it but a lot of it sold
S***
A lot of it
There was a clip from endgame
Drew
Misattributed recited quotes
Then
So here's how this ends and I would say that he has failed
And robbed you should get a complete this project
I laid out
Corporation
Powerful video it's at Man. Video
False
Now this is critical
Jackson now they're going to kill her
Attention fellow American just missed the break after the special report so sad
Now do you know why I know for a fact my
Kardashian Cuban planning something to worry about the weather
Have you seen the Bee Movie
Dog With The Wind
By the club of Rome
They're on the f****** think they know what's going on and produced it
I got to say I
Once again and pixelated by Alex's incompetence when he tries to prove something none of this proves anything
Oh God it's so bad
So bad it is a Rob deposition of Nvidia
Well-done Rob Purity paycheck
So Alex comes back and he starts picking up on a
Conspiracy theories
I'm going around the internet
Absolutely right that
There are thousands video we try to plan a few weeks ago
Hospital
Now more more people
New York
Wisconsin to Ohio to
You will see all the news the news
Hospital
Posting videos
Local
YouTube channel
Normal people
The Beacham
Hardee's
I live a mile from this hospital and they said they're long lines and people dying everywhere
Pretty funny Alex is a little late to the empty hospitals conspiracy
Subtraction online and then places like Fox News days prior to this episode
Also it's really funny to remember that Alex declared war on Cuba.
In the April 1st episode of the show to the day before this.
Episode
Because a lot of these videos he's claiming to have research were created by qanon followers with me hashtag filmyourhospital
Yeah cuz there is at War
Are you going to understand your enemy dad by promoting 12 course
All these videos are shot in front entrances of hospitals which showed no real traffic which
Supposed to demonstrate there's no real coronavirus pandemic and the stats are a lie
What they actually shows pretty decent evidence that things are bad
Most of the people you would see coming in those entrances to the hospital people coming in for minor things or visitor
So the fact There's No One Billing about ism
Isn't active
Are there not being visitors coming which is right in line
With the current situation
None of these videos show anything that's happening inside the hospitals and people inside the hospital can't legally release those sorts of images
Of things that they're see because of patient privacy and HIPAA laws
And honestly I don't know what these
Dumb dumb conspiracy theorists are imagining should be happening outside
Do they think that if it wasn't real outbreak there just be a couple hospital employees running around screaming for affect
I guess that what they would expect
I I think what they would have
Is there
Here's why because here's the real
There's no line there so the like this was a real pandemic there would be lines down the street of people needing to get treated
And then of course if there were lines on the street they would like to see these people are all paid to look like there's a pan
Dammit going on
That says anything in
Fox News host Todd Starnes he went outside the Brooklyn Hospital Center
And is made one of these videos
But unfortunately the exact same Hospital someone else was
They release video of
People
Loading bodies
Picture of 18-wheeler truck
Maybe not at the front entrance
I'm amazed that there that the Fox News host are being spit on
Regularly
If you're if you're not if you saw that guy as I swear to God if I see that guy anywhere I'm going to spit
No no
Maybe a little bit Way Beyond
The pals
What do you mean is disrespect
Like
Old timey like Violetta
This needs to be brutal
So Alex is talking about these videos that have come out about like these these empty hospitals and s***
And he remembers that he had a guy on who it made a video of along these lines
I think in Hawaii any tries to come up with this guy's name
And
When Alex started talking about anesthesia give you brain damage
That's why I felt like
I can't touch the floor anymore
I'm a little worried
And I was like
Oh no
The pool is 20 ft I can't tread water
If I see a shark
For this cuz this is a f****** freak out
He was the first chain reaction
Any reaction and then everybody just starts going out
Toosii
What's going on
Get back on
Quick fact check it's not you Michael Jones it's actually a guy named Jason Jones who's this guy with the YouTube channel
Doesn't have a million views as of April 5th
Thousand little difference but also Alex thinks it might be e Michael Jones
Which means he doesn't know who's
His guests are
Because he was he was just going to be tested
Ladies gentlemen and it's a chain reaction
Hospitals open
Table Mountain
Cross
The board
There are people lined up there
In hallways
Can eggs
I really want them back on
That's another Jones Arthur Jones
That's why I begged hard I want
Asian gentleman
I totally butchered and just just two Tire once in a suite
Absolutely out of control
Baby daddy
Protection
From the planet
So in the middle of that rant Alex's earpiece fell out
Haha
So the party towards the end there where he's growling
Is what he's trying to subtly put his earpiece back on
He's really struggling with it
I'm becoming more certain than ever that he's just getting
Like stage
He's not getting dressed like Jesus time to go to break through the air.
I think you being fat lines through there
Because he's really freaking out when is your piece falls out possibly
One of the reasons he seems all over the place all the
The time is going to Carolee integrate all the information that's coming to him through his ear
And you just like
Maybe skips
Protopic ab2c ride
It's disjointed cuz you can't disjointed information
Write a lot of people think that he
Conspiracy theory that he
That Bill Hicks
His own death
And what they don't
How far is that
It was actually Veruca Salt who faked her own death and became a
Did you have a earpiece famous haha she wanted things
Now
This is not Samantha bees husband
Jason Jones
I don't usually walk. Recommend watching
The video of Alex but this little segment is pretty funny
Watch
Try and fail to put his earpiece back
Through this country
Just it's just you know what it is
Is it the perfect encapsulation of his impotent angry baby
And I can't I can't
I can't
Get my hand around my head my earpiece. 41
God
He doesn't want to like Jaw tension to it so you
That's why he's doing a lot of like Beatrice would like
Such a dork
Anyway it deteriorates he descends even deeper into
Anger
Of course
And you want Satanism to you're going to be killed very slowly they're going to inject
Oh boy
Will do nothing
I got to turn into a giant blueberry
Do all of this over and over again
Golden egg
Oh
You want some chocolate buddy
It's the same problems that whatever cuz I'm insane
Grow the f****** no s*** absurd
This is so weird
Wow I mean
I read the day before
He's having this breakdown about how Everyone likes qanon more than him
Right now the breed any of that
Add stuff to the next day's episode please
Clear still struggling with something
This is a sad outbursts
America's being destroyed
Just mad about it
You can get this far while still being a chow
Kind of an accomplishment in itself to be a nine-year-old trapped in a
Giant
Connect monster
America's being destroyed and it is not cute
Alex is not in control of his anger he is still
Profoundly mad
Everything our ancestors fought for is being murdered
Wiggling around
It's fun and it's cute
Cute
Funny
Let's go to the Elmo song
Have never guessed
Nothing
Alex isn't really being honest there about the flu vaccine
It is true that all sometimes flu strains pop up in human populations that aren't the ones that are covered by that Year's vaccine
Ridiculous to say that scientists have never guessed the right strain
Just want to admit they're scared of needles act if they're a little dumber than they think they are
Intellectualize their immature response but the point they're making it
Is childish and stupid that's all I can obviously I'm not afraid of needles
What is the same behavior
Display near
It's Alex there is still like really spinning out
I think he's gotten his earpiece back in now but
Just all over the
Whatever it is
German Italian and other firms
Vaccine and scanned it
Engineered
The news by the Italian government
Because
The manufacturer of the vaccine in the who shed
Did
You're not allowed to scan what we put in there
This story that Alex is talking about regarding is that it's about to anti-vax folks
Italy named Antoinette
The end Stefano
Montara montanari
In 2017 they released the paper called New Quality Control investigations on vaccines micro and Nano contaminate
His paper was released on a non. Viewed website and no one has an anyway confirm their findings which according
Analyses of it that I found where not even scary to
To begin within our little dubious
Have some of the metals they claim that they founded vaccines
Could easily have been found due to methodological errors
That lie to themselves being because
The contamination as close to the vaccine itself
I can't find any reliable sources of their office is being rated but I can't find a ton of logs
Claiming without evidence that that did happen
How does no idea what the actual story is here he's just seeing articles about them on dumb anti-vax blogs he skins headlines on
That's all it's going on here I feel like I could have been like
If when I was 9 and my parents were like we're having spinach
You got a
I was instead how to be like here
Eat spinach
I was like actually
The government is using spinner
To get inside your body to give you an abortion on top of the abortion that you already had sent me and I was
Spinach Slovakian scientists control weapon
Thrown in the hoosegow and then cuz my parents were birchers they were like
That actually makes a lot of sense
We need to get you out in Paw
Yeah
So Alex
His turn to you on the audio
And I'm saying like f*** it
F*** all this I can't do the show f*** it
Is working with Bill Gates
We have
Not really disgust
It does
Fall by the wayside for sure
But Alex goes out to break after this like weird
F****** fall into anger by two
Like I think
Y'all get his audience that they're all going to burn in hell
Everything they give you is for another
Play Tetris
Wow
Okay
That was
A bit much
I do enjoy being left with a
Positive
That's a bit much
It's Alex realizes but like
I think someone gave matoke
Commercial that was like
You just
Yelled at your own audience
They're going to burn in hell
I know you do that a lot when you say it towards the globalists or something
This was a kind of a real dick thing
I think your audience might be weird about that so Alex comes back
And as a clarification
Now we deserve everything is about to happen to us
Nyet coward jellyfish
Killing babies
I love that kind of apology I love that kind of listened I wasn't mad at you when I told you
You specifically
You are going good I hate you you're piece of s*** your eternally brought
That wasn't about
You that was just me being mad at people who rejoice and getting abortion
Okay okay now I'm sorry I didn't mean to be threatening when I said I would kill you personally and stop on your gut
Meant to be
BRAT diet
But also the idea that I like
If I mean I don't know what the reality is but if he is just mad at people who rejoiced abortion and that is called
Empty Outlet is audio
They're all going to burn in hell and all this that we deserve what
Coming
I would suggest
That maybe when Alex says that he paid for a bunch of abortion
Somebody was younger and he's repented and made peace with that
Maybe that process yet
Because I complete
Valentine
He was the last person who could make peace with that God only understanding
He is not okay with all this maybe some of what we're seeing manifesting is unresolved issues
Surrounding that
Okay that maybe he needs to take a look at this a little closer because you seems to be
In a bad place paraphrase you I'm glad you're starting to get the word dealing with a lot of his unresolved issues here
I think some of them are becoming
Farmer over
Yeah this is bad
Exclaimed in the beginning of this clip that
He has played a bunch of clips of women
Rejoicing in the bushin
Knock play these clips
That is best as I've seen their things he's misrepresenting
And people trolling
But
Sarah Silverman joke
Why not
At the end of this clip he gets into the Andrew Cuomo nipple ring controversy
Going to be on just four months ago when suddenly on all the comedy major shows all over the news
Love killing babies and I like to get pregnant and then I've done it three times my boyfriend
Like to have sex while I'm pregnant what to think about the baby a little girl as little boy
When I go in there I thought shut the power they
A little piece of trash up I feel like
Again
I don't know what again
Got it I mean again with being served
You don't
Care
Crazy
Okay if your nipple rings
Yep if you're gay if he's your blackmailed gay politician
This is obvious then I mean I'm sure there are some issues that come with that
Some I mean not in terms of blackmail
But there's some
Social stigmas that people would probably feel about there
Their sexuality and public and private license
I don't think they were as evolve to society as we like to imagine sometimes
But to the point where it's like
The 50s
You know if you are a
Hypothetically gay person
You must be black
That's
Is a sign of
Something bad and I was praying he never group
McCarthy
So in this next clip I know that Alex is always talked about how like you know the global 7 extermination is playing and either
Against it
It seems like he kind of thinks we deserve it
Now
Interesting
Abortion devil worship
Republic
The operation of God they're the ones
Incentivize it thanks
Play God do it the same time everybody
It seems like Alex's problem is that he wants to run the extermination
Look yeah
I guess we should be exterminated people cuz I haven't,
Where do I go from there I just don't like that the globalists are playing God
Terminate the people who have gone along with the globalist
Yeah they aren't they are an arm of God
Wow
That's not good
Globalstar going to fail
Slides
Before that they're going God's going to let him kill half the planet or something
I want it
Never going to work right
Text Emily where they were empty them
God is going to allow it
Fruition
To coerce
Revelation says
World population
Social distancing and doing what they say and taking their inoculations keep you safe
Good
You take the shot
Jesus
Call yourselves
You know Dylan
How to make me take your shots
Wow
You just still get the other radio
I use already available but like there's a real like
Really getting into this dark side
Don't get this other place
No I think that's because struggling to feel like this is real
Beforehand
What are the reasons if it doesn't happen on other shows
It's because other people have bosses
These behaviors are so unprofessional
No matter what you're doing if you're like
If you have a job that's not running a show where you lie for a living
If you act like this you're fired
He said he's only been rewarded for the Warriors
Entire life can get away with whatever you want I'm sure most of his staff is
Terrified to
To respond to these are things you don't get what you want
You throw a tantrum like a little bitty baby ear plug falls out of your head
I wanted
Go ahead kill your kids
We all deserve to be exterminated
Ahmed
The message for the BuzzFeed people out there
He wants to know
I told you
Is it going to happen
Call Sunny
The BuzzFeed New York Times folks out there
Got your ass up and feed you bug poisoning radiator Athens take every damn dime out of you
So after break Alex declares himself a
The prophet of God God said Alex Jones
Do Warner's that's not good and God is really striking out these days
Choose the lowest Among Us definition Alex is about the lowest
It doesn't get much lower than that
There are very few
So earlier
Alex said that everyone's going to burn in hell he came back from break
Zen spiral deeper
Exterminator
Now it's goes back for break and he has another
Hello bello
A little bit
I have been really upset about what's going on because
Operation
You just can't control his emotions like it's just
It just preferably saying this is just
Embarrassed
Got to watch it at a certain point like I like looking into things like that Rockefeller report you know that
I like looking into that I can enjoy that
There's a part of me that feels a little bit dirty
Listening to this
Like
There's a part of me that feels like
This is so sad
It's it's funny
On what level Alex
Socket everyone deserves to be exterminated
The behaviors are so like a child lashing out
Almost doesn't feel good
It's
Like
It's it feels a little bit like maliciously laughing at a three-year-old for not knowing out of string sentence
Kansas together relax
Stupid you three-year-old same time the three-year-old is actively trying to get the hundreds of thousands of people who'll
But at the same time too you know acting like
It somehow so far above
You know however operating is also a little bit condescending on my part infantilize him to the point where it's at
Looks like this is a child that these behaviors are f****** childish
Well this is a difficult bike weird thing
I mean this is
This is somebody who should be
I receiving a large amount of help right now from
Medical
Not getting out of it
Yeah you think so
We're done with emotional outbursts for now
Now it's gets into like the heater starts hitting like
Buckshot
Some of the stuff does not
Connect to each other it does not make sense a lot of its non secretary
And a lot of it is wrong
There better be
Bildungsroman
Before Christ
Okay
After death
What are different
Common
Before the Common Era
That's the modernist thing to get rid of the Christ
Sobc does mean before Christ but ad does not mean a death
Exactly
For in the year of Our Lord
33 years when Jesus was alive but didn't get number didn't count very weird
Tom is great
You know if you want to be marked I'm based on your religious beliefs
But we're all going to share the common reality that this is the year 2020 baby
That is no reason to not secularize at a little bit so Common Era and before Common Era are completely acceptable copper
Unless what you're angling for
Berkeley religiously-based Society
Is one little clues that might be what Alex's into
That is so funny to be
In the context
Dove
How
Awful he is about the year zero
For him to actually be like no
It's actually 1974 right now okay idiots
That's because we didn't count the 33 years or 1991 whatever it is that's so funny
Snowden idiot
Here's another thing that sounds completely unrelated
Because it is
60% of births are
Really
So it's interesting history
According to all the data I can find this is absolutely a made-up stat about 60% of births in Travis County being C-section
According to the 2017 healthy Texas babies databook
Released by the Texas Department of State Health Services
In 2016
34.4% of Altex
The deliveries were delivered by cesarean section
The number is actually slightly lower than it wasn't years
2009 through 2015
But right around the same level it was in 2008
This report does not a full breakdown by County every year but it does include figures
2015 putting the early non-medically indicated elective Caesarean section rate in Austin
21-point
3% or lower
A 2019 article on the usnewsandworldreport had a county-by-county list
Counties with the highest percentage of C-sections based on CD
ABC data
The highest was Rapids
Parish Louisiana with 47.3
Percent so there's no way I believe Alex's dad that he's absolutely just making up
According to their data Travis County was at number 176 on that list with 32.8%
Stop at our to say about Cleopatra is even stupider he's not even getting his fake history right
There's a legend about the birth of gas
Julius Caesar that help that he was
Cut out of his mother who died while she was pregnant with him
But his mother wasn't Cleopatra
She was irelia
True mostly prove by fact that Caesar's mother survived
Birthin exist
Historical record
In reality the name is most likely derived from the same Latin word that Caesar seems related to is Sora
Kadari
Which translates to
There are some other theories but would normally take seriously the idea that it's actually named what it is because
Became popular after Caesar or Cleopatra or whatever
But by all means
Alex's Eddie's fun
History
I was want to know a little
I was going to say that's that was the first thing cuz I don't remember Cleopatra dying in childbirth
And if I remember
The history of the C-section though
Is a
What are the pioneers of the C-section that first
Successfully the mother and the Child live
Was actually a woman
Who was
Raised as a man
In order to go to medical school because women weren't allowed to go to medical school
So at the age of six she was raised as a man
Man who became a professional doctor
And was
By all accounts
Incredible one of the best doctors overtime.
And they didn't find out that she was a woman until after
She was dead
When they dug her up and then
Performed an autopsy and realized that
She herself
Had given birth to two children
Until I don't know this story at all
Very fast you could be making this up
This is from The Book of the Dead which was written by the
Fantastic
Q iPhone
I've looking today
Stephen Fry
Spurlock's
Funny way everyone's getting C-sections now and soon
Vaginal birth
Is going to be outlawed
Right that's out to prediction
This clip
Ends
Weird logo
One day
They will take
Children from mothers that try to have babies at home and try to have them vaginally
Also get your money with cesarean they can run quicker
Need to make vaginal birth
About a third smaller brain
And fluoride is Douglas tricks
Yeah
My mama Target was 18 months
Goddaughter skirting I said Mama
Oh Gotti
When I was 18 months old
Breastfed for a year-and-a-half I guess I don't know
Whatever the reality is that makes me incapable of looking into any of those other nonsense you think
The story goes on but I do
I had to take a break there for a minute
I want to buy Mom and Tony about 18 months
Mama
Energy said no no no we got the car
Which I never did
Big head
The milk my mother predict
Conspiracy theory
Women's breasts
Ever
Okay
Wilson this some Game of Thrones that he's tossing people out of the f****** Spire like what is this dude doing
He kicked his mom laughs
18 months old
Teddy
God
Idiot Alex gets into talking about how is going to go into the
Situation soon
How do you say something about
Trump
Pretty disqualifying
We're not going to do that
Projections too well I guess we better
Because
He's never gotten from the media settling
We're doing a good
Problem because we're buying into the fear and going along with it
How old were the people go
This is a sad level of blaming yourself
For Trump
Ridiculous
Also I would say
That like
If Trump
Going along with this because the media's praising him that's
Evidence he's a terrible leader
Yeah if you so desperate for the media to
Give him a round of applause that means that you can't trust him to make a good decision
Real bad hahaha easily manipulated by Praise
Might be somebody who is incredibly stupid as well
Feel slightly better about them
A little bit as much as he constantly fooled by Steve pieczenik
Flattery about like first person to ever cure the coronavirus antibiotic
Alex read the headline that I'm almost certainly didn't
Mean to read
Cause of death in United States
Usually
But that's not true and it's also really dishonest
One will meet in early April here
This year's not even close to over so using the number of death Racine now to compared to a whole Year's Day dies intrinsically dishonest
You'd only do that if you're a liar and trying to minimize some piece of really bad information that you wish you hadn't just accidentally said huh
Also the flu isn't really a top cause of death in the United States
Even if you accept a 60000 a year estimate
That's still far below the approximately 650
3000 Oz
Heart disease or 600,000
Cancer the 170,000
Accidents
Who's absolutely shity work
Positive
He just was cold reading that I had no idea I was about to come out of his mouth
It's
Another headline that's a bit of a problem for him
Coronavirus outbreak
Official
So it is true that originally Alex was yelling about the Chinese government lying about the virus numb
That's fair
He's basement literally nothing other than his hatred of China but just saying those things
Yes however more recently he completely change that story as evidenced by this clip for March
March 24th
Operate
It's a real problem
Older people go ahead and video tape it put it on the internet
Locked up for that
The party said
Everything
To get the maximum feared
How to turn middle of Trying to minimize the virus at March 24th at that point was on the party line of saying that everyone had to go
Go back to work
So he was invested in pretending that the Chinese that inflated the number so Trump would take it seriously while the Chinese went by
Back to work or something
Now the narrative has shifted begins Alex's pretending he was never reporting
Wall Street Journal numbers now there underreported
Nothing Alex says means any
He's just making it up as he goes along to see whatever the party demands him support
That's fine
I guess
That's what a Thor attarian propagandist
Do they prey on their ID
And how willing
Let's go along with
Constantly changing
Self-contradictory narratives
Now what would be really abusive would be an Alex immediately after me
Making this claim that directly contradicts them
Reported as fact
About a week ago
When are the Reds by the globalist
Don't want you to have a memory
Get nasty I get negative because
A lot of compliance enabling is virtuous. Virtuous
Tchaikovsky
Flying about an incubating at the Democrats
It's really not virtuous is it people don't
Remember
What just happened a month ago
That's abusive
That's hard
That's what I'm talkin about shunning
This is this is
Stunning
This is like everybody if you see Alex Jones outside
You should say calmly and quietly
Alex is a very bad person
Space you are a bad human being
Yeah but calmly part is good but it's still imagine you're a demon with like a face
That'd be great
So Alex Goes to break and comes back and he has
He's found a
Video on Twitter
That Rob do or someone has told them
About
Now they just don't put me in there when I said it
Bet your ass 300 100%
Areas
When
Forced coronavirus test
Dragon Blood
The old desk
I'm sticking a needle I need
This is on Twitter
Here right now. Hush this is bad reporting procedure
Like he's found a video on Twitter that may or may not be real there might be other circumstances that you have no idea
About
With this person
I don't know who this person is I don't know what
What circumstances are
I'm not going to get into it
Alex is reporting it as like
All things being equal no other surrounding context
People are now being
Held down and forced to have their blood drawn for Coronavirus test
Which is not really good it's not good
He's pushing it he's got to push it because if it weren't it's the line right now exactly
You got put in the u.s. is confirmed real
A Abril
Sorry G Edward
This morning
Days ago
Michael Porter something Edition
Okay
So he's got this video from Twitter that he's not reporting is real
And Rob do is giving him some other pieces information that he knew days ago but he's mad cuz he hasn't done it or covered it
Too much data I've got to go to a special report
Andy gets
To what the news is
Involve some fake crying
And
The story that when I said casus belli earlier
This would be that
If you was like
Legitimately
There's no conclusion to this other than
Go to war with China
Which is
Not an ideal outcome
Battle Cry
They sent testing kit today at least they sent
Here
And they're sending in Matthews math
But the last delivering to be able to spread it
Add
A wheelhouse where you can't just sit around and talk about this owner
Exactly
Doesn't move against the people doing this
Then
What are we going to do exactly your rhetoric is becoming a problem
The escalation has gotten
To a point where it's like what the f*** are you going to do Alex you just said that China released a worldwide attack
So
What is the
Well I guess
We should
So here's one of the reasons I don't trust this reporting
Alex is going off a story on National file and here's one line. Haha yeah
One line from the Arctic
The United Kingdom reportedly of covid
19 testing kits sent from China found to be contaminated with the coronavirus when they were being surveyed by a Luxembourg
Berg based company
That line hot links to a story on MSN news but if you
Read that story
Nowhere in it does it say that these kids were being sent for
Vagina
It says the kids were Bound for the United Kingdom
And they were from a manufacturer in Luxembourg
But if the sources
Do what they're using for their claim that they're from China
That's absolutely fabricated from the source
It's not in the article and based on the reading of the actual article it seems like this was more of a lab error not an intentional
Contamination
I brought a bunch of other articles about this and none say the kids were from China or the China was involved at all this is
A pure fabrication it appears to me on the part of national file but they don't have another source
It's it's
The editors added into the Meredith that's just that's murder
That's that's just trying to get people
2 kill
Like
Play it could be argued that
Now the other thing too is that they're also mixing in a bunch of stories of like
Defect
Active masks the China ditch them to like
Experience
And that's lesson issue of them being contaminated from what the article said I was reading and more of them just not being well
Producer
And that could be a function of
There
Manufacturing not being up to
Snuff but I'm more Furious because two weeks from now
Alex is going to be saying that we need to hold
People down to draw their blood in order to test them for covid and that America released this to attack China back
Who knows I'm running out of giving a s***
Alex's found the story about the tainted tests and he is really getting wild with it
Towards the end of this episode
When I got this new info
I said the Rob.
Let me guess who's behind it
The latest company on record contaminating people in England with the test
I wonder if Alex's audience ever get suspicious that he never gives specific details about anything
Like are they wondering when he says that he doesn't use the company's name
Do they think that maybe it's because
You might get sued
If you did
No
The only company in that article is eurofin
And Steve luxenburg manufacturer and I don't know if Bill Gates is involved with
I'm up for Alex to try and explain that connection and we'll see if he does
Wait hold on a second
Do you realize that a few episodes ago I said that it was
Luxembourg's fault
Oh yeah maybe you did
I don't know baby we're Wizards
This is evil
So when you were saying that this is like murder
You know
The trend of Alex blaming Chinese people as opposed to
You know having certainly some reservations or
Suspicions
About
Stop mishandling by the Chinese government
The difference
Is becoming a real problem
In this next clip Alex is really f***** up man
Parrot they do it
It's not trying anymore they're saving us a Chinese please
What did you just say
Celebrating
America
What is this called information overload
You're doing a bad job real bad job
Real bad job Alex
So you suspicious
You're saying that
You don't know which Chinese people gave
But you do nothing specific
And forwards made a specific accusation about a chinese-american Rodger
Just don't got sued for 100 million dollars
So I think
Alex is better than to be specific
So Alex can't handle all this special report before
Trying to
Really do a good job and he doesn't
It's very important because during that break I was unable to get the
The articles I need nobody's fault
I'll be focused on my office to get the article say a little prayer
It all just came together
Red handed in every country
The Chinese Center
It's contaminated with Coronavirus
Purpose
Companies
Melinda Gates doing the same thing
So Bill and Melinda Gates and China are in cahoots
And Alex's got to go say a little prayer and get some headlines together it now Jordan
We have a second instance on this episode of Alex saying
He's going to prepare and try and prove something
So here we go
One of the one of the big problems
With not having
Universal Health
Guaranteed jobs in
Is because
If you are a person with a
Conscience
And you worked at like Infowars or Fox News or any of those places
You have to think of it
Hey I got to stop working
Immoral
Officially
If the buyer was a while ago
You are contributing to
Deaths that are
So
If they had
Income or Healthcare
I would imagine the people with a conscience
Ends with stop
F****** work
Yeah I know and you know like I know from that Josh Owens article about his time working there
There was
The feeling of I be unemployable anywhere else
So I mean like there's also
That's kind of puzzled in with that that's kind of leaving
That fear of leaving probably does keep a lot of people there I would assume so
So Alex tries now he comes back
Back from his special report and he decides he's going to really break this down and heater
I have just cut out the specific
Instances of him trying to prove the narrative
That China intentionally sent contaminated test to infect
The world
Labradorite
So this article is from about a month ago
And there's nothing to do with China this is about a lab in the United States that had some
Some contamination issues
It's not even necessarily indicated from the article that it was there has anything to do with
After being contaminated
So here the next one is
What kind of a non sequitur
Just one place
There's another one Los Angeles
Ladies and gentlemen
I don't that doesn't have anything to do wealthy
So
We get to this next headline
The Chevron countries
Natural.com
That's just an add-on file headline
Tender.
Are the virus of independent
Kitchen The Daily Mail
These are all just stories about the same underlying story The National file is lying about so that it's not another story
Are you just have one
Haha
Headline here you don't you don't
Get credit for reading all of the headlines about the same story different places
What are you doing in your office when you're preparing there
I guess
So the next headline
Proves that Bill Gates
Is in the mix
Analytical
LabCorp
I can't believe it
Foundation
That's right
But this is a different side of the business from the eurofins that's in Luxembourg North America
Answer food division that purchased a different company called Craft Technologies
Car Technologies
Had received a Gates Foundation Grant back in 2015
Is a very weak connection but the best Alex can do it
Why the f*** not pretended mean something
Got them
So that's that's bad
Headline that really is to make this case
What continue coronavirus testing delayed
That's the same story
The Daily Mail and the guardian and then he brought up and now the last thing
The Daily Mail it's all just the same headline about the same story that is being able to
Turned into
A narrative about China having sent these because of the manipulation of the national file Hadley
So what you have here is a load of bulshit
2nd episode
But that's not how it is
Because it's Alex Jones
Auto-tune your family right now in Fort Worth Florida
That's what it's all about Adam
That is what it's all about
Get this really intense
Spilling of China affect the world
We're all going to die world
By myself
What is Gammage
For the lowest possible state
You know
Making enough money off pills down to justify
Well that's a problem like I'm saying with the like the escalation of his rhetoric has nowhere to go
Already at the point of life
Any rational person listening to this that believes with Alex's saying the natural conclusion is call for
Yeah
There's nowhere to go past that I look
I get it if your Chiquita banana of course you need the United States government to overthrow a bunch of
Governments for you
That's that's just got to be done
But I'm not going to war with China over f****** zinc sales from the red pill
Based on wachowskis
Different types of different Wachowski movie
Yeah this is
I wanted to hear about qanon
Still build
Instead I was just
The f****** messy getting rid of the whole serialized and episodic
Nikes
I do think that it's
It's very difficult to do episodes about Malta
Multiple episodes of this show anymore Jr to f***** up
Getting to a point where it's just like
Like this is a dude
Losing it
David David
Out of
Yeah so anyway this episode has been
Interesting I always enjoy when Alex gives me a chance to try and take him seriously and he failed once again
In one go records
But until then Jordan website
We all relied on this ugly go to activate leaving review it's at local charity of your choice
Build it back but until then Neo I'm Leo I'm dzx Clark I secretly Road V
For Vendetta
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with your trip and I love your work