Collegeboard.com
I have great respect for knowledge but I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guy
Need
Dot-com I love you
Little bit about Alex Jones
Indeed we are.
Jordan Jordan
Whatsyourprice
You go first
I go first
I assume this has nothing to do with WrestleMania so I will say
That my bracelet as we were on this week's episode of opening arguments
Thomas over there real appreciate to have a conversation
Illegal podcast
Ton of legal questions I have about Alex blanketly like
You can get away with saying at unshit yeah it seems like my main conclusion for being on a log podcast was
Everything Alex Don't Shoot Me
And yet somehow it's
Yeah yeah
It's super fun and thanks to them again for having
I doubt if you I've not heard it
My bright spot
What is Night 2 of WrestleMania from Sunday
I am shocked
Cheers in a jigger
Yes to the radio
And add the last man standing match
They built up a great
Feud between two that was really engaging as a storyline but that match went on 40 minutes
40 minutes 40 minutes I got very bored
Difficult to beat up the other person
Can't stand up within 10 second always the tension of but getting
Seconds and struggling to get to your feet of course of course
Such a f****** stretch Tyson Punch-Out rules
But all of that was banished
From my mind
After the John Cena and Bray Wyatt
Firefly Funhouse match
The best we were talking after the show and you were like
What I'm looking at
The scene has a habit of pulling out people's old
Pass characters
And then I recalled edibility of
Overtime in space
He also has a character Bray Wyatt is possessed by this demon called the fiend
That has superpowers of some sort
Like their psychology or something and show them something of themselves that maybe they didn't want to ask
OK Google
It was masterful
The short film that they put together and cuz it wasn't a match
Wasn't John Cena fighting
Bray Wyatt
What it was was basically a short film
The audience was taken Inside the Mind of John Cena
John Cena's the most
Like the biggest
WWE wrestling Superstar from like last 15 years ago
Did the hero of the
The children be like the bigger
The top of guy in the brexit team time world champion tour
Seeking inside his mind and thoroughly deconstructed
To the point where he accepts
He's the bad guy
It was
Remarkable
What is going on
First of all the
Bexar does the complexity
And the story is something I
Did not imagine the WWE's capable of
Like giving the how big of a person he is and how much he doesn't need to do something like this
Bray Wyatt
Put him into a psychological prison
No he's auditioning for Shutter Island to that's the days you're going to feel next I think that's
God it was good like I really I had very
Scared expectations about it
I'm an old-time Bray Wyatt
I mean as much as I am a wrestling fan
That's my kind of thing original character was a swamp hillbilly cult leader
Ramblin weird riddles
Absolute nonsense so good
Impenetrable want something like really to workout and then nothing
I never does his is a story lines always kind of fizzled a little bit
But until I have to take a real feeling that like this was going to be another one of those things
Cuz they tried to do some Bray Wyatt like spooky house matches in the path of his master
I just really thought they were going to do that again and instead what they got was a scathing portrait of
First of all John Cena's character trajectory through his career to the WWE itself
Haha
Vince McMahon
Deeply emotional resonance
Because
Throughout it
Character of Bray Wyatt is sort of guiding John Cena through these realization
To recognize like
This thing about himself and because of John
Ego
Recognizing leads to the ultimate conclusion of John being destroyed
David Lynch is working for the WWE for one night
I will claim that I'm not like a huge wrestling fan
I don't think that I am in the same way that most people like wrestling
But I think it has a remarkable potential
As a storytelling
Medium
Both earring matches and stuff like this the characters that they're able to build
Because you suspend disbelief to the flowers like
You get a demon anime
Cookies neon shirt wearing a fake soldiers last battle rapper
Geico
What are you guys think dick Whitman is more believable I am just I like the medium for the things like
That that it is capable of
Very proud of them and it's very big break
Canadian visa this week
Loved it I'm glad I watched it a second time.
Yeah I had to go back and like
That those
I watched it the second time the next day cuz I walked away from it feeling like that was
Tacular
I second-guess myself
I don't remember to be clear I don't want them to do a lot more of it
No absolutely
Probably f*** it up
Yes
Compared to the Undertaker matches
Did your feelings on that I would not have been as bad as I thought it was corny as hell
This was corny
In some ways but with
Perceived be a lot more depth to it
Okay I don't know the difference between do you want like a goofy 80s Thriller action movie
Horror movie or do you want some like 10 psychological Thriller
It also gets a little cornball every now and again
You can't go wrong
Unless you talk about Oliver Twist
Yeah you can
Get some weird like
Union nonsense going on here wrestling a scrape
Ever get into today's episode where we're going over April 5th 2020 baby
We are going to
The first Galaxy
Fire
Galak fyrir thank you so much
You're not a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Emperor checks
The flatulent thank you so much you're now call if you want
Sarah SM
I can serve ever
Xavier
Policy wonk
I don't like
Alex Jones erotic fanfiction Society
Are you very much Alex
Mission Society
First of all Chris thank you so much you are now a technocrat
Charles
Thank you so much you are now a technocrat
We got to go.
Heroin
Chick-fil-A large
Thank you so much Chris and thank you so much Charles
Member of the conspiracy
No that's only for Christmas
Or you could find a local charity in your area to help out with the folks
Yes we would like both
What are the other
Alright
Jordan said I said we're going over the April 5th episode of Alice the show here's the thing
Bathing B Cassidy over Project Camelot
I just didn't I didn't I wasn't finding a lot of inspiration and some of the places that we might look for Wacky Wednesday
Episode
And things got kind of kind of weird with Alex to cuz you put out a Saturday
Episode of his show that was
Long
And boring
And awful
So I wasted a lot of time listening to that Friday's episode is no good Monday
He was out of Studio
Wasn't into it was meant to be on the 6th cuz he was in Family Court
He was having to deal with that emotion
That to his ex-wife it filed
Right
So you thought he was up Studio that leaves us really
Only with April 5th the Sunday show
And we should check in on this so I wasn't actually I actually think this is a pretty important
Cover because
There's something really stupid fun things here but also there is a development
Some narrative that will probably be a problem
We start off
Alex
Pretty do me kind of feline
We are live ladies and gentlemen hummus April 5th Sunday transmission which is down
IHOP
Attalla Fishel the United Nations has released guidelines written by Bella morte agates found
Or go back to work under the new worldwide martial law
Until you been forcibly inoculated
Okay alright
You did not find any evidence of any of that stuff but
Vegetarian little something
So on some recent episodes
Assertive coming into into existence
That is
Comparing the coronavirus to the flu
Pasty started to really get more interested in talking about it as cold
And I think part of that is because
Maybe someone told him that coronavirus is in the family coronavirus can cause
Common cold
And I think that he's like you know what people are way less afraid of the cold than they are of flus
Run with that
Really downplaying try and get as many people here this week
Yeah so now that is evolving
And he's starting to suggest that people who are testing positive for Coronavirus
Covid-19 they actually are false positives of God because they have the cold
I'm not joking around
Common cold in your life
Chelsea everyone that medical doctor come on show about this
Medical doctors
Lung problems or other diseases
Old
Heart attack
Telangana
You died of Toby
Create
So I understand Alex's desperation to come up with a conspiracy here but what
Justin does not mix
Partially because it's a scientifically dumb but more importantly because he seems to be ignoring a very little relevance
Statistic
It's probably safe to say that literally everyone on the planet
Planet has gotten the cold
Most people catch colds at least once a year sometimes a couple times
In a year
If it were the case that the coronavirus test for just creating false positives reboot had the cold
You'd expect a did he wouldn't see so many of them come back negative
How does Alex explain that there have been almost two million tests done in the US and only a little over three hundred seventy thousand of them
Positive
If it were really just catching the common cold that number would be much higher
In order for Alex to credibly even suggest
This conspiracy I'm going to
Need for him to deal with that gigantic
Problem in the beer
How would she want to because you're pulling
Things out of that
I doubt it
False positives from the cold man
This is also one of the
Situation
And where
There's a
Deserve
Media
Blackout over
Like you can't show any
What's going on
People are being intubated
People are coughing up blood they are they are this is how people are are dying their lungs are f******
Exploding
That is not the goddamn common cold
No by no stretch and if there was some if there was a more general knowledge of like
This is how people are dying
It would be real hard to sell the common cold there
Yeah I would have to sell it anyway
Says words
So he has now base this he's established this narrative that there's a lot of false positives just people have a cold
And Egyptian to predicting the future
Where anybody who dies they'll say it's Coronavirus
I'm cold
They will make sure
They're going to roll it out
You got
Antibodies or you can't work earlier house
That's all
The one thing is really thought about this narrative this thing of the vaccine
I already existing
It started when Alex began covering the internet conspiracy about the pier
Attitude which held the patent free does vaccine for chicken
Which was completely misrepresented you know just because it involved
Coronavirus
Chicken factory
What is the Coronavirus
Hey don't worry
This is fun because that conspiracy before Alex picked up on it it all traces directly back to Jordans
Who's a big qanon guy
Alex is in the middle of this supposed to war against
Even recognized or accepted a bunch of his information and narratives come directly from the very people
He's attacking his idiots
So I was watching Alex's show from Saturday like I mentioned and he had Francis Boyle on the show where they discuss this Gates patent
Situation
In that segment they addressed the fact
The purebright patent is for chicken
But then they claim that there are other
Oh okay well that helps which Alex been flashes up on screen
Sure you can Google him I'll give you the patent numbers
One of them is US patent
10130701 B2
This is for the pure Brighton
Coronavirus
Alex just shows the first
Page on screen which is good
It says that
Coronavirus
Purebred
But if you scroll the page for you to your grass
There it's about the incidence of sneaking
Which is a thing that chickens do
The second graph is for wheezing
I guess humans do to
However the y-axis of a graph is quote
Percentage of birds affected
This is just the chickens being again
Alright you're telling me that no people's neck
I think people snake all of its
That's just a thing that normal people do as I understand it to be correlated issue
This guy
Adobe
So the other one
That was about
The only other patent Alex shows.on are is a filing from the European patent
Number 1575
3.5
Which game is just a b chicken vaccine
Alex has nothing but I will grant videos a whole lot of nothing
It's true he has tripled his nothing
Yes yes
And all of it off
But he's mad at me
It is
It is hard to
Focus on those
Styx hear what you said he is
What is it is very difficult because this is so awful
Yeah
Also like with this like he's
This is all just arrived from Jordan sather stuff who was a huge qanon guy
They like to visit
Today is the day that Alex unmasked
Studio C
Microchip out that's my guy
So Alex gets down to talking about the house
The gate spokes
Cuz they already have this vaccine injury
Sure
But they're also doing this tattoo thing the tattoo that'll give you your virus record
Stuff
Apparently
The Source on this
It goes bad
How about this for a long time
Covid-19
A digital tattoo
Nanotech
Black light
Have your medical records
Cut it out a digital
DNA mark
I went to dinner with us tonight
Church event about the microchip
God gave me a vision it's going to be a DNA tattoo
On the left
Okay bo back then
And I was like
Do you like move to another state
Was it
Ladies and gentlemen
That guy is hanging out with your friend of yours in high-school girlfriend state
Christian identity
I believe head vision
Good night bro
You didn't break anything uses
Reporting on another article in some some publication about this research that was being done
We can't they don't have the technology to do these tattoos yet
Alex
To break a story
Certainly doesn't have that to have brains
So Alex gets into legit lying about primary sources that stuff starts kind of slow
Picks up at the end of this irresponsible starts off a little slow
Talk about
Actually went to Berkeley and gave a speech
Everything
I remember
Publix
Is not
Didn't say that
Is a futurist
Projection of the world
We want to build my 20
Did say that
Crazy person
Contemporaries
Talked about diet injections and injunctions controlling you and making you dumb answers
Vaccines are trojan horse piggyback
With
Systems that lower IQ
So none of that is accurate from the Brave New World Revisited
I highly recommend speaker
And you can get a little bit more context of what Aldous Huxley was actually saying in that speech it was mostly about
The comparison between
Himself
And Orwell 1984 system versus
The Brave New World System
What which which would be the more likely version that this
Could rise up in
That's kind of what he was getting at this is our plan as we doing haha sucker
Absolute
But the other part they're his contemporaries. But Bertrand Russell
Right now
Diet injections and injunction
Send blind
Alex just takes out of context we talked about this a bunch
Bertrand Russell was talking about what would have happened if the Nazis had won World War II and had become a sign
And typically run system
Amazing they were that to be the case
Had the Nazis won
Which is a bad thing didn't want to happen
They became a scientifically run system
Diet injections and injunctions
Control the population
This is not them saying
This is what we're doing anything about like
Hypothetical situations or analyses of
Sting's
This is what everyone
Right. It's very weird I mean it's it's
Go back to
Obviously
Doesn't he doesn't do this with
Other
Things that don't with that work against his narrative
Also
Bertrand Russell was wrong anyways
Because as we all know the Nazis won World War 2 + 20
60 that's pretty much how it went down
Two ended but then there was a re-emergence
Yeah the Nazis Nazis had a great comeback
Back is bottom of the ninth
President
And then they swung for the fences
Speaking of pretty shocking comebacks
Alex has been really against the globalists in their extermination plan
Him sort of coming around
Well it's not a bad idea it's just there the one
Yeah it seems like that wasn't what is really starting to feel like
They finance
Is pretty lazy
Doesn't cramp
Maybe Bill Gates is right
Not fair
Okay
I would say that if you're hearing person
I don't know why I like
Extermination of the population is warranted because people are lazy and dumb
Miniature pit
Exterminator population all those folks
God kills road so no one could be fine and you know
God Exterminating people all the time a God-fearing man is probably Pro extermination lesbian
It's it's
Seems like a misunderstanding of some of the finer points
Christianity
You know people
I think that the New Testament is a bookie
Great nice disagreeing
I think
That it is ludic
Chris and also very fun / scary
That Alex is now coming around to this like
Pocket The Golden Shoe
Entails
Mbway more fine with
Mass death
Yeah
Like I don't know Trump do something f***** up
As long as it's couched in the sort of
Framing
Fighting the globalist
Or whatever
Why should I
F*** you
I killed by a backstory
But there aren't dark moments that I've had looking at Biden poll numbers going
You-know-what f*****
I got nothing for you you guys want to do it you do it
I'm not saying nothing
But that's not a way to live your life
There's a difference between the service moments of Despair you might have of like
We are we are not going to make Prague
Those are those are
Tough moments of reflection much like me
Before
WrestleMania Night 2
And then the dark
This comes right
Well maybe not but
There's a difference
Between that and being like a long times I have prophesied if I ever needs would exterminate everyone and I
Dedicated my life to fighting against that Bubba have f****** maybe the right
There is a difference validation of Alex's protect
Everything
Bill Gates's Redi-Care
We'll see what happens
Well so we have this next clip Alex
Has had
Famous people
Call there like a man
And you're right
Ted Nugent
Probably
Bragg's
Rock stars movie soundtrack
National talk show host
Well I thought you were wrong you really a right and and I'm going OK Google do something
Nothing to me
I want to talk to you
Monisha
Right
Alright bye
Come out and do something
Alright you strfkr
Hold on what you got is going to lose everything
We would fight
On average
Soft
And we're stupid
Okay
Even further deserve to die
Good
I don't know he's Rich famous super-mega stars are but I do love you I do love the idea of
Thanks for telling me I'm right but if I can't get any PR out of this I don't give a s***
Christopher Walken
Can finally call her back after all those
He's just calling back he doesn't want to tell Alex he's right but he has another chicken wrap
Listen to the bells a little bit more read
And I got to say you're right
To you
Who do you think Alex's
His version of like
Really famous like
Megastar
I don't know I
Play me some country music
Willie Nelson's drummer
I don't I don't know who this I don't know who these people are and I guess probably never will
So Alex has Gaston the show and it's a guy who gave a speech at CPAC at the z-pack
Of course he sucks
Is
His speech at CPAC was pretty boring
Is just bad comedy
A real tough time with it
Based on this interview he's Rising the ranks in terms of like people I really dislike
He has one of the most annoying
Speech delivery like just the way he speaks very very annoying
Very condescending
Epic Dodge
The world
Won't check it out
Another bright side
The Pampered Pet Shop
Comedy
Story
Breaking down the fact that
A big money
Nope
Bill Gates is running
That's a very inaccurate reading those
Philanthropy
So it's so weird how whatever these people are getting Patrick
Howley's credit
Holly Hawley
How we adjust lurid why where I grew up so I do not entirely.
Patrick Holly
Forget that he started big
Politics
What does just a shity right-wing conspiracy blog that eventually sold to a right-wing political consultant
And it continues to exist as a propaganda Outlet in some cases for the very politicians
The website that never comes up almost like even though they know it makes him look superb
Credibility
They say when you come
To politics
You got to get it in
X is not one of us out there
It's a rapidly conspiratorial publication that Alex just likes because
Ferociously pro-trump
And super anti-cheat
It's run by the
Falun gong religious movement
According to reporting from NBC News
Former practitioners of Silent Kong told NBC news that Believers think the world is headed towards a Judgment Day
When those labeled communist 2bcentral kind of hell
And those sympathetic to the spiritual Community will be spared
Trump is viewed as a key out of eye in the anti-communist fight
Epochtimes employees
You can see how it's really be into that kind of editorial position
It's run by the spa
Okay
On October
The October 17th 2009 the founder of the following Kong movie
Spoke to the staff of the epoch times
In the message that was sent was a little messed up
It's very clear that the newspaper is in
An extension of an apocalypse
Religious belief that looks forward to an Ultimate Clash with Communism particularly in the form of
China
From the speech
Beach quote
Visions of the epoch times in other languages are crucial as well for dafa disciples are the sole hope
For salvation for the world's people whatever corner of the earth and have it
It wouldn't work if I leave humzy who serves as the master to the Disciples of dolphin took on this work as we
It's something that you must do
My involvement will happen later
After the fall rectify the human world
Before the time of the Fall rectifying the human world you must save more people
And allow more of the world's people to remain
In the process of clarifying the truth invalidating the thought and saving the sentient beings sugar enabling
A people to survive the great catastrophe
And the only just portion of the human race will be worthy of seeing
During these stage of boz rectification of the human world
The true picture of the cosmos and all that is occurred so
The world's creation
Only
After that we'll I commence fall rectification of the human world
Many things need to be done if this plane of existence has to be kept for human affairs
Are really not so simple
Saving sentient beings is something that has to be done by you and during this. You are given this path so that you may
May establish Mighty virtue
With Your Righteous thoughts in action
Head towards consummation
Most of the beach is about how you need to get this in line like
Normal media Outlets
Alright everybody
You do all the work and then after it's over
I will definitely help out
And that is nothing at all like a cult leader and it's nothing at all like hey if I were like
Really directing everything here people would see what's up later
You guys got to do this because it doesn't really look like
I'm
Exerting my will through this publication
It's not ideal
The situation between falun gong in the state of China is far too complicated for me to unpack here but please don't take anything that I'm saying
2B minimizing of the repression
The China has engaged in regarding regarding religion
Absolutely I'm not minimizing guide at all answers
You know just because Fallon Kong Run
This paper that is
Bad as f***
Doesn't mean that it's
Within
A reasonable response
Incarcerated
A depressed people
Yeah yeah
But anyway the point here is that this is not a good news source
Is there any communist propaganda Depot run in the service of a religious mission
Can you believe that's heading towards in Apocalypto
Standoff against demonic communist
Oh and also yeah you know there's a lot of overlap
Now where they differ Jordan is at the epoch times has definitely promoted the qanon conspiracy
That's the only one okay
It's almost like
Batteries
It's almost like there's really no difference they're beating
Into just about
Anyway Patrick Ali also writes for them
Yeah he's a hero
Do Alex believes that
Bill Gates is out to get him
Because
Garcia's
Like the good doctor Ali shows
Is dumb
Asian gentleman
I want more than Facebook
Yeah that is more I need more than
Demonstrating some way that Bill Gates is behind lawsuits against you
It was Bill Gates did he buy osaki
Absolutely
I miss Soros or somewhere of course
Gates
I love I like the I like store
He's actually
Seems to be a
Fairly good guy
Where's Cape Cod
Cirrhosis more relevant to the like antifa narratives that Alex has
So the contract contracts
I think that
You know
Certainly antifa isn't getting
In the mix
Well there's a
The quarantine going on
Appear whenever there's right-wing demonstration
And so
Tell Patrick jumps in and I got to be honest I don't like this guy but
What you got to give up to him
You got to tip your hat to the fact that he is using
Good at saying he has sores
What the hell's going on here
Insiders
And
I am
Thesaurus
Back to Insiders
$0.01
We do agree with you he has the most annoying speech patterns
It's rough it is really rough listen to this
He seemed like if he was talking about something that I was interested in
I would still think
You are really angry
Yeah
Dude
Calm down you are so mad
Like I would love to hear analysis from other people about the Firefly Funhouse match and it Patrick
He was talking about it I would not want to listen
You're so mad
Talk about how good a match it was still
And he's on the chloroquine
Narrative
We can't believe we're still doing
We're going to be
Hydroxychloroquine
Trump discovered it
Call Mom
Is there a chrome reference bro
These people
Yeah this is a little this is a Little Lamb
I just
Lineup
Just light up the
You guys are
Feel like
There's such a rank misunderstanding about these folks
Got to be careful when you're talking about something like a medication
Yeah they take that to be like you're opposed to it
Actual good human trials that have been done that hydroxychloroquine
Was effective
I don't
Think that anyone would be against it and no one is saying like hey
Cut it out
Reel it in
You can get people hurt with talk like this
We've already seen some like at least one
Documented death
From people taking this advice
And the possibility of a lot more does
Exist that's what you have to be careful with those things
That's not being anti chloroquine or whatever
It's such a
Such a stupid black and white way of looking at
It is it is interesting
If if we accept the hypothesis
That Alex
Knows he's
Lying about
Yes then it is hard to take his opening
Bank statements
Everybody's f****** stupid and sheep and I I just I guess maybe they do need to get rid of
As being anything other than him talking about his
Is Brett
Well we know he complains about his friends a lot
Exactly and his listeners like this
If you believe with Alex
Alex is talking about
Might be
Put away
Fauci
You know he's coming out here and he's saying the chloroquine the devil they spray
But it turns out
Used to be into chloroquine
Obama like this
And
Bobcat
Coronavirus
Stay-at-home order
Freedom
You're a shity Lionel
Donkey Kong
100 million-dollar Grant fears go
They were arguing
Begin your job
So many selfies history as it relates to the HIV crisis
Is simultaneously a complicated one and a not so complicated one
The HIV activist to put him back then exactly the sort of government bureaucrat
Kind of guy that you might expect
But he was receptive
Alyssa
And eventually became an important Ally in that Public Health crisis
Oh that's a recipe for getting killed by the right-wing in 2020 an article on the body
Epro discusses how
He dramatically loosened HIV drug clinical trial requirements so that a far greater number of discs desperate
Patients could try new compound
An approach called parallel tracking
Expanded research on hiv-aids and its treatment in under-represented women and or people of color
And gave activists and people living with HIV seats at the table
Of the planning committee of the AIDS clinical trials
Group
The article quotes
Jim iGo who was an activist with Act
Stop who said quote
Thought you was a sparring partner with us
Then a friend
They also quote and Northup Northrup
Another act up
I would say that at the beginning of his encounters with us he was a pretty typical bureaucrat
Making excuses for the slow pace of drug investigations in approval
I still give him credit for turning into someone who listened more to the activist point-of-view and eventually became more of an ally
They're definitely plenty of criticisms that could be made of his and any government entities handling of the HIV crisis
In the eighties and nineties but it's a little much
Say the factory was involved in this cover-up or something
And it's especially Rich coming from Alex who constantly has Jon rappoport on his show as a medical
Expert considering the hiv-2 nihilist who sells DVDs of his lectures on the subject
Nyitcom
Wheat lack of medical qualification
Answer the question of course Quintin burst
That's a completely different matter than what we're dealing with today
One with Patrick is probably referring to an article in NBC news from May 20th 2014 title
MERS cure
Lots of drugs
Might fight virus study finds
Corcoran was one of the drugs that were included in that
Lots of drugs
I'm here's what Anthony fauci said back then
It's a good start
You try to stay ahead of the game there's a host of things were doing
Hopefully we will never have to use any of them
I would need Patrick to provide stronger evidence than this to back up his claim to Tachi was all about chloroquine back when Obama was President
But now he's against
It also
What does Patrick mean when he says that Deborah Deborah birx was appointed by Obama
She was made the US Global AIDS coordinator by Obama in 2014 but that wasn't her first
Position in government
Who's the director of the cdc's division of global HIV and AIDS since 2000
Which predates Obama's presidency
If you was working at the NIH
Obama became a senator in 2040 probably appointed her back
You became a community organizer he was anointed from
Inform
He was appointed as a position by Obama but it means
Nothing
And the stupid conspiracy that he's going on so whatever
It's easy whenever you're ahead guy
Whom you love so much your dear leader has never held a position
Giving government for you to convince your listeners that
Nobody else has eyes
Yeah
Or that everybody who you don't like in the moment their history starts when Obama did something
Quite accurate public servant
I can't imagine somebody wanting to be a public servant to serve the public than that sounds crazy
That sounds absolutely insane I'm going to assume that she's a globalist out
Probably help
Anyway
There's this weird Obsession that I see on Alex's show make another point of that
I'm at is the Alex is only real argument that he has about
How Trump was handling this correctly
How many used to be the Trump secretly declared an emergency
Fancy month ago
No and Alex's stop saying that
The only thing that's really consistent in terms of evidence that Trump was on the ball
He was taking care of business
PCB
Turner overdrive out there
Is the only example he has is the Trump tried to block flights
It's from China
He did it only thing he could have saved us
Flies
You talk as though he acted later sis Walden
He's been a bad guy
And everyone that has
Incredible
So Patrick agreeing with that is disqualifying
Is like
Ramble through a load of nonsense
I understand him agreed with the narrative the Trump tried to block these flights and therefore he did everything he was supposed to do
Nonsense
Tccu directive that literally laid out the
The plans for what
Needed to be done in
The situation
Adhered
That would be great
Right right there is there's a there is a
Hon of breakdown you could do on that show
That front
But Alex does have a xenophobic position just as assertive
The center
And so the idea that he tried to stop travel is like that
That's all you need to do
Which is silly because it's not that Caravan
Now he tried to stop light because I mean
Obviously
I think Anna episode talked about
Spasibo the stuff
We talked about how the
These travel restrictions
Don't really work
They can slow things down a little bit but they don't really work
Because if you have these cases that are identified in China uses
Shut off travel from China
Look some of these cases might already be outside of China
So you can have someone
From
Russia
Neighboring country or whatever
Who comes over
You don't have a travel restriction there
You can still get it
There might be some slowing down of progression that you can do
Maybe there's some value to that but consequences of it are
Our baby makes things even worse
It's a complicated picture but
It's the only thing I would stairs about but I understand the idea that Patrick would agree with that
The fact that he's just like yeah
When Alex is saying that anybody who tests positive for antibodies to the Cole
Any kind of Coronavirus
Is
Being called covid-19
Is he even have anything to base that on
He gives no citation no evidence of that at all
I I don't
See any reason to think that he's not just making that up
Yeah cuz he's
Probably making it up
Patrick's
Communist propaganda gas and guy so
What was the b******* I was about to
Why not agree with you now and skip that
Patrick might be about to swing you
I doubt it
Cuz he's been talk some s*** on Joe Biden okay
Now I still doubt it
Tubi
This is an instance where Joe Biden be done dirty
Corsi is because criticism that you have a bite and are almost
Equally applicable to make up some b******* this one is also from 2005
Yeah that's good to Roberts confirmation
Joe Biden
You up
The mark of the beast
This guy is an Angry Kid
I've never been checkmated more than I haven't seen anything in the Bible about vaccine
So this is really fun
All these dumb dumb conspiracy theorists like to trot out this quote from Joe Biden during the John Roberts confirmation
The claim that bike wants to microchip everyone and bring his into the bark of the Beast or whatever
This always use in a recent post on National file
Will be faced with equally consequence
Precision for the 21st century
Can a microscopic
Quick Tag being planted in a person's body to track his every movement
There's actual discussion about that
You will rule on that mark my words
For your tenure is over
Can brain scan be used
To determine whether a person's a person
Inclined for criminality or violent Behavior you will rule on that
It's sort of a quote is one that is begging for surrounding Conte
What do we take a take a look and listen to abide with
Actually saying that we don't have recordings from 2005-10 that's too far in the past
I actually bought one of my magical powers
Is I go back in time
Cuz I believe our constitution is
Is big and a
Is Grand and a
Is great as its
Archives
Journey did not stop
Women being Barton
Being lawyers
With 10 year old
Working in coal mines or black
Forced into differ
Preschools in white
Because
The Constitution
In the concert
Does it mention
Texas
Emanation
Child labor
Segregation
It doesn't meant
Our constitution Journey did not stop then and it must not stop now judge
Then we'll be faced with
Equally concert
Decisions in the 21st century
Can
A microscopic
Tag being
Planning in a person's body
To track his every movement there's
Discussion about that
You will rule on that Mark
Mark my word
Before your tenure is over
Can brain scan
Be used
Determine whether a person's incline
Criminality or violent Behavior
You will
Rule
Enjoy China
I need to know whether you will be a judge
She believes
At the Constitutional Journey must
Continue
The speak to these cars
Consequential decision
Gone far enough
Checking against government intrusion into our economy
Into the most personal decisions we make
What is a critical mode
Whoops Pipers actually bring this possibility up as an example of Robert temperature
Government intrusion into our autonomy
Is that before confirming him
Patrick jalapenos good and goddamn well the next thing Biden says in their confirmation
Hearing is that knows that
Because it invalidates the narrative he's trying to build that out of context quote
This is what lawyers do
Touch bullet for as much as I hate by
James O'Keefe
He's came out with a video professing to show anything I feel like
Go fuc
Yourself I don't give a s*** what you lying piece
To say it's one of those things are like you shouldn't
I mean you can almost always make that assumption and you're almost always be right
You know airing too much on the side of I assume you're wrong therefore I won't take anything you say is being Plaza
Can be just as destructive of a pew
From bikes.
Constantly looking into all of these things over and over again never is something above
Put out by almost anybody using associative Alex Jones I will give them 1% of the benefit of
That's a little bit of a hybrid across for me to give a
Did the thing is like
That quote
You can use it and you do
Like someone like Patrick does
But
The reality is he knows I can he
Unless he just read it
On some
Website completely devoid of context
Any dinner
Look into it
He has to have watched
Cast of Xena
I don't believe that he wouldn't be like wait what does that mean what is he trying to say
And he's not that he's not a curious person he and I
That means like I don't know maybe you shouldn't be in the line you're at
You shouldn't be in
A position where you're conveying information to people
If you are not curious about what that information means
Inappropriate content
And his job is not to convey information is
His job is to spread propaganda
Isn't the perfect line of work and maybe right
So also he is against a Patrick is against immigration
Quite a bit can't imagine
He doesn't like the idea that government giving money to bail out these busy
Genesis
Had something to do with immigration he wants them to he wants these businesses
Fail
Sure
Something to do with punishing
This is weird this is a weird Clara outside
Backward Disturbed
Democrats
Weather
China virus
We're shut down
Guatemala Dustin
I don't know how it's admittedly
Globalist operation
Take any of those things they're saying
Now the thing I think is really itchy
Is Patrick
Polly is
Clearly serious
These companies for
Encouraging immigration
Because he believes it will lead to a Democratic Socialist
Locksmith Corporation
Sure
So that's weird
MoneyGram in responsibilities as f*** it let up
Dealing with right now
The Reeds bilotti's businesses will fail is because business
Is it have to be closed
Because they're on essential business
So when he's talking about this that's
Clearly what
Is trying to be mitigated by these government effort
Yeah you would
I think that doing a good thing would be recognized as a good
What do you mean
Alpha triphala
Talking about small government
Google
Like that kind of like the cruise line
Industry
I don't know anyway
The distinction is very is very weird because he want these businesses to fail as some sort of a punishment because they
Encourage immigration
Can is mine
Simultaneously
He also wants people to go back to work
We've been wondering
Set a one world government
Greta thunberg
This guy gets it
Go to bed
She's go way on the one hand he wants all these big businesses to fail and then on the other
The stock market is going down
Back to work
Nmds are things that are said with him like a minute of each other it doesn't make sense to me
It is
Trump to save businesses
Stock market
By making people go back to work
Risk to their own personal safety
Hate each other safety
But also f*** these big businesses they should go out of business because I hate immigration
Yes I don't get it
Perfect sense
There's there's nobody that I want to
Support
Somebody who looks at
Hundreds of thousands
The people dying
Across the world
Thank God we have a republic
Can president who's willing to look at
I want that's
Damn man
Support you know
Yep
Lying on my craft is
You know what is Annie's real.
You know what I like to do is Alexandra stock-market right
I take a Stock's price
On the exit
Church is not on the y-axis
Gotcha Patrick Ali is gone and good riddance
I do not look forward to his next appearance on the Shelf
Voice is tough
Continuing to speak ever
Even if you was interesting
Has like in the same way that someone like Leo zagami is or something I still wouldn't have a real tough time sitting
Yeah I wouldn't like it
Euless Junior light
Yeah really shity version
Voice is super annoying I do get a lot of feedback from listeners about that pie too much Lionel
It's better than that
So Alex is next
Yes
Start the second anniversary
Thought this was big news a shower we got good news next
You think that.
Chloroquine
Good
Or something even matter I did a bunch of research talk to a bunch of medical doctors at a lot of stuff from today about that
Medical
Almost there till
Myself
On whether some talk about this
Coming up
Bellingham
Multi-vitamin the real red pill
50% off right now you know
You know what just got think they're now I'm not saying this because anything I'm not
Connecting zigs to any
The situation right now that it has zinc in it
Perhaps on episodes prior I have made it baby
Maybe you could use one of these things called a hypothetical syllogism and put together a quiz BB
Equals C equals Seafood
Together on Durant
CiCi's not smart
Figured that
Maybe that's not illegal
So what are the things I think is really funny there's out cuz I don't know if I want to bring this
Information that I
I'm presenting is really important
Health information to you because
I know that I'm going to cause a run on a product that I want to make sure I have some myself
Estranged
Altruist
Two-person rates
Tell you about the Cure
As soon as I already have a bunch of it
How do you know that mice like beat myself
I've been a fan of shows in the past
And I know that when a certain guest is on that show
Like a podcast this is going to be good
What shows up on Google
Yeah that's going okay I'll be Lee's here exactly like that I wonder
There are people who listen to Alex Jones
He's like we got Mike Adams coming up in the like holy
How to get the good info right now getting real
0 dead everybody
I wonder if there is a community of people who like legitimately view his
Recurring guest as
The same way we look at like
NAD daily or Mike Schmidt on never not funny or something
Have to be right there
Has to be something
Let's discuss
That's really sad to think
Think about
That's the reverse of right spot
So Alex Goes To Break
Ups that Mike Adams coming up he's not here yet
But he does have another guest
That is a big old gun on his desk
Noticed that I have a very nice
German firearm
Submachine gun
For hunting
Smaller butt rifles
308 and I've got
338 Lapua
This is part of my favorite gun
Bullseye
Pretty much
What time is it in water yards without even trying with us
Magnified scope
When hunting
But this is this is what I've got my car
Super accurate
People robbing somebody
Robert
Bank robber
Boat situation we are all very often
I'm driving around with my by rifle of the Guard I think the bank robbers
Stop a bank robber look at like the Hamburglar running into the First National
If I hear about what the Dalton Gang is up to I'm going to be there buddy
I love it I love it
I guarantee he's never used
Is that gun if any of her bank robbery
Similars
Situation
I don't want to be a dick and be like that you know like you know whatever having a gun for
Protection and Edsel
Is a categorically a bad thing
Ludacris and so funny
Imagine
He keeps it in his car just
In case of bankruptcy breaks out
What is the right
Do deliver fdic-insured they're mixed up with the Fed
Does it give a s***
I feel like from be more likely to use that rifle in a bank robbery
Yeah
That is such that I didn't like
Mark Wahlberg be like mad if I was on that plane I was.
Misguided heroic
Go away
So Alex gets into this next clip talking about like
Why
Is the Ghana
The desk beyond the fact that he loves guns
He likes to show him
What they lie about
Little kids
Tell you nobody forgot her by vaccine their damn Liars
The car wreck
Play Saint nobody died at Sandy Hook
So Alex Baker completely incoherent
If you track his logic it breaks down like this
He loves this gun
Because it gives protection
Can also be used
In the same way Alex would love vaccines the gay protection
Except they're being used to hurt
Vaccines are bad is there they lie about them being safe
Which I don't know what you mean by that
In my experience the lies about vaccine safety that I've encountered have almost entirely come from Alex's side
Doctors in public health experts don't say the vaccines in or any medication or totally
They generally are pretty clear
Everything comes with potential side effects
But that the incidence of those side effects are almost negligible
Compared to the benefit derived
Vaccine
Also Alex and his friends constantly lie Bavaria side effects
Play Imagine
A vaccine
Vaccine courts are not Secret
People's identity being kept private because that's confidential medical information
It can't be released without invading pay
Patients privacy
We talked about it a bunch of the past but these payments are made not because the courts
Definitively
The negative experiences possibly related to vaccines were caused by vaccine
But because
The system were set up in any other way
Medical progress or be completely stalled
And these people would end up losing almost all of the
These cases in normal courts
The burden of proof is actually way way lower
Any vaccine damage Court than they would be in any other venue
Mostly cuz very few of these people could ever make their case in an actual Court
The comparing this to the situation with people being shot by guns as interesting
Because the folks that receive coverage by these vaccine courts
Protected by them to accept
Yeah the vaccine
They were certain amount of liability protection
Because of the gigantic public health benefit they provide
Which would be stopped
By having to deal with
The time
But gun manufacturers are even more
You really can't sue a gun manufacturer if one of their products is used in a murder of one of your loved one
The Supreme Court decided in November 2019 that Sandy Hook families could
Remington
Which is something to watch
Historically
That's not been something that's worked out because
How someone uses a product isn't the responsibility of the product
Maker generally speaking
I don't understand that concept as it relates to guns perfectly well
And he yells better all the time
At the end there he says the giving a kid a vaccine is like shooting them with an MP5
Which it's not but let's imagine that
In the case of a kid being shot with an MP5 Alex would scream bloody murder someone tried to sue the Gun Man
Manufacturer
Or the NRA for promoting gods or anybody
Accept the person who did the shooting themselves
But in the case of vaccine you want to put the entire system on trial
As opposed to just the Doctor Who administer the shot
Typically I think all of this is stupid
But I only bring any of this up because Alex is trying to use a metaphor that absolutely does not work
Given his beliefs
Unless he's willing to accept a gun manufacturer should be opened up to liability for Damage Done by their product
It doesn't make any sense for him to be advocating that kind of thing for vaccine manufacturers
It doesn't it I mean
If you want to talk about someone who's hurt by like mouth
Practice that involves a vaccine
Isn't that might be the same as like accidentally shooting somebody
But the metaphor doesn't hold if it was an immigrant
Who
It's a malpractice
And Alex Wood
Never ever ever ever shut the
Certainly that would become a years-long running thing
The immigrants are the ones you created
Texting problem with the way he is
And the only reason I think it's actually interesting at all this cuz he went out of his way to put a gun on his desk in order to make this better
For this poorly thought-out contradictory
Yes
What's a good summation of Alex's show
I've got a gun out here to make a point that doesn't make sense
Actually
Goes actively against who I stated principal
Gunn yep that's
Janelle Alex teas that Mike Adams is going to be on
Talk about this new miracle cure
And
Has Alex already got into
Has he already gotten a bunch of the miracle. I mean in the last like 15 minutes
Maybe even bless
I know it's probably a couple
No
Alright well then I can't believe I didn't matter cuz my cuz already put an article out on natural news about desk
What is out
More Ebola
No
No this is actually like
Closer to like
In terms of like the really irresponsible stuff they do
The kernel of reality here is closer to like
This is in the Publix in
Tristan like
Maybe discuss a little bit okay but
We'll get to that ear Alex intros Mike
To get into the the topic of the day
This is a big story naturalnews.com
Whatever you do information War
Burl Ives
Essentially Limited
Material
Covid-19 hours
This right now is my calves this is really exciting news my
News
I think the
Way to defeat the globalist is to
Defeat
The Coronavirus
Because if they can
You keep this thing circulating
We would cut off their vaccine agenda is to be
Even taking much time at all
We can beat it I believe with these kinds
The off-label
Prescription drugs are off pathan
So what we have here there is that what they're promoting is this thing called Ivermectin
Is the name of the the drug
And so will what you got here
It was a study that came out recently in the journal antiviral research
She was released on April 2nd
News report about some research it was down about the anti-parasitic medication
Ivermectin and its possible effect
On the Coronavirus
Their findings taken simply show that Ivermectin could decrease the viral load approximately 99.98
Percent in 48 hours
Which sounds
Pretty exciting
But it's important to recognize that this is not conclusive
And there are caveat
The first is that this study was done on human cells outside the body or what's known as in vitro
So to take these findings just
Assume that they depict exactly how the body would react to the drug if you took it is pretty reckless
It indicates a little bit of a lack of understanding about how the body works
Which is what these dudes are about to
Engagement wholesale
Don't ya
You can get one result in isolated cells outside the body but these cells went inside a human body.
Exist the same way they do in a petri dish
Their components of a larger system that has complicated inputs and variables
They can completely change the results of any in vitro study you might do
This isn't to say that this test
Through this sort of thing is worth
But the results of a test like this or things that should be taken as a stepping stone
Is a sign of a possibility
But not something that's
Whatever the effect
That this
Ivermectin has
On these human cells
Could be
Undone by some biological process within the body when the cells aren't isolated
You don't know
It's interesting
It's compelling
Almost demands further study
But it is not something
That you can say
Gets rid of 98.98% of
Coronavirus taken by people or whatever
Like that is that where you get them
Trouble you just blew my mind
So you're telling me that
The human cells outside
The body can read
Differently than human
Inside of the body
That's f****** great I just found out that you can transmit a disease when you don't have symptoms
Dad I take all of my scientific advice from Georgia governor
That's what I do here they might not even know about the other one
Yeah
It is because I like what I was saying is like this is interesting
And it's not something in the same vein as right the chloroquine because
Who studies were pretty
Cuz I know I certainly would be in no position to know this year
But from what it said on the website of this of this journal this
Antiviral research Journal Review
Just some
Thrown up again
Promising study that shows
Real signs of possibility
However that doesn't mean any
Incredibly promising
Is putting a
To strongly
Yes some potential
What did Emma study itself which concludes quote
Altogether the current report combined with known safety profiles
Demonstrates that Ivermectin is worthy of further consideration as a possible Source coronavirus to antiviral
The study shows that more research should be done and
Not
But this should be promoted as a cure
Without to my car doing and getting ready to do is deeply a responsible
They just jump from one unproven miracle cure to another because
They can't do anything else
Their worldview and narratives has no depth
So they just have to keep moving
Deep crap
Crafting elaborate and exciting things to
To distract Their audience
Realizing their full of s***
And also another element to it is I think that they
To do stuff like this
Because the alternative
Is the stuff that Alex was doing on the last episode that ended up getting into
Cause for war with China
Like
If you if you pursue that path too far
You're going
Tons of people killed
Yep through Street violence against chinese-american
You have to do something like this
To make it so the focus isn't all on Sabre rattle
Because there's another way to do this is just do neither
You can get away with
Influencing a lot of death
Slowly over
Time by
Easier than
You can get away with calling
Infor War
Probably I'll do hold that thought until the end of this episode
Cuz we might also be at War but hey what you going to do
It's a mess these dudes
These dudes are really taking this study
And going
Too hard with
Doing too much
This story is about Ivermectin
Which is an agricultural drug you can buy it
Supply retail stores
Deworming
Drug
Inexpensive
Oh you're getting sick take dewormer I remember him drinking dewormer
30 years ago bro
We miss him
Bro
Hobbit drinking Ivermectin
30 Years bro
Can I eat can't be reached to guest on this episode cuz he died
This is a medication that is mostly a Veterinary medication
There is a human version
But it's called stromectol
That is
Prescription drug
What human is doing is advocating the people take
Animal that's
Really take a step back and let that soak in
The health Ranger is promoting animal medications is a cure for the Coronavirus
Based on his very much inconclusive study he doesn't understand
That's staggering stuff like Take It Outside of the prism of life
Yeah we are we weird in this world so we have like
So much jadedness to the
You just do write that down on a piece of paper and you give it to somebody to read who doesn't know about
That's bleak
Yeah yeah
Like a TV Plus
Like
You got to eat like it was like the guy who's
Been in a firefight
And he's running away from
The Constantino's can't go to a real hospital so he has to go to his Veterinary friend who still knows how to stoke
Pull up and pull the bullet out and
X-Man I can only trust you like that's what we're living in
I'm thinking more it's the sort of thing that Alex Wood
Judge
Someone in a third world or developing country
For advocating
If they
Animal medicine
Yeah it seems like that kind of thing
So it's kind of tough to see that
Instantly or just inundated by the shop.
You Take It Outside the context of a being Alex
Bike
Which means it'll be on Fox News
Hold on
Mike wants to be very clear about this
He is not
Recommending you take her medication
We're not recommending
This for human consumption
I've had people Tech
Paste for horses
People have
It works a little bucket not recommending it
Really feels like you're walking that line
That sucks
I just want to be
Legally clear 100%
Legally clear I am not recommending you take this miracle drug that I am telling you the Coronavirus
That I know people
Who took the horse paste
But I am not saying peoples
I really feel like that's the main line they're trying to walk there which is
So Mike gets into talking about this study a little bit and I don't think
That he engaged with it well
Published in antiviral research
Simian virus
Dengue Fever West Nile Virus Venezuelan
Equine Encephalitis virus
Influenza
Anybody pseudo rabies
Virus
And this is available right
I am not recommending
Not for the coronavirus yet
So this study doesn't show any of those things that Mike is claiming
It references other studies that indicated for Ivermectin as a broad-spectrum antiviral
Mike is really over selling this
Also as it relates to dinghy
Study literally says Ivermectin was the focus of a recent phase 3 clinical trial and Dengue
Patience in Thailand
In which a single single daily dose was found to be safe
But not produce
Any clinical benefit
Maybe something worthwhile here
Information that's available
Kind of talk
From someone pretending to be a health Ranger is f****** premature
This is
Dear overhyping this
Except it's just
Deepa irresponsible
Listen I am not going to I am saying
You should not take this drug don't take the horse
Dengue figure
That cures coronavirus Coronavirus
Pedicures to do rabies
White over it
Polio
I'm not saying that you
Not rabies
Sudo rabies
I'm not recommending
Franklin
I think it would be responsible for somebody to say you should
Bing bing bing bing
Oh man that's crazy
That's crazy
I'm not recommend
Take it but this person on my phone definitely
Is real
So Alex seems to think that what's going on is that the media doesn't like
People taking
Things off label
Right like whatever the drug is they don't like you using drugs
It's for different purposes
Then
X I thought like everybody
Sure
I mean b drugs have
Different uses for Wellbutrin as an antidepressant but itself
Cessation drug
Issue is
The thing that people are pushing back
Against easement
That like
This is an author
Label use
Is that there isn't good science that shows
That this is effective
And it could hurt
So when the president
Comes out and says what up
Hey what are you got to lose
And then the American Medical at everyday
The living
You have living Toulouse
Staffing with the president
That's what people are responding to not so much of vague
Concept of
Now he's complained about this is is dumb
Makes it worse is then
He goes on to name him and might going to name multiple drugs
That are used
Four different things
This might work if the Hydroxycut
And doesn't work for a patient this is another Avenue
What media has been promoting off-label use of all kinds of drugs for for many
Many years.
That's nothing new to them at what they changing their story now but love them
30 years
90s that was a high blood pressure medicine
Now they'll only grows hair
Yeah right exactly the little blue pills were
Your first research has a heart truck
Give men erections so
They changed it to use their as well
Yeah but here's the thing
Each of those cases that you're talkin about didn't get changed just on a whim
Dover trials done
I remember the 90s Clinton specifically came out and he's like
I don't know you guys what Boulders give it a shot why not we got to lose
Exactly what
The difference is the process
The process is very important
Because
If we didn't have that process therapy people taking off
The fuk up things it will kill you and don't actually work
Which is why
Mike Derrick Mike
Ebola cure Adams want to do
Right
Really scary
Level of thinking is really f****** scary
The reason is really scary is because those examples they come up with their like
Is that always works
You're on
Those things
Process
Did people you're mad at right now are
That's their point
Like it wouldn't
Rogaine wouldn't be used
They will grow hair
If there weren't
You know like people who
Try it out there to see
Yeah
It's just such to stupid
Can you not their children
So we have these now
Launch a treat
Hydrochloric
We got Ivermectin
So we don't need
Listen to the demand
This effect is that
Blocks
The replication
Tested against the Coronavirus
Virus is not this
Treasure chest
Available right now
And if they give you a vaccine
F****** run
You get away from them and you takes
Hydrochloric win
Insubuy rovectin
Zinc
Hold up and go back to
To work at the same time get some mud dog heartworm medication and
Do you call it a day
Bright
So you fell into a little bit of a trap there that exist I'm very to
Disappointing and that is that you thought that stars Cove
Was until the Coronavirus
I didn't realize that code to was
POV in the middle of it is Coronavirus 2
One of the names of the eye
I'm fine with their the same thing
But Alex
Doesn't quite get that as well
You and Alex might be in the same time
Thank you
Common Angie
Cereal
Major study
That you're laying to
Are the study is about thesaurus coronavirus too and now it's saying it's in the virus
The same it is named covid-19
We're talking about
Just using a
Print named currently in order for a
Anime YouTube
Yeah different contacts
Tries to bite correction
Like no that is the same virus
And so Alex tries to cover for not knowing
He tried to pretend
Well you know I I I
You got this big study Lisinopril
Antiviral research FDA-approved drug
B2n
Meat rub
Covid-19 explained
Lv2 correct
The coronavirus Wuhan Coronavirus
Cop 2
Vietnam
What happened many years ago was the SARS outbreak
People don't get that
Original name is SARS
Dash covid-19
Trying to really cover for not knowing it
As opposed to you owning up to like realizes that I have absolutely no problem being in the same
Boat as even Alex
In not knowing some
If I was a in
The same boat is Alex in denying that I didn't know something
Then I have a very serious
I mean it's unfortunate that you didn't realize at the same time
Is a nice moment of the differences reaction
I just threatened by cool
Great
Wrong to Alex does
He does
Is it real
You really is trying cover for it that's great
Mike
Looks like Patrick Ali
Is really
No
Taking aim
Rip to the eyes
Dr. fauci
Fauci
Enemy
Underoath
Ida Congress
About
Vaccines
She wants America to suffer and die
Until
He can push
Sinon to
Body in order
Does that mean we just got this
This this inundation
This guy is Trump
Anime
I'm confused as to what the game is
I mean this
This seems alike
We will taking a harsh pivot towards this being
Primarily an ant
Evax
Yeah yeah yeah
You just give they just can't put it at
Fair enough fair enough
They just can't put it aside for like 5 Seconds
Like it doesn't it seems like
Told you you and the bestie
With the expertise he has and the limitations that he's dealing but he's not he's not perfectly in line with Trump
Bulshit so he's a threat
User anime
But that seems so stupid
It does
Just
Well
I mean it's exactly what you should expect based on right last couple years that we've been
It seems like you should like you would imagine it like
From all the stuff we've seen they just be like okay look f****** around for a long time sorry about that book this is serious now
I were or find a way to keep the business profitable while like
Not being
Yeah
Jeopardizing of people's house
Yeah I know this is this
This is that thing we know things are the anime Kill the smart one and it is like
People who are
Of the opinion that
I like all all it will take
For Humanity really come
The threat outside of
If Humanity that
We can all unite around
Sounds like no
Alex Jones will be like
Independence Day is bulshit there are no aliens sure you saw the White House blow up the white house blew up on it
And it's just like know it
These people are daily and they're working with the globalists and they're just trying to scare you saw the glow
You to bring in martial law they tell you that aliens are running around so you shouldn't leave your house
That's just because
They don't want you to leave your house
Will Smith was born in Kenya
Like whatever
You guys are going to try and kill the human race who matter what
Yeah it is really a bummer
Yeah it is it is
A lot of the primary
Directions that this seems to be going on this episode
Obviously anti-vaccination narratives have gone throughout like Alex
The fear of
Imagine forced
Received
But seems like that's becoming a bit more primer
Also
You know
The idea of killing off everybody through a
World War also seems like it might be in Alex's wheelhouse movie about
That this next clip
Alex's
Trying to start a world
Okay
I predicted this in early February
Support the virus
In fact is many other
Countries is
So they can shift the blame away from China
What happened
They're just trying to make sure they can rewrite history
Trump
Instead of
Incompetent
Videos of Chinese trying to spread
What the hell
Again it's the anti-American hatred that's been put in place
Because China
Is what proceed War
The United States in more ways
Weapon
I've been writing about
That recently as well there more attacks coming
Kind of the big news right now
People better be ready
Worse
We're at war with communist China
When is the
The time to
Yeah we already look way back predicted a ground invasion of the United States showing China's over him
Been terrified
This is all kind of in the same vein as some of the other b*******
He's been saying but like
Due to a point where Alex is
Like
What are you doing
Advocating for a world war with China
Yeah it's just like going to be no big deal
Do you think I
China doesn't also have allies you think the brics countries aren't all basically going to formula
Let's not do this again damn it's good versus evil we don't need to worry about the world getting involved
Everybody's going to stay out of the way it's going to be like a 10
Going to be like a
Achilles vs Hector
Scituate America vs. China
Get him in the ring one-night-only we're going to solve this whole problem
No it'll be like
The fiend vs. John Cena
Nation of America Vigo
God that needs
Re-read pretty hard
I just
I think it is
Is so
I think it's I think it's really irresponsible I don't obviously don't think it's going to lead to a World War
In terms of the rhetoric that he's putting forth I keep getting to that point where it's like well
What you seem to want
To happen
Is that
You seem to want
Circumstance
Is that would lead to
No other option
Then
Open War
Between the United States
And China
And
That is a
The hellscape
That is something
I can't imagine anybody wanting even someone who hates China
I can't imagine the morning
Here are the options that
Has tide
Provided us an issue
There is
Global cooperation
Between all of these countries Satanist try and destroy
To try and overcome
Combee
Sars-cov 2 virus
Thank you
Global World War
Killing
An exponentially
Greater number of people
For the sake of life
Ultimate irony to is that like what
He seems to want or the path that he
His rhetoric takes you down is much
Closer to that lockstep scenario is in the Rockefeller
Is nation-states becoming even further insight
Autocratic
At work
Response that is the summation of his entire career as we've learned in the past
3 years
Is scaring people in
Terrifying them
Something so much
That they work
To bring it about
Maybe unintentionally
I don't know what that was
Oh I'm so terrified of addicts
Tater out of a tyrant of all of this s*** and
Thank God we can elect Trump
To stop that
Suspend all election
Enterprise voters into all of his other shoe
Near like
Are you f****** with me was this a huge reverse psychology situation the whole time
Dido
Now I doubt it
Lyrics to stupid
So speaking of people are stupid
Text Mike
Fox bathtub
College
Supposed to be in the context of his
He wants to make about 5G
Oh I was hoping
Is the movie pork
No
I don't report
He's perfectly well but there might be seeing similar
Probably not
5G Tower
His point is that 5G set you up
To get Coronavirus
Because the
The way is it it electrifies your blood or something it makes the cells
Calibre the virus
Wendy's this is the same
As when he was in college
Okay and his buddies would lick batteries
Drunk faster
By the way
This is the health Ranger
I know people
It went out back in town with you with
Drink alcohol and they would get drunk
By having a voltage pass through their fingers they would hold
Battery leads
Alcoholic
5 times more effective there actually get drunk
Due to the electoral process
Yes pushing the alcohol into sells it it makes you more drunk
Yeah man this is like when I used to hang out with the bus potheads and collagen there's a God you got to cost to get off man haha
The bong and you're not really getting high
That reminds me of a I don't know if you saw this press conference
This one was
Not his wife
Dr. fauci
You should not take
Hydrochloric win
Just yet
Because we don't have all the evidence
Think about it in the same way that when I was in
College we used to butt chug and it didn't turn out that made us get drunk
So I think
Strongly disagree I saw in the Lancet
God
Yeah boy
Not good
I really think that
College drink
Making short stories
You shouldn't need a base
Cases for a lot of Health decision
Battery
But if you really want
I don't know if there's any truth to this but I tried to look into it and I did not find any evidence
Electrifying
Voltage makes you drunk faster
Nobody was even testing for whether or not
Licking batteries will get you drunk fast
Some dumb thing that you said
Yeah
So it is next clip Mike says something else stupid but it's all that is fun stupid
This is more paranoid stupid
Blood draws by the way this what governor Abbott announced for Texas you know when they test your antibodies they're going to
Track your DNA to so this is
Lost our way to just secretly
Steal everybody's DNA
Permission same thing with the nasal swab
Get a little bit of virus on that
On that nasal swab that deep cavity swap
Also getting your DNA
This is a way to create a DNA
That's why I'm not going to get
I'm not going to get an antibody test I don't want the government have my DNA
So now they're trying to make everyone scared of
Traffic contaminated test narrative
Curiously absent
This episode
In the
Days
Couple days since then but
Yeah crying about China sending out contaminated tests and now is
Not even bring it up at all which is super suspicious everyone scared because they're going to take your tea
DNA and put it in a database
Do not think that any time you've gotten any kind of blood drawn or anyting
They could do that if that was the intention
Nope goddamnit just
I'm at I'm at the place now where it's like such an unreasonable paranoia
You idiot
Bike
Alex
Trump
Whomever
Contract covid and then curette or shut the
I'm done
I'm done with all these lies about what cures Bully from Mike Adams
Did it
Great
I got them give somebody else Coronavirus
And ends up becoming
The E test on himself
Penicillin and malaria situation that he does the whole thing
Can infect his son and tourism in front of the Nobel Prize can
Becomes a hero for the ages
Good
He's a guy telling you to take cow medicine
Yeah f******
Put up or shut up I'm done with this
Bulshit
So the two of them here talk about this is the last sort of thing that they have
Together
And that is actually kind of interesting
Because
It doesn't belong on Infowars
It can be used by Infowars
Talk about this little bit
And he's just
I got a thank you so much we come back here going to be gone but
I looked it up
Bombshell play from.nyc ICU doctor coven
Suboxone deprivation not
That one minute
I'm coming up with this because
The distance is not ammonia
Very important story this Emergency Physician
The ventilators are causing the lung damage of the running the wrong methods that
The dogma of the medical system is thinking that this is viral pneumonia
It isn't viral pneumonia it's oxygen deprivation
And that Emergency Physician knows exactly what
He's talking about
That lungs are being damaged
I need a bit higher oxygen mix
Different method with lower pressure and just support the lungs absorbing oxygen not take over the lungs
With higher pressure that causes tissue damage
We're going to play with the doctor said I'm sure the left
So this doctor in question is a guy named Cameron kyle-sidell
Put out YouTube video claiming that he seen things that indicate that this is not an ammonia like
Disease and its recommendations
Changing the settings on the vent
I'm not sure if it is good data to back this up but Alex's comment at the end there is really stupid
Like there is an article in like a New York Post
Another art Outlets about this guy's video and he's bringing
To the table
Discussing he's there a possibility that there is a better treatment than
What we've been using
It's an interesting Prospect
But Alex things
This dude's going to get a ton of pushback
Because Alex gets a ton of pushback
For his irresponsible share
I don't know what to make of this doctor and what he
Please bring to the table I don't know
I can't possibly know
But the response that I've seen from
Not Infowars Outlet
Isn't like
F*** this guy because it's not him telling you to take dewormer
It's so 8
Someone saying
There's a possibility that there is a better
Treatment is it
Is there something to this
I don't know we don't know yet
But Alex thinks he's going to shut it down
No
People hate you
How you say to different Behavior
Yes absolutely
Alex says he's going to play that video as he's going to have to break there any comes back
I did not
Are you sure this is
Not like other intelligent people don't know what we're talkin about as accurate as they decided
Decide to join with
Four-legged flattered being offered to be part of the flower
I've always been sober
Every time I got around to Satanist
I didn't feel strong
How much danger I matter how much I may attack
Stop.
Discontinued
He was like an hour ago talk about how people should be maybe exterminated Bill Gates strike of their job
God
What a dick
Also I love you ideas
Chef
Projecting any of his family
The other one of the other things too like in terms of
Friends that I've been seeing a little bit one is the
Flu to cold
In terms of
Discussing coronavirus as the cold
Flu
Losing a lot lately
Alex seems to be getting really
Sucking profit like
Lately talking about how God is speaking through him
Yeah that kind of thing a bit more in this next clip I think is like
Really indicative that
The smarter
I Gotta Wear Shades
I'm in control
What I tell you
It's not me.
Yeah until I don't look forward what I'm going to do to make
Every door that closes other doors open there's profit
It's a real thing
My friends and and don't be fearful
Sodial body
Are you can kill the soul
14 weeks
That'll unreal you were f******
Dancing around like
Absolute Banger Avenue delivered
Friday
Unreal are not in the room I was doing a bunch of religious poses
Alex's talking about Providence
Daddy's
Gets better
God speaking through me
I have this Providence
For a while
I know you lost your job but you got a tithe
To me you because the Lord deeds and so on and so forth and Paula White Cain
Should be the bread
Have to assume Jesus would turn over a table and Alex's Studio
That whole non-violence policy and be like
I really f***** up on this one guy
I'm going to take care of him and then we'll do the nonviolent confiscate Alex's rifle
So he doesn't playing that guys video don't get me wrong I realize that I might have made it sound like he doesn't
But he has no analysis humpback
Also has no analysis for it it's worthless
Until it just turns into like a bit of a
Add thing and then he plays it right at the end of the show
Goes out but
I have one last clip and it's just
Like
Alex
He's been trying to sell his zinc obvious
A lady's been doing
Great well I would say that it's been
This is even worse
You seems to be trying to tell his audience like
Hey look man I don't know
Don't take it for me
The doctors have been telling me to take
A dangerous level of zinc
Sold out everywhere
People debate about how much zinc should you take
Today
100 during this virus
You have covid-19
250mg
Well
Please
But he said you know this is so
Wow
George Soros Bridge breathing down my neck
That is the great moment right there I've got the George Soros people breathing down my neck I'm not giving me medical advice
I see if they weren't breathing down his neck he would they take 250 ml
It's dangerous it's dangerous but doctors are telling me you hate
If you're not giving medical advice
Don't do that
Don't have this conversation at all
Useless
Yeah there is no point to have this conversation
Outside
Some sort of insight you're giving your audio
Yeah and insight that you glean from this as I give you trust
Alex is a source of information
He's talked to doctors who are like hey look this will cause damage but you should take tons of zinc
Because this
Higher
You think that needed time
What's up I would be
Be so much
I would be so much better
If all of these people
Continue pedaling their b*******
Conspiracy theories
But
For now the point was like
Stay home so
Social distance don't do anything f******
Stupid
I'd be fine with
Because at least now we're like
We're just going to do the thing now and then we'll deal with all this s*** later stay home
But we saved you is aromatherapy
Yeah yeah
But as long as you stay home it's on for this
Think you could do that
But I think you could murder
I think you could busy I think I would be
Potpourri that helps you relax
From the virus now that's fine I don't I don't think I would be as offended
That probably because there would still be like
Contradiction
Right
Wilhelm
These guys are just now
Tantamount to a f******
What
Manslaughter
Criminal negligence
I don't know what else
To describe these be like I don't know how else to describe Trump as as anything other than somebody who's
Committing maskell murder rate
Payless
Well the problem is the law clearly doesn't mean anything anyway
Milestone
Yeah it's it's stuff
And what I think I think is really interesting about this episode of particular
That you have the development of the hydrochloric win narrative into the
Ivermectin
And
It's better
In terms of like
Some reality
Right right
But it's still the same behavior
Reckless Behavior
Yeah
These are these dudes
To the level of criminal
Without
Doubt to the level of criminal
Regardless of whether or not there is a law that you can
Can use your ports at this is
Cry now Jordan what pisses me off the most
They didn't talk about you
Well that's tomorrow
I understand. Today is your listening
I understand but I wanted like
If you are building to a pay-per-view in wrestling
It's not like you're going to not talk about the fight your now you pretend it doesn't happen
This is Alex
Called qanon out
A week ago and he has done almost nothing on his show
In terms of like building the feud
Because
Pinky realizes is going to be a butt
I am going
To lap up your Des
Disappointment like
Ambrosia
What hurry hurry
I bet none of that is going to
I just going to be fantastic excited for it
Don't think you get some sort of schadenfreude out of it not at all
To be delicious
Snapped
We will see and talk back
Next episode where we will do you with Alex's
Until then
Yes we are on Facebook
Don't do the whole thing thank you very much opening arguments bring designers
Until then I'm Neo I'm Leon dzx Clark
I am Patrick Holly's diction coach
Alex
In color