Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for knowledge B I'm sick of them
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Alex
Joan Jordan
What do you got for break
Well I just saw that the FDA has send Alex a cease-and-desist letter about his
Various claims products
So in this in this in this moment when you know things look
Weak in some ways I can take solace in
The fact that Alex is getting
More letters about his sales practices
Even trumps
Fda's like weekend
We can't be doing this
I slept nice I thought I'll take a little bit of happiness from that
Pat's
I got two dogs
Play all I do with my time now is take pictures of them and keep positions and draw
You finally figured out to Twitter that's exactly how it works with Twitter is Right finally got into dog pictures
That's how you're going to go viral
Be sure that you put a QR code on those pictures of the dogs
X2r podcast I don't know
Maybe maybe not
I still do not understand q r
Neither do I and I never will.
Sworn on the altar of God Eternal have resistance to qr-code understanding
Qrn
Thomas Jefferson
So Jordan to go to next episode to go over going over April 8th
20/20 abandoned Appliance asking you to bring it back I'm going back and forth
So today I agree this is a really hotly-anticipated episode because this is Wednesday of this week
Damned if you'll recall
Back on April 1st Wednesday of last week
Alex got really pissy but however unlike qanon and no one likes him course and so he decided
To make a threat on air that he was going to reveal qanon side entity is they did not reveal themselves
It Is by April 8th and he's going to do it today you made it very clear that they had until Tuesday
Wednesday
So here is I'm saying that back on the 1st
You know what
I'll just exposed
Deadline
It all
Documents
The based on that
This is real this is not talk I exactly
The literal definitions of those words
Require
I would say that maybe you could look at this in hindsight as an April Fool's Day prank
If he pulled that'll be so bad
This episode
This is not going to be a long episode this is a really bad episode of Alex's show and we'll discuss
You know the will he won't he
I'm trying to play a little game here where I'm like not going to just tell you right up front that he doesn't reveal
I did
Don't worry we'll discuss some of this before it gets out of business we could take a little moment say thank you some folk to sign up for supporting the show
So first of all Jesse thank you so much you're now a policy wonk
Thank you so much and I'll probably walk
Text Josie thank you so much
Thank you very much
Next Timothy thank you so much
Journal policy walk
Activity
I'm a policy wonk
Suzy azzam thank you so much and I apologize
Thank you I didn't lose because people donated on an elevated level
Drew thank you
Technocrat
John thank you so much you and I was like
Democrat
How's your 401k
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
Infowars
Would like to sportsohio with these Jets
Local charity in her area and sports
We would love it
If you did I
There you go
Not baby maybe surprising
Maybe unsurprisingly talkin
Not about the identity of qanon
Not at all it's more about Xenon that's zinc
Trump is come out and he has
Mentioned zinc
In his press conference
But I know Alex is going Buckwild on this
You pretending
He got kicked off of the Google app
Store the Android apps
Because he was like
Tonic water
Prescribed hydroxychloroquine
Scription version of quinine
We're giving our patients
Canada Dry tonic water
Off of the Google app
They said specifically for that
Hydroxychloroquine
I'm just telling you you don't have to
If you don't have a oxygen you died about 4 minutes everybody knows that
Everybody know
Astro
Foods are so
Damn empty
12 Oaks
Get your vitamin D3 yes get your sink
All your multivitamin
Non-synthetic
Absolutely
He had the real red pill red pill Plus
Wow
For adults
I don't know what it is
When I do this showed the preparation of the show there's like
There are different kind of feelings that I have and a lot of the time I can really indulge in and enjoy Alex's
Stupidity and
And all this
I don't know why but today I could not
I could I am sick of the bulshit I am not interested
I just listening to them do that over and over again basically really frustrated
Partially because he's supposed to be revealed who qanon is
Let me out but he's not doing that
F****** rambling about the zinc in his real red pill
Hawkeye this is just
It's not what I want
Exhausting
It is tired of it
Yeah you give up
Going to stop
You really excited like a threat to reveal qanon
Following days
Just like
Propaganda narratives that he's ripped off from Jordan sather and other qanon
Do his big reveal with
What the f*** you even doing man
Is this
God just opened
Potential
Did the keys know released
Thank you for 3 years
Very frustrated
So Alex has been kicked off all these social media things and all this
Big Tech
There are there censoring him
Course
You should be afraid of them
All obviously but you're not
Because they look like hippies
Okay
If they were suits
Scooby scared of them
And then Alex gets a little bit so I don't know homophobic against him
Different colored socks
Burning man that's they're sick
They were wearing
Hugo Boss in a Nazi uniform he be scared
Professional-looking
You just let him
Wraparound
You know because
You can be both
Tearing around
I think it's a little bit of a gross thing or the end I really only kept I clip around because of the
The obsession videos with people wearing two different
Colored socks
That comes up
So I don't understand it
He's just got that you weirdos with your different colored socks
That is like his mom written all over it like when he was but he yells mom-to-be
What the right Fox
Mama
Sounds like actual personal story behind the colored socks thing probably
It's very
Very mysterious
Situation
So Alex has some graphs that he's he's touting
But he purports to say show that this virus at the whole situation
It's basically a hoax
That's because he's pushing this as largely a
Malnutrition
Situation now
Because we're selling
False
But here's the paradox
You're saying Alex you just said that this this thing is a hoax and used to take our Liberty but you're saying a virus is real yes
Millions and millions die a year from now depression
Regular flu
Malnutrition is a giant issue
We talked about it here with Mike Adams
The answer is
How do you get sick
But it's still dangerous
Alex has been saying that a lot lately and I will say that he was to say stuff like that a lot more
Back when youngevity and dr. Wallach where his main sponsor
He certainly said that's her to stuff a lot
More back then
Hasn't been his number one concern for a while now outside
Yeah it's his belief
Basically is that you know you're seeing the number is going down
Perhaps be flattened
The curve is is underway
And Alex believes
He's found a quote
From Dr birx
About
Them taking people who have
Tested positive
Who died
Included as covid-19 deaths
Yes
And then of course you know there's an autopsy
And it's determined whether or not they actually died
From complication condition
Or bullet wound
Could have been cover
You'll never know the
It's not ever that but that's what I would say
Exactly and so he's
Determined
Context
But he's read that they're just saying anybody who has a cold is now covid-19
Numbers
And so they're they're making fake numbers
That's basically where he's at it's very boring
It's fun to me
That that ability to just like wave away a very reasonable criticism with lies like
He's like now
You're thinking
How is it that you can call it a hoax
And then one second later say the virus
Is real well
Here's some b******* that doesn't answer that question
Know that still doesn't answer the phone
Get some zinc
You can't just bring up like here's why
Captain Kirk
Not going to happen
You answer the question
We see the numbers are going down
Sort of
I guess
And Alex has an explanation for this video has absolutely no basis in the inmate
Are you get sick
People have bought it off the shelves everywhere
Why the numbers going down
McLeod
So there's your private messages you're texting about chloroquine the AI I'll shut you down or something
But yeah so apparently everyone's gone out to the store and bought this directly chloroquine and that's why
Numbers are still illegal
It's iffy might be getting another letter
Somebody saying that if you have it it'll help that
Cargo depth
I'm still going to go with us
It's not the it's not the kind of thing I would like to see out of him
So he's pretty mad about the New York Times
Because they have recently put out
An article that
Discusses
A little bit of a financial stake
Drum pad
In a company that produces hydroxychloroquine
Well I mean I think he's probably more mad at other
Peoples
Tweets about the article than the article itself would assume that
Cuz here's his take on
I'll show you the New York Times
Trump
Pushing hydroxychloroquine
Money they went and looked at
Folio he had and he had
Less than four
$100 at the peak of the stock market
$135 at the low
$29 oh yeah
Evil Base John
Did report on a small investment that Trump has in his funds
Not even a direct investment
These funds
Invest in a company called Santa Fe
Which produces Plaquenil
Does the brand name of hydroxychloroquine
I don't think that most of the reporting surrounding this suggested that it was his motivation for touting it as a miracle cure
I think that's probably just
Sweets that Alex is off but I think it's understandable for people to have that reaction on Twitter like Trump is corrupt as hell
So what do you have the appearance of impropriety
It's going to give people like
If you are going to give him the benefit of the doubt
Yeah where am I
Like five or six Senators now who have
Committed up very obvious Crimes by taking
Secret information and using it to make money
That seems like now is a good time to remove all better for
For the doubt for election
Officials announce
Stealing money
Sure
Yeah it's
It's a mess and I understand
Like
You know there is there was also the article that
It was about how like Michael Cohen
It gotten some money Trump's lawyer got robbed money guy
The other copy of Novartis but like I still don't think that even the articles that I read about that were
Saying like this is why he's behaving this way
This is
This is why you can't have someone like this be present
Exactly
Cuz the appearance of impropriety is here
All questions and all like all things are up for grabs it's hard to deduce what the
Reality is it be like if Jimmy Carter
Kept his Peanut Farm and then using his powers president
Raise the price of peanuts by 10 million percent
Planners
New York Times They don't want you to have
Chloroquine right there are attacking
The idea of having a
Just wants to push it on you cuz he has Financial intra
But the reality is man
They're all taken it
They're all taken
Are there making sure you
Don't get it because they want my dad's for the economy
Inoculation
It's all official
When do they make it official I don't know
Alex tested every one of the New York Times or hydroxychloroquine
Then who qanon
I don't know if I don't know how this is all officials but
Entire staff
Set the New York.
It's just I don't know what it is they're just something about how I'm feeling
That
Like I hear stuff like this and my reaction to today's to roll my eyes
Bagel Factory
Yourself have fun Alex
I think that's a fine thing either I think we all need a vacation from giving a
I need to listen to him and go
Fart
Yeah it's tough for me to give myself permission to do that because I feel like it's so much like
You know within my nature to all well let's find out if anybody at the New York Times
We don't need to do that f****** fly a kite
Spell definitely
I mean that makes this episode I don't even know if we're going to make it to an hour I'll just episode
Horrible episode of the show
A large part of the beginning is just like
Hey I'm right about zinc and hydroxychloroquine it's the
Need to belabor it
Benny has two guests
One of them is a guy who just interview David Icke
About a bunch of Coronavirus
Conspiracy nonsense
5G makes you susceptible to at what have you
Totally
Hundred percent legit great
Stop this guy probably had his video taken down from YouTube
Or something along those lines
Interview where we wind together about how we're so victimized and we don't have
The show is this useless interview with a guy interview David Icke I don't care
The guy who interviewed
A little bit like that the drunk guy at the end of the bar whose
55 years old near just like
Hey man you seem lonely and he's like you know I almost made it to the majors once and he like off your printout
It's not into the drunk guy at the end of the bar is like I knew someone who almost made the noises
Fieldworks story
So I don't have any clips of that interview with the guy I think it shows called like London real and I just
I died it was listening to it
I could not I could not
Be bothered
To give a s***
I just
You know what you here's the here's the God's honest truth
If this wasn't the episode where Alex said that he was going to reveal the identity of human body wouldn't be doing and who would
I was listen to like her eyes
Go on here something going here nope
Just I have
10 Clips total
You know what bugs me out
No conspiracy theorist are stepping up
That's what really bums me out about this whole thing is that they're all doing the same shity boring lie that Trump
Open spelling
Nobody's really stepping up and give me
Giving me something absolutely insane
They've been bitching about 5G forever and they just had the virus to it
They've been bitching about big Pharma and now they just got there but they're all doing it
We got the globalists and they're doing the whole thing.
Race specific bioweapon
Replace the population with forced inoculation
All of this is the same shift we just added the virus
I don't know man you know what the problem is I bet that there are some really good
Conspiracy theory
Stuff going on in the open
Mike scene in The Conspiracy open mic in the conspiracy Open Mic like weird message board you'll never be
Deep
Review videos on YouTube
Flowering of alternative comedy Oliver
Receipt Erie boom and now we got the
The guys who are really going to work on the
The craft of
Yeah yeah there's
There's something going on bubbling under the surface I'm sure but it's so inaccessible
But you never know these Young Guns until they release the conspiracy
Comedian conspiracy
Pretty
We're stuck in that that sort of
Almost corporate conspiracy
Things down a little bit
Who's giving us all a conspiracy theories now.
The prison of the establishment is giving us our
Conspiracy
Yeah we don't have anybody in the weeds you know
Yep and all the people in the weeds are just slightly weirder versions of the same thing
Camelot is like okay
You believe more life
The same thing but then there's Raptors
Good
That's a real bummer Alex has that guests on the London real guy
Diane play
London fake
0 in
But before that
That was another guy
A guy right never heard of
Before and this guy
Trouble
Use problem
He's a problem for me because
I really have about a
50/50 feeling about even talking about him okay because I think that he's unwell
Oh okay
If you would someone who's on Project Camelot I wouldn't talk to him talk about
Okay okay cuz I think that there is a mental
Unwellness
To him it's not that he wears the same outfit
It's just no
No name is Cyrus parsa
I was probably going to ignore a good bit of this but then this clip happened
And I was like
This is so like this is in our wheelhouse
In the same way that that clip about the people wearing two colored socks this is a running gag on
Electric companies
100 War
Timeworks Chinese and over 600 World Western companies which
Comprised
American companies
I'm European companies and some other companies that in Japan other places
Got my phone
This is
This is deserving of a cup
If you don't want me to sit here and eat a sandwich or not give a s*** that you shouldn't
Sit here and eat a sandwich so great if there's like a guy stop stalking you
Images cuts to like Alex the big submarine sandwich
Surprised by the camera
What is why do you put a giant gun on your desk every day man get a Big-Ass Sandwiches
Just take fingerling B of its all day
Clips
So f****** funny to me like
I get it man
You got to eat
Commercial break
Would you leave me to think that maybe he's constantly eating
We only
Ketchup
How can I how can it happen so regularly during these interviews
If it's happening every
Has to be happy every single day
Then why don't you do it during the commercials there's minutes during the commercial
It's not like he's stuck on are straight for 4 hours and it's not like 4 hours is he gets on Aaron
11th snack
Have a nice meal or something
Kids low blood sugar in the middle of the show he's got to take a bite he's got to keep going
Great Snickers commercial
Alex Jones in the middle of a rant about devils
Snickers
Made it starts about think
It is Eddie's
Because you got to figure that he gets caught like what
I mean even even if you're really bad at
Getting caught for doing so
Stuff you only get caught like
She got to figure he's eating all the time throughout these interviews
You think yeah
And I think
My suspicion is that it is absolutely a sign of disrespect
And it is on
I think you really knows when I was like
You guys are done
And I don't give a f*** if I get caught
Even if it's not intentional sign of disrespect
It's a disrespect
It's also disrespected the audience
Disrespect disrespect to
To do babe Rush Limbaugh
Eat chips throughout his old
Powerful
Powerball
The government is doing
Yeah that's that's good
Pennywise
The government
So this dude
He's what you might call like a self-styled 5G expert
And Alex wanted him to come on talk about like
AI take over
But I just couldn't care and I heard that clip of Alex very clearly eating while talking to him like
Fine I'm going to have to bring up that he's on the show
So I lose listening to it I was like
Okay
He's just he's researched all these companies
And all this in
You know
Whatever
I'm not really interested in
And idea that you wrote a book about Trump
Pain shopping
This next flip is where I got really really worried
About to Alex having this guy on it
I had to wish to discuss
What's going to happen 20 years from now
Facebook
Book the same change about our world
Go to
Take me seriously I had some kind of dream and the future I see
What president
Pick34 become
Empower
Civil War
Chaos
People
All these bad things are going to happen a lot of people
Dream but I put it inside
I wouldn't
Feel like there's more
That's that's really troubling to me
That's the kind of thinking
Is
That's not what I want an expert
Here's what I wanted my 5gx but let me tell you I'm a guy who's into lucid dreaming
I do believe that you can't control your dreams I think there's an amazing power that lives in the subconscious or daughter
But like a
I still don't I don't
I do believe
Lucid dream fair I don't believe
I believe this is a repackage story I believe this is something that he's come up more and more recently maybe
Baby baby
I don't know here's what I want
5dx
I have degrees and things that are unrelated but I saw Seven Years in Tibet so I think I got this under
That was a good movie
Music
So
This dude
Like I said self-styled
I don't know about those degrees
He's a thing has don't know if I agree
Or believe in any way
That he was kicked out of school for not agreeing to
Promote pedophilia
I think that sounds dicey
So interesting Leon April 2nd
This year
This dude Cyrus he posted an article
On his website about Biden being involved in some kind of a bioweapon transfer to China sounds good
That article itself is not interesting
But what's fun is that his tweet
Promoting the
The post
You could be hashtags
#qanon
A hashtag Great Awakening
Which are pretty good indication
Cyrus parsa is a big old guy
Find it the whole way this is Alex revealing who qanon is
Syrup
Titius Lee
He had to fulfill his promise growing through the dude's timeline there's a bunch of tweets these hashtags as well as Q Plus which is
Is the qanon name for Trump
It's so funny on this episode where Alex is supposed to
Expose hookah wise Hampstead is interview about AI nonsense
Also Cyrus parsa is the guy who claims to file the lawsuit against pretty much all of the villains of the extreme right
Quote on behalf of the world's people
On pure altruistic reasons to prevent harm to the world citizens
Like I said
This guy has Project Camelot written all over him
That is a really
Yeah but I'm
That's a pure way of
He's better than the guys we normally talk
And if it takes a little bit of crazy to get there it's better than the crazy that we deal with all day
This is a man who's filing lawsuit
Aristocles
Larry klayman
Imagine you think
Larry klayman understands what altruism
I ain't think that this dude is
Are you all tourism to me is giving Rochester
Stole your computer
I hate to say this
Because I don't know how it's going to sound
But this guy
He seems out of his element
On
Infowars
Like he doesn't seem like he's ready for the show
You know what I mean a lot of people who are terrible and bad gas
Alex has
Barry's Holocaust deniers and
Steve pieczenik
Narragansett
Same thing but
Yo he has awful people on his guests
Presbyterian little
Slicker not as like
Oh no
I looked at I was listening to this on my
You're on this show talking about a lucid dream that you had about Trump
Saving the world
You're not ready
No no no no I mean
The first big show I did is this
Stand-up I was all admit I wasn't ready for
You know I had to either upset but I learned from that experience
I'm sure the next time he goes on and Infowars show
He's going to have it.
This guy
Is going to get it
Well I mean if you get Sinister and talkin
Can do from Alex bring up your dreams
You make us look like Project Camelot
Life I already did that
So lest you think that you know Alex is going to hear this guy talk about his prophecies and
He's going to be like
I had to go
Nope he loves
Martha is
Author researcher
Iceberg
Very smart guy and
Far out his own name for him
Man
That's a commitment
At the committee
Yep so I only have one more clip left
And
It's revealing who qanon
It's Cyrus talkin about how we all owe Our Lives
Insta Trump
I don't think that's true 400,000
The people
Connection of disquiet alone
China
Middle East
You're up
A President Trump China would be enslaving us right now
Wouldn't you have
Save all your butt
For him right now I might be half the country would be dead and maybe everyone else doobie
Everybody including the lap you owe President Trump your life
You better talk to him
That sounds like an angry child
I do agree
I do own apology the truck
If it was
Death or slavery
And Trump stop that with all the other stuff I'm going to have to say sorry
Yeah yeah he don't think it's true
I know I would say that Cyrus is like
Just passed the line of like where I'm comfortable making
In front of somebody
I hear him and I get bummed out
I don't really enjoy
David of
Good that that pm
Just sounds indicative of
Adolescent
Processing
I think it's almost worse
That he is acting like that idea of him acting are
Altruistically it's almost
Legos Alex I get it you're trying to make money you're on your hustle bulge
You know
I'm going to make fun of you cuz you're
Complete a****** liar
Right
This guy is like OU I
You are
Do you really do
That's because
Cuz you are not all
Where you should
Well I don't I don't
See this is where it gets really muddy for me is like how much of that is me over reading thing
Yeah I can only
A little bit tough to say but it's
I don't believe that this dude
Is processing reality
Thought accurately
Sure you have a sense of that from the things that he saying
The way he leaves from one thing to another
I just don't
Do not like Alex having him on his against it really bums me out
It's the same thing with but to a lesser
Third-degree cuz I do
I didn't even cover that
He had that that 12 13 year old who would just say offensive things videos
I hate him having people like that on because I can't cover
Right I can't
I can't do that
It's too nakedly exploited
Yeah yeah I think be exploited for us
To really
Do too much time
What's Iris at least like
I mean
He's at 2 degrees
More degrees than a legend
And I have never been kicked out of a Ph.D for any
He's got that on me too
And if telling the truth this guy
I might be a hero
Well that case is not going to make it through the courts
How to lucid dream in 2002 about that case failing and I got to say
I don't know I went to Tibet to
To pray for that case to succeed Dan so we might be at cross-purposes
Fire fighting it out for that case he's not going to
Alright okay I'm almost certain it didn't get filed and is just an imaginary thing
I don't know man
What's
It's just
Can you do this show
You got to hold on to those things that are exciting
And Alex
When he says that he's going to reveal qanon
Hey Pocky is s*** about it
And he says this is something real this isn't talk
Yeah
I want to believe him
Cuz he's an adult I know
He's a person I know dude somebody
Should just be able to get away with things like that like saying I'm going to do this
Get the documents ready
I meant not
Do it
I don't I don't know I don't appreciate that so we come to Wednesday and
I just I feel
I feel like he's eating a sandwich will turn to talk to me it's just disrespectful
And the fact that he's having this dude Bucyrus guy on who this is
Where to buy fiocchi
Completely out of his death
I am
Acuminata
It's just it's it's
It's a level of self-parody that Alex's
Engaged in that like
I just
Might just be my mood
I'm having a tough time enjoying it
It is something that I want to tell him to stop right right
I got it I got to let
Gotta let you go buddy man
I stopped in
Expect
You know
You hope for the best from the worst people and sometimes you expect
From the best people and that puts you in a tough situation where you're dealing with the worst people who are always giving you the worst
True
And I think that I put myself in the situation
2 because
I've been really
Expecting that you wasn't going to
Of course not do it this time
Course you are trying to and yet
Still you got your hopes up didn't you
Well yeah yeah I've been Avenged
So did like oh here come
The most
Charlie Brown
Make it seem like it was in his interest and there was like there are people that he could have
Pointed to that exist are some names out there if you want to look into
People believe are the people behind qanon
Alex could have gone with any of that s*** like you could have
He could have just reported something that you can find The Daily Beast
Let me know that he needs to start a feud
He's got to start
Refute
Like that's his that's his only real moving right that's what I thought this was going to be and that's also what work
Works for his best
I know cuz he
Maguey mix
It is the same way that like
You know
Wrestling gets
More eyes on the product that is a good fight you want to see these two people go out against each other
It's the same thing Alex needs to get eyes on the product by
Starting up
Good good
What
I don't want to give him advice but I say go after Turning Point USA you're not going to
Can't beat
Nick Fuentes
Nick's already on that space exactly
Nick smooth
No nickel coops
I'm not taking into account easily Nick took over the Seebeck effect
Just thinking you know Foreman
You know he got his ass kicked
Search for a while many came back later in life anymore
Come on man
We got to get one more big win
From Alex and I feel like you got left
I mean if you think about it there's like okay what are you do Steven Crowder
No Crowder will still let Alex come on as a guest every now and again Alex needs that kind of attention
Can't fight him
Turning Point
Not a terrible idea but Nick already owns that
Trump
No good
No
That's then you're going to get piled on by everybody
Yeah that's a space that you can carve out you know there's so many Brave
Never trumper's are all like trying to act like they're aloof
When they're above all of this
Bulshit even though they
Gleefully
Accepted all of it in the past so long as you weren't rude
But Alex could be the only never Trumper
Who is
Furiously and violently insane
I don't know if you'd be the only one but he certainly have
A bit of that Marketplace
I think you're probably right
I think that's what he should
Do but I don't think it will now
He's a coward and and it would
Require like taking a real serious hit in the short-term in order to stay solvent in the long-term I know that he has
I need to do that he can't
Space oven neither
Know what you want is a flashy Feud with someone that is kind of like
Beatable
Yeah
And I don't think I don't think there are many options anymore
Jordan Peterson
Disappeared right
Gone now right now you stop means to lycon
To put that videos
Peabody agreements
Yeah
He's not friends with e Michael Jones
So
I can't do that
I say I say here's what you do
Here's what you do
You you f******
Kiara
Hugo Hugo the old Route and you manufacture Abby
So he
Goes up again
The Oath Keepers
How about that
Oh so they're in on it together the whole time they're playing it off of each other
About the
So they're so
Inline with each other
Let's see
What are we got
I don't know
Aren't isn't The Oath Keepers guy a little bit more reasonable with the hate let's not all die from covid
I'm not sure I don't think so I remember one time where he was like
This is all crazy but you know it's still a good idea
I'll let you know I think that was Mike Adams who sang that for a little while
And you can't get into a fight with Mike Adams
No
And David knightwood before I see I think
I think maybe you the way you do with Palace intrigue
Uolo here we go
Here's what we do alright it's
It's time to put
Our boys over
Yeah I think it's time to put them over the two of them have to start an on-air Feud
At their own network
And then charity box
I could see them getting that desperate
But I don't think
It would interest many people
I think most people just alright
She said
It is a wood bee
And no matter who win who cares
I don't know
Owen
Stuff
Yeah I don't I don't know what the answer is but
It's not this socks man
Walking sucks boo Alex
Boo
Episode short if you want to be mad about it don't be mad at me
Don't be mad at me
Alex is ruining our show that's how bad Alex's
Yeah
Alex had one job
You gave it to himself
He committed to it
He had a week to prepare
Eddie did nothing
He probably doesn't even remember
You probably another
Don't even remember
Damn have a dick
Does he not know that there were people hanging on his every word
That's it
Inexplicably unhappy
I'm not hanging on his every word
Weird words
Yes
How to hang on those weird word absolutely
So we'll keep our eyes on this base and see if Alex eventually reveals cubed
Sure
Bomber
It was destined to happen
You know it sucks though cuz we've talked about this already
Be a disappointment
But you know what sucks
It wasn't even a good disappoint
No it wasn't like it was the worst possible path because there's the option of him revealing a
Like a fake name
There is the option of him
Armin tamzarian
There's the option of him pretending
You didn't say it
There's the option of him just complaining about qanon and not revealing it
The option
Did he did take was
To be boring
Complain about zinken 5G all episode and not even
Address the fact that you
Made
Commitment
How do you expect the best
Now it's kind of beer
Doesn't feel like it
Well
I want
The people
Feel better
That's not what I'm frustrated
So frustrating
Boo Alex
Shame on you for
For doing this stupid pageant
And
I hope qanon Eat You Alive
Kind of do to you you have it coming
You lost
Starbucks Short episode will be back on Monday with another normal episode
But until then we website
But we do have a website
Knowledge right.com
It's also qanon
Dot-com
Ross on Twitter or fighting that go to bed qanon. Com
Facebook Facebook
Qanon
99 43 to 1094
Tune in Monday because we are going to reveal
Qanon is it
Sure
Leo on dzx Clark
I am qanon
Alexandra Thurston color