Damn important I sweat it
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Need money
Dot-com
Talk a little bit of Jordan Jordan
Sweet spot for today is
Aspirational
I agree it's not it doesn't exist yet
I haven't existed ever exist
But I intend to
Okay I realized sitting around
A little bored
That I have never made lasagna
You've never made lasagna
Okay but I realize that it's within my ability to do that
Is it I just need a pan
If you go to the store I can go get one of those vans
It seems like such
Pie-in-the-sky kind of thing like
The f*** out of here
Seems it seems like some I like lasagna quite a bit and get so delicious
I could never do that
I've decided I can do it so I'm planning to hit some point
Eventually that I will make a lasagna
To make a lasagna
Visualize making a lasagna and I think that
How about you
Missouri five years and five years in 2015 and I played it and it's
F****** incredible I saw on your Twitter account
Babe there is apparently a regional version
Was it was hinted at in the original version what they've done is they took the first
A few hours of the original game and expanded into the entire game
Okay there's some stuff that was hinted at
When they blew up there cuz
Okay
And so on and so forth literally sucking life out of the plant
Everybody who is really
The interested in video games will tell you at nausea migraine
Any of the Final Fantasy games so it seems like
Give a shot at something
I might not
Movie after this lasagna
It's amazing just because
Everything was in Elder backgrounds were in 2D
And so
Now you're going through and you're actually walking
Through as if you're walking into
One of these in alike woolmarket
Where you win at danscomp
Petitioner lawyer to get address for your main character and where
I don't need to deceive a guy who's
Obsessed with
Perving on women essentially sure
And all that stuff like walking and looking at it 3D I swear to God I didn't even need the
The game is Sage
Just had
Like all of those layout of the Enders absolutely I just walked around the whole time
Lasagna aspiration
Cool
Thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Jessica thank you so much
Thanks Jessica
Prophet of the Griff
Thank you so much and I'll probably walk
Very much so
Big Easy blasphemy Journal about
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you Big Easy by Sweet
Ewok
What's the business that heroin
Why you pimp so good
Freakishly large
Either about happy things Jordan get going in this episode
Proper to give
Solana special announcement
From one of our listeners out there
Just got in touch with me and he wanted me to share with the
They wide
Community out there at the announcement of the the birth
Avenue child
Into this world Alina Pearl Newport
I would like to say
Congratulations on joining the world
And welcome
I don't know how one does a
Time what time did you end the world but I think it's a lonely get better from that's not circumstances
Maybe hopefully
I hope your first birthday is better
Entirely I don't know what they normally take
Congratulation
Chris
And I hope you are and I your
Family roles
Doing great
Yes congratulations
Chris Smith
So I want to say I also I would apologize
He's about the last a week
Somebody episodes
I could feel myself not
Not caring
I could feel myself
And you know what I sat with those feelings I reflected on what was going on
And I think huge part of it is
I was starting to get mad at Alex
I was really starting to get pissed
Because a lot of his stuff is really boring b*******
The stakes are pretty high
And stuff to watch him manipulate people in
Nike for the reasons that he's doing it in
In real-time like wow there is it an actual
Event in the world happening
It's not it's not abstract
Acts in the way it's so many of his lies often are
I'm it's very real and
It's a bummer
It's not fun
And then on top of that
Everything is a disappointing
He gets a DUI and he just lies about it
He gets a letter from the New York
Attorney general but I give him a cease-and-desist
He just lies about it
He gets a letter from the FDA
Just the other at the end of last week and observe just lies.
Everything is just like
He says he's going to reveal qanon
Doesn't do it for
It just there's no payoff to anything and I was just getting to a point where I was actually mad at him
Doesn't really work it's not really fun when I'm mad
It doesn't
It's just out of balance it's it's a Cortana Scottsdale
Has to be mad at him
And I have been
Pretty much since we started this
Almost
The first
That's
Good
My job is to take them
Distance
Of course of course I'm mad at you for stealing my job
This is this is the way of boss and I don't know I don't know exactly why that was happening
And you know we could talk all day about
Now what's going on but
I decided that you know what
I got to put Alex in timeout if I can't be around each other
For a bit we got if you just got to see
What happens when
And are you seeing
In the real world
That
Deplatforming
Has a certain amount of effective
Hypnotists are when you're mad at a propagandist
Document your platform
Deplatform Alex former show today
And I will be doing something entirely different
Hi everyone I'm Kerry Cassidy
From Project Camelot
8 today
To go over some of the things that are going down around us
And talk about
What's really happen
So today we are going over to videos that Carey put out last night
Camelot has some news
Coronavirus
So there's a couple things that I want to highlight
Some of these theories
Are pretty out there okay alright
A lot of the stuff that you believe is exactly what Alex believe course
So I want I want those two things to mingle in your mind
And I want you to recognize that the theories that Alex.
That's about right at home on
On Project Camelot
And the sort of discourse that he brings into the world deserves as much respect
Assembly
Wacky nonsense
Licari's
Explain to me how inter-dimensional space beings who are evil controlling things that also
Literal Satan is real and that's how we're dying everyday
Seems to belong on Project Camelot
That is what she says and it's also what else says
Exactly
The first report
The distance from the set-up
Was last Tuesday I think it was Tuesday and Wednesday
The first one
What are the things that's great about Carrie is that she
Has no
Sort of
Cabello's
About
Admitting that
Feed
Has terrible sources
They're great sources
But she'll say who these people are
And and then you can be like
Lieutenant Colonel told me that
His bulshit sources whereas
Carrie is
Out and proud about she's imagining
Beginning of this before we eat here
The carry
I know somebody who's basically figured out a cure for the world
SS credible
I just dinner interview
Andrea
Kalker who has
Basically care for the world
So
It's similar.
Trying to put out there which is an old
Cure for malaria
But as Andreas
Explain
It contains
Chlorine
As one of its main
Can I show the ingredients
I know case it has tonic water
Oh
For the heart
So this remedy that
Andrea Scott
Call Curtis talking about
Is actually
Water
And chlorine
As I understand it
Standing a certain way
And you can go to with his web
Website which is Andreas
Soccer.com
Take a note
Bleach as a Publix
Pool
And drink up
And then we'll all be safe
Kalker is knotted
He has a degree supposedly titled quoted
Doctor of philosophy and alternative medicine and natural
Charlie from a real University
It's from the open University of advanced Incorporated
Security Incorporated Incorporated
Corporate Incorporated site in the name
Anyway that's not a good
Good sign
I checked out their website is anything other than diploma Mill
Which makes sense
Project Camelot associate
Andreas kalcker is a big anti-vax guy who got his book pulled from Amazon last year in their sweep of
Kicking off books that Advocate drinking bleach to quote-unquote cure autism
You the real unreliable and dangerous source of health information but
He's able to pretend that he speaking
From a place of authority and expertise because of his
Doctorate degree
Which makes it funny
The landing page for the open University in advanced studies Incorporated is not about their wonderful Edge
Educational programs about the history of the school
What's a disclaimer
It starts quote
Open University of advanced sciences clarifies that it does not maintain any type of link with each genesis2church
Or does it advocate be medical or therapeutic
MMS
MMS is the Miracle Mineral Solution which is just be fun brand name for a bleach
Product these dumb dumb self
The genesis2church is run by Jim Humble
The guy who invented
MMS
A project
If I understand the situation correctly he knows that it's illegal to advise people to drink bleach
But he can plead religious intolerance if you makes drinking bleach part of the sacrament of his made up Church
Along with Alex Jones the genesis2church were among the recipients of the letters
From the FDA the end of last week
About their coronavirus scam
You know if you have to have a disclaimer write-up
The gate that says to me that it's
The opposite
It's true
On your college
Well it's because
Andreas kalcker is one of the main people who like
Uses his degree from this
Play saz
Of course they're associated with him by virtue of like
We told him the f******
You know when you wanted to scam people
You had to fake your own degree
Glad to have some graphics
Designware take
Classic calligraphy
It scrapes off seals and put them back on
Natsu
Pipe it up and Xerox it that's a bummer
But looked so anyway
I guess
Sure
It's not good
It's a bad thing. Oh it is a bad idea
Carrie's done it and it's great I'll know
It is curing doctors in Spain and
I've used it myself
Myself and my ex
Text partner Bill Ryan and I came back from Russia
Had a virus
Back in those days this is over
Can yours ago
Maybe
Around 12 years ago
And we interviewed boriska
The boy from Mars as he's called
Came back
Rid of for 2 weeks
We took
Finally took
MMS someone told us about it
The gym humble was marketing
The time
And
It cured Us in two days
So
That is an indication that this flu like
Situation
I can definitely be handled by
This new
Version of MMS witches
But Andreas
Conquerors talking about
I got to say case closed
I mean I think the science is in
Dare you believe him when he says he has a new version
Dare you
Slightly mixed
Differently
F****** thing
I am certain it's almost exactly
Brutal about there's a strain of science denial that goes through this
I might not have decided to do this episode episode about something else for today while Alex
Is that for me
There is
Veal
Some beliefs that Carrie has
Shocking
In there like
Level
Reality tonight
Okay talking about someone who believes the rappers come to Earth
Level
Denial of reality
A lot of it does sort of circle around the
Told you call it
The medicine medical aspect
Of the Coronavirus
Salina
Bleach
Is better than better
He's been doing some tasks
And the doc
Doctors are all
Coming in
Healed after two days of taking it
Take your chances
If you want to
Do not take your chances
Conventional
Madison
Then go ahead
But the bottom line is that this is actually
Quite possibly going to cure the world
Drinking bleach water is going to
You know it's
It's so hard not to have a brief moment
Because she says it's so confidently I do have a brief moment of what
Maybe please would help I don't know and then immediately like why does that happen she says
Chance with conventional medicine and probably die or drink bleach water
And Liz straight
You know you got that choice in front of you which using
False
But Carrie wants
Trump to make the right decision
Trump to drink MMS
Stuff that is
Absolutely unheard of
That's not what she's saying
But this needs to become like government policy
There are solutions to the problems we have all you have to do is listen to
The people
As opposed to
To the so-called
Experts out there
So if our president will get wise and do the same thing then we will
Get out of the situation wherein
Very quickly
Trump just needs to listen to the bleach people
F*** would you listen to the people who haven't spent their entire life
Studying epidemiology
Listen to the baseball the bleach cream
I will listen to the people when they're like we're serving
But I'm not going to listen to the people when I've got an epidemiologist over here is like I need to do and then the people are like Drake
The people
Are good
But not epidemiology bleach people that bleach people are not
Which people will say
Just drink cyanide
Whatever you want
Believe it
I can't take a flipping
Approached
Because like she has
People
Cioppino
It's not
It's not just advice that exist in a vacuum
People are being told this
Play someone who pretends
You know what they're talkin about
That's so scary there cuz there's a part of me that just wants to be like
Hey we got to have
At some point in time you have to have per
Purcellville agency and if you drink bleach
On you you are the person who decided to drink
I also think the person who told you to drink
Bleach is evil is
I don't think that those are
His room
For responsibilities in Mexico
Corners
Alex doesn't
People drink bleach
Although he does
Drift into unproven
Medical stuff
Especially as it relates to this
Between the Hydrox
Chloroquine pushing like crazy
The
The new one diaper Ivermectin
Horsepaste
Just plain old
Yeah sort of similarity and difference there
I think in this next clip you really see like
Complete
Overlap
Now needless to say they're doing it on
Purpose
The virus out there talking about how big Pharma will benefit from vaccinating everyone
Getting your DNA at the same time
And shooting you
Up with what is an essence
Nanodots that will track you and everything you do from then on
For the rest of your life
Nanodots
And also hook you up
25g and
Vai
The planetary AI
The board will I get better service
The hivemind
So this is
Impart
May I apply
What that is
Forth by the
ETS that are backing The Darkside
The Darkside
April out by the way
What Trump is doing
Darth Maul
Team play
So I mean you see if you see that you just got to recognize like
These are similar
Absolutely
It's not that different
And the things that are very similar are things that relate to things that
Matter in the real world in the real world
The huge issue is REI Cary
Really stupid s***
About nonsense
But doesn't matter coming down and killing everybody not on Alex Jones Show
Take this miracle drug
On Alex's show of vaccines because they're just wanted
Take your genetic
Material into into an AI grid
Amazon
Alex
Anyway
It is like nanodesu
Alex
Carrie has a i
She has a list here of like ways that you could tell
Trump
Is actually doing bad
I'll give you turn bad
Looking out your window
Is that one of the ways you can tell if he's go bad
Certain things that he could do or not
Do that would tell you if this is like a limited hangout situation
I want
Pay attention to this list because
This list is
Unattainable
It's amazing
You're setting up
A list of Cirque
Circumstances
That will never Attain
Almost to none of these
He's probably will ever
That one of them has to be him saying
Why don't we let the virus wash Over America
That's not in there
So how will we know that Trump
Qanon and the military that's working with
Trump
And not all the military are
By the way
Also I should like this at I just might be
Not something we've talked about a time to
Security is pretty into qanon
She makes a little bit clearer when she's not talking to a gas leak
By yourself
Too pretty
I believe
Are are basically
It whether their plans been foiled and whether they're working at
As a limited Hangout
Or whether they're the real
Nothing
First of all
The 5G gets rolled out in the US
And there's no
Fail-Safe
Protection for the people against his radiation a harmful
Facts
If that happens
Again this is number one we will know that Trump is under control of some group
And that group is negative
Number two.
Vaccines
Become mend mandatory for travel
And in general
Number 3 with the rollout of the new Financial system people find
That their money is worthless
Inflation is a sign for
There is no visible dent
In child trafficking and pedophilia
There is no sign of the arrests or trials for those
Arrested
So if none of that goes Pub
+ 6
The censorship going on right now in alternative media
Continues
And YouTube is not rained in
And
Continues to censor
Those of us
Telling the truth
So these are some
Some fail safe ways
Determining
If
Trump is the real
These are all things that you
Until like if
These fail to happen
Isn't the real thing
None of those things will ever happen
Absolutely
Zero chance
You always end up in the
The conclusion that Trump
Is not for real
Yeah that's
That's a real set of
Criterion
To judge the guy you think is the good guy, some of them are kind of things that you could
To just do whatever you want with
Sure
African human trafficking stop like you could find ways to make
All sorts of like
Prostitution arrests are like Trump
If you wanted to make that one come true
Biog
Is probably going to happen
Amore expanded form
Probably going to be not real according to you there
Vaccines are not
Probably going to become mandatory
But they're going
To be in the mandatory in the same way that they are now
And that's going to be a problem for you because you hate vaccine
Kohl's at mandatory
Is not real
Yes
Then just
Justin place
Just
Trump stops
Inflation forever
Yeah
Ludacris
Psiquiatra
We've already got the no bump into if he
Hides indictments for
The people who are
Soros in Alton
Right
Not going to happen
Talk to those people that kind of
Trump's going
Be shown to be fake
Are you there in the last 12 social media censorship
Did the Japanese Army
No chance
Trump is not going to
To get you back on YouTube
So you see a lot of parallel with what
Alex believe Trump needs to do the things
Thanks Trump isn't doing
That he wants him to do our things like fight 5G
Get rid of vaccine get me back on Twitter
Arrest my political enemies
Almost all of that
Standard destroy the Federal Reserve
Everything
It has a concrete connection with some
Something that does exist that isn't
Alien
Has a connection with Alex
And that's why you need to understand that people believe these sorts of same theories
Also might believe something like
This
Now the beaches are closed
Malibu
Could be a situation where
I mean who knows
Baby bottles
It could be a situation where the County of Los Angeles County
I decided that we can't take the risk people are not being responsible around the country
Where are beaches are not closed they're all still congregate
And it's too big of a risk to the body politic we just need to close these public spaces that's what happens when you don't listen to the
People down there listening to the app
Epidemiologist closing down the beaches
Well it could be that it could be a concern
Could be something else
We know that in Malibu they're closing the beaches
They won't even let you park along PCH and spirit
The ocean
Which is what people were doing
Couple weekends ago
Having nice little parties in the car
Be more than 6 ft away from another car
But that wasn't good enough so then they stopped
They blocked off all the park
Hiking areas along PCH
In Malibu
And
You could go five miles north
Ventura beaches and you would be fine
And they would let you go on the beach excetera
But not in
What was la
What is LA County
Different County
The answer is either there is
There's a sea animal coming out of the sea only in the Malibu area
Cthulhu
They just
Hate us in don't we
Strelka closed all the trails and all the
Parks in Malibu as well
With no one around you you're still
You know suspect
Getting the viruses supposedly
But in reality these rules have nothing
What to do with them
They have nothing to do with
You know a social distancing which is a
Plot anyway
It's a plot
What they want to do is they don't want humans
Communicate
And I don't want humans to actually
Get close enough to share the truth and they certainly don't want you
To be able to
To Riot or do anything
Substantial
So they are
Enforcing the stupid mindset of
6 ft
I saw a sea monster
I'm 6 feet away you can't get the truth to me this far away
Alright so
Only two options
They hate you
Leviathan
This is this is
It seems unimportant
But it is very important
It's this level of
Thinking it's being brought
Two things
Is the same level of thinking that's required to end up in Alex's political
Abused as well
They both
Are the product
Incomplete
Prophecies
Alice's of thought of
Educational
Curiosity
Takes a lot
To get you to
It's either a sea monster or they
Something is a plot
Would sink like normally I'd say
Carrie she just don't want to host the stupid YouTube show but it turns out she has other
I and I can
Can tell you that
In my view and I am a natural healer so I've been
Alright by Chinese Chi Master that I have very
Activated Chi
Etc and
So I do know intuitively
What is
Healing and what is not
And I can tell you that
This idea
I'm keeping 6 ft away is nonsense
Oh I didn't know that some Chinese guy
I should have known studies Incorporated
God
How do you hear if your if your
Kochi bastard
God beating Karim us
The best day of your life $7,000 a month
So when someone tells me that there are natural intuitive healer and they know everything
Feel it with Archie
Point
Determine
What are what kind of thing they bring into
The table cuz obviously I can't to ask him
Can she give me a Kamehameha
Could you give me a cheap glass
I don't know but she can give you a blast
Absurdity
Which is business wear
This is where ShakeOut real tonight
We Are Spiritual Beings having a material experience
Any sickness as I've said in my other vehicle video starts first
In the layers Above This
So this is the
The physical layer this is where it comes last
So even a bio-weapon
Put Out Among Us
To make you sick
Is something that you have to decide in your higher levels of cell
Weather to bring in
To move an ant
Out of your system
That's where I got a little worried about advice from the show
You have to decide
To get sick
Old-time puritanical
Christian
Feeling to it
Old kind of moralizing about illness
Like somehow it diseases at
Deficiency of you
A tree leaf
Humor's earning alignment Dan because you were mean to your little sister and that's
What you're sick and now everybody's got the
Play I mean if you believe this if you believe you
How old is he's basically is something that you have to
Your spirit has to allow it nor accept
Then it does
You would look
Look down on sick
Sick people
You would look down on people with
Electronic
Conditions is because
That's some sort of a failing on their part absolutely
Lupus
It's
If it's a really troubling I don't know if she's hinted at this in the past but it's
Felt a little new to me
It felt like a element of her character
That I wasn't aware of that I had I haven't talked this much about
Not good
Things even now you still think that there's a general agreement that it's
Like we're taking this one
For granted
Germs are real
That's how we're doing it
That's just what we're going to do today
And forever and apparently I was wrong
About the others real
Fundamentals
What is she think Adams Armada
Adam's a real how do you get
Nadeau's
And not have germ Theory at the same time
Extra when you have Zack
Kind of weak not going to win
Process is going to end up
Hey talk about nanoparticles and all this weirdo dumb science
But also at the same time
Except diseases it in your spirit
So don't have to accept
The nanoparticles if they are the disease in your spirit are you
Oh cuz they're too small we can't hurt you unless you accept it be it hurting you why should you ever be worried
About what any evil forces doing
Weak people out there this isn't for her
Richie's to straw
Play the Chinese Chi Master told her
She got the best you she's ever wired she have that bull Taylor attack
But you were so worried about a
Walking now I don't care
Anyway
It's not just her saying that she hasn't asked for
This dude
According to Robert Young
There are
Dr. Robert Young
There is
A doctor
Basically an indoor internal environment and an external environment
So in terms of the Earthly level
He's talkin spell exclusively about that
And I are highly recommend his
Disinformation
He's also one of the people who was well aware in the early days
Of what is it basically what we call MMS
Chlorine dioxide
And healing properties
And abilities
It it has
To heal everything
And he also
The talks about there being basically only 12
When
When disease
In-N-Out
Oh my God that's all you need is one method
Taking logs
Bleach
Subway
I do not thank God thank you sir Sunday thank the Lord
Robert Young
But he's actually way more not a doctor than most of the other people to carry reference car
Because unlike people like
Kalker Hooda solicit terrible advice
Robert Young
Actually decided to
Pretend to be a practicing license doctor
Which he was not
Here's a little bit from June 29th 2017 article in the San Diego Union-Tribune
The author of the popular pH miracle
Book series will spend the next five months in jail after admitting that he illegally treated patients at his luxuries Valley Center Ranch
Without any medical or scientific
Epic training
He previously been convicted of two counts of practicing medicine without a license
He's also arrested in 1995 and 2001 for practicing without a license
Is Dude Love
Those practicing medicine without being in any way qualified to do so
Programmable weed with this dude can fall spread
Does medicine over and over and over again to get five bucks but this justice system
It came out that young supposed to grease came from a Bachelors
Degree and doctorate
Within the span of eight months in 1995 flautas
Impossible
School he might be a genius maybe still in pain
Robert Young gets of jail time recently for pretending to be a doctor but that wasn't it
In November 2018 the San Diego Union-Tribune reported on a Civil Trial brought against Young by one of his
His patients who had
Cancer
Who claimed t quote
Held himself out as a doctor and councils hurt
24go traditional medical treatment
And of course
Cancer got worse
Victim was awarded 105 million dollars by the jury which was over double what you assume
Because f*** that I would go with
Still too small
This is a guy
Who is Leah Felder
The rest of us f****** life
Yeah he had the luxury lifestyle and then by the end of this case yet
Do the public attorney
Public defender
It's one of those
Feel good lines in a in a news article look like
This guy who made millions of dollars
Telling people this
Bulshit Brad doctor
Having to like
Basically the broke by the end of Alec
Obviously I don't
Necessarily want someone to be
Punished
More harshly than is deserve
But all those ill-gotten gains
Should be splitting
Gone
She should also have been given
Boeing like that's how much that guy should have been sued she gets a mask
We got to give it to you
Andreas kalcker the guy who wants to drink bleach
And
Robert Young
Pretending to be a doctor
These are the people
Carrie thinks of legitimate
Like Alex who has unlike Steve pieczenik all these nonsense dingdong weirdos
They're just Alex's version is a little higher
Except for
Some of these people lately who are
At least Alex used veterinarian as it
Yeah
And a chiropractor
Based on their oppositional Defiance disorder like
To jail only proves how really was you know that's
Central Elementary
That's a very interesting talk
Masks are stupid
According to
Scary and she has
Talks a little bit more about this idea of like you have to want
To get sick
In order to get sick
And I see people out in nature
Stupid masks on
Which is also looted
So as far as I'm concerned this
It just is.
Dr. Robb
Robert Young says
It's not possible to actually catch
This or any other disease from other humans
You
Actually
How to make
The decision to bring it in
We tend to resonate with each other so if you live in the same house
You're breathing the same air and hanging out
With other people in the same
Environment
We are
Basically
Senders and receivers and we tent
People tend to
Reflect
The disease is that
Set those around them
Have and decide whether or not
Actually manage
Pesto's
Their sickness is as well
Themselves
This is
You know it all to mately
The real
What we really are as humans in our spiritual abilities
Are going to be more and more known
And of course the X-Men movies try to make these things
Oh God hears
Watch bigger story than
What's movies are showing
Star Auto
Are telling you
Well
You know we got to the point where it's either Godzilla
Or they hate you and
X-Men movies were trying to warn us about that then
Diseases unless you want to
Saying we're right
If you have people in your home who get sick
You'll get sick
Because your likes
Sympathizing with Elmer's
Make sense for like
Asymptomatic
God transmission or
Obviously there were cases of people
You know you don't know your sake and then you get someone else sick
Your family
Check transmission work
Around 4 that would be like your soul knows
F****** magical thinking
No
But you have
Like your soul has to
Except the Delaney's sure
But then the next clip becomes a problem then
I understand that
The elderly
And
People even young people with weakened immune system
That have been sitting you no eating junk food and staring at electronics for since they were born Pratt
I mean you can understand there is a
There is an epidemic of a weakened immune system of humanity here on
On planet Earth
About that
And most people don't even know what Kundalini is let alone
Orgone or meditating and how to remove elenion
At and
Join them and
And get to sumati excetera
Said right which I have done and I can talk
Worth it
What can I tell you I
Buddha Guru
Whatever you like I reach somebody a long time ago
I got a giant T-Bone
Worth it
The problem I have there is
If you don't believe in disease why do we have immune system
I don't understand
Problem
Problem those are put in there by the globalist
I'm sorry the interdimensional evil beings right
Convinced just like how Jesus put the dinosaurs in there
To make you think
The Earth was older than 6,000 years Dan but it's not
It's a test of
Okay
In that case why is it a problem that we have weakened immune systems
Your immune system isn't protecting you from diseases that you
Can catch
From things like I don't know
Eating dirt
Or something cuz if you're
Weakened immune system is
Inward out
Go to the spirit
Then the spirit immune system is weakened
Boy this one doesn't make
Scary believe that all of this is spiritual
You're going to just be staying where you're sympathetic responses
The people we hate everyone
If you hate everyone but you will never get sick
You're impervious
To disease if you are the biggest misanthrope in the world
The only person who has never been sick in his entire life
With the Unabomber Dan and I believe that to be true
I guarantee that is
Never have a sympathetic reaction to anybody
Cleanse yourself of any empathy or human emotion
And you'll never be sick
So
Carrie in the sex club talks about how the bad guys
For all intensive purposes
Domino's they got a knockdown right to get the economy the disease whatever course at the same time
Just like dominoes and they might be using psychic
In order to make
Their plans
But
So is drop
And so
They have
To do these Domino's all together and one can imagine their using things like Looking Glass Pro
Sick looking glass
They're also using
One could imagine that
Used to be called Craig
Computers that are now basically probably d-wave
Which is Geordie Rose the
The five
You know going into the
Dimension looking in the future trying to find
Hi
Probabilities
Absolutely will work and what won't work
So they're they're basically
Figuring out at
Trajectory for their moves
There is some evidence that Trump
Qanon and team are doing the same thing
In other words using precog
That's using remote viewers
Using
There is a heaven
Try to strategically figure out how to navigate
The future
And being a cop
Competition
Each other
Teams of Psychics working against each other
Get sick
Have control over their mind Powers right
Push-out disease
Think they couldn't
Also anybody
None of these people that you know should be in prison
If
They have psychic friend
Sean David Morton
Is like a remote viewer and all this s*** he shouldn't have gone to prison for fraud
Maybe it's part of his
Or perhaps
Perhaps this
What the psychics and the Pea
Precogs alno
Is that
There is absolutely predestination and so he had no choice
Play it out like
I would imagine that being able to see the future in a system of
Destination
Bummer
Probably be best not to tell
People that everything's freezing
Similarities of Alex just like
Some of the villains are the same
And why these narratives
Are very very similar once you strip away aliens and everything
As I said it's going to be very
For Trump to stay
Step forward
To fire
A cheat for one thing
To get rid of Bill Gates
Arrest him
And silence him
And I and I
And Melinda Gates for that matter and and and basically
Take down
This is very dark
Deep state
That goes into the secret space
Is program now how far they're go
Going to be able to go
With all of it I don't know
But I can tell you that keeping you in your houses
Is not stopping them from doing their operation so that
Nonsense
If someone tells you that
That's not what's
What is really happening is
That the
Dark
Deep state
Is basically rolling out
A global
Artificially intelligent
Linked-up
Through 5G
And Nano and an n
And targeting more words
And putting words words words
Get their vaccine off the ground
This is the
The endgame
Game that they're working on
It's the endgame
Eid
Vaccines the tattoo that will track you
Call Vince
All the same
Because this is dumb
This is bad
Aside from Aliens she's she's just like
Double white lady Trump
She just has aliens on top of everything other than that just feel like
My kids are bad for playing video games and it's kind of a way to be condescending within that
Space a little bit
It's interesting
It's and it's like oh yeah you all know this but I know even more
Cheese
Raptor you guys think qanon is cool but it check out my cheese
Off-the-charts
Qanon Karim I believe some of the parts
If you were not particularly
It's My Hope
That is true that JFK
Junior is alive and working with Trump
Why
Sincerely hope that's
That's the case then I think that would
Be a very
Good thing
Why
And I'm told I am too and on says in in there
Broadcast
Not
But in there
Text
That they
Plan to come out in July they also say there's going to be a disclosure announcement to do with ET in July
The weather.
That's going to be Alien Invasion or weather is really going to be a real disclosure with some
Intelligence behind it
I don't know you certainly don't
And I can't wait for that
You have no idea ladies enjoy
So she's already said
A game
And she does it again she's using it a bit
It's interesting because of the way she's framing at and using the term
It's very similar to Alex
Conception of
The New World Order is doing right now
They have decided that we're at the
The endgame here on planet Earth
Until they have to baby
Bear Armageddon
And it is based on the Playbook
Witches in the Bible
And sorry
Horsemen of the
Apocalypse everything that's in the Bible
Will be adhered to by the Illuminati as
On
Rolling out their new one world order
Alex's stuff like that quite a bit I mean talks about how either Revelation is
Trueandco
Completely accurate
The globalist are using it as a
Template
You know it's
It's all the same people are similar
Is she pretty or post-trib rapture
I mean if she's pre
That's the only reason that you can Alex own catalog
You brought up the oppositional defiance
Our earlier additives really insightful because I
Carrie
My
I don't see whatever chats she's getting
But I think someone might have pointed out that Robert Young got arrested
Super faking being a doctor
Is she has a little bit of a response to it
You might have
Have been
I mean I don't want to say that you're have a great Chi energy
Orion natural psychic
Giving her exact
Rebuttal Looking Glass
I don't think they even understand viruses and I think that there's
I don't think you are
But I'm not an expert
So I'm not going to
Be able to stay
One way or another what a virus is I can say dr. Young
Gives you a very convincing argument for what
But it is and I you should read his papers on his website
Watch his videos watch my interview with him
And maybe you'll begin to glean
What is really being said and what's true about viruses and what isn't
Now
What else and by the way anybody who is arrested
You know
Disinfect
Credited excetera by the Deep state
Is a lot more like
Likely to be telling the real truth
Then someone who is lauded
On some platform and has all these Awards except you wanted us to listen to the people when the system Rewards
It's very possible
That
That person is not telling
And the truth in some
They're playing the pie
They are
Basically on board with the Deep state
Agenda
So just keep that in mind for all of you who think
Do they been in jail or do their you know this or that
Just like people to attack Mark Richards.
Captain Mark Richards
For murdering that got
Open frame for murder
Hello that's
Tell you he's probably telling the truth
I mean people do not be
As to not understand
Our entire world is run by the Deep state
It's the
Darkseid
So this is these are the people they love
Are the people that are
Probably
Worth hating
If you want to
Bothered
Put that energy out there
Which I don't
You do
Tell you I know a liar when I see one
That's the funniest wow wow
You are not allowed
I know a liar when I see one
HarborWalk
You know
Yeah I mean
The problem was that sort of thinking
Is
How do you determine who is the
Discredited by this deep state
Who's been discredited by being
A little
Who has discredited themselves
How do you differentiate between the two and I think it just
Compass tattoo
Where do you watch an exactly
Absolute win
Because
You're right I mean
I bet there are 100 people
In prison for murder who have a great story to tell
Could be exactly the same as Mark Richards
I imagine she complained 106
Space Program whistleblowers
In all sorts of places
I bet that there are a number of people who also would tell her things that don't line up with her narratives and she would
Write the probably
Put in prison
As a psyop against her or something
It's a yeah it's all just whatever you want
To believe
You want to believe that this Robert Young
Is
Right about stuff and they're for his crimes
And his
Direct
But you did to people
Is the Deep state discrediting
A guy who
Committed crimes
You know what when the crimes are fraud
Import
Has an impact
On other claims
Did liar multiple times over
I am going to go with I'm not going to trust what you have
That's just me crimes like if you're in prison for some crimes
But might not ruin your credit
Like if you were in prison for selling drugs or something like that
That doesn't necessarily impact
What I would say your ability to be taken as a credible source of information
When you were somebody who is doing a bid for a
Radu related crime
That does have an impact it matters
Gary refuses to recognize that
Cuz she likes fraud people
She likes bleach people
Who are a subset of fraud people
All I hear there is just there's no hope
No that's all I hear is that all I hear is there is I will never listen to
Ever ever
Not going to happen
I know I can
Can spot a liar is the saddest sentence
Anybody could
Yeah I mean if you look
I mean if you look through
The list of people that she's interviewed
I've been like this person gets it
I'm going to truthsayer I get it
I can absolutely you tell when people are lying all the time
Idaho lottery winners who won
My Skype you from this first report from Tuesday
And it's interesting
She said endgame a couple times she's definitely referencing a bunch of
Narratives
Heavy overlap with Alex
And now she ended the show with Alex's literal catch
I do want to say
You Are Not Alone
There are pockets of resistance all over the planet
That I am Kerry Cassidy you are watching this you are
Are they resist
Fence
If you're watching this
You are the resistance
Who plays in voice-over bumpers and out of commercial breaks on Alex's show
Report
Terminator Salvation or something
More importantly in the conspiracy world something that Alex has branded
The answer to 1984 is 1776
Could be in a movie somewhere and if you're quoting it you're still quoting Alex
He's on he's taking it
Man
It's there's too much overlap with Alex on this
2 Frisbie Court
Incidental
Although that makes sense for somebody like
Swery Carey to start going that direction is because
In a crisis
Instinct
Is to-go megalomania
You know like she before she was telling you about the Deep State no big deal I can see the future I can
Remote
View I'm a psychic I'm all of this stuff
Is a crisis
She's like
F****** leader of the resistance
Since now she is too strong
Basically Sarah Connor
There's another video that you put out
Be honest
I probably wouldn't cover this one either
Except for habitats
Why did Wilder theories I never heard suggested
It's not accurate
Has a problem for her
No one gets sick unless they want
Two theories that sounds right
But
Comes with an idea like this
You can't not
Tell people about it
If you're listening to the right
To this right now you are obviously
Build this up before the neck
Text 45 minutes
And it would still not disappoint
What what
More
Surprising
I'm really tired
Restart
And apparently she has another source
Of a guy who
Had some idea
George Webb did a video that actually related directly to
My recent article
Which I wrote
I think was yesterday
Or the day before
End
Basically
George is talking about
Information
That appears to be factual related to
What's involved in the
Show called Stevie and it
It has
Come from it's basically he he nicknames that have
Bat virus
And says it has
Protein
Covering the
Receives the body
Intuit
Accepting the virus to covering a
Protein is called
Glycoprotein 120
And apparently back in 1985
Waterfowl key
Profound she was
Who is obviously that
Start of CDC
I think he's a CDC guy that
With Trump
And and hopefully will be fired soon
Who was involved in developing that protein covering and without that protein covering
Our body would just naturally
Reject
The virus
This is a spirit
And if he hears that he has some background in this field
So I'm not even going to even
Care enough
How to get into the content I don't even think I was going well thinking about
Delivering this information wanted to talk about
The first is at the end there where Carrie says that her Source in the mechanics of this virus
George Webb
Accused
He appears to
Terry doesn't even actually know if there's any idea what he's talking about
Bake fauci look evil
She's going to assume that he's got the background in the field
This is what someone who's very clearly engage in the practice of believing whatever the f*** they want to.
But they're also
Trying to insist
But they're following the process
There's not good
And also like you
Responded to you can tell that you just winging it
Because
That's a major problem
Is there some random glycoprotein
It shouldn't matter
If diseases aren't
You have to decide to
Which is what Kerry has its
Breast is being her belief
Did you have two wheeler disease into yourself and Engineering that
Disease shouldn't matter
Shouldn't have any effect
On anything
The idea that
You can just be like
Well he appears to be reasonable and since I know how to spot a liar I'm just going to assume that he is
He didn't seem like he was lying to beso
There you go
No
They like
You can't get sick
Absolute way to get tickets to will it do yourself
He spent the last
35 years
Having their engineer this glycoprotein
Oh God so stupid
It just doesn't matter nothing matters
Why doesn't
It really doesn't
Big part of that is because
Is Carrie's working on two different
There's this sort of like
Man human potential bigger than our
Your higher self allows a disease in or whatever
It's kind of a hippy-dippy our version of
Of this belief system
Yeah the second track in that is this paranoid New World Order
Conspiracy stuff
Are you trying to run both of these tracks
And they are not
Complimentary
And also the problem is that she likes the paranoid one
Itsfunneh
It's probably more interesting
4 people
It's it allows you to
Express a little bit more anger
Yeah I probably is more profitable
So I think that you probably just
Like entertainment level enjoys it more
Do you have you have
Things like
You know
They're trying to get everyone sick with is engineered thing right
That seems to be
Completely undone by the spirit pseudo-spiritual
No one ever get sick
Leave that aside whenever you want to
You can't you can't have both
Historically
The people who have reached enlightenment
Do not engage with be paranoid
Train of lunacy
That's kind of one of the things that they put away
What are the things that they shed from this
Earthly body
Spray
So like it
It's just
Not okay
I think
To have such a scattered
Disorder
Disorienting
Contradict
Victory
Paranoid
Conspiracy world
You have to choose one
And I'll let you do it
I'll let you do it
I'll still make fun of
Don't worry.
Of course I don't have as much of a problem
With v
Like
Hippie-ish
Love
Is a vibrational frequency we can all feel like
Animals
You know the New World Order
Both
It's not good peanut butter and chocolate it is more like
Bananas and anything with pain
Together
Internally inconsistent and make me Furious
But
Kerry as a
The theory about Malibu
Your call
There might be a beast
Then that water
Stand turns out
Fix that
She's been in you know
Isolation
Does she big TJ Miller fan
TV
I started with kind of just letting people know that I was watching
Series on Amazon called
Invasion
And what I found was interesting
In that series there
It which is
About an invasion that is
Coming from the water and secretly
Taking over people
Appears to be something in some kind of
Creature
But we don't really know
What the creature
Is although it
It shows it at one point
Looking
Kind of
Alien I guess and very weird
And
Basically they go into lockdown and curfew
In part of the series in the beginning eventually that seems to be
Taken up
As far as the
Curfew goes and the lock
Lockdown but
The Invasion continues
So that's
That's kind of what you might say kind of a
A jumping-off
For me to talk
Talk about the fact
That thing's just
Are you is it good though
One I think it's hilarious that
She'll sit down
I'm going to watch the show
And then find Invasion be like I'm going to do some research instead of watching a show
I'm going to watch invasion
You can't
Have an Amazon Prime account if you think that
5G is coming to kill us all
You just can't do it
Weird
It's interesting that that also doesn't seem to be problems
The thing that I want to draw a really
So I can shower
Focus 2
On the 7th
On the report from Zach day
She's speculating that there might be a beast coming out of the water in Malibu and the beaches are closed actually then on the 8th
On that one to like well I have been watching the show called Invasion if there is possible that these are related thought
I start on Monday
I thought there was a beast in the water on Tuesday and now I still take
I don't think that there's any correlation relation
To pick that
Do I have a long endless track record of doing that
Presenting his reality
Is she enjoying the show
That's what I want
I want I don't want to be convinced of what the truth is so I won't watch it
Something doesn't
Doesn't add up
Or something it doesn't matter
And
Things just don't
That there's no reason for one thing to keep people off
Trails out of parks and
Peaches
And an n
This whole emphasis on 66
Speedway
Is actually very Ludacris and doesn't
Mean anything
And
Barry White
Reason to believe it's not even
It's not even contagious
Okay really okay we're going there
Alright alright okay that's a big swing
Great
Hundred thousand people dying
Contagious
Curious what cases
I'm curious
What's a treasonous
Cuz I don't hear one
I do hear her elaborate on this
What's the reason for thinking this is
Other than you not believing things are ever contagious
There's some reason to believe in
Is it just because you didn't I that doesn't exist I don't have a reason I'm just saying that somewhere there is one probably right
Oh man
That's so scary cats so scary
Just spent
Again
Ruby
Constantly reminded
Two people
Very easily becomes convinced
Cast of the exact same
Alex Jones believes
Because they were
Require
The same level of
Disconnect from reality
Start teaching germ theory in like
Kindergarten
Just to make sure that this is that this
Kind of thought does
Doesn't happen
Open as an adult like we really got
Hammer it home
At the at the
Point of birth
I'm not I'm not sure I think that's treating a symptom
I think that's treating a symptom as opposed to the larger problem that is
Denial of reality
I think that you
Instill reality well
And people will go ahead and
Figure out the deer germ Park
Sure sure
Oh man
I do appreciate on one level
Unlike Alex
Then I will shoot Shield name people who are silenced the tube laser X
Appreciate
Another thing that I appreciate is that she will just kind of cop to the fact
Fit like
I think life is a movie
Just be making stuff up
What I'm doing is
Taking sort of a jump-off
If you want to call it
And
Really just connecting some.
And giving you a
Hypothetical
Look at what might
Be going on
Outrageous
And maybe off
But there are some interesting things going on
And because I see the
That you know I see I tend to see life like a Hollywood movie
Cuz I'm a screenwriter
Did I write screen rides
Speed into
To my kind of
Conception of that
Yes it does
Maybe and maybe in a way that's a
Problem
Declarative statements about what's happening
Christian funny
Somehow
It makes me even angrier that she's willing to admit she's just making
Step up like she's not
She's not like Alex saying he's right 100% of the time even when he's wrong but she's like
I'm putting some guys together maybe it's stupid
To be clear she's not saying that about everything
She saying that about specifically The Narrative we're going to get to the end of this up
So
I do admit she's making
Okay but she also is not
Presenting
Get that way
She's not presenting it as like
I just
To give you a spoiler
She's talkin about something
Completely insane
Event is at the end of the
This is the most likely explanation
You cut that sincerely true but it's the most likely could say it
Hayward
And it doesn't apply to other things like her using this
Play doctor
Germs don't exist
When people get sick
Because a member of the family is sick
If this is a sympathy
Ascetic
Fonts in my view
It's not
Because
You know literally
What we called germs or
Bacteria
Where
Picked up
That's
You know now I have Doctor Young who would
Sanchez.
As
As well
He what
I've interviewed and
The links are on my website
But on top of it
There is
Simply
No real basis for understanding what those things are
As opposed to
Why we would bring them into our body
1st place and
Gotten into this another
Think other videos
So I really don't want to repeat myself
I don't want to get into it
Wow wow
Look I won't bore you with the Gory details of all the stuff that I don't know anything about
I'm just going to let you know that I proved
Science is wrong and I'm right by felon friend
Yeah you know
Does she just go through like local newspapers to see who what
Fake doctor might have gone to jail and then she just visits them in jail and that's how she gets all of her sources guessing it's just whoever
Believes in Bleach
Anyway Kerry Hudson dreams
Prophetic dream sharp course
The question is
Should be we be watch
Watching the skies
And there is reason to believe that there's an asteroid headed towards us
I did have a vision of this
And then it came out in the news
After I had my vision
About
I don't know week later and
What's happening now is there's more more
Bartok of this
But you have to realize
For I suggest you realize that
We actually have the Weaponry to shoot down
Shoot away
Ion asteroid as well
It's on Prime music
Jstor account that is Amazon Prime
I mean yeah whatever man
Division of an asteroid
I don't care
Maybe and then she'd be like now it's not Armageddon that's stupid
Is Deep Impact
That's way better
Pardon my take
So here we go
I want it I would talk about her visions and how I don't care about being a source of information
But I can't be
Because we got to get that a business on
This
Fun
I'm so
So
There is a problem
And that is
In China
There were stories that came out about people being welded into their home
Quarantine sure now
Some people might think
Is the act of an authoritarian government
Trying to contain
Osiris
Sounds like what they would do
An extreme example
What I would believe
A government like
The Chinese government
I do
Now there's another explanation that's possible
The question becomes why would you weld
People into their
Hartman
And that
Comes into a sort of almost Syfy
Idea and this is where it gets
We have to go back and look at what the viruses so
They say the
That
Most of the information coming through
How to do with the
40 track
And then
Allowed
A pin
Bioweapons lab in North
Carolina
Making its way to Wuhan
I am a Chinese woman
Who was working
For the u.s.
A
I also being involved in that
And maybe
Even
Involved in the transfer over to China
Does appear that China and the USA were working simultaneously
On this
Nuclear
Virus type
Thing and that they were getting
Something from bats
There's something going on with that
Some going on with bats
Not quite sure exactly what's going on here
His next class
As
To use her own
Goes right off of
Okay
But it also you also have to save yourself
Okay why would somebody
Wanted lock these people in unless there were developing symptoms
That are similar to some kind of a vampire
React
Results
And that this was what they were afraid of or
Well the mints
Of course the possible explanation
Parties out here you got a welder
That was Van helsing's first idea
Wilderman
Welder into that f****** Castle
Now what the stock market
What Dad did you notice the state
Wake up the steak business
Did you know that
Look at
Who look at the numbers
They're making vampires
And now here we are
They got taken stuff from bats
I did not we got vampires can't believe that you didn't get that when she said they were taking something from back I was so worried
Vampires are real
I thought for sure you'd be like oh she's
I I didn't think anybody with an Amazon Prime account would go straight to vampires and I was wrong I was just
Play to turn people into vampires
Strakos whatever
Also probably has to do
That nefarious race of aliens that pops up every now and again
The dragon moth out no
That's our blood draw
Basically the DNA
Coming from batch that would be involved
Open whatever
They took four from them
Presumably
And something that is known in the Asiana Dean material
About a very
Very diabolical alien creature that
Said to be more diabolical than just the straight-up
Draco
Courts know we have the grace
The reptilians and the Draco
Kind of in a pack
And
Glassmaking going
At Westside
Various governments and also with
With with
Especially with
And so it's very important to understand that this
This sort of New World Order is coming
From that group
Which is at a very
Got top down
Hierarchy
Call Society
That they purr
Prefer humans to
Basically be
Following in that
That tradition
The humans they weren't allowed to live that is
And
They are
Still in a takeover scenario and one
Topeka
Complete control
But there's another group
Call the dragon mod
That apparently
Might be related to the dryer
The dragons but they're
A whole step
Aside which app
Appears to be
This is just my conjecture I can't remember what their actual
Combination is there
If they appear to be
Yeah you can say instead
Aptoide dragon
Dragon so there's some dragon
Insectoid
Creature
And even related possibly to the burg
Like a dragonfly
Exedra
So
And it's well-known the birds
Pixar
Related to Dorothy
Draco Andretti
As a species
So
You get the connection
Are you getting Burger in on it too.
It makes sense
Words related
To the Raptors that evolved into alien
And reptiles isn't there
Kind of a difference
Path isn't a branching path branching pathways
Could say that they have a common ancestor prior to the Raptors escaping the
Extinction of all life on Earth
Probably at the burden they are those wings Birds
The way she's talking about
I don't have a lot of faith in this
Do your f****** research on your fake bulshit at least I need
Pull on entry in the
In the dragons manual for your boat
Dragon Mods
Baby birds
Wings
Insectoid
Little bit
Nefarious
Very diabolical diabolical
Explain to me how
What grit dacian of diabolical
Are we dealing with whatever we're talkin to even more diabolical than the ones trying to enslave an entire planet
I don't know
Also I don't understand how
Maternity Ward vampires
Scworks
Put those goals
A bit from Vampire Lord
Immortal
Standard vampire powers are we dealing with here
Okay so the Chinese in USA government
Both turn people into vampires
Because
As we all know vampires
Can I get
It is simply impossible for them to turn into some sort of smaller creature that could literally Fly Away
Outside
There's no something was up Iris and don't give you capes
Widow's peak attic
Dead ringer you are a vampire
Building to get treatment
And came out Hungarian which is really strange
That was really strange for me
I don't know man
I guess you weld them in so they can't
Sherry
Easier
Especially if they're not like good at being a vampire yet
Mentor
A vampire Mentor so I assume that the dragon Bots have been make
Can vampires for a long
Right
I mean the only goal of this would be to spread vampirism
I mean I would be to make everyone vampires
I was a vampire that doesn't seem so bad
I mean
Yeah
Require
Fundamental restructuring of society
Public transit would not be an issue anymore that's it that's a positive we're not talking about that all right
Get down to it on like a kind of a basis shooter
Healthcare cost to go down
Snow certainly blood banks iPhone reproduce
Other than by a vampire
B Brian
I don't think you can
I don't have time
Yeah yeah yeah
I don't think they're
Packing a good sperm count
My other problem
Is that if you're trying to
Create a subservient population
Don't go vampire
There are historically in literature
Rebellious
Absolutely
The social order bus
Because of how much chaos they bring into a system
Also there but that's what maybe that's what the Diabolical Dragon boss are trying to do to the dracos
Attempt
To bring an order across purposes of the Draco.
Believer
Vampires at the Dragon
Especially considering if I understand Mi or correctly
Vampires are just a thinly veiled anti-immigrant message
There's also like
A sexuality thing to it
Again it's a fear of the sexuality of the other European coming into
Europe in order to
Have sex with all of our women and our cultures and steal everything about Mars
As well as our economy like there's
It's a really really racist book if you get down to it
About the vampire law passed that makes sense as something
Abusing in your dump
We have a baby
Wildeman
It's really important to recognize this
That like she's in the middle of
I'm talking about
Dragon Ball is on probably create
Dating vampires
And then interspersed with that is stuff like this
Falcon who's running this whole show
It appears
Ephraim
The side of the medical side related
To the CDC
Is yuno on stage with Trump
All the time
Although there is indications that
Trump is very likely going to fire him very soon
Now he's a vampire
But he's a very diable
Follicle care
Durand it does appear that this was
What's the plan
So he's orchestrating
In some ways
A lot of what's going on here especially in the United States
And advocating all of the Bill Gates and you
He's basically in bed with
The gates and all that
This is what we have of you know it's a very
Diabhal
Concoction obviously keeps
So you have this
This presentation of maybe this viruses aliens tribe
Scrape vampires
At the same time
Very much Alex Jones theories about real-life things like being in bed with Bill Gates
Play Thursday real world version of that which is
Yes he works at the NIH
Forks of the year of allergy and infectious diseases
Bill Gates
S550 has to do with infectious diseases
Why
They be in some sort of
Association with each other
Whatever
It's something you can convince yourself of if you do such bad
Game that you believe
Maybe this virus
Is vampires
You have to be asking yourself at this
The game here
Why you trying to make vampires
Because we can't figure this out I was asking myself
Doesn't make sense now
This is convoluted
Does have an answer
This was
Do you know I said earlier
Aspiring to make lasagna is a bright spot
That's just because I
Couldn't tell you about this clip in advance
The clip was a bit of a bright spot
So you have
Have to also then look at
What trumps doing so Trump is
Hunting down blood Drinkers and Peta
Adrenochrome
Attics
Sarah speak
Who are all related to the Draco and
Killian's and greys
And
Presumably goes into the dragonballs who are
I'm sure
Equally as diabolic
Local and said to be worse
Actually
So we're talking about
Beings that
Feed on human
And humans getting shot up
With
Type of a virus
That
Is going to
Possibly shoot.
DNA into
Human
Turning them into
In theory
Blood drinkers
Themselves
And
In Mass
And this is the kind of thing where if he were an Illuminati and you realize you were being hunt
Two down especially your leaders are being hunted down
Then of course you want safety and numbers
You want somewhere to hide
You have nowhere to hide
And
The way these people think they would be
Diabolical enough
21A create
A basically a
Turn humans into vampires the more you have in your on your team
The Morrie
How are you have and
Possibly to come back
This the loss of some of your leaders
And
By creating a hole
Species that would
Bass is basically have a similar lifestyle
And taste
To what you do so
This is
Unbelievable stuff I know
And it does sound
Crazy
But this
Is very likely
What's going on
This is what's going on
I want
I want to laugh
Brain
So Trump
Alex among among the population
So in order to create more vampires
Do do this virus
The creates vampires
In order to get
New recruit
Store
Here's my biggest
What I'm hearing is that there are no vampire powers that
Come along with this
You just like to drink blood
But also
So they're like
Jesus man we drink all of his blood
Down
So what we're going to do is we're going to make other people who drink blood
And then we're all going to get into a big circle
And they're going to be like all we got to stop you it's like there's too many of us.
I don't have to be powers
It's ludicrous to do this without having
I mean not not to everybody but I mean to have this story
Without powers
Believer
She said the X-Men was real or powers
It's just like
She's not giving me any powers
She's not giving me any clear-cut powers all I'm hearing is that the globalist
Are making people
What to drink blood and then they're going to be malnourished
What's drink blood leaves the address
This is not really that far off
Is this the cheese
Aliens involved in that coronavirus is making people at the
Do I got to lock them in the house
I don't I don't know about all of it is
It's just like
Stupid cuz once you start talking about that like what about all the other stuff
Like you I seen George Soros out
Did during the day yeah I know that's just from book
The game's not worth playing
We're in the moment in every vampire movie where they're like
Now throw about it throw away everything you've heard about vampires and
Books and movies
These are the real vampires and s*** like that
Also
The Illuminati
Does not need to turn people into
Blood drinkers to make
Make friends isn't that kind of what you saying
Friends
I guess you could probably get enough people to to be fine just by being a good guy
Attract more flies with honey
Injecting them with a blood
07 Trailblazer
That's an incel idea right there any
I did not consult are not a health Ranger
For this episode
I don't know if
There's something
In bats
You could inject
Into a human
That would make them drink
I don't know if that thing exists
And I would need bad ideas to specifically tell me what that is
Otherwise
Is dumb some sort of enzymes
Breaks down blood into a more efficient
Nutritional system I still don't think that would make me want to drink blood
Woody Pizza
Just have
Pizza made you sick
Now what if it just inverted everything or probably
Gotas hot dogs
Would need to be something like
Wheatley rewired
The way you took in any kind of substance
So only blood
Cuz otherwise
Like right now
I could
In theory
Maybe drink a glass of blood
Baby
That would be all I needed for the day
Awesome God willing I'll never know
What's a what's a
If it gets bad enough then I will absolutely give you a pint you can see how it goes
Are you running out of sandwich meat and lettuce
Here's a pint of blood
I ate some I'm typos so you're you're even clear on that will appreciate the offer and I will hold you to
Thank you
It's scary to think
Official guidance
The people might get
Remember
She thinks that people are being turned into Vampires by aliens
And these are my suggestions and I I realize that
If you
Think otherwise
You should follow whatever you think
You should follow whatever your heart tells you
And don't do that
Tells you to wear a mask
And gloves when you go out of the house
And cower in your house excetera then
Do by all means
Follow that up
And
If you want to believe what
Open the mainstream news and all of the
Propaganda
Around you you are certainly
Welcome to do that at
As well
What I am providing here is an alternative View
And that includes vampires
What I do
I'm a psychic
Intuitive
And
The gosh
And so this is what I do and I've been doing this now for 4
15 years
What doesn't mean
I've been right about anything
Nope well if she hadn't been doing it this way
Wouldn't somebody have stopped her if this was crazy
Just ignore it
Yeah you can wear gloves and a mask when you go out if you want to believe the dumb propaganda
Tell you that I'm a psychic intuitive
And
Vampires
Disease isn't real
Also every other
Conspiracy that
Is promoted by the
Extreme right-wing folks like Alex Jones is
That's that's basically what you got here
3 minutes
It's interesting on one level and it again
There's no way I would not do an episode about
Vampires
Absolutely
Must know
China is making vampire
Welder
Dragonfly cheetahs I have a good handle on
The dragon boss
I get it
Aliens are out there who knows what they could be
But we start bringing vampires into my house
You're not okay
Moths for making vampires
They're fine
They're fine they're leaving us alone for the most part maybe they're doing a diabolical plan here and there but now they're making vampires dad
What's their diabolical plan
I don't know
So dumb
I wanted to really draw sharp Focus
I think we have is that some of this is really
Big fun
But the stuff it's not really fun
The same as ours
It's pointed Bears repeating over and over and over
Because
The same bad thinking will lead you to different places
But also the same
Play ASAP
It's a it's a problem
Technique
That manifest
For Alex
Reboot away is that it does for him
Add with carry in the ways that it does for her
And she's a little bit more fun
Sometimes because of vampires
It's fundamentally the same thing
100 examples of this
That's really the spiritual connection
Between these two
Artio
And some other shows don't
Save-A-Lot
Yeah a lot of other
Options would work in the same way
Just being the same
Bed thinking process being
Manifested by
Who does not as interesting
You're not as
Stupid
Yeah I was a Not So based entirely of Sgt entirely on
Oppositional defiance
And
A staunch denial of reality Jeff
Because everyone else agrees on that
That must be that it's mine
My friend who likes
Bleach got arrested
That must mean
Set the man was trying to make him look bad cuz he's
Did it do
Those things are so common
With all our
Yeah I was I was just thinking or I was wondering like
Was there a moment where they cross-pollinated the the two
The Sci-Fi weirdo community in the hard right-wing community and then
Like I'm trying to go back through history to see if I can remember the guys like this and it's
It's always been there
They're like the
Worst Gamers have almost always been like these hard right guys who believe that
Part of the part of the reason
That you are allowed to get
Scammed is because you're actually a bad person
It filters in the
I don't believe
But everybody else
But me is bad is going to lead you down to some hard right
A lot of these paranormal and
Government oriented
Conspiracy theories germinated
Similar places online message boards
Similar places
Good things that
Drew 121 by draw them to the other as well
Frederick Cooper like he was
Largely especially towards
Later stages of his career definitely more
A patriot militia
Type of
Conspiracy theorist but yeah a lot of paranormal stuff going
The
Sort of esoteric
Occult stuff in his career
You have a lot of stuff over the last like
30 years right 30-40 years that have been like
Very similar
Places
But if you're into one you better
Is a decent chance you might be an algorithm
Impossible to ignore
I think that you see a bit of it manifested in in these two different
Terrible shows
Too bad one of my long-held
Conspiracy theories
In that
Dick Cheney orchestrated 9/11 because now I know
F****** vampires
No
Dammit
Alright
So close and yet so far
Forming brake
Find out
Then but until then maybe website
Red Jordan we are on Facebook we are
Meo amleo I'm dzx Clark
I have achieved some
Secrets
Is that one of
I can't remember I just know throwing
Copper was what
The song called run to the water
Scry I heard on the radio
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work