Alexandra Thurston color
We're couple dudes like to sit around and drink
Talk about Alex
We talked about usually a day
Currently
That is something we generally do and the twist is that you listen to a lot of Alex
Listen to any Alex
Which is the right amount
Hope I wasn't too way too much
No amount and there lies the fun of the show I get to tell you
All about
What's happened and I get to scream
And that's why we drink
Which is in French
Before
Well as far as I would prefer if it was
Susanna
Hey Ma alright alright
Recertify
Just weak ale
So tell me what we're going to be doing
A donation from my best friend in the world Nikki
I'm a policy wonk
You donated to the show Apollo if you want
But he bumped up his donation in order to get himself a time travel episode
Yeah man we're going 2014
Considering all of the news
That's why we had to escape
I don't think there's any
There's my Twitter feed and seen even the slightest
Cute puppies
In Alex Jones
His show has been dogshit the last 2 days
Right he's at Rodger Stone in studio
On Monday
It was just the two of them having a Skype conversation with Mike cernovich
And they were just like
Aren't we great
Who's kind of just like
And the whole time
They were talking about how reince priebus was the leak
And they had information from their sources that reince priebus was leaking everything
And how like it
It finally time we can come out with it
That afternoon
The news broke
Trump
Giving information
Tuesday Russian
I forwarded bassador lazaroff
No no
The president has
Even better than that
It's even better
Because it's happened
They had to adjust their narrative because it had to be someone who was in that meeting
That was
The person who leaked this to the washing
The post
Ansel
Human Rodger Stone just do like a Facebook
Video in a hallway
Weather like
We knew all along it was McMaster
Invalidating the last day of Grace
That's such a snapshot of the Republicans forget what happened
Coralville
And then today Tuesday as we're recording this
Alex had Rodger Stone in Studio City
I like Rodger Stone being very close to the border of Mexico
Personal reasons
He's a Flight Risk if it ever has been one
So he was on and then again we're just talking a lot of s*** and it was really uncomfortable cuz I think Alex was drunk
Really
Like he couldn't
Stop losing it like
Controlled himself
I wanted to pull some
Clips of it cuz it's just like
It's out of
Control Impressions left and right
He's doing like Chuck Schumer as some sort of
Wizard of Oz villain
Kind of
Issue where it's at the disaster
Not if you mess with her this guy cannot can
Control himself at all
So then Rodger Stone
Adductor group comes in
They do about it
Hour-and-a-half
Maybe an hour little over an hour commercial for a new product
They put out
Best basically
As best I can tell the function of it is it makes you pee more
I already have proof
Prostate
It's against your prostate cancer
Is in the light-bearer no
Heavy metal
And stuff like that
Utopian s*** menstrual blood enough that is basically what they were saying
They were saying that if you don't like
If you don't discharge
Enough
It will however you discharge
Metals
Philippine you in like funguses on your break married on specific
Do they know that
Mint
And women men's
That's in the Bible
Nothing is not a consummate Christian
Missing out on
Although
This Thursday
Looking forward to it
Jon rappoport should be back in
Studio cuz it's been a week
I know you like that
God is
If you wasn't
Studio
Master
Worlds would Collide in studio
Things to find
Jon rappoport
In some
Stray episode
I have not yet but I'm looking forward to it
LabCorp
Origin story
Appearance
So
To see how it goes from
Oh yeah
A problem
He comes out all googly eyes with a huge beard
I'm just driving myself now
Do you have a cross-eyed you have a big beard
My teeth are going to fall out
Certain
S***
I got it I got to start
Your optimism
Is insane
But then I'm going to turn into Rappaport that you're going to live that
So today I will Iowa and play this out of context
The date we time travel back
Conclusion
More than most
V not so much
He is not a detail guy
That really sums up third of how Alex Jones lives his life
Not really a big deal
So
Today
Got my assignment
From the gift
Eddie told me
You got to go back
To March 8th
What Jordan
Was Mark you don't remember March 8th
Ifucking remembered
This is this is a disgusting
If you if you give me a humorous collar a man of letters
OK Google
Open and I tell you to think my brain works the Malaysian plane went missing
The greatest day of my life so
March 8th
A scholar
DJ for all of us
Also on March 8th Alex is doing his show and 8
Awful he doesn't mention the plane at all
So
Sxsw Music Festival
They're trying to push an anti-gun agenda
With Bloomberg
What have you
I don't know
It's nonsense
So he's he's getting really excited to most of that show is him talk about how they're going to
We've got guns March
Revlon has gun
Progressive
It's like a can
Horrifying racist
Torches
There's no negative connotations associated with a bunch of white people holding
Which is a whole lot better than the old
Yeah dammit that's what 2.0
Yeah
I guess
Next episode
I think David Knight was hosting the next 12 Mike I don't even care
I'm starting to notice at Redwood big things go down
Auto Studio
The David light was in like right after
Director for the last one
I don't care
The next episode
Is backing
Studio hosting
Everything is back to normal
Is March
11th
Recovering
Hey man I'm glad cuz
This episode is
Profoundly stupid
Waterfall
But
Siri
He is
Out of Studio
When big things have
Because
The people who work for him are like Lissa
We have to
Hispanic
Because if you go on there
You're going to say
All kinds of crazy
Right
Are not going to sign off
I know I disagree with that theory because he has such a like an iron grip on
On Infowars
Rob Dooley
Just because Rob do his narrative it doesn't mean that Alex is going to Buck that naira
True
Can't be contradict
Did everybody else can
What's the matter if he's there.
Anyway
Alex Jones The Bells calls
Alex Jones
Wheel shakes
Alex Jones fan
Ice shockingly small amount of this episode talking about the Malaysian plane
Right up his alley though in the Wheelhouse it's like
So here's how he begins the episode
A little bit about the
Mystery
You have it this Malaysian
Airline
Disappearing
Of the Iranians that were boarding the flight
I got to tell you looking at the eyes and the bearing of these two guys
They look committed
And I'm not saying they're guilty but my gut tells me
And they're very serious automation
They look like
Iranian Republican guard or something
Looks like the exact type of infiltrators
Ashley
Infiltrators
Looking at this photo
Infowars.com or any other new server that Mattern
Drudgereport.com
Can't possibly be true
Back whenever he was afraid of Muslim man
And it hadn't yet
Extended
Small Muslim girls in Starbucks
Yeah islamophobia doesn't really go over it but
He's talking about is there was a story
About to gentleman
Who'd gotten on the plane
So it's actually
Spookier
Jesus Christ
Sketchy
Where was
I don't remember
We're dumb
Flight 370 was a scheduled flight in
In the early morning hours
The vaith of March 2014 from Kuala Lumpur Malaysia to Beijing China
It was operated by Malaysia Airlines
The Beijing Capital
International Airport
Scheduled to depart at
Boo
I don't know how to
Translate military time
Hahaha
That number
Another number and then 20
Too difficult
Airplane flight duration was 5 hours 34 minutes which would consume an estimated
37200 kg
Aircraft carried
49100 kg
The fuel including reserves allowing 7 hours 31
Extra fuel was
Ultimate Airport
Which would require bubble by little extra
Airport
If that was like rid of emergency
5 hours
Caring
Heartless heart
Billion other atrocities
Who's one that was right in the middle of the whole situation the Ukraine
So
The fun distraction
For everybody is like
LA Galaxy
Repeat that Alex
Does fingered
Term
I know but I'm
A little twelve-year-old walk
Fraudulent passports make
Situation reasonable
He doesn't talk about
He holds up a pictures they're brown
That's basically all he say
Yeah it's crazy look like
So he goes on a little bit more profile
Of people
Commit terrorist Acts
Disappearing
Just like when the playing who would like if you were trying to commit a terrorism
Committed Terror
About now
What you want
A giant explosion
Quite a few of those getting hijacked out of Egypt another area
They will take over and they will get the cockpit and they will fly the plane into the water
General
Firearms are bombs they smuggled on
It was a false flag you have naked body scan
Christmas
Is the CIA
Videos putting his face into
Muslims
Airline are there in Amsterdam
So that testimony
That was a staged event because
Because of this
And the outgoing head of Homeland Security shirt off
Affability
What's the total TR Rolla
Promise
Because there's no weird thing
Garden-variety
Globalist
Yet capitalized on the crisis
Right which is
I would say
Cuz if you're if you're a secret evil Corporation
Globulin
You wouldn't
In-N-Out
Favorable
Right so if the outcome
You're describing the hegelian dialect
That's basically what it is
You create circumstances to get the outcome that you want
These bodies
There is an internal logic to it it's not
Sensible
Like you need to do more ground work on it
I'm not going to get to
Through Alex
I'm just going for trying to understand what his
I think you have done that there
If your
I'm listening
Amelia Earhart
She came back
She's the one who made all
Has disappeared
Did Amelia Earhart
She's responsible for like the Devil's Triangle
This has as much legs I haven't why hasn't her body
I'll tell you what
Still hijacking
A lot of the Malaysian plane
Because Amelia Earhart
Great at high speed
Mypoints
My point that I want to make on the Alex's
Siri is
Reasonable
Daily readings
Obvious
Assertive
Watch to Learning Channel
So
But that part that added bonus part
That you can't eat and is disgusting
Is
Fondant decorative
Traverse in the fancy parties that you go to
Adjusting people on television so you're not supposed to eat it I have no idea
I don't like cake
Anyway
It's a foolish expectation that if something is
Is being done
If something is real then nothing will be done after it is something is fake
By the shadowy organization
Then they will be ready to push
That doesn't
It doesn't make any
No it is
You need a lot more ground work or else
Anyway.
King idea
Now he starts to in the sex with a mediately sore waffle on it a little bit
Can I put a real hijacking does especially
Stop connected Greaser involved
Airplane
Into the water
I don't know a lot of suspicious check people on board but my gut tells me is a hijack
Are car Old Alexandria
Really suspicious people
Where's the special
They were the ones who made the Arabian guys
Is this is Alex in 2014 and the complete difference
From Alex Jones today
Alex would never say
I don't know
Today
True
But the thing about caring water is you always have to
Have to have a source
Where is
Basic news
Even
Nobody knows what happened
Asian
Did men tell no Tales
Like Amelia Earhart
Dead women tell Tales I don't know
Look at their new stereotype for women
Seances
Anyway where we started
We have now played a couple of clips
Is that pretty much all of his coverage
Which of the Malaysian Airline things go off the rails pretty hard and
In this next clip go
Most a lot more about how sxsw to try to take your time
Go on that tip he gets into a bunch of TVs
He raps
About a
Bunch of nonsense
Then he ants
With
I don't mind spoiling
The weirdest
Longest commercial for his product
That I have ever seen
It all of my time watching Infowars
Amen
So crazy
Back then
He was only on the radio for the first 3 hours
The signal
Whatever he was only broadcast online
Phil's wife
20 minutes
Talkin about
And then continued
Ends up cuz he would literally just like a like he's in the middle of his commercial and then
I'll just cuts
44 minutes
40 more minutes over drive where he takes phone calls people about the Malaysian plane
None of them have any good theory it's
Terrible
But
Okay we've laid out these
Like the syllabus of what's
But now we got to get down to the meat
My man
This neck
Clip
We're going back to episode 2 of our pocket
We're going back to something that came from Y2K
Episode
A little place
A very special place
In Colorado
Anyone that did this would be informed
Catherine Herridge Fox News Channel Hiester taking my question Datacenter hold the data of Amir
American citizens know
Part 1 I can't go into all the details of the Utah Data Center
Hold data on US citizens
The head they do and did
Cybersecurity that's the Pentagon branch
Northcom domestic
That should already operating completely illegal
Operating
Call Rhonda
Space command that runs everything
Space command
Nexus Quincy public space
Most from sources other eye
It's unbelievable
I'm already gone
The General Public
Start a war with Russia
I'm not saying Russia's good
The witch is starting
He is now
Well
Vivint
The real fun there is space command runs everything
Secret behind NASA
We're going to go to bed
In space command is like
Start a war with
Russia
This is 2014 15 years after the Y2K episode
He's still on space command
How many times has space command come up in the intervening
Quite a bit right and so but the other thing is
The context of what's going on
In March
Is that
Invade Crimea
Sam
That was why people were mad at Russia at that point
Yes leasing the globalist
Maybe some people did want to
Be like hey don't invade
Your neighbors
Cuz that's kind of a
Kind of big thing
Call neighbor's wife and also don't Annex
Player like
Slickly Russian
Tire country
Also did he say did he say
Interstellar program flashlight Interstellar program
4 or contrary
That mean
Within Stars between Stars
That's a long way away we're going to Stars
We are man
Is it easy
You got a f****** watch The Mindy Project Camelot Interstellar the movie come out
24K Magic
They're responsible for Interstellar is a movie because it's predictive programming
You know before we can reach the
The stars with the shake off
The shackle
Of the programming
Infested our brains in our souls
Alex Jones
About the downfall of
Humanity
Got coming from a very high place
Where were you
Together
We did
To now
What we have
Become
Animation
They're all sitting around
There there there there
There
Kissing a girl for the first time under 12
They're getting in a fist fight
Suddenly everyone has a television set
It's a sign of status of your two television sets by 1955
Not in the real world you're entering the Proto Matrix
Don't disagree with him the TV is our kind of
Shity
Theory
I think the more important Wally on everybody and we're all going to be fat sitting
I think I'm in leg list
I think the more important even
3 years ago and
System piece of his
His sort of ethos
Is that the human
Rag a kiss girls
Your fist fight
Exactly
Stars
Fishing in a creek
I thought
You get a little crawdad URI
That's exactly how I replace
With crawdaddy
Do you know if it's possible
Possible
You talk about TVs and basically
They take over your life
He's basically saying they can hypnotize
But let me tell you this
I'm not sure how far we're going but I want to say this
TVs aren't the only thing that can happen
You're welcome
Allen and 19th
Joan
Suddenly they all gravitate around the television
Flicker rate
Design
Hypnotized
False reality
I can't
That's why they're so dumb that's why you can't get through
That's why they're so suggestible
I don't even try to be manipulative
Using basic systems that they use in television and the people literally go back into trances and
Identification
Alex Jones Alex Jones
What's going on
Watching television
They're having interact with people
Deal with all sorts of crises
In the military is a white cuz I seen the corruption
But like so he
You can hypnotize anybody into
Just happen to their programming
That's nonsense
Okay
5 vets
But his secondary thesis is that
His wife
Can tell but like
He goes on
He's like
The police and the military
They're more awake
Good God damn
But his demographic is largely police and military
How do you know it's not to insult them
So he says everybody else is stupid
Way smarter than everybody else
Show
I just don't know why it is such a weird 121
Compare like donate money to us and not idiots
Like I don't know why there is just that relation
Will probably probably never know why that is the case but I
Give me money
Because and I don't like revealing
On the show this should be an offer conversation
You can
Tap into their program
Right
I'm a regular person out there
You're hypnotizing me now the evil cross-eyed
The powers for good he hates the Matrix
So this whole
This whole idea that the whole good old days
Right
Is it
Like this
People worth
Smarter
Before TV
Because you just said people have only gotten
Dumber and dumber
So does he think that before.
TV
Everyone was just
Walking around with
Knowledge
Rare
Like the interstellar program
Because of
TV like that's what's really going on people would just go down to the creek
All these pencil-necked with their TVs that are educated
Chicken neck
I'm using I'm using
My colloquial
Alex Borstein
You know that
Accepting to crawdads sing
It's just social program
It wasn't until the Supreme Court legalized
Relationship
It's part of the
Conditioning
Matrix that were in
Thoughts about the Matrix
Yes
Something incredibly dumb
Everything is about getting people and just for themselves
See what's around them you're never going to
Tell them about it
They've got to see it
Unfreeze the truth
I feel so good
Dumbbell press are are heavier
And 6070 hundredths
Because I'm not used to listen to White weight
Muscle memory
Addition in the wind that is going to rain will not try appointments in the wind and rain will grow and thrive
Pressure
Sweetness leaving the body
Your money
In the real world clips
Yeah man
Yeah
They drove math
The Dons off cliff
We need to get back to that time whenever also Couldn't Write
Will could draw some of them
But yeah
Is weakness leaving the body first of all are blowhard assholes
There a gym shirt
Red pill thing is is the
Bulshit men's activist
Are men's right assholes
What the
Voters
It's the gamergate Buckhead
This is all
All of them
And a million pound dumbbells
It's been pointed out of 100 times but the whole red pill mythology does comfort
The Matrix movie made by trans women
Innovative
The time and the only reason
Was as a f****** that's it
The other thing is I was
Thinking about this redpill idea quite a bit late
And I realize that we are really took a wrong turn
What a bunch of people
Realized
That they could present
Being tricked
Is being red pilled
You're mean
Alex is tricking people
Right
Most of these online communities that are about men's rights
A certain things
Into falling into their world
They're not
Opening up anybody's eyes
Truth or reality or
The Matrix Man
If there's any community of people who are actually doing that like
Broadly speaking
Like some of these hallucinogen base communities
Maybe
Baby p.m.
Baby we're seeing with the red pill stuff is just yet another
Application for doing
What you already wanted
I am taking the red pill
It's getting others to do it to its Evangelical in nature
Any idea is tricking P it's almost like an intellectual pyramids
Like you don't get much out of it unless you get other people to fall in line with your ideas
I mean like
Say religion
For one month
Community wherein they become an echo chamber for themselves
How's the naked talk s*** on women all day
They can do I call
Matter really the victim
Why they need to evangelize
Is just standing alone in saying that
I hope your apartments decorated
I mean
The penny
Collective
Does any Collective Community entirely
Like
Even a small
Towns have that same
Chamber Of Life
Is it to live in a small town
Sure
Fidget cubes
Pinging at back
People into those
Smile to problem is
India
Case
Some parts of it are great
Support small town living are fantastic rights activists
You have all those dudes
You get to hang out with dudes all day
Angry
Miss f****** aligned like Monsters dudes not thrilled with it
Jim root
Broom broom
Watching that dude
Grunt
Scream and then pi5 is Bros because
It's not great you know what is the best
What is the best
I remember back when I used to
Wasn't it the best
Flip out of church and I'm sure you're in the same boat
Not a great sermon
But it is a sermon
F****** Alex Jones
Trying to hyper match at the next
Pay-per-view between himself and the devil and it's a little long
But I wanted to fight all the way through
I think I would much rather have had
My pastor
Do I have the Lord on my side
More or I'm thinking
He's going to play chess with
I'm not sure which
The first the prior is closer to it Alex is about to do on this one and just let it ride
This is
F****** crazy
In the middle of this
On the screen
They flash up the Wikipedia page
So like as a reference
You know how great that is because you can
Really flash up
Any verses of the Bible talk about the
The devil really
We are being sucked in
Evil
Animation
The animation that I want people to come up with
I'm sorry
I forgot to
Interrupt red setup totally correctly
He's also wanting people to draw an anime show
He wants a cartoon
He wants other people to do he's doing the contest
He's very lackluster about pitching it
So I have to explain he wants people to
Draw cartoon of
He's describing @ms where he loses his shift
Human Spirit expression
Of the Mind Control
Controller
That is the ultimate against free will
God gives us free will to the enemy the devil
It's in front of you on our road
Tennis stars
Human development
They control us in thomastown
Play God and build an artificial system
To predict the future
Omnipresence the devil is trying to use human made in the image of God
I got machine over everything
He is a Deceiver
What the frog
Is going Interstellar
Challenge
And a smartphone to the NSA
Culture destroying the chemicals in the water and the war on the Family
Coming down
The fire
Beyond
Animating contest of Liberty
The devil's doesn't give you the animating contest the devil lies and tells you
Bedeviled
Nothing
The Creator
We are made in the image of the master builder
The Supreme architect of the universe in idiots
Heavens
We are made in the image
And the lightness
In our bodies
Supreme entity
Systems that our minds cannot even begin
Jen to imagine
And the devil wants that's because the devil is never a maker
The Devil is a taker
Counterfeiters from the beginning
And a fraud
With a false light of Black Sunshine
History there
You know what that is
Got to fill time
Talking about either
Here's the problem
Because he
Two things that plays
There is a contest
Then he's trying to run cuz I shouldn't have to give $10,000 to do this
Designer you here
But if you're also still does to this day
He talks about the animating contest of Liberty
What makes us Ally
But animating is imposed to us not being
Talk about an animation contest but also talked about the animating contest
To mean a lot Olive
God created us music Eminem
And the devil
The devil warranty never would have created a woman
He wants to make a god machine
Tell the future
That's what I would do
Sure
The flamingo
And how would you do that
Smartphone
Destroy the family
Crawdad
Problem-solve
Yeah
He's trying to steal the power that God.
Benevolence
Do we have a do we have a reason for that
Like does he have a goal
His goal is to create a god machine cuz he wants to know the future
What's the endgame
Control the present
But that's what he thinks I mean it's all it's not really about a literal devil even though he is yelling about
It's all about the global
Wright Road no that's that's a good point
Create a god machine
It's just a convoluted metaphor
Screaming about
Biblical scripture in the literal devil
Right it's just
It it really comes down to it that's a lot of fun
And he's losing it
But it's just filling time
He's not saying any
What if you were
If I went to church
This is great
I've never I've never seen any Pastor lose it like that
But thankfully never seen some of the guys who handle
Snakes though
19 videos
Yeah but I mean I thought I went to church that had that
To get bit
Boca
Friend
Gets me we're going to break sign
He comes back from break a little bit
America
Weekly turns big
Everything
Wichita
In the fraud and it's basically
Human species
They want to ban the word bossy
Because it's associated with women henpeck
Well when they're supposed to be
What the man
Never happy when they are bossy
The men are supposed to act like men as well so I don't blame women
Sxsw
They are sponsoring
Open carry armed March
Amazon.com
So then gets into his March a little bit there at the end just give you guys a little flavor
Butts
Is it pissed off
They're actually
Aaliyah really interesting example
Some
Feminist
Push
But Alex is mad about
Because it's one of the ones that I can
Really understand what they're saying
Better
Alex is missing entirely
So
The whole thing about like a Beyonce had that campaign about
The word bossy being sort of
Negative
Right
That is a great example
I never watch Thomas Bergman
Show that just got
Conservative
The budget was way too high his salary was ridiculous
Can't have
Voices on ABC
I hear a campaign like that
And what I hear is
I don't enjoy it when you use this kind of language
It makes me feel bad
That's what I hear
And my response
No big deal
I'll just a little bit out of courtesy
No big deal I just want to call you bossy
You know what gender do people throw around
I'm not sensitive to it because
Another woman and maybe your experience is different
Is Alec
Asia
If I knew that
You know what we should have done
It had a trigger warning
To let him know that we were going to
Need to be staying the word
Cuz I know you really angry
Alarm is I love his anger
Women are never happy
No it's not what they're
Supposed to
Women are only happy when they're doing what they're
Opposed
Rent-A-Center
They're trying to outlaw this word
They're trying to ban this word
They're trying to take away my ability to say things
Better
You can still say it but you can still say it but once people have alerted you to the
Doesn't make him feel good
They just got to wrestle with the fact that
Your choosing
You know make people not feel good
People tell me
Natsu
Rachel
Sure
Horrible
Assholes
That it's a it's like
Alex
Fine fine
Don't use
The word because that has a
Connotation
End of yours
Towing with
You're acting
Bad for the way that I take
So it's the word bossy when used
In that regard
Memes
You know
I am supposed to be
So I mean
1st Timothy 2:11
Sure woman learn and also
Submissiveness
I permit no woman to have authority over man
For Adam was
Suck it
Scripture
Yeah which you appear
Really cannot do
Give the broad stroke
That's important
We will be putting that scripture up on knowledge fight so you guys can
Confirm for yourself
1st Timothy
It is fun for me how
Little
These assholes
Call themselves
Christian
Like if you're going to be a men's Rights Act
Wouldn't that be the
First Bible verse you put up
You would think
Not at all
Because of You Reba
Believing
The tube is being slow
Stockton B
Yeah well
So before we had all this technology though
Alex Jones
Used to get information the old school way
Pony Express
There similarities
With the biotechnology
It's a lot more seriously I'm an engineer
Television show Washington
Now
That is a
The bad experiment
I don't understand why you would do that experiment
I don't
Understand what the goal of that experiment would be
To figure out
But that would be
Yeah it so I mean you don't really even know it still people anymore but
An engineer at
UT
Yes
Videos of wires and their brain
The Monkees
Or did it just risked
I'm not sure
Was it just like like
Jimmy I see the the
The blast Shield doors
You just see a s*** ton of monkeys
You put a
An infinite number of monkeys
You get the new girl I don't know
I don't know what reference
To make their
So you talked a little bit more about it
You thought that was it no it's not
You trying to warn you folks weapon system
It's so advanced
They got a monkey Farm in Bastrop close
Rhesus monkeys all night
We got chimeras
With their humanized
TV and crying
Over closed circuit television
DARPA facility
Excuse me
I just spoke
It half measures are not going to defeat
With wires in their brain
With flicker right to mind control
Governments were going to do this
That's the first thing I would do
He he made one unfortunate piece of information
Public
Trucking rant or whatever it was
Bastrop
Go to the town Intex
I thought you said it was at UT
Aquarius Restaurant
And then he said he saw it over closed circuit
Okay
Which of the monkey wrench so bad I've looked into this
There is a place called The Screaming monkey Ranch
Basically
There's some outdoorsy but I found their Facebook
And it's mostly
Keybar
Pictures of people drinking gentleman's Jack
The guy who looks like someone I know
The bar public
How would you hide
Ranch
You would make people think it was
The regular bar
What's the name
Public it in the white paper
They're doing this program in front of everybody
In front of you
Hypnotize by the idea of bars
Old 5 Star reviews one of my favorite places
Some of my favorite people in the world
Months ago
I love this unique Rich good friends and
UT engineer's Tiki Bar at the screaming monkey Ranch
Swift men's rights
Open Instagram page
I don't believe it
Snooze
Diagnose
Ceramic elephant
Goats
Fake boat
We're people can drink
Nefarious and there's probably tons of torture experiments that are going on there
Because that you can just Google
Just clearly what he's talking about
Absolutely
Now
I guess
If you want to go like
We might as well do you know how in Lake
Roswell restaurants
Scream
At the
If only it was a pizza place
Basement
So
And the monkey
Pedophile
Seams are on the up-and-up
Ultima 40-year program
Monkeys don't live that long
Doing 440
Also it's
Like if you're talking about monkeys you're not you're talkin about 8
Just to be very specific
You're not going to get many great experiments on Monday
Does chimpanzees or what you really want a mica Pusheen
We don't want a bonobo
Closest
Right on their super close which is which is the evolutionary theory
Human beings
Bonobos
Chimpanzees rip your face off
We're somewhere in the middle
So I don't believe you Alex
Let's try another thing I don't believe them
Obama Surgeon General
Pick
Guns are public health issue seeing one's about two steps ahead of us on this
Is narvon yesterday
And the mayor of London
Has called for anyone
Visitors
To the screaming monkey
Shell for 300,000 lb
Airport for no reason
We'll grab your shoulder
Kids are gone
Harsh
Can your kids away and
Sending them to salary.
Dude
That I have a Tor Browser for this reason
I am saying that I'm sure you can buy a kid for a lot
I don't even want it
Engage that line of horrified
Is not as expensive as you might think you just make it
The very
The very idea
If you yell at your kids
Exactly nonsense
Because
Cuz if you're in the air
Right and you're a fine upstanding citizen
Just one time
Apparently have not been
You look at those parents yelling at the
Somebody should take those kids away
Icing parents hit their kids
In public in the airport
Nobody public airport. I've seen people not do anything about it
No it's
That's working
Stupid thing I wanted more point out though is in comparison to his modern tone
He's not saying things that are different
Like you still saying that your kids are going
It's backed up
And sent to a Dungeons and what have you
You still saying the same stuff but his tone is so different
Now he's like
They're going to end up in a Saudi dungeon matter-of-fact
Flippant
I don't enjoy it
Are you sure it's a little different
I'm just I like to know.
Differences between
Current Alex
And passed out
Especially when he's saying the same thing
But now everything is so
Black and white
Where is before I do believe believe
No
Kind of kind of on
Say in this
Like from what we've done
As far as our previous
This is kind of
Alex Jones
Tumi
Like he's been doing the show for 9
19 years of this
And he's just kind of got his he's in his like little flows
Now
We're seeing him taken
Sweetly out of that
20 year flow and he is
Always under attack
He's
Get this wagon to the worst president in history
I was I was like
I was before Trump was what I even did a bit about it where
You know the worst president
History was in
Andrew Jackson
Unequivocally
Trump is be single worst president
In the history of the United
MLS
Well if you're going to pick one you might as well go Whole Hog you might as well if Meijer number two
Absolutely
Music
This
Text clip
Human Ed McMahon for the
Prairie
Reference
From Publishers Clearing House
Put that last clip I think
I'm done with it
F****** try
We got to get to
We got to get to this next thing I'm going to let you talk
Cat litter up for that which does not speak
So
Taking my Dallas philosophy a little bit too far
That last clip I believe
Something
Different
About Alex
In the past
The present
This next clip is something
Clearly hasn't changed
And that is Alex's accidental willingness to outsources
Cuz he snitches on his cousin
Pretty hard
Oh yeah more
Oh by the way
It came out about a month ago and Wired Magazine
The sign waiver form to not be depressed anymore
Help PTSD
Cool Ranch
Secret operations in Mexico
Getting out
Coronavirus
Do all the articles about
About time
That's the one about PTSD branch
Let's blast to the Head
Pulling up with the
Implants to help
PTSD
Hey Alex want to sort this out pre-show professional
Implant
Plants
Apologize
Special forces are going to be getting chips
Start with Z noncommissioned officers
Admitted
Of course the Mexican police
Attorney general got about 10 years ago in Mexico for kidnapping or whatever but he have the chip in Miami
Baja Beach Club
So cool
Stop by Southwest
For sure
Stuff that he's talking about in terms of troops
Experimental PTSD treatment
Sure it sounds pretty unconventional but also
There's a rash of suicides that are happening with returning veteran
Number one killer of American troops
And so the idea that someone would try something unconventional suicides
Doesn't really
Doesn't seem to farias
Studies that I
Giving mushrooms psilocybin or lsv
Houston
Which is why
I was saying the redpilling the real version of it
Could be hallucinate
To some extent but I again I don't want to fully step into that
World cuz
Some people are real idiots
$50 a month
To the patreon
What do a time travel episode
Will take a bunch of mushrooms
And time travel
What we will do I could not handle that
Anyway
More important things
Is there a
Within
It would be so easy to figure out who is cousin
Yeah his cousin was doing Secret work in Mexico just got out of the army alone
He just said on a
F****** public broadcast
Cousin was leaking secret information thing
But he did
Clearly
His cousin wasn't allowed to talk about it
Because it's cousin didn't a cousin
You know how I know that his cousin
Is not responsible for it
Hypnotism
You're right
Alex is probably lying
But if he's not lying
That the Christ is cousin he's just
Snitched on cousin for a felony
Great use of your time Alex
Talk about the globalist
Here are you snitching on your cousin
Can punk ass Alex
Betty White
Could be
You got a brain chip now is not the same guy
Human
Is that a position I don't know
He got he got chipped
Years ago
Fits like a tracking chip
That's basically find my phone
Basically work
With any dog
Adopt
Or LoJack
On a car
Horses or like
Traveling
Killer whales dolphins
Frankly
Directions
I get it there's privacy issue
You don't want to be
Where's like that
As far as
GPS chips
If we can't open
The Floodgate Of chip talk
Because if everyone had
They Carried with them at all times with GPS technology somebody couldn't
Maybe there's a f******
What's it called
Whatever it is
Specifically for the NSA
Do you ever you are
Turn into a recording right
Like all of this
You have a f******
I do
Anytime that mean
Right now I have it in the refrigerator
Definitely not
Right next to
You could have
Sidekick
Taking a sidekick
I mean frankly at this point
Walkie-talkie
Isaias released on the internet now
Stroom some horrible stuff on this
Which is
My advice to everyone listening to
Download signal double-ended encryption
You're much better off
That is
Publix
The public service announcement
It's a given this next clip
Whatever the reasons you think
It's not racing
Really
HBK
Because
They didn't love guns
History of the Civil Rights
To look
0 understanding of that I'm putting words in his mouth slightly what I'm trying to say is that he believes that
Gun March
Is more important than
Some civil rights
People already there Center going to show up
Weather firearm
The Alamo
Marshwood land commissioner
And we can
He went and ate the lunch counter and you can just go straight to hell if you don't like it
Hardcore human rights god-given rights civil rights movements
Liberalism
In Thomas Jefferson Gunn property
Consciousness
Association tomorrow
In The Patriot
I'm so excited
And I just can't hide it I think I may go down
Even your flat Alex your Flats
I can't think of anywhere
Obviously you are a large group of all white men
Only corollary to your situation
You're so off base already
Jakari Jackson the black dude and the woman
I already off
Thank you
So this next clip Alex Jones said some things about
But I don't know what
Alex Jones talks a little bit about foreign influence in the government
Which is a little bit
It's a little nowadays
Alex UTSA particularly
Being usurped by degenerate criminal scum.
Control reality they're the trendy's
Chicken neck
Gatlinburg vacation
You never want a serious crisis to go to waste
What I mean by that is an opportunity to do things that you think you could
He's an officer in the Israeli military
Call Manuel
It's not fun is there is there
Any position
That
The GOP
Were you literally
Butwell
Everything
Single position they
You can go back
Very short
And find them
India
0 people free of this
Especially endemic now because we had Obama in office
And they hated him so much
F****** McConnell said it
My only job is
Make sure that he is not allowed
Things to do with gov
And everything to do with
Don't want him
Forgot about this
So the craziest part of this is vague
The
Situation that there a debt work
We're in our government
Utterly
Worthless
You can't work with anybody because they already set the
You can't do it and you know they're going to get snake bit
Somebody back bite you
I totally forgot about this
Today on the show
Rodger Stone
What's going on why did Jag
About how Joe McCarthy was a good man
In Hollywood
Where were they were they all red
And he's like
You know what who has real Blacklist
Oh no
The Blacklist
Calling black anchors on CNN
You can't do that
Also repeatedly has Roland Martin calling him a quotes
Stupid negro in a fat negro
So
He also referred to Rowan Martin is
Quote quote
Spy CNN
Rodger stone is
Is attack
Last year tweeting Misfits
Immediate matters funded by Dirty Clinton money try and orchestrated hit on me for calling out idiots and Navarro
And Roland Martin
Really not that you called about it
You called him
Negro
You're not allowed
Well we find this behavior unacceptable
Anyway
So yeah McCarthy School
For now
We're going to get to some meat and potatoes
Supposed to be about the Malaysian flight
Again you forgotten already
It's hard it's hard not to
After the death unless he ties the devil in
The reason the Malaysian
Play
I'm going to forget he's talking about the
Play Devil Went Down
Now he doesn't do that but he does
Think Siri Amelia Earhart
Plane went down
Can I talk about
I told her 11
Came out
Free smart devices smart cars appointment
California Australia
So I would tell people about this
The only real Ender phone calls.
Battle came out
The real are phone calls there's gas we can't breathe
My alarm
Regardless
Don't know what happened in Malaysia
They could have blown it somewhere else change the transponders we don't know
They could even crashed
Yeah Siri
Right
Lichen
So Alex Jones apparently I didn't even realize this
But that was the theory he landed on
Control flown into the building
I didn't know anything he landed on in terms of
I guess that's
Is that better than a false flag operation
It would be it would be like the NSA
Control the government
And this is also the terrorist around on it
Revelation
Which is why they're going
Regional Alex
What are the sources
The devil
Both
They tagged
Call Alex
A real call
The one from 911
Yeah it's kind of interesting
If you read the transcript of it
But it doesn't
Save it there's gas
And we can't breathe
What does it say
They were saying
Who was on the phone
Was saying that
She believed
That someone had used me
And that some people were having trouble
If you want to go really far with it
Extrapolate
As Alex loves
You could take that to me
Hey there's a lot of hurdles of a story we don't know
To overtake the attackers with maze
Some of the attackers might have had mace and use their own people to
If you had any
Like if you had met
Of course you're going to do
There's a number of explanations
That call
Involve the planes being remote control
Anyway
I don't care
So Jordan
Be ready for this
No
It's time
We've gone on
A very Malaysia plane list Adventure
So far throughout their what is
We need to go deeper into the zero we are
Because Alex Jones
Gets super defensive about super male vitality
He starts a commercial that last
For f****** ever
I put up some parts of it but just to give you an idea it's at least like 15 minute
This is how he starts
Answer this s*** so defensive offence
Is it about it
Here we go
Comments on YouTube
Male enhancement drops
Really
Yeah you better
Herbs concentrated blow your freaking stock sauce
Yeah you bet
They ain't even seen bone broth yet
No idea what kind of male enhancement there
Yeah
Male enhancer
Rent is coming baby hold on
This is so important for our analysis of Alex Jones
It is basically a boner
We talked about it as a pill
And we've been kind of glib
Cape May
You know that's a powder you put in milk or whatever
It turns out
Weave
Superman Vitality is a liqueur
It comes in a dropper
And you put it under your tongue
Basically
What it comes like in an eyedropper bottle
Lakers it's
So
What
You take a dropper
Yes
You put supermodel Vitality underneath your tongue
Is there a reason behind that I don't know does male Vitality come from
To get into whether or not it's a boner
At this point
The time has come it has come
And I'm going to tell you this
We're not going to get a direct answer
Between $10 each
Process
That is
Male enhancement
Nobody put shop products cost twenty bucks
I'm about to buy a product for mitochondrial DNA nobody else is putting out
My dad was at all to get four
Your dad the dentist $60 a bottle
To get this Farm
Dennis can be inventors
Cost $100
Message is going to cost a 60 we got to have RNG money and all the other money among the fund all the operations
Stuff we're rolling out
Really powerful stuff okay
And
Disability
Story
Everyone in the office
We don't advertise it as an aphrodisiac
That is not the intention it is
It doesn't have any
Testosterone mimickers like most
This is design
Get your body to release its own growth hormone
I don't know what it's doing
So that's what
So that's what group
Says it's doing
Now
Dr. group
Is the guy
Who makes
Right
I looked up dr. Drew
He works
Run
The place called
The global Healing Center
Based out of Houston
And if you go to their website you can find a picture of him he looks crazy
He looks like a hippie kind of weirdo look like
I'm Petty there's a little bit of that like
Unfortunately they give
His educational background
Ishq
Well I like that
It's from the Texas Chiropractic College
Yeah it's a doctor of Chiropractic
Can you even do that at the Texas Chiropractic School
I don't think that accredited
Not accredited
So you also went to the MIT Sloan School of Management which there's no real like graduation
But I assume he actually went there
Got the other is a diplomat
A diplomat of the Chiropractic Board of clinicals
Attrition
From the cradle
Board of clinical nutrition
He's a diplomat of the American Board of functional medicine
Britches
Dubious
He has a bunch of degrees from the natural healing Institute of neuropathy
Greed from lies
Is a neuropathic practitioner degree a certified clinical nutritionist degree
Holistic healing
What is certified clinical herbalist
The Great
From
The natural healing Institute of harappa
Do you know what that means
WhatsApp
Not neuropathy I'm sorry natural
Little letters
Okay
I get
Why you would
Say it to
But
The mitochondria
Is not where you find
Perichondrium
The engine of a cell
It has no DNA and then whatsoever
More important
Alright
Basic biology he also claims in his educational background that he went to the Harvard Business School
Go to the Harvard Business of developing
Bulshit Prada
P.m.
From the Harvard Business
I don't know what that
No one really does
The owner and president
Management program
The Harvard Business School.
If you look into
You pay $30,000
You pay like $30,000
And there's no educational requirement
They just
Like a fundraising business management
Tyra Banks got in big trouble cuz she claimed that she went to the Harvard Business School at Trinidad it was this
Everyone clown daughter real heart
But now more importantly the natural healing
Institute of naturopathy
I look
F******
Homeopathy
They have a Yelp
Lotto one-star reviews
I want to read one for you
This is a terrible School
I've almost completed the distance learning program for holistic health practitioner
And I would not recommend this cool to anyone
Far from a completely disorganized
Trouble completely disorganized staff was asked me to resubmit work
Typos on most of the task
And hidden
Extension fees for
Completing the course with an 18-month
At the top of each study guide
Dear friend and student
We wish to emphasize that there are no deadlines
Complete your lessons
Complete your lessons and submit your open-book exams and or projects at your own pace
As your own schedule allows
What they don't tell you
Is it for every 6 months you go beyond 18 months
They will charge you $5,200
And hold your degree hostage until you pay them
I'm only finding out this information at the very end of my training course
It gets worse
I took a shiatsu course
I took a shiatsu class in person
I took a shiatsu class in person with them
So we could draw meridian lines with magic markers on each other
I told him accredited
I told him if that was how he felt
You should make all the guys wear Speedos
To which you replied
No one wants to see that
That is the type of school where dr. group
Has
Super weird but that is also what happened in
English let 1014
Who's the fairy difference
Is it I had to wear a Speedo otherwise I
Pass by
Alright I'm done
6 degrees from
He has a doctorate only from the Texas
Chiropractic Chiropractic
He's a Chiropractic Doctor hold on
The other doctor that involved at all the enforces dr. Wallach was a veterinarian
Dick
Hanging out who are fake doctors
Dr. group
Is made this DNA product
Anna patch
So makes Alex's dick hard though
Alex in that last clip said
I don't know if I can
And that
Is a reference
Throbbed
Rob do what did Rob do do while we're going to find out
Cuz Alex
Is so obsessed with telling the story that he can't tell
That he has someone go grab Rob do
Who is putting together the Nightly News
Yeah oh yeah
Cuz I was like this is classified as
So he goes and has someone fetch around 2 and bring him in
And Rob do
Precedes to give
And Incredibly weird super male vitality
So here we go
I totally correct
You just called for me and I'm Superman
Regardless
So I want I wanted to stop here for a second
Because
This is going to be a little bit it's like
3 minutes long
A male page
This is where it ends
It gets
So f***** up
Go fuc
Did they remove Rob juice
Penis is Rob Dewey eunuch
No
I can't
I can't prove or disprove
Alright
The craziest Revolution
Revelation ever
And that isn't Alex Jones
Who are the same age
No f******
No way no way Alex
You're 52 if you're a day
Anyway
Like I said
So f***** up
I can't even
So f*****
Superman
About two weeks now
I think it was after we shot that interview
Yeah I know
IPads
In the morning 3 in the morning
In the morning
Kind of fog when you wake up
About 5 minutes
And I'm thinking clearly and I feel like I don't I don't feel overly abundant energy like when I drink
It is definitely mellowed me out
I started doing now
And I like it
And I've definitely noticed that maybe that's why they're all insane cuz they're all taking their own
Project energy
It does
I took them this morning and I feel really aggressive
I don't really
So right there Alex.
So now at this point Alex is about to get really weird with Rob do
Don't f****** say a word over this
I just know that the entire time Alex is smiling more than I've ever seen him smile on the show
We're so happy about the question he's about to
It's great
Surgery of energy
And I'm I'm definitely a Believer after that but what about the classified
Bedroom
List
I love you babe
Women can take
Fluoride
How f*****-up is I told you I told you this was the most f*****-up commercial ever
Wow
Alex straight-up suggest
Hey I tried to get my wife to take it
Give her the Funky Cold Medina
Wow
Not only that
Like what
What's your dick is too hard
No
There's something
F****** weird
We can see the aggressiveness
The comes out in Alex
I don't know Alex
You should take less
That's
Not a good time
Don't do this
Please rob do
You're ruining your marriage
With this insanity
That's like a Cialis
Commercial wasn't
The two bathtubs right next to each other and then the wife just throw it away
Tell your husband
You need a good dick
Kia
Smiling
Like he knows what I've talked about her
With Rob do any is 11
You can't get enough
I mean why like I said this is the end of the show
Like they're running out of time to talk about any real news
So I want to play for you
We can't put
Too small a point on the fact
Dual wife told him to stop
Taking
3 droplet
In the morning and night what the f***
What is wrong with you
Seems like too much
Like this
With Rob.
Trying real hard
To get Alex
Actually talk about news
The Malaysian plane
And it's f****** delicious
Is just going for the day
No he's off the dick
But this is so funny
Cuz this is literally just don't break
Michelle
Route to comes in
Some information
List analysis
You know it's not like
It's the wrong time you got walk with me playing
What do you think about that I'll see you in hell before I talk
So then we come back
Long super male vitality
Commercial
Not done
Cuz
Again
More about what's going on
Yes
History Boys
This is insane it's three lovely boys
Do you know what else
If you want to have a boy
Superman
Alex's
Vagina
While Rob do was in studio they're doing basically bro-down podcast
The Great
Toonami
What's happening
There's something about 3 boys
Anyway
I don't understand that at all I think he's trying to compliment and connect with him and it's just weird enough live
But hold on
This
I hate
Keep saying for the f****** Mike down
But this is another one
Literally
It's one of the t-shirt ideas
Design
What are you guys
Anyway
Is IU fight about Twitter
B this mine
I can check his
Official
Ewok artist
Acknowledge
Designs in sending over with
F****** shirt together
Listen
The next clip
Is theater of the Mind
And all you really need to know
Is he is literally doing everything he says he's doing
Right he has a hamburger
Okay
Is important
It's not
It's not imaginary
It is a literal hamburger
Evan Visser
Call Steve Mike
Cam
Missing Malaysia flight
Article
Changing it on air
Missing Malaysia flight
007 McDonald's
That's the weather
You're watching on television
I didn't ask for this
Department
Fast food
And this is satanic
Vicious
Ferrari
And the rapids-rice is cuz it's trying to
Mighty python
Dot-com displeasing element you satanic
This is a P Terry's hamburger
An item
This is hamburger has no cheese
No ketchup no mustard no lettuce no onions no tomatoes
Android
This is not right
This is anathema
I'm going to put Superman
No one has ever done this before
Vons.com
But Superman Got Talent
And handsome survival she'll make tonight on
And Now ladies and gentlemen
Longer satanic
I have transmogrified a word
The most delicious Burger in the galaxy
I am about being silly
But you did some serious topics
The Minnesota
Hey Alex how you doing today
Oh I don't know the others.
SpongeBob ideas phone around but I wonder if I might have something to do with the 10 was possible
Nukes that were secretly shipped out I know you mentioned that the plane could have been
I'd rather maybe landed at some
T.i. funded terrorist base and maybe their retrofitting it within stolen nuke
I love that so much
That might be my favorite like I want to I don't have the time to isolate the video but it's so
Cuz he is literally putting multiple
Black Blotter Foles of super male vitality and the
On his hamburger
And he just takes a big bite out of the burger
You're on the air
You just could give a s*** about this person
Dismissive
Malaysian blade
Guy gives weird. About nukes
Alright alright
New Angle
We've come
Billy talked about whether or not Alex
Is evil or stupid
And when
He's being evil
Stupid
Baby
His brain is
F***** up
With all this s***
He's taking all the time
I think that this might be right around the beginning of his supplements
Destroying
Why would you put
And you've already
Lego full thing you get irritable
3 minutes of the show
Burger
Rob has asked him to Steph
Stop
Telling Alex
Imagine his ex-wife is probably telling him also
So
That
Is so
Dive on
Weird
Hallucinate
I don't know
This is this to me
Is slowly poisoning
They might be
Jimmy
When we talk about the stupid evil continuum
That's genius
Tumi
Really funny
It's hilarious
I don't like the idea that
Dressing up as the Joker
I don't think of it like
I like the idea of other people taking his supplements
But just him doing it on air
Overall this
Boner pill on this burger
This burger
Without all this
Satanic
You put some super male vitality
Not satanic lyrics
I can't stress this enough
The facial gestures and his body language once he starts eating a burger at gets on the phone call
Are there
There
Like top-notch sketch artist
Kind of nuance
It's so funny
Picton
Physically
How little he cares about the phone call all he wants to do is eat to supplement laced Burger
Kind of want to try it it's like a
Like a
Like
If a new drug comes out like I like if there's a better mvma I'm kind of like
Give that a shot like I want to see what about adrenochrome
That seems like a bummer
Two more clips
Left to play
Work
Vitality
That's a good question I don't know
If Alex is a false flag
Which some
Even harder right
Conspiracy theorists believe
Superman Vitality might be
Be the first taste of adrenochrome for
Could be could be
We all know the elites
Take all your products
I want
Super male Vitality on my burger
Vitality
Animal style
In this
These last
Clips
Finally gets
Stop talking about Malaysia
Playing up Malaysian flight 370
Super male vitality
Yeah and he's off the air
Ladies in overdrive
This
Clip is about
The best tea does it's been two sizing what do you think
You don't think much
There's really not much of anything here so I'll let him get to it
Malaysia flight I'm leaning towards hijacking and somebody's flying
I'm not sure about that
Yes you do
Persian Gulf
Terry
I don't know
Whodunnit
It's kind of sad
We want him to come up with
I imagine within like the next week
After this key cop puts together something that's fun or something that's nutty
But at this point
But you you latched on
Something
Of course
How to say is that it's
They already
I'm thinking
Yeah they
Facebook it down
Everything
Play Audible
Iranians
Are you talking about before I pretty much
Appreciate your call
I don't want sugar
Reportedly
I just think they look like capable very serious
Automation
Obama's innocent of everything as well
That really kind of the pictures real feeling
Yeah
I do think that this is so
This is so
Considering this
The guy who is like
Yeah Chobani yogurt is hiring Muslim refugees rape people
How how can you be so sure like this is a like I said he's on autopilot
His his racism is just kind of like
Like
Look like
The part of the most important part and I also do crafts
Vitality relationship
With my wife the reality is
Could have been
Could have been that wet the whole the whole thing was about Superman
Do you want to divorce your wife
I think I think they're still married
You do with the lady asks
Not if she's bossy
Why didn't Alex use that opportunity
To be like
Beyonce would say cuz he's back by the bank's multinational corporation
Bossy ass wife
Coppell
Spell rhabdo
I don't know
Colossal fantasy there
That was a weird little reverie you dived into the other thing I was thinking about is like
Akira
It's not
You're the one who's in love with Leah macadoodle in love with her
She's great
The other thing I was thinking was the possibility
That his ba big on autopilot
Is somewhat related to him being super
Cuz he did say
I forgot to eat
I would never blame
His being off-topic
On being hungry
But maybe he was
Hungry to really ramp
And get mad about stuff
Like he's spent a lot of energy on that devil
Right
I don't know if that's possible
There's no good series on air
With supplements on it
I've condom
That's the most
Disgusting thing I can
It was rough
Roast
This is
March 11th
2014 The Alex Jones if you would like
Time travel
YouTube has a really long week
But please you can donate to the show
Over on our website knowledge Linksys support the show donate 10 bucks a month we'll go back
History that I can find the episode of
I have consistent archives
To about
I would say
Mid-to-late 2012
And then I'm searching for more
Before that I might be able to find it
But consistently to around the
Let's
October 2012
Obama's
That's the one.
Oh man
What kind
Biomass
Probably pretty terrible
Of what we've learned space command runs everything
Devil
TV hypnotizes Alex
There's a monkey Farm
Monkey Farm
Cocktail
Government
Great Margaritas government's go tell your kids to Saudis
Comparison to guns
Gas
Death remote control
Superman
On the Malaysian flight
No idea
So
He gets my man I appreciate you giving us this assignment
If you guys want to find us you can reach up
Tunica gifts with love and
To the rest of you Polly policy
He walks out there
As well as the
Soon-to-be policy wonks
We toast you
Thank you so much
If you want to
How to build into an ad to knowledge fight cam
To be a much better resource
So please check out the website and see what kind of stuff like
I'm trying to make this a one-stop-shop for all your Alex Jones information
And
If you guys help out you know build
The traffic up
I did help a lot
Inspiring me to put the
The kind of work I'm already put it in in
Cuz it's a lot of work
And when I see all great firing dance
20 people came to the website
Inside is not that
Are we getting more and more downloads
Which means you guys are f******
Sharon the s*** out of
Knowledge
Is there an under
Knowledge underscore
Can you find
You can
Just now it's right we don't have a picture
If you do please involve
Give us a review appreciated
Also if you want to directly
Gmail.com email
But
Husband fun
We advise
Do not try
Super Mel B
Please don't buy any value products
They're made they're made by a chiro
Protractor and maybe if we
I don't think you should be taking me Product absolutely not just my thoughts
Look if you take me
These products
If you take me from Jordan's episodes
2 hours last one wonderful
It has been
Pennywise
More time travel episode
Rapoport
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work