Air Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as if through the good guy
We are the bad guys
MoneyGram
Stripe.com
Jordan Jordan
Okay this week
I went to the store and I got a couple of
Limited-time-only Foods
Okay we're sort of weird things that I've not tried before
Is a risky thing but I always
Especially in like snack foods or or candies or
Or something
I will never
Not buy them because of that Universe like
This can't be good no way
Got to fudge
Eminem's Eminem's okay
Those are good game changer one was wild Heat
You like that too
Yes he is where these were
Impulse purchase
Very rare
242 never happen
Complete
Disappointment disaster
Fudge brownies
Jacks Link's wild Heat
Good amount of heat
Really cleared
Give me out a little bit
All good
It's bright but it's turned into snack reviews I mean there's not a whole lot else going on
What is Viber
Hey graduation to tell me that a month ago
And now I finished the menus
Completely yes
Congratulations like this sucks and this sucks in this sucks and you should rewrite the entire book
But how about you start a page want to give me another one
Page one rewrite from the very beginning
Do you have any titles you want to tell the walks
Seems appropriate
Look for that on Simon & Schuster then the next 6 months
Caldecott award is what's it called those children's
Deep in my memory banks
Wolfram
Play Spotify
Some folks who signed up the show
So first cognitive dissidence
Thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Text Brandon thank you so much
Thank you Brandon
Next thank you so much
Are you very much
Thank you Jennifer from Houston
Android
Next. Explore dungun
H e x
Plore our Explorer
Thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Next
Finally
Two words l a space
And I see
Thank you so much
Thank you Ellie Turkish
I think it's the
Okay I have a bad track
Or you can find a local charity in your area that helps
People
We would like either
I'm glad you've learned a difference between
Conjunctive versus disjunctive those are important concept
Schoolhouse Rock
I am in a difficult position
I'm in a bit of a pickle Barrel
He is no longer allowed
I am
Jack from Twitter
According to his at his relationship with
Our media his app is removed from our store for Shirley and I felt like it would be kind of
Lame if we just deplatformed him for one episode
So I was like okay we got to do something different
Again
And f****** K22 Project Camelot episodes
No good no
A lot of weirdos the tertiary weirdos that we have like Dave daubenmire or
Reverend
Very very boring what is brutal Criminal
Maybe bow
And then the other one is a reverend
So we have like it was it was a difficult time trying to figure out something else to do to keep Alex
The platform
And then
Trump had his coronavirus press conference
Where he said that the power of the president
Is Ultimate
Weird ways you could
You know weasel around it and I'll be interested to hear Alex do exactly that
Do not talk about it he spent most of 2009 yelling about the temperament yelling about the rights of Governors super
Proceeding that of the president he tried to get a constitutional convention going
All of the governor's work for the
Deep State and only Trump is there to protect the
It's because it's so fundamentally against Alex's professed beliefs about what
Our government is how we operate
I got to untie his response to that
However
On Tuesday which is a recorded episode what a mother
Galaxy
Around
So I watched a little bit of incredibly boring so I am not going to do an episode about what
Response
So I I found myself back in that same Pickle Barrel
And what I did
Cuz I I I sat with
Some feelings
I reached out to our friend Robert Evans over it's a behind the bastards
Now he's got too much influence over this suggestion of Direction
Bill Cooper
Let's do it
Unfortunately
Tell Cooper that I want to talk about and I think that a lot of audience
Us to talk about our gigantic
They would require essentially
The same sort of thing that we did with endgame
Even more than
Play I want to get into his stuff about the Oklahoma City to Waco
You know these are things that he covered as they were happening
But they're so
Much got to do like it's so much preparation will be required cuz he does
A lot of episodes and unlike Alex they're all about the same thing and their tents that he talks about
Yeah
Alex is rambling about nothing
Until I want to do those but I can't do them
Today
Can't do them just
No half-ass
That's why I'm thinking about maybe
We shift things around
And
For a little bit
Only do Bill Cooper and check in on Alex periodically
Audience wants us to do that but it's something I'm considering like slipping on Monday and Friday hours on Wednesday
I like it thinking about that only to be like a way to
Get through
Some of these larger topics that I want to but everytime I'm in the position to do a Bill Cooper episodes like wow that's
Way too much
That we have
Sandy Hook
I'm considering
So we will see but anyway I wanted to fulfill some some of the audience's desire for some Bill Cooper
And so I went 20
And so I listen to a lot of stuff trying to find a good episode that was like this is a
It has some content that doesn't
Not something it's going to take us 40 hours to go over
And it was.
I didn't really find
Much
Immediately
I did notice
The bill doesn't number of Colin episode
Sporty looking just give him a call and talk about whatever that is exactly what I want
And
A lot of them are labeled
Calls call
Some of them
Are labeled calls
Good so those ones
You would think would be good
This one
That I got today
Is an episode from let me get the date on this one November 29th
Okay A bit late writing bills career just after
The election of 2000
And this one is labeled calls
Really good
I do really good
So I decided we're going to go over there
And I think it will be good because
Thank you
I want one reason for that is that we know for listening to act like so much water the pixie does it take straws
How to eat lunch is very rude
Solicitors
What they call in with stupid s*** like don't pop air bubbles cuz they come from China
Love it by the sandwiches
Frenchie ating some of the things
That's a B cell
We'll see your number of those okay opening up
Floor
Whatever you want to talk about
I don't care
Let's talk about it
Call hour tonight 50-33 3457a program
You can just say whatever you want to say something about whatever you want to talk about
I don't care
Movies coming up
To do
With a bunch of
Movie trailers are coming movie trailers and QuickTime
I fucken love this dude
Whatever I don't care about what
What is it what is a good 2000 movies
Actually doesn't want he references specifically blue my mind
This is Bill
The saying like I asked you to do
Because that
Is something that I used to say a lot as he is want to do today
Friend Marty DeRosa
Impressions of measly
Bill throwing that out
Kindred Spirits if opposite sides of the dispatch
Yeah it's weird
Very rarely hear anyone use that expression
And in strange
We're in November 2000
You're asking yourself
What movies is Bill excited about
Put on a CD in little video files media player files
He's got one in particular that he is
Super excited
Coming up
Avalanche
Trailer
For the whole movie I mean
Quite beyond the norm
I thought it was
Kind of movie screen and keep your seat right on the edge of your chair and trailer
Is this Buzz Marketing
Can you name race on bills
No but I do think I saw it
I remember there being a point where there's a jump
Acrostic
Movie Hughes
Which was released on December 8th 2000
A few weeks after this episode was recorded
The trailer I know but I think I worked at the movie theater when it came out because I did see it
If it wasn't like work-related
I can't imagine shoes
Review on Rotten Tomatoes not agree with Bill
The trailer for the top and piled one on top of the other
This is completely off track but it also is illustrative of a good point
What's good for a trailer
Sometimes not good for the movie itself
The conspiracy theorist often doesn't understand this difference and it's closer related to how they often fail to understand
How what works well in terms of writing a headline
Men are always work best in terms of telling the whole story
Anyway Billy probably letdown by Vertical Limit but it warms my heart to hear this guy so innocently enthusiastic about this upcoming
The movie it is really weird he's not saying that this movie is secretly revealing the plots of his enemies
You just think that actually looks good
That's so surprising just like
Another one of those things that makes me frustrated with Bill Cooper because he's so
Human god dammit
He's just a child being like
I really want to see the new Terminator movie when it comes out
And not because there's a massive global
Beersy because Arnold Schwarzenegger
I see you trailer for like
Series movies and I'm like
That looks really fun
He's just saying that looks scary. That would be intense to watch
That looks great yeah I think it's that it's uncomplicated yet he does not consider that it a trailer is
Full of Ebola
Wow
You know like now that we have Marvel movies where you can see a scene in the trailer that doesn't even happen in the movie
Trailers trailers
We put all the best parts in there
It's true
Movie corner and now he takes it to the calls
And I Source call Isaac
Vertical Limit
Open
Open now
People learn more
This isn't like you want to hurt me
Primer
Okay
Whatever driving book
Exactly the same
Always been
Every single night
Please get some fuzziness on the line I love that calls for anybody who wants to talk about anything
Calling my man my wife I isn't working that well right now what do you mean what do you think I should do
Actually be a problem of bills uplink
Broadcast
Hicksville Ohio
He could have got they could have gone to a song or something like this if there was any production at all but instead we get
Okay
Disconnect me right now
Copart
Ominous
Lego horror movie
When the phone is off the line you're like oh well obviously they're dead
Hello
This is the one box
Really good
Technical difficulties
I love it
In the same way it is like his movie reviews are like this naively kind of
Sincere whatever this is I can't handle this
Can't figure this out
Who's on air
Tony boys
A little bit resign to like it's not going to
No I don't know which whatever he did fix whatever they call this problem
Was no problem
No idea but it seems like everything's better now
Answer another call
And this guy has an interesting
Question to ask
Actually think implicates a whole bunch of different things in the conspiracy theory world right
To alot of things that Alex's
Pitched in the bride
Even has some connection to present a narrative
It's largely about the idea that after the 2000 election
Quinton could stay in office
Oakdale Clinton could end up staying in office
Really fun to see how Bill response
Canada
Vanilla yogurt
Mario
Is no way in the world
Beyond the day
Battery Specialist
Comeback
I don't think that there could ever possibly happen I don't think anyone would even
Alex is suggesting kind of
Trump impeachment to bring Hillary
President Clinton Hillary
Hillary Clinton even things
Along these lines at the end of Obama's term
This is just something that is a consistent preoccupation of the very dumb
Parts of the right of course it's just something that they are they're really deeply invest
Sit-in thinking is going to happen
That is never going to happen
Greeley
Cuz if that call came on Alex's show
He would be like
To do that
Bill saying no
Shut up is a really fun thing anybody
Dog
I seen the emails in the websites all over the Internet playing
He won't have to leave office when he coming
You'll be there
If you just
Declare himself
And he would have to have the military behind him
So you're saying there's a way it could happen that's what I hear cuz I listen to Alex
So what you're saying is this guy
To declare that he has total Authority
NFL military
A lot filled with right-wing reactionary type folks
They would have to be directly behind the president are you saying that's is that what Bill Cooper is
Majestic I made that Z-Wave things could happen
Can't happen
In the circumstances surrounding Bill Clinton because
As Bill explains this next clip
Military does not like
Bill Clinton
War
Chances of the military
It goes beyond
People have a brain
Yeah man I feel you I just want to make sure that everybody knows
But that last caller
Is is got rocks for brains he's Beyond sheeple day as well be alright
Stupid be a rock
Probably calling again
It's interesting
Too because I don't know this to be this case
Be two spies of Alex's trafficking
Some of those theories
Around this time
Websites pudding without
I don't know really could be really interesting as I was going through some of these episodes
Things that like obviously this wouldn't be a whole episode
I think the bill hated Alex a lot more than even we recognize couple points
Obviously he did an episode about Alex being a liar he didn't episode about is Y2K show
Like things that he did
Yo
Find
I think that he brings him up a bit more then than even we recognized
Here's the clip where he's at right after 9/11
Bill is talking about the out everyone's in a panic about anthrax
And
How everyone should just calm down there's no need to get
Crazy about this
Any opportunity to take a swing at Alex
Listen to me
Carefully
Directions
Performing
Cutting drywall
Drywall
All of a sudden somebody
Powder form
More
Coronavirus
Alex Jones
Florida
Ghetto Little Bill
I think if I were to listen to all of his episodes
I think that you'd end up finding a number of Pop shots like that I think that you probably held his tongue
Well I didn't care for a while then
Two of them got into a little bit of a like I'll wait this guy sucks
He's lying restaurant started taking taken shots
I bet he takes it a lot more personally than
We were like
Of course because Alex
He's ruining his
Ideas
Spy parroting that you know like he's the real s*** and Alex is becoming more popular at
This time yeah more popular him baby
I don't know exactly going like
Why is that kind of how I feel like why is it that b******* is good so much better than this
Better be getting attention than the truth
Welco's bills not really giving me
Truth Network
More right about something
And I'm completely wrong about other things
I mean from his perspective
Percy used to be a good-faith effort to get to the bottom of things
Yes is being kind of hurt
Actions
If I were bill I would think that Alex
He's going to f*** around and ruin everything she gives what he's trying to do a bad name right
Gives the public pretty face
A crazy person
Yelling into a bullhorn
When it snow
I'm actually sitting here reading thing
Conceivably doing the info part of Infowars
If you were sucking it
Yeah it's interesting I think they'll really hate it out
But anyway back to the call-in show
Bill gets another caller
And this is
Again as you pointed out
This show was labeled
Really good
Whatever you want
The airtime that I'm paying for somebody's working out there and I want
Girls talk about coconut
How to do
I don't
Furniture
Did you want to talk about that
I can do something about it
Broadcast East Ryan is trying to do radio broadcast
You call that one an hour I want all of his fans to call it'll be like
We're going to get this sorted out and then at the end the last 5 minutes and like
He's calling in to say like hey someone's jamming you and that there's a
Conspiracy fun angle
I'm not
This is not what this show is for
Probably some other problem even goes on to be like all right fine
Find get like a radio transmitter identification thing
And figure out where the jamming is coming from they reported
Are solar storms going on that's much more likely to be affected your radio that somebody jamming the signal
I bet he would love Carrie
I think that he starts to get a little bit
What to do about crazy jitneys getting tech support
Well it's unfortunate though because sometimes calls do come in like this next
Guy don't want to talk about something
What pill does not have time for it
Good evening I'm here
Doctor general
Are Newark listening to me
Listen to but you sure weren't listening
Are you don't have time or to even
One minute in the amount of time that you're going to be on the telephone
You need to go and
Listen to the mystery Babylon series on the internet that's why I put them in 40
3 hours
42 hours
God just
He's become the human Avatar of letmegooglethatforyou
You got to be disappointed
If you're him
She's really good so I do too
Disappointment
Padre two-time loser
But you got like
In bills defense
He did do it 43 parts.
That is true cover but
No I'm going
Going to do it
Either as a human or ghost we will
Coverall of bills mystery Babylon popular in hell
Yeah
Yeah yeah yeah
So at this point
The phone lines go little cold
Afraid
Builder
Sabila declaration
303 3345
Rubbermaid
The number
Guerneville City
Pause
So what's going on here to silence the reason that he's waiting for a caller is because there is no
There's a caller
Talking to no one can call in
Wait for a call or
Straight up and waiting for a call
On the bed music
Hello
Got to be disappointed
Grumpy Old Men go to bed no calls to because they're not
Are there because the chicken plucker
Is it this way of not cursing on Arrow though
He ends up causing a bit
Well obviously
Call me I guess you supposed to go to bed now but yeah
No
Diu doesn't up getting call pretty quickly after this is going to bed music
The guy was saying the Clinton could stay in office
Choosing the Vice President in these circumstances
And then a little mad at him
Hello
Turn the radio off
Read your car producing it's all there
Happy birthday
Easy-to-understand
Talk about it a million times on these broadcast you should have a copy of the Constitution if you are American
Will you do welcome to
Get out of here
You never had one to start with
503-334-5782 number
I could listen to grumpy old Don Rickles all day
Yep
Just a weird Patriot conspiracy theories to f****** fed up
Continue moron cuz what's great about it it's like
I want level
Bill's right
These colors are trash
I agree
You got to feel for it
Don't trifle with me god dammit
You kind of feel for but at the same time you can't be too mad cuz these are the people that he has called
So I don't know babe it's it's very conflicting but I would
I would absolutely listen to H & H
Bill just being like
Progressively more mad at his listeners
I would really like to know what probably some
Deep cut by the Beach Boys
I don't know
So those were things kind of turned around
There's a decent caller
And he has a question about photography for Bill
Lidl near me
Bertolotti
Probably best
Great if you have a birthday
Call Adam
Completely changed it totally different
Yep bill doesn't let the anger that he feels toward those other collars carry over into the next car
Individual
People still mad at the guy who lied to me about having a constitution
That's kind of nice that's a little bit ruin him for a day
The inverse color is the one who
Infuriate alexovich Montag left
Photography
You need a darkroom
Well in the same way
A human thing you like
This movie is excited to see vertical impact
You also have hobbies
It's like he had either fully drawn
Person like you someone who has yeah you know I love taking pictures
I'm in the dark room is like
And Bill gets to talking about how he has his own darkroom
Rihanna radio
It made rapper
Around here right now
Packer fomite
Darkrai
But very quickly now that the other room
Pregnant any prolonged
And all this stuff is going to come out of the dark room darker
For what
Video will be
Artistic
Creative interest outside of his conspiracy theories
It has to go a long way
In terms of dyke
Alex's interest outside of the
Drinking
Doing commercials for his product his staff
If there's anything like isn't paint
Doesn't doesn't write poetry or doesn't have anything that seems to be a passion outside
This
Twenty-something years like his entire career I don't know
Then cuz you can't call his documentaries anything other than
Slightly different extension of his show
Absolutely
It's interesting. Cuz of bills not taking pictures of
Fake documents
They're going to be like a landscape
Beautiful black and white
It's interesting
An interesting person
Chubbies
I'd like to find some of his
Prince
Yeah
Lakers
I feel like find the nearest pictures as much as Kanye West High School drawing
I imagine whoever would
Have them
Wooden Park
Iced it seems like
Yes we had a couple kids
Exactly how many
Because again
Another most interesting things
Yeah baby
I don't think they would part with him either remain bear
That call was a delight
Had a great time
Great-aunt
Good evening German
You look beautiful
You're welcome
Call
He is saying that the Mormon Church bought Pepsi
That's so different
From
Alex would have spun a simple question
Intuit
Oh nonsense all the way over here need
He'd not be like
Pepsi to be like
Mormon churches on all kinds of evil things throughout time in history
Maybe yeah instead bill just gives it a yes or no answer
Absolutely not
Conspiracy meth it was originally Pepsi and then later iteration
Comes up at work Oak back to the
Conceptions that Mormons can't drink caffeine
Answer the phone like hypocritical
Pepsi
What piece of it is like that apocracy argument and then the other pieces that the Church of Latter-day Saints does has like a 4
Prophet side of it they do have a lot of
Came out and actually had a list
Right of the firm the things that were invested in Google alphabet
Call Dad JPMorgan ton of like really big
Joseph Smith
Taken quite a bit off the top the Mormon church just has to
To keep that going
Absolutely I do think
Existing
Is a part of why those conspiracy is bubbled up these various companies
There was something
Untoward
Then and because of that and because of the like sort of
The intrinsic other nests of Mormon people in Patriots
Regular
Very staunch
Christian absolutist
Yeah
Conspiracies
Linger forever
Even to like fairly recent days
Do you get bored with all the s*** the Vatican
You know you got to find some other Church
To do some hypocritical bulshit
You know
Sometimes you just need a new flavor
Like a Coke or Pepsi
Jericho that is all
Yes so this next clip
The next caller
Is kind of a bummer is a little bit of a sad story this guy has he got attacked
Mm2 now no longer read
Can I do now that I can't read
Really interesting
Question and Bill
I think the bill respond as well as you can
I don't know I have a lot of feelings about this called
Okay
Gurdwara
What what is it that you want to do
I don't know
You know
Find somebody that can read for you
What is it that you want to do
Two other people
Wake them up
Okay
Stop playing around
Conversation
What's that
Panera menu
I remember
But make sure you know what you're talkin about
Don't spread rumors
Don't
I really don't think I would say don't spread rumors to a guy who can't read
Because of a
Yeah I mean it did
The situation is presenting is really sad
That's the most terrifying thing I can
Are you mad
Fine advice imagine it might be difficult
To find someone to read as much as you might want to read on your own
List of the bills to find out the truth and tell people doesn't that require reading it's what I was thinking while he
High-end audio books
Like nobody is
Doing an audiobook of
These lunatic Conspiracy Theory Book
Somebody I think he might be able to find some in some weird catalogs
Newsletters might have
Can do that you can listen to Bell whatever Bill tells him
Face value
Assume that's as good as reading
Right
That's a difficult thing and it's much longer
Skype for quite a while and
He gets around to being
Barely trying to be really encouraging about you can teach yourself things again
Yeah like you you can
I don't like because the guy does is not specific about what his injury was or anything I have no idea
The bill was just giving him a lot of like you
You can
Put your mind to it and work really hard
And you
Can read together
I don't know you even yourself
Inspirational and also
No
Just not
The inspirational Parts good but the actual advice that he's giving
It kind of is just
Repeat things you heard on my show
It is get a living reader or something
Is within the reach of most people
I guess if you're married maybe you could have your spouse review
Yeah latian Shipoopi
You take it too far and visit particularly interested
Yeah there better be a True Believer
Bitesquad Bill talks about his show from the night before
And I tried to find this but it's not on the website
So I don't I can't find what the actual show is
But you talked about it a little bit and apparently what he did
Is he played the same song over and over again
Like he was doing the music show
If I understand correctly the point you was trying to make is about how
We keep talking about the same thing with this election and no one's tired of talking about the same
Same thing
Play the same song
Artistically make that point or whatever
And he describes it in a way
That is maybe accurate
Directly about
Subway what would Bill me without hearing that I can't really accurately say
Closer to what might be described as satire just don't want to understand the show
Alex
I could easily see
Pinky
Albany liquor
What this colors describing is Bill lost his mind
Alex
Play that was a calculated
You didn't lose your mind you were specifically making a point through something that you think is absurd
And I'm not saying that I think that Alex a listen to that it misunderstood with that tire is it's just interest
That
One guy does understand satire
This is so wild because the the right
Criminally incapable of understanding what satire
It is simply not within their bow
And that
Bill Cooper is
Both
This this wacky
It's it's a complicated man I think Bill would be exiled from a lot of the right-wing to me
If you were still alive today
Cuz I was listening to a number of episodes from like
After 9/11
And like he was talking to Tom about how
Not doing it for no reason right they are there is a geopolitical reason why someone would commit a terrorist attack against
The United States
I just think he would have
President declared himself King
I think Bill Cooper hope
Would maintain some
Based on the way that I that we've seen him
It seems like he is a
Staunchly committed to his principles
And capable of accepting information
Which is
A rare thing
Also thought he was going to buy good now
That is true
He's a complicated man
Beat the thing that I always I always can't decipher and I probably never will be able to is that like
If Alex had died
Years ago you never would have thought you would join Trump eat
Yeah
It's not
It's not inconceivable that bill would change with the time someone
But he doesn't ever get any of the episodes that I've listened to
From his show he never seems to be
As
Chasing of anything as Alex is
Alex through almost all of this seems very desperate
He seems very much
Needing of
Something sure
The way he
Goes around with a bullhorn is early career trying to make spectacles of things like
That is desperate Behavior
I feel like there was more like
Things,
And even if they're just asking for text
Yeah
He's just
Annoyed is just annoyed
The issue with like
For the president electors are voting for the president of bills
Satire piece
Answer the colors like
Why you were talking about that you talked about that a lot
You talk about that
The issue number of times
Why why'd you talk about it
Adidas
How many times have I told people to get a copy of the Constitution
Very short written Motors anybody can understand
Got a copy of the Constitution
Tell me the bill has a keen awareness it is audiences not like they don't listen
That's fascinating I guess I guess if you suppose if you're dealing with any kind
Like
Ideals
Education
It has to be a
Near Lake Constance
Stream of people disappointing you
You know yeah yeah but you have to get over there pretty early your ass probably world
And you also have to have a lot of patience
Probably he does remind me of a like a social
Two studies teacher I had in junior high of just
Just like that
I've been doing this for thirty years you're not the first kid to ask me this
I am sick of
People telling me that the constitution says some s*** it doesn't f****** do your homework a******
You ready
You ready.
Yes
Guitar parts
Bullshiter
Yeah that's it
And get it does just keep coming back to More Humans
To understand
Listening to you without getting mad at
An individuals periodically based on the way they're interacting with you
But would like Alex hates his audio
Oh yeah to the point where he fears
Interacting with them is receiving multiple times
Then in his career
And I don't think Bill hates his audience
But you definitely hates
Some of these callers yeah oh yeah 100
You only hates or is mad at anybody because they're disappointed
Yeah they are not they're not
They're not living up to what he wants them to be
You're calling into my show
Don't b*******
That seems like a really simple thing to do
And Alex can't do it because he's entirely bulshit
Where is
Bill thinks that
He's the one who's telling the truth
Yeah that's it
Had a little bit of time on the show
The end of the show but are his called by saying that
You are the greatest
Be that as it may
Jezebel
Largest Revere that young our side
I hope I can meeting
Before I die
I think
Bill died like a year after this
It's kind of sad
That's a little bit of
I almost think that
It is like I'm imagining this and I think Bill Cooper would have
Listen to Greta thunberg speech at the UN adjust been like
God dammit I disagree with everything she said but
Way to take it to those assholes
Maybe a climate change
But
I don't know if you caught the
Very specific expression
That I use all the time
Be that as it may
Now we have as isn't there once and be that as it may
Episode
I worry I worry
Incarnation work
How old would they be right about
And were you secretly adopted favorably
Could you
I got to go talk to my dad
No I don't think I don't think
Texas
Lovin everybody
So it was like Skype
It's weird cuz you hear stuff about Hillary
On this episode
Wii U S
Bill is just leaving office in 2000
I forgot
Did Hillary ran for Senator in New York wow bill was still ending completely
I forgot that was the overlap
And so of course Hillary the subject at the comes up
Intuit building leaves
Okay will do
Hillary Clinton
Nobody told you about
Introduce
Remember
To do away with the Electoral College
Armoire
Heard
Elected president
Bill does not like democracy
That's pretty consistent with a lot of the right-wing
The tyranny of the majority
She didn't do that
And the irony
He could never have guessed is that
1816 years later
Had she have done that
That is very fun
Is that is that is a sad thought
It's very sad thought in all Hillary in 2000
Hillary loses the presidency because of the Electoral College
It is kind of ironic that it's
Doubly her fault that she lost
Alexa
The election in 2000 election for President
Another caller here who says
You want to talk about Al Gore
His daughter
Is married to someone from the shift family
And so he eat you speculate about how the shifts
The Rothschilds
And Bell has an interesting response
The best
Fortune
Where are 12 women
Lot of rumors
Wagner Alabama
I could find no verification
I'm talking about
The part where he grew up with The Rock
Directions pineapple no verification
So you never hear
Noah's Alex absolute
Rothschild
Right
There's a lot of rumors
I'm so interested I almost have no interest in what he does believe and I'm so much more interested in what he
Because Alex doesn't seem to reject anything other than Q which he's secretly loves and probably believes in or whatever it is most
But what he reject
Create this kind of series of boundaries that he'll act within as far as what
Conspiracy theories
Chooses to believer
And the boundaries are
A really fascinating
In comparison to Alex who doesn't seem to have any does Alex does have anything
Prolessa
It's Pro multiculturalism pro-feminist
Pro
Lgbtq
Is
Conceivably right wing
Cuz he's a he's a leader of the
Exactly he's absolutely the leader
I do I do agree with you cuz I don't agree necessarily that has no boundaries
Much weirder
You don't
Put up with you Doug leave does
Give
Like
Framework have to find out what you're not before you can really find out what you are and in Subway's
That's a sign of somebody who actually thinks they believe song
Yeah because Bill is willing to like no
You can't prove that I've looked at
He can't prove that right
That introduces a barrier
For like
His ability to go down fast
Wouldn't do that
That's another thing
I could find absolutely no evidence
Yeah it's not it's not his trademark a phrase
So
You know it's great
To hear things like
Best where Bill is saying like that the rumor you can't prove it
But at the same time
He also says stuff like that
Ain't no mistake about it I'll Gore is a dedicated
Marcos
His goal
WorldCom
God bless you too thank you for calling
So Al Gore's a dedicated Marxist
I'm trying to bring World communism
That rumor I can find no verification
That I've I've looked into
So it's a double-edged sword of like
He'll push back on some things that are brought to him it doesn't apply the same level of criticism towards the
Things that maybe he's already accepted
Improving
And like that creates a little bit of a problem
Last eclipse
Trying to
It's unclear exactly what he's trying to do but it seems like he's trying to say is that women should be allowed to
Cateechee bill
For the third time
Episode
Shut that s*** down
Serving other guard
Harvard
Call Greg
You will have
Broadcast message
Know that you are
Goodnight
God bless
Everything
Arlo
But I mean
Really good
That's a great answer
We don't allow preaching on the show although
You does
Absolutely
Not not the same way that Alex is still some
Some definite religious inclinations
Yeah I would be interested know if he
Crap
Bubbaques his belief in God seems to be sincere
Also seems kind of
Functional
Like there's a third sometimes expressing things are kind of go along the lines of like Pascal's wager
If you believe in God and he doesn't exist there's no
Eagleheart
Yeah and if you don't believe in God and He does exist
So why not just believe in him it no matter what it works out better
You have some
Mike
Things that I've heard him say that
Kind of going
Direction
And then the other thing
Is that he believes
That with
Audi existence of a deity
Creator endowed rights don't
Exist
And because of that
You know states can come in and Rule your life and that's why Communists want to get rid of religion
Because if they get rid of religion they get rid of the concept of Creator and outright
I think that he just has some sort of a belief
B fundamental rights can't exist outside of
Them being bestowed by a deity
At least in the episodes I've listened to it seems like a lot of his
Primerica primary interest in religion comes from
Those
Places
And I also don't hate that much I don't agree with them but I don't hate it that much
I mean that's the part about like being against communism
Directions home
Seems like an odd
It's not as bad as Alex's then
No it is
Like
And in a way it is a kind of functional thought process
In the sense that
If you believe that
There is a creator that gives you rights
That reinforces your superiority to the natural world
Otherwise we're all
You know
Like Tennyson you know where nature red in tooth and Claw
You know that kind of thing
So
Without that idea of Creator endowed rights
Or punishment for negative moral action
He probably believes
That people would just go insane and start killing each other all over
It's probably something along those
Maybe
Witches because there's no
Godsoe
You know in the same Pascal's wager
Why not
I mean I guess that would be the flip side
I don't know he's a he's a fascinating weirdo
Similar to Alex in a lot of ways and also
Similar
I think it's really interesting that at least three instances on this episode
Only an hour-long times within an hour of taking calls
I mean the first 15-20 minutes of the episode
He was able to have a caller who said something is sucks
Yeah
F*** that
That's good stuff
Yeah
And no
Indicates to
Complete lack of concern with
Turning this person off
They're not resources to him people who he wants
Get a message
Trite
And that's pretty
He's fundamentally different
Alex
Pretty clear that they're just people to Market
Yeah
Dollar signs in his eyes if he
Here's that its audience
Not like I've
I have greater reach to spread my message
None of that
And who knows if it might have been
Different earlier but certainly
None last year's I'm sure
The pursuit of money will kill
Whatever that
TJ
Thomas Jefferson paraphrase
Dave
Hit me up man I don't know this is this is an interesting little trip
I am glad to be able to know that I've made reference to bills call in shows
And then also how he
Cheetahs audience
Much differently than Alex does
I think it's
It's nice to take a little glimpse
At this ya
So there's this
I think the next time we dip it into Bell
We got it we got to be undertaken these bigger project
And I think
I want to do it
As much as I enjoy text
The court calls there's nothing really to research other than Ham radios
What did you need to look into that
Do
We'll see about that
I think I probably get to work on some of that stuff and so you can
Crank something out of the near future
Back on Friday maybe Alex will be back a platform dry Friday
It really honestly depends on if he's in studio tomorrow
I don't know
By will see
5 - 8 Jordan yes we are also on Facebook
We are always looking for that downloads
Local charity
I Love You Mio I am Bill Cooper's darkroom