I have great respect for knowledge b b
We are the bad guys
Acknowledge
Alex
IMDb
What are you up to today
I went through after our last episode of went through and I numbered all of our episode
Official episode numbers
For all of our back catalogue
I'll just something that I have not said I never thought it would I need to do the episodes
Named after the date of the episode isn't that good enough
Turns out
We jump around a bit so that I
It gets very confusing
Answer now it's the time has come and I feel really good about it I feel really good that we have a number
System
Although it's
Kind of sour grapes because I got to the end of it was an hours-long process of renaming episode
Mike wonder how many episodes we have
Take it to the end
The last episode we put out Wednesday's episode was episode 4
It was too late now we can't make that joke absolutely not
Episode were really mad about it
Episode of
Past 420 shows on Alex's show
Because I'm usually minutes
So it's all good
Also trying to figure out if any of our Milestone episodes episode 100
Any of those were like any Brett like major episode
Oh that's perfect
Let me know a ring
We didn't start
I didn't know how many we didn't
Until you just
Just told me that's
So I think in the future I might try like 4450
I might try to do something special for actually have numbers
Start to turn into an actual show
We're getting close
My bright spot is taking long walks
Taking long
Long walks just to keep my sanity
Love walking to like a Walgreens and not going
Just walking back
Just walking around to Walgreens
Hey man you got a cat.
Yeah it feels good
Good feels good I mean it's one of those things that I think that like
I remember playing football junior high
Worn out and I remember this very visceral Aba
Water tastes so good
I had that thought of going to look no it's not the water taste good in the state I'm in
That's how you are with walks right now
Exactly. The walk is that good
It's a huge ibidun today's metaphorically
Well that's good that is a bright spot and I'll I'd like to take a little bit more of
Walk myself but it's tough
That one nice thing is I walked a mile or so to get here everyday
Everyday that's fair
Coal mine that weird episodes episodes that are never worked
Just come over lyrics
Transporting show do first
Was poor for a while now I got those
Trump bucks thanks about your now policy walk
I'm a policy wonk for a while now I got those
Sonic Zachary think is about you and I'll probably walk
Exaggerating
Thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much you are now probably walk
Transformation
Thank you next
You nzar thank you so much you and I'll probably walk
How much
You are now a technocrat
And I thank you Dominic
You are now it's like a crack
Heroin
Why you pimps
Barge
Spirit
Go find
A local charity in your area that you can go help people in need we would appreciate that as well we would loved either
Spiritually the same to us
So if you're out there listen
You're probably thinking at this point
These dudes haven't talked about Alex Jones in a while
We had to do that with Alex cuz you
Getting out of pocket box reveal
That was the final straw for me really infuriating have much of a dumb dumbass holy is
But you are very bizarre twist
He ended up being out of Studio during the time that we were deplatforming him
Almost
The entire time
So I wanted to bring back Alex on when
Wednesday I didn't work out because Owen Shroyer was house
This episode this Friday episode
I was like what we got to get back to the business of looking at Alex he's had his time out
We got to do it
So I was going to go over Wednesday's episode of his show
Owen Shroyer hosting
Again
Now we record these the day before they come out
So Thursday
I texted you last night I told you
Word
Call Uncharted Territory ye might have to do something else
We're scrambling yes we don't know what is going to happen
And so I woke up this morning
Dappled around for a little bit
11:00 rolls around
Alex is back in studio he hates the returns
3 days later
Right around Easter
Not a coincidence
What's the opposite of thrilled
Anxiously regret to reply form Alex
Outdoor podcast
So we're going over April 6
16th 2020 abandoned
I'm and Hitman
Shows about what you'd expect
I've tried to eliminate as much of the just
Additive nonsense as I can
Deteriorating like even more so in front of our eyes and normal
We're be bad to talk about him
I think it's business is falling apart
And I think we'll see some quotes about that
As we go along
Let's start off here with Alex coverings
Some big news out of the Associated Press
You notice the big news
Receive documents confirms Wuhan was where the
Run
Early March
Has all been confirmed now
So there's a
25 second Clipper so interesting how many different
Things he's asserting in that tiny spam
What the first thing is that this AP story confirms that the coronavirus came out of you
Institute of virology lab
That is not spelled out at all story that Alex is referring to
On April 15th the AP released piece titled quote China didn't warn public of likely pandemic for 6 key
EBay's
It's mostly about how the Chinese government is likely aware of the situation be very severe but acting to downplay it public
In order to avoid panic
Until there was a clear case outside of China that is in Thailand
And then the situation
Drastically change that's wild to see a government actively downplay it and act like it's not that big a deal
It is so crazy that one government out there is doing
That singular one single government
Obviously I'm not going to defend any countries attempt to minimize Public Health crisis
See where further reporting investigation
On this delay in China brings up
Did see further reporting on that
Open
To learning more
However I think it's important to recognize that Alex can not use that article to bash China
Because all it's saying is that g did you know what he did is exactly what Alex is praising Trump for doing
Rumba
Other experts noted that the Chinese government may have
To Stave off Hysteria
And then it did
Quickly in private during that time
This is literally what Alex has said Trump did because he's an expert president or something
Alex has the Trump declared a secret emergency way back in the early days but downplayed the virus publicly because he didn't want to risk her
Stock market and he said that was
Great great idea
Love's about I guess article is no good for Alex
It does not work
The article about the virus originating in the Wuhan Institute of virology is not from the Associated Press
Who's put out as an exclusive by Fox News and was based entirely on Anonymous sources and
I have no ability to determine the veracity of the claim
However even take this article
Face value
It's important to recognize what the story on Fox News actually says
Here are a few Choice lines
From the article
Here's the opening paragraph
Quote
There's an increasing confidence
Flappy covid-19 outbreak likely originated in the Wuhan Laboratory
Do not as a bioweapon but is a part of China's attempt
To demonstrate that its efforts to identify a combat viruses are equal to or greater than the capabilities of the United States
Multiple sources who have been briefed on the details of early actions by China's government and seem relevant materials tail fox
News
Right out of the gate we have toothache
One is it this is not factual reporting
It's reporting a ink
Priest confer
That's not saying this is
The case figure is an increase confidence
We could mean any
Fox news reporting people feel a little bit better about this
Specific
The second thing is that even if
All of this is true
Definitely not a biome
Which runs counter to
All of Alex's narratives about the virus
A little later the article you get this line
Sources emphasized as is often the case with intelligent that it's not definitive and should not be care
Nice caveat then there's this line
Sources point to the structure of the virus and saying the genome mapping
Specifically shows it was not genetically alter
Most of this article it's actually read run
Counter to most of Alex's beliefs and rhetoric surrounding the Coronavirus
All that matches the perception that the headline promotes
Which is really all Alex trades in anyway
All the stuff you saying In that clip is based on his Fox news story but he's pretending
It's an AP article about them getting documents proven the virus came out of the Wuhan lab
Who is covering it up
Simply put that's a lie
Exact reality of Genesis the viruses that's a big will learn in the future
And the evidence that Alex has currently doesn't prove anything
He's with a rambling a-rollin
He's full of s***
We get to get to move along here and
You know
We got a I was just going to make sure that no one blames
That's right you really think a lot of people infected everybody should blame the guy who's at fault
Well you got it
So here's the thing if you're not going to blame Trump
So Alex is insisting that in order to
Must make sure
That we blame the UN
Predicted about a month ago
Hearing White House come out and say
Okay
Come out of the lab
Is going to come out and said yeah
You gave it to us
Really
By saying what you saying
But you and Kyra.
They're the ones that are guilty
But you must blame them
Warwick China
Wow
What
That sucks
Alright
Okay
You're all right I'm going to I'm going to say that I'm I'm altering our shelter in place order to
If you want to shelter in place
Annovera right-wing conservative
I don't know no no no no.
I don't know if I've ever heard someone say we need to take care of X for once and for all
Not men
Kill these do you need to take care of it once and for all means
Bringing up the
Rich the little bit higher that that's taken care of it
You have like a pretty consistent going on this
That is like we're already at War
Regina
I don't think there is a
Good outcome
To that sort of
It's
Seems like
Should
The people in charge
Country start picking up on this thread
We find ourselves in a not good geopolitical situation
Yeah and I can't help this is what Alex
Like it it seems like
He's the only person who's
Not only saying
We got to say we are already at War
Seems like he's pretty into it I mean can you imagine
If
Came out and
And said that this was a Chinese biome
And it was released in the United
I can't believe he would do that I could believe that he would be like and I guess
Like this is insane I can sadly
See
Something in one of his like weird briefing
But what I can't see is like what happens after
I have no idea what would happen
Now it's Kushner is Stephen Miller just send him like an Infowars article and he's like well obviously this is true
We are already at war with China and I didn't know about it
Obviously I need to tell the American people that we are at War
And I'm sure that everybody would take that fine
So if we get to Alex talking about How likely am for this
Coronavirus covid-19
And it's really just because they want to give you a vaccine for the common cold
Or something
It again is
This is weird
But what's really funny about this
Is that Alex Goes
He talks to people at the grocery store about
The vaccine for the common cold right like him
Newsreel bio-weapon
It is a real novel manufactured virus
Shows that the multinationals can
Vaccine for the common cold
Cold
Comical
Just stores
Well because there's so many thousands of mutations.
Well then how do they have one for this
This is ridiculous
I love it when
Like you just has all these random NPCs and is that they talk back to him in his own dialogue
Crazy checking me out obviously we were all still sitting in a hot tub
The same three globalist from several years ago he was even at the store could buy any other
Multiple stores
Have a cold
Not one of them said
I don't
Caravan go away
Yep
So
You know it in terms of
This whole thing
He's just saying that you know if you have the cold
You have any coal
And you die then your counted as a covid-19 death
And you relates this to other
Revisionist medical history let's say
Use what I would describe as maybe the worst citation I've ever heard
For medical information okay
A heart attack diabetes
Dying
Covid-19
They have
Cold virus in them
People
Getaround have any one time
Claim you had the HIV virus that's what did it
A little kid
Stop knowing
You're an adult now but in the medical community and you should be able to work for the government
Really
CIA
My dad did dental work
But
You're still a little kid saying that like it's ridiculous
So here's the situation I say
I see him working on a CIA guys.
Hey so I heard something about HIV that it was
Collection of Iris and then he's
Play confirmed it
Okay I guess that's true then I think I'm going to share that with my son who is 9
Make sure he knows the
So here it this is
Really important
This is such a good example of why Alex Jones is a pile of s*** and no one to take
Seriously
With or without looking into anything he says
Here he's making the claim that runs counter to pretty much
All well-accepted documented history
That HIV is actually a group of diseases that the man just cooked up
To cause a public health
It's pretty stupid for a number of reasons
41 beeves HIV epidemic was basically ignored for years by the government health age
If you did something at all the effect of gay people so they didn't really care this is not the response you expect from
Federal government if they had cooked up the disease to cause a public panic
Make sense
Even beyond that they never did rollout in HIV vaccine so that's supposed goal that I
I was imagining they had for this plan was never achieved
Which seems weird
If the problem reaction solution thing is true
The globalist cause problems in order to be able to provide a solution to the reaction the problem causes in the
Public
When you think they wouldn't introduce a problem they didn't have a solution to
This is kind of a big question mark and Alex is dumb Theory which he's too stupid even realizes there
Now passed all that stuff
This is the point that I want to make
How to make a claim that requires Evan
It's not something that you call Common Sense or widely accepted reality
Normally when a competent person would want to make a
The claim like that their evidence would be a study or body of literature
Possibly even just some highly credible person in the field whose work you could
Alex don't do that
What do you make this claim he tosses it off as definitive because his dad told him so as a child
That's a load of s***
And no one was trying to do a good job would ever think that was good enough
It also tells me that Alex has never looked into this issue at all because if he had he would have a better Citation for his conspiracy then
My super-cool CIA dentist father said so when I was a kid so it must be true
Even if that's where this information came from
If it were real
He could make this story sound like something an adult might say
Appealing to other actual sources
But he doesn't do that because he's bad at this
My dad says so
Yeah let's see I'm trying to think of all the things my dad said that didn't turn out to be true
That I that I don't
Still believe just because my dad said maybe you should you never as much fun
Credibility is this ding dong
He did say that jerking off will send you to hell and right now that is inconclusive for me so it's possible that would make
Maybe where is still out sometime before
Yeah I just stuff like that
Sucking dick
Supportive really like I really get frustrated by is
I don't give a s*** if his dad told him this when he was a kid like I don't think
Good or bad things about that
But the fact
That's his reference means he has nothing else
It's not because
That's the worst
Dad was a CIA dentist you don't need to look into things your dad says it's obviously I'll turn these in the jumper
Maybe flight beat that lease purchase Jason
So anyway
No
Globalist
Need to be taken care of once in awhile you need to wear a mask
And you should be wearing a mask
Not doing that because of any kind of
Concerns Republic
They're doing that
Because
They want to fight
Trump
Was trying to open the economy or something
So again still fairly repetitive but there's new little wrinkles like
Anger at masks that are popping up so there's that
Rollout and all of it is a scary and I hope so notice right
Economy
Democrats
Leave your house
Michigan
California
We have that from State Police in California
These State Police people in California actually went to Alex's dad for some dental work
That's how we learn we learn this stuff
CI
I don't
I don't know I don't have much of a thought about
Any of this other than just like
Alex
Enjoy
It's silly
It's silly that it's
Reactionary stupidity
Just on it like
I'm so sick of the Liberals being correct about the coronavirus killing people that I'm willing
To get people killed
That's it cuz they were on board with everybody like 2 or 3 weeks ago and it's like
But it feels like it was itching In Their Skin just
Like I don't like a
Green with the left I just don't wear jewelry with the left we got to do something there's some of that and then there's also some
It runs through it that's like
Everybody was saying these really high numbers and then now it's only in
And like the United States
Hey like you just playing this counterfactual game it's like
Yes those estimates were if we didn't do the things we're doing now
Announce refuses to accept any of that stuff and it's all the
Baba baba
Talked about this a million times like if
The actions you take work
People are going to pretend that there was
There's no problem in the first place exactly to keep from learning a lesson and the fascinating thing is I
I do recall a number of times people in public health position
Coming out and saying things like
The ultimate goal is to look like we overreacted like crazy at the end
The goal is to make it look like we didn't
Need to do all that stuff
Because that will mean
That we have made
This display out as smoothly as possible
And unfortunately even if you prepare people with that
Expectation like the goal is to look like we
F****** overreacting
It's still dumb
It doesn't matter it's be able to be used
There wasn't a problem to begin with Ryan
But the thing about overreacting like that and the thing that makes
Makes me so Furious
When people make that
Dumb argument
Like the numbers are
Is by overreacting as hard as we possibly can
We are going to save lives
That's
And if we overact solahart that would maybe that's two or three extra people who
Didn't need to die don't die
Like it's that
That kind of situation in because so many people have died there willing
To just take it as like
A good s***
I feel like I might of
Anon Twitter
What an idiot
Well
Bruno's right the right will believe it
TV personality over an expert no matter what
Yep
That's why we have our president
So Alex sediment last club that the virus is a hoax please play A Real Fine Line on it
Because he's not saying that it's all fake
But you know everything surrounding it is ratified
He has to make it very crystal clear
But this is real
People dying from this virus
Cold every year it is
If you look at the grass compared to other viruses
Very weak
Communicable
Think we're all bad we're all involved in the Hysteria
The new way of life
Which is a technocracy
So it's all souped up
Today at meeting with Sterling
It's souped-up located they gave it some Noss
Hold on to that idea compared to other viruses it's not really that bad because later the epi
Episode he's going
To follow this thread
And he's comparing it to the bubonic plague
Damn that was an issue for that
Plague outbreak
History
Not that bad I mean it turns out when you're only medicine is
Sense of smell and being like this doesn't this smells like plague
I'ma put on this mask with oils
Dislike
When you want to play a game where you compare this situation to smallpox
The plague
I don't know what point you're trying to
It's not as bad as malaria
That killed everybody right
You will try a little bit later
He's got to get mad
Bill Gates
This weekend instead
Yeah 700,000 people that bad side effects
You divide that into 7:07
So this is something that I was just taken from a highly and absurdly edited video of an interview Bill Gates
CNBC back on April 9th
This is crucially important to understand
I want to sing a Bill Gates came out that 700,000 people would get bad side effects
Strawberry covid-19 vaccine
A cover-up in text
Tens of Millions
Here's the actual clip from that interview that Alex is talking about
The Epic
Huge challenge
Isn't that it
Most benefit
Younger people not
Spreading
The racks
Community-based
Asus the elderly
Here
We clearly need it backs
That works
Rage rain
Because there
Most
At risk.
And
Doing that
A Apso
Older people and yet
You don't have
We have
1 + 10
Side effects
Way more
Thousand
People who will suffer
So
Really understanding the
Sapien
Chantix
Scale across all Lanes
Pregnant male female
Undernourished
IJustine comorbidities
It's very very hard and that
I'm okay let's go and
Give this back
To the entire world
Government
Be involved
There will be
Some
Riskin and demna
Needed
Before that can
Be decided on
Contacts it's very clear that Bill Gates has talked about the challenges
The cam was trying to produce an effective vaccine
The numbers that you chose was just arbitrary to describe the situation
Is not good
So what you have there is describing like this is
In terms of a large-scale rollout or something like that
Typically when people discuss challenges in the process
They are so just secretly indicate that they want to fail
Generally adults discussing difficulties in a process are doing so in order to
To give people a better understanding of what goes on in the work
And what considerations experts are trying to balance
Alex's either unable or unwilling to recognize surrounding context
Because that's surrounded context
Hertz the false narratives that he's trying to push
That's the entire game that's being played here and that's why if you go and find the video of this that he uses
It's like
Little tiny Cuts with Bill Gates
Same like
Vex the flu vaccine is not effective in elderly people
Okay hold on
To kill the elderly
Really it's really gross yeah
So anyways
It switches
Florida
Always
Why not
This is great
Is one of my favorites
So last week
Alex Warren
He was going to reveal qanon
He did not
No and it made me very mad
In the meantime he started
Talking to some qanon people and maybe
Sounding a lot like you and on the way
In the sex club Alex might as well be doing qanon
Cosplay
Waiting for an Awakening
But they need to have courage
Okay traitors in our government
They had us wear them
But we're resting all these people
They're going to get tried
Okay we're open for business again
Another war with China going to shut off economic operations with him
They want to watch other pilot Akron have to have a war with him
Because we're already there
Moving into invade Taiwan right now they've announced it
They're already wanted by would tackle the Deep state
The lab
I told you
Lacitycollege
I Know The Enemy folks
Another operation
Okay
The entire conception of the qanon world isn't there Patriots fighting the Deep state
Inside secretly
Msq fellow information
College degree
Great Awakening
So that the masses of enlightened people wouldn't be freaked out when the storm came
And Trump arrests all his deep State enemies
Stan Wright
Secret indictments
Alex and saying
Patriots
Who are fighting the Deep State need people like Alex
To disseminate this information
So the public won't freak out when Trump comes out and says I've arrested all the
Chinese secret agent
Flavor of the same cake
This is so laughable that Alex is so mad at you and all but seems to be
Completely playing the same game
What you're right
Also make no mistake about that
The only function of rhetoric like this
Sister preparing audience to accept an authoritarian ruler
All it does is recontextualizing power grabs Empower consolidation as the dear leader striking back against the evil
Who work in the shadows
So you come to love
Your new Ken
You know we're being trained to Not freak out when the executive of the federal government does things look a whole lot like the things
The Dictator
It's not something you would have expected Alex
Did you get to Butler
You know what I want
Is I want to
Demonizes
Certain section of the Publix
Specifically based on
Geography or race
In order to
Consolidate power and
That's never gone bad
I can't think of any situation
Qanon cosplay
Pure and simple
Only keeps it up because another big thing about the qanon mythology
Is Secret
All these secrets
A lie I'll explain that game 2
Quietly resting
Hundred hundreds of secret arrest
The Trump is doing against these Chinese communist
Whatever
That could not be more I'm not bragging
And then he brag
Yeah I'm not an authoritarian
So Alex is thrilled the Trump is secretly resting all these people and he's wearing his little cute hat and that's fun
Is not saying
To kill people
He needs to be very clear about this cuz it sounds like
The Logical extension of
Lot of things that he says
Should be like a go kill something
But he is not
Saying that
You think Trump should go kill people
Good
Kill anybody
Trump and the Pentagon
You know that
China's going to move into Taiwan before
The end-of-the-year probably sooner
I thought you said that they already
Moving into Taiwan
Yeah so Trump got to kill all the Chinese sub and whatever
Yeah I can't think of any situation where a leader of a cup
Of a country
Creating
What are essentially going to be death-squad
Preferably with black water is involved
Sure I can't say a surgery is already volunteered
In the past the globalist have done
Things
They're 10 years behind
They've done things
It gets worse
Sure whatever they do gets worse
Everything just keeps escalating to the point we're at now where they've released a bioweapon dates to get all over the world
To secretly murder people
Problem
What's after this
That is
This is worse than anything before
Right
Got to get worse
Walgreens McGee larger
You can say it's over for Humanity
Congress shouldn't be in session in the buildings
Should never be in d.c.
You're in a total war
The President should be moving around moving around
Permanent Air Force One Flight they can always be refueled in the in air and he just flies around the
Baby I do everything
Alex love so much
See this being like a situation that I like what Alex would like is like Trump is just a dictator from a bunker so much
Highly-technical safe bunker
Bouncy that's the best thing to do but
Cuz even if Trump dies you can just say that he's images of a hologram of a something
Start the unlock Dell Technologies
Tend to see leaves on forever it is secret immortality
Bunker
Steele's detect
Technology from the technocrats
That they already has her upload your brain into a computer
And that way he will always control thing but we know for him to use it and bad for them but we know that they do
Don't actually have that technology it's a trick
Right just want to kill you and tell you that
But secretly they
Do you have that
Technology they only say they don't have that
Technology in order to do what they want to do witches killed
Navigate to combine all of our world our world
Spaghetti
Tell me the Getty Museum
Now everything
Everything comes full circle
Alright whatever
So anyway we moving around the country
Just got a lot of things he's got to do them right
Sharax.
Alex
Thanks but there's some certain thing if he doesn't do right
She's going to hit the fan
You better be ready with guns and ammo if the president doesn't make the Right Moves and we go into a Civil War the globalist one
You got to be ready with the Patriot Governors and others
There's a war going on
Collaborator moron sabotage
You're stupid right now
F*****
Good China
Mattress your guns absolutely and let me tell you something funny
Jesus
That wasn't even like a Segway into an l
Thought of this
There's no other explanation for that is embedded
What is so deeply
Inexorable from his is content
Bucked up
Also I love the idea of original styles pavor
Like Coke Classic
Charles Manson just decided to sell food
I feel like we're being the very similar position
You claim to his payment processors
Do not allow him to accept credit cards anymore
Percent of checks or something
Wonderful I hope it's
I requested that we do an episode about that but I went to his archives and I don't know what episode
The most recent episode of David Horowitz
Sorry I will check in on him eventually but I'm not sitting through multiple episodes
Although is how much was bacon Studio might have had to
Well there's a lot of episode there's almost
So Alex gets back
Into yeah I was just some ads to go out
Who comes back
Gets down to business on some
Virus news
This is dumb
We told you that
P2015
Transferred the weapons to them
Mira
Hold
Virus
Kylie
Edible
With a nanotech game
Function
Viral miniaturization technology
Words words words words words
Somebody could be
Mutated rapidly
By the Tricom
Sure
Died
Navarro bloom
Would that be fed to
Fed the dog
The Creator
Zoological transfer
Hard-to-get species
With the new virus
I need a citation off because that doesn't
I think Alex just read a headline about a recent preliminary study the theorized
The dogs might have been an intermediary species between humans and bats
In the chain of the virus but honestly that study
Has been roundly rejected by scientist to have looked at it and said the
The data editor
Does not support the king
Conclusion
Is being offered
You know I looked into it too and
The virus did look exactly like
A lion with
Dragon wings and a tail of a score
So I think he might be right on the
Possible I'm just saying that there's a possibility
So the thing that he's talking about about the bats being fed to pigs showing
That's from a Daily Mail article about some research
So like there is then fed the dogs
This is the Genesis of the coronavirus is not
You can't available information doesn't
Sport that but
It the way you present to get makes
It sound like a child
He's doing is taking little disparate pieces of things
That aren't connected and then connect
Yeah
If we had
If we had a spider that
Write some pig
Are they wouldn't feed it to a piglet
That's just they would they would we would never have the
Probably
Is trying to really really stab Lachey
His credibility he's trying to go over like
We've been right about all this stuff over old headlines
Like really demonstrate
January 31st coronavirus contained Hy-Vee inserts and stuffing fears
Artificially created by 11 infowars.com zerohedge
University
University Gold
Boldy
China watch it on purpose
I was just making that stuff about the Indian University having
Funding threatened if they didn't retract a preliminary unpure reviewed study about the Coronavirus
This is just what he needs to believe because he can't possibly build the narratives that he's building if he has to concede that the research behind that
I didn't stand up to the scrutiny of other researchers
He can't deal with reality and keep his narrative so we have to make up his own story to explain why the study was retracted
But doesn't threaten the fiction
But he needs to use to sell this s***
Recently though is this claim that India is now saying the China release the virus on purpose
That's not true
However there is something real Alex is lying
Embarked remember the Indian Parliament named Manish tewari was posting around on social media
Release the virus asthma attack
This is disgusting an article in the South China Morning Post
About how India was seeing an uptick in
Conspiracy theory around the virus with bunch of a drifting into some
Fairly racist territory
If that was the case with tiwari's comments I'm not sure
But the larger picture of the missing
Information landscape in India was one of direct xenophobia and bigotry
I'm going to need a better reference
Send that but is out doesn't provide any so as a stand
Seems like as just another thing of Alex's fabricating
Because he's a liar
Yeah that does seem like a thing that Modi
Might think
Like in the same way that I'm sure buzza.
Who is
Actively trying to
To kill people
It's totally on
On that tip Maybe
But I don't see any
Announcements from the Indian government
Seems like it might be a little bit of a misrepresentation
Can or exaggeration
Norlyda
Like being so accurate
Even though he's
Not really but
I like being actually like this I don't like this
Me neither man
Yes
Have to go up against these people have the Democrat Party
Yes early
Trying to put me in prison by the scenes
They're not
And yeah I do think you'd want that everything about every everything I know about Alex
Believe
A war with something
Inconstant
Play like whether it's our own government or China you'll take whatever it is whatever manifestation of
Apple communist
Around in the Cold War make it hot
It's just Who You Are
This is the world you exist in
Well you would have said Megan hot if there was a Republican
He wants a big war
Trumpkin just essentially
What better way than War
With China to be like
I'm president for a while we're doing this thing and then we'll see what was in office
Cold War
Decided to attack Soviet Union
Directly
Yeah I think you would make peace with the
Paradise
Yeah
Anyway
There's some Misfortune in the Infowars world
And that is that one of the staff members Davis sister right
And her sister won't talk to them anymore
Good everybody works at Fox News shut up I assumed I assume there's more to the story
And I think he's making stuff up about this
This
Oh to be a family member who is exiled
Communicated a family member
Senior
This is Rob do
Walnut
Talk to him
Because he works here now
She hope she she paying
Worship CD
That sounds right
I remember
I think the beginning of this falling out because of the Boston Bomber
Because
Rob you lying about her brother or her husband
I don't know if it was just like from then on they hasn't talked
But I remember
It being a single they want
Turn Rob's phone call
Maybe they patch that relationship up. She was like
Hey now you work for a guy who's actively murdering people in Rob do is like
I know you want to
I would assume that Alex getting on air and saying that she worshipped
Probably not going to help the relationship to help him patch
Probably not I wonder if I'm being too hasty in my assumption that it's Rob do but I don't
18 years under the counter around a long time
Maybe there's a
Cameraman
I can't imagine
The turnover is hi there
Has probably been there that long I feel like he's been around for as long as
He's been our long-time user news director Alex have a sister
Yeah well
Is an adopted sister who I know he refers to Asbury and adoptive
She should not talk to him
Alex has
Felix about the director-general of the World Health Organization
And they're not good feeling
Is bad feeling
Weird that smart
The truth
AP report
New
The World Health Organization
Admitted
Bombings on Christian churches
Blow your charges up
The World Health Organization has plenty of room for criticism
And I think when we have the gift of hindsight it would be processed things were done
Find places where there's room for improvement on how International response in regards
Do International crises
The documents Alex's referring to have nothing to do with the World Health Organization
Cover-up of the virus
And this is honestly just the latest in the Trump quotes desperate attempt to divert attention from their dear leaders failing
To handle the situation responsibly back when I could have made a huge difference
I'm not particularly interested in this at this point however when there's more information in a clear picture I'm open to revisiting
The World Health Organization response
Stick fashion
For now all the stuff I can find it
Like this
Goes this direction
Is this clearly partisan attacks being used
Defend Trump
From well-deserved criticize
The thing I think about what
Anytime I
Is this was such an opportunity
4p
Like this was such an opportunity if I president had come out and been like
We know everybody's f***** up so here's what we're going to do we're going
Suspend all of this s*** and we're giving AIDS Iran giving a to all these people
Finally think we're not the shitbag that have blown them up for the past
20 years or whatever he's the sanction making it harder for them to
And then just be like hey will go bullfight Wars later there'll be a time for bickering and not mad
It would have been
Incredible how much events better than Al ship
That's too bad
So the leader or the head of the World Health Organization
It was a part of the cabinet
In Ethiopia
Is the Minister of Foreign Affairs
Previous to his position of the World Health Organization
He was in an Administration run by the eprdf
Or the Ethiopians people Ethiopian people's revolutionary Democratic front
This is a coalition of four different parties and is actually dissolved in
In 2019
Regardless it should be noted that the eprdf rose to power in Ethiopia in the early 90s and you know house
They Rose to power
The people's Democratic Republic of Ethiopia which was the communist-run state as it existed at the time was over
Throne
Because there were a coalition of four different parties it's kind of challenging to nail down the exact character of the eprdf
But it's a little reductive
Just call them
I know that's how Alex would see them so whatever
It's not really worth arguing but it doesn't deserve pointing out that this is an elementary level understanding
The politics is it go on in other countries
Whatever atrocities might have taken place during the Ethiopian Civil War the Eritrean War of Independence
It's pretty well accepted that I large
Number of them were carried out by the existing
Ethiopian government
The eprdf were against
It's not to minimize any of the things to do happen during Wars
But I don't
The tewodros was involved in in
Bobbing any churches
You know the the old quote is the tree of Liberty needs to be watered with Anna
Authoritarian military coup every
I need Alex to demonstrate his clients anyway seeing is in the late 80s and early 90s Tedros wasn't
College
Insurgent
He's never going to have any consequence
For them
Whatever
Nope
I think we'll be bad if he follows through with it
I don't know I don't know how anyone is going to stop
I wish that would be so great
Playing along with this
For the people to be ready
Amazing Drone footage
Dot-com
Lockdown
Projazz
So I mean I feel like this is just sort of a logical conclusion of
The anti-vax mindset
We're going to have mass demonstrations
It's unsafe to do so
I am your personifying fret in a way that's like
Really just a danger to everybody
Stupid
From Bill Gates
This is like
Young people getting the vaccine is going to help
Keep old
From getting it is less effective in the same way we're right here where it's like
If you guys just stop doing dumb s*** you're going to be better for the world and now you're doing this dumb s*** then you're going
Also like because of the reality of how dangerous
Mass Gatherings can be during this time
Like what you doing things like this
Only makes it more likely that you will see
The authoritarian Crackdown
The Optics of it that you are
Prophesying and so afraid of
It's just it's a self-perpetuating
Problem reaction
Solutions
So Alex
W
His enemies to be hanged
Particularly Ted Roos at the World Health Organization
Mid-level or whatever the world director-general nevermind
And then also she
Globalist openly trying to block now we are
Reopening
Corporations in Alliance blue states and cities
Direction
Will not open until the UN says so
Bio weapon released
Trying to get the Chinese into the country
Bio weapon
Alex
Is for regime-change
Get that man a plane right now get that man a plane so he can take care of this problem for
Thank you if we got a one-man Army really disappoint
Cleaning 80s action movie
Alex Jones First Blood Alex's sickness goes over to China tries to overthrow the
Communist Party
Is -2 thick
Lodges in that neck
Juggernaut there's nothing
Respect
A guy who has the balls
Come on air and be like
Golden saber shows
Alex
He comes back and realizes like
Really into
Discovering the news this episode
I've been so into covering a news
That there's news I haven't gotten to
And this is frustrating for him
Play Spit
Get into something that he's not been able to get into
Because it's been so busy with the
Ladies and gentlemen we are back live and I have been so hot and heavy on the news the news which I'll cover my comeback
Reviewers and severi semiotic messenger
Live right here off
It was important
Either that really offensive
Thought you so off guard plenty of plugin
I was at this place the moment
Said that I was like
Either this entire segment
Is going to be him rambling or this is an
There's no other he says I need to get to the news
That's the only
Situation where
They're back on sale
There's a reason for this
There's actually a revealed reason for why
Shipping times were so high why they needed to stop
Taking the waters
And we'll get to that when we get to it but for now
Alex is like
Go to any this food
And the reason is.
It might be time to bug out
We're going out I got the piece of property
Forgotten already
You know I knew was needed because I've been on so much on the offense I thought they were going to win this fight
But
I just can't be often during this
Able to have the full shutdown economy happening Beyond
Even our depression
Family
Bonkers
So for the first time ever in the last few weeks he got got some property together I'll wait was this
January 31st of this year
Father
The future
Outside
In 45 Acres with a
Saving food
I'm leaving empowered
It's all just b*******
He wants to
Express
What now
Is the time that this is getting serious
This is the time that I've had to make it
Talked about all this time
Either lying before or you're lying now in order to escalate the mood
I'm not sure what it is
But whatever it is
Call Marco
Some dishonest presentation
Oh yeah
I see an issue
Right
Okay
If it's time to bug out
Shipping times are 4 to 6
Do you see an issue here
Wake up wait about a month do you think he doesn't have a Dropship address
That's probably for you Alex
Total Civil War lawlessness total evil mutinous blockades of the West Indies dog run by
Solar eclipse started really interesting to me because
Middle of this plugged restorable dialysis drifting off into this whole thing about how he's gotten
Going outside of town because
That's just how serious things have gotten in the last few weeks
Talk show host
That's weird
Constantly talks about how he's a general
He's the first to hit the barbwire and they destroy him they destroy him
Doesn't seem like it is in his nature to
Be like hey you know sometimes it's time to evacuate I'm just a talk show host
Counter to the entire ethos
Valic suspect haven't you been listening
He's it look Infowars is the butt of the spear Destiny Pub in the behind
Branded the button every
This is so stupid
The whole like no retreat
Up against the globalists
Riverfront line
The f*** are you doing
It's not a retreat nothing is more Alex time to
There's a real problem
I have a doubt guys I'm at auction I mean billions of dollars off you all and I can afford
Doubt you can
Because
I have your money
Literally drink your milkshake
As I was hearing
Bulshit
Another thought struck
Alex hasn't been selling his ink on this episode
What mention
I wonder why you know what else not one mention of hydroxychloroquine
Horsepaste that the health Ranger was pushing
That's odd
Probably a coincidence right
I think so at the end of last week Alex got a very Stern warning letter from the FDA
Telling him in no uncertain terms that the way he was marketing his product
Was in a way that was close
Intended to mitigate prevent
Treat diagnose or cure covid-19 in people
I don't lie it only took them
Three weeks for them to
Into one of our episodes
This letter is very clear and it points out specific instances of Alex going past the line in a sales pitch
Andy Gibson 48 hours
To get in contact with him and describe quote
The specific steps you've taken
Correct these violation
Include an explanation of each step being taken to prevent the recurrence of violations
As well as copies of related documentation
Failure to immediately correct the violations cited in this letter may result in legal Act
Including without limitation
Seizure and injunction
This letter is explicit
Alex doesn't reach out to them and show how you correct
The FDA my f*** around and sees his product
Later in the letter they further say that failure to operate in line with the FTC Act
May result in legal action seeking a federal district court injunction
And an order may require that you pay back money to Costco
The FDA can make Alex refund all of the sales of his silver product and possibly others
He was found to be selling them inappropriately
Wheatley destroy his business
Hard now see
If if they were if they were fun people
Here's what would happen
They would have sent this exact letter
And then they were sent it
Email with a r drop
Saying it's time to pray
Now that would have been gold that would be nice
Maybe spiteful
So it's got to be a coincidence that he got that letter that he was gone from his show for 3 Days of the next week and then he comes back
Mysteriously using promoting is medically dubious products
Is yelling at everyone
It's not yelling about the hydroxychloroquine being the greatest thing in the world anymore
Weird
And instead he's
I would almost say angrily and petulant Lee threatened
Going to start a war with another country
Maybe because he's personally
You know that's not totally out of character for him
Screaming I would have Cody China and overthrow the government
And hangs easy Pig might be a little bit
Borax acid maybe a little
I have no idea what's actually going on behind the scenes I just think that these coincidences seem a little sis
Suspicious
The timing of these things
Right here Alex man sometimes you got to retreat just to talk show host I'm not going to be a general in this war
8 / 0
Against what
He's been
All about
It really makes me think like
He knows
You've.
I know that I've gotten that feeling on the number of times in the past
It's not been
Movie accurate or he's been able to Dukes of Hazzard his way out of there yet but like that to me seems like a guy who is
Giving up
It is hard to jump
The General Lee over the
A very big building
Yeah and one of the things that makes me think
They're like this is a little bit more sincere
Then other time
Is
He comes back
NFL
You're talking about this stuff
You seem to be like
Completely
Be freaking out
Broadcasting world
Country
Rope watch adults
South America
Ashley more positive
Nothing I'm doing
People don't know the times they're living you better hope this is some new drama thing you're doing
This is a dewdrop
Look I'm going to leave
And maybe I'll come back
Because I'm a professional talk show there is no there's no fighting spirit in the country
Translates to sales
Pissed off about it so I could go away maybe I'll come back if you buy thing
To exemplify the lack of fighting Spirit while you're
There's no fighting spirit in America anymore so I am going to leave
Concern
About this like a fighting spirit
He starts fake crying
About how I stupid people aren't
Now
You look how childlike and stupid people are everywhere
TV all day and they live in a fantasy land
And ensure people are in a sleep study
Not as over of a fake crying
Cracking his voice there for sure
Stupid people watching TV or stupid
They have reflected light from the TV in their eyes
I would suggest
That
95% of the things Alex references are TV shows and movies
I don't know
So Alex
Is that he's got a Play Special Report
You might come back
Might not
Minot intros the Special Report even to go to is just so f******
Three Little Pigs
Play Guster radio
Always Bagels
Eschew
No that's called
Doing is marketing two different people than the ones who listen
Go to watch
Myvideos old boy
Target Distortion issue it's like when you're listening to a comedy album and you can
Can totally see that there's a visual bit because you can hear everybody start laughing and you don't know why Yahoo
So you know that the
The comedian did something
There is an album
That is entirely that that's what he's about to play
More less yet but not an album
It's just a dumb Special Report
He wasn't gone for too long he does
They're cool his head or whatever and then he comes back
Of course he's coming back so he's got a kind of apologize for being a dick
By the way our shelter back live is awesome
Pray to God but you make me not be like this
Yesterday
Driving back from
An emergency
Terry Wright my family
Talk to the FDA
Add me on Facebook because
Morning resigned ever been
Wow
That's bad
Does he realize or four years into getting our country back and we still haven't gotten our country back in
Red Bank
I would say that when someone's like I'm not afraid but also I'm going to go hide out on a redoubt
It's getting conflicting messages
Keyboard going to my armor
Some people might do that side
I would say
Alex's
Afraid
Consequences
Who's ever had to face
Eastern
And it does still have to go
Court for various things
He has various lawsuits that are all still pending
Has the DUI situation
As far as I know still not fully resolved
What you got you got issues
So I mean I will be angry about that too
I don't think he wants
Any of that too
Come out on a hair
No I doubt
So that leaves him to have to get off here sometime come back and apologize
Because he doesn't want
Is essential staff to quit
Where is where is the latter part of Scott stapp's Bhai
Brim
So Alex can't handle this on his own
And so we get a return
Very long time
Is a steady hand
My study of a boring as s***
The hour
Videos
Uncle David
Cannot serve I would like to get the word oxymoron sounds
Only loaded with information and then
Pissed
That it's hard to even operate
I love that I love that idea
Alex is like
Told David Knight
To study less
Will you study these things you're fully why do
Bird
I don't I don't
I don't know
What I would call that
Call Beto y
Most generous description I would save that
Is a lack of focus yeah that could be a
If you have prepared for hours
Are fully ready to go make all your points
And then you're unable to because you get mad
That means your eyes are not on the prize in the game
You need to get
You need to get f***
Lansing Iowa
I've spent
4 hours writing up that report for you I really thought it was a good idea
And then I got so mad I lit Mike
Computer on fire are you going to
Do anything about that no consequences
School
He's boring as hell but
Little things that he brings up a typo
Strange
And one of them is you talkin about that gentleman via professor at Harvard Charles Lieber who got arrested
Lying about his involvement with the Chinese recruit
Program
And it's interesting I don't really care about a whole lot of the stuff the day of say
But David
Makes one claim and I
I think it's super important
Are they paid him a lot of money
Been arrested for
Espionage
I don't care to get into the nitty-gritty details about the Charles Lieber situation since we touched on a previous episode and from everything
I can tell it has nothing to do with
The coronavirus situation
I wanted to play that clip to demonstrate how everyone at Infowars plays fact games
Weber was not arrested
And charged with
According to a press release from the Department of Justice he was quoted arrested this morning and charged by criminal complaint with one count of May
Making a material materially false
Fictitious in fraudulent
Statement
There's a difference
It's an edge that dum-dums like Alex and David Knight like
Play Both Sides up
I can see this case I'm thinking the reason that Lieber made this false statement
Investigators
It's because he was doing something that he didn't want them to know about
That's the most likely explanation
It doesn't rise to the level of espionage
And she was charged with
Infowars
Venus piano situation so they just say that it is
Conversely consider the case of Rodger Stone
Some of the things he was charged with were lying to investigators
Obviously he was doing that to cover for something he didn't want them to know about but
That to be there situation there so in that case they pretended lying to investigators as a bulshit charge that's just how you
Jam someone like Rodger up
They wanted both ways because they don't operate in reality
This is a purely narrative advancing
Money-making operation
And little things like that really show how it's just something that's in the DNA of houses business runs
David Knight supposed to be too boring scholarly one around here
And here he is lying about what Charles Lieber was arrested and charged with because
It suits The Narrative better
Yeah well
Okay let's try this
Is a bulshit charge
In either Direct
So they charged him with lying to investigators
And that was because they couldn't
Charging for Espionage they don't have enough
It's for Espeon
And they charged Rodger stone with it
Because they don't have any evidence of anything
Espionage
We doing that
All of this bike is just
It's just trying to have cake and eat it as well
As we say
Another little tidbit of information that hasn't been brought into our sphere through Alex
Yet so let's let him bring this up
We just had an Israeli
Former General
How come out and say
Report this today
He said it doesn't matter what you do
What are you go
Draconian or you do nothing at all
For about 4 days at 7
40 days
It doesn't matter
Visible man named Isaac Ben-Israel who has recently come out
And every country
You can't just
Define shutting down economies because it won't make a difference
His comments and Analysis of received a whole lot of blowback ranging from
You don't understand epidemiology to
The localized data in places like New York and around Italy that seem to contradict your conclusion
From what I can tell this perspective is not one that's widely respected by anyone in the medical community nor anyone in public health world so
Perfect texture for Alex
Two sites yeah my response
Go fuc yourself
Get the f*** out
Him and viruses just it just for today is May what
Kind of dumb s*** does that
Viruses
They know
They've got 70 days if you need just know if you do nothing
At 70 days that's how long virus is live for right now
I don't know
They were saying that the Democrats want you to wear masks because they want to fight back against Trump trying to open the economy
Sure
You know what masks are also another way that Alex can open up an economy
We are already Rush Manufacturing
Infowars.com Mass
Also Rush manufacturing state covid-19 is
Open I'm going to go to local stores
Tucson time
Ridiculous
Subservient
Okay bye
Enjoy
Enjoy those publicity stunt videos you
Probably won't actually end up making
I would assume
Can I go to a store wearing
Jaguar mask
Although I will predict will follow through with covid is a hoax mask
Which is kind of message
Yeah he's jumping on the bag into
He's jumping on the bandwagon
Yeah
We get to where Alex
Brings up those other plagues
In order to minimize the current Coronavirus
The little weird
35 million
12 million
Look up here
5.6 million smallpox outbreak
Destiny
That one little area
19 right here
They got your whole universe
Zoomed into this
The whole universe
Couple of thoughts first Alex
I was going to say I thought that's what it was
Also one reasons to focus more on the
Current day situation then things that happened in the past is that
What are the death toll is from the plague outbreak
Edible
Play way back when
I really do anything about it
This is something
Minimize the amount of acid end up coming
You can make it so it's never gets
To the point where it's a plague of Justinian history
For sure you know what I think it might be
Is what if all of these plagues happen
And there were millions of people.
And then they were like
What if we built an organization
Specifically dedicated
You keeping this from happening
It's almost a really smart move
To do that would be some sort of an organization for like health
I think that would be a good place to start and then instead of millions of people.
What is dumbest people in
You don't have that
Again Alex is semen to not recognize
That like
A lot of those things have helped create
The medical state that we live in now
Medical advances
Necessity is the mother of invention
Exact that kind of thing I ever let us to the place we are now in the Renaissance
F****** do it
Goforit Alex blinders on and all you see is this
Well I mean yeah
It is historically relevant
Interesting to talk about
Outbreaks of the past
In terms of saying like
That one was so big that's this one's not even that big a deal
It's a dumb conversation I don't really even fully understand
The point he's trying to make
I have a difficult time figuring out what the next step of that is like the point is trying to make is when he's making
By accident
Which is people in the password dumb
And people who are telling us not to get
Another plague
Carsmart
And he doesn't like
What is a conclusion you could come too
So it's next clips really interesting
David nights there right
David Knight
Brings up hydroxychloroquine
Now and Alex throws a box
The tissue that is bae
This is really the only point in the episode where it comes up
An
The thing I think is really interesting is I think Alex moves off the topic pretty quick
Where is in the past I think you would have heard a bit more on the subject
And then Alex start plugging
Other products
I just talked about
Doctor
Who stopped
A nursing home from becoming another one of these hot
Washington
Hydroxychloroquine
50 some odd
4C
We got to go to come back
But I just want to chat list or something
Why are you pushing supplements
Wintersun
Percent off
Comedy
.
Closest
Percent off
He's probably sell that
Good clean
But usually really nice
Any trouble
See I feel like that
Different there was no red
What's the real feel like in the past when we heard
Things like stories about hydroxychloroquine being
Effective
And that's just like quinine is in tonic water everybody got to drink tonic water that today
Begin the military daggers
It's like
Something's changed
The way that he's like let's go to plug other thing
Yeah
Different
It's very obvious
And Alex is back
The plug
And it turns out
I believe it's in this clip but with the reality of what happened is
That the people weren't able to take as many orders
Because it was increased demand
But Alex said and all these other ding-dongs at artificially created
Increase demand in order to supply
What they needed to
My Patriot Supply open up of multiple other
Package
Who in the period when they were getting these up-and-running they weren't able to take as many orders
Now they have these up up and operating
So now they're back to like that for 26 weeks delivery went out
All the other Distributors are lying do you have the biggest we have the bat
Because the other places can't be proud
Going to do
Sales
And they are actually ahead of schedule
Admit your feelings if you orders we might be right on time
A child
46 weeks times 7
People want to know this doesn't matter
I talked to my boss he's got a really good deal for you told me
I don't know about that but I talked to the boss
I think you're going to be driving out of here in that.
Is my friend this is such used car dealership shed
I love it
I love it he's talked about how they're so trustworthy and that's how Alex operates cuz
The first thought I had was like
Diamond gusset jeans that's why they always deliver
Something for the home game gorilla
Yeah
Did the thing too is that
I wonder if this is a good move on there but these better be temporary facilities
Yeah because there will come a time when you will not need those extra Factory
I don't know what their business plan is
But that might be an overextend
I would think that the one lesson that
You should have learned by now.
Is that bubble
Mazar a bad
I went to said that before
Turns out this at the same time
You should ride the bubble
Keep these Assets in the form is like these extra Factory in when
Supply-demand returns to
So Alex
Wants you to know that you got to get this food
You got to get his yet
I also
They're hitting
That are about to kill
Wait what
Infowars
Corner very soon it's all about finances here
They are going to start wiping the Patriots out
You know I don't just say so for no reason
Flights right now
If you don't spread These Wings
You're aiding the oven
Wow
Oh boy oh boy
Aiding the enemy
Who are these hit teams
No they're just guys I don't have a secret agent Alex can't even remember that used to yell about antifa all the time
If he hasn't been in the news for
People are
Forgot
If you can't remember something that has he hasn't yelled about in a while
Cuz if you were smart that's what he would do if he likes a Soros isn't trying
Find a mix things up at rallies he needs or something
Ready to take out the Patriots at a moment's notice because I want to bring it there or communism
You know what you do you can't take that
Fake contract they have to sign a bill really put a little you have to spread the virus
Just edited in their fight might as well
Exoduspoint has Francis Boyle come in
And it's a 0
It's a snooze of an interview
They're quite pointless
It's mostly just sort of treading water rehashing all the stuff that they've already talked about
Almost the entire third hour of the show and like
I got to buy minute 40 something as like I have not found anything interesting
And anything that these dudes have been talk
So we're not going to really play anything except for because
Has been trying to downplay
The severity of the virus
Hey man it's not the
It's cold it's still a bioweapon but it's just a cold
Doubt the different Francis
Is bringing to the table
Republic
The Last Resort
Imperial assault or whatever they never got over here
Is here
Where we are right now
He's being presented as like one of them
Experts in the world on these sorts of issues
Who presented the big expert
15% of the United States population
From this virus which is
Very out of step with what Alex is
Did he did he listen to Alex's show a month ago to prepare for this one was on it
Yeah remember we were doing the show the Panic thing Alex come on
I'm playing it now come on
Canadian Winnipeg lab
Remove the law
So
Introduces
Difficult
To figure out
What the actual point is
Yeah I mean
These two completely
Conflicting things being presented as coming from credible
That's Tuff
But the important thing is
Batman
Well tell the truth
I love you all everybody
A different perspective
Gallium
You better get your firearm for self-defense of your storable food
Great supplements
The show with a little weird add pitch
But they also did so weird
I love you all girl being truthful
We got different ideas but we're going the right direction
You can't be all truthful
That's how they that's how the right operate
It doesn't matter what I say I'm
I'm telling the truth
Shorts in direct opposition to the guy I'm talking to
I think he's telling the truth
As well even though they're in direct opposition in
It's very disoriented
We reach the end of
The April 16th
Excursion
It's interesting to have Alex back but it's also like
I don't know how much longer this is going to go on
I don't I don't
C h w
His Caboose is running out of steam
Yeah you can only weasel your way out of Somme
Yeah you would think if you don't want to the other things really frustrating weird out of its frustrating but like
He goes away for a couple days
From the show
He comes back
And he's still doing that same thing he was doing before
Where you get so mad you can't do the shippo
Like that you would think a couple days off.
Maybe you come back at you still do
Real bad sign
And I don't know I very well could be making too much
Out of that
And those sorts of things but
What the FDA is expecting of him
Is not the same
As a cease-and-desist letter from the New York
Attorney General
They're very different
Expectations the very different things that can be done if Alex fails
Comply with the process
Like its
Seizure without limitation is a very scary things
To say refunds to all your customers
Like it
Very much
Like
It is
Is existentially threatened
If they follow through
And if Alex doesn't comply
Pink
There might be more behind
It this time
In terms of my feelings that like
Alex is preparing it
I got this
I'm the butt of the
You guys go fight the war highlight lost
Alarm for 1
Just sounds like a guys like
I'm done
I did it I did what I could
I prepared you not go
I got my money now going to get out
Yeah cuz if I keep going
Exactly
No it's the smartest
This is Ben
What how long
Almost a year the smartest thing that he could
Could do is stop
Wow
No
The smartest thing you could have done is stopped a while ago
Well the best thing you could have done is never started
Right
Tough
I don't know I guess I maybe my new catch phrases I hate to make prediction
Yeah because we're always
Identify this pills
Like
A guy
Start
His way out the door
For a bit
How much longer can you keep going like everything keeps
All this bad should keeps happening
And we can't pretend that it's
The globalist
They're just a consequences of his actions
Trump's ft I mean I guess you can call it the day
Trump is definitely not very anything
Apologies
Yeah that's the other thing too
If the FDA does follow through with this stuff
Tough time convincing
Stop.
There is a there is a very simple text that
To be sent
Look all you had to do is whine on TV and you get your name on a check
Man that operates he could win at the f
Ba and they do whatever it was
Yep so we'll see man I don't know I'm very interested
See what happens
Not from a Content perspective
But just from a like
Narrative art
Perspective
I'm going to be disappointed
It'll probably end up being blip on the radar whatever but
Who knows
We'll find out
I am a hero if we're going
I think the new normal does not in
Include Alex Jones today.
I would help
We'll see
But until then
Until we find out more
We travel websites knowledge.com
We are
City of your choice
The relative of Alex's employee who I'll talk to him anymore
Alex
I love your work