Air Jordan
Nola.com
I have great respect for its knowledge B
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Alex Jones
We are Dan or Danny Jordan
My bright spot is something it'll be a bright spot 2
For you to hear perhaps season
Listen to some music
Look that I've heard in a long time
Annie Lennox Annie Lennox
I don't know why but I listen to soundtrack
Good atmospheric music I enjoy the feeling soundtrack from the 1984 David Lynch film
Gather some
There's a little bit
But a little bit little bit of dialogue
Now I'm asking you this question
Do you know who did the soundtrack to do in it
The 1984 movie
Resume
No no
Warren Wilson
But the Brian Brian Brian Davie no I don't know
Always write a disorder but you know who else
The band Toto
Diva soundtrack the guys are brought you Rosanna and hold the line
Bring you the Doom soundtrack
What it what is closer to Africa been doing I think that's the only thing that makes sense anyway soundtrack
That was fun
I don't have time
Sting performances legendarily quiet
Start timer movie
Plenty of time for the soundtrack
Fair enough fair enough
Toto
Where are you I just did truth wanted with Daniel Earl's Adams
Actively Dan on Twitter is a great
Time is fun calling show
Yeah there's a podcast version of it you can download it was
Is great and a huge thank you to Dan for inviting me
So for anybody who wants more Jordan
Yeah go check that out
And I do work
Exclusively with
Actor bet the Only Rule I have now
If you are a Dan I will, go travel back in time and do some MTV remotes
Is Dan Cortese absolutely
How to dance
Dan Rather
Sure I'll do interviews with Dan Rather I not
And that now we are official
Jordans
Episode to go over doing a little look at
The present-day still we got April 17th 2020 of dances 2020
Just one moment
Before we do good things
Thank you so much you're now about to walk
I'm a policy wonk next Luna thank you so much
Very much Luna
Text Brian
Next ambient Kansas thank you so much
Text Candice Infinity thank you so much
Elevated level appreciate that very much
I don't think there's much you and I were technocrat Laura Jo thank you so much you are now a technocrat
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
Thank you so much Adam Mandalorian
Enjoy the show
Export these Gents
Website.com
Thinking about those workers show we would appreciate that if you'd like please feel free to take that energy and direct it to
Do a local charity in your area that's helping people who are affected
Goodbye the current trouble
We would appreciate
So Jordan like I said April 17th
It's going down
It is it is going down
I don't know how
Alex's just bought some b*******
The day before
It's on Thursday it came out that
A bunch of Infowars employees got kicked off
Yes and buy a bunch I mean Rob do
Andover Drive
Who got kicked off and
It's not about getting rid of
Exercising all Infowars a choice it has to do with the fact that the two of them Paul
And Owen were Act
Italy promoting
Is protest
Against
The quarantine
I actually
Did the protest
It was that they were using Twitter to spread promotion of it
16th to 17th
You just had some tendrils
Stop chopped off
Is getting his word out
So you know it is about what you do
Expecting that it's also not what you'd expect
The men also
Pretty f*****-up
So let's jump and here's the first clip Alex is talking
About course
Because
These people who work for him were kicked off social media
Obviously there's going to be some social media grievances on this episode
There had been draconians developments
Dreamed of just six months ago
Unfolded carry could this
Agree with you
Members of
The Congress
When they say that the coronavirus came out of the Wuhan lab
They're openly
Announcing that I got all the Articles right here
Strong suspicion that he's starting off this way so we can complain about Owen and Rob getting kicked off Twitter
But you would
You can count it
Coated in this language of universal censorship that's the way that he can get away with throwing a little while pretending
He's mad about something other than his employees losing their social media account
And their ability to Market on Twitter
Heady dinner
But he respects
And Robert Barr
Time to book on record and said they have no idea why Owens account was suspended but it's super clear
Like I said
In the days prior to the suspension
Promoting his
You can't close America rally which took place over this weekend
According to reporting on Media Matters Twitter had announced on March 18th
They were not allowing
Quote tweets that could place people at higher risk of transmitting covid
And if you think about it for any time at all
Using his account to promote a giant rally in the middle of an active pandemic
Is basically is clear and example that is you can come up
Now we'll Twitter apply that logic to Trump
Probably not
But even if their enforcement is less-than-ideal it's pretty indisputable that owners acting in ways that are directly counter to the rules
It had been established by Twitter
They took action when he was suspended
The same is true most likely dues account and like I said it's probably why David night Paul Joseph
Still up
Because they were too
Explicitly engaging in Behavior
Do directly lead to people putting themselves
A community at risk
I have no idea what Congress members Alex is talking about Sons
I can't find any stories about this even on his
Wheatley unnavigable website
But I would assume it's just a situation where they are subject to the rules of the platform as well as anybody else
50 faith and Twitter's commitment to upholding these
These rules and considering the trouble literally tweeted out multiple exhortation
For various states with Democratic Governors to be quote liberated
It's pretty clear the problem
It's far past
Anywhere any social media company can even handle it now
It's super clear what the messages does liberate
Starbucks
According to NBC News a spokesperson for Twitter said quote the use of liberate in the pizzas too vague to be at
Actionable
When the president of the country is on social media saying a liberate Minnesota and liberate Michigan and
Liberate Virginia and Saviour great second amendment is under siege
If your rules consider those statements be too vague to be actionable
The new rules are meaningless and really just sound more like
Cop out then anything else
Of course
Trump Twitter
Be good either and would also
Likely lead to a far more severe backlash particularly in an Alexa
There's essentially no good answer here the people in a position to actually make it
Decision like
To say that there is no reason they would ever suspend Trump or to apply the rules to him
Refuse to pick
The fear of the outcome
Whatever Alex wants to
Complain about his own personal problems
Still whatever he does that he has a tendency to externalize them
Exaggerate
When he got a DUI one of the first responses was to put on his Jonathan Swift
And suggested all restaurants should be closed cuz if you have one drink will get a DUI and then everyone's
Get jammed up
It was a massive societal issue that he was upset about
Not the fact that he drank and drove
And spent the night in jail
Is it the same thing
Is employees got punished on social media and Alex knows that having the lead stories like that
Hey my employees that sounds weak
Siri frame it is a story
You're not about to
It's not about your person
Interest
About the world you can portray yourself as a champion another week loser
Maybe I'm talking about this because they personally affected me and if it hadn't personally affected me I wouldn't give a s*** about that but this
Sisme I'm the butt of the spear dad
Yeah
So
This is this goes away out of control
You know I mean like it starts with this
This
Externalizing in in in exaggerating of
He's employees being suspended their couch
But this turns into like
A massive
Narrative on this show
About
The the who's doing
The dispensary
Exactly
Europe
Australia
Children
Do not try
Watch them carefully
Rapport
Them
China is behind the virus
That's good advice
Wuhan
The other side
Church
Bio weapon lab
Is number 2 in a man
So that's not true
Weapon Labs have like a social media division there or section division
We need to really do a better job as best we can of pushing back to something
Framing in the language calling it a bioweapon lab we just put up with
And just like whatever puts Move Along honestly that in itself is terrible
Idea
Yeah
Leaving that aside
The real story is that there's apparently someone who works for one of the groups that Facebook uses
For fact-checking
Anderson
Professor with many published articles on a field of virology and infectious diseases
He's a professor at Duke nus Medical School which is a collaboration between Duke
Any National University of Singapore
And the very legitimate and accredited
It's cool
Dinner time at the field of virology she's done some collaborative projects with the researchers
Happy Wuhan in
Do the virologia into the Wuhan lab running the fact-checking about the virus
Which just isn't accurate adult wow they are
They are really scraping the bottom of the barrel is it really going really not giving a f***
Expert who was consulted by an organization called health
Which is not owned by Facebook
If you was there an independent political entity that fact checks medical claim
Many of the outlets and abusing their work
The Source because it's solidly produced
Hope feedback is One Wing of a group called science feedback
They also have like climatefeedback.org organization
Scientists knock this s*** off their website include the section that lists all their donors from $5 donations up to 5000
Dollar Plus
List all the grants they received
As far as things that like this guy rarely seen this level of transparency from anything else I've looked at
Do you know Koch brothers folding I imagine that Mark Moreno works for them
Time to time like they really ever
What now absent from that page the money to be found
This relationship with Facebook that's where things get a little bit complicated
In April 2019 science feedback was approved as one of the entities that helps with Facebook's fact check
But it wasn't approved by face
Facebook as a pre-existing relationship with a group called
Pointers International fact-checking Network
Weaver is a group that approved the fact-checking entities which then helped fact-checked stuff on Facebook
If I had to guess
I would take this Arrangement exists so Facebook and talk as much
Responsibility as possible what happens on its platform is kind of like
100%
The reality is that there was an
Expert advice virologia infectious disease who teaches at University in Singapore who has worked at the wuhan.lab in the
She was consulted by Health feedback for a fact check on some claims that were made about
Lab in Wuhan
This story is not being changed by Alex into a situation where the fact-checking is being run out of the Wuhan lab would you can easily see you
Eli
Van if doctor Anderson were trying to obscure or hide her association with the lab in Wuhan
Probably make a pretty decent argument for some kind of conflict of interest Maybe
It might come off as a bit unethical to use her as a reference
But as it stands
She's completely open about her working at that lab periodically
I on some project
In the very article when she's consulted as an expert
Kind of gives
More Credence to her that like that's why you would go to her because she's actually
F****** been there
Relationship
Of her feedback
Slippers elf
Yeah
There's no indication that she runs it
Write any of that stuff
But just choose someone who was consulted by these people for a fact check
Take over as Alex's number one narrative
But there's some things that I get lost
Along the way gets a little sidetracked on
Because you seen 84
For these guys is a
Patience
My favorite books
Manual
Start
Directly into your face
For how much
Get to the point here I should say that's what you was heard there was Alex making a real big show out of drinking from a paper cut button
Swirling the ice around
Which is not exactly what I would call in character for him
I see them pics wigs everything seemed like
Give coffee mug and sometimes you'll have bottles like Topo Chico on hand but this is
Very showy
Taunton and it worries me a little bit boy
No idea Facebook
I have no idea
But if it is
We are three minutes into the episode at this point
That would spell trouble
That's called the beginning of the work
And it's when you take your first drink
I'm not convinced
Necessarily from the way this episode Ghost
But he was drink
I'm not I'm not sure
Is it possible but I'm not I'm not I'm not sold on
He does get real weird by the end of the episode but it's not like
It's not definitive in the same way that so many of these others
Yesterday clip first of all Hillary was not co-president
That's just nonsense
Second
Alex isn't talking about comments Hillary made back in the 90s and she didn't say 1984 was a how-to manual
That's just a stupid headline that French
Conservative blogs ran with when discussing an excerpt from her 2017 book titled what happened
In the book's you rights quotes
Attempting to Define reality is a core feature of authoritarian
This is what the Soviets did when they erased political distance from historical photos
This is what happens in George Orwell's classic novel 1984
When a torturer holds up four fingers and delivers electric shocks until his prisoner sees five
Fingers as order
The goal is to make you question logic and reason I just don't mistrust towards exactly the people we need to rely on
Our leaders the Press
Expert usikiaye public policy based on evidence
Ourselves
For Trump is as with so much as he does
It's about simple dominant
Alex is making up a Hillary quote and here's the fun part
I know exactly where it comes from
There was an article in
2017 about this passage from Hillary's book
On the website
Conservative review
And the headline is quote
Hillary Clinton thinks Orwell's 1984 is a how-to manual
I really don't get where they saw that in the quote
No it's not it's not in that quote and that's where Alex got the idea from
In the article if you actually read it it doesn't include any quotes for saying that it's just the insinuation of the author of this blog post
He's grape is that he feels that Hillary got the wrong message from 1984 and that her point was to encourage blind
Trust in the government and media
I think that's a little bit of an unfair reading from the text
Particularly considering the last thing in her list of people we need to rely on ourselves
But whatever
I'm not going to spend my time discussing
Circle in any way passing
But this headline is absolutely where Alex
Something is imaginary Hillary quote from
He is me either
Not read this article at all or he's willfully lying about it one of the two
You know what's it what what is interesting is that in a sense
I agree with the Sun
1984 is a how-to manual
I just think Trump is using it not the other guy
Emmanuel could be in
Some context of value neutral site
The terrorists like that is not to say that George Washington was a evil there red right
I'm not I don't want to I don't want to unpack that right now but
There are ways you can
Don't say something like 94 is a how-to manual without endorsing
That's all fine that's all good well even if Hillary had said something like that
She didn't f****** conservative review blog post headline
Don't they have to not read them in order to maintain their their strength
Like Samson like if they read a book then they lose their power can only read anran
If you're weird
Mariscos
So Alex believes that
The AP
Has reported
That the virus came from the Wuhan lab
They wish they end
The Danielle Anderson
Working the from the Wuhan lab
Is Banning stories from the AP that demonstrate
It's it's a whole mess but that's how Alex gets around forming
Narrative
The Associated Press
Reported two days ago
New the virus came from the Wuhan lab
Knew it was weaponized
Knew it was
Spreading
Flights from China
You're a xenophobe
Will not be allowed to be shared
Platform
Anyone sharing the article
Will be bad
He doesn't
Again this is just Alex misreporting the same AP story that suggested that the Chinese government knew that the virus was more serious
The situation then they admitted publicly for 6 days
Between January 14th of January 20th
The rest of the stuff relating to the Wuhan lab is it just stuff I like reading a Fox news headline he's trying to disguise it as an AP story
Because even he knows that AP stories are far more credible
Then Fox News Post citing Anonymous sources that are full of caveat like none of this is certain
Absolutely
Alex wants the audience to think of the mainstream media is reporting on
On the same stuff used covering
Because he knows
But even amongst the most strident
Conspiracy theorist
Ignition that real journalist to do different work
And people like Alex
Is Alex says something maybe you'll believe it
But if the AP report something that you know they can back it up
This is a fascinating dichotomy of the paranoid
Conspiracy world
They hate the mainstream media and yet constantly appeal to it to give themselves credibility
When they think they can
Alex brother wants the audience
To think that this totally legit Outlet is reporting US News
And censorship has gotten so out of control that if you even post this AP story you'll get banned
This is the primary function of rewriting his own band
Some social media platform
Because only the only kick them off cuz they knew we was right about all this stuff and even now the AP saying
None of this is real
Go to the ramblings of a liar circling the drain desperately flailing for anything to grab onto in hopes of saving the ship
They going to work media Outlets that reliance
Entirely upon expediency
Not good
No
But you know what's really funny
Trash
But Alex is so cocky about it
I really love
Like you really like is acting like a f****** nailed it
These people
Science division runs
You can say about
Vitamin D
Chloroquine
One of the top
Real cocky
Two scientist
At the woohoo
I don't know
She's one of the top Subs
I would need I would need further information on that
It looks like I forgot to cut out this clip
But Alex is also claiming one of his other big pieces of evidence
Is that the code
Discoverer of HIV
Has come out and said that
Alex is using headlines say that he saying this was definitely
100% made in a lab
And that's not
Like super activity list
Who is the coach cover of hiv-1 Nobel Prize in 2008
He came out when an interview and basically said that if there were HIV pieces inserted as the RNA of the virus
Then that would that would not have evolve naturally and it would require lab engineering
This is all good while but as far as I can tell no one is in any way demonstrated that there are hiv-positive been inserted into
To the Coronavirus
The only reference people can make on that is that unpure reviewtube retracted Indian study
Which was seriously flawed
A follow-up paper published in February 2020 in the journal emerging microbes and infection
Look at these inserts that were said to be HIV and found
Quote all results demonstrated no evidence
The sequences of these for inserts
Are hiv-1 specific
Or the Northeast 2019-novel coronavirus virus has obtained these insurgents from
Hiv-1
First the result of the blast search of these motifs against gym bag shows the
Top 100
Identical or highly homologous
Are all from host genes of mammalian insects bacterial and others
These other fees for inserts that are said in the Indian study to be hiv-related
Have a ton of other non-hiv sources
Further these. These insertion
Are also present in multiple other Coronavirus
So the conclusions reached by the Indian paperwork definitely hasty
At least
So basically what you have there is Doctor Montage making an if-then state
If the virus has HIV sewn into it then it must have been done in the lab
That's probably fine but I just
Beauty if portion
In logic when you have an if-then statement and the premise is false
You can completely ignore the conclusion
It legitimately doesn't matter with the conclusion
Right because there's no truth
Reserved through the process of inference
Also this dude is theorize and got the lab in Wuhan was working on an HIV vaccine
And this leaked out which is not really in line with Alex's bio-weapon there it is but whatever
Alex will run with whatever he
Some credibility with the dumb s***
Also
I don't think that Alex should be able to use these guys like
Guy who coached Stanford hiv-2 some kind of by proxy expert
Seeing as he doesn't believe HIV is real
Nor does he believe it is connected to 8
Kind of Festival leave that Luke Montage yay
Have to be in on the conspiracy right
I mean that's how you know he's telling the truth
Because he's lying
Can't have it both ways but I look really wants to
You can't trust this guy and John Rappaport
Just Dance
You can't
I can't have it both way
The right-wing exist outside of both ways they have it always
All they do is hold us hostage with their lives
That's it
Important to point that out a little bit
So not only
Is this person who heads up the Wuhan lab
Track checking Facebook
Friend
Man
Fake Facebook is really
I got to say
If their staff
Might be a problem
The things that Alex is saying
German police that were worse than
Yeah
Thousand of them
What
So
That's the wild year old dude
10080 year old dude working for Facebook so just be clear most of the people who'll be the right age
Anastasio
Pretty
I would imagine you'd be hard-pressed to find 10,000 Stasi members still alive today let alone 10011 where the kind of shape you
I need to be in to Riley modern
Accompany
Inside haven't seen Lisa
What is enjoying
Leaving aside how stupid that is
It's based on what you might call a colonel of
Something real
In 2050
Tienda Justice Ministry in Germany
Established
Task force
Look into online hate speech particularly directed towards Hemet
The goal was to get a sense of the scale of the problem which they would then use to encourage Facebook and Twitter to take the matter series
What are the groups that was included in this ngoie was an NGO called the Amadou Antonio
Foundation
Named in memory of an angolan immigrant killed by neo-nazis briefly after the reunification
Germany
The group's chairwoman is an etiquette on who is he
What you was a college student
Burger Time
She was an unofficial informed
For the Stasi
I can't really defend that except to say that I see no indication that she's been dishonest about that part of her past
Incenta around 1982 what you stop being an informant her career
Kind of speaks for itself
In September 2015 Paul Joseph Watson wrote a really misleading article about this task force
Tending to imply that is a body within Facebook
As opposed to a German HD studying the issue and able to advise Facebook
August Pohl credit that in the body of his article he does say that Kane was a informant
But I'm going to take that credit right back
Because the headline quote extazy agent hired to censor xenophobic Facebook post
The informant
Recognition 1 Turnbull Road
Personally hired by. Yay
Anyway this is where Alex's Facebook is hiring the Stasi narrative comes from it was one person who doesn't work for Facebook
Has now been exaggerated into Facebook being run by 10,000 Stasi members they fired
Disguising amazing liar have to be pretty f****** dumb to buy things like this and he said I can't imagine
Look
If you said like
Four former Stasi
Maybe maybe I'll be like
I mean that you and you don't have to be up with the modern technology you could direct things you could people could bring you stuff
Emails for you but 10,000
Stasi
This is all really just
Probably an issue for Alex because Connie's advocacy is surrounding the rising right-wing
Extremism and their education towards immigrant
Communities
And you know who makes money off that
Oh no I wait
Alex oh my God why would he choose her
Anime
Stasi deep-dish Facebook
Great
Give me 5 News
Give me five star
But it's not just
These 10000 Stasi agent Facebook
Security
I can legitimately find no articles on this that don't trace back to Infowars or prison
True so true
Too true for the rest of the world even
According to a 2004 story that's now mysteriously gone from their website so it's still on the way back now
Machine Paul Joseph Watson Road about how political analyst named almartin
It alleged that Homeland Security and hired Marcus wolf
There's no
Substantiation of this claim in the article outside of this
Quote sources close to Martin have told Alex Jones confidentially that the appointment of wolf was also
Confirmed by us congressman
How many different levels of not
Talking to anybody that
That's a tell for me that this is b*******
Also Marcus wolf wasn't the head of the Stasi
He was ahead of the main directorate for reconnaissance
The foreign intelligence wing
The Stasi
A2000
For when this would have happened he was
81 years old
And I can find absolutely zero concrete evidence
It's that he was employed by US Navy
National Security
Or I mean you could say that
Right I tried to figure out who almartin
Since he's the only real source
But this traces back to and to say I was not surprised by what I found
He has a long-dormant website called almartin Draw
Where he would write blog
But what interested me the most was that he wrote a book called quote
Shocking secrets of Iran Contra
Albert is yet another guy who's claimed he was in on Iran Contra
Look if you want to talk about that guy do you know who you guys hired to run the NRA what are you people talking about
This guy is also involved in Iran-Contra
80% of these ambitious right-wing type claim they were mixed up in a wrong contro it's kind of strains my ability to believe
Most of them
To Martin's credit though he calls himself a quote fourth level player in the the affair
Whatever the f*** that mean
At least he's not like Iran it that Larry Nichols is like I was hanging out with
Either way I don't believe any of this until they can provide a little better evidence in this week's yet
Also just a small Point even if all of that is true that happened in 2000
For when there was not a democratic Administration in charge of Homeland Security and both houses of Congress were control
Go by the Republican Party
I've literally zero idea how the Democrats could have hired the head of the Stasi to be involved in Homeland Security.
Sweet gop-controlled of all the parts
The Federal
But I guess that's why Alex makes a big bucks he can imagine that
Through from the entire
World next order that f****** head of it
The Stasi whatever
Get away with that that might be the only thing they
They could sneak through with the right-wing running things in 2004 just like
Do you guys want to hire next agent for us to work with
Hell yeah
Yeah
So Alex
In his next Club he's he's talking about he's going to really get down to business
Really get down
And as far as I can tell from listening to the rest of this episode the only thing
He has to get down to is more yelling about the Facebook censorship
Checkers
Story seems to be the only thing he has to get down to
Get down to business
All right now
Play it all out
Write a layout to the present
Add to the Pentagon everybody about the choices we all have to make right now
I know
Play it out as well to your husband your wife your neighbors your church
Ulster County the United States
Okay
Alright so I am anxiously awaiting him laying this all out I just got 10 pages of
Of all the stuff prepared notes has been working on this for years
Sounds like I'm so f****** ready to do this
I'll do it later
Also by the way the you getting yelled at for not wearing a stupid f****** mask
You sell mask Dallas
Pick a lane
Galaxy S10
So anyway Alex
Complains
About the Wuhan
How are the lab right there running the Facebook fact-checkers
Course and
Steps to worry about life
Don't do something about
Still why
Wuhan bioweapons lab of the Chinese operatives running Facebook
Blocking
Is the president an incremental trance
I'm listening
What do you
You know what
You can't handle the truth
So yeah is its conclusion is the Trump pics if you can't handle the truth
I-90 we go back to him being poisoned with his Diet Cokes
Is there a woman that was fun
Also like
I just don't get
Why you want to continue supporting a leader who you have to question if they're in a trance or evil
Like that doesn't seem like the sort of person you want to get the high
Is it possible for us to find a candidate from either party that couldn't have that question asked
It's a constant thing for Alex
You simultaneously always sure the Trump is the greatest and then also like I might be going to
Bobby going to kill us okay
So he's my guy
I want him to be an authoritarian leader
But at the same time
He's not doing anything that I want him to do which is why he's
He's my guy
So how is it that I
I can continue to support him if he doesn't do anything I wanted to do special
If I'm giving him all of this power
Plan don't care
I'll just yell
So Alex gets into some like sort of virus
Conspiracies here and
He's really leaning towards I calling everything a scam and fraud
Fraud
Not true
They're not counting anybody new in the last 2 months. Of the flu they always take
So he's just making things up there if you go to the cdc's website you can find plenty of information about the 2019 2020 floozies
And there were plenty of influenza related deaths that have happened that have not been double-counted
That is Coronavirus death
There's a little truth with our two saying though
It is true that as of April 4th the cdc's website will not be posting updated flu season burden
But that isn't because there's some kind of a cover-up
Because flu season is mostly over
Any updates would be kind of irrelevant
States are continuing to collect their data which will be used to update or revise the cdc's numbers after the fact but given the flu season
Has crested
The cdc's role in this is ended for now
Almost certainly Alex just a headline that the CDC was going
GameStop releasing revised estimates about the flu season sometime
After this April 4th data came out he's just completely unaware of what he's talking about or wilfully line
About it if you want to find out information about the flu season all you do is look for it
It's pretty
Available
But I wasn't interested information
He wants to pretend that the coronavirus deaths are all secretly just flu deaths being passed off as something else of the globalist
Grab power
You should recognize that he if he's wrong about what he saying
Which is
He stamps be personally responsible for the deaths of people who look up to him as a voice
Guidance
I really hope it is
Ready and prepared
To handle that kind of spiritual weight
Cuz that is
Going to be
Devastating
If you ever have to look in the mirror about that it would be devastating to
Non-sag
I just don't think
Man I just don't
Think they have it you better be ready
For that to be a lifelong commitment psychopath that goes like
That's how you become the president
You ever
Have a Moment of clarity and it will destroy you
You know
If if it were possible for somebody like Trump we wouldn't
Be where we are but I could watch
People die in front of him and
Not give a s***
I don't know if Alex is that
Purely psychosomatic
So Alex
Complaining about Bill Gates
Apparently Bill Gates Wants to Rule the World
To know that
Empower
Intelligence
Sure why not
Knowing who the players are in
Terror
Bill Gates
President of the world
So Alex has presented the Bill Gates wants
Take over the world
Now
What
This next clip
Part 2
Pentagon
Alex
Every move and how they operate what they're going to do next
About this
Sounds like you are
Pentagon intelligence agencies in the White House
Because
We're not naive
So you got up this is the part 1 and part 2
Part 1
Bill Gates going to try and take over the world
Park to the White House
The Pentagon there in all of Alec
That's interesting manually put those all together
Elsa's the middle of this weird rant about how evil
Vaccines are and how Bill Gates could take over the world
Nefarious vaccine
Substandard Infowars bulshit
However this Rises to amazing comedy
When you talk about
Being in all of Alex's why doesn't
And that's because Trump say to this
In his coronavirus briefing on April 17th the same damn day is this episode
Is today the FDA in
A new collaboration
The Gatesville
Us cotton
To greatly expand
The supply of a sin
Schwab's including
Polyester
Q-tip types
Schwab
For the
Coronavirus test
All of these acts
It will help us
Incapability
Need to grow
Oh what's that Trump announcing a collaboration between the FDA The Gates Foundation helping
He's closer than doesn't sound like something a guy who thinks Bill Gates is evil demon
Set up to take over the world
Maybe he is in many ways I am also of Alex's dumb bulshit
Just because
It really does seem to never stop it just doesn't seem to stop at the
Old Faithful
You make a good point
In all could be another value neutral statement
Could meet a couple different things
So at this point Alex
Takes on another theme
Videos throughout the show that is like he's getting real close
Stooges
Straight up advocating
Literal War
Is what I'm saying screw we have to go to war
People at the local level the international level
We're at War
Chinese Chinese
Censorship in the US
They're expecting you to not seeing what this really is and deal with it
Only by full commitment
We can annihilate them now
So we're getting much
Closer to Alex
Directly you saying we've got to have a World War
But it's also a local War 2 it's a Civil War and World War simultaneously which
For that sucks you know what if I were reading 1984 as a how to Mandy
It suggests convincing everybody in a certain group
That they are constantly and eternally at war with everybody in another group
That's interesting
Sounds like Hillary break with this talk of like
If Trump comes out
And says the truth that I know if I'm right about this stuff then we're at War
By okay
You should be talking like
Like this is
This is so irresponsible and comes back
A man he is just rambling
About how like I will be destroyed but by destruction will be the true destruction of my enemies
Exactly how you
Blasphemy
Basically
Cornea
Everything
Things me Reborn
Women friends
That's the good guy
You're right
World government
Year
Academy
And those it lots of stand against it
Discrimination will be
The temple
So blinded and tortured
Predicted Indiana.
He misses that music
Yeah
That was really helping about
These are the times that try men's Souls
I can tell you at this point
I can't do the show anymore
Do you sort of overly a symphonic music
I don't have the backing music anymore I don't know I am not trying to be dramatic I can't do this anymore
Alright man
Whatever I don't think a lot of movies have
The good guy give a speech over f******
Gotterdammerung there whatever
Meijer instruction will be their destruction I can
That's the guy I want to root for
I just love the swing there within like the span of a minute like this
I can feel the power and all that like
I haven't done this for a while
So Alex prays for focus
I will do my best but not like I wanted to
After I just pray to God the focus and Clarity to get it
Just the facts
Just lay out the big dimensions of this
Without going into little my new show like I like to do to prove he's little factoid
But it is
Untenable
Have the Communist Chinese
Officially given the run of the big five
Tech companies
People all over the world
Anyone off their platform
Going to go out and protest to reopen
I would
At this point if I were there
Name the five
Put a name down
Just right just close your eyes and say anything for five big
Maybe like Facebook Twitter Google
Is MySpace still a thing
AOL still going well
Anyway Alex tries to prove in this next clip the Chinese censorship
Thanks
I will see that it is just the same story about dr. Danielle and
News confirmed
Put out this info
Whether it's Google
Weather is app
They have
Media Matters
No
They're giving way
To the Communist Chinese
The division
Armies of Chinese
I would
Pet brace that differently in public
Checker
Wuhan bio lab
Ruled out viruses
They have their media other culture there
Kitsap so I want to clarify something in case it's not clear already
Dr. Anderson the person who's done some work at the Wuhan in
Urology is not employed by face
Dr. Anderson is not in charge of Facebook science whatever Alex imagines that is
As for the people who were trying to say their work at the Wuhan lab is somehow a conflict-of-interest again I have to stress that in her comments about the
Virus originated at that lab
She brings up the fact that you work there
He's very very transparent about it saying quote
I worked in this exact laboratory at various times over the past two years
I can personally attest to the strict control and containment measures implemented while working
The staff at wivere
Incredibly competent
Hard-working
An excellent scientist
Supertracker
This doesn't work well for Alex
Does narrative because he needs this to be an instance of China being in charge of this internet censorship
Not just an instance of someone we're doing some work at the Wuhan lab being consulted
In an effort to assess the accuracy of an editorial column in the New York Post
And why does Alex desperately need that right now
Superyacht
Owen and Rob do just got kicked off Twitter and you can't possibly accept it was a result
I'm trying to start a mass rally in the middle of a pandemic
It has to be because China secretly in charge of social media censoring
Thumper Lane
Desperate
Yep also there about 2.5 billion Facebook users
Alex is off by about a billion but who gives a s***
Does Aniyah doesn't swing the other way to point five billion is still too many yeah it's a lot yet
Sunnyway bisturi just keep going
This is all he wants.
Checker
Wuhan bio lab
Rule out virus leak
Wall
Debunking article
Run
What do you think the chant
So this is very very clearly Alex's number one story
He's hitting this thing so f****** hard I'm getting annoyed
However in this clip he claims that there's an Infowars article that somehow proves it
The doctor Anderson
The charge of Facebook science
So off I go to look that dumb article up
Direct me to articles up on Infowars about
The story
What is just a reposting of the story of adidon zerohedge
And the other is by Steve Watson
License really thought had quit or died
I'm very sad to see bulshit work
I thought he'd grown up
Maybe you got fired for
Is real estate job or something
I've good babe
All this information and Steve's article by Daniel Anderson is just ripped directly from the zerohedge article so it's it's barely even
In a new blog
Neither article in any way demonstrates a doctor Anderson is in charge of Facebook science fact-checking that's just completely made up
Even if you accept everything in these dubious sources
I think it what must be happening is that Alex doesn't read the realize that science
Feedback is the name of the separate business
Yeah he just thinks it's a department of feedback related to science within Facebook exactly
That would explain at least part of the confusion
But even that doesn't explain the assertion the doctor Anderson run science feedback that's just not true and his article on Infowars evening
Include the link to science feedback website
With the list there
Which doesn't include dr. Anderson
This article doesn't show any of this stuff
Ignore does it show Kate's funding at none of its supported by the evidence that he's providing at all
Alex presentas kind of information he has to either be
Consciously making things up
Reintroduce so little work that he just sees the word like science feedback
It assumes that he knows the whole story
Either way this is scary level of unpreparedness you showing as it relates to his clearly
Read story
Yeah I could also see him just reading it and saying
Science feedback and then just transposing is that is like science Facebook
Yeah that works there that's fine
Chirp
It's always about the same people Alex
Because you always
Making about the same people just fitting the same people in two completely different things and saying that
You look this makes sense
Course you can make it always about
About the same people
Have you just make stuff up
Is there a super easy
So Alex gets on his next move and he seems to be hinting at some trouble
There's a lot of things going on behind the scenes
About right now
Let's just say this
The enemy knows
But
What the Pentagon right now
That's why
Will you be taken off the air at any time because they don't want the source information
The president
It's okay
You know how things work
No matter what happens to me
You're going to continue on
We know that the Bible attack
America kill the economy
Sir Alex's
Deeply insinuating are things going on behind the scenes and he might be off the air anytime now
So
About that
It came to my attention thanks to listener name Rashawn over the weekend
That's Alex's a gigantic legal battle going on that we've not heard about at all
When he was out of Studio over the past couple of days it seems like it might have had something to do with the FDA or possibly his
Is DUI
But now they reviewed some court documents from Pacer
I really think that there might be a completely
Lee different hidden picture going on here
Back in January 24th 2020
Alex is ex-wife Kelly filed a petition in bankruptcy
Seacourt
She was making a claim of involuntary bankruptcy
And requesting relief under chapter 11
Cleveland voluntary bankruptcy is one where a party who's owed money
Can file a petition
To get that money they're owed
And if the party that owes the money can't pay it
They can be forced
Bankruptcy
Involuntarily to pay the debt
According to court filings
Things when they got divorced
In 2015
Alex testified that he could not afford
To pay the money that you was awarded
The divorce
So he signed a real estate lien would promise Kelly
A certain amount of money related to their shared property as well as 10% of the value of quote the businesses
Who created during the Joneses marriage
The state of Texas
I'll just read to hear from the file
Micheli put into court
The note requires Alex Jones to make monthly payments to Kelly Jones in the amount of 43900
$33 yeah
When Alex Jones defaults in anyway the note may be accelerated by Kelly Jones
It goes on to say that on June 28th 2019 Alex stated the quote he would not pay the entirety of the Jew
July 2019 note
And that he would not pay part of the August
Cenote payment
I can't possibly claim to know whether or not Kelly's claims are accurate but
She's a legend in this filing
But Alex defaulted on paying her for a promissory note in the amount of 700
861 dollar
I got to marry somebody I hate his rich
That's what I got to do that's what I need to do for some context that the proxxon
At least 30 2786 bottles of Alex's VSOP
A lot of sales
Make that up
So Alex naturally tried to get this case dismissed and a hearing was scheduled for March
Interesting Lee March 11th was one of those days that Alex happened not to be in studio last month
He hosted the first little bit of the show then Owen took over
When we covered that the feeling was that he had just gotten the letter from the
New York attorney general that is silver sailed and he just gotten DUI so it look like what was going on with the funeral
These desperate sales pictures going on
But maybe it was
Nobody was really going on with it is
Ex-wife is suing a 3/4 of a million-dollar uncut gems
No it's Adam Sandler's most recent movie
Is one non-stop guy going from
Creditor the Creditor trying to handle all this money and move it around so we can finally pay everybody off but with his gambling
He's trying to gamble his way back in
Indoor about it the whole time
Constant like
Not that it's so stressful to watch this movie because you like
Just pay a bill and stop
I got really stressed out not maybe not the same level but like look
This stuff is really like
Adding adding all of this bus
FDA plus the AG plus has his
Current of Santa Claus suits plus all of the other shifts like
This dude is
Racing around from one nightmare to another but this one might be the big one
So he Alex left the show in Owens hands on March 11th
And then they have this hearing
But
Prior to that
On the night of March 9th Alex got arrested for his DUI
And the next day Kelly filed an emergency restraining order on the grounds of child endangerment
To get their children out of the clearly chaotic environment
On March 11th Kelly filed an emergency
Motion for clarification of the law
Easy she's representing herself
So she was requesting the court Informer if there was
The conflict between the pending involuntary bankruptcy case
It is emergency protective restraining order
She was worried that the bankruptcy case would
Would preclude her from being able to file the restraining order
And in this motion for clarification she makes it very clear that if it would
She would automatically dismiss the bankruptcy
A document like that is a Real Testament to her priorities
And it is horrible World of Alex
We spend our time and
I couldn't help but be a little bit move by the fact that you was willing to
Completely dismissed if it meant that it would impede her ability to try and
Get her kids
Into a safe environment kids are worth more than
Three-quarters of a million-dollar
I mean it's such a low bar not to save it
Dunno and not to impugn which
Like her at all because of how many monsters we talked about life
That means you're human
March 11th they had their here
And the court decided the Kelly's cases were not in conflict and she would not have to withdraw our bankruptcy
In order to file the
Protective order
The court also dismissed Alex's motion
To dismiss the bank
With the court
Determining if there was a legitimate dispute
They set a trial date of April 23rd
This will be a quote evidentiary trial on the merits
The involuntary petition
Answer to terman whether to enter an order of relief
Against the alleged debtor
Alex
Dismiss the involuntary petition
Where to enter any other appropriate order
I normally might have considered something like this to be an element of Alex
His personal life which I generally are on the side of not covering
Sent it involves his divorce
And ultimately
It's not about his worldview or rhetoric
It's just a dispute about his payment or non-payment of money he owes his ex-wife
But I'd like to explain a couple reasons why I decided to bring this up on the show
In the past 6 months or so Alex has been way way more fatalistic on everything I've ever seen him before
He's been finding himself talking about quitting and recognizing that the end might be near in ways that I don't find to be similar to other
Breeds of his career that I've looked at
Many of the things that he's dealing with could be what's driving that
From his supplement warnings to his upcoming Sandy Hook trial
There's a lot for him to worry about and a lot of various things that you could think
Might be
What he's worried will sink the ship
I've considered all the Dynamics at play and I become fairly convinced
What's this pending trial with his ex-wife
In what's been motivating most of Alex's Behavior
Over the past
Let me walk you through that reasoning
According to her filing
Blank the notification of non-payment from Alex
Regarding the July and August no pay my
Back in 2019
You would assume the talk of filing a lawsuit over these defaulted payment
Wouldn't happen to mediate
You know that there's probably so
Grace.
Probably pretty good chance things were normal for a little while
Early September 2019 is when we started to hear Alex repeatedly have breakdown
What are you talkin about how enforced might not make it another year
How we didn't know if he was going to reorder supplies
Some of that definitely could have been about his need to sell out stock so he wouldn't have to pay taxes on carryover inventory
But if you recall
Do you talk to whole lot about selling his house
This is interesting because
The debt that Alex has to Kelly is secured by liens on two properties
But it a hat
Found to be in default of his debt one way could be paid
Is by foreclosing on that property
Alex knows what these houses are what is used to secure his death
So he knew that he wasn't making payments
It would stand to reason that he knew was only a matter of time until he lost his house
January 24th was the day of the bankruptcy filing was made
Another couple of interesting things
Is it come from looking back at that show
The first
Is it Alex
Start the show on time that day
And when he did come to the mic
This is how it started
Reading all the news and all the information
This is probably one of the first
First times that
I just physically could not go on air at start the broadcast
Add
Just comes a time when
The world just going to have to be judge
He's another pretty f***** up headspace of Doom
Very much projecting
His own judgement
Or later I'm going to have to be interesting Lee that was the episode where Mike Adams declared it over
Over for Humanity
That's less relevant to Alex's mental state because it was coming from Mike
But will we pay less attention to about that episode in hindsight
Is the other guest that was there that day
Jon rappoport
I've noticed that Alex doesn't really bring Jon rappoport around much these days except when he needs a bro
I've long suspected the Rapoport is hypnotizing Alex but maybe it's a benign kind of
We're talkin to Rapaport really does make Alex feel better
Almost episode it really did deteriorate into
Alex kind of needing some therapy from John about identity issues
God is pretty well so how do you
Yourself up to died
But not the bad stuff
Back to it I'm going to meet
Aaron do it but the point is
Be in that place the most of the David Dog Spa
In the song
How do people begin that Journey
How do you do that
Either you recognize that
Your
You're an individual
You're not existing by virtuous
The fact
People and so forth
The source of your excuse
Goldman Sachs you need you need you
You need you
There
You're going to go on
He's getting this for like real
100% therapy
The Rapaport to set him right about things
And he was deeply
Backed up about identity issues on this episode
And of course that ends with one of my favorite
John report you got to come on more than once every 6 months please come back on next week we love you
No more fake news. Calm your beautiful till we love you John beloved on report thank you so much
Thank you Alec
Thank you so much
Hours Lowe's on Route 4
So after this point Alex goes back to normal for a bit
There aren't so many instances of him saying that everyone's going to die or the world is bound to be judged
I think there wasn't any real reason for Alex to be too worried after the immediate situation
Snow going to end did file his motion to dismiss the case
Super baller been successfully kicked down the road
For now it's normal as Infowars stuff and there's no
The one thing though
Is it theirs
Dramatically increase sales pitches surrounding the food buckets and his silver
Write that
That is when
Everything went
At this point at this point he's engaging in the coronavirus as he might with any other sort of
Completely made up and zero Stakes conspiracy
That he engages
On January 31st he's freaking himself out about Resident Evil me
Give you some sense of how seriously things were being taken at that point
Wild stuff is just info
The coronavirus Meredith takes
Kristin Turin
In late February Alex gets
Distracted by Rogers sentencing and then he launches into a full-on
About going to see pack
And associating with Nick Fuentes
Kelly had until March 5th
Defiler response to Alex's
Petition
So Alex
Up till that point she doesn't file
Assumes
If she doesn't file on the 5th
She end up filing on the 6th
But it was still accepted by the court given the coronavirus situation making things
So by March 6th Alex had a good reason
Think this wasn't just going to magically go away and he knew that
The hearing was on
On for March 11
On-air things are too different but on March 10th
He doesn't show after a night in jail for a DUI
On March 11th Alex only host the first part of the show for all and takes over
If you work almost
Depart Alex hosted
What about his Vaso beets how they have nitric oxide in them which Alex thinks Is nitrous oxide
Also this is the show that he ends his segment
Of his I know what he's hosting before you leave by surprising everyone with free shipping
What you swore he'd never do again
Things get pretty complicated at this point because
By March 12th
Two things have happened
One is that he's learned from this court that his motion to dismiss was reject
And he'd have to go to bank
The 2nd
Is that he received the letter from the New York attorney general ordering him to cease and desist from the sales tactic
He was using surrounding his silver
March 13th on his show is a complete break
He started talking about how we're all dead already
He got really mad at callers you promised
To hit himself on air if you didn't take enough calls
He started rambling about how easy was to
To kill other people
And notable
He ended the show predicting
Imminent end
Of his show
I feel like I'm almost
Also talk
Megan bad about to happen
Take a note
Police officer Bryson
Don't say that
Let me know Matic I want to tell you I love you and I appreciate you
But
A lot of big stuff going down
Maybe that's going to change
But that Trump is said any minute to declare a national emergency
What are declared three weeks ago
There was no show on the 14
Because it was a Saturday
And Alex didn't do his show on March 15th 16th or 7th
But by the time he got back the coronavirus situation that developed to the point where things were so crazy that it's legitimate
Really impossible to discern what input is leading to what output for
Since then we've seen Alex increasingly be unable to do his show
He's left the show on a number of occasions he's descended into rants about how the public deserves to be exterminated
He's gone out to break yelling things but I was listening to burn in hell only to come back from commercial and apologize
There's something very serious up
This case seems like a possible candidate for what it is
Yeah
I could be entirely wrong
Admit that entirely
But I think that this timeline somewhat
It suggests the large Secret
Contributor
Dallas is complete inability to do his job
Is frequent dalliances of the thoughts of impending doom
It is notable recent absence
This could be this bankruptcy case
That he's doing court for
This Thursday
There's another reason I want
To discuss this a little bit
I have no idea how the case is going to shake out
There's a real possibility that this week could end with Alex losing a massive settlement
They could stay at the bank
I would hate for that news to break and if it's been sitting on this information and not discuss
At the same time it's entirely possible that the court will decide now it's his favorite
Or the trial could go on longer than one hearing
Or Alex could lose an appeal the decision
I've no idea what's
Going to happen but the more I look at the
Timeline of this stuff
The more I saw possible overlap
Please don't just take this as a possible thing
Definitely not something that I'm claiming it
Is definitive
Most of the things that you can see that lineup is being possibly Alex responding to things in this case
Could easily be explained by others
Like the New York attorney general's letter coming right at the same time that is motion 2
Dismiss was rejected
You kind of got so much
Chaos going on in his life right now that it's almost pointless as an exercise trying to figure out what
Contributes to what
But I thought that we had some information about a case that
To possibly recollect
It's worth discussing
Yeah also
Small point
My birthday is this Friday after Alex's trial
The universe really wants
Give me an amazing present
Do what I want
I think it's I think it's sad a little bit for Alex
Because I don't think
He's capable of that
That Clarity that comes whenever everything is
Like it seems like this has been my experience whatever you're not until it's too late
Yeah yeah whatever I've been in a situation where it's like just
One thing after another
Everything pisses me off until it get
Get to that point where I'm like
This is just so bad I don't even I can't even feel
I I can't even feel angry about this I just have perfect clarity of how I'm going to be
You f***** and I just got to live through this
Said he just cannot do that
Maybe maybe maybe a fairy does
I don't know it's impossible to
Hotel because of that
Smack dab in the middle of him realizing he has to go to court and the day he has his hearing
Like it's so
Right there it's
It's really difficult though
It's 88
Almost impossible to say
Anything but I've heard any
Like real talk of this cake
That does Veer too much into the personal which is like I don't
I don't think we have any business covering
So in this next clip
Jordan
Okay and Alex is talking about how you write
About everything
But because he's right about everything
Temp won't save
The same things
Alex does because that means
War
People that created the virus
Did the Pentagon keeps going we don't think it's man-made
We don't think
We got to go to war with him
I understand
That President Trump
Keep forget
Tucson
He's saying that Trump needs to say the same things as him even though that means war and then in the middle of
He's like my ear pieces and then I'm going to go up there
How little does he care about the seriousness of the topics he's covering
This is insane
I'm just going to leave you with that little tidbit of I think we should be at war with
With China I got to get off a real quick on air
That's that's shocking
So no more half-measure
Playing games at half-measures polish
Playing patty-cake with Ash
So the old rules of being chicken necks
Cowards is over
Were you being mad
Really bad and really crazy really
I don't even talk about things that we can at least do
If you don't have firearms and ammunition
Uh-oh
If you don't have water filtration
You're insane you need high-quality water filtration
Lexapure
But such as we have wrecked one
Alex Alex knows damn well that alexapure water filters are not sold out
Because they can never really be sold out
Is it doesn't actually keep them in his Warehouse
If you go to his website you'll immediately learned that he doesn't really sell likes
Superior filters
There a product that he sells through my Patriot Supply
Survival food sponsor
They also sell the Alexa Pur
Alex doesn't handle by Patriot supplies ordered
You said on many occasions that they take the orders directly from Alex's website
And they go to my Patriot supplies for filaments
Then they ship it from there
Obviously this would be needed to sell any of the food buckets any kind of scale because no matter how big is space Alex
Is renting You couldn't possibly afford Eva Warehouse big enough for both food and water filtration
System
This is spelled out on his website shipping
Information
To ensure quality and reduce costs this item shipped directly from the supplier
If you purchase additional items they will be shipped separately
In order for alexapure water filters to be sold out it must be true that my Patriot Supply itself is sold out of water
Filters that case it makes no sense to say they're great just try and find them somewhere
Not real
Is an involuntary reaction for Alex to say things are sold out Edward near sold out
Because I create the perception
An artificial scarcity in the listener's mine
It's a pretty old-school manipulative sales tactic and what you know
What you're selling isn't
Product
It's the what you're selling is the fear that you might be unable to
To get said product
Don't you feel dumb then
You're thinking about this Lexus this is a great car I don't know if you're not on the fence lights
Dinner's already let me just tell you right now this one on the lot
The last one we
I have two people coming in later they already said they want they want to buy
Look we might be able to get free shipping
I said I would never give Reserve Bank Alexa's mobile
Generally I don't believe Alex when he says things are sold at or near selling out but typically I can't really do anything to confirm or deny
Tonight is claim
In this case it's a clear-cut in
Santa biking
Eli so we got a new water filter
What
I did go to the website I need to go to my favorites play they're still in stock
Black horse
But you got to get this food
Right you got it we got to get the buckets
Got to get the water filters in cuz you're going to need that food
Time.
F****** bug-out ago
Because I don't
Evacuating for the worst things I've ever felt terrible doing it
The total collapse of its being taken off the air in possibility
Never been more disgust
I feel kind of selfish they got there
For me because I'm out here in all this
We may get our asses.
You definitely want to get
Future
You want food that easily transportable and that you got ready to go
There's not going to be any currency out there more valuable than food
So get my food money
This is pretty
Do me
Yeah
Now let me let me follow his lodge
Real quick
There's no currency that will be more valuable than food
Right so you should trade your money
For my food
Haha
But he doesn't actually have the food true true
Occurrences
Well the past you would have said gold
Staking that now so
No more hate the bottom is going to fall out at total societal collapse summer of rage, and get gold
None of that anymore
Greenspoint
You got to get food
Because of global Astor at war with us
And food is the
Global economic and cultural war against us
Overhyped virus
If you don't give them all the power all the control of your life you're the bad guy well
Give yourself
Our
Your life
Neurotic
Supplement into the future
Knowing its container
It's ready
Easily transferable
If you got a bug
Waterproof
Do containers
Write a boogie
You say
So Alex gets done with his dumb
Very extended sales pitch and he wants to let you know that he's been dropped the ultimate
Smoking Gun
The China is doing
This
Censoring or something
God
If you can gets kicked off the air before doing that I'm be furious
That's one of those like things like that sometimes they'll be storylines going in the WWE and then someone
Gets fired and I never get the end of the story live
Alex
F****** stop doing the show without doing that surgery
Amrish Puri I really don't want to have to say that Alex's show was canceled too soon
So I
Smoking Gun
I'm going to lay this on the White House
Warriors
Everybody else
Dramatic the only way out of this
Leveling with the people is the only way out of this
Total War
With globalist
Chinese
Who developed the virus
Propaganda
The TV shows the movies
That literally spent
Hundreds of millions of us tax
Money
Reprogrammed
Town of the industrial world
Bombers couldn't do
Conventional munitions
Prepare yourself for the ultimate smoking guy
Smoking Gun is just in covering that story about the fact Checker again
Is it really
I want am I being prepared for that I've already prepared you guys already done a bunch
It's like I've already eaten all the food I don't need I've already prepared for this
Story story
There's actually a couple of added element
Details where Alex's
Missing nuance
When you look up dr. Danielle
What do you find
Us
200 billion dollars
Very loud that release date
Develop a test kit
Hahaha
How convenient
Fake laugh
So we have two claims being made there primarily
First is that doctor Anderson involved in the development of covid-19 test kits
And the second is that you stand to make a ton of money from it
Johns Hopkins Center for Health security as a list up on their website of all the tests
For covid-19 that are currently used or are in
And if you want we can take a look through all of them
They're currently four tests that have been approved for Diagnostic use of the United States
9 that have been approved for Diagnostic use in other countries but not here
26 that are quote approved for research and surveillance purposes only
And 11 more that are currently still undeveloped
This alone should give you a pretty good sense that there is
Really erase to make this test in order to Corner the mark
There a lot of people working on a very similar gold no one's going to make 200 million dollars
Pardon me
People might make 200 million.
That is not used in the United States was developed at the Wine LAB which is a part of the Duke and Us in Singapore
This test is only used in Singapore and its for antibodies
To the virus
The test was developed by Professor Wang
Linfa
And so it took a while to find evidence
This was the case
It is actually true the doctor answers
Did collaborate with him on it
In a March interview with and US News
Professor Wang said quote
In my research with assistant professor Anderson
We were are working towards making our serological test
That's great so I guess this is kind of a half-truth being used to create a whole lot
Dr. Anderson is involved in the development of a test at Duke
And us but there is no reason to believe that she's motivated by profit so that she stands to make billions of it
Wants to complain about that he should
Start with celox or chembio
Who are the two companies that don't test
For two of the companies that don't test that are approved for use me and I
Midstate
In terms of a conspiracy
Her test is not even approved in the United
Not just in Singapore cool
Cool I'll
Thanks for that
Just because a man
It's
I'm good for her
I'm glad she helped develop the test
Something wrong with it
What
I'm not taking into account the fact that she f****** runs Facebook
She runs Facebook who can say what
But it turns out
Says
Call Bob's
Covid-19
Oh when did it do that
Handle anybody studying they did
You're all talk
So that must be why they want Alex off here cuz no one
Can handle the level of Truth and investigation he's bringing to the table
The globalist
Just have no rebuttal of this high-end truth coming out of the Infowars
Shut it down
First claimed he was a doctor Anderson runs Facebook's fact-checking would you've already disgusting
Detailing it's not true
The second claim is at this test
She was involved in developing and Singapore words that designed to make people with colds
Does positive
Covid-19
Actually really interest
I mean obviously it's not true but impressive
According to an article in these Straits times an English newspaper in Singapore
The development of this test was actually very difficult
For exactly the reason Alex's suggested
Serology test
That looks for antibodies against covid-19
So it's important that they actually find the exact
Antibodies
Just kind of useless
As it turns out Singapore is kind of the perfect place for that kind of thing to be developed primarily because the
The country was hit hard by the sores outbreak in 2000
30 there's a lot of people who have antibodies for SARS and their body there
Stars and covid-19 are both Coronavirus
And according to dr. Wang there Approximately 80% similar
So the challenge he faced with
Develop an antibody test that was so precise
That it would bring up false positives if it was used on someone with antibodies for SARS end
They came up with the
Screening test is approximately 90% accurate in this very quick
As well as a quote gold standard
It takes four to five days and a level 3 biohazard lab
What is supposedly
Completely accurate
What's important here is that the test
Developed in Singapore is actually the worst possible example Alex
To come up with when he's randomly trying to accuse people
A creating a test that will just call any cold covid-19
The team of researchers set out from the jump with the awareness that they would have to create a test that doesn't create false positive
For very similar antibodies
Achieved
Anyway no one
The imaginary globalist
Least of all are worried about the alleged truth that Alex is spreading on air
I think people want him off here because he's an unstable narcissist who seems to be drifting deeper and deeper into calling for a simultaneous
Simple and Cold War
Seriously right when his own personal life is falling apart
That's someone who leaving politics aside should not be on there
Is only the danger
It is it is like he correctly identified the problem and then just assumed it was insurmountable
Yeah of course it would provide false positives because
Okay
That is a good start and smart people
Caught that before you
Right that's why no one's afraid of you thought somebody had it first
Is Buddy common cold is less similar to covid-19 and stars
And if they're considering a purpose
It terms of this test which again is
Globally used
I don't know I don't know what Alex is trying to prove here but it's all bulshit
The episode Alex was complaining about
Parents children being told to like
Confront their parents
It's about misinformation
And he doesn't really get around to explaining what that story is
About until later
We get into that and man holy
F****** s***
This balls off of
From Australia
Canada
They are
Are calling for people to get their parents
Home
First.
Porsche 930
Does your dad
Wuhan lab
Getting his face
Definitively
Danielle Anderson
Charizard covid-19 to create Hysteria
These people
Ridiculously obvious and stupid
First thing I would say is this name has never come up on Alex's show before it gets she seems to be the
You master over all areas of
So baby that's
That baby that should be a red flag he's behind George Soros did you know that
After now you know how evil she is she has a
Degree how do you f*** this up
Never
Exactly
Another obvious problem with a narrative that Alex is selling here at least as far as the US goes is that most schools in
The country are closed
So there's no class where they be playing these videos
For kids
I'm not sure how elementary schools operate like
Except for outside like my experience they don't have periods
For older students like in junior high and High School
But I have no idea I haven't been
School in a long time
So this video isn't something to play for kids at school it's a news piece that the Canadian broadcast
The company did about the uncomfortable situation that a lot of people find themselves in
Where someone in a group chat
Possibly a family member is spouting insane
Conspiracy theories
The pieces basically just
Explaining that your instinct might be to call them crazy
But that kind of Shame and behavior will often just reinforce the belief the person
Previously had as a defense mechanism to deal with the embarrassment
To being called out
They recommend inclusive
Empathic language like reminding the person We're All in This Together
It doesn't recommend anyone you use the resource
Put out by Danielle Anderson door doesn't
Dimension Health feedback
They just suggest sending them a good link to a real source
Good sources we are well past the point where his point makes any sense
He was actually referencing my video where I
Gave examples such as like I
Listen up Mom
If that is your real name
You're wrong about everything
And also
As it turns out I have dinner later is not as concerned with confronting mom's as he is about
Disputing a real Attack on Dad
Is
Pretty f*****-up
Pretty f*****
He starts trying to play the video and he can't
Control himself
What's going playlist
So what are you doing this happen
The loved one
Drop Center
To the family group chat with something
Israel
Show him
Danielle Anderson
Bulldog
Sounded a little person
That sounded a little personal I would leave it alone
Map Thailand
Yeah
He says
Mike alright maybe he'll get
Further into it this time
So what do you do when this happens a loved one
Dropped into the family group chat with something
What's barbacoa
It sounds personal dad
No
Listen to your daddy
It's definitely feels like he's working through some things
Personal going on
Vicky has a great relationship with the women in his life currently doesn't seem like it
Third time could you do that
So what do you do when this happens a loved one it's your dad
Dropsy
It's something
Is Real China
Foolproof
I know this is how many times
He makes a little bit further the next time
I mean
It did say it seems like he's really hinging on that bad thing
Maybe it's about the HR Director at 7 floors
F***** up trying to express
Legos
Break yelling about dads Maple Place
Catherine
Just staying home
Chinese love you
Dad
Admittedly that is the type
A behavior that would get a dog neutered
Yeah
I don't really have much of
Comment
Like it's a logical it's not it's not using the source material to provide,
Commentary it's not
It's not really even
Expressing
Appoint
It's just lashing out
Angry it's just responsive anger
It seems to
All circle around the idea of listening to Dad
About somebody's children not listening to Dad that seems really important to have right now for some
Very weird
Yep
So
He goes to break and he comes back
And I guess maybe because of some of those issues he needs a proxy son
So brings Owen Shroyer into Studio
Cars
Straight up calling
War with China
Play be honest
The disc came out of a lab and was man-made
Then you could actually say okay you know what hey
Hey we got a serious situation here this biological warfare launch against by the Chinese we need this to phase out we're going need a month we're going after
Do some serious social distancing
Blaming our speech when it's
Is the government
The president now
It's totally out of control
And I'm not going to try to
Any other reason out
I mean I'm sick of that
Why is Alex saying that like
Trying to fight over like bumping into somebody is a good impulse
It's not I don't think so I think that it is
Do I go to war with China
Which is not good
Nobody
Even listening to death
I needed somebody to listen to Dad so bad
Thank you
So they they start discussing how like we're almost
In a nuclear war
Nuclear war right now
I don't know what the presents waiting on you this point
Reality
Man man oh man
Hope no one's listening to this
So Alex and Owen
They're goof they do a lot of Goofy
On this this interview
If you want to call it that
Comedy segment in impression I think of like a Rothschild
This is
Where I kind of felt like maybe he's drunk
But I think maybe not I think he just got like really emotionally overloaded and now he needs Owen to like f*****
Around what's going on
But him being drunk
And this is the price
Rothschild like the old Rothschild royalty their kind of losing control Bill Gates
Central Bank
You had
Forget about you
I didn't say this is great
So we got
Putting out Chinese prop
Propaganda in the United States
Facebook run by the Wuhan
Okay
So I mean like it's not it's not there like Telltale drunk sign or some little thing
Things like the constantly interrupting then start
Happens when he's drunk but I think it also happens when he's sober.
Inconclusive on the side of sober
I think he's out of his mind
Coaches be like
Like that
Damn
So they get around to like
They're doing this s*** that's like f****** around
Adnan Sen
These weird impression total nuclear war
Another jump back and forth because it in the snakes that they're talking about how like we could end this and that
3 hours
Leadership these guys are awesome
Literally
Capitec people on 3 hours in the military
Yeah brother
They're attacking us
You lost for violence
To an insane degree and
Lying about
Your bloodlust
Is terrifier
3 hours of taking out the leadership involved have to overthrow China
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
Do you have to take out all of the globalist which are pretty much everybody
The entirety
All of big Tech
How the healthcare system in the country
Yeah I already said Democrats
Stupid f****** idea you've got using an assassin
Is it a
Small if it one person
You know easy for one person to get into places if you're using 1,000 1,000
Somebody's going to get
Get tipped off
Does he really think that 1,000 assassins could take out the 10,000 Stasi that run Facebook
CR old so maybe it would work
So and of course is there to complain
That's true
Owens are mostly to complain about the fact that he got kicked off Twitter floors
Score and it's B
You know courses because he was trying to do this rally right
Interesting Lee tries to
Compare his own rally to those of
Civil Rights era people problems
You don't like black
Whatever
Literally everything stop
Breathing actually
I tell you what I really think even if it ends up hurting
Maybe they're f****** around
Tell me there's some problems with the with the
Comparison
Like what
My head I would just start with like racism not being contagious
Well
If you listen to Alex it might be
I would also suggest that possibly during the Civil Rights era were there
A gigantic outbreak
Why so much about the black community some of those protests to might have been put
They would have still happen
Maybe a little later probably civil rights as one of the most important things
That you could possibly add to pay for
Protest in favor of
Still think you might want to hold off a tiny bit if your hair is
Counterfactual I can't say for sure that that is what would have happened
Yeah I would I would hope that
Martin Luther King Jr wouldn't be like
Well we've been being f***** over and murdered by the white oppressors for our entire life
Lives in the entire lives of our families and back and back and back so I
I think it's a good idea for all of us to get
Together and wipe out two to three percent of us at the same time
Second difference
His whole thing is meaning
And there's no point to Dem doing what they're doing
The other big difference
Perhaps in the next clip though I should say it
No end of that last one owns their f****** around it's saying like hey if we stop breathing
Don't spread the virus
Well
It turns out this becomes
I'm just going to stop
Because I want to be a leader I want to stop at
Madonna
Okay
We do have a sandwich alarm titled Ipswich by placing music onto the certain stations get mad
Like he would get at a funeral
Around about this I thought the headline like
Breathing breathing
Goodbye
Go to bet you can't take that away from
Well-executed welcome
Can see you when I'm done caring
Go for it at that goes on a bit longer
People dying from covid-19 and then go outside and have a big rally with all kinds of
People around
Go to it
Fun
So it is night scope they talk about the
Twitter and they have
Three primary complaint
About it or Alex does
And all of them are dumb
Coronavirus
It's not about coronavirus
Organized a protest
Assembly
All your BS
Doesn't
The president
I apologize three complaints are in a later clip this is just
First complaint
Is the right of assembly
Obligation
Protect Alex are Owens right to assemble somewhere
The first amendment is about what the government
Can and cannot do
The government can't stop free assembly that's
That's the rule
Twitter can suspend people for trying to put together huge gatherings in the middle of a pandemic that's
Totally within their rights
I guess what these rallies over the weekend went off mostly without a hitch
Because the government didn't infringe on people's right to assemble as completely f***** up and stupid have an ideas it was
Yeah I can find one story about a person in Raleigh who is arrested at a protest in this introduces an important
The right to congregate or assemble is not absolute
For instance if you're breaking a different law to protest still be arrested
Like an anti-war dim
You can be arrested for assault
This happens all the time
Assembled my fist to their face buddy that is legal
Right to free assembly common things like left-wing protesters
If you talk to him
Protesters are arrested for trespassing
All the time
This is one of the fundamental realities people and activist communities are well aware of and it's part of the price of doing protest
In the context of
Declared emergency like the one we're in now state governments do have the ability to do things they might not have had the ability to do and
Another circumstances
When there's a stay-at-home order in place from the governor the police
Can't arrest people who are protesting
Not because of the assembly but because the ACT
Being assembled as a breach of another legal order
So a lot of this was very state-by-state but generally speaking you can still go protest
But if you do
You very well might get arrested
Your first amendment rights are still intact
But exercising them in a way that jeopardizes Community Health
Could run the risk of getting you arrested
It's not ideal but it's also not tyranny
What that is so exemplary of
Is
The difference between right-wing and left-wing protest
Right-wing protesters
Are so used to never being bothered
And left-wing protesters alike
Big kick us in the face every f****** time we're going to jail all the time they're trying to murder us did you guys not know the
The cops are patches and right-wing protester
You guys are letting us hang out
Oh no
Could anybody who's
Been involved in any of these sorts of things
Know that you get arrested a bit
Like it's just something that
All the pictures you see if people would human
Chains and staff
It's kind of a part of the bed
And I they just can't handle the idea of getting
Suspended
Twitter
Cool
So Alex now comes back from break
And he does another comedy
I got to say
Really good
Really well conceived
Well EX
Executed
Goodbye
You know around here earlier your back live
Terrible things about the globalist
Then he finally got reason
He said it's time for all of us to die
To stop covid-19 spread
I don't just believe we shall be given masks
Grocery stores
You can put on Twitter
Promoted
Ourself
Like they said they're killing people so
Ramona Lane
Eugene ding dong
Is here
Escalade
Actually I represent
The future babies
Planet
In the world
Sewing his comeback
With a plastic baby mask over his face which is
Sort of blocking his ability to be heard
Clearlake do you mean the things that he's supposed to be doing
A comes back as a baby or something Alex says
Jinping spirit animal of the commercial break their sort of work
Tina cross-purposes
They don't really have a good yes and that is Owen has just
Invalidated
The premise that Alex is established
That's good I'm not the thing you said
Is the best form of improv in terms of the game
And that is that
This baby is there to kill Alex Alex
To kill him
Will you kill me right now so I don't
I just want to say
This is an example of
And the future of the world
The Democrats
Really care about the future babies instead
We've been sent Alex
Come here and to kill all humans
So that we can save the human race in human volunteers
Waterstones has volunteered as tribute he will be the first down
You really exist
I'll be uploaded live forever
Of course
Great improv there that I'm not actually going to be killed
Oh yes of course that's what my plan
God this is so bad problem with
Getting good at comedy
Part of getting good at comedy is making it seem like
You're not working
That hard people who don't realize that you have to work insanely hard to get there
Think it's easy and you can just do it anytime you want we'll something that I thought was really interesting when I was
I went and watched it was like
There have to be some people
Probably not a ton
But some people who are like
This is
Hilarious
Not real
I mean there's got to be some people think it's like innovative
Can't believe Owens wearing a baby
Baby Owen kills Alex on air
You're a real hero
Oh yes
Red Palace
Good
Good good ass
So ladies and gentlemen as you can
This is the future of mankind
This is the only future if you want the teacher babies of the world to live
Listen to Bill Gates
Ben take your loving back scene
And just die
Dinosaurs and humans
Give me forever
Until then
Now Alex Jones digital hologram rises from the dead
So wonderful
This is
This is this goes on too long
It's me Andre
Anyway I wish I could say I hadn't seen anything like that at a community theater before but how we going to do
Really fun for me about this
Is that Alex now gives up on the bed
Brighten the middle of it and still trying to go through
Keep moving forward and Alex's look like f*** it I'm done
But I think secretly what's going on
Is it Alex is jealous that Owens wearing the mask and is the center of attention that's what I think is going
That sounds right
American
Images willingly die
Don't worry we'll put your car into the system for
You're an imposter
Breaking the fourth wall
Siam
He's putting the baby
Hello
Love you
Alex I think was jealous of Owen getting to have the fun of wearing a mask
That what that reminds me so much of is
Chicago comic who will not be named
Wildwood show what show
Just he was headlining your bottom so bad for like 4 minutes that he just left
And then the hosts came back on I believe this was Matt drefke
Started doing well
And then he came back on and he kicked back dressy off to drag her this is him being like it's not my fault
I wasn't getting the labs it's cuz of that guy where the baby man
And then wants to get right back into two
I want the ball yeah exactly
And get back to Owen's Twitter
Situation in this is where the three
When I learned last night
That you had a bunch of other crew members were banned off Twitter
Because you're going to violate social distancing
Process
Platform Act
Symbol
The First Amendment
Calling Owen getting
Suspended from Twitter a war crime might be a little overly dramatic
I thought
Calling him
Civil rights leader was overly dramatic
It's actually a nice
That kind of talk hurts a person's credibility but to be fair Alex doesn't have much to begin with so he's probably fine
Alex has three complaints about Owen suspension seat to come down to the issue of 1st Amendment
Due process and the question of off-platform activity
These are all bulshit complain
As an issue the First Amendment doesn't apply here so I just reject that as an argument
Do process what rights of due process does Owen have with
Twitter that are being violated
The fundamental concept
Due process related
It's the state respecting a person
Rights and how a person has a right to a trial before they're executed in prison or have their property seized by the state
None of that's relevant to Twitter
Twitter doesn't owe anyone a trial before they suspend their account this is just word salad Alex's throwing around
The question of off-planet for behaviors even Lamer
Because that's not applicable at all
It's Oliver just organizing his rally and he didn't mention it on Twitter there's a good chance he'd still have a Twitter account
However you mentioned it a bunch on Twitter
One did Periscope video is already promoted at what the hospitals to show there were cars in front of
He did a ton of on platform activity it was meant to promote is off-platform activity
We just kind of the problem
All through these complaints
We bulshit you just trying to
Grab victimhood to to wear like a
Cape
North pole shift
It really really f******
Your pennies hold rallies like I'm I'm really really mad
Because the media is doing
It all over again
This is all
Made up AstroTurf bulshit
Party all over again
Just ignore them
Everytime they cover it and they do it as though it's like
Right-wing protesters instead of being like these people are
Literally f****** AstroTurf
People trying to people like Alex
Yeah that that many people really
Matter what its two men
It's too
Stupid
I don't know I don't
I don't know if I agree 100% that you should just ignore it but I do think that maybe the coverage has been a little bit off
That's what I would agree if you want really bad
I'm talking about his fees sales
Bright future
And I want you to know
Look
My sales has never been about the Vine
I sell my products but it's not about the virus
It's about
Do you need food
Because he's going to collapse sure
I knew would China shutting down
Coming I said you better get ready better
This was planned
Six months ago before this even started Shore
Hand sanitizers
Alcohol
Royals
I was getting into the game
God dammit this is been planned for 6 months
The issue is that no one
As a good Prada
No one has
We looked at
Organic
Hand sanitizer that actually leaves your hands
Not oily but not dry
What does that mean hate me it means they're not oily they're not dry they're healthy
Okay
So they're doing the sales pitch for this hand sanitizer
Yeah I get through it
And then Alex is like what's coming up on your show
What are you up to today
I need to say I will be definitely
Talking about these new hand sanitizers
What's the time
I normally you know you tried to squeeze it right and then
With a Sprite how come no one's done it it's a spray it's a spray hand sanitizer
Organic hand sanitizer
Spray bottle off the top of the head you have dr. Bronner's are primally pure
Plenty of others
Is only new to someone who didn't know it existed
It's in no way an innovation
I looked at the bottles
And the ingredients
Of Alex
Suzanne sanitizer
Edwards Essentials
And I would bet just about anything I own that Alex is just private labeling dr. Bronner's hand sanitizer
They're both packaged in almost identical to ounce bottles and they have identical like in greedy
Ethyl alcohol water essential oil and glycerin
Dr. Bronner's sells hand sanitizer both peppermint and lavender
But they also sell the number of other so products with eucalyptus
Which covers V3 set
Spitaliks
I have a tiger
To create those three
Has just entered into a reselling agreement with dr. Bronner's
And he wants to pretend that he's been developing this amazing hand sanitizer for 6 months which
I've no idea how cute even do that
Wouldn't have a f****** life
Get out of here
To absolutely
I had my best scientists working on that
Motivation
By that are very very clear
So this is the end of the third hour
Here be the end of the show but Alex and Owen do a little bit
The beginning of the fourth hour
And this would be how the show ends if he actually
Let the fourth our hosts have the whole for that
I really want to take a lot of phone calls I got a lot of great
Oh my God
No for David Brock
No I think it David brought Rakim
Wow
They're Nazis
He also said they're sexy
Yes that's that's how we go out to break with the playground
Childish insinuations
But Owen is gay
Yeah yeah
Why it is surprised that you I was amazed they made it this far without also belittle
The queer Community that's a great idea
Alex
Play Around by calling Owen gay before
Just like
You're calling for war with China
What you can't have a little fun all the way Dan do you can
It's not fun it's childish bulshit in den den
Incredible
Credibly
They come back
And Owen
Suggest
That Alex
Put his career on
You know Alex that used to do career
Diamond matches in the WWF WWE you should put your career on the line
In a bare-knuckle
Bra UFC style shutdown
You have a lineup just Royal Rumble Style
Over the ropes
Put you out
And that'll be it you put
Free online all these people that want Alex Jones shutdown
You can
And his career he'll put his career on the line
Would you do that
Proceeds go to charity
. sewing
That's the Paradox close to
Martial law
Paradoxically under massive threat
Because I'm intruding myself
That's a completely unrelated thought
I would suggest
Pointless
Put your
Career on the line in a physical fight
However
In a knowledge fight
Alex
Debata point
In a formal debate
Like some point that he has
Actually like independent position where he can't yell you can't just like overpower be like
Like you can't just
Talk a mile a minute and throw out all these pointless pieces of information
Would he put his career on the line
In a debate
Absolutely no course not
Put it on the line in a physical fight and he lost he wouldn't stick to itself course not
And that is what they're talking about the end of Alex's Twitter
You don't have a retirement match when you're in the middle of your career in order to retire
Well that's what I'm
I'm thinking right here like
Owen should sound more worried
A phone doesn't have all the information
Then that would explain why he's very nonchalant here but
Owen is not going to have a job
If Alex goes down it's not like Owens going to take over Infowars and it's going to continue running
It's not like Infowars is like CNN or something where it's at boss leaves
Yeah yeah I know it's Alex sogos
Who's going to get a job somewhere else
The only way that Infowars survives past Alex is if Alex somehow gracefully exit
With millions of dollars
And a willingness to fund someone else's operator
See that ever happened
Especially considering that the way Alex might wind up leaving Infowars is going to leave Infowars bankrupt as well
Actually
You know what there is a way I could work but it would require Owen taking over
And then taking a bunch of money from like dark money
Funny places
If one of these right-wing
Places wanted to pay millions of dollars
Beekeeping fourth running
You could see that but it would
I fundamentally change
Probably some pieces of what
Infowars might be the only company that spanfeller could run properly
And you know when you're talking about a retirement match your not
In the business of staying around for very long
And Alex ends with the pretty Doom
Doom soda volume
It's money
Wow. They have all the lawyers
Hold off
Stayed
You know about
Just been money
Black
Anime
Let's let any
Right now it's
Now more than ever with a gun to my head
It is now 100%.
Tell you about the stuff right now but
I got the stick
Is right now
Does about it
And White House is just cut off they just think they say
They can only put out made messages that's about it they're they're cut off as well
So he's got the key they had the carrot now they've got the stick
I just can't help it
Would feel like there's something like as a shoe he knows is going to fall
And I will see
There that means there is a Sikh
Yeah and I don't think you would be saying that about the Sandy Hook case
It's not till the end of the year if it's not even going to be postponed because of the Coronavirus
Easily see that happening
So I don't know it's there's something
Sort of immediate thing he refuses to
To discuss on a RN
Is only a few possibilities a deck
Man this is
I really really will be disappointed if he doesn't
Get
Taken down by this
Something
Soon
Yeah this one
Again I'm going to feel really
Despondent
Like there's just let yourself
You can't let yourself put
Put build too much assumption that you only have to win once
So you can lose and lose and lose and lose and lose but if you wouldn't want to
It's
You know
It's it's done but
And if he just
Keeps escaping this b******* I'm going to be real disappointed
Damn that's a failure on so many people's backs
You know I don't know I don't know
It's it's a situation where like
Probably
We'll end this week
And nothing will happen
But there's a outside chance
Alex could be
Booked this week
I mean no matter what
He's not going to be on
Are most this week probably
Talking to lawyers
Wacky Wednesday
Friday this week
Or will have the best week of Our Lives
Episode of the weekend
Anyway Jordan
We do have a website it smells
We are they literally like that was some reason I choose rate
Review Agoura patreon page or donate to a local charity of your
Clark I am Owen Shroyer in a baby mask
Alex