I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Need
Knowledge fight
Alex Jones
Indeed we are Jordan Jordan related
Somebody's Seltzer's
Year the Year of the seltzer
Drinking whatever Seltzer's I could find
Turbo heater on Twitter
Pictures of all the shelters were drink
Getting a back-and-forth
This quarantine can't hold me back quinine or anything
Every five years of the year of the shelter's like the Chinese New Year the year of the Rat
2020 is going to be the year the seltzer
And an opening Salvo of getting bad business on the Seltzer's
Got this aha aha Cola product
Maybe a little bit disappointed
The got the flavor that seemed the most
Interesting and the most dangerous
It is a cheer
Coffee
Seltzer
We were talking about this before I was scared to try it
I did not know what it was going to be like
Advantage
It really is I'm drinking one as we speak of already almost finished it in the past 10 minutes
Is the coffee flavor isn't really coughing exact comes off like a chocolate and chocolate-covered cherry
But not overly sweet
It's very Define Seltzer and I'm not disappointed to have a couple more of them left in the fridge
Reasons a bright spot is because we're starting out the Earth itself the real straps
Second verse good Seltzer the year
Second you got to take
These bright spots
Who's kind of July
And celebrate little things that are almost meaningless that are still there still really nice
And like you know you can buy a flavor like Cherry coffee and you like I don't f****** know how this is going to go
Well we've got to take a moment and say thank you universe
You have kept me on a good hat
Like the only the only argument I could come up with is
This sounds so crazy the only reason it could
Possibly exist
Is because it has to be good
No way that anybody would be like will it put coffee in black cherry Marriott
Like s*** and then put it in the store
It's not like some weirdo makes these it's a company
They have to have a border around a good idea
But I've also been burned some of those other
I don't know if I should put them on blast
Spindrift
Over the weekend was Corona relief
They had the Summer Games Done Quick lineups all set up and they couldn't do it obviously
Speedrun
Fundraiser that they hastily assembled and they wound up raising
On a last-minute thing and it just makes me feel really good that
People can just
F****** decide as a community be like let's f****** do they
That is very nice together in less than a few weeks
Have it go off pretty well
Shut up Jones Hill game dorks
Never heard of it it's like a it's like Dance Dance Revolution PaRappa the Rapper
That kind of thing and he played it
Our street and is the most complicated thing that I've ever use
An incredible tap dancer
I remember PaRappa the Rapper
Ubiquitous
April 20th
We're going to take
And I look in the box and see who's
First of all
Thank you so much
First name Phil
Last name your hands
Text Laura
Not sure now bazzi walk
So is giving me trouble
Sarah Banks
You never doubt don't want to pronounce it wrong but Terrace last
Very much
So first of all Jeffrey thank you so much
Stoli thank you so much you are now it's
And rolly live show all bring a quarantine bubble for Thomas thank you so much
You are now a technocrat
Heroin
Freakishly large
Jeffrey stahly and thank you so much rolly live so I'll bring the party
Trouble for Thomas
Or please feel free to drink that will help
People who are directly affected
In the worst ways by the troubles
So Jordan it's April 20th it's 4:20
Alex's show
So I figured
Start off
With some chill music getting
Lalaloopsy
Alright
Okay we're doing this
I did that
I don't think the 311 is reggae
Stop it just ridiculous make Alex the least chill out of the world
People who smoke a lot of weed often like 311 and it makes Alex
Loses
Get time to Natural clips
Today's episode here's an out-of-context drop
Haircut
Saturday on the black market
Did the black market haircut man
That's wild
What's fun about that
It's really crazy about this is Alex's buses
Save-A-Lot out there like protesting
But I get busy like I want to get a haircut they have like really
Complicated
Skip 5 minutes
I'm saying that if someone buzzes his head
At this point I would not need anyone to come do it I'll be a waste of money
He's a media personality he needs the finest Buzz haircut
There's literally no
So Alex starts off the show Reign take a bit about vaccines and apparently turns out that
Some vaccine
They're not really vaccines parts of your brain
Because
The globalist
Use these vaccines in order to make sure the people no longer has
The parts of their brain that are spiritual
The part of the brain cease vaccines attack
So you get the vaccine you'll no longer be able to connect with God
Play the man you worship the world government the mark of the beast
They demand that you take vaccines in your body
Engineered viruses literally
Parts of your brain
Associated with religious
My brainwave
Yes ladies and gentlemen that's what's going to be available in the gates
Vaccine
Okay
This is interesting
Because you know in his
Conception
These vaccines are going in in order to disrupt the connection
Between yourself and the divine
Yeah which is weird
Spiritual is no longer a kind of nebulous concept there is a
Like the medulla oblongata if you
You f*** with that a little bit God can no longer talk to you that is what I would like maybe
Electrochemical transmission that is God speaking to you or something
It's not actually spiritual it's all very mechanical
Like there's a physical explanation for why it's a little weird I'm not into it and I just
Reject
Alex has a big narrative today
Takes most of the show
And I'll be honest I'm not going to play him repeating it over and over again
But it does set him off onto a really f***** up sort of space
Complete the very groups that engineered covid-19 and launched
Manitowoc now
Prepared
Cyrus is already patented
Relations with the vaccine
Contracted to use as a digital
With all 7 million people
Under the skin
So you're allowed to buy and sell
Same time it is
Make that up
Recently
As the allegation that Microsoft had applied for a patent
It was essentially the mark of the
Hey why not
The real evidence provided for this traced back to a patent on patentscope
Number 2020 060606
Or at least it appears to be
Cryptocurrency system using body activity data
I read over this thing and it seems really f*****
And it's something I totally opposed to
But it doesn't seem like the mark
It really seems more like a patent for maybe not even something that's real yet that better technology that would allow bile
Metric data to be used in Bitcoin mining computations
Which person
Academic be awarded for
If they wanted to allow their biometric data to be used for said copy
Mutations
So basically like you would have a stimulus from the operation or whatever and then
Rising heart rate or whatever would somehow be used in the computation of the Bitcoin mine instead of
Servers that would be using
Humans like the Matrix like is as a energy source to farm Bitcoin
I don't know about energy source but yeah I mean I'm not into it
I also doesn't seem as like
Sci-fi and f***** up as
The Matrix and also the
Cool thing that I was saying
But if it were something to do like
Betabeat participate in this
I don't really know if I call it wrong or evil
Audi more evidence
But this had any kind of applications outside of what it appears to be for me to be too worried about it
Or even that they can't do this when you file a patent it doesn't mean that you have the technology mean
Down the road we might be able to
However dad there's another issue
And that is that I don't
Think that this patent number is what Alex thinks it is
All that traces back
Tube this post on Patton
And scope but if you search the u.s. patent office
Your real hard time coming up with
Black patent number
There's a number of problem
The first of the patents are numbered beginning with the year of the patent
So I would start with
However the alleged patent patent
That's six digits long
Time to begin with 20/20 and then are followed by seven
Another gigantic problem is that the number doesn't mix
For context an application for patent
Filed on April 16th is number 20 20011 99-82
You can tell the nowhere near Patton starting with 06
It took me forever to find but he searched the US patent and trademark office you can find the exit
US patent number
Which is 20/20
009-7951
The number 2020 060606 is not a patent number
The publication number provided by the world intellectual property office
Exist in the United States
Cooperation
3D people can file their patents with the world intellectual property office The Protector intellectual property
In 184 countries that are members of that treaty
So I guess the bottom line on this is that I don't care
Every year some patent ends up with that number and striving some kind of significance to it seems pretty arbitrary
Every year some patent does number 420 69 or 911
It doesn't mean anything
Also this is not the patent number and even if it were a person applying for a patent doesn't control the number another application
As far as I can tell the defining characteristic of the biblical mark of the beast is that it's something that you need you need to be alive
Allowed to buy and sell things
This patent is not for something that you need to buy yourself
Thanks
Add to that the application number games you know this whole thing and I just end up at a position while I feeling is I don't give a s***
Important point to consider here
Is Alex's reporting things like the mark of the beast being here and real and this specific thing
Can't really be any confusion about how there's not much Road left in front of him
Where do you go after you've escalated your rhetoric so extremely that you've reached the last book of the Bible
When your end times
It doesn't happen
How's Alex ever try again
Like it's one thing to pretend it is dumb radio show averted a gun grab
It's another to pretend that he held back a literal Armageddon
I think that's one of the essential problem
Mixing political conspiracy with religious fanaticism
Political conspiracies on endlessly flowing self-perpetuating in never-ending Road
There's always another secret player you can pin things onto your existing Theory start to look on satisfying
But there's really
Never anything definitive an ultimate about political
Conspiracies
Religious fanaticism on the other hand is a car that's driving directly toward a conclusion
It's fine to use religious fanaticism
The teaser audience or to augment your narratives a little once it becomes a central
Component as it appears to be right now with Alex
It's only a matter of time before you're wrong and at that point it's really hard to explain away your error
Liking someone like Harold that guy who's I tried the end on this date you miscalculated
You'll have a
Retention problems people's face
This is
Anyting
He could
Say that God was like
I got you
Maybe
Seems like a bad narrative to me even from Alex's perspective
It seems alright
I'm kind of
I can understand if things don't work out you can let a little trivial xenophobia base narrative drop
This is the mark of the beast
You can't move on from that like
This piece of the Book of Revelation being fulfilled
Because it demands continued coverage
The train is on the track
I don't know I think they
What where every 5 years we got a new mark of the beast everybody likes Fox News even has a graphic that's like
Some people are saying this is the new mark of the beast like
I think my I think my Gordon it's one thing to say some people are saying cuz of Artemis.
Like sort of almost Local News Human by the way
We have definitively proven
It is the back of the Beast
That will be something better
Escalate to like
I am discussing the ultimate fulfillment of
Mi religion
Prophetic vision of the end times
And then like we do eventually if you still on the air will do something like that
Sales Market Beast
That's only wanted you to think
They're taking it out of context
I find it
I find it kind of weird and maybe sacrilegious that it seems like he's removing space
It's from the entire religious process
Like he even liked with the with the brain
Like he's adding midichlorian
Like that's what the brain stuff
Listeners have pointed out on a number of occasions that Alex
Is clearly a prequel
That's true
So that kind of makes sense if he's more into the Star Wars prequels bad
There is more of a science
See you like a f******
That's so lame that's so lame that God's ultimate Arbiter requires a f******
Well that's because like that that whole like they have to tell you what they're doing
Thank the patent number is a little wink for those like Alex who could see through the b*******
Or whatever
Blame then the devil
Tell me to get up some creativity
Totally
Alex isn't just like basing this on nothing
The 666 really important
3pi 6
Secret number
That is the highest secret of the Illuminati
Implanted in us as part of a ritual
Directions Believe by the sun god
I feel like Alex might be high
420 shows that Alex just pull it out numbers so that we build Magic
22 * 3
Magically becomes
33 * pi 66
6 something-or-other is a secret number
Stop go home 54321
So Alex that's
Boat like as big as
Different narrative from other things
We've covered in the grass
Leaves me cold
I'm not end in Thai
Believe that
He wants them to keep the I keep his name out their mouth
Joy Behar
The View today
You are essential
I look forward to Alex turning this into all the Democrats are saying I'm a terrorist
Like really Auto really basic level
The only things that he really has the right to be like
Really all that mad about our Bill Maher interview
That makes me really sad
It in in contacts
What else what else is he got what else is imaginary
What a loser
So Alex
It complains in this next clip
About how Bill Gates
And the foundations or whatever they're teaching kids are.
With a little game called
Spaceship
That's a game they play on Foundation funding in public
Malfunction Arizona food
We have to get rid of a third of the crew
Who is essential
Well we need the chapter moment even scientists what we need to
Engineer
Engineer volunteer for esta
Blow you out the airlock
Ivolunteer I'm not essential
Lifeboat
We're all going to starve to death
Unless somebody dies
Time
Do we have to die
Don't know if it's going to die
Noble to do that
You're saying no humans are essential
Wild-caught
Not sure they are but also I want I can't quite Alex's denying that there are
Situations like those
Describe the most thought experiment
Like to volunteer to sacrifice yourself to allow
Other people too
It's kind of a foundation of
Your life so that other people visit is an expression of love and care for other people
Globalist
Pressure Jesus into going up on that cross did you know that
He didn't want to do that but Bill and Melinda Gates
In time they got the globalist brainwashed Elisha
I'm not even actually the Son of God they made the whole thing up
Yeah
I think that Alex is just maybe mad that one of his kids is learning vitality arianism
Okay these are just like really basic philosophical Concepts oh
Utilitarianism
Does more people survive
Is Lifeboat
Make it
Moral to pressure someone
Do not survive in the Lifeboat
It's an open question
Have you heard the game that they're playing now with kids it's called
Like so you got a train right and you have control over the train and you can either turn it so it kills five people
1 people
Have you heard about this game
Find a way to kill six people
You have to you have to not
Do anything
And it kills
Do something
Was like really just like 101 philosophical
6 total
What happened
If you multiply that
333 phone number
Secret
Back to the mark of the beast idea
It's pretty clear that Alex is like
This is it
This Is the End
Next countries news today
Gators today
Oh my goodness
And goddamn step in Step Up
Jay garlick because the
That's only in the first
Then the shaman
Bruce Spring
God dammit
Man place
Bruce is just going to come.
The devil versus God
Oh I got out I got daughter
He's going to come in he's going to put the globalist into a Tenth Avenue freeze-out
It was going to happen
We got we got one scene on drums I'm feeling great about that the force ghost of Clarence Clemons coming back
Play some horn
Bro you know it's it's
It seems so crazy to me that whenever these type of guys see there
Personal incoming they always say that the end times are coming is that a weird coincidence
Always happen at this
It is very strange so weird
I think
I think there is a lot
To the ax perhaps but knows I mean
Pretty f*****-up episode like
It's not like he's not doing well
That also could just be because the Beast is coming I could be that I forgot about.
We just played
Does it still count if it supposed to close 6
All right there we go
You got me
You want
Who have understanding reckon the number of the Beast
Fuller's
A human number
Sabbath
Umbrella man
I think that Alex is just riffing from the Iron Maiden song Number of the Beast
Not revelation
The tip-off for me was that he said it was a quote
Quote a human number
Which is right from the lyrics of that song but it's not in the Bible
Corrected it to quote the number of a man
Regardless this theory has had some real problems that he needs to explain
The verse is at the mark of the beast according to revelation
It is the work of these beasts
Like some prophecy coming true
Filter
Dunn tribute salted Obama
Even be like
The second beast is the UN
The first Beast was the League of Nations
House is really good if you predicted the entire un being the second base
Some good stocks got a baby is the best
Yeah Alex's pretty mad about masks masks it's a sign of Yusef
Admitting it because he's selling too many of them well that is a conflict even existed missive
Very short clip
But I just wanted to
Let you in if
But only 6 months if you don't
Grocery stores anywhere
Right now in Austin
Are black
Infowars.com
Shoot your mouth off talk about how it's a fraud plug websites
Whatever
I love
The idea that
Look
Design of submitting to the globalist agenda
I'm sorry I can't take this mask off real quick
Have you guys heard about the mark of the beast
Saw it it's a real bad sign
Hahaha just
Did this is Stacey stupid dumb assholes
Would you like to buy it
So this leads to Alex freaking out a little bit could it be selling a story
About
What happened to him this morning
Apparently you want to grocery store
People were concerned that he wasn't wearing a mask
So he starts yelling at them
Course maybe got escorted out by security
Clear from the telling of this story
The store this morning
Buy some groceries
Where you stupid gloves
Do something
I see how it makes everybody a suspect
What is xiumin called essential others are called non-essential
That's beyond racism
Subhuman
And I said no
Follower
God why you so mad
Oh you thought I was going to kiss your ass
You and your family are dead in the global they're going to kill your ass when you submit to this
Trapping I'm leaving
Are you in the future, like a farmer something
Get on you
Valentino's in Delavan
Put you under their control
Not good
So close
I don't believe that story happen necessarily but if it didn't happen quite like that
Small security cameras
Sir sir why are you so angry
Have you not read the
The new zombies
Goodbye everyone all you dumb assholes
All you dumb assholes wordmaster mad at me
Hey everybody not wearing masks in here you are absolutely right but also you need to buy Mass to be in here
Imagine Medical
That's that's
Pretty fun
That is why I'm selling masks to you
This Nightclub not quite as fun Alex has a bit of a
Conspiracy about hospitals being empty
That's a doctor's order just drinking vodka and f******
I'll leave it at that
They're doctors and nurses
I don't believe you
Indiana California other places
Giant VA Hospital
Why
This is a giant vacation
Okay
Because the insurance companies
All of these opium
What
Do Anthony surgery areas and they'll get
Harper digit
This is back
Seems unconnected as a thought maybe
Hundreds of them out of the hospital
2030 Anastasia
Everywhere
But the Opium addiction despise
Text parking lot
A joke
That's not sad experience that I've heard from
Somebody
Care Professionals by whatever Alex
I mean like I don't know maybe maybe his dad
Is it
I'm just drinking booze
Drunken noodle okay having barbecues of his Park
What I would say that I needs a little more than Alex's supposed to relatives
Word on
I don't think Anonymous sources are the way I'm going to go on the
So there's something that I was hasn't said
Yet
Uno's
Or something
This is really mysterious and I'm not
I'm not entirely sure what he's trying to get out
I'm not joking I'm doing the show and then I'm eloquently in most cases covering all those facts
Eloquently
There's something I haven't said yet
Conscious all but your conscience should notice
Do you think about all day
About that business partnering
Commenced
What did miss it was fraud or
Your daughter you didn't notice at the time but later you thought about it in
Conscious is a thousand times or more
He called the subconscious the connection of the universe it's not just
Medical Orion
When I come back from break because I wasn't able to segment in Anaheim
To Shook Up do it again
Epic this is so real is everything happen when it was coming and I just
Where watch billions died
Murdering people in mash and people are just dying everywhere
Finally wake up
Something up here
He's not saying what this thing is
Not positive that he does
It's weird civilians are going to die but you need to understand about that
Is it there is a bit of a timeline issue
They're not really clear on sure
Could be tomorrow
Could be five years
Take more time than
Tomorrow
75 years
5 years ago
We're going to see the Antichrist they're going to be having sex with kids on TV
You're going to see
Ocean die in nuclear war billions dead
Unconnected
Oceans are going to die God sucks if he's real in oceans are going to death
Probably just because
A lot of his doing
So Alex is talking about like there's a difference
You know you have your soul
Give your flesh
No you just have one spot in your brain which is also party
Prisma captain that one part of your brain that they're trying to get rid of
According to Alex because if you can get a back seat ruined your soul
Then it's physical thing
Who cares
Alex believes that the
Flash
Wants to side with Sade
Ensure
The fight my flesh My Flesh
Play sadness and submit to the New World Order
Your flash
It kind of wants to side with Satan
Decide what my spirit is like
Get out of your pee
Get me out of here get me out of here get me out of here
Oh no my friend here going to
My children and my family
Godlike hey you decided to have them
If their Spirit right getting close to godson
Why you still
Because I'm going to destroy the Earth
Okay
Is he just an alcoholic is that
I'm not positive
Face the Dragon
Trying to get me a legendary wolf
You know what do they think it's interesting that he's presenting his dichotomy between his Flagship his spirit
Go to that must stand up inside
Right you said explicitly multiple times that his plan is to go to a
Seems like his flashes
Oh yeah it's already
Express the plan to follow the flash what did you not know he got the MMR vaccine
Is connection to the spirit world
Manny's in connection with spirit world
Alex is Flash
Is evil
He wants you to know that
I mean I already assumed that
Is Flash
Balisco military 11
My God
Conscious
Cuz I know you're there too
I am not
Addieville
We know
Oh yeah God do is not something I want
Big boy pants on
Because
Because you are facing your watching an interdimensional satanic
Fish in the science fiction movie it's not something
To the Draco Maybe
You talk to Carrie about this you been Consulting kept in Park Ridge
I was thinking earlier that is his view on how is flesh and spirit
Eerily similar to
Carrie being like
No you can only get the virus if you will visit if your will is broken and you can't fight it off with your own brain powers
There's there's some similarities pretty deeply into like
You know the interdimensional attack happening it might as well be aliens
No it's the end times
Sure
Being announced through this patent
Intercourse and Alex
Kind of
Giving up
Huseby makes it pretty clear in this next clip
Find
Very outside of the norm for his rhetoric
No one can
Can beat this
No one can be.
Better get on your knees
You better get on your knees before the Creator
None of us with no matter how strong we are
We cannot
I tell you that
Not happy right now
I wouldn't you be happy
What the hell does that mean
Do you not understand the words
Thousand-Year information
God literally
Do you think there's all that damn game phone
Is the real deal
This isn't a simulation
Solar system
Built For This operation
You don't think God created beings with free will
How are the universe right away
What
Image of God
With free will
Red
So I mean that's just the this world is a test
Interesting to me
It is interesting that he saying that no one can beat this
Regular info
The devil
August 1st once at the bar
Robert why we're going to take you down finished
Do you know what hey
You can't win
Yeah, seems like that means that people should stop funding the info the only reason that you fund
So we can fight that you were funding a Winning Side
Boats but whatever I mean
Yeah I guess you bought him an armored
Cuz of God because you bought so much my Patriot Supply he got a really good deal
Yeah yeah so great
Oh boy
The reason why we can't win is because these are bullies Spaceteam
They were fighting against
And Alex discusses how they operate
These are
Bad preachers
You're ugly to the Earth
Isak
We got rid of
Everywhere these entities go in Creation in the universe
They are throwing out on their asses
Where else have they gone
And so these are bullies
God can't even comprehend.
Around
That is a really great question that you asked because it doesn't fly there are a ton of inhabited planets
These bullies face Stevens have gone to wherever it out of here get out of here by Steven
That is a piece that Alex does not unpack question support
Patrol around the universe going to other uninhabited on Mercantile.
Okay I'll get logical cats and kicked off that planet
Looking for
An egg
Giant space baby
The engine hear me though
Area for it
Like a virus
The planets
All eggs
Get in
To tell us
What to do
So
That's what's going on
Demons
Space Belize
Kindergarten cross that one off and we officially have bingo
So earlier Alex said he has his flesh
Is a spirit
Spirit says fight the dragon right
Flash says
Leave
Hi up let's get your face with the dragon
Precious one
Directive
Impossible
In the mud
Spiritual nature of having chickens
The nature looking up at the stars at night
We have to nail move from warning about the mark of the beast
The moving into the defensive posture
You're awesome taking your kids and cut your heads off the bed
What
We've done our work
Broadcast
Affordable Suits now
As long as possible
That is amazing
Why
Why would I
For your own purposes perhaps but in terms of like
To get it so Alex can
Make money stupid
I mean like when I heard that clip the only thing I could think is are clotted for Wars over
Like that you were you've lost the info or not exactly
There isn't anything else to do I will be on the air for a while maybe we'll stick around
If you give us some more about who try to stick around but
There's nothing you can do the enemies can't be defeated
Whatever I'm going to go put my feet in the mud
F****** procor that was
Chicken
Starting his own reasoning
You're better off getting your head chopped off then buying store
Yeah be right with God but you can buy my food
Kill yourself
YouTube
The the other thing too that I kept thinking about during the eclipse was there like back in 2017
I don't remember what episode was on but there was an episode where Alex is crying
Talking about how you wished you was just a farmer
The life he should be living as he should have made a bunch of money on the supplements and stuff
A gotten outrageous hide
Take a new life
Yep Wyatt away from everything
There was no end to this that was good
If he could have
Gotten out then no one would have probably even considered
All the things that are getting him sued now so like those lawsuits wouldn't exist
He could just have a really happy life with his chickens
Many crops need more than a couple million dollars probably to live out the rest of his life
Insomnia
He's going to be too
Probably
That that's like oh that's a realistic thing
He couldn't have done you f***** up yeah back then he was crying about how he wished that's what he was going to do and now hit the
Appears that the universe made of forest
And now he's going to do that but it's going to
Also come along with
A real public Fall From Grace
Is going to be
An extent to which like he's going to have to take
Compare
Who knows but like he knows that this is Bissell
Is Don pretty much over
2nd nature he kept stopping
If you wasn't selling anything you'd still do an ad pivot just did nothing
Well we're here just so you know
Just go ahead and get your nothing anywhere you got it we got it in store for 4999 if you get it on auto-ship
You get it for 4599
Again it is not
Don't worry about it just give me 45.
So he's ceu selling the food there that leads to hand sanitizer that he
Sanitizer
Eucalyptus peppermint
Attack formation
Weird
If you give us money you know who keep us afloat yeah destructions going to be spectacular
Well now
Now you're just buying fireworks
The more money you give him the more spectacular
Try to be more money
Knots that doesn't Inspire confidence that feels pretty bad
Just a nice little
Controlled burn do you want a hood and with a
Your choice
We're going to have
We're going to do a Facebook poll will see how you guys do
It cost one bottle of Beethoven to vote
I don't really care about it's not really important but I'm going to play it just for fun
To give you
Demonstration
Do you want to see what the modern Hitler looks like bug
Zuckerberg
All the time and I never play it I never play things like that because that would be stupid right that would be
I know he met Mark Zuckerberg
Other one right people misspeak all the time
It's not like hey Alex you're so stupid you don't even know it's Mark Zuckerberg
But you know what there are people who do s*** like that Alex would probably do something like that
Losi clip where she speaks and he's like
Employees doing
What the f***
This is I wanted to play with as a demonstration just to be like
I could do that to any point
Yeah because
6.8 people misspeak
Any wife
This is where things get real
Alex
May have tried to make
Some
Kind of social media website
Sure
I don't know what this is about
But apparently it failed
You know I create a website
That offer me again of the email I'll cover right now actually get that
Everybody always trying to use Twitter
Facebook
Could we create a website and get people's emails
Take it down so I can go right
Because we're
Habituated
The Facebook and Twitter and Google
I want to promote the site we launched
You programmed it's over man
He wants
They
Get
You
Programmed
Aldous Harding
Let's go ahead and
That is very important
Whew Alex leaves again
It's like everyday now
I can't do the Shelf
And you'll just play special reports
Let's
I know that in the past like
Even outside of our little like maybe last six-month time frame
There were occasional times and he would do when he would do that but it was usually pretty extreme for him to leave the show
I guess go do an interview on another show right reason for it
Oblong or something
It's everyday now and it's
Only
Is
Like feeling yeah
And his feelings are
Try to make a f****** social media
It doesn't work
No one wants it
F*** it I'm just coming
Why would we launch this until
Done
As a really good question
I keep hearing is just in
A consistent and insinuations that like
F*** it
F*** it there's no Road left
Confronted
The wheels are off
We were done
We're basically
It feels like he's wrapping up
The show without actually saying yeah yeah
Absolutely even if he didn't
I just don't
I can't escape that like
That's the escalation towards
Revelation the Deep state
If it's just
Yeah he is existing through the end times
And I think he would prefer it
If everyone else was
To he's very disappointed that
Seems to be the only person is really getting
End times
Narcissists love it when other people feel the same
So Alex talked a little bit more gear about his experience
At the store this morning
What are y'all two people
Whole new area
This morning and people get to my face about the bass
Stupid mask you're selling them also
A mask isn't 100
Assigned to protect you
From Catching something as much as
Does it is to protect other people in case you are
I already sick
Part of what makes vaccines functional is it makes it
So you can't give it to other people who are either immunocompromised
Take vaccines for some reason it's it's more protective for other people really sexy large
Part of
The rationale for
Announcers doesn't understand that
The globalist
To want you to protect other people
Can like we've seen they want you to line up and sacrifice yourself or others so
That means that helping other people
People is actually part of the globalist
Altruism is a plan of the Bowie Space demons who go around and find eggs
How else would they trick us
Play Alex believes of the globalist they're trying to take his kids
Well
Public
That's
April 20th that's where we are
But that's not anything other than your ex-wife
That's your ex-wife globalists
Their mother whose concern for their well-being because you went to a f****** rally in the middle of a pandemic
Yeah you put your kids in danger in theory yes the argument could be made pretty wild that is the case
I will talk about the the custody stuff
On this at the show for a very specific reason as I've no idea what's going on
Interpersonal level is not our business Alex tries to present like
Flight being some sort of politically-motivated thing as opposed to it being
This is a dispute between you and your ex-wife don't try and pretend
That this is some Soros
Plan Gates trying to take you out
Cockamamie b*******
And that's that that is again the same sort of thing that I think
Like through almost all of Alex
Stop this
The perception that he
Is this
Drastic political purse
Persecution
And it's massive fight against demonic
Otherworldly
Forces and what have you
I really
It's just ups and downs in his personal life
And he can never be
Can Satan never see himself as anything other than the champion and the good guy
At no point
Point-in-time could he ever for once Avid moment of introspection
And be like oh yeah so you know I mean it is kind of reasonable to think that if I go out and share it
Space with a lot of other people who may be infected then I'm putting my children at risk so
My ex-wife very logically would say that I should not be anywhere near my children
This makes perfect
I made a mistake
I don't know all the like variables are play but I just think like on a very basic level
You do have a pretty
Decent argument that if someone is behaving in ways that are going to make them more likely
To possibly catch this
That's awesome babe
Don't
They should be
Sequestered
I don't know you should we should
She probably
Put some
Aluminum on top of his door
Make sure that
He's not a vampire
What if he's a vampire
That was that the only thing that makes sense to me at this point isolate himself
Beast kids are filled with blood and he loves that s*** now he's in trouble
Could be
Mentioned earlier the David Icke was coming up
Scrape man
Great this is bad news
I want to hear
From David Icke
This is bad news bad is really what I was looking for a lot of people
Leave it to David Icke
To try and outdo all of them
Ocean
Oh boy
So David Icke believes that there is no virus
Fake virus
What you mean
Oh maybe or maybe it's just other things that are being called
Covid-19
Maybe it's 5G I've no f****** idea
This is interesting though because Alex at all always been trying
To present it as David Icke was talking
About 5G
There's no virus because there isn't
And that's the point that he's making on this episode
And what's interesting
Is the Alex
Carnival Cruises
They're not debating it almost all the tests false identify
Coronavirus is dead
Whether you're totally right it's all fake
Alex's order coming
Coming around a little is like saying that there is no virus
Nothing you can say
Right on there are these
Tested false positive
Talk myself into this
Realize
There is no spoon did you realize what there's no smoke
It takes almost no time at all for David
To convince Alex that there isn't
Antivirus
You can lose control of it
If you
You
Wow
That was fast
That's pretty amazing
He put together a really good argument for why it's not a biome
Because it would be a bad idea to release a bioweapons we said that matzo
Exactly
So that's a good argument
For why it's not a biome
His next step
I think is where he falls
That's usually how it goes a David ATVs bad for you
Lizards
Answer I can't go long you there
What's interesting to me about this
Is
That
For Alex to believe
That this is a fake virus
He has to
Get rid of
So much
Dial
The whole thing
The game of function
Whole thing about the UNC Chapel Hill
That was dumb
Viruses are fake but the perception of a virus I like it I like this for him as a noodle
Action to go in
Well yes that incredibly stupid so why not just go even further
Go harder band I mean it's the difference between trying to construct
Conspiracy narrative
And just engaging in blind to nihilist
No
You don't like it
Because it's not true
Why not
Just do it like this especially not over for Humanity and there will be way more than
Survivors mainly because apparently the virus didn't even exist in the first place
Man
Yeah Mike Adams is a really bad Health rating
He doesn't know what he's talking about
This is such a Hallmark of Alex's ship though like
This is why you so stupid
That's because like
That is him agreeing with David Icke
Later though I captured by tomorrow he'll be like
We're just discussing both sides
I have opposing viewpoints the conversation
We talked and you know what
Everybody I believe is very trustworthy sometimes I will agree with something that completely wipes
About the past
Months of my reporting I would largely agree with just about anything some crazy wingdings has to be on my show
That being said
Contradiction
Explicitly said
And I'll still agree with them because they're crazy it is fun
This is where I want the spirit of Bill Cooper to come in and just s*** all over.
David Icke be nice
He did not like David Icke as well that's that's for sure
Here is I
I hate to say this because I obviously can't prove this
But the sense that I get is a pay-to-play
Situation
I
Kind of feel like David Icke might be paying for airtime Alex is profiting off this because
There is a trend that goes through this like the interviewers Alex's is letting David Icke say all this stuff
Invariably
Sporadically not interrupting him all that much
And then
After a couple segments
Alex is like for my own selfish reasons I want to talk about what I want to talk about
If this is one example of a
Hospital
Should be
3/4 a lot of great points in your main topic what about
400,000 signatures
We'll pass the number they need a lot out. Gunn daveste bowling 12-gauge
I don't know if that proves anything but there's a real feeling of like all right you had your time now
I could think of you also just be an arrangement between the two of them because like
For both of us
I don't know it's it's very weird there's there's a
There's a dynamic it plays that is not organic
It is not normal
I think that might be a part of why Alex is so
Happy to be like
That makes total sense that have a fake virus if you want to control it yeah
Because he's
Basically in agreement of some sort to
Platform David Icke idea
Ben. s*** on them if you'd like to know
I have proven this is a real virus and
It is a Franken virus yep
With HIV parts inside
It's been literally proven he said many many times
Can't be swayed by David Icke saying it's fake
You can't
Fake fruit
I mean obviously the proving is fake
I could also so you just Alex
Not giving a s***
At all
That at that you know if he if he's willing to walk off his show just special
Video I could see him taking this opportunity to be like
I got my sandwich ready
Had to
I don't have to work right now I'll just chimed in and be like yeah that sounds right
Possible explanations
And the only reason that comes to mind
For me is I like
This is exactly how it would play out if it was like brokered programming
Just like whatever the f*** I don't care say whatever you want to say
Bandidas ideas about and then you'll help me with my s***
Sell anything of his own me I'm sure it's between
Katana ship on the show
See that would make me like is also like
Much more established and find that I'm being sued by everybody
I'm sure that you more like to get out the there is no virus
Alex needs
Do use them as best you can
And so does and I'll tell you unless you're clear on a major operation interested level as they can
And the fact we're here bring you guys like David Icke
But they've already went one use food to control you
Will high-quality trouble food
Nobody else does these prices
No it's all me David Icke saying they're going to use food to control you but you can
Control back by buying my food
Okay
The main thing like David Ike's interviews are always so goddamn boring in the end
The same sort of stopped
Over and over again with weird
Noises and stuff awful
Big thing is there is Novi
That is his
Pieces
For this
Which makes it troubling this
Mainstream calls
Get what you're after Alex Jones
You don't even have Spirit behind that s***
Call Elizabeth interview
Play happier
Expat
They are like this is a better way to go
Just deny the virus
Some of the people on the staff
At a point where they realize I
We're in over our head we're on the water
Gone all over the place and and not found respite
Baby
Faver-dykes there is no virus narrative is the simplest solution
Yeah that doesn't seem like the path of least resistance
It would have been
But the problem now is explaining away view old narratives
Like you if you now shift
Do there is no virus
You have to explain why you were wrong when you proved that there was
Vagina Georgia
I know you and I would
Yeah
It's real frustrating
So this
This is the thing that I find the most interesting
This entire episode picture
Alex
Reporting on patent 666 or whatever is
That's that's whatever
Little bit
Boring
I find it fascinating to David Icke is allowed to come on his show and say there is no virus
And he agrees
And he's convinced
Are you going to fit into a conditional could instantly
After after that clip I played he's convinced David I can walk back a little bit
But you can't
If you believe anything that you're saying
You can't even conditionally agree with her
You know thing
You don't
Pink things you know things
Oh no here I got this
I got this easily for you
Okay
There is a virus
But it was not release
So all of the proof about them selling the virus and all that stuff that's all true
However
They just have the virus and they never actually released the virus
Only because they have the virus
They can say they release the virus
To create the panic and then if anybody asks WI
I've got the virus right here I know it's real
Done
Figured it out there is a virus and I've even proven that to me I agree with there being nobody
Jordan is just done the work for you
It took a long time
So the other thing
Beyond is just this sense of Doom
Like Alex saying that there is no way to win
I'm going to the woods
F*** it
8 minutes out the show ends to
The time is coming up hopefully with connections ready
AR
Prodigy the game
Capitol Beer and like beating somebody attacks but
I just didn't hit it before it spread the word usually more going to like these horrible to India right now
That's not
Does this feeling of like
Buy this stuff
We're done anyway I thought we had money to make it the rest of the year
Ouija
Yeah and I mean like we talked about the the bankruptcy case on our last step
Episode and I'm 50-50 on thinking like that
It felt like
This is this is a real
Eminem
Feeling
I really don't think that you would be feeling
I don't think you be acting like this
If it weren't
If it were just a situation with this abstract
November or whatever end-of-the-year court date for
Sandy Hook stop
Don't think he'd be acting like this
If it was these
Warnings that he's gotten from the FDA and the New York attorney general because those things are things that
He can result
Yeah he can't change his actions
And cooperate with the process
And continued without any consequences
There's something like this
Sword of Damocles hanging over his head
And I can't tell how much of this is me talking myself into believing
Yeah that's a good question
It definitely feels like he's fun
And he knows
And it's not like
In the past where he you know he's doing this and then
You know he'll just bounced back the next day
This seems like
He's already for like
Resigned
To the point where he's saying
It doesn't matter if you buy buy food
We're all going to die anyway
Like there is no way to win
So
If you're not if he's not even selling
Then I think we all know that
That means it
It's it's over
Right you still selling
Yeah but listen to
Yeah he's not himself I don't know
I know that he was in studio on Tuesday on the 21st I know that
So we will still have some
Thread to follow for the end of the week but
I don't know man I'm excited
It's going to be gone from Al Pacino to Jack Lebanon like
Like four months in a different movie
Yeah
It's a rollercoaster
We'll see what happens I mean I'm curious to see if on Tuesday we think I was still thinks that the virus is fake I have no I
Be back on
You have website it's also
We aren't underscore fight not go to bed Jordan
Israeli review patreon page and if you'd like please donate to a local charity of your
Yeah I also will be back
Up until then I'm Neo
I'm Leo and bcx Clark I am the bully space demon
Holding
Alex
Same color my huge fan I love your work