Air Jordan
Nola.com
I have great respect for its knowledge B
We are the bad guys
Need
Alex Jones
Seed we are Dan Jordan Jordan
Whatsyourprice
You go first
I will tell you right now
Obviously stir crazy
Part of the way I express that was bleeding
Cabin Fever
No I I purchase chocolate Lucky Charms
Oh yeah yeah
However
If you put them in some yoga
Black cherry yogurt
Specifically intersec incredible absolutely incredible delicious
Complimentary flavor profile
Strange but it works out well here's what I would say
That's not a good sign
That sort of a purchases
A little iffy
You won't be in a crisis and less you get that Captain Crunch
Cotton candy cotton candy
Boxes of Captain Crunch that ice cream
If you buy one of those
You got it you got it now it's time to call it help
I don't know what
I guess the bright spot is the yogurt pairing with it I guess it's okay
Just that turned out to be
Here's my brights by Jordan
You believe the seltzer
Is more than just drinking seltzer
What do you got
Okay I believe that
To do is we need to look at it as a metaphor we need to look at it as a thing
We all like soda so delicious
You don't need to do better
You can have a seltzer water
Calories
The number of cases you can take away the caffeine I don't want that don't need it anyways that we can break the chains
The binder
And two unhealthy habits yeah
Marches On
I have nothing
Ivan update
In the spirit of aspiration
Surrounding the year of the Celsius it is this
I am making the committee
Call God
There aren't even 500
Absolutely. 500 difference I have not looked it up
But I guarantee there are you better
And I'm willing to do it
More than one a day which is going to be tough
A SR20 is the beginning of it
PO420 2021b
End-of-the-year of the seltzer
As opposed to
That was easy that's number one that's the first seltzer
Of the year and I have two new ones
Sure I'm on my way
Okay
The pretty good okay and then I went to the store and I saw that Luke had a new flavor limoncello
Forget
Who is interesting and has like a lemon vanilla
Kind of vibe
Great Mary some alcohol okay
Desert boozes
I'm going to do I have a
Notebook right now
Eventually we'll end up having
Being spreadsheet
I will be giving updates on every episode
Out of 100
Now the scale will obviously become more refined as time goes on
But I have given the AHA black cherry coffee and 83 out of
Holyshit
Well if it's under 50 that means
Bad
Over 50 is good and I think that I probably elevated that one a little higher than it needs to be by think it was out of
Surprise openings
Yeah I think I got that first bump
Yeah where you're like
This is the one that also I embarked on my journey it's really hard to uncouple from the like
This was so much better than I thought it was good.
But 83 I'm going to stand by it
Baby maybe
By September November will be looking back on.
I can't believe I did that but whatever
Orange grapefruit
Giving a 7277
Not as good not as good at also wasn't at there wasn't any
I accidentally I found myself leaving the can
Time I got to the bottom of it
It wasn't like ice cold and it really suffer
Okay it was very tough
I do think 73 is too hot
Lacroix limoncello we will have a rating by the end of September
Not yet
Got to finish it before it could be done
Okay alright
This is
Stir Crazy very exciting
Very interesting
Personal statement discuss April 21st and 22nd
Business and making the year of the seltzer
The first spring
Like bright
Express
Text Laura thank you so much you're now probably want
Russell
I'm a policy wonk
Christine with a k
Thank you Christine
Thank you very much altimate so now one of these like if he saw dragons
People who donated on elevator
Tinker's Dam
Thank you so much
Freakishly large
Ida Claire
Edward thinks much tinker's Dam and thank you so much Aaron
Area and
Oakside
Be very grateful if you did either
Jordan yes sir
We can't start the episode yet
There's more business.
Shelter update has been made
First thing is the recordings on Thursday and this is the day that Alex's bankruptcy
Hearing was supposed to happen
And we don't know exactly what's going to happen because by the time we started this episode
Consult the docket
This morning
Oz ex-wife
Filed an emergency motion
She's trying to get Alex's lawyer disqualified on the basis that she says
That the two of them have an existing relationship
From back
Preclude him from representing him in this case
Bring Barnes back
Order motion the cheese filed
I am feeling that she was like
A motion to continue
Which would be to postpone it
So there's a very decent chance that by the time
By the time this episode comes out the hearing baby postponed
It's also possible that that motion
Feels like we mislead
Anyone we did not we were going on the information that was available and this morning
Thursday morning great emergency motion was filed
Satisfy
Goddamn Jones family yeah so that's a little bit of a bummer but the other bit of business is a little bit more of a
It is my birthday and I thank you very much
I'd like to just take a moment to say thank you some folks you know sent nice things
Sandman and presents
Sweet
Right I need to apologize for that publicly
Dragon Queen Christi for sending very nice
Absolutely also Kelly
Need to say thank you
Me talking about how Netflix password
And gifted me a Netflix account
I unfortunately have not been able to open it yet because I haven't had time but I intend to sue
What's a little bit more free time
Also you Jordan
URI gave me a copy of Final Fantasy 7
So thank you very much for that
I really had a whole lot of time to get I did play a tiny bit last night
I don't
It's not my style of game but I definitely enjoyed the opening of it
Probably enjoy it but it'll take a little of just
But we'll see
Oberlin finally my friend Adrian got me a very nice
It's a brand
Understand it is a favorite of the
Canada
And so we have a little bit of a spruce beer
So I've no idea what to expect
Butts
That is pretty good
What is a ginger to survive to a
It doesn't help I feel pine needles I've ever eaten I feel fine
I'm not sure if eating a pine needle but I feel like I have
What you qualify as part of the year the seltzer
It's not very beer like now
Not at all. I was I noticed that I had the champagne
Cleanliness
Clear it doesn't have eight
Yeah it's very much seltzer
Yes nice
Delish
Let's get down to business hour episode many thank yous and good tidings to all
They're coming for your balls
Alright alright
Alright
Focus in quite a bit on the idea that the coronavirus is specifically designed to attack men's balls
I'm happy
Cool
So we starting on the 21st and Alex's still mad at Joy Behar interview because
To these
These are protests against corn beans and
Measures
Are terrorists
And he's not happy
Here's Joy Behar
People are being
Right-wing media people like
Rush Limbaugh
Bringing guns to a rally
Protesters
Thomas Jefferson
And it was paraphrasing Beaver the data
When the government
Here's the people there is Liberty when the people for the government
First of all I don't under percent agree with Joy Behar
Necessarily inappropriate thing to say like to do
Really see how that
Could be applied
All sorts of directions
Some sort of a terrorist Act
This should surprise no one but that is not a Thomas Jefferson quote
It's commonly misattributed to Jefferson as well as to Thomas Paine but Monticello the world's foremost authority on the word
The writings of Thomas Jefferson
About no evidence
The Jefferson ever said that
In researching the source of this quotation the Thomas Jefferson encyclopedia reports the first note appear in
Prince was in 1914
In an indictment of socialism delivered by John Basile
Provident
Interesting Lee it's currently Barnhill birthday
So happy birthday to him as well as me
This quote comes from a debate Barnhill head with socialist writer Henry Kitchener
And in the context of the debate it's very clear the Barnhill is not quoting or citing an existing a
Expression those are his own words
It wasn't until 1994 that is gray was first repackage and presented as the words of Thomas Jefferson
In a book called It's All In the game butterflies
Control The Razor's Edge
This book was written by. William Somerset mouth
Which is the name that most people would not recognize
You spell because I did a thorough breakdown of Alex's film endgame
Name rings a bell for me
Giorgio Sirius Hatton is
The guy who was one of the big sources for Daniel estulin book the true story of the Bilderberg Group
Which Alex uses a
As a Cornerstone of his theories about that
Hatton
Of course is not a reliable source
Here's how Hatton describes himself
Quote
I'm Giorgio Sarah Earth Project transition Pleiades sector flight command
Lactic Federation Fleet command
Earth representative to the cosmic Council in The Intergalactic Federal
Federation Council on Earth transition
Hold on one second
Hat is a Nutty space space weirdo
But he used to at least sell colloidal silver 1990
Let's debate and reintroduce it as a quote from Thomas Jefferson
It's not a Jefferson quote but since that point people have regularly Miss attributed it to him
Again this is Alex Jones having no actual connection to history of the founding fathers of this country he professes to love some
He doesn't love this country or actual history
He loves come
Completely nonsensical conspiracy theory
Revisionist history and what he generously called
Patriot mower
Another words
He's living a fantasy land he loves
His founding fathers who bear no resemblance to the actual
Yes yes
So obvious when you look at like the the quotations that he is
So Alex
I think he realizes that on his previous days episode on the 20th
David Icke was on he said there was no virus
Is it by this point that that was like oh wait that's a problem
Doc's here
People lie
David Knight
Mike Adams
David Icke
When it's completely normal
The government and the media
That's been caught lying. So much over and over again to question everything and that
And you should do it
With David Icke
That virus science is in
Shouldn't need to say that but okay
Iman
We don't have one view like CNN or MSNBC and imperative
No Yuri you affirm
I've been pretending
It's fine is norovirus your response needs to be what
Talking about
Just be like oh my God Bingo you nailed it goes
Problem was not
David Icke
Views always Alex's response to David that you allow him to say these things
But you double down on them
Totally right
Fox News
Would you guys are crazy houses on his smooth transition towards that same
It's disgusting but none of them will be held accountable
Disgusting of things that Alex is definitely.
He's now really firmly of the position
That's how those videos that were coming out of China
That he was reporting on as being totally real
Are now obviously fake.
Put a video about they don't like
Not all these videos.
It was staged
The welding shop
Safe
Garbage
All of it
Was
Not real
So those are all things that he has reported as very real in the past
Is because the only time I'll ever be a third grade plays like his kids
And feel good
Dad whenever he says your place
Playlist
I'm trying to be supportive. Did you suck at acting
Nobody nobody cares about
Yep that's not great
He does from time to time I kill off and talk about how his websites being under hack attack
Attention
He does that on this April 21st episode
This is
This is absolutely did not
5-minute video
Video stranger down
A child
Satellite TV
The fiber-optic
Milk
Look up contact for the roof
Virus
Attacks
Gcn feeds of Alex Jones Show
Involved
This reminds Becky Emilio Estevez was still an actor
This reminds me a lot of Bill Cooper to honestly there's another thing that I'm retired cover eventually in the future but there was
There is like a number of times throughout bills career specifically under attack
Answer also tradition among conspiracy theory
Castro's two
Create
Sort of dramatic
Parks around Vero
You have to create the presentation that what you're doing is somehow dangerous
The only way to do that is to
Manufacturer
Nothing is being
Terry is under attack by aliens
Whenever there's any Tech glitches
Because aliens are interfering
Consistent meanwhile we have Dal good luck man
My stuff's not that good
My my soundboard is a little old
We're talkin into cheap Mike's still haven't gotten that compressed air yet
Do it again
Alex's pretty mad that the media
The BET of the bad guys
That he has the
To divide us or something
He has the Cure
Alex and his next clip is complaining about how his friends
Believe that
The media says that he said it so they're asking for the Cure
Sure this is
Convoluted
But
The thing that's important is the
You have to recognize so many of these complaints that Alex has
Trace back to him having conversations
With stupid people he chooses to associate with
So
You can't
You can't generalize this to the population
Close to that
Steve pieczenik
You still run that headline
Colin Dolan
No I don't know
People that know me
French
Oh my God my mom no
Do you have the chair and I'm like no but the news says you have it
Media so little
Sonicare
When the media says I do cuz they trust me not them
Doesn't it mean that they trust the media more is they believe
People saying that Alex
If it distrusted the media then they would think that Alex isn't saying that he has a cure
I don't know what's going on here
Not really important
He has the Cure
As well as Heaven I think he got it from meeting with a Chinese
National
Some sort I believe is what he said
I don't care
It's all nonsense
Alex mad are just dumb people and his family members
Or imagined conversation
Yacht
Alex
Talks about his custody situation a little bit talk about that
Because
Interpersonal things are impossible to decipher from the information that we have at our disposal
The reason I'm saying this is because Alex says that there's that and then there's bigger things
We can't discuss
I would suspect
We have a pretty
Fine idea what that might be
Play pray for us because there's stuff a lot bigger than this I can't tell you about
That is your final warning
Play Bill Gates alone
Leave us alone
Do your work
It's a robe
You said you were moving yesterday
He just explained a lizard
So when he says like I've gotten my final
It's either nothing or
He knows the shoes,
Flying directly
He also made
Yet again
A classic mistake of not understanding that Defcon means
The higher the number
Safer
I've not looked into Def
Scary everybody going to die
DEFCON 5
Pretty boy
That's
Unfortunate for him but I probably would make the same mistake
Probably with the
And it's also their fault for doing it wrong
Stupid whatever the reality is or whatever is behind this there is a real sense that Alex is just like
F****** done like that there's a finality that I've got my last warning
Leave Bill Gates alone
Google doesn't care if we talk about
It just goes on throughout this episode like it's a real it's real serious
Just the way
He feels like I've come to the end
Foxhole
Overrun by a group 10 times our side
We need to conquer Mexico
I'm just let you know man
Dispatches
I want to explain something to you we're not normal. No more
Alex has always seen himself as Colonel Travis
Yeah he's always seen himself as this archetype of the guy going down in Alamo
And here he is on are saying like these are the final dispatches
Where the Alamo
Hey guess what in the Alamo those reinforcements did not come
And just like Colonel Travis Alex is a drunk and he brought this upon himself
Is more accurate about being
But he knows
Alex gets off this
Feeling lady has to talk about Shroyer had this Saturday
Over last weekend
Another one this weekend
The last one
You didn't you didn't even notice
I didn't know about this day turned out
Antifa try to agent-provocateur Owensboro
And here is what happened
12:00 noon
At the state capitol
Randy.
American flag outfits whenever they are
Top State Police
Getting arrested outside
We can
Appreciate your doing
Chaplain will protect you from me
Club stuff is going on here in America
Movies AMC
I do believe Stephanie
Because they're all
Same to
Yeah
My car
Absolutely
Yeah I know I mean it is
They're really begging the state to go Blue
There's no more of these guys
They believe in
In Christianity
They are damning themselves to Hell more than anyone ever has
It's insane
Yeah that's a state government
Add some
Problem there grey PEX collected f****** kinky I don't know why you're not running for life
Get kinky and for
There is nobody who could do a worse job than what they are doing
Yeah it's bad
So you got this protest it's coming up on Saturday and Alex's really trying
To push that you got to go or you're with
The anime
We don't need America to think of it is extraordinary
In the face of this tyranny
The only thing we have to fear
We need everyone to realize if you don't go out and demonstrate
Get over your fear
And you're dead already at your part of the enemy operation
You say no or you're with the Enemy
Owen Shroyer so great
They went out there and didn't wear masks don't they have courage
Courage is one word you could use
I suppose sure
Yeah it's it's not it's
Exagear
Mentality
Yeah yeah
You are a you are with the virus
Speaking of the anime
Dr. fauci
Anime anime
Alex has dug up some footage
Shazam
From a couple years back
And Alex has decided that this
Is proof
That he planned this whole thing
He was trying to f*** with you
Don't ever shake hands with anyone again
When did the space alien from Hell Land here that ran the Hy-Vee cover-up
Wuhan lab
Real quick
Alex
What is the HIV cover-up according to
2u urhi Vida nihilus is the HIV cover-up exactly please
Second
Whenever Alex says he is very consistently think he's up to his eyeballs
And that is a very specific turn of phrase
That Francis Boyle uses all the
He says people are up to their eyeballs in The Biohazard labs
Bioweapons lab the Nazi bioscience
Time to time I think it's great I understand that very consistently to talk about dr. fauci
Francis Boyle
It is it is
Very
Not traceable
Gates 100 million from last year
He's here saying
Don't shake hands with anyone ever again
Crisis
Very very soon.
Is that there is no question
Be
Challenge the coming Administration in the arena
Diseases both chronic
Pieces in the sense of already ongoing disease and we have three
Neolodge Bergman
Be ready for that
So Alex strategically
It did seem very abrupt
Almost Midway
He took it out of context without that hard out
But also
And why
Hotel
No Doubt
This is from a speech that Anthony fauci gave a Georgetown University Medical Center just before Trump's inauguration
It's very clear fuel this dude commented context it's Archie is discussing the very normal phenomenon of surprise outbreak
Experience a surprise outbreak is not an outlier
It's exactly the same thing the previous presidents like Obama have expiry
It's a fact of life that there will be emerging diseases there's always outbreak
The question is entirely about
What these emerging diseases are and what their response to those outbreaks will be
Clipper Alex.
Teasing that Trump unlike past president
Has a disease Outbreak on the horizon
Switch to be misrepresented misinterpreted it to him making some kind of
Its proper context its completeness characterization of patchi's words
An example of an absolute fabrication either knowing or
Someone's feeding Alex's information he doesn't vet anything that he says you just black
Text August
Then he took out of context you need to provide the full contact well and Alex saying the clip is completely opposite
If you understand that the show is lying is cool
I am taking about a coffee
That is a fair accusation
So in this next battle starts about the globalist plans right
So Trump wants to open up the economy right
He does that
Globalist are going to respond
Prophetic dream he's talking about really fun things
He's saying he wants Trump tries to reopen the economy the evil globalists are going to release more strains of the virus so let's look at the possum
Outcomes in the real world
Literally regardless of real
If Trump
Doesn't open the economy
There's no reason
And for the then part of it
That's not a problem for Alex
Situation
If Trump opens things up prematurely there's a decent chance that the infection numbers will go up
That's a natural result that you'd expect to see and it's pretty much the big argument against rushing to open things back up
You think it's a very obvious our
By pretending that the globalist or respond to transaction by releasing more dangerous strains of the virus Alex
Rewrite the increased infections as a globalist attack
Instead of what it really is
The consequences of trump Shady leadership
But what is Trump reopens
Things and there isn't a big increase in infection
It seems unlikely but it's certainly possible
That would be a problem for Alex a team since he said that the globalists are going to release more bio-weapons to punish Trump for real
It's not a problem for Alex
Because if that's
Situation comes
The past that he can say the globalist couldn't follow through with their plans because he called it out on errands there skiing absolutely
A lot of Alex's narratives work like this
He tends to populated world of things that can be spun no matter what happens in the real world because he's just making this stuff up to the
Some
That's fun
Oh God
Nobody is
Zelda
Accountable
On the right
It's simply not a thing
It's just not a thing
Like they just don't do it it's fascinating
How a large group of people
We'll just believe anything and then whenever
It's done
They just switch it and they like
Insane
So Jordan
At the beginning this episode of thanks people for some nice birthday gift indeed
But I got an amazing birthday gift in the middle of this episode
It's someone we all thought was dead
Is shown to be alive
Nah, still.
Your phone calls
Let's go ahead and talk to John and
On the air
Alex
Sheridan Wyoming
Call my house phone
Jobs for Wyoming old man how so amazing
What a tree guide
Give him a few still going after all of that he's got to have a show Alex
Give Michelle jeanfreau Wyoming old house phone
I heard that I almost freaked out
New York some nonsense about
Yes please
We need to have one of those lights website
Yeah
We need to have one of those like is Abe Vigoda website
Yes but I can confirm that as of April 21st
He is
And he's much older
Exactly he did say it on a R1 pointing at something
Is an old old man
Sounds good
Sounds great
This is where everything falls apart
On the 21st
This is profound
Like Alex is just like
F*** you man I'm f****** done
F*** this s*** I hate my own show. It's f****** stuff is stupid
Incandescent
Free things
I just want to die
Too late for you to do this
Maybe 3 years ago
After Shelley Moore I do like We Do lyrics
Easter torture now
Wow
That's pretty open-and-shut I f****** hate this show
Call Deidre
F*** this s***
By I think that's pretty comprehensive to the first time Alex and I really
We agree with except for the American
Absolute's
Must be torture to do its absolute
Think that that is a new wrinkle a little bit I'm even in the times that I've heard hit be pretty
Darken like
It's never like I hate this show
That was New Balance Direct
Yeah
Which seems
A congestion that he is not yet
So he continues on the elaborates on this need to for America and the world
The burn
That's why I feel
We need to we need to pay for what we've done actually
You do
Alive anymore
For you but
You know
On a planet of dumb
Rent a planet of slugs now
So now Alex is become
What's the world destroy everybody
Obviously in the same way
Is this Crusader against tyranny United supporting all these to Renton Boeing
I'd like of course it's so obvious
Back in the day pretending that he cares about humanity and everybody so great and the human spirit that refuses to submit it
Burnham down
Meijer
My personal Arc hasn't gone the way I wanted to so everyone must die
Great
That's an adult
Yes
So this caller he brings up
His suggestion
And that is that he thinks
What should make some specific shirts
Suggestion
Is so f****** funny
Okay so I brought up the idea and you thought I was a good idea but
Couple years ago and I said hey
Collapse
My job
I want to buy no one cares
Darkness
Now this is what I've been looking for from Alex's colors
This is Bill Cooper this is where I'm at with this
Well excuse not
Because
Listcawler
Giving
Productive
Feedback product of the coming economic
Collapse
Then you can use it when the market does go down in allocating with a good faith
Within the world
Pretty good suggestion
Where is like the times I'm sure Bill Cooper
The times that we've heard him responding
It's mostly because I bring up stupid ideas
Somebody's still different
Alex's Alison
In the real world
Infowars it's a good idea
Always about me struggling with you
Analysis responses like
F*** you
The f****** tantrum
Eddie's
Spirals to the point where he seems to be almost celebrating the idea that Civilization is going to end
We are cowards we are trash
They're going to have everything they're going to starve to death
It's a blessing
Why's that
Call a blessing
Fake stuff
Stupid
All the conspiracy theory internet program
I don't know if he's going to collapse entirely but it's Netflix
Don't have a f****** account
It won't affect you at all
Alex is real
Real f******
In that second
That was bad sex
Pretty bad
A little apocalyptic apocalyptic
I want to make t-shirts no one cares
So Alex Goes To Break outro music
And of course
Bob
People don't want it
And so we deserve it
Tell you we're not going to know I'm on the world will burn
That wasn't very apologetic
Well I mean it was kind of like I'm getting a little bit dark here
Wilshire
It's me
You know
It's the introduction to like that last segment was pretty f***** up
Someone gave me a taco
I need to take a few days off
When we get to the actual sort of about
Should have taken some of this back
Academy the things I said
That is great he's the childish like
I want everybody to die f*** everybody I'm sick of this s***
Hey listen I'm really sorry
I really apologize that my my dad came in and told me that no one's going to give you money if you can
He's right so I'm sorry
To me or I should say that there is a counterargument
But Alex is going to deliver this next cliff
Which is that he's not doing
I don't shut up here and do this show so
Running this place
Puron arrowleaf
Enough money
Continue on with the level rat
Think about the fact
People really realize how serious is one
They would do their job I know a lot of You Are
The gas can
Shows
Real
Desperation here lays gentleman
Rages me
We are a nation and a world of Watchers
Not abjures
Watching
Conquering us
Tronix Psychic Spiritual
An overriding of the planet
Systematically
Mark of the Beast the whole nine yards so yes I will
Already need
Through here
I want to take Stephen Santa position
The criminal nature of the system that if you haven't flooded us wouldn't support
We wouldn't be here
Longer on Capitol
The more they just want to kill me or put me in prison which is fine
Because
God's plan
You want to do it to the fullest extent
Acupuncture around everybody else to take this damn serious because
Damn.
They running
People have lower IQs
. gov
Because they don't have enough iodine
I mean like this whole thing about like I don't want his want to stay in the fight
Prison
Sanitation
Healthy and talk about this 100 times like the iodine deficiency
MC numbers that he's talked about her developing
Countries
And they're being fought
By people like the UN
The people who ordered the globalist that Alexei so trying
To solve the problem
He's pretending
Exists
Largely in America
Just eat some salt
Eat applesauce
I have an iodine deficiency
So Alex I mean it's just
That it's almost like an entire segment of
The show just like this
I don't want any I'm not doing this for money but you got to flood us with money
I understand how this argument work
Like yes
That's obviously Alex
Is presenting it in a way that's like
I don't want the money I want the money to be able to continue
But it seems like the only function of the show is to spread b*******
And make money
So continuing
It's just a continued to make money later money so I can continue to make money
With the presentation of her actually doing
Yeah
Not
So Alex is his whole thing
Big narratives that goes throughout the show is about
Some numbers
About starvation around the world
I am sorry about this this next clip
The care about the
This is what we like we like to be hugs let me tell it in the hose
Thanks to this right now
Die
Trendy
I'm so bored
So disappointed Alex kept hitting on this episode
20 times that are to bring it up
Realized
Here Alex is trying to pretend that he has literally
Any concern for the well-being people in
Developing countries
That's a topic that we can discuss and I will get into it here in a minute
Has absolutely no rights
Pretend to care here at all.
Supporting Trump Alex staked his claim very aggressively and supporting Ron Paul the only honest politician
It is 2018 2012 runs for the present
One of the big things that Ron Paul believed in was the elimination of all US foreign aid
The number of deaths that would result from that kind of a move is
Incalculable and it's not even taking into account the hits the developing countries and take
In terms of their educational capacity or general sanitation programs
The Staggering level of Cruelty that you have to accept to endorse a candidate who wants to get rid of all US foreign aid
Precludes you from ever being able to credibly pretend you give a s***
Let anybody in the developing world
Can f*** himself
You bet
The number that Alex is citing about 30 million people being on the brink of starvation
That's not a number that they don't have any people are predicted to starve if we don't reopen our economy
Our economy has nothing to do with that figure really at all at least on a one-to-one level
This is something that was put out by the UN
World food program
It has the potential to leave Millions at risk
If we don't do something
This was something at their executive director David Beasley was warning about even before the coronavirus situation was here
Tissues that there's a whole lot of issues
What's happening right now
ABC News article about Beasley's comments quote
Because of wars in Syria Yemen and elsewhere Locust swarms in Africa disasters and economic
The Crazies
Including
Lebanon Congo Sudan
Eddie top
Reason album
Another country
Economies as much as if we
Can't afford
Provide for an eighth
The countries are facing famine condition
And there will end up being severe humanitarian crisis
He's in a lot of people could die
This is a very serious issue that deserves
Attention but make no mistake about
Alex doesn't want our economy to be open
So we can send money in foreign aid
Repeated by the UN
Alex is using the abstract idea of the deaths of people in developing countries as a prop for his narrative
Legitimately disgusting
This has nothing to do with whether or not Trump tells people to go to Jim's or not
This has to do with whether or not weedy prioritize people in developing countries
When things get tough at home
That's the central question as it relates to the matter of people going hungry around the world
And again
Alex's hero rampal would happily let them all die
So I guess if Alex actually cares about this at all he'll call on Chopped
Provide Inc
Increased funding
To the UN world food programme
I challenge him to do that
But I suspect you won't
Because this is a game to him
Yeah the idea of 30 billion dead people in foreign countries in the developing world
Is just a prop that you can use to argue
In order for the economy to reopen
So these, these companies
These large companies that he pretends to be opposed to can make a profit
If a millionaire pretends to give a s***
About
Anybody and it develop
They should
Have their money take
Play from mnb tarred and feathered
I think that would be the way to solve most problems
But yes this is a real thing and you know what
Un world food
Actually on the ground
Working
Humanitarian crisis
Not people like Alex blowing hard on the radio
But how he doesn't like his show you what's up
The f****** quit and run away to a redoubt but no I'm going to stay here forever
Nonsense
What am I
So as this episode ends
Alex Addison's into bit of a situation where he's
These narratives
About how doctors are just
Grant Hospital
Doctors address
Drinking and talking
The hospitals are empty
I know they're nurses doctors are having sex and watching p******
They're drinking
Text same time
Sure
Which record
Pills
What
Rockin everywhere rockin everywhere
Players Club
Truly going on is
They're at the Players Club
Propelled
Party party party party party everyday
Everyday
100 on my Highway
That's what's going down baby
You say it is a
Giant orgy
Again this is just based on things that is dumb friends are saying
I also really true
I suspect this is mostly about like Tik Tok video of nurses dancing
Filled in the blanks and try to apply like
I think I think one way to reduce his
Outside
Aggression
Towards
Hospitals
Neuter am I think neutering is a way to solve a lot of his
I'm covid-19 coming for your balls I really think that's a good way to go
Envy episode here kind of excited that these nurses that are all just f****** taking pills
Stop
Future
And then he admits that he hasn't really done his job at all because he freaked out and got really mad
There's nothing
They'll be crying for mommy they were Venezuela can we will be don't
To look at these people
To Craig and EJ
I love you to death I didn't do it I'm a bad person
But I guess I should call or two in here
Jeff Zuckerberg
Again Jessica
You dirty filthy
Go outside
Yeah that is weird you maybe it's do not make that mistake yet irregularly
I'm still
I'm still of the mind that it's
Miss speaking it doesn't mean anything's play it is weird
It's more consistent than originally
Medical professionals
Dying begging for mommy is gross
More importantly to me I think is this admission at the entier
Didn't take all the calls that I said I was going to take didn't get to these stories that I was going to cover
I had to be really defensive about just money and also I hate my show
And the world deserves to burn then I got to talk
Dunescape back on outside
Hey sorry about that little babies all I heard
We should change it
To First
Do no harm to anyone but Alex Jones
I don't think he deserves medical care if you are saying that nurses are making
Fake videos
I feel like I could videos after 16 hour shifts
I feel like it's okay
I feel like it's okay for you to say that but if I heard a doctor say that I would be offended
Because I think the doctors
And medical professionals
This is true from number that I've spoken to in some friends that I have who were in the field
There's a hot there's a colon
To being interested
Take away your ego or whatever feelings you have about like
This is a bad person
You know you be denying care to people on all sorts of arbitrary
Denies
Who lives or dies for YouTube
You're not a doctor
No
I will give him Medical Care
Attends the 21st 22nd Wednesday's show
And he opens up
Real real high
So insanely important
Doing Pediatrics
I don't know what the big news is
It's confirmed
I listen to this episode and I think I have maybe two possibilities
For what the big news
But here's what he says immediately after which would lead you to suspect
This is what the big news is it's causing Alex to choke on the 22nd
Saying from numbers I saw 3 weeks ago that.
Right now
Next month
Show me the numbers I saw
Play Timbaland the numbers are now in from the UN themselves
Do you hate
CorePower
Million
Are starving to death
Globe and Mail
Canadian pipe
Possible that's Alex's big news
Is the story
Not being dramatic for
For sure
The story that covered the day before
30 million people dying in developing countries
That doesn't make sense.
What does make sense in Infowars World it doesn't make sense from a perspective is like actually taking this
Sincere actor the news that you reported yesterday is somehow
Today
I don't know
Global Mail article that Alex is talking about when he's here on air
The same issues we talked about earlier
Also if Alex's argument is that the globalist want to shut the economy down order to kill off all these people seems to be what he's getting
You can have to contend with this quote
From the UN world food programme executive director David Beasley from that's very Globe and Mail article
But deciding as a source
If we lost our funding a minimum of thirty million would die
Over a three-month period that would be 300,000 people dying per day
That's why leaders have got to balance out the covid response with keeping the economy going because otherwise
A lot more people will die from starvation and economic
Deterioration
Then from covid itself
So the UN simultaneously wants to crash the economy to punish Trump balance keeping some of the economy
Provide Aid to the developing world
Seems like maybe the first one is just Alex's paranoid imagination
What you got to understand
Is it about what they're not
The Jazz exactly
Whatever notes you can't hear that makes the notes
You can hear
Paranoid
One possibility is the big news but it doesn't make sense
It doesn't make sense since he's already reported this
I don't know that's one possibility is
Not a possibility
Old man house phone
Grand Prix
Alex tells a story about getting in another fight with somebody about masks
What a child
He apparently was driving around he saw his son driving around
Into a liquor store parking lot
And that is the Cai the setting
Historic
Pulling in
Front row
30 ft
Liquor store
Place
And from an AT&T store
Boxes out front of it
And one of them looks at me
Put your mask on
I talked to my son he walked over with me
My phone
Shocking
Yeah
Roberts today
0.1%.
Showing
At the moment
Blonde bombshell
Liquor store
Coming out when I'm arguing with a guy
Telling me
Show the video
Yeah no s***
Howard Triplett
You're being dog trained
And all this 6-foot separation
Chelation
Set up for medical tyranny
The guy was laughing at me
Yeah no s***
Liquor store
What
You are a willful
Moron
About a couple of security guards came up and
What a dick
That's why I'm successful and you're not I know how to lie to people and I never learned how to read
Another one
It really is just the delete in
I'm so much
Gas station
That's the reality of where we are
Bunch of massive coming in next week
Infowars.com
Its submission
Airplane and got to go in the grocery store
Comfortable
Plasma
While you're at it and shoot your mouth off
The whole time
Limited edition covid-19
Hulk smash.
Jokes on the page they didn't solicitor like
Yeah why why is that probably some sort of law
Question of like you saying it's a hoax but you're selling Basques people should ask themselves why
You think
No it is almost
Like you know like let's say
There's like
Lakeforest work the comment
Yeah we're selling a transportation to the
Dude
You got to do do the Semitic thing with the two
As that's not that's not what the Patriots would do that is not what a heroic
Dissident
Incident like Alex should be saying
Fuckmaster
.
If you wear when you're a warrior or something
That's the line he needs to take not like
Hey will make a brand out of this
It will come up
The folks will find a way to profit off Spears
Talk about fighting guy yelling at a guy in a liquor store parking lot Alex mentioned
Video of John Roberts of Fox News
Talking about the the coronavirus death rate
Hey Auntie it's to do with
Study
SC
This is the other candidate for the big news of making Alex choke
Plus thousand people in LA County Health Department reporting
Something dead
Today
A of died from Coronavirus
Add
Boxing test
Bara so they may have died from
Free People
Estimate from what they've been testing now
No more
So close
Calculator.net
Can you put 66
And add three to it
663 divided 400000 equals
The number right there
0.001 657
5 equals
0 point
There's a final number
0.1
If you flip it upside down it says boobs
Brutal
That is
Even close to 1%
So I think this might be the big news it's a story that he's covering a lot of
This episode
What is bulshit in the others
Presentation
Bulshit part is it all boils down to
Photographer Doug Mills
Before one of these White House Press briefing
The video has been used to prevent the idea that the virus and the response to it is a hoax
Even though if you watch the video Mills says quote so it's a hoax
George Roberts replies quote
No I don't think it's a hoax
This videos when used by all manner of conspiracy theorist
The big narrative has been that bills accidentally slipped up and admitted that there is a secret vaccine
Robert says that Mills doesn't need to wear his mask because the fatality rate is lower than we thought to it smells replies quote
Oh yeah we've all been vaccinated
It's clear that their friends f****** around the comment Roberts even said
It does just Gallows humor
Don't discredit he's not selling the vaccine portion
This video
He's interested only in the lower fatality rate part of it which is was John Roberts
Discussing be misrepresented
Alex is narrative
Roberts was bringing up a study conducted by USC that reached the conclusion that there may be as many as 400,000 people
LA County who has had Coronavirus
This study has yet to be pure review. But if it stands to scrutiny all it really shows is that there may be a much lower face
LA County
Then we currently new to be the case
Most people had assumed the numbers we had worked fully accurate for California because relative to other states
They've had other states that have had high numbers of cases
There hasn't been as much widespread testing in the state
I could well be that the number of people who had the virus in the state is higher than the confirm number
But I don't really see how that makes me outbreak any less serious
He possibly puts California's fatality rate into a lower range but that's about it
Also given a lower proportion of test administered in California it's also possible that the definite Brazil we have for the state
Inaccurate
It's unclear there's a lot of assessment study that needs to be done here to get a complete
Really clear picture of w w and this study is interesting
But we need to see what
With it moving forward
Once that happens all the sex things once they're more concrete because unlike Alex
I don't base my beliefs on preliminary studies
There very well may end up being a well-done study
But there's plenty of examples in the past where it's
Things appeared to be
Some
It is
Because I am
Technically one of their peers if we can serve on a jury together
That means I'm up here and I give it
Start.
Whatever
Alex has some complaints he wants to make
About
This is their globalist Revolution to cut
Industrial state
We are done because we're evil
Doing this
You're hearing the whole un Gaia
World Government speech
We deserved it from Hollywood
Everybody else
Shut everything down to say wives
So the pope and the globalist and the Hollywood trash that we deserve
24-hours let's
The planet on
That's why I feel
We need to we need to pay for what we've done actually
We are cowards we are trash
They're going to have everything they're going to starve to death
Got it means I said last check
All right I can't believe that the Pope
Open the government and Hollywood squid say that we deserve it
How dare they
I said it or maybe Alex is part of the globalist plan or whatever
Did not expect to be a secret pagan
Why not
So the last scoundrel scoundrel
According to Thomas Jefferson
Quotes
But it turns out that the last Refuge of the Patriots scoundrel is
Business better than Hillary
You imagine
Glenwood present today they would be carrying out
This exact same plan except
Give me 10 times worse because you wouldn't have Trump in there trying to block it
Find America
Ride the wave or you would have been destroyed
Economy which they basically already done
Has never been at zero
Process crew is on his way down to zero
Cold cardiac
Yeah I love sweet crude
So the negative oil prices were specifically that Futures contracts for May for West Texas intermediate
It's crude oil
The reason was because it was a day before those contracts work
Be closed and if you held those contract when they close
You are obligated to accept delivery of the oil
Because a lot of people who held those contracts could not stop unless they were desperate to sell off the contract
Price for West Texas intermediate June 2014 dollars a barrel
When I Was preparing this episode
Infernus however if things don't change
It could very well hit negative rates as we come up on the closing date of those contracts
It's possible but for now it's not the
What is presenter
There a lot of issues with the situation
And some of them could combined spell trouble in the future
This particular incident with the negative prices
That shouldn't be the main thing that people are Focus
Sing on
During the coronavirus. There's obviously a decreased
Royal
In response
Decrease demand
It was requested that OPEC countries cut back production
But this has not happened to the extent that would be needed in order to balance out the supply and demand
That sucks there's an excess of oil being created with people having a difficult time
Well I should say there are
Difficult I'm storing it on land
World economic forum
Bring your excess oil at sea
Recent anchors at high cost
Summer believed to be paying an excessive $100,000 per day for each
Tanqr
I'm no expert but I feel like massive stewardship soil Odyssey is a recipe for trouble
What when is that ever been an issue damn thing I can think of any civilization ever never know
Great let's put it another compounding factor is that Alberta
Which is produced from oil sands
Is no longer profitable
Produce
It cost more to extract to transport it then it would sell for which is cause people to flee from it as a commodity
Financial times this week not on its own cause significant damage to the US Energy sector
However they know that it could hurt the perception that oil is a safe investment
Based on their assessment the solution is fairly simple
We need to either slow production of oil
Start using a ton more of it or find places to store the oil work
Currently producing
Unless we do one of those things the supply and demand will be out of balance
And we'll just keep seeing volatile pricing
It's a bad situation and what could cause some potentially troubling
We could also provide the political will
To finally do something about the deep-seated problems in the US Energy Market
It seems like there could barely be a better time to start making moves towards Alternative Energy models
Scented incident like this demonstrates the benefits are not being so concerned with a single commodity that can blow up overnight
Seems like you're it seems almost like
There is a silver lining right like right
Counterpoint
What If instead
Trump just
Gets his many of his
Followers killed as possible in bales
Why not both have you considered that
This could be a situation where I really take it on the chin
I would very much like to give him one of the two
So Alex talks about Ike how he knows that globalists there eugenics
That's for really long time because back in the 60s
They were trying to get all the lake smart kid
Places like University of Texas
The top students in the country
Teaching them
Where they breathe
This is this is a really important stuff is Dad is the smartest boy in Texas and
Globalist
Lower that is absolutely
Do you have to really recognize how much stuff
Alex believes
And repeats
Pretending to come from authoritative sources and things that are proven
Are just bullshitted his dad probably
You can always trust
The CIA dentist
So damn sure
Look for backup for all this stuff
You know Alex has his is standard examples of what are all the time
Is Bill Joyce article and Wired Magazine why the future doesn't need us I really don't want to talk about that article
No because it's very obvious if you actually go read the article doesn't say what Alex says
Really similar to excerpt
From the Unabomber
They Bill Joy includes
In the Arctic
That I know this
And if Alex had read it
He would know it
Text clip when Alex brings up Bill Joyce article
I get a little sense
Did Alex is keenly aware that he's actually just talk
About the Unabomber
I think you were useful l
Call Joy Road about in 1999 and why the future doesn't need us Wired Magazine
Decision
I think it was a dead giveaway I think he understands that he's just talking about the Unabomber
Alexa connect those dots
It's a sad attempt to justify using Bill Joyce article dishonestly
Also Ted Kaczynski was not a
In the CIA
The psychological experiments that he was
Which would later become the CIA during World War II was involved the OSS during WWII
Pretty clear that he did was good
According to Alex Ted Kaczynski the evil globalist plan was sending
Except that's complete bulshit
It's just a fantasy that Alex is making up
There's a lot you can go learn about the Unabomber if you want and this is not
Accurate you got a you got to find some way to really love the guy
Scent bomb
Two places
And blew them
Alex's likes white terrorist yes he does
Hey you know what that's similar to
Something Joy Behar said about him
In the next clip Alex talks about the big
Playing with this like crashing oil and crashing economy of course
The the way that the Rothschild
I did his economy at all up short that again
Salix tell the story again this story is not
True but listen to how passion
That lady tells the story
Walking people I've been with
Scooby-Doo
Just like Scooby-Doo
Was the Battle of Waterloo
Thanks
Corvette
Call Ash cross the channel
Is the stock market open
Wellington annihilated
Went to 1% or Rothschild bought them all and became
A ruler
Nope
I do remember that
Down to nothing all the oil down to nothing that story is not true that's just a standard feature of anti-Semitic
Propaganda over history
So you believe this
Came the Supreme
Like this is
Just believe things that aren't true
He passes off his knowledge of this Bill Joy article really been noses
Yeah this whole narrative about it
Yep what he knows is this anti-semitic propaganda surrounding Rothschild family
The Battle of Waterloo
They put out during WWII
Like he believes that he presented his real he doesn't know s*** it's almost like he believed
Nazis more than
Not not
It's it's almost like
He will believe whatever a Nazi
He says in order to take
Advantage of it
And I
He's a Nazi
Yeah
So it is next to Fox News
Angle and it's to do with the
The idea that what happened there was the reveal
Did the media knows that this is a hoax
But nobody
Behind the scenes
Because that is so massive
The cliff
When you go in the store and
You're an idiot
What do you want to show them the part of the clip where the guy says so it's a hoax
Jean-robert says no I don't think it's because you're saying
Probably
People saying. It's not a hoax
I don't know what kind of ruins thing you to show me a music video of my favorite
Banded the store
Noel
Come up to me and say watch this video
Especially if you're Alex
And if you're not wearing a mask
So Alex
People are not getting
Recessed
Acetate at hospital
Like if you go to hospital now
Too busy f******
Right
This leads into some pretty weird
Conspiracy theories about
Financial motivations
The hospitals have
Playing along with this
Hoax or whatever
In the last few months when it gets bad
People that have heart attacks
50 years old or 8 years old
We need the hospital space
The hospital
But now when you have a heart attack
Venezuela resuscitate you because that's
Non-essential
Give
Ammonia
Thousand dollars for covid-19
There's two pieces nightclub that are complete
The first is that when Alex heard people talking about doctors not being able to help every patient and having
To decide who gets
Care and who doesn't
She seems to be making a joke out
It wasn't a discussion about how things are happening
Now in the United States
It was a horrifying Glimpse or what could happen if my medical system was overwhelmed by the number of coronavirus patients they were coming
To the hospital
It's a pretty simple Dynamic to understand
Is the number of people requiring Immediate Care is greater than the number of people who can
Provide to help
In that situation you enter a nightmare where you have to write off people or probably going to die because you can't save everyone
This conversation wasn't happy
Shooting for no reason
Is because back in March that's exactly the situation doctors in Italy were in
Open article in Politico
In an interview that went viral after it was published in the Italian daily corriere Della Sera
Monday
Christian salerosa
Anesthesiologist from hospital in Bergamo
Recounted scenes of wartime triage
Have to be left by the wayside
Call the choices made inside of an emergency room used for mass events
If a person is between 80 and 95 and a Severe respiratory failure he probably won't make it
Also from the article
For now the marching orders are save scarce resources for the patient
Who are the greatest chance of survival
That means prioritizing younger otherwise healthy patients over older patient
Or those with pre-existing
Open conditions
The AP discusses what that look like in real life
And quotes Marco Resto
The deputy chief of Pollock
Lamico Donatos in intensive care unit
Discussing how doctors have to decide who will get access to newly-opened intensive care beds
Even if there is no chance he says
You have to look at
Patient in the face and say all is well
And this lie destroys you
It's horrifying to consider in a few weeks later
Doctors in Spain or dealing with the exact same Horrors
March 25th article in Bloomberg discusses a Madrid emergent
Empty room
People are dying in Waiting rooms before they can be admitted as a coronavirus pandemic overpowers medical staff
With some Funeral Service halted in the Spanish capital and no space left in the morgue
Corpses are being stored in the main ice
The conversation was not happening because this was something that was happening in the United States but because it was a horror that are can another country
We're living through
We could easily be our reality too if we made the wrong decision
The entire point of the distancing and masks
Carefulness measures is for everyone of us to do whatever we can to make sure we don't end up in that situation
Because once we're there
Cannot help you if you have a heart of
This is one of our medical system has all its resources completely depleted by one person
Is automatically a lower priority
If we do these things
We helped make sure that situation is one we never have to live
If you have a heart attack now or hospitals will be able to help you
Largely because of people doing the
Things Alex is actively protesting
Against
If he gets his way with his job rallies against disc
Something measures and all that s***
There's a chance we will end up in the nightmare scenario
Against
As for the payments thing that's just something the David Icke told Alex
But David I could just repeating both Shady heard on Fox News
Minnesota State senator Scott Jensen was on the Laura Ingraham show inside
Anytime Healthcare intersects with dollars it gets awkward
Right now Medicare is the term that you have covid-19 admission to hospital you get paid $13,000
If that covid-19 patient goes on a ventilator you get $39,000 three times as much
Conspiracy world started revving their engines hospitals had a financial incentive
Calling everything covid-19
We should remove the financial incentive from our Healthcare System that's what they're saying right there very angry about there being
Financial incentive in The Help
Medicare for all right
Maybe
Factcheck.org
He did not think that hospitals were intentionally misclassifying cases for financial reasons
Hardly matters
The Cradle of the IDI been presented
And once that happens
I didn't mean it like that
Turner is alive
Fact check
Reached out to some doctors to get a sense of what this is all about and as it turns out it's b*******
This is just the amount that Medicare pays for treatment of
Covid-19
Not diagnosed
But
Kaiser Family Foundation these numbers are very much in line with its from Medicare
With respiratory infections averaging about $13,000
Any cases of escalate to the need for ventilators
Comes in around $40,000
The coronavirus Aid relief and Economic Security Act
Trump signed into law
Did give you 20% uptick in funds for Medicare patients treated for covid-19
You think that hospitals are just going to be
Italy diagnosing people
A small bump in Medicare funds
If they're caught doing that
They run the risk of being removed from the Medicare program entirely
Leaving aside how they could be sued or charged
Criminal malpractice
Yep
Alex is accusing these doctors at these hospitals of a crime
It's a pretty serious allegation
So this kind of situation is one where he's going to need to prove his case or shut the fuk up
You can't just say numbers about Medicare payments and they say Case Closed like improving some
This is a disgrace
Nonce
It is never
Too often
To say how high the f******
Mistakes are
And how dangerous he
This is
Terrifyingly Dane
This is a this guy is
And somehow he's technically not committing a crime
He is helping
He's getting people killed
Fox News is getting people killed President is getting people killed and somehow that's
Fine
Somehow our legal system has no
No problem
And neither do we
Apparently word intersect with
Foundational
Freedoms that we have not considered the limits of
For a very long time
Really had that conversation where is
Other countries in Europe
For instance have
Are these fees real stations like a holocaust denial being illegal
Where you recognize that your free speech rights are not absolute when there are real
Text solid consequences
Did that you know we understand that in terms of like you can punch
The air
Jeffrey way
Consequence consequences do matter in terms of the action
And I don't know I'm not sitting here saying that I support
Like
Understanding of free speech
I don't think that the conversation is necessarily on Warren
Doing now
Is not as good as
As other stuff that we
We could be doing
Edward not even talking about doing anything else
It's possible that the perspective you're bringing is a key
That being said
It takes into account the side
Unintended consequences of your
Because it's very possible that you pulled
Fred a little bit you start to realize
There might be more severe consequences
Promise that you'll realize
I'm not saying that I have a problem it's another possible
I'm not saying that I have.
Plan to solve it right there is no way that we can look at what's going on right now and say we've done the best
It doesn't feel like it
It's not possible
So Alex is talked about this
Do you have a heart attack now they're not going to resuscitate you in that last clip
That this has to do with the story that he read in New York
Coronavirus
So there you go
So this is a great example of why I really just don't care for Alex
Much
New York Post article with the headline New York issues do-not-resuscitate guidelines for cardiac patients
Coronavirus
Iris
This is about an order that was floated that emergency workers to not bother Reviving someone
That person doesn't have a pulse
Previously the sander was to try for 20 minutes
To revive people
This article cites in approximately three to four percent success rate in resuscitate
EMT
Which is a small number but definitely not an insignificant one
This headline news article from April 21st
By the time on April 22nd
New York Post
The headline quotes
New York scraps do-not-resuscitate order during Coronavirus
I know this article came out before alex.ani
And if you covering the story he has every reason to be where this up to
Paramedics unions were not happy with this guidance and they pushed back in the order was reversed
The conversation about whether or not it's necessary for New York EMTs to conserve their resources to be extensive. Spend
20 minutes trying to resuscitate patient
Define without a pulse
That's decidedly above my paygrade and I don't know
Here's the situation
From where I'm sitting
How to complain about a problem that is already been solved by the time he's discussing
He's misrepresenting and already solved the problem
This is a perfect encapsulation
Much of his career
Yep
You nailed it
Danza
Only three people voted
Reserved
We get here on the 22nd
Episode
Is Alex really
Really keeping on swinging
About how doctors are just
Nurses doctors
People
Well what do you think the nurses the doctors are having a good time what are you doing what do you think we're doing
Nobody here
Nobody in the desert family
They're in there having orgies ladies and gentlemen
Call f******
Is Family Show
If this conversation happen
And which I don't know if it's
Here's how that conversation
What are you guys doing
F****** Alex what do you think we're doing
Maybe
The real thing is like
SquarePants becomes clear
The only thing you taking this from is
His family members telling him that switch I do
Don't trust
I talked to some family that works at the biggest VA Hospital one of the biggest country Outlets
We had one
Guy that had a he's fine they walked everything down
But overall feel victims
Text messages
Hospital
He's a doctor he was just like no it's a
Animal House
What are the most
Doctors and nurses it's like a
What about
Party time
Open hospitals are doing elective surgeries
Are all happy cuz there's nobody in there
Is ridiculous
Contiguous
Wow the function of this
Rubius places
Disinformation
The function of it
That
These medical work
Like the ones you saw standing in the crosswalk
Opposing these protesters
That they
Are fighting back
Against the open the country back up folks
Is because they're having too much fun f****** not kidding that's Alex's near
The house is a Rockin don't come a-knockin come on in
I appreciate your call Kenny
You stupid f****** a******
That is that's the level of thinking that he's bringing to this
These doctors
Love f****** and taking pills
They're having a great time and say these they're secretly Evan orgies in these hospitals and that's why they want the economy to
They can f*** when they're off time
I just can't like
I don't think Alex actually believes
No absolutely not a chance
Who are saying to themselves
Sounds true
Which means they think
The entire medical profession
Is willing to
Do a sacrifice everybody's f****** life so they can
F*****'-a Hospital
That's it
Think about how f***
What is so awful
Very stupid
That's just awful
Silex complains about vaccines
Of course they're going to be a nightmare there already
Exactly where you'd expect it to
Scenario from hell
Hey
The New World Order is out in the open
Pedophiles convicted your school to mount your kids underneath
Obsolete
Thomas Jefferson was asked once in a letter v
Virginia
Legislature they ever f****** a hospital
What is the limit of tyranny
Always
Fresno
Limit
The black hole
Thomas Jefferson quote I was actually a Frederick Douglass
Repurposing
Yep we have one last episode I don't believe that the 22nd is nearly as
Has the 21st
There is there's a little bit of stuff in it
And I might not have
Really
Ben is interested in covering at
Because of the psychodrama
Far more interesting
Alex's just like
He also
What are the reasons I decided to
Include both of these episodes is because
Concede
How different is mood is from day-to-day
F*** this I hate this show this is stupid we all deserve to burn on the first day
How the next day July Infowars as usual
Clock
The choosing doctors of having this
Spirit see where they just want to f***
Enter scamming Medicare Bonnie
Goddamnit right
And then the second reason that I decided to cover this episode is
Because
Something that Alex says at the end
And is very important
The Attorney General
That would take hours to go into 18
Doing the right thing
Mark all stay-at-home orders
House arrest
So now Bill Barr has said something that Alex likes
So looks like he's a good guy
Whose phone is this game
Who can forget Alex's Show from
And Steve
Bacon
Trump to fire William Barr
Because Bari come out say the Trump tweeting about the doj recommendation for Rodger Stones trial
And sentencing was not
Cool
They were on the warpath
Alex even went so far as to bring up the fact that there is a Jeffrey Epstein connection with William Barr
We know that attorney general Barr has really come out against the
Some people are saying that it's a lie
Kabuki
To get Democrat
Attorney General
I don't send that stone to an exorbitant amount
Yeah no s***
Is a smart guy
Not the lawyer bureaucracy but beautiful
Military
Those areas
Call the lieutenant colonel
Bar
Michelle today
Because of the pedigree of
You know bar
Is up to his eyeballs
The list of reasons why Alex should super f****** hate William Barr is a very long one
Republican report on April 15th specifically victims families from access to
The FBI Files the promise to open
Sing the even discussing why he can't release these files would be a threat to National Security
For someone like Alex who made his career on 9-11 conspiracy theories this should sound a lot like someone
Aging in a cover-up
Don't even bring the story up
It's looking like he's real
Plenty of examples about this why I should hate it but this one's particularly funny for me
Alex's primary identity in his early career was a 9-11 truther
That's being completely subjugated to his need to be a blind Trump follower
It's really sad to see where this at this road he's on his leg
It's led to repudiation and rejection of self
Oh also
William Barr was the Attorney General under George
H.w. Bush during the Ruby Ridge standoff
Movement in the 90s
And he's questionnaire that he had to answer for his Trump confirmation
Barr says quote
I spent approximately 80 hours
Is organizing a toy
Attorneys General
To support an FBI sniper in Defender
Gets criminal charges in connection with the Ruby Ridge incident in Idaho
I am listed a law firm to work pro bono on the case and assisted in framing legal arguments advanced in the amakai
In the district
And the subsequent appeal in the night circus
That's nice
Defend was the person who shot Randy Weaver's wife
While she was holding her infant child
William Barr should be a villain.
The highest order
Alex
She looks like he's real after all this principal list
Tyler Shipp
And for all the reasons that he needs to be off air for like for his own effect that he has on the public at
The danger to people
He also needs to be off air
For his own
Good
He is he is
Exactly
The opposite of what he pretends to be
1/10
Care about all these
Did this Patriot right wing world
Even
According to that he's a f****** sellout piece of s***
So go f*** yourself Alex you should be telling yourself
You're a pile of s***
You should be looking
Dick in the mirror
And really wrestling with the fact
Happy you're defending William Barr
Go fuc
Yourself you'll pretending to have any connection to that militia world
If you if you had even a
Colonel
You never be able to the entire time but there's been this will-they-won't-they with William Barr he should have all
It'll always be
That should have been disqualified the second
F****** Trump
Attorney General
I know this guy
I know this guy because you know what the FBI or the villains of Ruby Ridge
And you know who the FBI reports to
Attorney general who runs the Department of Justice
William f****** bar
I'm sorry I'm getting
Do your nails look like
Look at his entire existence is
Such a
Rejection
That was cheap
Pretends to be
And
And it's just
You're done you're done
You've done your
You've done your work
What you thought you were doing Alex
And now
You have disgraced yourself who who who
You've become the villain
Even to your own feeling this world
It's almost
Looks like
Terrible and every moment
Is torture
Hate to quote Thomas Jefferson
This actually ends with Alex has an interview with a
Torba from Gab
It's really funny because Alex has he has a massive huge announcement
His massive announcement is the he hates them
And the Gap is coming out with their own version of zoo
Is it called
It's about something that doesn't exist
Alex's the David
Like click
Stop
God know I don't know I don't know what's going to happen
Been in the immediate future
Surprised to see Alex take the rest of this week off
You know take Friday probably Sunday off
I don't know we'll see what happens but I am
I'll be keeping an eye on it
Lookout because
You know what
So we'll be back at the Seltzer marches forward
The court has promised
The beginning of the show I have a rating for the 11 cello what's that
80 Audobon
80 out of 100 continues to be good as far as you drink
All right till lower than the
Coffee but extinct
Mostly the surprise I think of it
Excited
It wasn't a one-off
We'll be back with more seltzer
Website
I think that's a no
Twitter
Yes it is at knowledge underscore Seltzer and sandals
Also on face office
Download the show please go to ice seltzer
Leave a review go to a shelter page
If you want donate to to a local charity of your choice
Until then I'm Neo on house phone
Alex
Color