Nola.com
I have great respect for knowledge but now it's like I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
MoneyGram
Dot-com
Everybody likes it around Alex
Jordan Jordan
Quick question
Whatsyourprice
I got two little ones
After our last episode
One is a thank-you to Anna
Out there since some masks
Some homemade masks wander around the streets
And actually a couple of those are for you and tell your lady friend so please
Do you like bigger that you have to take the one that's avocados
I'm allergic to
Allergic to avocados
I cannot be seen walking around town with such a millennial bathing mask
You're allergic to doesn't mean you can't wear it proudly confident
Cocky in a nice cool math
Definitely not Health Ranger John as a as a present
Sent over
A selection of some of his favorite hot sauces
From a company called matouk's alright that's not one of them
No sausages
Offensively salty
Chance to try out these sauces yet they just arrived
And so I will I'll let that
Folks know when I have a sensitive butt
They look really exciting one of them is a Trinidad scorpion sauce
One of my favorite of the peppers
I'm not allowed to eat
Nobody else has it been nice fruitiness to
John said his favorite was the
Calypso sauce
Switch shot worries mate
But I'm excited I'm really missing some like real good hot sauces right now
And so I haven't some of this
To supplement to meals
I said it's great that sounds awesome
Dan is a very simple
I was last time you had brisket
Cuz I'll tell you right now it's
Love Ricky
Right we had a freak out my partner and I
Like I already so so frustrated and then we decided to order a s*** ton of brisk
I'm just went into a meat, and
It is been
A good cup
Couple days off that beat
That's great
Good for the two of you I'm happy for your rediscovery of the love of brisket
Hey hell yeah
Talking about April 23rd and 24th 2020
Dammit Thursday and Friday of last week but before we get down to business on that thank you
Supposed to sign up for Michelle at also do a little recap
The year of the seltzer
Minnesota Skeptics
Journal policy walk
Thank you so much and I apologize
Next to Ross thank you so much you know about Asia Wok
Hygrocybe Ross next
Could go either way. Bazil's or basil not entirely sure but either way thank you so much you know policy wonk
Having to go to the bathroom
Vicky they could come up here and I'll probably walk
Text Claire Genevieve
Elevator
And Richard thank you so much for now.
I'm a policy wonk
Business
Money off at heroin
Usually large
Website.com
Some folks are in need and carry on that spirit
Jordan we're making good progress on the year of the shelter I'd like to say thank you to everybody who has responded so positively
Play to the idea of me drinking an absurd number of Seltzer's
This idea
Ball people very interested in
To take a moment to honor the people and I understand
Why would anybody not be into the year that some people don't like seltzer
Position
And as such I'm not going to
Talk about every single Seltzer that I drink
On the podcast
To be annoyed
My Seltzer Journey
Which is knowledge freight.com selfie
And there is a graph charting the rank of
To know all of the
Specific shelters that are being drank
Please go check that website it'll be updated
Periodically probably after every episode as I'm editing my gel
Update website but we are on track
For the
Really I mean
It's only the first week you know every every long journey begins with a single step we are at 12
Right now 12 doctors tried
Which is at the point of our last recording
What I'm going to do is
Almere the Seltzer what I'm going to do is I'm going to bring you some of the standout okay
Alright because one of the things I'm realizing as I drink more and more these shelters is f****** most of Hummer
Check the page there was a significant course correction it look like everything was trending downward until you got to like
Like a median level like the first Seltzer if you tasted it now would probably be
Closer to the middle that it was at the beginning coffee one would be a little lower probably
Hello would be okay alright
Baps was definitely the passionfruit wonder by bubbler
It's a bubbler without an e
S*** I think I might be discovering a love of passion fruit
I don't know if it's a flavor that I've had much exposure to over the years I might have thought it was a fake fruit
IHOP
But if
It was really good flavors good the Seltzer's fantastic
I think it's also one of the ones that have cancer
If you want to
Still want a little kick
Dorothy oh no
That's another thing I should point out is we have not
Nor will we ever take any kind of sponsorship from a Seltzer company
So if you're out there and yourself accompanying ticket hate maybe I should get in on this game seems like
Pretty exciting people really enjoy the year the South Shore let's give these guys a few bucks to do some Buzz Marketing
No way
You can't however send filter
No we're not going to play Frontier company name but if you want to send this out there if nobody's going to say no to his luck no matter
How much money Spindrift gives me I'm not going to say it's Kush
And no matter how much money bubbler doesn't give me I'm going to say that that passion fruit
Wonder
Strong stuff for the sad
But now let's get down to business on today's episode let's start with an out-of-context drop
From Today Show
The New World Order
Oh no don't say something like that.
Oh no
Hey yo
I don't know
Alex at the New World Order
Knife and then he's going to get NWO spray-painted on his back
Let's start here on the 23rd
Alex starts the 23rd
Play
Yeah it's just that he has the key to solving all of Humanity's problems
This is so big
Rosetta Stone Skeleton Key
Universe
Why don't you talk about this
Music
That opens the door the trees America in the world
As well
Are we killing time
What is happening
And it's not
What topic
I just come out and put it out there
Lost in the shuffle
I guess
I don't I don't really know exactly what he's talking about
Time
You could have used to talk about the thing right and then it wouldn't have been lost in the shuffle
Right
Episode I'm not positive I know exactly what the thing is I don't know
This
What is this what is this
What is Yuzu
Yeah I don't know it's dramatic
It's Beatrice castle that's what it is
So Alex downright and he wants
Breakout his
Definition of the word
Lockdown
Is that it
Prison
You had your comments Donnie but I'll go outside in a minimum
Medium security prison
And walk down is when you're put back inside your jail cells for night
Lock.
Wow it goes down
Down
Seldomly after us
Control of a riot
State of isolation or restricted access
Initiated as a security measure
Mercy is on lockdown nobody
Okay
I like to have fun with definitions of dictionaries and see what other meetings we can find for the word lockdown
Pacific prison riot
According to dictionary.com another meaning for lockdown is a freeze or a pause
The word can be used to describe a temporary State of Affairs that
Requires a positive normal activity
That was even more fun
As we consult Merriam-Webster find the definition for martial law
Quote the law administered by military forces that didn't vote by a government in an emergency when the civilian law enforcement
These are unable to maintain public order and safety
According to Encyclopedia Britannica wanted most defining characteristics of Martial law is the military takes over the
Creation of Justice
And none of that stuff is happening at all right now
And if it were happening the only person who could invoke
Would be Trump
This highlights an interesting problem with Alex is rhetoric
I don't think he knows what martial law is
Yet it's his primary fear and his Brandon
He seems to think that martial law is just any kind of law he doesn't like or rules or guidelines that he finds inconvenient
And that's not what martial law is
I think he just knows that the name of it is scary to people
And he's just going to yell about it all the time not having any idea
I also I went down a long Rabbit Hole looking at the history of martial law
Two of the most
Important
Figures in terms of the early history of the definition of martial law
Work Thomas Jefferson
And Andrew Jackson Andrew Jackson
Enacted martial law on New Orleans
And refused to lift it
Yeah after the imminent threat of an English invasion
Ended
The people who Alex lionizes and admirers
Are people who have a rocky history
In terms of
The definition of Martial law becoming something that could apply
Two civilians
Yeah it makes
He's talking about cosmology includes blind hero worship of the people doing
The exact same thing that he's been fighting against his entire life that makes perfect
This might be it
I don't know what is it
I don't know what is this I don't know if this is it or this or what
A big story that Alex has on his episode in so
It might be at
Messages that
Cihs
Twitter and Facebook and Google
Porsche official Chinese government
So this is an amazing level of abusive rhetoric
Alex's literally spent years Gathering about how it doesn't matter of Russian actors spread misinformation on social media in order to
Help Trump in the 2016 election have a completely meaningless
But now he seems to think it's a biggest deal in the world that some Chinese actors of done something on social media
Seems like a problem from a consistency standpoint but whatever
Alex is trying to get the idea out this is this is the way he's covering the story is that the entirety of
How the virus panic
In the United States
Is the result of the machinations of Chinese agents
And at this New York Times story that he's referring to prove it
Call
Is New York Times stories from April 22nd
As a headline Chinese agents help spread messages that sowed virus-panic in the United States
Officials say
Like I said you trying to use this headline to suggest
For the entirety
Of the fear surrounding the first is a Chinese misinformation campaign
But that is not what this article is about
This article is about messages and text that spread around about Trump being set to lock down the entire United States back in
In mid-march
From the article this passage begins with a section of the message
Question
They will announce this as soon as they have troops in place
Prevent looters and rioters warned one of the messages which cited a source
Department of Homeland Security
Corey said he got the call last night and was told to pack and be prepared for the call today with his dispatch orders
This is an article about misinformation campaign to take advantage of the virus situation
But Alex wants the presentation
To be that the virus situation itself
Only feel so sleepy or because of this misinformation campaign
Which is just not supported by his source
If China isn't back doing this like what the New York Times articles describing then f*** them that's really shity
But it's still not what I was talking about
Also this article relies on an assessment from the intelligence
Community who Alex is supposed to not trust and be again
And while we're on the subject isn't the New York Times supposed to be run by the globalist tours in bed with China
Why would it be running a story about Chinese agents spreading misinformation
Wouldn't they not do that
Well then
Your
So now the globalist I don't know if you heard this
Globalist
Because of the quarantine have split into six separate faction
One of them controls the New York Times that it's fighting against the other five three of whom are pro-china.
Two of them are anti-russia but Pro Trump and the three horipro China
Are all over the map.
I got to go
Good fun catching up
Raptors now I don't even
The story has
Take care of yourself.
Complicated
Okay so Alex is thrilled on some level because people yelling at him
About Bill Gates
But you know I shouldn't be negative because
Last night
I was driving home
I pulled up to a red light
Ford F-150 roll down the window and said
We love you Alex
Then this morning
One of their parking lot
Hydrobike
Plumbing repair truck
Hey rolls down the window Legos
We're winning Alex keep it up
Adele boy
Redneck
24-hour. Frozen I'm not Alma Street
People riding I know Bill Gates of the enemy
I mean look
The way I look at that is like I do show better much Alex Jones sucks
And he's the worst
Yeah and if I walked around in my daily life and people yelled at me
Hey fuk Alex Jones I would find that to be an uncomfortable situation. Look at that as like
Victory
On my part I would look at it as
This is this this sucks
Do you know what concerns me is that based on what Alex is telling me if I were walking along with
Said he hears all of this stuff
I would not see any of those people
He would he would turn to be like did you hear what that lady in the F-150 just sent you said f*** Bill Gates and I'll be like
Alex but there's no one here the F-150
He hasn't been sold for 40 years it's the ghost
This road doesn't exist
We're in the woods Alex
We've been camping
A 6-month it is a concern that these imaginary real I would say that that's not
Like
I don't feel like that is a good audience
Yeah we're like
Healthy
Sort of way that people interact with
The content you put out
I wouldn't
I wouldn't like that
Because it's not really about making any change
Or anything
It's about riling people up
We love you
Alex's getting the response that he want
Which is blind
Visceral anger
And that's just stupid that's
Just not
It's not good
So earlier I think I was on her last episode Alex's developing
Narrative about worldwide starvation
Starbucks
You have a complaint that like
Okay man we're all talking about people dying of coronavirus cuz that's sexy people dying in the devel
Jumping World
Not
Who's riding about
How are you reading
Oh no no no
Global
I'm out of infections
The White House task force a pads last find all coronavirus cases deaths is coming
19 regardless
Pause
Liberty Chevrolet Charlotte
Boston's
Well I believe it
Getting to the fear
Sexy it's fine it's cool
Cell phone
You're a hero
Put shop
Happens all the time
Here's what I'm going to do
Call today don't tell guests joining us
Because
This is really really afford information I got today off balance a lot of stuff today
We had used to turn this around
I wonder what it was that threw him off his games that morning baby that is ex-wife filed a motion
Tuesday the 2nd to have that day
I don't know maybe I don't know I don't know what this point
Maybe
I looked at the Ivanhoe
Cointreau
I looked at the docket and apparently the hearing to possibly disqualify his lawyer
Is set for this Friday 8:30 a.m.
I don't know if
Like
That is the fundamental thing he's wrestling with obviously it seems like
Like what else threw you off your game this morning
It's definitely not whatever this is
Right
I want to make you hear about the two things that Alex is comparing in terms of relative sexy
So there are people who were talking with the issues of the potential food crises in the developing world
Those people are officials in the UN who Alex hates enough
We can't possibly accept that they're actually the ones raising the alarm about this issue that I was just trying to pretend no one is talking about
Also reopening our economy fully will not solve that problem
If we reopen everything prematurely we run a real risk of seeing infections and deaths Skyrocket
They're which point our economy will be in a far more severe situation
It isn't now
The choice between safety and protecting the economy is a false choice
Anything that will help people in the developing world the most
Is for us to continue and accelerate our commitment to providing foreign aid for people in other countries
Revere even if times get tough here
That's a policy Choice the Trump could make any should
Second as of YouTube all deaths being labeled coronavirus deaths
Alex's is lying about that
It all traces back to an April 7th press conference in Wichita
Said the quote if someone dies with covid-19 we're counting that is a covid-19
Team.
This is in line with the CDC guidance
Switch says the patient to die with covid-19 positive test should have that listed on their death
And if it has two isn't available it should be listed quote
If the circumstances are compelling within a reasonable degree of certainty
Fact check spoke to a professor of epidemiology at Harvard
Who did concede that there would be a small number of cases of people listed as covid-19 deaths
When that is not what led to their deaths
But quote
A greater issue as errors in the other direction
Deaths caused by covid that are not counted as such
He went on to say quote overall it seems likely the well the few individuals who would have died anyway or getting called covid deaths
There are many more deaths caused by covid that are not attributed to covid
They also spoke to Sally Akins
Spokane County Medical Examiner and president of the association of medical examiners who said quote
The true facts
Are the covid-19 deaths likely will be underreported on deaths
Certificates not over recorded
This is Will especially be true as deaths that occur in homes
And not in hospitals mount
Not all jurisdictions are able to test home dads with typical symptoms
For covid-19
Alex can play games by spending Burke's
Sis, it's all you want but it doesn't change the reality that the medical professionals in this country
Are not just taking every death and calling it a covid death because that's sexy
It's equally untrue that no one is talking about the food-related humanitarian crisis
It's looming because it's not sexy enough
I was just making these things up because that's what works are
Designer
Yeah it doesn't seem like either option to talk about is very sexy
I find them to be both incredible and pressing it up.
Entirely on of avoidable
Almost entirely avoid
Like it is it is him complaining about stuff that
Should have been taken
Care of a long time ago and acting like it's not
Huge party
His
Worlds
It's treating things like this as like an inevitability of life as opposed to like it. This is a choice that's being made
There is a way that could be taken to the places they need to be
And I bet oversimplifying things obviously there
A million different variables. There are more things that
As a country we could do
I'm even in the heart
Borat meme just more simply if you want to start talking about food food banks are running absolutely die
Lilo and
They're letting food spoil because they can't sell it to a grocery
Like it is it is absolutely disgusting
It is f****** tragic that we are letting so much food
Just died and when so many people need it. There's there's resource allocation issues that
If we could die
Really prioritize and solve those
They would make a
Massive difference
And
But we are making
Not also In that clip even is Alex didn't say something through him off his game this morning I think you can tell that he's not in
Game shape on this episode
It's
Drastic
How bad he is at his job
Adjust like
Stammering and kind of like long
Pauses you doesn't seem to know where he's going with anything
It's really
It's jarring like
This is this is a real life
Shocking kind of example of that
Share this video just submit
Forecast
4 minutes
And then we'll
Come back and
God almighty
You just seems flat there's like no energy doesn't seem like he's really into this like it really hurts to listen
Listen to like not because I I care but because it's like
Literally
Shakin all over the place like slow register Alex
This is like walking through mud
He is he is not killing time he is guilty of first
Degree murder
This is bad
So Alex gets to talking about how like there's a trap
Blood blisters have set a trap
Alright
Well then what's the point of having the key there's no doors help
The Alex layout Astoria
The bear trap close
Elastic
Don't either get our lag out
Color light off.
A good position to be in
But if I can't get my leg out of this thing very quickly I'm going to pull a knife out and cut my leg off
I'm just trying to get it up and I'm going to drive myself off
Going through my own ankle
A couple dozen wolves
That's not enough time to get your ankle off
Climb into a hole
Hey leg
Alex's leg is Infowars
He's talking about closing Infowars and quitting in order for him to be able to retain a certain amount of wealth
Carrying on
Living a reasonably comfortable life
Police talk
I'm about another this makes sense in any other
There's a worldwide pandemic going on but that is not reason for Alex to quit
When she gets weird or bad that's when propagandistic conspiracy Liars make their bread
All the things that I put Alex on the map are examples of him exploding tragedy and profiting off other people's pain
Permits co-opting of the Waco standoff at the beginning of his career
Dim rising to prominence is a 9-11 truther
Mayweather highlights of his career
Sandy Hook denialism lying about the Boston bombing
Consistent antagonism towards immigrants in the lgbtq community
All he does is profit up
And this situation is a perfect opportunity for him
It's almost like a meatball right in the center of the
Play I just don't believe that absent other circumstances Alex would see what's happening in the world as anything other than a chance for him to
Make a shitload of money
That's exactly how we behaved in the early days of the outbreak
Maybe Alex is taking this so seriously because the global threat
Right and that's what he wants us
I don't think so
Wants us to think that the global is just threatening him
But that makes literally no sense
Given that his entire career has been full of claims that the globalist are actively threatening him all the time
You said that they made attempts on his life before in that very specific threats have been made
They tried to pretend the drum corsi's coverage of the Seth rich
Conspiracies s*** was so dangerous to the globalist
About to make a dead man switch
What are the defining features of Alex's broadcast-style is a constant insistence
Globalist or threatening his life
He needs people to think that's happening because it allows them to pretend that the topics he's covering or somehow dangerous and bikes 10
Accurate
However he's been making these threats up the entire time
As he is now
Threats from the globalist should always be understood as code for consequences of Alex's actions
Sandy Hook families Victor the victims families suing Alex
Is presented as a globalist attack
But it's really the consequence
Movies action
And lying about them
And helping subject them to vicious harassment
Whatever you talking about now is no different
Whether it's the impending sign from the FBI FDA some other case that he knows he's going to destroy him
How to Preparing his audience to believe that no matter what consequences come his way
It's really just evil globalist punishing him
For being such a
Ineffective thorn in his side
That's why his leg isn't a trap and he's got to cut it off
Yeah it's like that old if you're if you're so accustomed to privileges any kind of any
Change feels like an attack on you he's so accustomed to the privilege of never having to face consequences for his actions
Now the idea of roosters coming home
Terrifying
I'm dying
My legs in a trap
Consequences for his actions
Younger maybe he would be more emotionally prepared to deal with this
Maybe would have f******
Quit already
Alex is dumb headspace where he is like
Really just like
You know I got to cut my leg off
Okay get out of this trap
Why the f*** am I even trying to help people
Why am I trying to stop the globalist
You let things even get to this point
Ask myself why am I trying to save this
If I really hate the leftist
What they do
I should be supporting them
Because they're going to be the ones of the first to go under this
Can I sit back to my realize
Process
Thing to do to just tell the truth and try to save everybody how
Deserve it
Is audience of amazing activist
They do deserve the truth
Great
Someone think
Children
Stop one
Imagine the start of the show today
What is this the Pentagon comes out and realizes
Jack was a mouthpiece for communist China
The covid-19
Stereo from the beginning to shutdown the US economy
See if confirmed because of that New York Times story that Alex is lying about
So I guess that must be the big news cuz he sang I haven't gotten to the big news and then immediately references
That story has already
Anyway Alex is a
Dump douche
He talks about like hey look we're responding to this situation
One-way responded to other things in history the same way
Great and he's very dumb
What you doing is taking something in this historical context and comparing it to the Past historical context that I think it's a brilliant
I don't think it's not I don't think it's always dirty pool you know like I think you could probably do it it responsibly
Alex is doing this
Just so stupid
Americans acting like this before we launched
Millions of people are Wars
Millions in the Civil War
Rice
Wow
You can go outside
You shouldn't think it's cuz black people have right buddy
So a couple points here literally before the development of germ Theory
We didn't know how diseases spread at that point
And according to a 1993 report in the journal clinical infectious disease quote
Two-thirds of the approximately 660,000 deaths of soldiers were caused by uncontrolled infectious disease
An epidemic
It's played a major role in holding several major campaign
This article estimates that these diseases prolong the war by as much as two years
Soldiers in the Civil War had to deal with outbreaks of measles malaria smallpox and a bunch of other conditions the doctors at the time had no
No idea what to do with or how to prevent
If Medical Science had any idea about what infectious diseases were in the 1860s it's entirely possible that has to
Filleti's might have been postponed it outbreak
Even as it was
Many battles were delayed because of disease
So I have no idea what Alex thinks he's talking about
Also
I'm going to leave aside the whole notion that the Civil War was fought to give black people rights
Considering that the Civil Rights Act was passed until 1964 in the Voting Rights Act
Just passed the next year
The question of what it means to get rights is a messy complicated question that I
Prefer not to unpack
Right now since it's secondary to
And you brought this up
Alex should not think the Civil War was fought to give black people write does not believe that the Civil War was about
Slavery
Countless occasion
His relatives fought on the side of the Confederacy and he's been very insistent that it was mostly about protectionism and states right
Civil War is a notable example to give black people Bridal
That would have been
Disrupted by an outbreak like the one we're seeing now
I want to make yours that Alex doesn't ever say s*** is words mean nothing
When it's expedient for him he wants to any wants to appeal to his races face
Is it warm up into slavery you dumb sjw
What is important to pretend that he's stupid anti distancing protest of the equivalent of abolition
Houston 1850s
Is it
Do black people ride
He can argue about things because he doesn't mean anything he says
Everything purely exist as a means to an end
Also Millions didn't die in Civil War the high-end estimate is approximately 750
I don't
Think he gets to say we either
When he said that's why we fought the Civil War
To get black people rate
I know that's why we fought the Civil War
You did not fight your a Confederate
People from
Yes
10 Stoopid
There's another thing that Alex teases a whole bunch
On this episode that he never really pays off at all and that is that he believes that all
All Trump media
Except for himself all the right-wing media
Has been paid off by the Chinese
Let me get this
Public relations firms
Almost
Every major news site that was Pro Trump
Taking money
You want to know those names wouldn't you
Sure
That's why we have those people to look up those names
Call Jaron while I want you to think about that understand that
I'm thinking
Chinese agents helped spread
Messages that showed virus-panic in US
Samart
Intelligence agencies
Yes you are
Way
Freedom
We the People control the government
Our will
Lighters in the president we unlocked
Is exeggcute
Judith Light
Dictators
Direction
Myself
Us intelligence agencies in law enforcement
Globalist
The minute they began to come under Us control
Paradox
Louis translate Alex's explanation of why he's not against the intelligence Community this time
All he's saying is that he accept the things the Intel Community says when it matches up with what he wants to believe
30 globalist anytime they say it is something that contradicts the position he wants to know it's there spirit
Can feel their spirit
Exchanged it's as simple as just
You can dress it up as a noble by saying goodbye
In line with my narratives
I don't think it's bad to have a healthy distrust of the US intelligence apparatus but
That is not what Alex does
He just uses them as a storytelling prop
In a way that makes what they say or do
If it works for Alex of Heroes if it doesn't the globalist
Just a filter you can take released information through to make it presentable to his audience
Make him sound like he actually has position
He doesn't
He's just a piece of s***
Yeah I mean that even that itself is so autocratic of just like
When they do what I say they should do
Then they're good people and when they don't they're bad
People I should have
Complete control over everyone.
Not yet the only definition of good or bad hero or villain
Is does this work for me
I'm really more interested in these people who have taken these payoffs from the Chinese in the right-wing media
That Alex is talking about
I don't know he doesn't say
I think he's about to
Okay
Your position in the universe
Providence
Genetic future
What type of wart is covert
It is very very hard to beat
Still I'm not release the secret
How to release some stuff that I was about to do it
Frustration
Hopefully I pray to God let me tell you on my lunch right now
Can you imagine if Brian stelter got on his show and was like top story
Let me report that
I'm sorry I was about to tell you guys but the biggest news in the world will save Humanity or something
Well I'm sorry I'm praying to her permission to be able to tell the story can't do it there's a key to a door
And I'm going to open this door for your own oh God we're so like inundated in the world of Alex Jones
You a******
I know that he's insincere in all this
Bulshit dramatic Pediatrics sincerely that's a level of like
Religious zealotry that is
So
Hey in the vacuum like if you just heard of that not knowing who Alex was like oh my God what you think is f******
When I was in 7th grade I remember my English teacher about to explain the somatic
Residents of A Separate Peace I couldn't do it
God told me I can't do it so we're going to watch a video today
Oh God
The biggest thing that Alex has going on this episode 19 Tire time is Miss representations of this New York Times
The article and so he has to deal with a little bit of an issue
And that is like wait
Anthony or X globalist
I'm telling you exactly what he told you
3 months ago
Chinese
Panic in the US
OurTime
Because Trump is fine
Wow
Stats
Somebody's listening to that and believed Alex whenever he says that b*******
There there
Yeah if you buy that
Nintendo I never believed the New York Times
But this time they were forced because
Cuz Trump is fighting back right
What are you f****** need to weigh to justify the misrepresentation of the headline
Wild Savannah
Even if you believe that
Like
Should be allowed to tell me
What to do
Imagine
Pictures of Barack Obama as President and he told you how would you feel about that
I think Alex would not be indoors
The right-wing media has been co-opted Buddy
He's not being specific
Also the keys dropping these weird
Like he talks about how come someone tried to buy him out last
Here I don't know if I believe this
This is just f****** weird
And then
You start singing The Devil Went Down to Georgia
Through ad agencies
Chinese have bought off most amazing news websites
We got a problem
One of the richest men in the world
Last year
Nigerian scam again
Devil Went Down to Georgia
Charlie Daniels Sean
Three jumps up on a hickory
You might be a football player
Not like that
Experiences and you don't have
But here's the difference
Sellout
To the devil and then not you you
If you don't want me to sell out to the devil you better buy my products
Sure I've been railing against how you shouldn't sell out to the devil and that that is a literal crime against God
Criminal
Think about that the most is that
Definitely
Call all of the only person who like to be like dude I'm Alex
Play rock music
All about it
All about
So
There's a real
Conflict that I have
About Alex using
Concept in the idea and the image
People dealing with hunger in the developing world
As a prop
In his
Meredith yeah I find it to be really offensive
ICare
And thankfully in this Mexico Peaks playing but he really doesn't care about.
Hard
Definitely rooted in reality
Population
Really
Myself and my family retarded
Those people are being killed
TV
Amazon
Yeah well the concept of altruism as we know is made up from selfishness
Space aliens what was that was the plan
Look man I I I got to say
That's disappointing
That's exactly what I thought he thought though
But even then he doesn't actually care about the people sorry so he doesn't even believe his own lies
About itself in
Brian rose on the guy from London
Interview with David Icke
Kick-off YouTube there was no virus
And all that and like f*** this noise
Look I don't care it's a really long interview it's about half of the show and I do I don't care
Fairly interested but they're just complaining about how he got the kickoff
Any trouble birthday but I can consequences
He's really just an hour-long promo for how Brian
Is going to do another interview with David Icke and how are you trying to start his own YouTube I am very very naughty
Interested in this and I'm not going to play along with Alex's
The blatant promotional content like it's
It's
I don't
I don't know whether it's like broker content or if it's just like
Hey let's hope this guy fundraise for his
Fringe weirdo YouTube Project
That YouTube
$300,000 in donation
Wow Bryan Bros apparently it's somebody who has
A bit more of an audience than I had any idea
Autonomous videos
It is really hilarious cuz I'll excuse you in like I listen to you all the time you want the best like I've loved you for like 3 years
I have never heard his name come up until the David Icke situation
So whatever
I think most likely
The explanation of it is
Alex recognizes that this is a guy who has a pretty sizeable audience he's trying to go off on
So whatever anything and anyone
Interview from the 23rd and it's Alex
Again discussing this idea that the right-wing media is taking Chinese money
But he won't get specific
We have no idea
But I know about the advertising firms that paid them money
Today
It was the right thing to do
Some of the groups I know we're getting
How many Chinese money
Other names
Tomorrow but
Gus
Sometimes I consciously decide to say something
Then there's this other Force comes in it's always right
Call a doctor
Say something
Then I don't say it
Metreon
What
It's not God's mystery it's
Baseline awareness of libel
That's what I would assume that's the only way that that Alex has a recognition.
What do evolve well to like
Libel someone like
Hillary Clinton net worth George Soros They Don't Really Care and they're not going to
Even dignify you with a response or sue you
But you can f*** around and accidentally say something about some media organization
That's libelous like they're on the Chinese payroll
They might sue you
Fox News when bestowed
You run you run the risk that someone might actually respond to you
Anyway the people like Hillary or
Soros would
And I think Alex is aware of that and that's God's
So that show is a disaster the 23rd is the worst it's
Really bad
Alex's office game
Nothing really interesting happens
90/24
Comes around
I was like
I didn't think it could get worse
But this show is one of the worst
I've ever heard
Yes I really do
Maybe there is some sort of a cosmic connection with like my birthday
And Alex is just
So bad on this episode
In some ways that are actually
Incredibly funny
And some that are like that's
That's disturbing
I know there's that are like
Go to bed go home you're done
You're done a****** just call it yeah
So we start off with Alex claiming
But the New York Times has confirmed
Some of his narrative
Weeks ago
That
The population
A lot of folks had already died from pneumonia
Symptoms
But Steve already cured
Tuff Stuff
To all of it
The power grab
New York Times yesterday
Already in the United States in November
Down Jay Sean
So I couldn't find a New York Times story that matches with Alex's talking about that such
What kind of left to use context clues to figure out what he's rambling on about
I reviewed a bunch of possibilities and I'm pretty sure Alex is just misrepresenting comments that New York Governor Andrew Cuomo made
Stop by the timeline that the outbreak
Grandma was talking about the delay in action and said quote
So what's the lesson
An outbreak anywhere is an outbreak everywhere
When you see a November and December and outbreak in China
Just assume the next day it's in the United States
When they say it's in China just assume the virus got on the plane that night and flew to New York
Including Newark Airport
And now it's in New York
That has to be the operating mentality because you don't know that the virus didn't get on a plane
All you need is one person to get on that plane and China and come to New York
The way the virus Transformers that's all you need and you can't assume two months later that the virus is still going to be sitting on a park bench
In China waiting for you to get there
Grandma wasn't admitting that there were cases in November or December he was saying that your mindset in November and December should be to
Who assume that there are
Bottom line is this has nothing to do with her being cases
Is the covid-19 in the United States in November
As far as we know there's pretty solid consensus at the first known case was this
Coronavirus in the United States presented on January 19th
And was a guy in Washington who arrived at the hospital having a cough and a fever for 4 days
He returned from visiting family in Wuhan on January 5th
Is it possible there were cases prior to that
I mean it's not impossible it's just pretty unlikely according to experts
Alex has done nothing to demonstrate his assertion and until he does he's just talkingshit
I challenged Alex to show his work and saying that Steve
Sonic said so isn't good enough
Buckhead
I doubt that I'm going to take the word of the guy who killed
Coronavirus
In January I don't think I'm going to
I don't think I'm going to trust
Him probably not now it is another thing that it's impossible for people
Cross that line of like
A gross overreaction memes
U-Save lot
So how can it be a gross over-react
Do you know what I'm saying
Is the acceptable oh it's if we overreacted
Only 1,000 people died
That's 1,000 people who didn't need to f****** die
Yeah you know like that's that's not an over react
It's the correct
It's so f***** up that people are still framing it is though
That's that's our choice
A gross overreaction or even the Optics work at night is okay
Just tragic
Alex is he's on borrowed time
Because he's been getting threats
Like I mentioned
Do you see your glove
The wolves
Everyone
You better grow up
You should speak to a mirror semi
In order for Alex to be put in prison there would need to be a crybaby need to be
Criminal charge
I don't know if I'm aware of any crimes that Alex is looking good for right now
Criminal
Beyond that
The prison you need to stand trial and if you were innocent it at every opportunity to prove it
He's a rich white dude he would be afforded every benefit
The justice system
I don't believe that any of these imaginary globalist if they were real would ever want to put Alex on trial
Even if he's guilty as s*** all you're doing is giving him a gigantic platform to play the victim and create his own martyrdom
Narrative
So I guess they have to kill her
That makes even less sense
This entire time for Alex's
School career
His answer to why he wasn't dead yet was because he was too high-profile so the globalist
Knew that killing him would only make him more powerful
They knew the killing hours early confirm that his narratives are true or so Alex Bowie
It is that no longer the case
Because I want to still super high profiles
The globalist
Know that they can't kill him without any Berkeley proving him right about all the bulshit he yells all the time
To be clear I don't believe that Alex is alive because he's too high-profile to kill
I think he's alive because none of the public figures he targets really care about what he says
And they rightly view him as an idiot
But for 25 years Alex has argued that he is only alive because he's high-profile but now I guess that doesn't mean anything
The only reason the globalist Never Killed Alex before is out the window and I guess he's been told he's fair game or something
This is all a load of s***
It's clearly a pre-emptive narrative
About something
Do you knows his days on are numbered and he's got to be sure there's a myth
In place before that so no one thinks his downfall was his own fault
For posterity sake
You have to make sure you know that he was the victim and all that
Which is greater
Yeah that's
That's kind of what I was thinking whenever he was starting to talk about how all of right-wing media is owned by the global
This is like
Eventually when he goes down
Everybody's going to talk
There is going to be a national day of
Dunking on Alex it will become in probably a lot of right-wing media will even sell ammo
Or Nah them out pretty hard because they will want to differentiate themselves
From him somehow in order to like
Push him under water so they can get some air or whatever you know
No the way the machine works on the right-wing media is the moment somebody goes down everybody on the right we can beat
India piles on like
All of our problems all of the things that we f***** up forever those are
Him we are not like him he went down so he must be the only one who actually did
Something wrong
So Alex has been yelling about Bill Gates forever
The dude
I'm fine with that
Sure
In the next Club Alex talks about how like
Listeners have been sending him until on Bill Gates
Legitly but now he's got new information
There's one
Piece of new information which I get to at the end of this episode and it is
A dud
Know what is this
Don't know okay
The listeners
Dive right now
They're flooding us with documents in videos
Never seen before
You would think that
We think it's funny
Spotify
Can't go on killing everybody that's fine
I'm not scared of him
Fox
So I mean you got here is
It's really smart for Alex to have kind of mulch
Simple big villain doesn't work right now
No it doesn't work but when there were counter demonstrations and protests to the right way
Marches and stuff like that
LaRosa's the perfect balance of Bill Gates falls out of favor for Alex
Any focuses largely on Soros even though Bill Gates controls everything
Fact checker
Even above Bill Gate right and then Soros is somehow in the middle like everyone is feeling
Play
The particular villain of this season is whichever one is more primary to the narratives
And assertive
The themes exact stuff like this
Whenever there is funding the primary narrative
Right. Contracts this is how this work
I just had the image of
Some some
Some personal assistant to Bill Gates just like walking
I'm leaning down real close and just whispering in his ear
Alex Jones wants
To know that
He will gladly die if
If it keeps you from killing people and Bill Gates just nodding George W bush Styles like
Or he just pulled out of butt
That's a loaded
Not this is one of my favorite things
In the world
We know that Alex
Believe that movies are reality
But Alex chose a really
Wrong example
Cool world
Ian Fleming
It was like number
Demanded MI6
Moonraker in the
Where there's a world government
Kill the entire human population
Why would why would the number three guy in MI6 write a book about that
Because we're just going to f****** space
Ian Fleming was never third in command at MI6
Is the personal assistant to rear Admiral John Godfrey director of Naval intelligence
Some intelligence. But he was
Also Moonraker came out 1955 not in the sea
60 oz talking about none of that stuff isn't Ian Fleming's book version of Moonraker that's all just from
The movie Fleming did not write the screenplay for it pretty much has nothing to do with other than the book has the same title
You see what happened was that in the closing credits of the spy who loved me
It says Bond will be back in for your eyes only
What does plan to be the next Bond movie produced
But then
Star Wars came out it was a gigantic box office hit
The Producers decided to shelled For Your Eyes Only ago something that could involve spaced and the title Moonraker is about his face
Play sounding is Fleming's titles
The plot of the book
Is it there's a guy named Hugo Drax is building a nuclear missile defense system for England called Moonraker
It turns out Drax is secretly a Nazi
Any plan this whole thing in order to Nuke London
Bonfils the planet Save the Day More Les your standard Bond storyline
No space no false Flags nobody weapons are hiding out in orbit or bunkers or whatever
The film version is a bit different
However it wasn't written by Ian Fleming
Is there a guy named Christopher would it would previously written a series of sex Rob's under the pen name Timothy Lee
The entire plot was changed Moonraker was no longer defense system it was a space shuttle
In the movie version Drax
Plans to head to space and then released nerve gas onto the planet to kill people
Eventually repopulating the planet with people he thinks are from Goods
Stock
There's plenty of
Discussion about about this among Bond fans how is a completely different movie from the book The Fleming Road
And it's super super clear that the reason that they were doing that was trying to cash in on Star Wars
Bond movies think Moonraker sucks
Anyway Alex is just seen that movie and things
Expertise in any way connected to the book
Ian Fleming Road
You have literally no idea what he's talking about you just making s*** up
Please understand
Alex has Justine movies and pretends that he's done research
He's a f****** idiot
That is annoying
I didn't know that about Moonraker
That's interesting to know it's literally the worst
Example Alex could use in pretending like Ian Fleming
Externalize the plan
So funny never read Moonraker
I cannot believe that he would
Not cuz of course
You can get away with it
It's not like anybody is red Moonraker
Why do people have not who listen to Alex Jones don't know so you can get away with it
The movie
Also feature of a number of Bob not necessarily really accurate to the books
Yeah I'm here in Flemingsburg
I don't know I've never actually read them I'm not super interested in that genre I've not seen a lot of those Bond movies either cuz I take the
First of all a little bit
Interpersonal everybody is a little bit
Yeah I don't know if I love spy
I can think of From Russia with Love
Yeah that was a good Bond
And then
I think we're pretty much done after that
Never Say Never Again You Can't Say Never Again
Did you like I know that has a video game
I just love John being in anything I want Sean Bean die and anything
I thought you were saying Sean right
Knowshon being with oo6 in that one
I like the opening credit
Those are pretty funny you know when they got the barrel
That's great Austin Powers sucks
The Simpsons whenever Scorpio that one's based on a Bond film even when I was a kid
I thought
Austin Powers suck
I do like the Pink Panther though that's kind of spies
Like a direct parody of bond
They're so funny
Yeah
I love that I love it first
Laney
Very slow
But I like it
David Niven
And he's great
Best let's stop this
Xzibit raker is the real world plaid that's f****** hilarious
So I was just talking about there's no moonrakers the real globalist
Plan what have you and obviously as we just discussed
Sweetly stupid
This gets into him talking about like the globalist want to exterminate people
And he kind of says that he's cool with some exterminators
Some truth in the back
Environment
Innovating
Massive
Plunging
Hellish conditions
And the solution for that
Bill Clinton
Kroger
With high IQs
For drugging and then
Society
Sure love to hear that Alex is opposition to extermination is conditional
That's not absolute
Twisted no
Eugenics key would be better
And yet somehow this one see the problem with this whole Eugenics Exterminating people
Is this one's about power
If I were Exterminating people wouldn't be about power bi but by power
Yeah I mean
I think if you're sincere actor in you're opposed to the sort of thing like Eugenics or an extermination
It wouldn't be like my problem is who's carrying it out
Probably
Yeah your opposition to a would-be fundamental as opposed to like
If we kill off everybody in the Sudan or whatever
Time does he ever consider a more equal distribution of resources could also solve the
This problem
Do you know what I'm saying
Starting at the place of well obviously we need to exterminate
People that's the only explanation for what
What's going on I'm not saying that he saying
I don't know if there's a middle ground
I don't think there is a middle ground
But in terms of just taking him by the strict
Miss of his word that she was not happy for Peyton extermination he's just saying it would be okay if
If you need an ethical Aksarben
Nation dad
And they don't need
Need the Target high IQ males like he thinks himself stupid
Alex
Predict
Action about what we'll see in the future
I think this is from a movie I don't know what it is Maybe
Demolition Man maybe one of those c-note the three seashells
That's what this is no I don't know about the three seashells
Demolition Man it's one of those other s*** movies I don't know this is some sort of
I might be
Many people died
Structure going to come around
In
The back of that trash truck
You keep submitting like this about five years out from that
10:15
Thornton Avenue
Trash trucks
Okay
Alright so let me ask you the 2025 the next year the Seltzer will find out
Might be something does happen but not for like picking up Corpses
Is necessary to be picked up via only robot trash. I highly doubt that
I'm sorry
I just wondered
What would be preferable
If you know it's going to happen either way
Does it doesn't it make sense to just like get it over and done with us supposed to be in like I will fight as hard as we can
And for an extra 10 years
No because Alex is whole thing is it's about stalling the globalist
Plan
That's the only thing that's really worth crying
5 years to grow is
People in
Humanely connect with others but if we have 10 years
We could spend all that time fighting against this and not grow at all and then solve a lot of money
You sold me on that not the food
So we're in a situation where
Masks were trying to distance as best as we can
She wants to like
Talk solution
Cuz we are the world that require solution
Equal distribution of resource
Talk about Solutions
Cool
Solution
They can't make you do it
You got a medical reason
Where to print some of these up on Infowars
Make your own
Psychological disorder in my position
Dr. kornbluth
Do you want to put on there
Silence is suggesting the people fake
Conditions in order to be able to wear masks
Ain't going to sell masks that say that or something
I've got a delusion for your dad
Fraud Revenue stream
If anything happens to him
It was okay
Shortest continuing this trend of like
Amazing stuff yet
By the way
Bill Gates
Everything happens to you
You'll take care of thanks
Taking care of our children
Can't miss an opportunity racing racing through that at pitch
To a long thing about how like the globalist want you in City
So what they're doing is raising taxes to make it so you can't live in rural areas or something
Okay I don't know I don't I don't know about that but
Be there isn't met Alex's solution seems to be
But he wants people to start
Extremist Rod extremist right-wing
Compound
What are you going to do about it
Communities that say hey
Conservative
We want to conserve Humanity what Pro human
Laws where
Real safety studies that are out there
Followed
We're all this evil is not allowed
Giant
Electromagnetic
Thank God he made sure to point out this wasn't a cult
Me a call well it's either a cult or a
Terror cell
Think there's much difference between what he's describing
Extreme separatist
Community resource
Generally speaking extreme separatist
I've been shown to be Pro human
They accept
Definitely don't build these walls and fire guns at that
No no that be crazy
So Alex of the guests this is where everything goes
So f****** wrong on this episode
I ended up like
Okay Alex's to guests
Okay
I don't want to spoil anything
But I looked into them for no reason
YouTube
Diva audio Ray has an amazing background and I
Inventor of email I'm not going to go over zobaya believe procedures guide
Better now been 30 40 50 times
Working with
Reality was
First things first Chiva is a rare person on Infowars who actually has some credentials
You have a PhD in biological engineering from MIT but the climate invented email is where things start to get a little off
Track
Shiva claims that in 1978 or 1979 or maybe 1980 at the age of 14
Achievement is not been recognized because he's not white
You didn't work in the realm of by the system
This is one possibility or another
Possibility that some people have pointed out is that email existed prior to 1978
There were large
Computer networks that were linked
For Communications in the early 1970s through arpanet
And I have no idea what to even do with these clients
Hideaway wanted the Smithsonian to recognize him as the inventor of email so he sent them a bunch of documentation
And this is the Smithsonian statement upon review
Exchanging messages through computer systems what most people call email predates the worker by Dre
However the museum found Ida raise materials at served as signpost
The several stories about the American Experience
So they accepted as materials
Because they reflected his experience in the early days of
Computer techs that was relevant to history
But it didn't show that he invented email
The big piece of evidence that I do Ray has that he's the inventor is that he has a 1982 copyright claim
Or email
But it's not for email it's for his specific
Program that he wrote
This claim is clearly undefendable in court
Seeing as he doesn't go in Gmail and places like the Washington Post have had to print correction
Comes after accidentally refer to them as the adventurers no
I personally have no stake in this
I could care less whether or not this guy invented email but some people
Xbox in the world
Computing history who are not so chill about this
They do not like shivay Dre and some of that salve
Pretty scaping responses to his claim
Praise the fact that he was a teenager and he made a program to send emails to a small group of
Computers in the 70s
Because nothing to take away from that is impressive
Consensus I seem to see is that he didn't create anything that didn't already
Zest
Outside of the stuff especially lately I had to re has become a bit of a public coop
In 2018 he tried to run as a republican in the Massachusetts midterm election
Hoping to unseat Elizabeth Warren
Did he do it
I suspect he had the good sense to realize he wasn't going to make it out of a GI
P primary so you ran as an independent
Ultimately 44% of the vote
No I mean some pretty respectable
It's not much
But it's something
At this point he's running in the GOP Primary for the 2020 election hoping to unseat Ed Markey
I predict he'll be running as an independent again
Coronavirus situation has broken out either a is gone full-on conspiracy weirdo and started spouting a bunch of
The bolshit narratives we've heard Alex disseminate
On March 23rd to publish the letter that he sent to Trump where he talked s*** about dr. fauci and suggested that all people need
Vitamins and iodine be good to go with no need to quarantine or distance or anything like that
Send that through computer network
This is ignored medical doctor sending unsolicited medical recommendation
Comes to the president which is the Hallmark of a non crazy person
What are angles lately has been to get to dr. fauci fired
That's one of those big things but we have bureaucrats
Madison and you can talk to pretty much anyone and I could tell you behind closed doors that
Fauci this disgusting bureaucrat who graduated first in his class of Cornell Medical School wilda Medical
Unlike Ida Ray
Hydreigon past Infowars Gaston fellow Senate campaign loser De Anna Lorraine Ortiz most prominent
Voices in the fire
Fauci camp
This has nothing to do with that directly with I'd already but I wanted to read this little passage from Politico about Lorraine
Complaints about fauci
Quote his projection to change constantly
I think he first started predicting 2 million + deaths Lorraine complain
Saying she understood the number is the total number of projected deaths
Quote and now it's down to 60,000
And you know why such a sudden change that's a pretty drastic change
2 million + number comes from the famous Imperial College Study
Forecasting the results of an environment social distancing measures taken at all
Lower mortality projections of the result of extreme social disc
Such a shelter-in-place orders
Business closures
Lorraine said she did not know about that distinction
Wow I appreciate her honesty I appreciate
Oh I guess I should
I guess I don't know what I'm talking about
Am I stupid or also isn't that playing out in the introduction
That's weird
Reactionary child
Anyway it doesn't look like I do re-invented email and he's in the middle of just that this lunatic Blitz trying to rile up the truck
Base for his Doom 2020 congressional election
Call very pathetic
Can dump but it's also causing direct harm to people probably so I hope you have trouble sleeping
Goodnight
I'd be a real bummer to invent something and then
Suddenly put your head like you're in your room like studying and you're trying to get everything you've met this system here like
This s*** is going to change the world and then you pop your head out and everybody's like
We've had that for a while now like
Well I mean it would still be really impressive and I think that you could probably just really I think you could probably get a lot
Lot of respect
Within those world
If you didn't
Insist you needed to be
16 as the inventor of it
Trying to take away the the work
Achievements people who came before you take turns off a lot of people kind of think you're an a******
Can Isaac Newton situation where nobody else has
Shared it with anybody before and then he invented they like we already found it and now it's
Eden
Is going to be on here in a minute dr. Shiva is known by his fan
For that Alex said something
Foundry stupid
How many have died worldwide from the virus
That has
Casper covid-19
Incorrect
Never had the flu in the last year so you
Test positive Coronavirus
Father covid-19
Hysteria in the left
The shutdown
Create a phobia
Where you just expect the ocean sharks
Get eaten by sharks worldwide
You got about
How did is making up that part about the test for covid-19 all being false positive
Is literally nothing to back that up other than just repeating it over and over again
More importantly Alex's severely overestimating the number of people eaten by shark a year
Either 30 people eaten by sharks every year when in reality it's only four people were killed by sharks every year on average
Last year it was only two
Now this might seem like a miniscule distinction
But I'm not
The difference between 4 and 30 is a 750% error which is very significant
Enter you can say that I'm being a dick
The point I was trying to make is that there aren't that many shark attacks but we fear them because of movie
Fair enough I'm not disputing that point
I'm saying that I was just made up the 30 number 2 train act like he actually knows how many people get eaten by sharks every year
He doesn't
It's completely made up as a number you just want it just trying to make up a number that sounds small to him
It's way way higher than the real world number
This is a deceptively important point
A lot of the time Alex knows some
In this case
Did that there aren't that many shark attacks
You wants to convey that point that we think there are more shark attacks in there actually are because he wants to use that as an antelope
Virus
But he thinks that just saying there aren't that many shark attacks
Have to be convincing and authoritative
So he just
Makes up something to fill in the gaps
You know this audience have no idea how many people are eaten by sharks I didn't know that they'll just believe whatever number you says he pulls 3000
Out of his ass
He does this all the time
With small details like this and big narrative
This is what he does with headlines
Dinos
What the headline of an article says that makes up a details of what he assumes are in the article
You seen the movie Moonraker so we just assumed the book has the same makes up stuff about Ian Fleming writing it noted
Goebbels plot
Microcosm of Alex's career is very well encapsulated in a throwaway by about people getting eaten by sharks
Just make stuff up in order to fill in the gaps that he wants to do nonsense
What they start to realize that
You really suck again everywhere there's another small problem with that is
This isn't
Because the only way it would be like sharks as if when you got bitten by a shark
You became a shark your
Yourself and maybe there's a little bit of a
Shark bites are not a communicable disease
Also there's a little difference between like being eaten by sharks being killed by
So we get to dr. Shiva coming in and there's
Trouble right out of the gate
Because Alex like I said he has to Gaston that
Episode
And it turns out that
Dr. Shiva does not like Alex's other guests
Failing
Need to put in big vaccine
Champagne and immune system
What happens Alex
There are people
Kennedy Junior
He's been in this movement
Freaking time
Who is suppresses movement from people building a
Ghostblind
One of the guys are going to have on your show
They speak the same rhetoric
Hillary Clinton
Kennedy endorse Hillary Clinton three times
Kennedy family post John Kennedy
Is institutionalized not-so-obvious album
Listen I know you're in Massachusetts and and then so we just so happen to have this other Jesse disagree with
On later you're welcome to get into that person as well
Get into the big picture
We don't allow bashing Hillary Clinton
So Alex is new brushes
Easter break
Is a shill and you know that because he works with Robert Kennedy Junior's at limited Hangout
To try in
Corrupt the anti-vax movements with Robert
And I did not know he was crazy no yes
Really good god dammit
Isn't that you didn't know that
No I don't give a s*** about the
Why would I give a f*** about the Kennedys
And I was like they had it they had to Goodwin
Baby I don't even know if I would give them to
Yeah I know Robert Kennedy Junior's want to be like a big players in the DNC Zacks world
Yeah.
I think most people just kind of like alright whatever
Alex's other guests
Somehow associated with Robert Kennedy Jr so dr. Shiva believes him to be a shill
Point the finger at Hillary Clinton hard at all
Or something
So Alex rushes to break
Ivy comes back from break
Crazy stuff going on here and
Bill Gates
Criticizing the vaccine
Man
Mom same time
To be on the same time weather
The way it is
What am I
And
You dislike somebody
Call Michelle talking about that you can do it but
How many people
New show
Always say don't go Alex Jones Show
And the people say
You have that person on I won't go on your show and I just don't do that
I don't do that
That's not what I'm involved in
Transferrin here
Ron I want to hear what he has to say
Abalone
There's that Trainwreck
And so
Probably table this issue and move on how do that too
Apparently dr. Shiva really really doesn't like this Rashid
Guitar character to the point
Is this like why there are for like 2 minutes
Start some s***
Alex roster break and now he's gone
Who knows what the f*** happened there but I can tell you this with absolute certainty
I don't care
Arizona Duel of the Fates there between the doctors
That's what
So Alex says that Rashid matar is a medical doctor
As it turns out he's an Osteopath
Which isn't a horrible thing but when you're an osteopath on Infowars
You're automatically very suspect
And suspect is a great word for guitar
In 2007 the North Carolina Medical Board recommended the pitar no longer be allowed to treat children and cancer pay
Ever found anybody charged a whole bunch of money to apply unproven
Mets on patience
Incidentally one of the treatments he apparently used with IV hydrogen peroxide which is bleach
Hey
Treating cancer patients is because his unproven and in effect
The treatments were severely dangerous the reason they wanted him to stop treating children
Was because part of his hustle was claiming that is chelation treatments
To quote or Autism
Pictures of course caused by vaccine
Guitar is famous because he had an association with fellow anti-vaxxer Jenny
McCarthy
And because the media played along with his bullshittin 2009
Inspiring cheerleader for the Washington football team named Desiree Jennings
Claimed that the flu shot have given her dystonia
A neurological disorder
But she was cured by protaras chelation
There are so many problems with her story Chief among them according to the initial story about her case in the Luton time
She saw over 60 doctors trying to diagnose her condition
Show me article Desiree has seen her primary care physician physical therapist speech therapist neurologist
Psychologist
Psychiatrist in a bevy of nurses
Amazingly it was her physical therapist Who provided the clinical diagnosis
Dystonia
That's intensely suspicious
The fact that you saw the neurologist who didn't catch this but somehow her physical therapist did
That's weird
I have no idea what the reality of the situation is but I don't see any proof that this is what she had
Nor do I see any evidence of this was caused by a flu shot notarize any evidence of retarded anything to cure her
Jennings case was championed by Jenny McCarthy and her group generation the rescue as an argument against vaccines
And the media ran with it shows like inside edition to the fact that her case was reported
To the vaccine adverse event reporting system to give it elevated
Credibility
Although that would end up being a bad mood
These reports in that system don't
Contain identifying information but they are public
And dystonia is super rare
So there aren't many cases that are filed that is a symptom
The Examiner looked into it and found her adverse-event report and it includes this line
Quote
The admitting horologist felt that there was a strong psychogenic
Component to the symptom ology
I made a final diagnosis of weakness
I don't mean to Mark Jennings at all because it's entirely clear that you was very likely suffering with a real condition
Add that you was trying to get help with it just doesn't seem like I said anything to do with a flu shot
Really just unfortunate that at all likely to choose used by people with a ridiculous anti-vaccination jenda
Anyway that's how I got a bunch of attention by being attached to this case
Notable as a coronavirus conspiracy theories been talking to basic asking for s*** about fauci and Bill Gates
Remember
Whenever I was still doing the hearing aids thing somebody told me that there a yoga instructor told them that they had
Had Lyme disease
And age
Just wear like
So are we went to the real doctor
I'm editorializing there we went to the doctor and he said that nothing was wrong so then we went to
Florida and tribune
Experimental treatments for Lyme disease in your leg
Oh yeah I know
No
Why did you do that
Yep and I'm sad
Guitars one of these folks who profits off that stuff
Talk to him
Or maybe he's not
Let's move on from this guy
Are we don't have gas
Okay
I do things for Monday
Take a break from The Gas Man
Because yummy just becomes a big giant
Klusterfuk
Junior High Junior High
High School
The Waters of which I swim
School
Free cancel all yesterday
Fiasco
Electric guitar
What the f***
They look at people are being dramatic little baby so cancel it all out
Yeah I like that totally grown-up response to you very much
Alex's scolding them premature
Pink baby himself
So I'm going to take my ball and go home
My dad is going
Realmatt
Select his own devices Alex starts rambling and he ends up complaining more about head about all these people starving
Civilization
Irrevocably right now
Maybe too late
Gigantic deep prolong depression
An extra 20 million people on top of the 10 million are starving to death
These are real people
Rib sticking out on
Oh my God the Liberals are always like oh let's go
Take abandoned dogs and cats
People
Because you write off all those people you just
Your self
Thing
That simple
Obviously I agree with Alex divorce be done to address the severe issue of world hunger
I have to ask why he hasn't cared about this up until now
I recently stopped right now in the developing
Worldwide support Ron Paul of eliminating all foreign aid since at least 1980
Would you lead to the dance of Untold numbers of people
Why is Malik scared at all than average of 9 million people die of hunger related conditions every year
Why is lipid a part of the normal coverage let's say back
In 2017
Is it possible because he doesn't give a f*** about the actual issue and he's only using it as a political prop in order to justify his other position
A time like you have some kind of a moral High Ground
Let me answer that for you
It is
Play I find it
There would probably be an overlap
Between the people that he would be fine with getting exterminated and the people currently
Starving today
That's just my
General Violet imagine
Yeah
If you can solve the world count switch tracks hunger
Just takes you'll see that a lot of progress has been made in terms of tackling the world
There's still a lot of work
In 1990 there over 1 billion people living in hunger but by 2015 that number was down to 784
Obviously still way too many
That's a drop of about 20% Which is not nothing
Every year since then
We seen a reversal of that trend
2018 we're back up to 822 million people
Struggling with hunger and undernourished
What are the big issues surrounding this according to the UN is it countries where hunger is on the rise are seeing Rising
Income inequality
Is compounding the problem for the most vulnerable populations
Another crisis in both of these issues are only going to get worse as the effects of climate change become more pronounced
Yep this is very complicated and serious issue
One that the UN Affiliated nongovernmental organizations do a tremendous amount of work
Combating until you find solution
It's deeply disgraceful for Alex
Point to all the people around the world living in severe food in
Security it would all be okay
It wouldn't
But don't kid yourself
It's a sign of the season for making not to put more resources toward solving these problems
It's a policy decision to fund or not fun programs that provide food to vulnerable people and Trump doesn't seem too interested
Policies that fun that stuff
In his 2021 budget proposal Trump looks a cup more than 180 billion dollars
From the supplemental nutrition assistance
Program for approximately 30% of its budget over the next 10 years
This would come along with cuts to programs
Provide free or reduced-price School meals for kids in need
Give a f*** about hungry people in the country he's the president of
How can you even pretend for a second he cares about people were hungry in a foreign country
F****** absurd
Considering how many times Trump has talked about and
And followed through with cutting funding to the UN
You have to assume he doesn't really give a s*** about the effect that could have on the ability of things like the world food program
Operating
Here's what I would say
I admire Alex scaring people in the developing World dealing with Hunger even though I know he's only 40
The care I don't want us to come to cynicism here
So I'll try to build on that pretend concern
He's presenting
And I challenged him to look in the mirror and realize that the only two politicians he's ever really loved
Ron Paul and Donald Trump would let every last person in those foreign countries die if it meant getting rid of some taxes
And you-know-who would be
Be helped out fighting
To help us hungry people
The same people who are now
Who have been for years
The people Alex in suits
Are the villains
So f*** you Alex
Look in the mirror
It is amazing to me that
Billionaires don't have
Somebody like right now
Them going here's why
You want to give away all of you
Yeah
Income inequality is at an all-time high combined with a less access to food and water
And basic housing
Sooner or later this is going to happen
Your money is going to go away
And you can choose whether or not you want to be around after
Because this is not going
It's either that or they feel like they've done enough to build a
Perfect castle that they can watch the rest of us die and then pick up the pieces
Not much other things to say other than their stupid I guess
I don't know
That's all I'm going to say about his stupid starvation
Cuz I really find it
Level that like
Money was narratives I find offenses in the same way but it sort of like
There's the goofy dumbshit
Like Moonraker just kind of like
I've thought about that all day and then there's these things that are just like
Repulsive
Is that the thing the doctors are just having orgies as right on that same sort of
Just quit
Now
We get to
The best
The best thing
This is really where things broke apart okay
Alright like being to guests
Fiasco
Here is where like I'm already on the second episode
Alright
Come to the end of this thing I felt like it
This is
Just the wheels
Off the wagon
Myself a country the world
I'm moving in with my dad
Today's
Alive this is just really kind of a precursor right now
I died broadcast
Because I
Turn this around
Climate were in what's happening in the world
Lightning speed
Level
Now is the time to record the final broadcast
It would go out
Horse Island
Make the most important statements that need to be made
Mannequin size
Elgin Way
What a douche
If you have things you want to say just f****** say them cut up a bulshit the recording a special episode
Released after you die
Like some kind of a low-rent Deadman dropped
This dumb dumb as his own radio show with no boss no sponsors to please in a
I completely browbeaten staff
Really don't stop him from doing whatever the f*** you want
Do we really expect anyone with half a brain to believe there's some kind of real important information he's been holding back for the past 25
Years this is spectacular theater
It's either just now it's being a dramatic little baby
Tim Legend building
If you're someone like Alex
And you know you need a satisfying dainumo that leaves people puzzling over your career forever
And what better way to do that then claim you're going to record a final episode that lays everything out and then never do it
Rumors will fly but somebody with a copy of it
Will become a hot debate about what was said in this mythical tape
The only way to make this better is if he insists on doing it on VHS
Because his career started analog and it's going out analog the awesome
Got it but the reality of is if he did doing last episode it would be the biggest masturbatory ever
Episode in the history of BMG jerking off there wouldn't be any new information to be like
Hey remember how great I was that time
Yeah I was pretty great I remember how great I was at other time
Alberta gray most likely he'll record something
He's crying and yelling but the global is referencing Bill Joyce article and why
Basically just going down the list of all of his buzzwords
The catchphrase isn't aligned with something like that to me or something equally
What I'm getting at is I refuse to get all excited about this I've absolutely no faith this will happen and if it does I have no faith in
It won't be the biggest dog of his f****** career
I will put this conspiracy theory out there
I already
And
He pulls the computer chip out of the homeless man
If the Ledger
That's the way it is so Alex in the first
Opening Salvo gears record this and it's going to be something that will be released once
Puppies that are very specifically said that
Changes
Let me just
Precursor
My final broadcast
Wichita
Talking about gas but will be one that I want
Broadcast what's on record
In some form though they are good at removing things now
AI system another little beautiful human helpers
So now I'm confused
Is that what you're planning to do a show where he pretends to do his final show but it's not going to be his final show and it's not going to be something
Sounds like a guy was really trying to hint to his audience that this s*** is over but doesn't have a balls
Just come out with
I mean what is them for him to say on his fake last show
What
Hasn't he had the time to say in a quarter-century on-air that he thinks he's going to prove in a couple hours
Yeah there's that warlike had globalist means guys
Serious things that I can imagine you being like this is the end of the career real might as well might as well
Yeah
I don't know I am Felix
Like what what what is his
Big secret that he's been hiding
That
Tape of Reagan getting Pig was real
Look he's got a copy of it the only way it works satisfyingly is if he doesn't do it but makes it
The big deal about how he's going to do it exactly what I laid out is the only way this is awesome
That be the best Last Broadcast to if you
Do he should reveal that it is his last broadcast
After saying he's going to do this whole Last Broadcast
And then be like
Surprise
This was
Play a God damn
Fake Jordan
Kind of feels like that's what this show is kind of does
It starts to get like really
Retrospective
Alex's talking here
It seems like he's reflecting on his career in hindsight
As opposed to it being something that's ongoing
Shove
Sadness but also of
Attraction
That
I much rather than I ever thought I would and I didn't ever expect to
Everybody believing they were men better than I was
BoBoiBoy
People in the government systems in Ark
Well dug-in into well-entrenched
Go-Buster too strong
We failed now they're going to do what they're going to do
That really seems like a retrospec
The dunes like I'm done
Yeah career is over
Oh that's that's got a dishes your life kind of fit that's a man
That's a guy at like
58mm company for 33 years
And is in force retired
He's giving that speech of liked it also just want to say that I accomplished a lot here I didn't do everything I want to do cuz they forced me out
I had seven years
Anyways I thought I did really great guy at the end of this but it's a guy who fails
Whatever his big goal
But also needs to be like
Totally Kyle
It really feels very much
After all
Bubbles are too strong they're going to win in this round or whatever but Alex Asher is everyone
That oral tradition
Will save us
Sure
So bad
That even with AI censoring
Spoken word
Traditions
The truth is getting out and when they
Till almost everybody
Be a large human resistance come out
And that's really what matters now.
And the good thing is we weren't kit
Put it
Going to get the people
But I was sure you
Pay for what they done
Dumbing us down turning us against each other promoting racism in the name of fight
Damn Satanism in there
Feel like crap everywhere
Feel.
Pure rage
That way I won't let you sell my body distorted
Some evil.
Enlightenment
Pure
I can assure
The New World Order the Hillary Clinton's the Bill Gates's the world
Rothschild
You are
Destroyed
Show me the ladders is fairly standard stuff
But it's also it also feels like
Exactly what
I think he launched into like what his idea of My Last Broadcast will be
That's how it feels
The globalists are going to win
I won't be around it's not going to happen but oral tradition
Getting the word out there
Avenger
It just goes on and Alex is like thanking his audience
Lake
This feels
Wake through
So attempted closure
Promoting the truth being attacked
Pushing out our articles and videos even though they're imperfect and
Coordinated
Because it is coordinated
Cereal
Seneca and the enemy knows that
Know what to do about it
Ice-o-matic beautiful
Cold War
Together
The first time my life began to feel guilt having children yesterday
The universe
Oh boy
And to
Not be selfish and immature
Become your ancestors
Sure
Action of the future there will
Rochester Vibe and Cher
Our time together and share our Humanity in extent
Experience
On the tells you that you're not essential
I want to tell you you're ugly or you're bad
Because if where you're from or what color you are
Any of that
If you get the f*** out of
So I'm listening I'm listening to this and it really sounds to me like a guy was about to sign off and
Not come back
And I noticed this is the last segment of the hour like he's in the middle of the last segment yeah it starts to make sense
It's Friday this is how he's going to wrap things up and then go on a sad weekend
And then I realize that this is the second hour of the show
Game theory he still has another hour of show after this
How do you recover from
Academy Award lifetime achievement on how do you do that and then do another normal hour of the show
Why the fuk didn't you wait an hour to do the xenos along and show is crazy
Another movie that is the broadcaster in any disaster movie
This is look
The asteroid is coming we have
8 hours last time I was
Eternally privileged to share this time with you if your vanity is beautiful we will survive
Beautiful and f*** you Alex if anyone tries to make you feel bad or skin color or where you're from
Message for black people
No
Color something
Did Andreas run to enslave and kill you
Publican Bridget's establishment Blueblood dorks
And don't know what's going on
They don't want to just get rid of what they call
Third world populations I want to get rid of everybody because he's people hate themselves they have live
Selfishness in bread
Disgusting ways
What anybody can you get monsters folks you get selfish
Psychotics
Because you're not supposed to have sex with your brothers and sisters
Can I supposed to have kids with him
People are mentally ill
Okay
They're dangerous
We got to fight him
I can't remember Jordan is this family show
Alex's message
Two people of color
Is that the Democrats
Want to kill everybody but the Republicans just want to kill you altruistic.
Dude or something Republican Maybe
I also recognize that I said that this is a message to black people but he says people of color
Do you know why
I was wrong
I never would have imagined that I would say people of trouble
What the f*** is up with that
Music
I'm going to use the Vista
Also I do think that Alex a rambling about how you're not supposed to suck your siblings
This is a real
Really if you wanted to still everything down
Took it out
They do that because they see Infowars
Email
Standing up strong
And rallying fellow human Shannon
Women getting involved in waking other waiting others up there they're worried about humans coming together
You're a winner is
When they say they destroyed me
When they say they killed me or they put all these lies out
You have to understand that they did that because we were too strong
Loser
Winners clubs you have to know
Bad things about to happen
Don't know that stuff you're going to hear a lot of bad stuff about
Because they hate males
So Alex discusses hell like they're only destroying him cuz he's too strong or something I need to remember is that
Star wars exist
Loser
Winter clothes
Analogy was not the loser when Darth Vader
He's a winner because he chose
The Young Generation will get pissed off
I think Alex might have missed the point of Obi-Wan's line but how Vader strike him down and become more powerful than you can possibly imagine
Alex seems to think that Obi-Wan is saying that his death will be a rallying event for the next generation of Jedi but I don't think that's the point
Make it super clear that you talked about how he'll become more powerful because he'll become one with the force
Gain all sorts of powers after he dies
About Luke being inspired to learn to respond to Obi-Wan's death
I shall become more powerful
All sorts of other minutiae about Force ghosts that have no
It's been getting into her exploring
I would expect Alex have a good handle on this though cuz we've seen he's a pretty cool guy
Yoda
Can still shoot lightning a post
Horoscopes
We know it's cool
Probably
Pop-up and whatever Planet you want to Pedal kreyn like you can't
Buhurt there's life after death and you can still hang out with your butt
Totally great
Samuel Jackson
So of course because Alex is
Doing this weird thing that may or may not be his
I'm tempted Last Broadcast or something
He starts thinking about Colonel Travis almost starts crying talking about that drunk Yahoo
Knew he was going to die
He really believed in Texas
You wanted his own tyranny of the massacres
Just like
British
Eddie Trunk.
6110 21
And so he laid down his life
What are the people
The other people would see an example not a failure
Victory
Like yourself
In the blessing
Persecuted
Lloyd of the right thing
And knowing you're right
Knowing god and knowing God's real
Doubts knows nothing about Colonel Travis
Description is my commanding officer the guy is like I've always
Showing up 1 to 10
We should probably get a better tactical position yeah maybe
Colonel Travis
I'm just saying
Maybe we're the ones doing it wrong
Travis end up at the Alamo because of some pursuit of a noble death he was running away from debts
The segment ends like I said
Like this should be it he should go
Go home
You got nowhere else to go screaming Remember the Alamo
Stop it.
Billiards
Not
To stand up for what's right
You have to turn loose
Any fear
Or even any guilt
The number for my children
Raw
A 2017
Promise
Providence
Sherbet on a 4:30 work
Blood
You will as well for the right back
That's it
Infowars
Go home if you are there and you are like one of Alex's employees it is your response
Ability to be like
David Knight will take over whatever you are you got to get off at
If you want to gather your thoughts and record some sort of a
Message by all means do that
Wheel of whatever shape you're in right now
Your lies
I don't know what the fuc
So he he he doesn't
Alex back to business house comes back
Forgot a sandwich during the break then he got blood sugar
So you didn't go
Restart
A bunch of clubs into the cover
Just gets to the point where
Disgusting
The good news is
Everyone I know is totally rejected stuff like together at home
World government
Propaganda with Lady Gaga
Lady Gaga on record
Got to have someone sleep with her in her room because demons
My mind and just see for Infiniti
Couldn't imagine serving a god
Rabideaux's your brain when you live in
Crystal Cave
Damn virus
Alex seems to be in constant torment you literally talk about all the time
Like
He's constantly tormented I don't I don't know any other way to explain it
How do I Alex's talk about a 2013 lawsuit filed by former personal assistant
It was made
Was that you was made to sleep in the same bed as Gaga because she didn't get her own hotel room and Lady Gaga at tasks for her
Even at night
O'Neal testified in a deposition is Lady Gaga was watching a DVD in the middle of the night I'm tired of it
She woke her up to take out and replace the DVD
Worst you can save this an instance of a popstar have an unreasonable demands for a personal assistant
But a little bit far
What he's doing is combining that story with a 2012 interview Gaga did where she discussed a recurring nightmare she had involved
Having a demonic Phantom
And how she discussed agree with Deepak Chopra
How to combine these two things into one story the kind of works better for his purposes but isn't
So that's what's going on
Yeah that sounds
It's all bulshit
Anyway good
Good thing you didn't go home
What is the way he describes
God is in his mind that's a total Gotham
That's one of his gods
Favorite things
He's got demons on all of us all the time
Yeah that is true it is it's strange
I would explore this longer but I have to go to this
This is
I was just talking about everything else we've talked
Today which is
Absolutely
Just mainstream boring normal nonsense
Doctors fighting
So Alex is talking about here this next clip about how the people go along with a new world order right because
Went along with the New Orleans
Yeah man
Trained to go along with things
Write something like that it gets into a metaphor about Village
And I find this really interesting this is one of the more fascinating
Weird things of his brain
Don't you see it now why are you
Why are you going along with this because humans are designed to go along with each other
Design a little village in dad and Grandpa and Grandma take it out and catch fish
Crocodile
Why don't you see that crocodile you know either beer or something you know they told you the truth in your whole life
People around the village were good
Crazy in Badin
Somebody so you know some of the men Brad demon
You know
Villages good
What
That sounds sick
Your village become successful
Because you're planted crops you're hunting
All the sudden you're not
You talk about you buddy
Shut up
You've been bad and you don't believe in this God never give an offering so
Sun
Okay that sounds like Rodger Stone
The bad witch doctor comes in
Alright Seuss weird
It goes on a little bit
This is very strange
Supposed to
You been bad and you don't believe in this God never give in offering so
The Sun
What
Dates the fees
Why what
Everybody laughs at the guy and whatever you guys are throwing out of the village
Michonne
It's eaten by the monster
Fireworks
You got out of a mind scratch them
God
Will make the Sun come back and you know cures illnesses and
You know keeps you warm and you really like it
And you get on your knees to him that goes okay
Wake me up in the back
So it just goes on exactly how you'd expect you start so I cruel in over the village
Stop this is really the same kind of is Ancient Aliens stuff
People have a complete inability to imagine that non-european cultures of the past
We're capable
Anything without some kind of outside help
Ancient Aliens people it's using aliens to explain things like a pyramid
Baloch satsang a bad witch doctor has had some secret knowledge of eclipses that they used to bamboozle ignorant people
As far back as 2136 BC the Chinese knew perfectly well about eclipses and history.com
Emperor Chung
Kong executed is Royal astronomers hi and ho
For failing to predict
Eclipse
They have folklore based explanations for what was happening all terrified of an eclipse
Way that Alex's
Describing
The Inuit people have legends about their Moon God and his sister's son God fighting which explain the lunar cycle and eclipses
Who's to quarrelsome siblings
Chasing each other
The story Alex is telling is fairly close to the tradition of the Guatemala people from Benin and Togo
And their tradition 22 matriarchs of the world
And pukapuka presided over the
First Villa
As it grew people started fighting with each other in order to get them to stop
The two made the Sun
That got people's attention so everyone made peace with each other and gave Gifts of reconciliation and women turn the sun back on
This tradition continues in the bottom Alibaba Bayview eclipses is a time to make peace with each other
Kind of is like Alex's story but it's also the opposite
I have no idea what Alex is talking about but it legit sounds like something from a children's movie
If you had some kind of a citation for the art of the originating in bed which doctor is showing up the villages around the world
Chronology of eclipses
Which they then use to become rulers I'd love to see it but I don't know if it's based on anything real
Interesting Lee though this exact story that I was telling is a Trope of early English literature from the late 1800
However it's white people using eclipses to f***
With Native people
From The Savage and literature representations of society in English fiction
58 through 1920 by Bryan Street
Quote
Gullibility is a future which enables British sovereignty to be maintained by the use of Western knowledge
And Technology to frighten the simple native into submission
Perhaps the most famous and memorable example is the use of an eclipse to overall the native
In King Solomon's Mine The Travelers
Take advantage of an eclipse to reinforce the natives believe that they are God
Also side point it's very likely that this is where Alex is taking his story
Because he keeps referring to the person
In his telling as a witch doctor which is precisely who the villain of that story is
If he and his fellow Travelers can make the natives believe it is through their power that the phase of the moon is dark in
Abandon their evil witch doctor Google and follow the white man
This is a very popular theme in literature around the time it's not to emphasize white Europeans
Supremacy
From Streets book
The series of anthropologists are used in popular fiction to provide various explanations for primitive attitudes
Which become traditional themes and fix
The ease with which of the Native can be deceived is brought home to the reader by the Vivid use of eclipses and academics
Siri is used to explain the natives reaction
I'm not positive that this is where Alex is getting this wrong but it is like a Trope of this
This European fiction from around the time of colonial
I've read books
Not realize
Looking back it does seem obvious
That eclipses are the white man
Man's Burden
Red-eared moussaka
That's what makes the most sense
It's just what we do we know
We just have to carry that knowledge of an eclipse on our backs
Yeah so I'm not positive and Alex never sites anything when he's talking about these witch doctors that would come
Because they have the secret knowledge of the
Brotherhood or whatever
I'm willing to explore whatever he's bringing to the table but from everything I can tell it seems like these
Are these
These eurocentric
Versions of stories about
The quote-unquote Savages
I think that I was just believes all of that is
Yeah basically
So Alex in the next with dr. Howard Huey
He got up really early that morning
Any watch Trump
Press conference
And
He has an interesting thought about it okay
Black forest
I watch the whole thing
Ultraman
Years off my life man
It will
Do you know
Dobby talks.
But he knows they put people in chili
So he does
Unlike might have been good
We have a big super Laboratory
For the first time that sunlight kills the virus
Amigos
That's good with your skin
Sun hitting your skin
Help
This is super interesting to me man in the past hour to just flatly ignored all the many many times Trump has said completely f***** up and
Stupid things any press conferences
You just act like those things didn't happen
I guess like you must have felt like this one was too big and stupid to ignore so he's just come up with this narrative
The Trump was acting stupid cuz we are also stupid
This amazing stuff and it definitely doesn't sound like someone trying to rationalize another person's abusive Behavior
As for the stuff that Trump is saying but like UV lights we've gone over that already
The type of UV light that's used to disinfect things would f******
Fry's Yuma
This is not Trump saying it's the sun wonderful 18 talk without his ass about technology does not
I have
No I have no sense
Like if you're if you still support Trump you get what you get
You just you just listen to the president the guy you wanted
To run
The country tell you to inject yourself
Well go fuc not according to Alex
Can rationalize a guy saying inject yourself with bleach away
You win the cognitive dissonance price
The sun is good for your skin
You want
Everyone should just be
Donald Trump is not a doctor
So he can't tell you
Sonny's
Honestly he can't
The sun is good for your skin
So you're the Trump side in that in the press conference that everyone is up in arms about
Supposing we hit the body with a tremendous weather is ultraviolet or just a very powerful light and I think you said
Has been checked
But you're going to test
And then I said supposing you brought the light inside the body would you can do either through the skin or in some other way
I don't think you said you're going to test that to sounds interesting right
And then I see the disinfectant where knocks it out in a minute one minute
Santa is there a way we could do something like that by injection inside or almost a cleaning
Because you see it gets in the lungs and it doesn't tremendous number of on the lungs
Should be interesting to check that
So you're going to have some
You're going to have to use medical doctors with but it sounds interesting to me
He wasn't saying with his son was good he was calling weird ideas about you he technology that he doesn't understand
Implying that because disinfectants worked
Kill the virus on surfaces
Baby
The next day when asked about it Trump tried to pretend that he brought up these things sarcastically in order to f*** with reporters
Just to see what would happen
And that Jordan is a release
That the president of the United States was using his press conference of the middle of the pandemic to suggest potentially lethal
Virus just a troll reporters
Yeah it's it's
Worse
If he knows what he's doing
Yeah he doesn't
He doesn't understand that he thinks that when he's
He saying I was being sarcastic
Then he's like see
I wasn't stupid
I was just really really evil trying on purpose
To get people
Killed his explanation of like I was just talking with reporters like Eva
Think ATAC in his mind is like you've done it yet.
Had no idea I was lying to you I'm a genius
Trump said he was just drawing and then of course it came out to one of the leaders of the genesis2church who promote the use of
Bleach is a miracle cure for all sorts of ailments
Pics of trump a letter earlier that week
Article in the guardian
In his letter Mark grenon told Trump the chlorine dioxide powerful bleach used in industrial processes that is
Textile manufacturing
They can have a fatal side effect when drunk
Is Coke a wonderful detox that can kill 99% of the pathogen to the body
Yeah.
Rid the body of covid-19
A few days after Grennan dispatched his letter Trump went on National Television that is daily coronavirus briefing in the White House
On Thursday and promoted the idea that disinfectant could be used as a treatment for the virus
The group is also the subject of an investigation
Because of their medical claims about bleach
And the article goes on to say that quote
Brandon said that
In the past few days to Trump at the White House urging him to take action
To protect Genesis 2 and its bleach paddling activities
Which they claim can cure Coronavirus
I have no ideas these two seem like connected
Things are related is Mark grenon
He was pretty pumped about Trump's press conference
How to find out what a bring up this part of Trump's comments and just wants to pretend that all is good
It does seem like the New York's attorney general should send trempealeau cease-and-desist letter for baking
False
Maybe
So Alex is mad like sunlight is good cuz the doctors
These doctors
Interactions
Psychological
Sitting there and
Tiago's
How much money does your company bring in a year
You know I was like 6 years ago
Talk about you in restaurants
Well Jones
25 million dollars we know that's not true
Put because he didn't know who I was
I made up 25 million dollars
People talk about me
Come on man
Island grocery store
Don't tell this to me
Is dr. Drew
It says
That I made it up
I did
Yep Alex is really pretty defensive about this idea that he was diagnosed as I have a narcissistic person
Disorder really going at this doctor from his divorce proceedings
Statistically
Amigos Peabody
Dollars
Also
Big Lots
I got completely mentally ill Fox
To go sit there
Wow
Wow PVP plan
Nobody
God
Eviction
Because I'm pro-human
Mental illness a competent man
So I can sell to the dsm-4 to see what kind of like what's the actual diagnostic criteria for
Narcissistic personality disorder
Picture of Alex there
Gillette Clippers either get rid of the Goldwater rule that clipped
Oh yeah that dude
The doctor music conspiracy
Criteria
Has a grandiose sense of self-importance
Jack
Is preoccupied with fantasies of unlimited success power brilliant beauty or ideal love
No idea
Believe that he is he or she is special or unique and could only be understood by or associate with others
Special
Check
Requires excessive admiration
Check is interpersonally exploitative
Lacks empathy
Is often envious of others or believes that others are envious of him or her
Shows arrogant haughty behaviors or attitude
That's all of that solid you are there any secret ones. On there in the 2011 the DSM
Or find some of the criteria for MPD
What are the defining features of impairments in cell function
Emotional regulation mirroring self-esteem
That sounds a lot like his broadcast sounds like that another Hallmark is a grandiosity mixed with excessive
Attempts to attract or be the focus of the attention of others
I know.
So I can't
Pretty easy to see why someone might think
That pretty well describes out
Kyrie just
Just the
I imagine that he had that diagnosis after the first question is just like
Hey how are you doing today I'm doing great how are you doing today you're the one who should be in here we should switch seats
I've always been
Family
The Alex descends pretty hard into this defensive
Don't care about people they don't give tips
Little pulp
Their little thing
Guild lawyers
All they are is grasping people on average
Wanting power
Real power is
Growing crops
Carrier children standing up for yourself
Go home
But if somebody wants one you want to get your head knocked and you will I'm out looking for
Okay
That's cool
I mean there's nothing like
We just got a diagnosis behaviors that
Indicative
Easiest way to find out if somebody is a narcissist has to just be like hey you're an RC
And then there was like if you told me I was a narcissist be like
I should have been acting like an a****** have a knife
I don't like that to Alex you be like your narcissist happened I will kill everybody I don't like
Because like that because I'm a Taurus
Remember times in my life I've had people that I caught Tauruses are stubborn and that puts you in a box
Because you can either say yes I say no and it proves that you are
Doesn't work universally
It is it is not a blanket
But now it is Alex Center
Alex is not plugging
Is water peltors
Although yet
Well you made the best gravity-fed filter
The competitors are 500
They're as good and sometimes not and others that it's a gorgeous
The most expensive
What you find about like crazy
Come out stuff like these
Percent off
So we got to sell a lot of these are fun.
That's going on
About a million apparently you have 25 million coming in here at you got to say you only making 30 on each wall
Water filter
It's amazing how the best
Gravity filters are also the ones that give me the best profit margin
But also 30%
So Alex comes back from his break commercial break
At this
Made me laugh
So hard
Your phone calls right now and I've got a piece of news
Let it show Gigantor
Yes well that is anime
I got a big old story
Shelter
Coverdog
Big news out of the Senate
Senator Strom Thurmond goddamnit he's dead
Stelter reliable sources I can only be trusted with small stories
Big story I will
Subway
Cuz you got to talk about how long it took him to get into work
Sometime
Because they're all looking for leadership when I drive down the road my neighborhood
Hood
I'm glad you're outside the virus overalls a hugs and is less than 1% death rate
Oops
Misty a break there
I don't believe you did that
Admiral Whispering about him at the same time
Videos of big news
Sort of like
Fox breaking news
He had said that he was going to get to this big news in the next second
So when he comes back he can't do it because they didn't pay them has any
Look at it
Okay so this isn't the big
News
Why earlier when I told you that Alex had said that his people are sending in
Until about Bill Gaither
This is the only example of something they could have been what he was talking about
And stupid
From 2008
Where their foundations real name
Depopulation
Agreed
19890 East
Beaumont engaged to run worldwide depopulation and they
Admit it
She's giving an intro to another speaker
Explanation here is that she misspoke
Gates group is it's not called The Institute for population
Control it's the institute for population and reproductive health
This has become a bit of a stupid conspiracy online all based on that little clip apparently initially publicized by Adam Curry
Socks
The most obvious explanation is that these speaker bespoke but apparently
That's just what
She would say
The internet sleuths have been trying to find evidence
Is that the name of the gates group is
Originally called population
Control Institute for population control
But literally all evidence
Except that Clips Institute for population and reproductive health
In order to make sense of his lack of evidence
The new claim
Is it a Gates people completely scrub the internet of any proof that their group was originally called the in
Population control completely
Evidence that the claim they're making is true is only evidence of a complete cover-up of the evidence that would prove their claim to be true
That's very convenient
This is why there's really no hope about against this current type of conspiracy thinking
There's a conclusion that they want to arrive at
Any suggestion of supporting evidence or even the mysterious absence of supporting evidence
It's good enough to be considered proof
I'm just not sure there's any way to work with that level of disconnection from reality outside of one-on-one therapy
I'm not convinced that their education
Woodpecker
Now there's nothing that
It seems to added that is what it is
That video is a Smoking Gun
And even if they were called The Institute for population control
Vindicate
Depopulation
Melinda Gates Foundation
So Alex comes back from break
Again
And this time they got the moves but it's also not what you'd expect but I thought they were going to play some like
Breaking news Fox musician
It did it the Law & Order dun dun I wish
Well this news really deserve some Fanfare it's very sad news but
Alright
Quintessential
Drop bombs on his number without her that's a mismatch
That is somebody
The clip and also I don't think we have the copyright rights I don't think we can do that at
Sirens again
Put something else in there
Call boy
Oh it's an accident China has
They just so happen to have the testing kits right the same
Rome
When the virus
So happen to accidentally
Hornet
On
The needles that went in your arms
And give it to you
Nailtoepia shoes for the massive ship them over in the
California
What
New York motor vehicle where they use masks
Run down Chinese cities where
Arizona
But the government doesn't care about the people in the people given up
Cdc's
Coronavirus
So I will say that it's true there is a story in arstechnica with the headline Coronavirus
Confirm
There's some important caveats to me
Make here
Is that this article is four days old by the time Alex is on are doing is air raid siren
Stop the presses Level news big news
The second and much more important point is it Alex absolutely is not read this article because you saying has literally no
To do the content.
Like this is
This is basically Moonraker book vs. movie territory
Do you think of the Chinese that these tainted test and there was an intentional attack
However this article has no relation to anything China did is entirely about protocols not being followed within the seed
ABC and their development of a coronavirus test
This was our government being sloppy not the Chinese attacking us
From the article
Quote
Now according to the investigation results reported by the New York Times
Federal officials confirm that sloppy laboratory practices at 23 CDC lab
Involved in the test creation lead to contamination of the test
And their uninterpretable results
There's no indication in this article that the contamination led to anyone being infected
Guess what the results that were gathered from the tests were inconclusive in on music
If you want to use this story and shine some light on the need for better practices and controls within the CDC by all means
Go ahead
However what Alex is doing this completely fabricating a story about China putting coronavirus on test needles
And sending them here to infect people which is essentially accusing a sovereign state of a crime that requires a declaration
In a war
He's playing with fire and he's all just making it up because he's either unwilling or unable to read anything past the headline
It's very disgraceful
You should you should
Would have to at least have the word China in the art
To make that ball.
Lie about it
Even if in the article is just like
We it's not from China
Play even then at least China would be involved in the article instead of it being purely
The CDC made some tests and they were contaminated
But brutal that's really bad
What 2 oz of lying about it
So this is our last clip
And what ends up happening here is Alex is saying that Bill Gates
Is running a satanic conspiracy
I meant h a little flight of fancy that I think might be blessed
Okay
We're in bad shape
PowerForce on Earth stuff
You and your family going to do
Because you want to kill you
Populator
What then
Because he wants to save it
They have
The metaphysical
The notice similar to Legal
Is it illegal
The notice Fair
The martial law
Then you can do whatever you want
The city council has two weeks
To hold hearings about the
What
Okay I'll bring them to hate themselves renovate America
Behavior children
I think that this is
Maybe maybe Alex just watch
Lost
There's some sort of connection with Jacob and the man in Black's relationship that he's describing here with God in the Dead
I don't know man
That seems like a shity god to worship
The guy who's hanging out with the devil in the devil's like a
Can I kill him in the Godlike
Can I trick him into killing each other
Call Jobe
Devil or was
I'm not smoking while
Who cares
But yeah I mean
Look I mean if God knows
Just how tricky the definitely
And he's like by all means you can't
Reckless
Criticizing Lady Gaga's not God that he created it for being a sitter God to then give us
I understand
Free will and you have to choose
Like if some other person
Is trying to
To trick you
Sure but if it's a supernatural being
It's not on you I don't get why people get blamed for s*** that Loki trick them into do
I don't know
Got you lose the point here is that Alex's batch
I think
Ike
I don't know
Obviously there is there is a piece of this they could be overly dramatic
But I don't know if I've ever heard him talking about like
I'm recording my last episode
I meant breaking down in this this way or he's he's discussing his career in hindsight
I don't know man
I feel like
Like really
Coming up to it
Yeah but that I could look stupid in hindsight but the way this feels it does
It does not feel like
Someone who's
Just trying to f*** around
It feels like someone who's
Trying to m
Well what it feels like to me is somebody whose emotional regulation is tied directly to their sense of self esteem
That's what it feels like to me
I don't think he's feeling good right now about his self-esteem
True and I think that's bleeding into other things that's my that's my personal opinion I'm not a doctor
I don't even pretend to be an
No I wish I could I think
Know the occupants to require education
Not like us movies other
Ding dong
I don't know I think
My feeling is we have a really interesting next week ahead of
I will say I
I'm not looking for you know what I f******
Yeah it does do his last show
I can't
Wait to tear that apart
God when he goes over his record that's going to be your f****** Superbowl
You're going to have how many
Like
I think
The opportunity to Legend kill is really excited
If he wants to lay bare what is vinyl messages
I can't imagine something more exciting than deconstructing that
So hopefully he does do that but I have a sense it'll be under welding
I'll be we'll see back next week but until then Jordan we have website
Is Monday today is Monday
Its.com
And if you want to learn more about Seltzer's it's knowledge outside shelter
I wrote on Twitter
Go to bed Jordan in that knowledge
Ross on Facebook
Or donate to a local charity of your choice
I will be back until then I'm only alone dzx Clark I am a robot trash truck
Holding
Alex
I love your work