I have great respect for its knowledge by I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Need
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Everybody looks around
Jordan
Come to mine
I'm not one of these guys who likes to eat when I get to work in an office
Their birthday week
Set bring up my birthday and I have so many times on this podcast
Over the course of from Friday to Monday that weekend the 24th through whatever
Monday would have been
Andy Daly put out his new album sweaters and then on Monday
Beginning of his new podcast bananas for Bonanza started
One of the funniest people on the planet call being dropped on my plate over the weekend at the end of the weekend it was
Just fantastic. Really really really nice
I've been taking a lot of pleasure
That I got to catch up on
That I have you still haven't listened to another alert
I know I know it's going to be
I think Andy Daly is one of the absolute funniest people in
A f****** plan
You're a little bit by it being Tuesday as a recording that said you haven't listened to either of those things so
Hyatt priority and I had to get my birthday yet
I definitely have forgot what the other thing was and it'll come to me later hopefully but
If not it'll be on Friday
Tomorrow's going to be a god
Days have no meaning my bright spot
Is a personal growth
Hey I had to go back and take a look at some of the stuff and we have done and
I was agreeing or show nothing Adventures
Oh okay
Turn the hall lights lot of time for reflection
And I am proud to say I used to be a giant shitbag and now I am slightly less of a giant ship a
What is a bright spot in a little bit of time to recognize you know that
Talk about like you know you don't really see gradual things are happening
Booty look back it's like oh my God this is
There's a lot of difference between a couple years ago and now day-to-day am I feel like and nothing's really changed
You got to take a take a step back every now and again that's great but I would say in the past two years I've grown in
Changed more than I had you know from 3232
But from like 23 to 30
You're welcome
It's probably Fair probably fare very nice people
Brilliant
I'm so Jordan today we're going over April 27th and 28th 2020
Yeah that's monday-tuesday this weekend
There we go
April 28th episode of Alex's show
This we're not going to get to it until you know towards the end of this episode
I promise you
Unheard-of levels of nonsense
I can't over-hype this stupid
And we will but before we get down to business on that we could take moment to say thank you somebody's wonderful people have signed up as part of the show and also
Also check in
The year of the Seltzer thank you so much
Kraig with a K thank you so much
Thanks Greg next
If he was a villain in Donkey Kong Country
Who is nothing like her namesake
Never thought I'd say that in my life
Yeg
Mixtrax thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk contract expect dreams
Somebody who donated on an elevated level and I got to say
Generosity above even what I am
We would classify in the technocratic are category
We got to go Raptor princess on this one
Baby got to this on the last episode of every episode before that
But I can't find the Raptor princess sound effects all over the place and I can't find it
So thank you to this this individual this person
I've created a new Raptor princess soundrop
So thank you so much the armor of contempt
You are now or after princess
Four Star
Don't get mad and tell your brother
It's over for Humanity
You're Beautiful song
They're coming for your balls
Black piss all over your God
Very few people
The practice of
When they are
Thank you so much the armor of God we preciate it I wanted to try and mix it up
So a lot of lot of non Alex voices there
Got a little scatological for awhile I did notice that trash yes but when I'm digging from like
More recent clip seems like Alex dark by pissing to a lot more lately
So thank you very much
Dot-com click the button says for sure we would appreciate it
Can go and find a local charity in your area
And help people in need that would also be wonderful
We would appreciate either
Yep so Jordan at 7 check in with the year the Seltzer up to 19 Seltzer's at the timer record
We are
Ahead of schedule on the 500
Black Market expensive
This might end up getting make people feel a little bit more comfortable.
Family members gave me Amazon gift cards for my birthday so a number of variety packs or available online
Do not use them on May 1st
Do not cross the picket
Amazon don't cross the picket line on May 1st
I will not do that for me the heads-up the other thing is that there's a bunch of grocery stores here in Chicago
And corner stores and a lot of them have
Lucy's
They have individual cans of Seltzer children often like between $0.60 or a dollar
Find
Carnivals that I've been drinking and are still in the fridge
12 pack up yellow am I buy another 12 pack
This is not going to end up probably being
Devastating
Right I've been you know going
To like to go get some groceries
I go through every aisle
You be surprised
There are beverages in more Isles than you think I realized
All over the place
So
Today Jordan
What are highlights
Well
Can all be good
Sometimes you got to give a little
I got to say this is this
This week
So far has been a marked disappointment about 3 to bring
By Vai
They have a line of not all of them
Have their watermelon lime and I gave it to 68
Okay I mean it's not like the line of them is trash
However
I did try the coconut lime
New Lowe's
4 rating system
16 out of 100
Damn if it's under 20 that means I didn't finish
If it's under 10 that means I find it repulsive and I wish it burn
I'm starting to realize that anything in like the 60s
Is going to be just like
Good but who gives a s*** right right he's going to be in a 70-80 that range to be like anything
Over 80
XXL
I am anxiously awaiting the day we get over eight
Our overnight I don't know if it'll happen but I'm ready for it to happen
Well due respect by I know you can do some good stuff but that coconut lime with a
The disaster
And
We'll see
The bad flavor I'm going to take anything that has coconut is going to
I love the mountains
Sometimes I feel like I'm not one of these anti coconut guys looking man in a drink
Terrible haha terrible
So do I
To be a list on this episode
Restarting here on the 27th April 27th Monday and starts out with Alex having a recorded message that he
He wants to send to the New World Order
Sirius my message to the New World Order
Darth Vader
Nope
Hopping around
You can destroy Alex Jones
Almost forgot his hair
You need to take
Do you love Alexa
I have a feeling that might be his recorded last
Episode
That's just
Like something to be played like in perpetuity the troops
What is on the tree of Liberty I'm afraid I'm going to forget how that quote goes in
Just say that tyrants
Lap up the blood
There's a harvest
Okay I kind of feel like that's his
His Salvo whatever I don't know otherwise it's just like a weird
Shoot promo about nothing
Eagan do to text
That is you to take no no you can't
Excuse me
He's getting any you getting out
Actual content and Alex has a little bit of a narrative here this throughout both of the days
This show and it's just stupid
Just a desperate attempt to try and make it look like Trump is an idiot
Cedar Sinai
Respected hospitals in the world's top five
Is doing light therapy and knocking out covid-19
Sneaking tube down into the lungs
Fiber optics
Their Twitter has been banned
Cedar-Sinai Twitter pages still up
I just checked this morning
Formation that is true
It's probably being misrepresented by right-wing outlets and those tweets maybe you're getting blocked
That's possible ones where they take
Sinai did Django like see you can use you right right inside and injected with you
That's where there is a little bit of Truth
It's also being super overblown by Alex
Other than the babblings of an idiot
According to nurse.org there's some research going on at Cedar-Sinai that involves a technology called healight
Which delivers intermittent ultraviolet a light through an endotracheal catheter
It's being studied as a potential treatment for viruses and bacteria and it's showing some promise but it's not at the point where it could be used on P
People like Alex's suggest
He liked is not yet approved by the FDA for use or approved as a covid-19 treatment
And more studies on its using humans will be needed before it could be verified as effective
Researchers are working on this technology and they're following appropriate guidelines for that kind of thing
It's worth noting that they were working on this project
Since at least 2016 so it's not something that's being developed in response to the Coronavirus
Hit some research that somewhere in the middle of the process and we'll see where it goes from there
Alex wants you to think that they're getting banned from social media because that makes it appear that the globalists are totally losing control
Bactroban is totally legitimate incredible Hospital
From social media because they're saying something good box the narrative
But none of that's real
So I imagine their statement
Would have been had they had they like been allowed to drop all the
God we wish we didn't have to deal with this to the president just said some b******* we're researching we're not it would
Why are you guys screaming at us don't use as we're anything we're just putting shipping B I don't know
Talia
Leave that leave without us
So Alex is going to lay it all out man
He's going to get down to just the bare bottom
Is that
I don't know what to do
Play this out right now what is that it needs to be done
Explain to the viewers and listeners
1 attacks so much
And the fact that he's for real upon this right strings
Let me try to explain
For my own
Hundred percent
Documented Spectrum
Right now
You know
You son of a b****
Chris
Incredibly obvious and what they want and what they've done
This is pretty early in the show man
I knew I knew he wasn't going to but the
The timing still got
At the right time
It's
It's like a master what's the opposite of opposite of
Goddamn
Broadcast
He does drop one little pieces eyes before he goes off
Fair
USA Today having to admit okay a true
Until they get to the park
Those
Can you read 4 pages
Hospitals get paid more patients listing
Covid-19 on ventilator
Snopes says it's not true Snopes and Media Matters our God
Explain how it's reasonable for three more pages
That yes they get way more money
If somebody has covid-19
Really funny when Alex says they make you read 4 Pages like I'm some kind of undue burden being put on his plate
Supposed to be this deeply competent researcher
Four pages is nothing
Particularly when there's Nuance to the issue that takes couple paragraphs to explain
I can say pretty comfortably that Alex did not read those four page
The article on USA Today doesn't save its nope said that with this
Point isn't
True
The only two points snopes is even mentioned using Snopes as a citation because they reported that a meme
About this issue was shared on social media in mid-april
And then later in the article Snopes comes up again in this line
Snopes investigated the claim finding it's plausible Medicare pays in the Range Jensen the guy was on Fox News talking about
Mentioned
But doesn't have a one-size-fits-all payment to hospitals for covid-19 patient
So nowhere in the article doesn't say that's nope said this wasn't true
Alex is making that up because he wants to make it look like Snopes
Who's lying in their fact check
This fact check is actually less detailed than others that I've read but it does cover the
Point which is explaining the part of this conspiracy theory is real
Hospital do get paid more by Medicare for patients who were treated by covid-19 covid-19
There's a 20% increase in payments that are dispensed by Medicare
Which was established by the cares Act
Act which Trump signed into law
The reason for the 20% bump is that hospitals are seeing a massive drop in revenues right now is people that other issues that might
I've sent them
To go get checked out they're delaying being seen or they're just toughing it out due to the virus
The increase of 20% is meant to offset the
The decrease is there seeing in normal operating funds
Not aligned anyone's pocket
There's a
It's pretty clear in the USA Today
Hospitals and doctors do get paid more for Medicare patients to cover the cost of care and loss of business
Resulting from a shift of focus
To treating covid-19
10 cases
At the end of that that that's so Alex would make it through very difficult
Can't expect that sort of effort
Back-breaking
Absolutely
Silence then goes to
Rebroadcast
It's funny to me because what he's saying there is
They make you read 4 pages
To get to this part
Is just basically saying like
They make me ignore all the context that proves the part wrong that I want to lie about God
Dammit yeah it doesn't matter anyway
Has noted that there's linked to this
Let's just admitting that all that context is to explain why he's wrong and so he can't get out
Broadcast Honey comes back
Andy said a rambling about how Trump listen
And everybody and you know
You good
You good you give him the right until when he's going to act
Trump didn't know that a Nobel Prize winner
Oh God
Virologist in the world
Had the virus scan
Know that the top-end in University scanned it and said the same thing
3 months ago
F11
Smart people are all scared
Because if you bring from prelim tell on who runs things
General Flynn
The former have
Defense intelligence
Ethika
The military
Know what's going on and I'll put Trump in
Is this
Are we okay what's up
We're going to
Put something up there about the Nobel laureates just put in
Nobel Prize winner
Virology
Covid-19 100% man-made that's the article I want to put up with you then
Broadcast.
Today
Stop
Okay
I may not come back
Seriously
Everything okay
Put the shot half-ass
Okay really
Better so many incredible reports we've been putting out I'm not going to half-ass it in Trainwreck
First hour of the
That's crazy
He blindsided me again never expect
Multiple times
Shop
So yes
Broadcast broadcast Special Report
Screw can't find it
Of course
When you got the
Let me know I'm in I'll be back today it's not a big deal.
It just will do this we'll just do this
Powerful it says it all
Really
Are John Brown's report
Report about the New World Order Plan to destroy America
Oh boy
CNL Athol
Second time saying I might not be back
That's a guy who's committed
So he leaves and comes back
Let's talk to you about the steaks
What's going on
Advise the president
Effacing
Prison
General Flynn
Advisor present getting good advice he's facing prison
Play the present good advice I'm facing
Right now okay
It'll be outside
Childish work at least people Target you and they let you know and they operate with impunity folks
Because the government is so full of
And social climbers
So I was wondering about this and I don't know of any crimes that Alex has committed outside of him
Bragging about murdering people
I don't think that's
True
There's no statute of limitation
No that's true but I don't think that's true
Monster
To think about this you know he has this lingering case with the bankruptcy issue because that his ex-wife is bringing
And who knows what's going to happen with that but I started to think about it
And I realized that one of the things that she's doing is she's asking for a lot of documents
In terms of Discovery for the kids but I'm thinking
Be what Alex is worried about is not necessarily
Losing that case I haven't
To pay her off right but the idea that a lot of his internal financial documents will become public
What is he's like hiding money somewhere what he is doing something criminal financially that's just you never know and
I don't know I don't know if that's true but I'm just trying to think of
What could he be worried about
Business-related right I mean
I think I think
You should do is
In the in the Discover
Instead of sending any documents he just gives them Rob do
And just like
You ask him all the questions
That you want to know the answer this guy knows everything
How do I be a good
Stalling tactic
So I don't know
Prison soon
I don't believe I'm going to God's true but if it is it's got to be something else
I don't believe he's murdered people
I don't I don't know of any other charges that are pending I mean you got the DUIs I go to prison for that
Maybe there's something related to that no
I don't think so
Natural but he's just making up the whole prison thing because it could be
He wants to try and compare themselves to Rodger Stone and in Flint
Really
So Alex gets against
Stalking some more and he's just not having a good day man
Let me do this
The same report
Oh no but I might do it right now
Does John
You know what they called it back when I was in high school to cause it to senioritis I was thinking that Eleanor last
He's dealing with right now he's like I know I'm
Yeah and I just don't know why I'm running hard to the finish line
I just saw some lightning thunderstorm on right now and I would like to be able to enjoy it a little bit of gas
A nice nice mood is a little bit of a dark and stormy
Thunderstorm when we have
When you have one Brewing
Sure
So Alex is going to go to this downtown report
Getting off are for the third time in an hour not handle this business
But just because he can't handle doing his job but that doesn't mean he can't self of course
I am grieving ever
Ms right now
Because I trust in God
And I do trust in God but
Look at how many truly evil people there are and it just
Blows my mind that our species until turned over to
You got a DUI bro
Because I've got to worry about the future and keeping us here on air Plus
Products you really need
You're completely insane
Goodnites
Pretty severe talking then then these ads episode are just
F****** severe
The Fightin side of me wants to stay and play Stay on Aaron fight this and I don't think it's a lost cause yet but
Personally making a lot of defensive measures
Really
Understand the long dark
So damn sad that we had a chance furnace around we made it just be so weak
Going to break lotion
Then at the very criminals that launched it will be our saviour's and then
I'm headed down injectors with bioweapons and laugh at us while we slowly die
But again infowarsstore.com horrible food now while you still can
Freezer Veer DanTDM
Mr. clean had that one adware chopped up babies and
This is the only way to clean up at Magic Eraser
Yeah man I mean it's pretty extreme language being used in service of trying to sell food buckets
Great
So the other thing the Run start this episode is a strong interest in prison
Hunting Trump
As like
Really the man of the people
Like he loves
You
Just can't say for one second guys
We f***** up on this
We were Alex. We we thought we could go
Controller
We thought we could do what he needed to do because there's so much Messianic stuff
But having visions about there's a how he's a psychic and all this s*** like
He can't be wrong about this because if he's wrong about it and all that stuff looks like total b******* too big to be wrong
Yeah he's too big for sale near me
And you know that involves doing a lot of dear leader s*** talking about how like and what he does
Like this is
This is nonsensical
He gets briefings has a secret Ally
Wood box
What people hand them
He demands
On overseas flights
From d.c.
They cannot stand it
Can't stand the Trump as a secret service go around and get letters
From the commoners you at the rally made him read
4 pages are you sure by the way
Adjusted.
Yeah but not Trump
Flights
And he insisted
The mail the collect at the rallies and you sit there and them
If he can read I would be one I think he would need to use reading glasses
And he can
I don't think he can read
Why would she really kind of don't think
I don't want to speculate on whether or not he's on
At the very least
Betrayal Penny Reid
You're not just on planes planes is he reading your letters
Don't joke with people is like I would watch that but I'd watch it on a plane
Stuck on the plane
It's not just on planes
Is like Superman
Bring him pallets of mail
From the warehouse down the road and then
And just just reads it
Battlbox
I am the night
I am mailman
Set the Secret Service call me
Okay
This is f***** up service
A secret
Could you leave us alone
Please stop
Alex just leaving
Countdown
Yeah so try playing brides and then at night
You sitting there just read mail they think
You crazy this guy special
Alex comes back
The break starts talkin about some bible stuff is really big into religion
Does say something here that makes me think I don't know if he knows much about the bike
Play bunco
Jose say
46 I'm sorry what now
James Version
Destroyed for lack of knowledge because thou Hast rejected knowledge
I'm also
Analog. I will also forget thy children
For me it's not a power
Everyday
Call Tina Peeples
Responsibility
I took a turn from the Bible verse okay
How old is Dick about this because honestly Alex's clothes on the pronunciation
He said the book of Jose but it's a book of Hosea
I know that's close but it's super far off for anyone with any familiarity with the Bible
I don't believe that anyone who's read the Bible or has been involved in any church with
With any regularity would not know how to pronounce the name
Of the book Hosea
It's just unbelievable to me but someone with any real history with the Bible would encounter that word and take it might be Jose
This along with all the other things Alex does connection with the Bible
Actually be super
Maybe he appreciates Mexican people more than we thought
No I just don't think
I think he's completely unfamiliar with the the actual Bible
It's the little things like that just keep coming up of like
What are you doing
Oral tradition is what will
Bible verse God can change the
Bible but you can't change our words
It's okay
Book of Hosea
Whatever
So
Earlier in the show Alex freaking out a little bit you might have
Mother noticed that
I did
He wasn't on the show
Right before he was on the show
Scrappy kind of explains why he was freaking out
It's because Trump
Relies on him for information
Boy pictures on air
Able to go out and and and
I know because we're just so much
What I say today
This is actually a real president
Founded by criminals and he has to get information from me
And then I just
You should
Picking up what are you saying there
Here's the way I'm interpreting that is more like much like the Bible it is open
The Constitution
What I hear is
If I say drink
People are going to think
Influencing Francais I drink bleach if I disagree with drinking bleach
I'm going to lose the support of all my wacko friends who would rather Trump drink Bleach then
Anything else
So he's caught in a
Catch-22
I don't want people to drink bleach
But somehow that's a controversial thing to say in my world right
I have a slightly different I can't do my show
Because of the immense
Pressure cuz I know Trump is getting his information from me and that's why I was freaking out earlier because I am not doing the
Good enough job because I know that Trump has a team listening to my show and whenever I say this is a message for the
President they cut it out and they give it to drop
This is the same thing with Steve pieczenik thinking the newspapers talking to him like honestly this is just
Cuckoo
Cookie Shop
If
If it weren't for the fact that Trump said let's drink bleach
Just feel like nothing
Feels more like the TV's talking to you than it ever has before I would imagine
Like if the president is saying
Wackos
With Alex he's not really on that tip
Sincerely I don't I don't hear APUSH drinking bleach
Or the bleach people
Maybe he's resentful
Maybe
Yeah because Alex hasn't even he's pretending they're all trouble saying the sunlight is good for you
Rebutting the part about injectable
Sure sure
I don't know
I think it's all just a rationalization for why you left the show three times
Earlier
He said the show went sideways
That I will say
Fexofenadine
So Alex
Gets Brill do me
Bitesquad
Vans
He's just like well this is over
Long after I'm settled in my grave
You can save this on a on a memory stick
So when they're killing you yet this out
There's still time to stop
Only in the future we lost this round
John Connor
We lost this round there's only we can only stop them in the future
That's pretty much it
Come with me if you want to die
Shorter
Time traveling what not do the 27th or isn't like a lot of really good stuff going on but trust
May it makes up for it
Bucketful
Okay
But this is really really just like I was listening and most of the time on the 27th I just think
This clip is one of the times that I had that
Response
Trump is not an idiot savant he's an idiot
But you guys have stuff online
Characteristics
Very quickly
But sometimes he seems disconnected
A person who is highly knowledgeable about one subject but knows little about anything else
So I would call him
Siobhan
But it looks like when you're talking to Trump
Jesus
He's probably the smartest person on the planet
Wow
This is
You say he did some dear leader type gym leader
Probably the smartest person in the world I mean
He's our god king he has Infinite Wisdom
You know how like a idiot savants I know one thing he's like for everything
I have word that he's rude when he's being rude to people or maybe looks like he's not paying attention
It's just because he's so much smarter than the people around absolutely attention span of a
Mouse it is because he is a genie
Right
That's had that was upsetting
I can't imagine I can't imagine listening to myself say something like that
And then like
Survive again
That's cereal
Breaking news that he wants to get to and also I don't know if you still have your bingo card
Hard but we might find out that another movie is real
Don't say it like that
Play
Or the bad guy
By the vaccines tainted he sells supplements
Three causes the Earth to die
And you see that the lockdown cities and all the precursors in the conditioning
So not only is Contagion real it's about Alex
Greatschools
So you got this breaking news that's a juicy
I really didn't like him doing that that really bums me out you don't like hearing about the new juice
Astoria
USS will not take
Launch
Covid-19 in it
Rihanna's with contaminated death
Global initiative on Friday
Speedy development and distribution of drugs and vaccines covid-19
A spokesperson of the US mission in Geneva told Reuters Alex's editorializing pretty heavily when he was appearing
Tubi
Juicy I will know also the underlying story here is insanely bad
I was presenting it as dropping too smart to get caught up in this evil vaccine work
In reality would have demonstrates is a really scary level of isolation we're taking on
Also this news didn't just break
The guardian reported on the story on April 24th for 3 days
Before the episode Alex is doing what he's calling this a break
Juicy piece of news
What happened is the global leaders got together on a video call and quote pledged accelerate cooperation on a coronavirus vaccine
But that's not all
It was also about sharing research
And as the guardian reported quote
The corporation pledge made it a virtual meeting was designed to show that wealthy countries will not keep the results of research
From developing country
Because Trump has shown such outright hostility to The Who
He couldn't take part in this meeting without giving an implied endorsement of them which he's too much of a baby to do
And so the supposed leader of the Free World the head of the world's great superpower turned his back on an international pledge
To make sure the developing world is not left behind because they can't afford to pursue the level of medical research that we can
F*** all this and f*** Alex for celebrating
This is
Stupid it is it is very much
Mayonnaise
It's it's like
He's turning America into the s*** hole that he thinks other p
The other places are
In order to justify America
I am flabbergasted
There are no adults and we're all
We're all stupid
We're all just f******
Stupid
But if there's a Saving Grace
It's
Knowing that Alex has a zone are are clearly number
Based on how frequently
Keep stalking
Think about how this s***'s over
Pho that's a scientific
Satanic
Go down to Gates
Personally
Talk to some Bear Hollow
Told them all of this just days ago
Over the phone now you can imagine what that do
Write on me
That's a two-way street the target
You know that
It's okay
Very very soon
Is this like The Running Man
What's that movie
Total Recall you plug into the Matrix in
Really it's all alucinacion
Cool Man Lego
Is very very soon as I get obliterated
Alaska April 27th
I think that this is real also interviewed Lord
So this is
Like this is a real real problem
Alex
Medallia
You better choose a side pubs anglo-americans talisman
Whoa
We raised right now
So that little line indicates to me a complete lack of awareness on out at 8 Alex of his own worldview
He doesn't know what he saying
What do you wants to say is that you're either with China or you're with his weird white supremacist Patriot buddies but he's using language as a
Very specific and very different meeting in the world of his conspiracy
What Alex's anglo-american established
He's not talking about the West
He cannot be
Because the foundation of his narratives about the globalist
Largely rest upon the foundation of misrepresentations of Carol Quigley's writer
Alex pretends that he's read Quigley's book tragedy and hope and in that book quickly admit
It's there's a group of people operate in secret to control the world
These are the round table group
Who control the Council on Foreign Relations the Royal Inn
Institute of international Affairs and countless other bodies
This group was set up by Cecil Rhodes and Alfred Milner and quickly very clearly refers to the collection of these groups as
The anglo-american established
That's literally the name of Quigley's previous book about roads and the influence he's had over the years
I've heard Alex use that term in relation to quickly many times it's shorthand for the Proto globalist
In the sphere of the Infowars
Conspiracy theory fuse to believe that Alex would ever use that expression 2
Denote something positive in opposition to the Chinese
Because it literally means globalists
You are either with the people I hate
Or you're with the people I hate
And I'm
On the side of
Somebody
This isn't something that you could possibly slip up and say unless you have no idea what you're talkin about you speak
Mostly randomly and you don't have a good handle on your Source material
This would literally be like me saying you can either support Satan or you can support the infowar that's the situation wherein
I don't believe that this is a slip-up on Alex's part I think it's an indication that he really doesn't know what angle American establishment
I think it was grasping for Words any remember that he said those particular words before it sounded good
Unfortunately he happen to accidentally suggests that siding with the globalist
Is a good idea
Cuz he doesn't know any
Doesn't mean everything
He's just talking s*** I think it's fairly easy to say that
If he doesn't mean anglo-american
Establishment in the way that even his conspiracies suggest
What he really meant is you're either with white people are you with
Mommy more or less like I said that's what he's
Pulling cord
That term means something
Right
Restart the 28th holyshit
I cannot wait
To get to
The fun on this episode
Why we start where Alex starts
And that's him talking about how the end is near for him
That we're not dead yet in fact we're stronger than ever hitting the final stretch
Complete the operation
Just save the day
Just f****** say next time he might not exactly when he plans to shut things down
You know like a lot of people
There's a there's a chance
This is all just the address
Yeah but it's so consistent going on for a while now
And it just feels
It feels more
Real than other times he's he's done these modeling performances
I don't know I don't I don't know
We could be talking about him in a year and look back on this and feel like idiots that we were like
Oh man he will not feel like an idiot he should feel like an idiot
That is not mine and one of the reasons that I take this more real than life
Other times that he said will be gone we're done
Anytime that blunt about it
But one of the reasons that I take it as
Morio's
Is a factors soup
F****** flat lately
Like he's just
Real slow in like
Lot of long pauses
The long pauses are not too uncommon but it's like he's just no energy just
F*** it.
Seeing the full force
How's the new world order system to shut off an economy bankrupt
Farms
And complete our journey just slavery
Through this process we will discover
Kashmiri
El Americano
The Renaissance in 1776
We shall set us free
I am
I am focused today
I have
Cogitated on what needs to be done.
He sounds like he has his own a tranquilizer
Descend you on
Next message
If it should you choose to accept the mission
There's no life behind that there's no vigor
Fairly regular these days
Which is one of the reasons why I take it like more
Because generally when you want to rile people up
To your calls or whatever you don't come in with like
Nugget
But that's that's the vibe he's giving off
Vibrate Now talks about easing to take calls
And also talks about like
Ever get to the news
I really want to have more calls in the show and only get it up
Within the first hour most days and leaves
But
You can't do justice each piece of this
And so why even get to it in fact
Videoclub
So
The mentality that says
There's so much news so I get to any of it it's very dumb
It's incredible
It's not how you get things done no. Cuz if you have stories that are all big
It's better to focus on well then just leave it I can't get to all 5
So it's a ludicrous a strategy
It's not uncommon to find yourself thinking something along those lines for a little bit but
It seems like he's been doing that his entire career yet
It's a dark moment when you want to get back to business and get down to
Get it done
Focus on actionable items that's how you maximized productivity don't worry about the fight
Look at the one thing with your whole ass not to things with her
That's right
Alex
Should be into he likes folksy nonsense
So Alexander sex with talks about his esteem
Bob and the good guy
Guys and everybody knows it
Could barely even talk or operate
You can't shut me off you can't shut you up
Platinum
The real deal
You're the real deal that's why
Your prayers
Paramount
Spread the word is penultimate
And then you got the trifecta there but beneath that is a vital support
Sure
Spread the word
Penultimate
And then that little added
Magic is the money
Never even wanted my until I tried to shut me down 15 years ago
God said to me
Operation
Prosperous and you need to do that and I did it you did it
And here we are today and so now
When you buy products in Fort Wright, Kentucky
You are
Woohoo so God told him to chase money so
I command you to get that
Paper
Alex this is God scare people and then sell them gold
Manipulative way
The only way to stop the demon
You need to
Scaring people boy
Wolf Alex
Have you considered super male vitality
Make men feel like they're weak and then sell them pills to solve their problems
Alex water filters
Beyond why did I make better water I like that I really do enjoy that
I don't know I don't
I don't know what God loves and what God doesn't but
I just have a sense
They wouldn't be so frail set
I started to get the sense of it like we're in trouble
Big trouble
Rohit go sideways
I don't even know that that's
Understatement
Tea kettle
Okay
I don't want to go to that level yet unless we can turn this around but
If you have nothing
Lactulose
One human
To do out
5G Towers
Before you get killed by the drums
Something
Running around
Not a bad thing
Vallarta
Do you want a puppy
I'm on the spit
I found your ass
Great analogy
Tell me I'm a slave
Take your gun
And what
You're literally going to bring a knife to a gunfight
Whataburger
Baby burn
Weight Watchers
That we're not at that point yet but I want you to
Intergenerational
Understand the power you have is all wet
I'm listening
That the weapon
Or is it
Write yourself to kill
Rather people not to kill your ass
Devil worshippers
Everything you've got and everything you ever are
Oh boy
One way or another
But you got to find that spirit and just have
Know that it's
Jumping
It's going to empower you to work hard and be good and not getting a
Your wife your husband
Why was it bad
Their ass
Is Blue Bloods scumbag
Unhappy
They print
Their hatred of themselves on.
And we reject
Yeah that was Rose like we're in trouble
That is a
That's a complicated psychodrama that just played out that way it's not yet time to
It starts out with
I could be the Unabomber it goes through to I was a bad husband and father
It continues on to ya maybe I am projecting my hate Onto You by telling you that your
Projecting
There are some players to it
I think there's some interesting pieces to with the like him saying
Lose one person could take out five of these towers are 15 V power
The idea of having Nothing Left to Lose
Is important to hold onto because I think that that's the mode that Alex is definitely in
We lost this round there's nothing left to lose
I have nothing left to lose and I am on Murder Street
Sprite
Is that vibe mnd that like yelling about murder murder
I think that it's fine I don't know like
You know someone's going to kill you it's not I do think it's morally wrong to kill them usually the horses
OU
Now
Is getting a vaccine the same thing as someone rushing you with a gun or a knife
I don't think so you know I would say that Alex is definition of what requires lethal force in self-defense
Might be a little bit off this is the problem with the intolerant left
Dad Vine
It's part of what I believe
Then he goes from the yelling about killing and burning these robots into chores
We're not safe we're not safe no this is this
We end up going to break a little bit after that he comes back
Do they needed to chill him out a little bit
They really should have this isn't
Dude this goes
It's a places you could ever imagine this goes so bad
Anybody should have stopped at any point really should have hit the big button that says like like
Whatever their first attempt to try and get Alex into a better headspace is playing
You Belong To The City
Every single time he gives a speech over it
He does but it's very cookie
Key cutter by the numbers
Your life your children live everything you got
Unleash your own life
I got you your slave all of us all of our people
Before being free
Men's was that promise that dream
So many was realized and soy
Incredible wealth power
Came here to try to take
Power over and try to subvert it
All they had to do was in Bryson
I love Humanity
What
Do your phone calls
Quick fact check
America being viewed Reba freedom
We had that
Try to remember
So you want six calls but yours wants to tell you about how he's now
Scared Bone Crusher
He's never
Imagine his advisors
Yes
Delivered president
Of info with all the
Pretty cool
What does that say
Everybody else is he scared
Emo
My family
You know what
How to kill the Big Bad Wolf
That was not the moral of that story Apple
And the Big Bad Wolf
We were going to attack Iran
Bobcat like 513
Call man sex
The rock or stick killing their ass
Everybody
I don't understand that but
False
The world is this
Lay it down
Kissing ass
But don't let them push that instinct laid out of here
Your phone calls are coming up
Money to fight these wars
The wind in my sails products you need put it back in stock
What the f***
Against
Monsters come out come out or I'll blow your house down in the first little piggy
Barrett 30 cal
Whatever the f*** I want
So Alex goes at the money comes back
Is where it all falls
That was keeping it together
Comparative
Comparatively
Total Staffing
Okay alright I normally reply
Maybe
I would spend more time on that but I can't
Because Alex completely loses his s***
Restaurant.com
Luby's
Does old ladies
Because he knows he being confident
Total depression
Nothing
Where do I
I got to be honest with you
Percent chance we on the total collapse
Sometimes
I mean baby starving to death I mean you ain't get your medicine I mean it's done
Vindictive person
And America shouldn't take the blame why would anyone blame Alex
What is first thought to be 60% chance of this whole thing's going down
And guess what
Not my fault probably because somewhere along the line he realizes that it's all of the things that he champ
Bands that are going to make the collapse app
I think on some subconscious level he might have a feeling about that maybe whenever everybody does the stuff that I was
I want to do as we've seen over the past 3 years
We're all going to die
Thermite thermite be sound like
Part of his brain that's unacceptable to his conscience that is screaming that I have
Topeka
So 60% chance total collapse we get some more numbers in this next clip
And then Alex makes a confession
That's
Will rock
The ages
This is something like
This this changes everything
Call Dwayne
You understand so I'll just rhetoric
Percent of people lived in
But half of those were self-sufficient
That's 45% of people were totally self-sufficient
Today's hits
We have a collapse
My superpowers being honest
Alex will eat his neighbors
When someone needs to send this broadcast
Quickly
Neighborhood watch
One of those neighborhood neighborhood apps or people talk to each other stairs one thing
The Alex should be concerned about its f******
King food
He said he's talked to do today Buckaroo protein isn't beat dad
Any sort of feeling of like
Because he's
Number one sponsor is a survival food company
Keep talking about how he's ordered more and more boom from Empire
He's had it for a long time
Kind of makes you think it's just time to get it done he's got that holy s*** so f***** up
For being Auto wolf
Also Alex is making up numbers about the Great Depression
Can I get Ensure
Run to the Library of Congress by 1900 the year 1930 percent of the u.s. population that migrated to cities
And we're living in areas you could be call Urban centers
I don't know if Alex expect people to believe that between 1900 and 1929 approximately two-thirds of the urban Poppy
Malaysian relocated
Back to rural areas but either way
According to 2018 data from Pew social trends a majority of the US population lives
In areas that would be qualified as suburban
At this point
Population of approximately 14% at that point and urban comes in around 31
According to Pew one of the primary drivers of the higher level of population in urban areas
Immigration
Most of the time people who come to this country from another country aren't doing so to settle in rural Montana
Most of the time they'll gravitate towards locations with the most job opportunities or places with at least some semblance of
Community that they can connect with like people who share their country of origin or religious
Just practices
Those things are not as likely to be found in rural areas as compared to Urban one
There are other variables but this is one big driver of urban and Suburban population growth
It's not shared by rural areas
Anyway I was just making things up but urban and rural areas is Wells with Great Depression
But good to know that he would eat his neighbors did not have a Koreatown
So I don't think people people like
Part part of larger assimilation is also
The entry entry ability has a lot of that is having people have some sort of a share.
Vanity with you it makes it so much easier
It's one of the big drivers as like you see larger growth in urban and Suburban areas
But I thought maybe you was just saying I got Eve my neighbors and it was a throwaway thing
Nope we're going to go on a long serious about water
My superpowers being honest
Po-boy
A few years ago
I'm literally look at my neighbor's downgoing
Try to hang them up and got them and scan them and chop them off you know what I'm ready my dog
Superpowers being honest
3rd Street
You thought about that yet
Because
My neighbor's neighbor
Chop his ass up
Radu should have tackled him long ago
This is really stringy you said you found this in the forest
Dad is this truck is this truck
Well technically your superpower is being honest
Chuck the neighbor
Not ground chuck while it is ground chuck
Who's on first year
I know we've heard Alex talk a lot in the past about how after 15 days of no food we all become cannibals but
Don't think I've ever heard him discuss his willingness or dare I say enthusiasm to eat his neighbor
Fantastical
It made me wonder if I decided to look into cannibalism a little bit and I got two interesting bits of research on the subject that I think Alex should
Reconsider
First game from a 2017 article in time about research done by James Cole the senior lecturer
Anthropology at the University of Brighton
Cool published a study of nature that looked at the caloric content of a human body
Like all the edible parts we came to the conclusion that it seems unlikely that most of the Historical Inn
Instances of cannibalism we're driven by a need for food
Except in cases like the Donner Party
The reason for this is that as cool put it quote the mental and physical effort to hunt a hominid would presumably be much
What's greater give him the hominins ability to fight run and think their way out of
The hunt
What are you getting at is that compared to most any other source of food
The Cal would expand
To eat a person
But almost not be worth it from a nutritional perspective
It's a bad strategy
Unless you literally have no other option and even then you probably do have a better option you haven't considered like various wild plants
So what you're saying is that he has come to
Movie scientific
Conclusion that man is the most dangerous game or the most calorie intensive
Yeah you'd be like most of the time I would like any kind of cannibalism was little ritualistic
Already dead
The second article I found was pretty interesting it was in the sun discussing a recent study published in the Journal of forensic science
Researchers profiled five cases of people who practice cannibalism in interesting commonality
Essentially what they found was the people who ended up eating other people are pretty consistently either severely schizophrenic
Or their survivors of intensely dysfunctional childhood
In the case of two case studies
He's quote
Feelings of humiliation seem to be the trigger and both patients assaulted their victims at a time when they suffered a loss of
Self-esteem
Rancid Alex's naturally he's talking about being so right
We suffer in a bit of a loss of self-esteem do think he's being serious I found that threat
To be trouble from the Sun article
In the cases of cannibalism in patients who suffer from schizophrenia the researchers found there was a history of emotional fiction
Hostility in their parent-child relationship
The academics concluded the schizophrenic
Performed cannibalism it as a very extreme reaction of self-defense
Do a threat of Destruction
Physical or psychological
Wow for the ones with a personality disorder cannibalism boosted their self-esteem and relieve tension
Quote ego and narcissism are the central issue
With a desire to overcome frustrations by means of an extraordinary Act
It kind of sounds like if you take if you just replace
I'm actually eating people and talking about eating people if she had that same thing
Is looking for you looking to overcome deep-rooted frustration
He feels
Seems like an extreme reaction of self-defense to a threat of Destruction physical or psychological
It's
I would assume he is somehow hostility in his parent-child relationships
What does all this mean
Maybe nothing or maybe I totally believe it when Alex
This is one of the few tabs where I'm really bummed out that
Set your researches
Is pretty good because
I was really hoping that this was kind of a
Tough talk kind of situation but now that he fits the profile I don't like that at all
Not like that at all about Alex
He would say that everything
To be clear I don't think Alex is going to eat anybody but I think that the mental state that he's presenting
Seem to follow at least some of the soup
Superficial characteristics in these studies
Which is not great
In some ways just being
I wouldn't even say I would eat a person
Unless I was being very obviously
Funny about
Probably in the
You know I hated that that's all that coconut lime seltzer
That be way worse because
So
I probably wouldn't have looked into that stuff if it wasn't like
He talks about it for a long
Oh boy
Your ass first
You're not
Did you out of those bunkers
You out of those holes
I'll get in there God's last thing I do imma get my hands around your throat
You know that's why you're going to eat your ass
You should have thought about that when you
The long time ago
I was going to eat the globalist accept Jesus Christ remember that I
Remember the letter to the Thessalonians
I do remember that where it was like look
You guys don't accept Christ we're going to eat your ass
That's just the rule
I just wrote Jesus told me this is
So weird
Turn your asses other cheek so I can eat it
This is the weirdest thing I've ever heard on this show a protracted rant about how
It starts with I'm going to eat my papers in order to keep my children
I meant dick out the globalist and I'm going to eat them first
I'm going to be honest this is starting to sound less about sustenance
I'm going to be straight with you Dad yeah I think this isn't about food
I think you've got
I don't
Like I understand he's being like a show man
Being over-the-top and what-have-you but I also don't think he's joking
Was a metaphysical hypothetical buddy it's really not and let's just let's just get past the
The jokes here
Yes let's get past though
That's what I was
Marion government study for South Africa. Stacy Jeremy directions to Panda South America
Shows about 7 days almost everyone committed murder for fun
Within 14 days almost
Suicide
Right before I
Did that but
What
Flat
That nice little stingrays again
Little Sig
I will eat you
Let's get past the joke
I want you to know
I will barbecue your ass
Flat
I will eat
So ridiculous okay also
People who've gone on hunger strikes
Just making that up because he's stupid not to justify his fantasies about eating his enemies which is an interesting new low
I got to say he never seen the show naked and afraid they're out there for 2 or 3 weeks every time and then
Never resort to cannibalism
Answer that's a good counterexample
I'll be interested to see his Source on this like 14-day cannibalism
I'm just rattling off countries and saying the word actuary isn't going to do it
Like a great diet
14 day cannabis
What a dumb dumb
So he's not done
Courtney
How you doing a ritual stuff
Cleo app
Watch a my daughter started at
Siding installation is it was a joke you can piss on all day do you understand you unleash Buckhannon
Once you to eat Unleash the Beast
And you're not the Beast
Are you
A DUI
I'm Godzilla on steroids
Z workout
As for the cords and everything I'm joking around here
Illegally freaking I'm not get anybody
According to the letter of the law
Parentheses
Will totally eat somebody to eat people for about 15 minutes now because of cord
Haha haha
That is the eating people version of if I did it
Alex is presenting this in like a really cowardly way even in this stupid hypothetical because he's saying like
Do this to feed my children also raises the question for me you're going to make your kids be cannibals
Of course that's
F***** up
Every discussion say don't eat people I'm going to eat them too
My baby's coming to the equation
I will cook your
Bastrop so fast
Baby
Iridescent my babies ain't going to die for your crap
God
God I say that in bed all the time your leftist ass like corn on the cob baby different different
I can't imagine like
I don't know I mean
It's such an it's such a shame that things from the show can't be used in court
I can't imagine how easily you could win custody if you just played a tape of
I will feed them until tell my children here on Earth
He promised to lie to his children and make them eat people
And he was not joking
He said he was a joke
Strike that from the record seeing as how it's obviously bulshit
Yeah
Wow
For three years now and suddenly you just say you found a cow in the backyard
What is stroke of a stray couches watering in the back
Yard was it Brandon
Do so
If he has two years worth of food or whatever the only people who are going to be left after that
A point or also can be pretty hardcore survivors at that point he's not going to be able to find easypickins to eat
Out of here is keeping his neighbor in the freezer he's prepared
I could I could see that
He touched on this team of like the globalist to me Spirit cookers like they took Society
He has like a joke
Really what was going on was real man where restraining themselves cuz they knew the monsters that lived
Die
You Want To Worship
You're about to meet something worse you dumb sack sack rap
You been pissing on civilization your whole life not knowing its men held it up
Savages
What are savages held up
Cute emmanouil pull the fifth
Shove it in your teeth
No good
I'll sit there and live off starving Latin Americans and Africans
What
Performance artists like they say
Dinos
Jesus
Next week I will be taking
Computer chip out of a home inspector
You think I'm not real
I mean
Wolf
What is sex
That is what an embarrassing f****** fat is
Is that is legendary that is
That is the stuff of Legend yeah I mean
Good call on his farts a couple times
Calling out like a haha no one takes me seriously because he
Also
It's route says
I'm not joking
No I'm going to be very much not joking
While
So in the case of a cold
Write avoid
Yes Google
Good call
If you have like a little Community like some self-sustaining Community Mutual Aid kind of situation
You going to eat you
This is
This is every movie where there that post
Apocalyptic movie we got the band of good people going in there and then they see that nice little house
Alex is Little House in the country
You got his family in there and they're like oh we've got plenty of food to share with you
Yes
Black pot
The background staring
Heritage it so that was f***** up
But kind of funny
Pretty fun
Barry
Daughter of a great headspace
Perhaps
I would say like I described as kind of a new low for him chocolate
Justifiable
Straight to Kohl's
Not really cool comes back
And he starts crying
Cuz he starts thinking about all the abortion
Cities paid for
And like this is
This is a real
Jarring swing of emotions
From
He globalism 2dq out he rolls and eat you
Everybody
And
I feel guilty every time I'm around my children
But I'm not building some
Because
They know what they've done
Genetic selfishness
Constantly like I have dreams about
Is Ron Ron go to Northern
But I just don't even worry about
My daughter
My daughter I just constantly worried about them
I think you're a bad father
Tried to save the whole thing and I you tried to save it I don't know if we can save any other folks
God tells me
How many
You probably killed 15-20 kids you know of
What
So now
That comes back on the ones that made it son
Cuz I know when I die Spirits are real
Epicenter
Incredible people
He tortured for 1,000 years one the filter.
Imagine the children
I've supported being shop
I never knew that
I know that well
I know I got to get a bratwurst
You figure
Caltrain
You don't get a strike
You think you like some doctor
Child brain or chop your daughter or son up
You don't then dye it I mean
Do Universe Works
You never kannaway was Chan
Does you reap what you sow you got to get off a man
You can't you can't do this
But you can't you can't do an entire segment about how excited and willing you are to eat people and then
That
Like I don't I don't honestly believe I think he was hammering that up a little bit but I do believe there is some sincere emotions
Somewhere
That were being
Who played up
This is a
F****** pendulum Ann Hughes
This is not like
No
This is
Did almost feels voyeuristic
Watching this is show at this point
It almost feels like we're
Seeing something we should
Yeah
Yeah this is this is
Somebody
How are you
I want to be in the
Room
Not that not the room with him I want to be behind glass that hopefully one production room
And I would like to be wearing an anti hannibalism
Looking around at the people next to you just like
Are wheat where I'll just going to do this she's going to watch this
Iron Man as he gets into his
Cannibalism chunk
Oh no it's great.
I know I call babies going to Straight Talk
Holyshit gets a commercial
Dodged the bullet comes back from break
What are you doing
Someone needs to stop it like
Someone cares needs to stop and there is no one
This is this is embarrassing
It's it's gross
Realizes got to go to calls
Keep references going to calls with about the best thing you could say after this
I don't want to talk about can't believe I actually thought about what I said it is
Cut the crap
You are and what you stand for forever
I guess that's all that ever matter
In New Jersey
What an awkward throat
Call Zack
Let's not talk about everything I've said here
Let's pretend that didn't happen I am Jovi New Jersey Alex quick question
Would you eat me
I will take my answer out there
So Alex doctor this Joe character and it's it's whatever but he starts rambling about the end of the world
I want to watch
That's why they did this if they're losing
Beautiful plant
In the projection it's exactly as Revelation says
They're going to end
I love you balls and come back
I'm sorry I've been out of control today
Hoo-boy
Just going to ride that at Mystic break in the other direction
Going to ride that at I've been out of control
So yeah
It's
It's interesting to talk him here in this next clip. Paul
Paul Joseph Watson
And something
F****** happy for a man
Apprentices
What does Asante say about apprentices
Children
The long after you've gone to come
I got a plan takes over nice car
Suppose taking over the next hour and I got to say something
He's not this is still the second hours
It seems like he's losing
In-Shape particularly in the second hour
He still has another hour
Wish I was that big but
Yes yes it does feel that way
Wheels
Bully off the way
So Alex gets to talking to more about this the world is starving narrative
Should I tease on
He's
Right in some ways and then wrong and some others
Hatchimals descriptions that conservatives
We need to come out and say I drama start African
White Americans and Asians the death
We don't support that
Don't stop
The president on this last week
Mobile horses
Kill your ass
Okay great
Dude
I can't imagine all those babies in Africa and Latin America
Overpopulated novel populated
Grandmother has off
Little kids begging for food and dying
Not in my DNA
The real world
133 million people
Starving
There's not a Million Dead worldwide virus
Millions are dying
Why
Do do
265 million starving sorry it's going up
To the Patriots a nationalist
Some Christians
Evil white man
Very much care
Yeah
If that's the only thing you're bringing to the table
Unfortunately everything else you talking about is wrong
It's not
65 Million number is not a new development it's just from the same Guardian article he's been siding on the story the whole time
He's ever read it though
I can tell that
The Articles published on April 21st and it warns that due to the crisis were in now quote
At least 265 million are being pushed to the brink of starvation
All experts on the topic agree that the two most essential things needed to stop the lumaca task
Tree is money and access
We can all donate and try to make a difference that way we can pressure our government to take
Seriously
And provide funding to organizations are on the ground helping
Beyond that these people who are the aid workers need access
They need to be able to cross borders to get the assist
Distance to the people who need it
The central message of this article which chiefly quotes Beasley the head of the UN world food programme
Is that quote
We can stop this becoming a world wide spread famine but we need to act quickly and smart
That's the bottom line
So weird
This article is published under the global development initiative at the guardian
And if you actually read the article there's a little icon that says
Supported by the Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation
The content is editorially independent but the only reason a lot is reporting that Alex is relying on to build his
Completely nonsensical and exploitative narrative
Exist the only reason it exists is because of money donated by the very people
He's trying to paint does the arch villains were trying to starve the developing world
So again I say take this problem seriously
But don't for a second think that Alex gives a single s*** about
These people are props to him and he'll gladly yellow about their deaths to make his political point but he wouldn't do one inconvenient thing
To help them out
So again
Very serious issue
And I'm glad that Alex is bringing it up
That's other people are bringing it up
I guess I'm not glad he's bringing it up cuz he's just using
Yeah
I mean even then it is
His hero his
Messiah
As he puts it
Is able to do this at any time
And is only going to use it as a trump
Card if
He needs to
Well
He would never ever do it
And this is the good
He's saying the trump card is accusing people of being racist if they don't help because he Alex believes
That accusations of racism are like Magic Bullets or something
I bet Trump could
Unilaterally take care of all of this V wanted to
I'm not sure that's a hundred percent true but he certainly could do it it's not even like
Mostly
I'm not an expert in these issues but I do know there's more we could be doing oh yeah
So anyway
Alex gets
The call now
And this is a bad call
Mr. Jones
Mind
I'm just wondering
Do you think we're going to survive
School
Hold on to that
So earlier when he was talking to that
Speaking extemporaneously
Teen 5G Towers
Another caller is asking if we're going to survive and he says no
It seems that way it seems like if you put these
Two pieces of
Information
Rhetoric that he's putting out on his episode your left at the conclusion
None of us have anything left to lose
Enter Wendy's collar discusses what he really wants to talk about with Alex
This sounds like a terrorist planning session
My buddy he just got in they are already.
Protest
And 30th
Pod beautiful
Your spirit
Totally survives but your spirit as free will
Centerpoint it
Tell you something you don't know Hunter
Play Giselle playing on her
For the Lord
Damn right brother
That seems
Yeah
That seems like a little bit of kind of
And I know they even made this gun to a protest
Isn't necessarily a terrorist act but the way he's talking about wheat being my buddy bought AR-15
To go to the protest
Matt is a different
Kind of vibe that I'm getting from that caller
I don't know I'm not I could be over sensitive on a
It's very f***** up it feels f***** up
The comparison
Things are like
Between
Leftist
Rally's in
And protest
Swear
The cops
Fuk up people for just wearing a mask
And then you look at these protests then you see them in full f****** Decked Out
3 better not wearing masks a lot of them but they're like that
But part of the difference in
The treatment is obviously
Ideology
The cops are Fascist
Another part of it is that
These guys
Do seem like they were in the brink of murdering a s*** ton of people at all
Apparently there is a massive threat
These protests
So Alex takes a break from calls
Cuz he wants to put a picture of his daughter up on screen
Which is f***** up
I'm going to Doc's my daughter yeah he starts crying talking about
Sky
Look at your children everything is good you see
DC. Right there
Is the times of the enemy coming in on assessor of years ago
So perfect so pure
God shines through her
I just feel
Because you can lie to yourself all day long
Join the New World Order man
You just turned your kids over to hell
And they're so innocent they're so good they're so pure
And they just want to
Understanding Universe look up here she is looking at you
They all you put your daughter on are you make her a Target she's already at Target
What she's already under attack by Eagles like every child
They want a corrupt that
Till that
Go home
Hey Dad.
Thank you for ordering pizza
Second shift today you said you were going to feed me people and then you put my picture up
So could you
Never do that again or be on your show
Please stop within like an hour
Yes doing this diatribe about cannibalism and then crying about his daughter was showing the picture of her like it
Yeah I can't stand like this is not okay
Number of
Different levels
It's really incomprehensible
And yet in 2020 hit mix
So much
I guess so somebody be screaming about cannibalism on the radio
Silly that it hasn't been that part I'm thrilled with I guess it does indicate that the Overton window
It shifted for Alex to an almost incomprehensible
Beyond The Pale at least
Yeah but if I had to choose
This last part
Mercury's crying and talk about his daughter for it talk about cannibalism
Kind of interesting and funny
This is sad
And doesn't belong on public Highway
Absolutely children and she makes me uncomfortable on her behalf
You're up I doubt it I don't know
I can't say yes or no cuz he doesn't
It's simply implied that he just did it
Anyway
Alex Goes to another caller that I feel like he's trying to prod on to do illegal things
Hey Alex would you eat me
Brother Ali
God bless you sir and the crew
I appreciate you Carlos go ahead
Answer as as usual you are on target
This is
Good and evil sir
Spiritual war
We are
How many levels but we're not
You are a channel William a channels will survive been given information on how to
Also combat
On a different level
One of my best friend's is a 30-year Army vet
Ready
Can't really get on Tober to Arab
Enemy
What I'm going to do then
Sir you kind of just did
I got a cousin that Leonardo always never going to do it
Always waiting too long to pearly plan
Wow that's almost like
You coward
PayPal
No that's not good
Oh man
You guys you guys don't even know I'm the butt of the spear hear it if I'm going to tell you that you're never going to do that
A dumbass I'm the champion and you're going to bring that in a buy house
I am respected get the f*** out of here
But the same caller brings up that his sister was possessed by a demon and Alex deals with
About as well as you can
For now is the one-year anniversary of my father
Okay
Sister who is under demonic possession
Exactly 28 weeks
2 days and I know that number cuz
Nothing I saw
During my father
Suffern
In the world
You're right as above so below Carlos God bless you I appreciate your call
In California another call from California go ahead night was not done
He was not heated not really made his point I was just
Psycho possession stories
My job
Not yours
I know it's b*******
So I can say it exactly
You are very serious about demon busy
And that is an issue for me
And I just said I was going to eat
People
Remember people using it back
In the earlier days
Remember back when we listen to older episodes people would call into be like
Hey can I promote my blog can I promote my new CD
I feel like this color is like really doing the archetype
Infowars collars from the
Repast
Real quick
I have a patent for a device
Temporary devices
Email server
God bless you both
What's up
Bye Felicia Collins ragged old Trump
So he's now a instead of promoting your CD or whatever you know as I can get it
Yeah
1 800 invention or whatever it is
What happened
It I mean they're both delusional like
Infowars being an outlet for your new album is
Ridiculous
But it's equally ridiculous that I have to call into Infowars in the president's going to hear about my patents going to save manual
Factoring in America
That's all I needed to hear
Sounds good another collar and it's a woman who is scared she's a little bit upset
I don't really care to get into any of the content of it but
Response is really weird
You're upset
What's a normal thing
You're an early warning system you care
So you're upset I don't give you on the same way
Airfly spring Lighting in
I just feel
Powerful
Hearing your voice concern
The men
Will respond you say that
Yeah yeah
I feel it
Oh that's really weird
That's
The phrasing on that is and yeah
I love eating the ass of scared women I'll tell you that right now it gives you power gives you so much
Yeah that's really strange
Nothing to hear
I think I understand what he's trying to say adrenaline to come to people's Aid
Whatever I wanted million-dollar in crisis if you can help them
Laq
Archetypal stories of people lifting up cars at
He's trying to say first of all
Yeah Ed second
He doesn't know how to spell
Cuz it sounds
Like I gain power from scared women
Yeah it does seem like
It does seem like he's trying to like referee
Prince's chivalrous
Bulshit
You're a woman in danger and I've become so powerful
But I'm worried about my daughter
Can't protect themselves Santa lies in putting a little box somewhere so that go
So also on this episode Alex interviews Jim hoft
From Gateway pundit but I don't care I found it incredibly boring
Alex signing off
And
He did not get to the callers he expect
Do
And this includes one of the saddest
Lamest sales pitches
You'll ever hear this side of the Mississippi
We'll come back tomorrow and I appreciate you to come on the show then
And get them
Suggest you got them
Usually the times that try men's Souls
This is Wild Planet deep space ball
A like being peace and others
But God giving us away to counter
Paul Joseph Watson infowars.com newswars.com
If you don't care those links articles who will
Who will
Wow yeah I made the sales picture of them
Alright Jimmy Carson said an end date for Heelys
Is 11 old
And you know you had a whole couple weeks of just look
Looking back at his career. Real softball interviews everybody
Everybody celebrated his career last week of over-the-top
Lashing out kind of way
Person that you eat
But
I would say not classy certainly but if you do after flameout I do definitely appreciate
The cannibalism talk I mean
When I heard that
I thought
I don't even know how to
Can't tell you how much I was laughing
While I was
This f****** guy
What it started I thought like that stupid
I've listened to Alex
Everyday for 3 years and I couldn't believe what I was hearing
I couldn't believe that someone
Hey Alex
This is too much
You are going on and on about brutally murdering your neighbors and eating them
Sake there is that it's too much.
Couldn't believe it
I think we got off the topic and came back to it and
Talked about feeding his kids it's saying it's beef just like
Ludacris
Honestly this is a little bit how I want Alex Trebek's last Jeopardy episode
I think that would be the
And now your daily double
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry the answer is what is it again
So
Schoolboy no one expected Alex to deal with the ideas of his own
Shows mortality
Gracefully
And I guess we just couldn't imagine
This would be
The vibe
Still still surprised
Spell surprise
What's next
If we're here now
Watch Wednesday's show like
Who's like one of those old relationship how do you guys stay together for so long
You know
Cuz they can still surprise me you know that we just it's a new adventure everyday
The most boring normal thing ever
Jordan but until then we the website
Shelter to find out about Seltzer's
The year of the Celtic the right we're also on
Facebook
And we are in review patreon and if you would like please donate to elope
Local charity of Utah
Indeed
I'm the author of the book of Hosea
Alex
I'm coloring with huge fan I love your work