I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Need
Knowledge fight
Acknowledge
I love you
Everybody was
WhatsApp
Start living room we got rid of the table that was there before we're able
Took up all the space
Rearranged it's like we live in a new apartment I strongly recommend rearranging your place right now
Went somewhere else at least for awhile you know what I'm going to do I'm going to say bye bright spots the same
Rearranged my apartment as well my bed to another location and I don't know why it's only a couple
Will beat away from where it was
So much less noise
I don't know how it's possible that in the same room
There's so much less noise a couple feet away sleep has been much less impacted by it's inside
Furniture moving both of our bright spots
You're you're stuck in a place
Make it feel like you're no longer stuck
I also I also decide to piggyback yours cuz I move my bed like a week ago
Only thing I had in my mind was
I had some put it in the other day
I feel like that's not good
I don't remember the brand what's whatever those
Pudding cups chocolate and vanilla
It's not moving my bed was
So Jordan today we had an interesting episode to go over about the April 29th and 30th
Anza it's so ghetto I mean it's pretty tough
Follow up
I don't know what you do is that
It's on the last episode on the 28th Alex is having a breakdown yelling about how he's ready
I need to eat his neighbors and dig the globalist out of their foxholes and eat them and so no matter what he does
No matter how crazy it is it's going
Disappointment and so I regret to inform you listeners if you're expecting more cannibalism talk
You can't find it here
And for me that emotionally disappointed me tiny bit but there is still some stuff worth discussing
As we track this dark dark time for Alex
And his his business now I'm looking forward to thinking do every time we hear and take a bite of sandwich while color
You know what that sandwich abused neighbor
The Neighbors
Business thank you to
So first
Austin
Occupied Austin
Text Peter thank you so much
Next ky11 thank you so much
Next John 6
Thank you so much and I'll probably walk
Are you done sick like around 6 next antiques with Raptors
Thank you
You are now a technocrat
Laurel thank you so much you are now a technocrat
MSI tetra
Thank you so much you and I were technocrat
We got to go
Money off that heroin
Barge
Thank you so much John L Laurel
Yes you can find in your area that's helping people and donate to them
Wonderful
You did either
So Jordan we're going to take a quick detour here to check in with the year the seltzer
Richard going strong Khan like gangbusters
This point 25
Notebook page
Bill what here's the thing I know that eventually it's going to slow down so you got to hit the ground running he's got to get as much
How much road behind you as possible
I am so
Today I got to highlight and lowlight I be honest
I've been having I found a number of varieties of a brand called Sparkling Ice at the grocery store
Hey by Maddie ice but I have to I have to report
No
No offense to Sparkling Ice they're all terrible
What baby daddy I could be there all like lacking and flavors are all just
Really got meds attracted me to them was I was looking at the flavors they had
Amanda black raspberry and blue raspberry and raspberry
As I try them in about trash
I did not see one at the store but I don't know
Swing and a miss those were 32 and 33 out of 100 respectively
So that's something
Hey man highlight but honorable the kind of mentioned is Perrier Perrier strawberry and
Orange and they're both great
Okay yeah
Both coming in at 74 equal
Cousins like they're good
They have a strong crispness that a lot of other ugly Seltzer's that I've been trying or lacking
Do you feel like 75 is a benchmark
75 with another emotionally put them at 75
They are mind-blowing is nothing like really close
I feel like that's deserving of a 74 however
Sparkling Ice
I got to go back
I'm not looking forward to it I have three more of them in the fridge three other flavors
3 degrees
StarTalk
Take selfies out the window when you're done with the day may come to look out for falling seltzer
So Jordan has been near the shelter report
Let's get down to it I got to tell you right off the bat the first half-hour of April 29th show
Is
Nothing
There is just Alex sort of normal and stuff that he says all the time
Liberals are evil global history of a liberal cities are run by demon
I found it completely usual
And it was quite a ways into the episode before I found anything
That even resembled something worth talking about
Standing that you cannot save a dental Society
You can reach out to some people trying to wake him up that's great
But you gotta move on
Peopleready
Dexter
Dust off your feet Let the dead bury the dead
Do not waste your time on them
Build up those that do care build up those that do have a chance
Love yourself
I know is a person that loves God and I know you love God as well that you really feel for people you can't wake up
Broadcasting information everywhere but just
Move on from that point
Say behind in the system is dumb system
Protect ourselves
Season of generally trying to wait. Before this got here
You just move on
Country Club
The general public figures out
The contract of God was with Roe v Wade
The judge was coming
What's the General Public
Figures out
We're in a long
Long distance
It just gets worse and worse and worse for
Many many many years out of the future
They're going to freak out of me dangerous as hell
Exploded
Percent
5%
Hell
On
Here's the beginning of the clip he's talking about like it's no longer the season for trying to wake me up
Yeah I don't understand information War where you're trying to wake up people
I guess the show is now just like okay I'm going to be talking to you while you're in your bunker
Has a really unhealthy kind of thing
If it's no longer about waking people up then
It's your preaching to the choir only
So also most sources you can find about crime rates
That you can find particularly right now
They provide caveat in these reports
Like how you can't necessarily attribute any changes and rates the immediate circumstances without further study
Any person doing that would be kind of acting
He's to leave so just off the bat Shaky Ground
That's said a March 25th story out of WGN discuss crime rates in Chicago
Down 29% and shootings were down 19%
Also later in the article that discuss up
On April 3rd the hill reported on the drop of crime in crime that's been seen in New York
The Newark police department said Thursday the crime across all five of the city's boroughs and within the transit system in public
Housing fell nearly 20%
For March 12th to 31st
And the second half of last month
Murder decrease 25% robberies fell by 10% and grand larceny dropped by 37%
There's some shoddy reporting on these statistics so you will find post on blogs talk about to jump
What they're doing is misrepresenting things
New York has seen an increase in crime when you look at
The year-to-date figures as compared to the same first-quarter numbers for 2019
That is true however it's irrelevant to discuss that when your point is trying to determine the effect of
City stay-at-home orders
Because in the. Of time since then crime has dropped drastic but you can only compare stay-at-home time with
That length of time
Basically compared to prior to
Tracing a causal link between it is is hasty
Also in that same article in the hill they just got to La crimes
Statistics homicide in California's largest city fell by almost 43% while rape drop by about 37
Percent and robbery decline by 40
18%
I don't see any evidence that there's a giant surgeon crime and even if it were
That would be a massive contradiction of one of Alex's other big narrative
For years I was his primary love has been the gun
He just one true passion
And it's an Infowars Axiom that when there are more guns around there is less crime
Because the criminals know that you have a gun and therefore that leave you alone
March 2020 was the biggest month ever for gun
The FBI Ram 3.7 million background checks which is an over 1 billion increase from March
According to USA Today fact-check this number background checks indicates an estimated 2.5 million gun purchase
Which would represent an 85.3% increase year-over-year
So there's so many more guns being sold into the hands of Americans it according to Alex this should lead directly to it
Decreasing crime
However he's invested right now and scaring his audience so he's completely ignoring the increase gun sales
Any pretends the crime is soaring
He's basically is creating his own fabricated reality for his audience to live in
It's so fake that even contradicts his own already established fantasy world
It's Wyatt
Yeah there is one thing you was right about
I thought which is at
We broke our covenant with God
When Roe v Wade happened
They ruled on it and then the next day the Ark of the Covenant which as we all know is hidden deep inside the Smithsonian just explode
That's what happened why doesn't Alex at least get interesting with a covenant with God when we ended prohibition
What is the earliest go with a different
Langevin
Generic
Cookie cutter extreme right-wing Christian
Come on man you better Alex
But you said you were going to eat people yesterday
Woodstock that's what it happened
Are not supposed to listen to band in bud
This is
In
The Bible
Woodstock 99
Everybody knows that
So Alex gets to talk about those I think it what we hear him say and what an advocate for
Is
Separatist communities
Telling people
Get yourself together you better get together with your family
Get your asses
What the pilgrims did
Europe to the new world
No it's not
And the pilgrims were kicked out
It's in far-gone
You just got to get together with your people to protect yourself
Because it's going to be absolutely
Wake them up
Yes.
I still missed it
It's amazing the three years that you can real be like
Instills Bound by a rat break
Eternally optimistic
Take that there won't be why there's some fact-checks here
One of them being with the countryside is not the new world
Those places are still under the the the laws
Worry about that s***
I feel like this is a pretty unhealthy development for Alex to be calling for people to just create their own autonomous
And
I'm definitely not what I say we allow this to happen
Open we give them Idaho North Dakota South Dakota
I want to give the Patriots Dakota Arizona Arizona it's gorgeous
Southwest is fantastic
Alright then we give the
Can we do that
Thrown at you
We're not trading region trading regions
I think it's I think
The fact that we're hearing like Alex
Discussing
The Infowars over
Start
Compound
Probably we should have seen it coming today but definitely what you would expect them to like Alex
Quote-unquote mature
But they are kind of cosplaying as zombie
Think so why not
Why not do the next step of zombie apocalypse in
Build yourself an armored redoubt to keep all the hordes of left
I think that's one piece of it and then the other piece of it too is that like you know Alex's career started
Co-opting the tragedy at Waco for his own
Sortos used
And it only kind of makes sense that inevitably once he started to get into a place where things were looking bad
He would seek to create more Waco's
That does sound exactly what how it would go
It maybe that's overly simplistic of me but it almost has a narrative
Residents of the beginning and appears to be the beginning of his amp
Yeah the story Circle
And I hope that's
The not what
Would be nice if that didn't happen
First of all Janet Reno isn't around 2
Protect us I don't know if anybody would appreciate you saying she protected us
What's going on in the world right now
Is
No it's a challenge but is your Alex what you see it as
HD culmination
Decades of his life
This is what it's all been about the whole time
And
Later
If he says something different
Don't worry about it
Age of research
Point right now
This isn't about me
Last moment
Do this
Can I get
So
Play Romeo
Microsoft Word tips
This is who I am
And this is what I stand for
What they destroy me or use me that's my body my spirit going to be gone
So perfect as of this narrative to establish when you say things that totally contradict yourself
Whatever I cut it to you or something try and save my own ass
Save my money or whatever they've got
Tubi
Oh no you know what's worse is that they download the whole Microsoft Sweden there's right
You got to get the PowerPoint but still there
There they make me say that I use PowerPoint
I think I think it's brilliant for someone who's really contradict
Type really appreciate that
If I'm ever called to answer for
My transgressions
That's
Building that allows you to like
Maintain the legend of your 20 years of service at the same time just being like got to go
So in the next clip Alex is talking about I like
I'm setting things up cuz it's over it is going down
He uses the metaphor or I guess an aphorism
Idiom that's what I was looking for
Completely wrong
Accounts with people
Shopping to say hey
Here's the news you need to know
So rearranging deck chairs on the Titanic
Is an expression that used to describe something that is pointless 100%
Talking about is like Vidal or age was like
Hey we got to rearrange these pictures on the Titanic
The Titanic sinking
Quebec Tears Don't Matter
MedExpress
He doesn't understand we got to pick up our violins and play on the Titanic until the end
Sure we do
It's as if he fixed it like the people on the Titanic had a checklist years ago I can rearrange his dick.
Or on the off-chance this boat sinks we don't want it to be in disorder Wednesday we're going to look terrible
Cameron comes down here
Tears of beterbiev
Yeah it's it's funny to me when he uses these expressions and it's just like wow that's the opposite of what that means
I do kind of feel like it's accurate just not the way he wants it
Whatever is happening
In his world is happening
There's not much you can do I don't think at this point
To write
A iceberg
Say What You Need to Say
The next clip Alex is talking about how's the world
They're happening and what's going to
Happen in the future as he foresees it we all deserve it
But if you really listen to it and you listen to a show with some regularity
I think you really can understand that he just thinks that he deserves some sort of punishment
Everybody else
We got a lot better chance of a baby
Waiting to see the universe
Here comes the knives
Look up the vacuum cleaner shut the back of head
Whatever it is remember
Babies went through this
Going to take your legs
Because we summoned this
With all the devil worship in the corruption in the abortion
God gives you what you want
Unresolved issues surrounding the fact that he was involved in
Paid for multiple abortions he was younger
I mean talk about it
A ways back and you said it was like 10
Last episode 15 or 20 even if it's
Maybe YouTube
I was knows but whatever the case is there's clearly some kind of
Unresolved psych issue there he has an intense amount of guilt surrounding that
He pretends he's forgiven himself in like God is taking care of everything but clearly not
And that is being put on everybody else
We all deserve this
It's f***** up it's just it's not appropriate
As far as narcissism goes the idea of guilt your own actions bringing death and despair across
Everybody else
Pretty sure that that
Qualify
I was just thinking that there's an alternate universe out there where Alex Jones has 15
King 220 kids just
That that fought
Really
Weirded me out for a second
Yeah I would be strange
That would be pretty strange I don't think his life would have gone the same way as a
I would I would assume that they're certain realities of that would bring into your life
Present difficulties
I don't know 15 or 20 people he's paying child support
Is there would be 50
20 board lawsuits
This show sucks
This episode is garbage
What was the first hour is
Pointless rambling nonsense
We brought about we just be talking about stuff we talked about repeatedly
I don't really have any
All that much I want to get into on this episode
And it ends with about like an hour or so with with a guest and this guest is a dick
Is it just anti-vax nonsense I talked to a guy named Dale big
Bri and we talked about him before
And I only want from this because I think it's just something
To call out
Valuable in the Ferrari
System setup
Working for somebody else
From that end and I've been involved
People support the work that I do
Bulshit and I don't really care I can't even pretend to be interested in
But
Their Dell is bragging about how he's independent
Other journalists media companies
The truth like he does
This is a fun thing to say but he's not independent not by a long shot
Wendell says that there people that's
Support his work he wants the audience to hear that is him saying that there are people who make small donations that make it possible like are those nothing
But the reality is there are two people who supported work name Bernard and Lisa cell
Score hedge-fund multi-millionaires who bankroll a lot of the anti-vax propaganda
Bernard runs the cells Foundation selz which dispenses money to coach charitable causes that he support
Through that Foundation be provides approximately 70% of 75% of the funding
For the informed consent Action Network which is an anti-vax outlet that's run by his wife Lisa cells and
Del bigtree
The sells foundation help fund the documentary vaxxed
Which is produced and co-written by Del bigtree
And focused on this flawed and discredited work of Andrew Wakefield
Without the direct funding of the cells Foundation Del bigtree be a dum dum with a Blog
He's only able to do the damage that he does because of the support of multi-millionaire benefactor
Please also smart enough to know better than to discuss that
Because it makes
Super f****** obvious what his role in the world
Three comes on Alex's show and pretends that he's is
Thankfully people support my work
Fuckyourself Del bigtree you know the problem with a lot of journalist
But you know they're working
For other people
And I just wanted to be grateful to the cells
For allowing me to work for them and say what they tell me to say
I think that's great I'm really supported by two people only and I just really want you guys to
There is no conflict of interest there at all it's probably
Play negligible to the amount that comes through those foundation and and
Interested
Just it's
Gaslight it's it's
It's abusive
To be like yeah I'm independent
No you're not
F*** off
Demeans the work of other journalists so much
You disagree
Exactly exactly
So Alex comes back on the 30th
And
I should say that this is
The day that there is another hearing
In his bankruptcy case according to documents that I found from
I'm keeping up on the case
At this hearing
Alex's ex-wife
Had filed a motion
For Alex's
Tire at state
And all of the entities that you own
To be put in the hands of a trustee
So at this point when Alex is on air
On the 30th
His lawyer
Is taken
Part in this case
Times that he's on air
There is a chance
Granted spoiler alert ultimately the court ends up deciding
That it's premature in the case get a trustee involved
But so they did
Reject that motion
But it was rejected without prejudice means I can be reintroduced
The
I don't know
If that is part of Alex's mindset
I don't know how it couldn't
Three small chance there's a small possibility
Well he's on air everything he owns
The title will be taken and given to a trustee appointed by the court
That is a nerve-racking day
Not least because he might get the call while he's on air dancers
You know there's an added element to this to that like
This is going to go on a while
This case this court proceeding
Isn't going to be resolved anytime soon
But I don't
Feel like there's any way it's not
Part of what's f****** him up
I don't know
Some people have speculated they reached out and thought that like
Yeah Rodger Stones arrest warrant
Shots are released
People worried about Zack being what Alex was kind of worried about in some sort of criminal prosecution regarding Nash
I don't think that's the case there was any kind of a charge
I don't know but I just I can't I can't get my mind around
The idea that like
The immediacy the Doom is somehow related to
Something about that I don't know
Find it
Hard to believe that
Having a Sword of Damocles literally atop your head
Wouldn't affect
Recycle Hutch
Clean Subway
And one that you refuse to talk about
You keep talking about other stuff behind the scenes going on that you can't talk about
There's one thing that I definitely know is going on behind the scenes you refuse to talk about
Seems
Like a candidate
Happened to releasing the names of those qanon
Didn't happen didn't happen how about the computer chip
What else has he got
He said he was going to sue the Associated Press
Said he's going to sue all sorts of people write didn't happen
So are we start here on the 30th and Alex's pretty extreme about what he thinks is going to happen
If you
Yeah once there's a vaccine
The General Public
Uniforms
Forcing forcing ovulation
Use a medical tyranny because they complained it's quote
This is exactly what I would do is
Oh yeah yeah
Can real
Will you just scaremongering about discussions the governors have had about in the future if we're able to ease some of the closures in
Social distancing measures
We will
Return to the containment model as it relates
The Coronavirus
This will entail an increase in the need for people to be employed in the process of contact tracing
Which is to say if they when there are cases of virus to pop up
People will be needed to investigate possible people they could have been they could have accidentally exposed to the virus
What was the job creation measure provided there's oversight
Depends on who's doing the
Sure
That's it that's a relevant question and something worth that I keep an eye on Friday
Robert wants to compare that to the red guards that's his choice but it seems a little overly dramatic
It might be it might be that possible but I would say why not
Alex gets to rambling a brings up his favorite book
And I got to say
Don't think
He knows much about his own favor Where the Red Fern Grows
I read none dare call it conspiracy
Oh yeah that's right
Born
Articles
The Rockefeller praising communism and now say tongue
I'm saying that he was going to bring communism to America
Blue is my man I very much doubt he went to a library
I further doubt that he looked up anything
And I greatly doubt that had he done either of those things that I don't think you
But he actually read those are two
Sure there's an issue
Also I should tell you that
Before
It was published in 1971 born because I think that he believes
Is it some kind of a sign of a cosmic plan
That was the year that these two really important pillars of the human resistance were both Unleashed or some s***
That's kind of my sensibilities ride to overly like dramatize this whole thing is a good meaning behind
I got I got that I got that vibe
Bruno's
No
Alex is misrepresenting what is in none dare call it conspiracy
There are references to articles about David Rockefeller trying to open up trade with the Soviet Union and China who the book
Call Zada Reds
It comes up a little bit short
Just to give you some idea of the level of s*** that's in that book hopefully we will do it
Breakdown of that book but
Here's a passage of what the author Gary Allan just decides to suggest that David Rockefeller did
Namely that he was Nikita Khrushchev
Boss
A strange event
Occurred in October of 1964
From the text
Quote David Rockefeller president of the Chase Manhattan Bank in chairman of the board of the Council on Foreign Relations
Took a vacation in the Soviet Union
This is a
Peculiar place for the world's greatest imperialist to take his vacation since much of the Communist propaganda
Deals with taking all of David's wealth away from have been Distributing it to the people
A few days after Rockefeller ended his cool to vacation in the Kremlin
Nikita Khrushchev was called recalled from a vacation at the Black Sea Resort
To learn that he had been fired strange!
As far as the world knew Khrushchev was the absolute dictator of the Soviet government and more important head of the Communist party with run
The USSR
Who has the power to fire the man who is supposedly an absolute dictator
Did David Rockefeller Journey to the Soviet Union to fire an employee
Obviously the position of Premier in the Soviet Union is a figurehead with a true power residing somewhere else
Perhaps
In New York
Really don't feel like that's enough evidence to
Approval
I think there's a lot of insinuation and maybe even circumstantial evidence that
Doesn't prove
Yeah
In reality Leonid Brezhnev had been trying to remove kruschev from Power since at least March
He organized the conspiracy what you put in place in October
Put into action in October vacation after which Brezhnev roast
Staying so until his death in 1982
David Rockefeller had gone to Moscow and he did me with Khrushchev in July
1964 but there's absolutely zero evidence
It is isn't it anything to do with khrushchev's removal
From Power passed people like Gary Allan to speculating that it was related
It wasn't a vacation
I've Gary Allan suggest
And it didn't happen in October
Also as Gary says
He's just wrong
Because he's not basing this on fact
Communist conspiracy lore
Suffice it to say that there's been a lot of information that's come out about this meeting between khrushchev's and David Rockefeller over the
Years has anything to do with khrushchev's Astor is completely unsupported by the historical record
But it doesn't matter
Someone like Gary Allan
His book is meant to be persuasive so you can see how he Peppers his argument with leading questions that are meant to make the reader feel like bathe
Themselves are putting the pieces together when in reality they're being fed a load of b*******
!
It's the same thing that makes qanon so seductive for people
It gives them a propaganda narrative but simultaneously allows them to pretend that they're actually the investigators
Pieces together
This is why this book was so damaging to the mind of a twelve-year-old Alex Jones
It's written intentionally to be read by people with less than Advanced reading skills and with a style that's so suggestive and
Repetitive drives points into impressionable Minds while maintaining an illusion that the suggestive
Mind suggestible mine
Is actually doing some kind of work to arrive at what is a predetermined conclusion
It's a book that
Keeps saying look at how smart you are a hundred percent hundred percent
I didn't do it I just gave you certain
Facts and you're the one who drew the
Conclusions problem all I said was
How strange! Without a? And it's it also like distilled
Those things down into like
Easily like
Like overly repeated little sound bites more less in the text
Do like make you remember that boy
And
We do need to do that episode
But it won't be one episode that's the problem
One thing that's holding me back from it is like
How long it would be
Is lockdown man we could do it
Here's the thing that bothers me
About that is that it takes agency away from the Russians
To let space
Know how to cool the f*** out of s***
The past 150 years there have been like 42
They know how to cool man
Rockefeller fire crew shows
All this nonsense by that blew out his mind when he was young cuz he didn't go and look
Daddy finger
Wealth Gap
Alex on the last episode on April 29th
Alex is talking about how like what's going on now is
The culmination of like all of his career
His career
All of human history
Besides interest exercises to Bible
Robin to these people
Spider species history
Will be
So what
It comes down to whether or not Alex lives or dies
Is there something that needs
To be done and if it's not done this thing
Then hooray
What is a down that f****** road for the last time
Who's roads with
Is it destroying the UN
He fails on a lot of specific
Check levels you know like what is it
To be done
Well it's destroy the globalist what do you mean
Here's my quest
If his idea of what we should do is Retreat into these communes
I mean I'm sorry
Not copying whatever they re don't call it a cult
Then
How is it that
He would
Not survive
Do you know what I'm saying like so
His whole idea is for him to live
As locked
Is possible
Yeah pirate
At the same time he saying that if he doesn't die
Then Humanity will have lost
You have a good point
I think your addresses
I can't I don't have an answer
No I don't know
So I bet I think that's the way he wants this to feel like
Simultaneously and ultimate fight for the stake of human existence in all of human history
The future of the species and also
Yeah I am the butt of the spear
I'm just a radio host man
I think he wants to have it both ways like it's more fun to talk about the fight for human
Future or whatever
But it's also not real
People come up to Alex people do not come up to Alex
Dammit he says this all the time it's
Constant it almost every single episode should also say I'm going to give Alex credit
Neither of these episodes does he storm off air
I was wondering that very question I was wondering
You know what
Steep raised
This guy stayed on air
I've got to convince that one of the things that you weren't covering on the 29th cuz we've dealt with it so much is that a storm.
No no I do think on the 30th he played a special report cuz he was taking phone call or something
But I don't
There's no infantry like
Hey Alex I got good news you get to keep your money for another couple of weeks
Sadly I'm not I'm not deposited but it doesn't storm off or anyting but
Or almost every single episode he talks about how people come up to him and they ask
How you handling things are you doing things are so top how do you handling things and what he tells them
You loves it
Every single almost every single episode he says
Alex
How you doing buddy
Disagree that I strongly
Doxepin
Infowars is dying
Last days America
The real world
This is what we have become
Goodbye
So yeah we're on our last days but it's America's last days because of
The same
Or something
So Alex gets to know talk about how much
So much Knew Too Much for him to cover some would say that there is but I will
I tip my hat to Alex
Yeah it does a really good job of explaining
The level of preparation he's done for this episode
Why
Emblematic
Conservatively
Trump
Wwhl
Is a
Only positive thing but it means so much and is
What about you
So
Iskandar over some of these articles any red
The couple of them
80 and over half of the man
Really came close to reading at that time to prepare I love it when he says like these articles in front of me these
Stacks of paper are props props
Yeah
I'm going to
None of these because I don't remember much of what they said but I don't remember their headlines and their emblematic
Really gild the Lily on just not saying headlights
Looked at a few memes
I prefer articles with
Carpe donktum sent me something
There was a guy he was walking with his girlfriend a girlfriend that had a quote that was like
Dogs and then he had a thing there was like me and then he's looking at back at the girlfriend and it said money
And that way
I will say that I do believe that Alex could talk for 10 hours about temperature
Drum set
About you is wrong I think you'd get very tired in the middle but I do think
You can probably do it if he had to
That's this this is the one thing I think
I bet if we is that
If there was going to be a 25th amendment kind of thing like today he's coming out and saying that they created it in the Wuhan
I did not see this
He insinuated it strongly didn't come out and say that he is saying that it came
From the Wuhan laboratory back
You could have told me like
Something like
Jobsite if there's a chance
That it turns you into a vampire
I haven't heard that
But I'm also a
You're making that up
I can't I can't tell with real or fake anymore without you can tell me almost anything
Give me a sec I got to look at my suggestions of the lab that's that's disheartening
The one thing we're eventually the 25th amendment is going to come into play where it's like okay
We're not going to start a war with f****** China over your b*******
I think it I think it's like once you get to the point where it's like a cause for war you kind of
Cuz it's made up now can't let things escalate to that level
You can
Because people are f******
Stupid
I worry
So Alex is thrilled
That's a trump is pointing the finger towards China and the WHL
Interesting the next thing that I would says about some of the Trump is doing
Somebody should be very again
Kind of glasses over it
Checking into this
A lot of time
That's not something you admit
This is a nightmare right here
Speed
Coronavirus vaccine
Bella Monica
The coronavirus coming rub patented
Not ready to put in the
Solution
And Trump is going to roll it out
Belmont engagement whole thing I know the next piece of it
Trump accelerating the vaccine
This is a nightmare but I know why Trump's doing
Never explains why doesn't get into that story at all
Just pivots and moves towards talking about the nonsense about the chicken vaccine
The patent for
But he's insisting is this
Chimera virus on Trump right now
Also
Think that Alex must
Think that a vaccine is just to take a virus put it into black rubbing alcohol
Good
So many people think that
So many people think that seems to be all video
All of the chemicals that go into a vaccine to these people are like the dead virus whatever that mean
Aliens and then just
Alexapure water filter is the filtered water and davirus you're good
That's why someone like Mike Adam skin like
Put out the Ebola cure that he did
Facebook just cuz you think it's dead Ebola right yeah you can hang out cohol about take a little alcohol in a bowl
Whiskey on their call Dakota cocktail
Mysterious mad anger doesn't transfer over to Trump reset is accelerating
Vaccine program but let's not worry about it cuz he understands
Explain and I don't understand what
Anyway Alex is mad at Bill Gates but
He is not
Going to hurt.
You got understand that he's not going to
Isn't he going to eat it
Later okay
Ncic evil thing you're going to go ahead
About to get hurt really bad if I want to eat
Stockholm Syndrome
Tummy bug
Icopy
Greenbelt
Running to people
Foot bypass
Digby running with mask on
Jog
What is a running with Infowars
The wicked flee when
Live
Wobbling
Going along got them ahead but that
Training
Here we go
Add 100000 sub tonight to run too many on the ranch
But I mean
Adelman
The Story Goes On while and it just has to do with that you like these cows and
Tell Kara.
More interested in the idea that his Grandpa took a government subsidy
He glossed over again as well
You know what I am starting to think that if they do develop a vaccine buy stockings
I think he might
Yeah I don't know you don't need to be mad at these people on the trail
Slip device
I don't know what that means
He sees people wearing masks and he thinks that their virtue signaling because
The premise is you wear these masks out of a courtesy for everyone else in public right
Virtue signaling cuz you are the math that's you saying you care more than Alex
Who doesn't wear the
It's like that is
Good
Well that would be like that would be like him saying when you're driving right is virtue signaling to look both ways at an inter
Section you act like you're better than me because you pull it up. It is
Stop sign
Weird it's very weird you're not understanding that is important cuz you could get hurt but as we all know
You don't need to wear a mask while jogging then
Jogging people
Can't transfer viruses
That is the one thing that the coronavirus cannot deal with unpleasant
To jog with mask on
But I don't know
I don't know people make their own choices I don't know anyway Alex gets back to this idea to Bill Gates went on TV and said the
The 700,000 people will be hurt by the vaccine
The number to Bill Gates
Randomly picked out of the air to discuss the ideas of the difficulty of scaling of vaccine
Two large
Population
Trying to cope with the idea that there may be some side effects to an effective medication
And how do you
How do you respond to that challenge
Alex has taken that to be Bill Gates threatening to hurt 700,000 people
Is dumb brain
Understand things
So you talked about that a little bit then this gets way off track
And
I think might end in
Something I've never heard Alex say but I think might be the root of some of his like
Deep-seated chauvinism
Like is
He's like yeah
Feeling of like women or something other than men when is Mom picked them off the the knee
Psychologically that might play a role in this is like a belief that he has that I've never heard that lie
Like what I thought like
I mean it's not as fun as eating people but it's as messed up
Oh yeah 700,000 people we get everybody this vaccine
Problem
Play down everything
Oh don't worry they're going to pass laws you can kill that autistic son
It is the Sun
New your first more
Some girls with genetic studies get past the information
Men in the first generation are pack
Donpa genetic memory
What
Forgiven
I'm insane
Play endolphin Active Duffy's Whatta Man
Women now
Worship
Capitola Beach
This is f***** up
Apparently Alex's entire conception about race memory
And like you're at you are your ancestors
It did very
Very rare cases women did they become Queen
Study that says women some women Simply Clean
They turn out to be Queen
But otherwise it's the first born son killed
Suncommunity killed the genetic memory
I don't think that was what was going on in that story
Maybe that's what he was thinking
Yeah
Does he have brothers
I know he has a adopted sister
I would see if he has venetic members that I don't I think Alex has another sister
I've always kept
So much of a hands-off thing with his personal life
I tried probably know a lot about his family members but for the most part it doesn't
Interest me at all
And outside people like Buckley
Was on out to show a bit of like what I would look
He's like a DJ and s*** right I don't know his family
Like size or
He talks about his adopted sister a lot when he wants to pee or not racist
I've heard him talk about another sister so I think he's the only
Mail song
Was he who now I'm now I'm trying to remember because I think the story remember the story where he's under the house
Sprayed with all the chemicals we got one of those people is one of his brothers
So is cousins don't have any genetic map
At least
I would like it written down I would
Cuz guess what
It's not in the Buy
Science literature
Alex Isley
Talks about it it sounds like something he firmly believe that and thinks it's almost
Like
Pointless for him to say cuz it's so obvious
Talk about these sorts of ideas a lot I've never heard him say that it doesn't apply to
Only the first born son
That's f***** up that's
Crazy
So what happened what happens whenever a father doesn't have any sons the whole line lose their
Memories
That's crazy
This is this is also kind of explanatory power about Alex's of
Persian to women
Sucks because it's
Show me the bad reason to be leaders
How could they be leaders they don't have
It's only it's almost immediately
Women are second-class citizen no it's not even almost it is immediately women are automatically second-class citizens about
Unless they're Queens you have taken over enough for you to respect
Right so Beyonce
She's got well for Alex no
Millie Weaver
Katie Hopkins Lauren Southern for a while
For a bit
Man maybe
She didn't defend her Hitler comment probably lost erase memories. Whatever
Weird things
Look so it doesn't slip Alex yells a little bit about how you can't sell out but you just can't do it
I don't like
The store for me
To defeat these people
Commitment
Species going on for
So honored to be your happy
Or something you gave up
What you do take me for what I do
Computer chip
Betray
Brody
War
It's cuz I'm alive
Day I die my soul.
Will not be damned to hell I will get away from me
Planet
There's a pretty part about it
How to control the universe
What I get
Call the other people that are good
Imagine how good that's going to be
My grandparents
U r g
The level above human understanding
Interface with them
That is what this is all about ladies until when is the next level
Why you cannot
Now in fear
They are
Start of the shower I told you that
Saturn
You did by saying obvious everything is but he kind of
Talking about how he's going to die and meet his grandparents
Tax subsidies to not raise cattle
The Coalition Builder
I don't think Alex is really 101
I just don't think he's willing to really meet people on there
No no boy
Yeah my reward I don't have to hang out with people who disagree with me
This is unhinged
It's boring though yeah
It's it it's weird like our last episode
Set back by like
Where's
In the same way I take some really hot thing for me to enjoy spiced because I've had so much spice so much
In my life
Him talking about how he's going to die and meet his grandparents and all this stuff it in like
Relish the torturing cuz I can't sell out
Whatever Alex
He thinks he's a journalist show
That's always difficult to remember
Really take the time to like really telescope out like really zoom out
Recognize
And I mean I think I think we did recent episode it bears
Bring up
Pretty regularly like imagine the sort of behavior from literally anybody else
Think about how f******
Farcical it is
Bananas
I also I think we can only really get into his bizarre cosmology now whenever he should face just because of the four way
To learn things
Where it's like
You're going to have to bring some kind of even more esoteric nonsense than just that
I I mean
Noteworthy to say that the first born son gets
Genetic memory but if he was drunk
Man we get some real good s*** out of that he's been drunk he hasn't specified the firstborn something right
That's what I'm saying he's got to be drunk to now
Oh man don't drive home
Don't drive home
The trying to get you
So Alex talks about things you can't talk about
Man
I'm broke
John today
But
You judge a man by his enemies
Play these criminals
Shut their mouths off things they did or just
High-and-mighty people at the Clinton foundation and the Soros group
Don't know people are like him stuff and given us documents
Don't know that when they really make moves like that
Don't
World
Pissed
Run the lockdown
Point
You're going to have everyone turn against you
You don't have your robots enforce yet
Yet
Make sense
You got the jump on you
Truly amazing is God is in charge
Got to give it all the God I know you got to give it all to God I don't want any cryptic here
Let me let me let me do that
Last night in this morning
Getting racist broadcast
On
Believably insane
Agreed
Is the head
The world food programme
Any says 130-plus million people are set
Farm desk
So I don't know anything about those imaginary Soros documents Alex's claim people are leaking
Usually is not even close to a breaking story
And he doesn't have any updates on it any other information to bring the tables
Like a breaking development
Whatever is going on behind the scene I can't get away from the awareness that this day
Behind the scenes
He knows that his
Lawyer is
In court
For a bankruptcy hearing
Like I can't I can't disassociate the two things
Big developments behind the scene
Bring us to Soros documents or shut up
Your argument
Is that
The globalists have one
Completely
Yes but they also
Sprung this too soon because they don't have their robots in place
So the globalists are also stupid
Play one and they still beat you
Yeah they won without their plan I guess
Yeah that sounds about right
Oh man Alex you suck it
Your job if your job was to win
They give you an old goal
They gave you an own-goal and you still on
Bossman Alex
That's Tuff
So Alex
Talking about like how he has over
He's like really
McCobb
Weird things he talks about on his show like maybe
Eating people
Yeah
Maybe some stuff like that but like
He's not responsible for any of that stuff all these sick fantasies and all these weird things that he talks about
He didn't come up with any of that
Protein powder
Babies and
Death and destruction and just
Play look at me and say
This guy says were bad
We just want to social distance to save human life
The leader of your group Bill Gates
Depopulate the planet and kill all the old people
Particle son
Iran's off of the family inheritance his Dad gives it to him he comes back a decade later
I got part of parents in the first-borns running everything great
He comes in
It says why are you throwing a party
Calf
Brother when he's a loser
Oregon 10 years around
What
We got to make him feel good
What he's done what
Might be
That's not the reading I got it from him
The mainstream reading that is
Prodigal son story is about placating and make it the Prodigal Son fuel cool
I thought it was about how like
My son who was dead is alive again we celebrate this
Kind of about the
Durability undying misses love and connection
I don't know
I mean basically the older brother is a fool
In the story because he doesn't
Supposed to be the point as far as
Every reading I've ever had it
Here's where you're wrong
It's about what is not in the Bible
You missed was the sudden decided that the father had was like don't worry about it I love you
So much more than this
Assholes we're just
Look we're just going to have a party and then he'll work in the Stables all over against back in talking if you have this
Exactly is a mob story
Okay I don't interesting to me about Alex
He's told the story of The Prodigal Son a number of times that sometimes he's close and sometimes he is
I feel like this one is pretty far off are you off
Here's my reading of the prodigals
Love isn't real
And your parents are always lied to his my reading of the Prodigal Son
Duchene to come back
Get a great life
He had a great life out there outside of the wing of his parents who you moving back in with your parents are you Michael
Rotondo
Vicky has a complicated
Perhaps
If it's nightclub Alex talks about
His own understanding of what he
He does and what his place is in terms of the greater picture
Of the world and I think it's fairly
It's accurate it's kind of revealing that he has
The best
Doesn't have a way to go into the general
He does who's the president
Used to quote radicalize the military the police
The General Public
Completely outlandish
Publix
Power
Always 100,000 people a million whatever
All this
Am I inside their heads lowered simpatico
So he's not right about any of the contents of that but I do think I mean he's fairly accurately diagnosed
His position and that is to radicalize enough people
To give cover for some sort of a right-wing leader
To enact authoritarian moves
Like that is basically the the function
And I think he on some level whether or not he's fully cognizant of it that's what he's
Express
Like he's pink
Well you presenting that he thinks the things that he saying are true
And so there's some sort of a noble
But all in all it really is is
Create enough confusion and enough
Fundamental distrust of reality that someone
Can exploit that
To consolidate power
That's the function that Alex is serving
My job is to create
A right-wing Christian Isis so our dear leader can exterminate
Play people who disagree with me
Cool
More or less
In his next clip Alex plays some theme music that I haven't heard
On his show maybe I kind of enjoy. The Highwaymen
But it is country
Okay and it leaves Alex to have a little bit of a wistful moment
Whoever on that range up in the sky
I don't hear the cry
That's almost listen to it
Backboard somewhere
Just listen to music like that then f****** go
Down here
Cuz I did a lot of preparation for the show
Already proved you then
Look at all this nose
And there's just an apocalyptic
At this point in the show Alex I don't know if you can tell just from through the pace of his speech but he's taken a real likes
Assertive
Yeah there's a down note
Play it's a it's a it's a notable
Dog starts talking about how we need to do something
What do we need
Well it's interesting because he doesn't actually say what we need to do but something needs to be done
Is it right-wing gun nuts
Storming believe it talk about the idea of gauges in
A bit of stochastic terrorism
Inspiring people to extreme acts while haven't plausible deniability in his language
When I hear this clip
I can't escape that
Feeling
Very strongly being in my mind
I'm saying this
Call TR scared
Never had a clear Target
What do we do
Getting up here and always telling you what's going on what's Happening
Ninety-nine percent of the time
Eat people
Naughty people
You got to do it
Somebody open and do it
Real quick don't do heart surgery after just reading a manual on heart surgery need to give
This sort of public service announcement
The heart stop
Cesarean they did
Po-boy
Where the mother died
Where the term cesarean formisano Cleopatra weed-out
Marc Anthony
The baby wouldn't come out
And I done the surgery before but it wasn't cesarean visit was experimental in
What
You got to do it
I can't take your money
You got to try
I don't know what
He's talking about
Explain when he comes back from break
I don't know what the Cesarean metaphor is about
I don't know what the like
The thing that troubles me is the language that surrounds it of you we don't want to do it
But you got to do it or full
Cuz it's up to some of the things we talked about not wanting to do all the time
Even the examples he gives all involve knives and cutting people open
Sure
Implicitly violin
We don't have a manager we just write Immanuel we need to cut a guy there
That's Alex's believer
That's all I'm saying
Like maybe we don't skip to the
February
Okay I but you don't have any
I just opened this team can I have the lid
Good novice clean clean
Let's do it I put a little fire on it in scalp
Oh yeah those things are Sharp
DIY surgery manual
Yeah that really troubles me
I think that the vibe that he's putting out is very much something that could be misinterpreted
Goodbye more unhinged elements within his audience
To be very clear tacit support
Right-wing Terror basically well I mean based on
Polling information it's like what
Less than 10% of the country people adults think that
We should reopen the country like
It is so minuscule that the only reason that these people are pushing it so hard has to
To be so that incredibly small minority finds a way to
The influence
The 90% of us that think they're insane
And the only way that 5% is going to do that is with
Peaceful coexistence
Probably not doubt it
So in the next clip Alex is talking about one of his favorite things and that's quotes and this one might be real but
It also might not become clear children
States of America
American Taxi
Bulshit
If there's anything you represent it's a childish drunk American
But you already broke the Covenant in the enrollment wait so
God doesn't even love America God loves drunks children Americans
And I am a child of drug America
Trifecta
So there's some dispute whether or not on Bismarck actually said that line or if it's Miss attributed to him
There's a decent chance he did say it either way even if he did it's a paraphrasing of along pre-existing French
Proverbs
Also the original meaning of that thing is
Not a compliment like that God loves drunks children in the US more than God loves others God looks
After the US in the same way God looks after drunks and children because they can't look after themselves
Yeah it's yeah it's 100%.
It's you have the ability to defend yourself of a
Drunker a child and the most
Abnormal lock the most American thing you can do is take that as a compliment
Exit you should be draped in an American flag while shooting a stranger
Exactly what I wanted to hear
What others going through these two episodes I found myself profoundly bored and there wasn't a lot of things to latch onto
Here on the middle of the April 30th episode
I found something that it showed
Promise
And that is italics decides to get down to business
And talk about this conspiracy
That he is against
And
Boy
If you want a history lesson
Recommend
You go to school
If you don't want a history lesson
Listen all right
Let me just try to quantify this in a scientific way as best I can
The decision was made
Okay alright
Appalachia order
Autocracy
Sure
That would keep me from knowledge and empower the establishment
That sounds right
From that has been an extension 2300
F******
Excited
We are going to
To get him really trying
To break things down alright this is what happened in Greece now
Flash Forward 20 years
Ostracized some leader
Excited I thought that was going to happen share
No
Alex makes a gigantic leave immediately Everest
Bigstar 2,300 years ago
And yesterday
2300 years ago in Greece it started a sort of autocracy. Keeping information
Meatballs
I swear I didn't cut out 15 minutes where he explains things
It jumps to the Black Plague
40% of population
The old corrupt establishments get devastated
Christian's will Christians are able to get ahold
Private businesses are
And the really
The Gutenberg Press is
So it's a massive jump from 2300 years ago to the time bubonic plague
Through those hundreds of years
So after yada yada in history
Who started the first public businesses
Private business
Excuse me
I don't know about this
Given that's a pretty well understood part of history that the Dutch
East India Company was the first company to offer stocks
I wasn't talking specifically so I don't know what
Actually meaning by this but I don't think you should be thrilled about the East India Company based on literally all of his pretend beliefs
Furthermore
Christians at the time
Very against the Gutenberg Press
To the point where they burned a lot of them down that's interesting too
Also the Black Death didn't happen 500 years ago it took place between 1346 and 1353
A few weeks ago press was invented in
50 it should be noted that the Chinese have developed movable type printing as far back as 917 ever heard
1200 books
Very common items Society
Alex's stories by human progress in this lineage of Destiny and all of this makes sense if you pretend that Nan
European history doesn't matter or it didn't happen
Alex talks about the human Journey he specifically excluding all other cultures Journeys in history
Because ultimately he doesn't see them part of his part of the human story
It's really pretty sad and at the end of the day represents a very explicit undercutting of his pretend Quest
To bring Humanity to the next level
He'd sooner call for the end of the world that accept non-european cultural Primacy in it
It's clear when you hear these things I thought was really interesting about these two days
Is this sort of thing
Really highlight
This part is like the non-european elements of History don't matter they don't
It might as well not be a part of our story
Exclusionary to pretty much every other culture and that means that you are not
Humanity you're interested in
Then you have him
The reveal of the firstborn male child is the one who gets the race memory
Excluded
Pretty much all of women
There is that yeah
Exclusionary even Within These two days that you've whittled it down to exactly what we know Alex is
Is always cared about
What does
Yeah yeah
Oh man
I think it's fun that he even skipped over in this globalist agenda
Autocracy was beginning
You skipped over the part where Jesus showed up
Not interest not involved in the in the blue dock receive the good Christians didn't even bother with the Jesus history
Very boring
There was there was Grease there was the Black Plague
And then there was a few days ago
Great events of History absolute
The Gutenberg Press happened
And now
I guess the bad guys they want
The Gutenberg Press or something
The Gutenberg Press
Is
Here we go
Empowering for
But you're seeing the authoritarian
Take control of that now
The Gutenberg Press
I mean I think the Gutenberg Press absolutely change
There's no doubt
Without question
Torn would not have been circulated as far as his wide
If there wasn't
The Gutenberg Press
Yes that's the number one thing I can think of the Congressional Record
Everyday by movable print it was it is it is interesting that the Bible and p******
Both went along the same network
Do today Gutenberg Press it had to be underground because the Catholics wanted to destroy all of it
What what Alex is trying to get at I mean I understand what he's trying to express and that is that like the legacy of the
Gutenberg Press is the availability of information because he's kicked off Facebook somehow now
I don't understand it as like a real thing
I don't know I think this is in the same way that his entire understanding of history is
Depressingly eurocentric
Is is understanding of the
The present is seltzer
I just don't have time for it
Also
That's about it
In terms of his lesson of History like it's really like
I got so excited when he said like 23 years ago this all started
2200 Peloponnesian War
And that was to defeat the plutocracy because the acid
And what would he loved more than this
It's right Battle of Thermopylae was false flag
Do you know that I did not know that
Globalist
Mister
Please he was also a globalist of course
Alright babe alright we did it
So Alex
Like sort of reason to exist right now is to train and all of the
Like business closures and all that stuff
Explain
You said that you should do that for a selfish r
I want to be very very careful here with everybody
We do not stand up
Hundreds of millions of people that will starve to death
In the next
Year 22 years
Lockdown
What's happened
Cloudy design collapse of civilization
Industrial world
And and the Rockefellers and Bill Melinda Gates administer plan
From a selfish person
Active
You will be reduced from your hoity-toity Rich Western Society to third world
That's all
Argument
Already have
It is said his position Justice
Ludacris nonsensical
It's
I think it's just
It's just so disappointing
It's so disappointing because I really want him to flame out with more eat people
He's not flaming out he's he
Flickered violently and now he's going to slowly remind can I tell you what my thought was after that episode
Reflecting on it
Publicity stunt
I think that was his I think he was hoping that you get a lot of coverage if you really like
Alex Jones to Sadie's going to eat people
I think that that might have been somewhat calculator.
Just the way I mean who knows
The reality is that he could be such like
Rapid Cycling kind of
Outburst
Could come suit like
Randomly
The most boring piece of s*** in the world
Cory could be like an intentional decision of like
I need to try and get pressed
What can I
Do all rant about eating
People
And on that level that is the case if it was like some sort of a decision
I'm super glad that I haven't seen a lot of people
Talking about it outside of our show I don't think I've heard
Hide nor hair from any media Outlets about how Alex entire sect
Take me to bat eating his neighbors
But I think that's great he does stuff like that
Do things that benefits him is the Free Press he gets out of it
And like we can talk about it and laugh
Yeah it is in a way that is not helpful to him
And
I am gone glad I'm glad I'm glad to see I'm glad to see people not taking that troll bait
It does very much seem like everybody else but us has just moved on from
Completely we've got
We've got Ben Shapiro in those dumb motherfukers
To deal with
Alex's
To enjoy
Perhaps
At the same time I do like that we're getting the Free Press out of his lunacy now instead of him
If there is a C+
Continue
Just do this and whoever wants to listen to it a listen to it
I look forward to being a footnote and I look forward to somebody being like and then one time there was those guys
That would be good
Radio broadcasters of like a thousand years from now
They'll be talking about
3300 years ago in Greece that started a plutocracy
Send
1500 years ago
The bubonic plague
Something something zuberg crash
In 2020
These guys talked about Alex Jones for no reason
I would love to be the center of these two guys were the true masters of the world face I would enjoy that
I want to be high really don't I don't think I could handle that kind of like a negative attention
Oh yeah
I can't hear but I can't cuz I'll be back
So Alex talks about one of the things that's really difficult is like
In order to really discuss everything that I would says
Like in a clip like this you have to be like okay well let's break down all of the inaccuracies that you believe about
Bill Gates wanting
Depopulate the world and all that
And I choose to
Ignore that cuz we've talked about it in the past
Image clip Alex just says that he wants Bill Gates to stab himself in the Ion Television
Really you like star will kids to death and what was too many
Can you dye fur
It's up on TV and he takes up
I'll say well I got respect to that guy
YouTube
My point is
You want us to die
What you don't
Little pink shirt you look on flip diving
Either one
Zuckerberg
You're not
A pink shirt
Show that picture of your ass forgot bag
I think there's just a hostility on Alex's part of anybody who is mail
Receives as feminine
I think it bothers me so much about that is
I agree with the sentiment
And he is working so hard to make it
The opposite you mean well I mean functionally okay the rich are not going to suffer from
Seabreeze opening
Sing the country
Everybody who is
Is going back to work
Work is going to suffer
So if you want to say you know like
F*** you you want to go back to work work on the floor you billionaire a******
I get that
But then he's also saying we should reopen the economy
In order for them to kill us
The same way I want Bill Gates to sell stavis
And I speaking
Do you understand like although I don't think the reality I don't understand
Beef stew what you think Alex's is saying I'm not person
Incorrectly
Cuz what I understand him to say is that
He wants to
Control the population or Bill Gates wants to control the population by killing humans
And Alex would respect him if he said there's too many humans that help
Because he's too many human right right so far so good
So functionally what he's saying is if the rich
Want to Bill Gates in the rich want to depopulate the
Start with
Bright
So I don't see okay I see what you're saying
Back to work yourself
But I still think that there's something there in that
He's doing the opposite of what he
He's stating he wants to happen
Fair enough
The problem that I had is you were saying it sounded like what you were saying that you supported the idea Bill Gates dabbing or something
I'm too far gone to give a s*** about what Bill Gates
If he stabbed himself in the eye
Great
I would stop just short of that but
But if you did it I'm not I'm not here to go to bed for Bill Gates say that everything he's done has been the past or the
Is he could with the means that he has
But I do think that the way that Alex Paints the portrait is is
Deeply unfair
Agreed agreed
When you have people
Think about population issues around the world
Aren't talking about
Cohen
People they aren't talking about
Depopulating the world they're talkin about
Offering birth control options
People in the developing world
Ways to make
The people who are alive live Better Lives
And the Next Generation do better
The generation that is
Is here now
Alex is turning that into a genocide
Mission that they're on
And it's just not
It's just not fair so when he says like you wanted you want everyone to kill yourself
You're welcome your premise is wrong because your premise is wrong
I mean functionally what they're saying with
Providing
Population quote
Control is
Free women
Yeah population
That well.
That's kind of where I'm at
Because that's
That's what it really is birth control all of those things are giving women
Options for living
In a way that is not essentially subservient
The guy who has Ray Smith
Or whatever you want to call
And that is the thing that terrifies these people
It does seem that way women have
Freedom of choice
And just Freedom at all
Is there fun
Alex
I think he says something and then immediately thinks
It was at
Like you think I asked
Shouldn't said that
Redline
Saying crazy
Right here where the middle of a very long pause
Right after he says everyone's pensions are going I'm not trying to scare you
That makes me think that there's maybe a voice in his ear that sang like what you talkin about or he's getting up
Date of some sort
But there's just some really long pause after he says that and then he doesn't really follow through with the thought
Because I think you have bought is the fear of this virus
So much
Launch do whatever
They want
Duty to do Duty
David in tabletop exercises admitted at all
Can we buy into a go long with it we deserve it
Guy though
Stockholm Europe
People doing all this to know that
The tens of millions are starving to death it's your fault
Bill Gates
It's your fault
Youtube CEO
Is your fault Sundar pichai
Google
Your fault Democratic Party
Along with it
Lazy this delivery is
Not about
Fault
When discussing the idea that people are
Struggling
Developing world not important right now if you care about the issues
Right now to be like a Sundar pichai this is on you
It's not my fault why would it ever be Alex's fault
Why would it ever be
The only reason he brings that stuff up is because he is singularly focused
On finding ways to
Not
Fuel to blame
That's unhealthy that's a compulsion that he has you so afraid of taking blame
It's a fundamental
So part of
Any kind of
Just relationship therapy of just like if you fixate on
Fault blame
You're never going to be able to move forward
Because because resolving the blame game means there's a winner and a loser rated Martin
That doesn't solve the problem
Figuring out who's to blame doesn't solve the problem
The problem still exists even do you have like a finger to point
I don't care I it is absolutely Bill Gates
Republican party phone it's absolutely all these people's fault
Who gives a s*** now right let's do something about it and until we
Do something about it I don't give a s*** some things that are terrible right now maybe the fault
People who are no longer alive
Yeah I also believe the thought of systems that have been built over time
That are
Cancerous
And
Not good
Spending all day
Trying to like
Parse out the ways that you're not responsible for it
Is a way to never deal with the actual issues
Invalid
Wants to invest in that he wants to play that game
I think that's right in line with his entire career and I applaud him for staying up
Of course
But I don't think that it gets anywhere
But it's so consistent with him
And it's less
Important icing
To him
To say who is to blame
It's more important to be like I am not
Mmm that that also is
Is just
I mean
His conscience is so guilty
He spends most of his time trying to convince himself that he's
Like it is it is a
Constant war in his brain I imagine Jeff just like
He's got those voluntary like oh s*** I am part of the I'm part of this problem and then he has to be like
No no no it's Bill Gates
And my conscience is convincing himself
Just talking to a mirror
So in the sex club Alex talks about how like
He might have been wrong about this whole coronavirus thing
Maybe Trump was right all
Call Mom
You know I was the guy
Play sigala twin hay
This is a big thing in China they're going to use this to shut things down
Democrats shut things down
Going along with some other he's got at least say he's worried
Emanuel Rahm
President Trump's wife
That sucks
Show me a hero.
BC the trap now
Never end
News
Are you go get sun
Awesome die
David
Beasley
The world health food program
He's up there
They're collecting money for the UN do never deliver
QPR stubs with a
Jolie
Oh here the laughing
Is your bag of rice.
Baby
When they engineered the whole thing and admit they want depopulation
Did they say that person is subhuman
So this is the kind of mindset that allows Alex to pretend that he cares about people and also support people like
Call Juan eliminate all foreign aid
He's just convinced himself that the UN doesn't do all these
These things that he doesn't see
And therefore it's not happening
It's very solipsistic and it's very it's very much like a I only see the pr thing
And therefore those are the only things that are going on
And to think that I want to stress really strongly is that this is
A representation
The privilege
And what
The Privileges is
You know things are bad in the world in a lot of ways and there's things that we
Should do more for those things that we need to do better about
We are so incredibly privileged
That there is an International Community
Does
Help you
Yes we are privileged
With not
Seeing
The kind of death
That we would see if those
Aide program
And
Alex
I don't know how else to say this then
Pray that he never gets
To learn exactly how wrong you
Because it would come along with so much
Horror for people like
If he ever got his way
That he imagines the all this Aid money goes away all of these programs dry up
Because all they do is PR stunts and siphon off money and all this
I pray that he never gets
What he desires
Because if he does
The amount of human suffering that would be exposed
Is
It's almost unthinkable
No I mean
Look at
He's getting a taste of what it is he wants right now and
Also I find it so funny for him to start it for him to say he's not a Stockholm Syndrome guy
And then
F****** he's been abused by Trump
Over and over and over
And he's literally like
I love him for the
I've ever look
I'm wrong
I'm wrong and he's right
Sure
He's made me give up literally every position that I've ever hold accelerating the vaccine program
I'll let him do anything he wants
That's probably the smartest dude on Earth for sure
In this next I'm going to give a little bit of a Content warning ahead of time therealak
Text talks about he's encouraging people to kill themselves in this next clip with your senses
For those artists
Please be aware that this might be pressed the 30 seconds every 45
Press it twice
Yeah he's he's
This is a really disgusting thing that he's presenting
Hope you enjoy yourself
Because you're going to get a big old heaping helping
It should be terrible people
You going to die
20 people
Slit your wrist today
Take those pills today
Get out of the way now
How about you get up there first
So much wealth
Show us how it's done
The big man dies
What's Bill Gates
Big man doesn't
It is dark
No is misspeaking
Not know what to do about something like this
Eternal death and eternal corruption
US army war with China
You forgave you want to turn loose on it
Jesus I mean like that's that's so f***** up and so inappropriate
Darkship
We're so
Browbeaten by Alex's in Sandy
What is a clip even is a little bit
Past look like
Normally use is
Cool
Like being like hey all you go
Deeply f*****-up
Even for us it's a little bit hooked up but then you consider like
This is a show he's doing
Imagine anyone else saying stuff like that Wolf Blitzer used to say it on CNN all the time though
You know you miss that situation yourself
This situation is
Done
I remember the time
Oh man
Here's your brother moment
I mean we hear stuff like that it's like really brings into sharp Focus like
How little control there is over the show
And like that doesn't even come up
As strongly my mind is
Money says things like
That's worse than that
No this is
This is too dark
Yeah it's too dark for him to be on are his mood is too dark
His situation is too dark
He is only
It's one thing cuz it's
Kind of funny when he's yelling about eating it's kind of fun
That's a funny expression of the darkness or whatever
That like
Alright
This can't go on wow it's happening
Let's Ride the Lightning
When he's saying like
Kill yourself and it and things like that along those lines
He's talking about Bill Gates it's so abstract and he's a
Public figure and then all this like
Then becomes murky and turns like that's f***** up but it's
Kind of in line with what Alex does
We talked about like all you left people kill yourselves
You think there's too many people that
Hit some
I don't know I feel like
I feel like it has a real potential to harm
And I I don't I don't like it
Yeah I mean
There's
When was the last time you saw anything on TV or anywhere that mentioned suicide and didn't immediately have the two
Suicide hotline
You know like this is irresponsible
That is
About life
No I know that's that's another issue
Nihilists Ellipsis narcissist on the air is
It's bad for me people who really care about mental health issues
Wood
Care about
Someone whose politics were different than them who would struggle
Absolute
You know
Alex.
No
I mean the think of other like
The deaths of despair
Well that's another thing I mean that is so many overdoses
Suicide by
Bygone like an ounce
Yeah and that is s*** that is like
How can you even treat that as I don't care what
Political side you're on
How can you treat that as anything other than as a human
Health crisis
Because he wants more people to have done well he talks about the deaths of Despair as being like
Like a laxative the manifestation of a war on white men
He talks about that cuz looking like opioid crisis as soon as it's all and all that stuff
But when he talks about things like this is like you think there's too many people kill yourself kill yourself now
I did become something where you you can't
See things like that if you care about the underlying issue of the thing you're trying to use
Like if you care about the death of
Asparagus and that's everything you can't use
Death by Suicide is some sort of
Prop like that
It's it's undercutting of
Of the thing that he
Chance to be no I mean like
I've got I've got a an attempt or two under my belt in that's
F****** me up
Like I really don't
I really don't find that
Acceptable to be
Anywhere near
Instruments
In this next clip we jump off that
Goodness and about videos ever coming out of China or fake
You're f****** didn't
Talk about it all the time.
And honestly this clip is just
Describe this is B
All made up
Everything in this is
True
Videos
Viruses man-made
Seriously
We now know why
Hey that's your Bill Gates who
Finance whole thing
Japanese
The vaccine
Because you could never
Have a vaccine
Or a cold virus because there's thousands of them in the Corona Familiar every year
Play new age
What it is
Religion
Creatures of three or more
Chimera
Nothing you saying means anything
Is nonsense
More by Celine positive on the rules but chimeras
So I
Version 2 or we saw conversion 5 what are we dealing I'd like to stipulate that I don't know the rules of chimera
Definition
It seemed
Pointless
So maybe chimeras have to be three
Don't care
Just wasn't as Charmed by any of this that I feel like even
Now maybe some
Baby in a different time I would have danced around
I don't care I don't care like all of that is not true every other piece
Of that everything that has any implication in real world
Is not true all that b*******
Yeah
So Alex
Little bit to distract
This is the point where I think he played a special report to be off air for a little bit
Forehand I got to go off air
So he did it smooth
But there was a special report and it comes back
We are back live and there's a lot of craziness going on today
Ago and it's important. So I still got them coming up
I guess just come back the next time now
Busy
Over there in the corner for me punch a bag live here
Global takeover
I don't think that he was busy reading documents this is around the time in the show win the
Documents were starting to be released from his case
Contacting him after the hearing
So I think that he was on the phone with his lawyers and he was getting too skinny
On
You know
What would how's things were progressing
So I just I think it is
Mostly distracted
Gas
Valentine's on is a guy who's been
We haven't talked about him because
Has been on any of the episodes that we've covered but
I did find a number that a couple episodes
Care about this guy
The ghost of David Rockefeller
No
It is not that Rothschild David Rothschild saint
It's a guy named Mark
Casio
And I don't really care
Here today and I want to get Mark passio and author and researcher talk show host from what on Earth is happening.
You know he's doing around investigated
Whatever Nicole Cribbs nerd
Okay
What intro
He's a former satanic priest
But
Look I don't know this this interview is
Is real stupid
Is it goes on a while and it's
A flame
Although I do think this is really enter
They get to talkin about the idea of Rights
Sure we can talk about what you think of right is
WRIC
Ght I have a right to do X
If he's a former satanic
Priest he definitely knows a lot about right
Yeah you think he does
He has a definition of right
That I think is actually
Really limiting
And kind of dumb
Have through
The forms of media that are embedded all around us and even through the toy
Types of waves that we are
Continuously
Human thought patterns
Physical control
People don't know what
Whites are ultimately
Really know what a right is
You can never truly
If you can't Define
A right is an
Action that does not
Cause harm to another Center
Camping
10% of humanity cannot
Simple definition
Correct
And ask people
Of a human rights
Problem and actions that do not create
What you call Sandra violations somebody else's for you
That's correct
Change or become
Crisis
Only build
I'll just accept marks definition of a cause harm to other people
Sentient being
I totally agree with that but it's not philosophical conversation about it right now
Takis definition
Let's just accept it
Let's stipulate it
Your rights
Absolutely do go in a crisis
He's presenting a definition of rights that are not Absolute Air Conditioning
And can be impeded as soon as the Human Action in question does end up harming another person
He's advancing an idea of Rights that's very weak
And I can actually use his definition to absolutely defend all of the stay-at-home orders and business closures that are happy
Country right now
That could possibly harm another human being
Is say you have the coronavirus and you don't have any symptoms
And the let's say state is reopen for business quote on quote and so you have to go
Go to work and you wind up spreading that coronavirus to other people who might die are you saying that that is
Not okay
Space on his definition of uses definition
According to his bio Mark passio was a former satanic priest to get super into Tesla and makes videos about the occult
I don't care
But from what I can tell about him he seems like he belongs on Project Camelot
However he's a good example of how these esoteric
Conspiracy theorists are often just Trojan horsing right-wing s*** inform something it looks more into
He's here talking about this spiritual definition of right
Really all he's doing is talking about the libertarian concept of the non-aggression principle
Like you see that a lot like it and it's
I mean we've talked about in the past
Like particularly when we talk about Stefan molyneux
Is completely
Self-contradictory and impossible to implement in your own life
There's literally no way that you can follow that as a guiding principle
That will get you to
Any functional
Way to live
He's talking about this this
Right
Is something Human Action the Dozen
Cause harm
Two other
Sentient being
Aggression principle
He's just using his weird
The natural law of reality that exists
Outside of
And also I should be totally clear about this
Alex should not at all
Be into this guy
Music for Satan
Granted he's
Not it's a different one
He's also an anarchic
Well there's that
Algebra
Musi
Deeply about a note okay alright
Alex we probably have some reservations about that seeing as
He does like status
Also he should learn the definition of words
Because if you want to start saying sentient
Then you're now talking about
Every mammal
Yeah you're a VIP maybe if you want to say sapiens there's an argument that
You only have to worry about
Certain terms of like
He just wanted to say Hugh
You don't sound smart
Honestly I think
I don't know I didn't look into it deeply enough but I did see something
Led me to believe that he might be a vegan
Concern for animals
Like Bill Gates
79th pick in his eye
I respect him if he's a vegan
Apparently if that's the
Lowest possible form of respect One Connect
Any wife is very boring
It's no good
About clip we have here
And they talk about
The idea that Bill Gates went on TV and said
That there will be 700,000
Vaccine
He only did that
Because he has to
And you always try to
Play into the emotional mind control
People
We're looking out for your best
Further from the truth
That's because they have to manipulate
People who
Want to do the right thing
Especially the order followers
You're taking on their car
That's how they're going to escape
Karmic concert
Quince
The laws of creation to spiritual laws of morality
The high-level manipulators
They're not
The karmic
What
Appointment
Corsica
They understand how
Really true
Those laws
Vendome they can manipulate people
Into
Breaking
So that's why Bill Gates has to say these things
And then he kills you with his vaccine but he doesn't have the karmic debt that comes a lot
It is that what's behind Alex's hold they have to tell you things that yes
Wow
I guess I am eating a load of nonsense is that what does that mean like
No
Military leader has to accept
The karmic debt for choosing to fight some battle or something
Like fuk off I mean I'm sure you'd be able to figure out the way to
The rewrite that story in a way that's convenient for you and not said
Can I tell you this
My clip here is titled this is nonsense
I'm glad that it drove home point we already Annika
But there are times when we come together in perfect
So I mean we come to the end of this
I'll be honest
I'm a little because
The thread of cannibalism did not continue I know
But it it was destiny
Not too
And I do think it was a publicity
Silly stunts
I still loved it
It's a lot more of it
Desperate sad yelling about eating his neighbors when everyone dresses like
Except us and we enjoy it I do I want him to find ways to escalated and yet not
Not receive the satisfaction that he wants yet
Because when he does this
I don't receive the satisfaction
Yeah yeah it's really
Boring
These last couple episodes
Kind of boring
Endurance
Flickers of things that are like
Alright I decided to get into the 223 Hundred Year history of their stuff like
Alright alright Alex Mendoza
I'm disappointed
I think there is a situation I've been wrestling with this lately a little bit in the present
Consistently
Covering it all
And I
Think that it's our responsibility
And it kind of sucks
Cuz sometimes he does shows like these are just not good
And unfortunately that ends up with the situation where we're covering an episode that's like
What you going to do
Yeah but
I do. Also think
That we're in a stretch right now where it would be irresponsible for us
Not to cover the present-day fairly blanketly
If only because
What if we don't listen what episode and he talks about cannibalism
I know it is this episode.
Immediately following the cannibal episode is
Exactly like
Whatever he promises next week I'm going to remove that
Computer kept yeah we knew it was going to be a disappointment
And yet you still hope every single
Exactly like the experience of
My life listening
If you get hyped
29 you get disappointed
But also if you ever have you read that book The Gift
Ping to Creation like when you create a thing cuz you recommended
You know you got to give back to the universe in order for things to come back like you will live
Whether or not that's actually true or not there is a function of like being creative it sometimes
Yeah take it on the chin
Does not work 10 hours
We're like trying to figure out a joke you do it
And then you do it again
And you Bob you do it again and you Bob when you finally realize hours Mount I got a I got a bail on this joke
Maybe I'll revisit it in a couple years that process of
Writing a bad joke and wasting all that time is part of the process that eventually leads to you writing a good job
Exactly and unfortunately I think these two episodes
An hour to show our
The
Bones we must throw back in
Into the ocean
They gave us the good need
I'm getting a little bit
It's mostly because I just wanted to say
Just want more of that
So Alex if you're listening please talk more people
Stop you should I make that your goal is not
Fear with your observations
And if I'd actually thought he was listening I wouldn't
Probably but I am
Board he cannot listen to a 2-hour episode
We said we were going to eat
I Willy
I apologize that I vote
Broken down at this point into a I'm bored with Alex moment but I know that maybe
Friday's episode will be
Bike
Right back on the horse Hope Springs yeah this is like the Prodigal Son
You're coming back to Alex Jones
And he's like
Listen
F*** you but we're going to play of play you the cannibal clip to just placate you and then you go right back
I'll be lured back every time
So we're back
Next week on Monday but until then we website
Also have a section on the website
And we are on Twitter that knowledge underscore fight not go to bed
We're on Facebook on Facebook it's Facebook / Seltzer and if you would like to go to
Drayton leave a review and so on and so forth
Please donate to a local charity of your choice
Yes but until then
I'm dzx Clark
Call Otto von Bismarck
God loves
Drunks
Children
Americans
And knowledge
Alex
Color with huge fan I love your work