Air Jordan
Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for its knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Dot-com
Alex
Jones
I don't like that a lot of these bright spots and up being
Food-related
We what what else do we have to clean to these
Here's how bad I am at cooking okay
Okay good get them
I just been meaning to do that
But I realized something else that I can
Sam Cooke
And this is very sad
I just realized that you can cook chicken in the oven
Oh yeah totally you can bake it all the time did not know
My friend that you can do at all yeah there's a lot of options for the longest time have thought like well if you're going to cook chicken
Get in a pan
And I'm not good at
I f*** it up every time it's chicken breast
Chicken quite a bit but I just realized the other day that I could take a chicken breast
You know marinated up
Toss it in the oven
Come out right to the point where last night
I was having trouble sleeping because I was planning to go get a ticket
Celebrate this new realization
Can chicken broth I am 36 years old I don't know how to live
What does a bright spot cuz you realize there are these things and you know what it's also a realization that there's so much more
That I probably
Feel is outside of my abilities that
It feels like that's about food but that's
Boudin anybody can eat a chicken you can just go get a chicken that is it about
Discovery
Shirts about finding out
A new facet of your life after this episode I'm going to go to the Jewel-Osco
Live my dreams
Nappy head
I can't do that it's beyond my ability
I rediscovered the red mask Renditions of Dave Attell skanks
Thanks for the Memories and which
I have told people about for a long time
It's
Thanks for the Memories classic Comedy album
And some DJ
1520 years ago
Under laid all these tracks to it so there's just a bunch of funk tracks underneath David tells jokes
We are I like there's Erykah Badu songs it's a copyright I've never heard of Orange
This thing no one has but I rediscovered it it was
I remember getting it cuz it was back in the Napster days yeah you would find a torrent randomly real
A lot of times things are mislabeled to think of some song by abandoned by another band
I'm glad to report that it is real
Okay I Googled it for a long time I can only find references to it on Last FM page written in
Different languages
Okay could find it Well that's proof that it's
It's real find it again
I have it I listen to it it's kind of thought it was in a dream
Time but I'll be honest I don't want to listen
It's not
Well one the album
A lot of it
Does not age well
I'm positive about
That's another reason that I thought was so
Perfectly funny when I was 12 probably now looking back Yu-Gi-Oh
No tolls
Horrifyingly event
Like the way he just says
East is such a fun delivery
Joe Keller even if some of the material is
Pretty problematic
Jordan today we're going to be going over May 1st 2020
As a Friday of last week and there's a lot of debris issues
To go over on this episode certainly
I look like a f****** idiot
Cuz on Friday varsho I brought up how thrilled I was that no one was covering Alex's ranked
His neighbors we were doing great felt so good we were like Icarus flew too close to the Sun
But it might have been it is your fault entirely Julie on some level I'm to blame for this and so
I have egg on my face cuz by the time episode got released
I ever wanted her toes Alex's outburst and I were giving him the all the publicity that he wanted
Yeah luckily nobody mentioned us in the in the whole night I'm not frustrated about that LOL I'm not
I'm glad I don't have to deal with all of that
I don't think that we broke
The story or anything like that like I think I know that I got some cleats for people who are like
You know you guys need to credit knowledge fight for breaking the trust I don't I don't believe that we deserve any kind
Kind of particular credit for like
Alex said this s*** and we talked about it could have been anybody it's not like
I don't feel any kind of territorial nastu the story
Or anything but I do feel like as a lot of problems
With the way people are engaging with it
I will get to that
Over the course of episodes does sort of come up
Butts up before we embark on this year May 1st Adventure
I should
The first
John H W thank you so much and I'll probably walk
Text Christine
Thanks Christine next Adam thank you so much and I'll probably walk
Text Gabriel thank you so much
Next Bonnie thank you so much and I'll probably walk
Thank you Bonnie and I'll probably walk
I think you took up people donated on an elevated level we appreciate it very much
First of all Justin's thank you so much you and Howard technocratic and Drew Dr you thank you so much you are now attacking
Money off that heroin
Really large
Drew Hill
It's not dropping Dru Hill which product Cisco
School that brought us these on song
Cisco
So much promise
Do you like the show do you do we do we could do that even supported by our website
Preciate that if you feel so inclined to take that charitable spirit
And find a local charity in your area that helps people who appreciates
That is well
Either very
So Jordan like I said today
May 1st
Friday made a made a lot of Labor absolutely covered
They were so much coverage of
Alex is in a particular sort of mood which is
I find boring in many ways but it does say some really stupid
Switch it out of context drop
From Today Show
Joined it
He's told a couple of those I went to sickness parties twice twice
I like the idea of presenting it is like they recruited me for sex
Which is to say they wanted me
What they wanted from me is my good f******
Of course sickness roving around just being like oh I bet that guy f****
It's good right let's
Pick him up in our van
I feel like they have a lot of
Options
Satanist to throw massive orgies
I believe that in the past he said they were recruiting him because they had like
Psychic powers and knew that he was going to be important later
Was crucial to the Earth's future or some s***
I believe I remember him saying that he was
He thought it was going to be a sex thing and then they sprung on him yeah
Is convoluted
So we start at the beginning of the episode and Alex
He's contradicting his mood for almost 2 days prior
Save the Earth
Because when you have children utility get closer to God you think about
Ancestors of the future
But I lost a lot of things in you
Don't have children by
Simply saying
Children
Crushed with
Sorrow
Feeling
Grief that we were able to get this out of control
We thought
We screwed around
But now we got to roll our sleeves up
Selling my body is commanding me
Commanding me
To get up off my ass schedule away from the people
Just a few days ago he was talking about how you can't wake people up
It's f****** over we're done
I think he's talking to him
It's constantly fluctuating
People up is over every cell in my body is screaming at me to wake up
The people pick a leg it's very frustrating
Equip Alexander reveals
That's how you know how maybe the Illuminati
Was the friends we made along the way that kind of trait bulshit
If you wants to let you know exactly is the destiny
Lesion
For them
Psychotic
Dealership
Human world
The destination the journey is the destination
There is not more beautiful not more open not more free or classically liberal
But one of
Trampoline
One of
Forecast
By then the average person lived
Really
Living
I have a strong suspicion that Alex thinks that the journey to the New World Order is the destination because for him it is
The end goal for Alex's show an entire business model is to never get anywhere
Because getting somewhere means you have to change something
The New World Order can never be defeated because if they were then why listen to Alex anymore
And they can't ever really win because then how do you justify the fact that you're still selling dumb pills while this evil dictator
Ship is in place
You need that sweet spot of their impending arrival to be constant
At all times
Because otherwise
You've kind of
He's like cheers
You know you can do 30 seasons
But you're always going to be in that
Bucking bar
Also that boot stamping on a human face thing that's for 1984 now Brave New World
The life expectancy in the United States in 1932 was not 30 years it was 61
For men and 63.5 for women
You have to go back to the 1800
Schedule. When life expectancy was in the thirties but guess what
That doesn't mean that the average person live to
That's a huge misconception about life expectancy
Satistics
That's the kind of thing you'd be here at you here caught confidently being declared by a guy you just talks out of his ass all the time
Someone like Alex
What are you doing if he's mixing up life expectancy with lifespan
There are aspects of medical advancement in sanitation that have helped increase our life spans over the last hundreds of years but
Generally speaking what do you see these big swings and life expectancy
That's not a representation that most people died at 30 in the 1800's and it's 60 or so by 1932
This number is heavily weighted by child mortality
When you see these jumps
That's almost always indicative of a greater number of children not dying in infancy
Not people who survived childhood living decades longer
As reproductive Health gets better life expectancy goes up
For this reason
And because people who are pregnant already greater risk of death
Then someone who is not
As the number of people who die in childbirth goes down
Who are generally younger
And the number of children who survived infancy goes down country see a rise in their life
Expectancy
Alex doesn't understand what this District captures
On the show pretending the most people died at 31 Brave New World was written
It's all
She just doesn't even understand the topic the very basic topics that he's talking to
Your life expectancy
Is 30 B
Because back then
People had 15
Kids in the hopes
Keeping five
You know it was that kind of like
Don't name it until it's 45
Live like that kind of level of right everybody dies so young
Smarticles about like you know like even ancient history
Knock knock
Baby
On a on a small scale shorter than we in the modern world
Well I mean Noah was 1,000.
Who is Elijah
Well there's I'm out talking about like in the Roman world
20 or whatever
It's it's a twisting of what these
Discover
Answers of Engagement statistics
It doesn't know how to engage with the idea that these models existed for what the coronavirus was looking like
And so you said stuff like that
Maria model we have been given in the last 4 months
The Royal College by development
Station House band
In the death rate
We know it is
Confirm
That they are counting
In Europe
China
And those hospitals is counted as a
Covid death
Alex is perfectly happy to misuse those same models that he's now.
The crying back when his narrative was that
For Humanity
There will only be Lone Survivor
Back then it made perfect sense to scare the audience about how there was going to be 3 million Dead from the virus
Isn't he just pretended those models were reflecting prediction
As opposed to what would happen if no efforts like social distancing a business closures were made
Alex even pushed a model created by the health Ranger Mike Adams
And had to be corrected by Mike on air that is model is specifically about the unlikely scenario where no mitigation measures were
Were taken
Alex is and has been willfully misrepresenting what these statistics analyses are
Even though you was all about them just a short time ago he's a real piece of s*** it has the feel of somebody who's
You told me two million people were going to die the only way you're going to be right
Is if two million people died
Anything else if less than that died that's because you're an idiot
Not because you were like
Let's do some
You're a liar liar
Can sunny out you son-of-a-b**** believe that
Also I understand him saying that you're up in the United States they're calling all death covid deaths
It's stupid and
It's not confirmed he just making it up but I understand him saying that
Extending that to China seems super weird considering the China's release numbers of Shona substantial drop-off in death
That's being reported
As covid deaths for at least the last month-and-a-half
You would think that if the goal was to hyper-inflated these numbers you wouldn't see China who are supposed to be the big bad guys and all
All this reporting very few covid deaths right now
But I was just saying even internally for his own conspiracy just doesn't make sense
It look like they're impervious to it so when we thought it was erased Pacific bio-weapon there to be like Siri
It's not a racist
I got to go
I don't care too much for whatever this nonsense is that he's trying to pay
I was listening to the show I had a realization that really really hit home
That is that people need to take this a little bit more
What it is
What did the what this show is
It's kind of at least
The in the most
Present day
It's kind of just becoming an intense religiously-based
Incitement show
The entire tone of what this is what he's talking about stuff that seems like
Oh this is just a
Be having the weird political belief no
He thinks it's Beeman's doing it
People need to remember that
Yeah well he's not
Going
Dead now
Definitely Army secretly
Four-channel point when things are so evil
That you just can't do it anymore you turned completely against
He said
Children
It wasn't because you know what it was
You know what it is
These people
Like to her children
Understand that
Until all the corrupt bureaucrats all the god
Those of you that Hayden about these people
You're going to face God God is so real
You understand that
Down here on this planet
Children
For your God Satan
I assure you your new order feeling down
The character of the show
That's what this show is
Core is just a guy rambling about his extremist version of religion
And accusing all enemies
Of being child abusing Satan
Worshippers
It's not it is
It should be treated like that
I think that should be in
Every
Article about Alex believes that everyone he doesn't like
He's under the control of an extradimensional alien demon
Who got stranded here when God kick him out of heaven or whatever
Mirror that needs to be apart of the thing cuz it treating him like a political conspiracy theorists at this point is
Is absurd
He's not selling food buckets
It's because the collapse is coming he's selling food buckets because an inter-dimensional space being is causing the collapse that's coming
You can wait
Four to six weeks because we can tour dimensional space thing is also probably a decade behind
Dimensional you to stay inside because I Collapse
Does the economy and Rob lot like everything comes back to like China is working for the internet are they in
Dimensional space beyond
All of it is this
And they have rules where you have to agree to it otherwise they won't
Do it well developmental not coming up in a relationship
Maybe it twisted the rules
Boy.
Everything that the man on the globalist
They're telling you to do like social distancing
The business closures all this at the past of this International inter-dimensional Space
And so that includes wearing masks which explains why Alex
Keeps telling stories about getting in fights with people
In public
When your
Walking
If she can join with the media on the Stockholm syndrome make you do it she's a hero and
Good
We're grown men
Sandy Hook
Okay
Who
Shootings and
I don't want to hear that ladies and gentlemen
Got to pause there because I like to almost said you know what kids are really dying in response to
Is wired
That is a tell
People
Bathing suits of cards are buddy
Illiberal
Catching around it's all sick
We won't be around here
Panda mask
Great shape
A big salad Masters or partisan issue now apparently which is
I'm thrilled I'm thrilled to see that this is the way the we've decided to to go
Some people have decided to experience things
Is a real bummer
You know it's at wear a blue state or a mask State and their red state or a no mask
State and somehow that's the world
Great
Sounds of course gets to a plug there for his a cool
Cool 5G shirt
I hate Man look
Plugging is great
There's something else that's better
Warmouth you need your word about use for the word you are Paula beer
Get it done now
Take action now
Should now
When so I know that everyone have fun with jokes about Alex eating his neighbors but ultimately
As you can hear from this clip before he was trending all over like he doesn't know about that when he's on air
Just giving exactly what he wants he needs word-of-mouth desperately up
You would have gladly paid everyone to do exactly what they did
On May 1st
On the day of this episode
Bonds to false claims he ate his neighbors
Already twisting f*** off exactly
Dammit the description of the video is quote
Alex Jones responds while trending number one on Twitter about eating his neighbors
Here is how that response begin
Proposal
Who is hands
The most
Famous literary
Example in the world
Satta
Now a few days ago
Live Oak it about Buddy
You in advance
The world health program head
Play MP4s
Starve to death
In the next year
Not from covid-19
But from the lot
Down the covid
Trigger
Where are you looking at a hundred and something
And it keeps going it's going to be worse
There are a further
People facing prices
Levels of hunger
Or worse
That means 135 million
People on earth
Are Marching toward
Break
Of starvation
An additional 130 million
Could be pushed
Do the break and starvation by the end of
Million people
The 300,000
Every single
Bay over 3 month.
What's not
The poor people like
Jabez whip story
Eating poor Irish
He proposed
Let's
Eat the Rich
Let's eat the elite
So that's how he's going to spend this and it's spectacular man I swear to God
We did this
We did this we set this up we did it
He's not supposed to be able to jump
The General Lee over this f****** nightmare of a situation and millions of dollars
If people just ignored it
We making this video we're going to pretend that he's f****** Jonathan Swift
Bulshit about like I suggested as we eat the elite
The guy for the f****** poor you
Hold this in with his exploitation of people in the developing world through a hunger crisis
It's it's all like really
Like it's exactly what
He would want
It's perfect from his aunt
Yep and he gets to argue that everybody's just taking a little quip
Contact man
I don't literally
I mean kill them I don't literally mean
Eat the Rich everyone knows that
So instead
Twitter Facebook Google all of them took a little 20 second 30 second one
What's a contact
Just say that I was at
My neighbors
Well I mean you did say this
My superpowers being honest
I want after the first few years I got footage
But I'm literally look at my neighbor's now going
Try to hang them up and got them and scan them and chop them off you know what I'm ready.
My neighbors
Superpower
Combat model
Probably later
The point is is have you thought about that
Because
My neighbors
You think I like
That sounds to me like someone who's actually talking about eating people butt
I mean
Who knows
Swift used to put in a little couple jokes here
They're you know he was he's pretty clever little turn of phrase going on there
Well I mean that is that is an essential piece of it
So back to his response video
Just basically saying the man I was just being Square
Do you watch the video
I think you're so
Stupid
But you won't get
Even though during that show I said
Allegory of Jonathan
Lilly did not end
And further
That was a metaphysical hypothetical but it's it's really not
Everything I'm joking around here
Anybody
Pilobolus
Dinos
Vegas
He went out of his way on that during that ran to be like I'm
F****** serious but also
Hey I'm playing both sides
Used such a piece of s***
It's it's it's great I'm really bummed because everybody ruined that
Clip for me too I was little I had so much fun with a open the Internet site
And they gave him all kinds of
Publicity and money and
F****** but now it's no fun that you can eat people
I had so much fun
Yep we were so innocent a few days ago
Where's the last clip from his his response video which
Ends of course
Commercial
Naturally but that is why I said of his car
I'ma say it again
Give Jonathan Swift
290 years ago
Really wanted to eat Irish shoulder
Yeah but we wait wait wait hold on hold on hold on
What are you saying
Say it again
Give Jonathan Swift
290 years ago really wanted to eat Irish children
But of course
He didn't
Willie want to eat
So you're not with him
Illustrating
Absurd
Satire
So you do want to each other
Which I knew they were
Will do when I get
That's how we have the
Is
Get a hotel
Here is my
Modest
Proposal
But actually eat
The people the trigger the global depression
And this is the end
Is not pointing out absurdity by being absurd
Webster defines it as quote a literary work holding up human vices and Follies to ridicule or scorn
A second definition is code trenchant with
Irony or sarcasm used to expose and discredit vice or folly
This is going to end up being a very standard definition and that second part is honestly the part Alex seems to be missing
Tires Direct
It's targeted specifically toward a societal Vice or Folly which is heightened and laid bare by the use of irony humor
A modest proposal is held up as an enduring piece of literary set Tire
Because
It did what it did was use a grotesque and ironic suggestion to expose and mock the prevailing attitudes
Society had towards the poor
Swift use the idea of eating for children as a way of highlighting how attempts to help the impoverished have been stupid ideas
And it was a problem to
To be taken serious
Conversely Alex was not talking about any greater societal folly or vice and his diatribe about eating his neighbors
He was not talking about this as a solution to worldwide hunger like he seems to want to pretend now
He was not talking about it because his neighbors were rich and somehow they're the ones responsible for the worldwide depression methinks we can avoid
Boy by going back to work prematurely
Alex was just talkin about eating his neighbors
Because you imagine a scenario where his children needed food
It was that simple
It's not satire
What Alex did fails to be satire because it didn't have a larger meaning
It was just him yelling about how he was an alpha male who was willing to murder and eat peoples whose children wouldn't starve
You can go listen to the whole thing if you want and you will not find a larger meaning to it than that
It's not a methodical active satire that wishes to convey a deeper truth
He was an idiot ranting about is post-apocalyptic murder fantasies
But I do believe that Alex did predict the people would talk about
It's amazing it took 3 days for people to pick up on the story but they did and Alex got exactly what he wanted
You can hear them that clip there he's saying that he knew people would take his words out of context and go here. His own site
This is working essentially exactly how Alex would help and ultimately serves as nothing more than Free Press Bonanza for
And I don't know if there's any other way this could have played out
That's why I was so impressed on our Friday episode the people weren't covering the story I thought it was a choice
You know
You're very much.
Yeah
And once folks
Found out one of the sites ran a story about it before you know it every other site had their own post about Alex eating his neighbors
Who's trying to get the top of Twitter most of the day Friday
And people were doing that that's where they put his rants over music is just bore Free Press sand
You know we saw her to work out with you we love our somalis video how much he embraced at himself
Too bad red masks rendition of skanks For The Memories
Didn't go
Viral shirt
And like I said
I just don't think there's any other way this could have gone
Alex knows that if he says completely f***** up things there's a really good chance that people will not be able to resist the urge to make jokes about it
Didn't post articles on high-profile websites about his comments
Everyone probably has good intentions that they think they're what he saying is nuts and they want to mock him or
Think of the coverage will somehow hurt him
But they're unfortunately wrong
There's probably no way to deal with this but Alex knows that he can essentially hack media attention with extreme outburst
Then you could lie about his intentions and pretend he's doing some masterful satire
He gets all the free press exposure from being blocked by everybody and then this down video he puts out where you pretend to Joe
Jonathan Swift
He gives himself the best chance possible of convincing the most gullible people who come check out his site that maybe he was onto something
The media lies about him
It's all a plus from his perspective and there's really no way to deal with it except by changing paradigms dramatically
I would suggest that no one should ever cover his helper
First because they're not newsworthy and anyway
There's no way that would ever happen though so long as his outbursts are interesting enough for media places to recognize their potential is Click
I think we're all just kind of f***** and we're all going to be stuck in the middle of this trap where Alex knows
How to get
Free Press out of people with
Escalating
Insane outburst
And people who are driven by clicks and traffic know that they can also profit off that
It's a symbiotic parasitic system that we just
There's no way around and there's people who aren't even
Necessarily driven by the same profit motive who are driven by like
The endorphins they get out of things being posted all night with her exact same joke being naked
Homemade over and over and over again people
Putting out memes
Whatever you can stop that
It's all it's all fun I don't know
Lego there's a part of me that wants it to be like
If you are going to go after him
Do it through our lens
Just so there's some sort of distance between
That his publicity and
And what he
You know what he wants but
I don't know maybe maybe that's a little self-serving but I might be a complete like
Lie I tell myself just to make me feel important man who knows
I just think that there are people who are they they're dealing with Alex one way but he's
Really together
You know there is
And it's impossible to convince people
How how
You should look at this
Because
Auto very basic level I'm a human
I completely understand that there's a guy who has a
Professional-looking
TV show yelling
But how he's going to eat your ass
Then we left
How can you not
Very funny
And without Carnival weariness of what he is how he operates how he does these things in order to
You get a rise out of people the benefit Sam
I just I just don't know if there's any way
To curb those impulses in people even if people knew
If they would do it
Yeah I don't know I just said I say we get rid of Alex nobody's allowed to put Alex Jones in a headline
Or in anything he just
To be called
White nationalist
Inter-dimensional space being believer
And that's that's what every and every single article and story and tweeted has that as his name
I don't think that helps him
No maybe I think it I think it might still
Cuz I was
I was trying to kick around ideas of like what you could do
And one of the things I thought was like maybe make the headline of the story Alex Jones pathetic attempt
Retention
But I don't know if that was something that I ate and if you make believe the story that this
This man is so sad
Is Steve going to give him the attention at least make it bad trying to get detention
I don't know if that would work but it's just a thought
Arrington
Transparent and sad
But
You know the internet here it is is he is a Force for good
In the world
I don't know what like
Man said he was going to eat your ass
Bright
I am at the same time it's not like
It was only an attempt to get attention
F****** struggling on that episode he came back he was crying about his kids
It's not like
It was all a brilliant ruse to get attention
He was
Horrible
Ridiculous
Heather
Outbursts
City had
That
Everyone turned into a brilliant PR move
Because of the way they engage with his contact
And like I said I'm not shiting on anybody for what they did I understand why anybody would respond to it the way they did
I just also think
I mean
He went
EXO
What do you do
Anyway
How do we keep losing
Game direct whatever
So in the next hour talks talks about how Trump knows that his numbers are slipping
Right
There's one solution
We are at war with
There was
That is huge leverage on the planet
We're shut down regulations they can do whatever they want
They're the New World Order is economically military muscle now but before
America
He can overpower that override that is wrong
Panera portal
Because
Because the internal polling shows
Depression
People are getting pissed
Way to stop it is to declare
Cool
We'll run
So that's awful hey he'll eat your ass Dan let's direct more attention towards this guy
The guy who sang that the president needs to do
Declare war with China
This is a this sounds more like a Coke
Field pitch meeting to Michael Bay
Like it's got all that okay so no
What's going on at the same time as the China is actually secretly at war with us
And that's why when we got the president in
Now it's time for the explosions okay
Explosions everywhere Will Smith
I don't care
Let's get it done
It's good to know that Alex like really gained a lot of his pseudo credibility early on as being an auntie
Turns out those words that we were injured weren't big enough
World
Wars
Awful Wars people who imagine themselves to be able to survive 12:50
To be those Lone Survivor
Christina Lopes true
The chance to live out my dreams unless there's a world or what
Our last episode Jordan you inform me that Trump had mentioned that
He'd seen proof
That the virus came from the lab in Wuhan and said
Iji not heard that by the time we recorded
I regret to have
Seen that
Maui
Bad
Alex talks about it here in this next clip a little bit
I will say just not analyze things much just right kind of his responses of course
Which is Mega that problem
Expect
They have
Martial law
Play our journey into a complete depression
But it already worldwide is already rated as the greatest depression
Every metric that is only going to intensify
Once we committed to Ally they know the general public likes the sissy pants around
What present
Bombshell info yesterday we already know the media totally ignored it
Viruses man-made it came from the wuhan.lab here's a president
You seen anything at this point that gives you a high degree of confidence
Wuhan Institute of virology was the origin of this virus
The world
Health Organization
Should be ashamed of themselves
Call Mike public relations Agency for China
Yesterday saying he seen
What is suggesting the coronavirus emerge from
I'm in Wuhan China
China where the pandemic
This is senior us officials are
Be looking into ways to hold China accountable for its handling
The virus
Compose the pro
President in the White House
Discuss tripping China
Immunity
Open the door for the u.s. government
19 victims
Still trying her for damages
Ministration officials
We discussed having you as cancel
Obligations
Sure
Star War
Alex wants
War
Like he's talked about it a bit in the past months in piano
It's getting to a point where he's being really blunt about it
Does he imagine happens after that
What is hematocrit happens after 2
Large
We're going to have superpowers declare war against each other
What happens that we each choose one champions
To fight in single combat
Whomever wins
Rules the world what happens after this
Protracted period where we've alienated a lot of our allies over the last couple years looks like
To fight against us
Imagine most of the Worlds
Allude are generally our allies being too thrilled
With the idea of us declaring war on China I would imagine it would not be the easiest cell
I'd like the White House needs to start hiring people whose only job is it it is to really listen hard and
Tackle
Like they should hire Brian Urlacher hair back now
Take the guy down if he starts to say
I think we should declare and then he's gone
That's what I would say
And didn't even if it's just a holiday
Still got a tattoo
Claire's Arbor
I don't know man
SMS
Yeah
I don't even know how to have any kind of conversation about it outside of
I I I hate I hate this I don't understand why people listening
To him or allowing him to speak
In any functional way I just don't
Stand it he should be like just
Find he's he gets to stay president
Put them in a box
Put them in a nice little box
Have him deliver addresses
People who dressed like the people who were there
He doesn't tell the difference
Create a fun little mini world where he gets to play act as president
Owen Shroyer is out at a rally of some sort I guess there's another protest against the disc
Something and all that
And so he brings up a couple of things in this next but they think are just like
Real stupid
We're seeing YouTube and Twitter
Banda videos
California
Is it working
Actually been doing the tracing
Apps for
People that stayed in not
Mood
Been out on the streets moving
People stay in and
We have the biggest
New Jersey
What
What's your true you stay hurting inside
No Lie
You're all scared
Supposed to die
Uptodown points there and let's take them
So the doctors he's referring to in California Arden Erickson and Artin massihi
Masihi
Two of the two of them are they run an urgent care center in Bakersfield
And they gained a bit of prominence lately because they put out a DIY press conference video where they said we need to go back to work
So bad
You're basing this off the information they've gathered their Clinic which is the first problem with their conclusion
They made the mistake of thinking that their sample the people who chose to come into their Clinic with representative of the general
Relation which it is not
Because they found a high number of people who came to their Clinic testing positive but not dying they extrapolated that to the entire
Population which is just not good work
Many many doctors and infectious disease Experts of come out in very critical about their information
And they've been denounced by the American College of Emergency Physicians
And the American Academy of emergency medicine
California state Senator Richard pan who's also a pediatrician and the chair of the Senate health
Committee harshly criticize them and said quote they're really doing this as a way to fish for a tent
You guys suck and they really just
Exist to give cover for
People to push the this isn't a big deal narrative
Which makes sense
It's their big hit Infowars they are a 0
The wee-wee tested and
Gave care to
I literally tens of wealthy white affluent people and
Looks like everybody is fine
I don't need to worry about the number simulating they're not percent of deaths in Georgia wearing the black
I don't need to worry about that I'm not particularly sure what the demographics or even the gross number of people who come in
Into their clinical but it doesn't matter
There's a reason that this is not a statistically representative sample
Just based on the idea that these are the people who chose to come into your clinic
So anyway that Facebook tracking thing I didn't even care to look in to see what I was talking about a misunderstanding because
Even if I pretend that everything he's saying is totally accurate it's so easy to see how he got the wrong conclusion
If we stipulated information
I'm just trying to say there's a causal link between staying in and there being a bigger outbreak
However that link is not established and it's honestly more likely that the relationship goes the other direction
In places where there's a larger outbreak people are more likely to take things seriously and follow the stay-at-home guidelines
Hey I don't know I was listen to that going like or
Maybe the people in areas of large outbreak
Know someone who f****** died and are taking it for very serious that could be and you dumb dumb
If you find a piece of data namely that in areas with larger outbreaks more people are staying inside you can't report that is
Staying inside makes outbreaks
Worse
I was just trying to justify that absurd theory that I was putting forth but it's just trash
Just trash work
It's definitely a fingerprint of someone who's trying to make information conform to pre-existing
Conclusion
As opposed to letting information guide them on their way to a conclusion
Which should be Infowars
Motto
Or something
People are avoiding beaches with giant shark outbreaks on them so naturally that must mean that if you stay
Away from a beach
Sharks are coming out of everywhere that's the only thing that makes sense to me
Solidthinking yet
So there's some good news
1500 types of assault weapons using the prices
The take the gun
Sowell
But just remember
If I don't make it worse I'm going to like that one troy here
Canada gun ban wasn't done using the coronavirus situation at all in fact it probably has just about nothing to do with it
C1500 models of assault weapons were banned in response to the recent spree shooting in Nova Scotia which was the deadliest
Mass shooting ever in Canada
Over 13 hours a gunman killed 22 people and injured three others at multiple locations around the province
I don't know too much about the Killer's motivation or psychology but the
Eutectic begin as a domestic
Disturbance
Against his girlfriend because that seems
Very consistent in these cases
Can happen
I don't know what else to say about the shooting other than they are an absolute tragedy that didn't need to happen
Canada is their own country and if they decide that one of the ways they want to remedy the problem
That they ever experienced is by restricting access to certain types of guns than they have the right to do that
It has nothing to do with the virus but Alex needs it appear to be because otherwise the story seems to be bad dangerous
Domestically Violent Men with guns can be
And that story is not in his best
Interested cover
That story seems like a really important
People should Alex
Is expressing this different feeling than Alex
He's frustrated the Trump isn't doing a
We've proven
Vater China attacked us with a bioweapon
Trump's not doing anything
Sewing
Had been
Sort of expressing some of these ideas
Alex is trying to reassure him here
And he says something that I think is very telling
You're like okay great
I understand
Mitch is going to collapse
I got to have time to
We already have blown up louder operation
Not in full control
DoubleDown
Because
Getting married
War with China
Stuff is all DeSoto discontinuing trying but he says there you need to replace me
I like to starting to talk more openly about replacements
Apparently it's Owen
But I kind of got that sense to it wasn't
It look like it should be Paul for years but I think ball
By virtue especially with him like
Did Alex was wrong about Sandy Hook
I think he might have tried to go out go into business for himself a little too much
Get 20 far out of pocket if you're apologizing Flash
Especially not with you you the very clear father-son thing going on between Alex and Owen
Some of the more Fringe communities of younger people that could be a prophet
Edible Market
Alex gets on doing this next clip talking about how he
You can't submit to his enemies
Americans into a ramp that is very disturbing and if you are sensitive to issues about
Abusive children let's say
Maybe be careful but
Images
Country
Is it war and we didn't start this war
1009 buffeted again if we were getting conquered by something better I join it
What
Position
Did not
You couldn't
Teachers
Newborn babies
Masturbation
Crazy it's not true
The teacher start
When the baby's born
Stimulating your penis or clitoris
Pedophiles man
They're vampires
Don't want to just grow your kids
Screw their innocence and suck them dry
Your child's first
Experience
He's going to be a nurse
Moth
Family Show
Why not give him a handy
The Who report
We will start
Newborn babies
You know that mean
Affordable food now you're insane
Wow I mean what the f*** is this the
Ram
Ranting
About nonsense
About masturbating infants
Getting into
Just no time at all
We got food.
12 quarts
Who playing is actually not
To Get Fooled Again
Know if you knew that one
They want today will not Get Fooled Again
Apparently bolsonaro recently came out on Facebook and made some pretty f*****-up and completely unsubstantiated and it's worth
Claims about that with the World Health Organization recommends
For children
This is part of his attack on The Whole30 no virus because
You know he's a strong-arm dictator leader type he's resisting the concept of taking things seriously they could tend to make him
Look personally week
Pinknews looked into his claims and said he that bolsonaro appeared to be twisting information for
2010 guy develop with the World Health Organization
For parents not children
By the federal Center for health education in Germany
The guide provides information to parents on how to discuss sexuality and gender with their children
And does not
Encourage sexual behavior
Business Insider reported that it seemed to come from this guy called quote standards for sexuality education in Europe
They review the guide and found that it was quote explains ettore and does not encourage masturbation or homosexuality
That's the part I was coming down playing
Most narrowest post results pretty homophobic because he's a huge anti-lgbtq pickets
And he's been pretty open about that
Alex wants this just to be about nurses masturbating in fence but that isn't all bolsonaro was talking about and none of it's even real
Even bolsonaro seems to realize that he was talking a load of b*******
Because he deleted the post
After it got pretty heavy criticism
I was just pretending that any of this is real but its not
It's just a strong-arm aspiring dictator lashing out against perceived enemies
Cuz I was just kind of guy
Even though he does not know his name
No
Cicero
Rosario know what is it
Standard pronounces that
Yeah I think for you I would bolsonaro might be
Unhinge right now
Now probably
His kids should be going to jail and so
We'll see how that goes
Right now
Sew-ins next clip
Alex has he wants this picture
On screen
And the crew can't find it a little
Image of my mind
About
Space suit standing in the m in the National
Parking Authority
How about a trout stream
October
Is the future
I see it
It'll be the Earth is uninhabitable for humans and let me to space with Fiona
We become
Cut off from the land
Now we don't know how to take care
Marcel's
Outside environment be so toxic from what's been put into us
And our immune systems been turned off
Pollen in the air
I was not having an in
Their whole roll out
We can't find it
Over there in the gym
Paint on the wall
Get a gym
Pull that off the wall I can maybe next time I'll show it to you but
You only work out your mind though we're talking about it
What heritage do you
Control a population
Pauline
But
It's it's not a
Let you know
Everybody get as self-sufficient as you can
The big cities are nothing but
Giant
Pilgrimage
Sure
Common Sense knows this
Time to get out
Open splices
We need to get
Get out run while you can
The clampdown and turn the clampdown off and turn the clamp down on
Infowarsstore.com good place Wednesday
Constant these pivots
But we talked a lot about the kind of damage Alex Jones does by way of his Crusades against people and how they can leave
Target has rathmann talked about how his rhetoric has the tendency towards people getting the impression
That they need to be the tool of God's Vengeance against Alex imagined enemies
What does clip I think represent another element of the damage Alex does the people who are unfortunate enough to believe he knows anything
You can just
F****** your life
It's one thing for him to profit off people by selling them bunch of overpriced and pointless pills but what are you doing right now
Completely destroy someone
Imagine you were committed Infowars listener and believer who lives in the city and you hear Alex repeatedly saying it's time to get out of the Cities because
Kilgrave
Is it not possible that someone might hear that and take him seriously
What if you have a good job your homeowner
What do you have kids of the dynamic web of social relationships already formed their school
Without you suggesting as a complete upheaval of all those things and he's just flippantly throwing this out there cuz some weird vision
Nearby people in space suits
To protect them from pollen or some s***
Like this is this could like really
Cause
A lot of trouble what's going on with you I will five years ago
Systems analyst
Comcast
Figures a year and then
Alex
Told me to move
So now I live here
Idaho that was released great
That was the image that I had in my head of like anybody saying the words I moved because Alex said to
Get out of the city and made me so depressed
Chop wood
Sure that's what I did I can
Run a trotline
I ran out of storable foods to eat my labor
I ate his ass
So are we get to guest coming up a little depressing to think about Alex
Affecting people up to that extent it's not depressing
Is the return
Of a guy
Who's Leo is Neo
Is the
Head of Matrix is on hell yes
I do not respect Leo zagami 1 B
No I'm so I don't care
You saying about the Vatican
I don't care at all
And I honestly
Got so bored listening to this yes
Except for when it starts to get a little apocalyptic
Take towards the end
And we have some interesting reveals but
He's a rattling on about the Pope I don't really care
Come on
A little bit about about Mark Zuckerberg
And I think that Leo reveals he might be a little bit racist
Obviously Zuckerberg just looks like a robot
Schematic
He's just learning Chinese
He's all day long
Regina
That's not good
Small Point Zuckerberg wife Priscilla Chan was born in Massachusetts
About her from an article in courts
A first-generation American she grew up in Quincy Massachusetts a working-class suburb of
A Boston
Her parents were ethnic Chinese who came to the United States from Saigon part of the wave of refugees known colloquially as the Vietnamese
Boat people
Could you literally put your children on a boat say goodbye and I hope to meet them on the other side says Chan
The Vietnamese boat people were refugees fleeing Vietnam after the end of the Vietnam War which if you were call ended when the People's Army
Vietnam took Saigon in April 1975
You would not think that someone with that element
And their family history would be particularly inclined to love the current Chinese government
That seems like I would I would be comfortable saying what we just heard
An expression of Leo being a
Raging racing that sounds more like a Chinese
Nobody's American unless you know
Right
So the two of them were talking about the how Alex's you know
In trouble
I guess and it turns out that recently
Marina Abramovic the artist performance artist
And Fiona Hill
The person who Alex attacked
Both of them have apparently said recently something to the effect of
I talked to him
Like oh no like something like
The guy keeps lying about me or I would be willing
To talk to him now
Alex believes that this is them trying to Parlay
Because of course it's okay
And sold so in the water it's a circle
Explain outdoor
So does Fiona Hill she wants to make
They're going to activate the circle that you're going to be trapped
Inside
This is the other way this game is played like to me and then people
We'll talk to me that's because I wonder what their plan is that why they're talking to me either they're going to
That's a perfect system for never having to actually deal with these people that you've lied about 4 years
Leo is on mostly talk
This is Akeem telling Alex that
The f****** in time Cheyenne
Always been talking about
Dangerous
Because once today
For the mark of the beast with the Miller and Melinda Gates Foundation
Yes
Republic
You're really smart
What is the best belief are you
Come on
The timeframe of
Governed by how we we respond it's not as fluid
It's a general guide but it needs fluid
2020 will be a year like no other because
Cars 4
Illuminati symbolizes something
Two numbers together this young and Young
Let's remember this year start there's no years
0 dead
What whatever
Let's leave that aside and just remember that prior to 2012 Leo zagami was going around telling any
Anybody who would listen
At the coming of the year 2012 would bring with it the rise of the Holy Roman Empire
That would have him Leo lion zagami at the end of it because you Jesus
We did 911 along with for Sama Bin Laden who didn't
Right so I mean like yeah okay great let's listen to you about these these predictions about things that are going to happen
It seems very relevant to his credibility
To ignore those things
I think it's good to know that he's more humble now
Now he's not saying that the end times
Going to end with him being this picture
Yeah he's just saying we're going through the end times
The only religion that would be allowed in his world is masochism of course
Because he's NeoCube Leo
Absolutely I got this f****** guy like
What kind of stuff it's like
It's
Hilarious
Let Alex talk to him and take some seriously it's so funny
Story how did you wind up here I don't feel don't understand
As an idea that's funny enough
You're going to need to
Actually listen to what he saying but unfortunately does say some really funny things like this
This is the great testing is now
Cities would become smart cities
Smart
Reality is smart
Is a nightmare there was a field
From 1977 called demon seed
They showed the fat
This woman was locked
She was impregnated by
Artificial
So that's what's coming in 2030
At your house
Who's going to impregnate you
The real bummer I was I was I was hoping to live my life without being impregnated by an artificially intelligent house
You win some you lose some
Yep
So that this conversation
Is awfully off the rails already
Topic of the end the end time comes up
I like this is Alex
I think if you listen to this
You can't walk away with any other conclusion then he legitimately thinks he's fighting aliens
Digital prison
Play Vance Troy Amore band species
Four-legged stilt real potential
Where You Are
Leo zagami
Scholar researcher
Launching their full attack
So I mean like this is this is the stuff that like the way I look
Should be treated because he's been like
More successful than anybody
And just because he has a studio that looks legitimate people should not ignore the fact that he believes he's fighting a space demon
That is
That should be front-and-center at all times
This is an apocalyptic
Extremist religious broadcast
At its core
And we should never ignore that we ignore it a little bit sometimes because of become burdensome
Cat pointing it out but
Like people who are doing these hit
On him
I don't mean hit like a hit job and like a media head
0 which one
Talk about him eating his neighbors
Also be sure you let people know these basically
Extremist
Religious wacko
Committed 911 we're not talking about that Leo zagami is responsible for 911 and we're just going to
Allow that to go
I think even more f***** up he didn't he said he did
Talking about murdering all these people in his past the obviously is lying
More f***** up if you want people to think that you did
I gave the order go fuc
Yourself I think Alex would do a great job.
Doing like just opening
In crawl in the ratio that movie martial law
The only thing that Alex could do that we
Productive for society
Would have been
That a little bit of talking dramatically over music
The perfect you could have found your pardon itch
LaFontaine you could have been there
Not that good
So you mentioned earlier that whole idea about like demons have to be welcomed in and all that and I like
You need to tell people what your plan is before you do it
Absolutely turns out that the globalist
Might be looking for a way around that rule
ABC reality
So they can
Translate
Into this
Dimension everything that
Covington now
Is only possible to be invited the floor country chose
Only if you was invited
His demons and his Legion
Cyberspace
Shorts
Do you remember what happened
Man
Conspiracy theories now but yeah
Discern is involved in Demon portals
A completely different thing as though they're the set like
Of course it's not a base
It's also CERN
What are what are you f****** talking about nothing
It's also important to recognize that like they're talking about this is very concrete terms
Poetically talked about
You know a battle between good and evil within yourself or something
Did they're talking about this is like
The next couple years
Global Awakening in the last few years
Accelerator plan
Which is why the Bible States build it'll be built for like one year
A very slow
A year
What is an esoteric mean
Couple weeks
The specific number of months.
Pitbull before we will be
Chanting
Armageddon because they will be
Confrontation between the two sides at one point
Temptation is it as asset inherited
Who are those Army and what happens when all this goes down
Well I mean there's the worcs
Of course the Goblins ride them the Orcs there's the Ulrich eyes well the Eagles come in and there's
Is Melinda Gates Foundation The Rockefellers
F****** Leo zagami
I love
That these guys believe in an infant
Evil devil
But they're like
And he can't get around this problem until 2020
Like he's never thought of it like the devil isn't even
Another was New Year's Eve
But Alex is concerned about like
Alright
Is it proper
Right
What happened to come back
Tulio when's that going to happen
Prophets risen backup Elijah and all that research
Oldest what
Let's say around 2025
This major damn fraud
And so
The next
Four years at
Of course the one that will change the whole Destiny of mankind
I applaud Alex for not turning that into a trump 20/20 at 11 export
I appreciate that
Depressed
Running for his head chopped off
2025 how where did you come upon that number is it because I just asked you that right now and you were like
Stop
Also
I mean
He was saying
Before
So where was 20-25 in that like
He did the math
Bright
I don't care is a f****** idiot
13 years from 2012 13 is a powerful number that's the number that Fiona Hill puts on her
Circle circle turns into a
I dream catcher and
That's weird
Dreams come from
From Dan
I think I lost the thread on
Earlier in the episode Alex talked about how
Owen it needs to take over for him
Am I might've just thought that was flipping to side
But the way this episode ends makes me think that Alex is
Really really thinking about this right now
Elio
I want you to move to Austin cuz I probably about the
Seriously I don't have
In prison right now
We need to get you here on some more bonus we daddy here with Owen everybody
Show show
How's that sound
Yes please
The other operations Young
Lisa needs a placement cell
If you want to be mixed up in the dock my friend you want to step another real fire
Give you a job
How did weiner showing
The way show you the way she
Either way
You know that answer is
You can't afford me
Got to get paid enough to go work it out
And whatever
Like whatever it is that Alex is concerned about
Imaginary or real
If he goes Infowars does not survive
This business does not work
Without him there and I think anybody
I will listen to the war room if it's just Leo zagami Rand know about
Out of the Pope
Mikkel ever know
I'm all about it listen to episodes where he's on and he does that
God damn it but it seems like it would have to be fun no
It's not
You may imagine that it is but it's not it's just a
So I mean we have this here Alex is in this real like
I mean it's ask elating on on two fronts there
There's the escalation that's coming surrounding
Him wanting literal War
Regina which is disturbing and very
On the other hand this I my time is pretty much over is escalating as well like
Frumpy we know we don't have much time left to this
Badtameez already one we lost this round all that kind of talk
Too much for concrete
I need my successors
Owen you're going to take over Leo move to Austin and
Do myself
It's it's it's taking it from the abstract
The more concrete
And that to me is progression right I think of it
I think it's exactly what you would
Expect to see but I would have
Expected him to be a little more private about this certainly less desperate sounding talking to Leo
That is that is a good point that it's gone from
I'm just being like
I'm going to my time here is going to end to concrete plans of like
When my time ends Owen is going to take over
When things are over I want Leo here too
Ain't nobody really want
And Leo. Leo does not want to live in
That's
There are very few Disco
That's true
I'm so yammy we come to the end of episode and
Yeah
I don't know
We got but I might my mood and my tone is maybe a little bit more down than it needs to be
But I think a lot of that is just because like
It's tough it's tough to watch people just
Go to fall into the Trap
But Alex sets
Hey bums me out at the same time it bums me out that it bums me out because
I don't like I keep trying to make this point because I think it's important
I don't begrudge anyone
For doing what they're doing I think it's bad I think is wrong
Technically
I don't think any
I have no interest in yelling at anybody who works for like slate or Salon or do it those places they posted articles
I adjusted it just bums me out
That's
You know if there's no right there's not a recognition that
It only helps him
Anybody who has if you have a platform that you suspect
Is larger than Infowars
Just don't do it
Spectre
Have no way of knowing for sure but if you suspect
Publication has more followers than him
Ben
Don't do it
Because the only thing you do
Did you run the risk of a wider number of people becoming curious
Going to his sight
Seeing stuff where he has more control over the I was doing a Jonathan Swift style satire
You know it's it's not going
Going to be everybody who ends up
Falling for it but you run the risk of
A certain percentage of them falling for it
And that's not good
You should do
Block off those pads as opposed to facilitate them
The second wave
Coveted
Like
Weedy platform to Alex a while back and look his numbers have gone way way down and so then the first
Stopper tunity it's like
Let's give him his wider platform as we possibly can
We were winning
Well he was going away I don't think the people look at it as
Helping him that's the crucial disconnect
The people have is they think that negative attention is bad for him
And they don't recognize that he plays a different game but then maybe
Normal people do
Because most people if you had
Most people if you were to have like a video of you yelling about how you're going to eat your neighbors
Embarrassingly
You know
Someone covering it would be a thing where I got to get a statement of apology I need to clarify
Whatever but for someone like a lien in retention out of it
More negative attempt
And so that it just I'm at strategic changes need to be made and
I would love to say that I know exactly what that is but I don't really
I just I think that
Calling out what the
Things for what they are in terms of like look at this desperate loser
I think I might help but it also might not
I don't know if there might actually be no solution
And that's
McKay's
Whatever I don't know I guess the only thing I can think of is that he doesn't talk about us
No ghetto so
There's room there's something about what we do that
Is immune from his
Feeding off of
Negative attention it seems that way
But maybe it's just again if that could just be self-serving
Maybe we just
Completely off the radar
But that's the thing is like
ANM
Again
Just a theory
I think
If you're going to cover Alex
You need to find ways to make it so anybody who has attention to the thing that you're covering
Will it it's negative
For Alex app
You have to you have to almost put
Within what you're doing
Fail-Safe
And that's why I think it's okay
For us too
Laugh
And make fun of
Alex's beating people.
Anybody who could come to us
I don't think would ever
We like to check this guy out there is a safety to it
That where is
An article about him
Might not be
I don't know our explaining how we might be a terrorist
And then they played me this bees but
Thing and I'm like
Maybe they're lying about him and maybe just love meeting but I don't know
Yeah I don't know I don't
I don't think there's a good answer
I don't I don't know
But until then we website
Also on
Are you like the others do Cleveland Heights in Wrigley review patreon dead if you would like please find a local charity
Donate to help
No you're the Seltzer review this the time I kind of forgot
But
Leo on dzx
Clark I am the juiciest Ice Cube
Alex
In color