Important
Knowledge party.com respect with knowledge like
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Wellsfargo.com
Fix it around a little bit
Quick Quack
Continuation of
I got some chicken breast
I did it
Easiest f****** thing in the world
I feel like
A world
The 2019
I do not have those miles
Last night for dinner made some chicken and rice
It was fine
For lunch I tried to kick it up a little bit more
Okay
Chopped up garlic
Jalapeno
It was better
Hazing is like there's a whole world of marinade excited to explore
My bright spots
For the foreseeable future might end up with
Some stuff also in a couple days I plan to make that lasagna
Enthusiasm
Can-do spirit
I like
I like it problem was really for so long I thought
You can really cook chicken breasts on top of the stove
I can't do this
It's for someone else
That's what other people do that
Chicken breast
Let me tell you something
Until you figure out that you can
Spirit on both sides in the pan to get a nice little grass and then bake it after that
Future Ray
Call my chickens
That makes it a pain
I might do some work on this front and then start
Sports mother recipes
Okay well I will tell you I just had some
I was really I was really struggling and then 20 minutes ago
Fantastic
Delicious
Wow
I'm glad for you to enjoy this candy I thought it was good not great
Ubi over 50
I thought might be a prude
It's very weird
And
Problem
Seltzer report
Call Jason
Don't call you Jason
Thank you so much
Short for Nancy
Text Elizabeth exciting
Feared enemies from Dynasty Warriors assigned to show
Thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Chicken
Chicken bath run the world
Sign up on an elevator
You're now it's like
Freakishly large
Lexmark
Beauty
Appreciate either
So Jordan like
Report
Struck out and I also was
Because the last time I dropped I stocked up on a bunch of the different flavors
Sparkling Ice
The couple in my fridge they were waiting for me to be the next
Is caffeine that comes in 16 oz
Plastic bottles
There were like 1,000
They're easily readily available they're all over the place
If I hit a wall
Sparkling Ice
These ones of a can
They're terrible
I still have these leftover
Drinking goes
Because we had a good head start we're still on track
For the 50
I'm currently 27 South
Yeah everybody
Number please
What's up
Definition of seltzer
I don't care
Is this music
About 10 carbonated I feel like it's a Celtic
Supreme Court definition of pornography
I should have fizzy water but I said Salisbury
Mistakenly
Spot
Before I got a
Bubble
Apostrophe
All of them
All of the varieties of flavors
You have a pretty solid consistency
Before this Venture like a really admirable rating
Guava blender
Terrible 76
76 out of 100
The 75
But also
The bubbler chapter
Is that one
The blood orange something
I know I was mixed with something
Cranberry something-or-other
Level of free publicity you better make up some new flavors of real quick
Otherwise you're not going to get the knowledge fight Bob
Fruit
Pomegranate acai
Mid-60s
What was the other one
Text for me to beginning
Of this year-long adventure Arrow
Sunday Monday
Swing to get through
Explorer
The increasingly side World of Alex Jones
Snooze the broker
Withdrew from representing Alex on Monday
Simultaneously Alex
Chris latronica
Also filed a motion to withdraw as counsel
According to the Connecticut Post
It's unclear who will now represent
This is really bad news for our
Explanation for what's going on
Most likely is
Continue representing him until
Case begins jury selection
And then proceeds for however long it's going to end up going on
He's likely not to be on the air in the
Not to disturb
Future
High-profile media playing
Nobody's representing Alex pro bono
It does have his own show on in Fort Worth now
Mother Walker
Go to work
He's not
Steve Earle
Has gone through a number of
Lionel Hutz is dead
Pass the bar
Inola
Okay start
Vinyl theme song play
Sorry we're told you to kidnap
It was worth it
That's not good I mean that's one of the big possibility
Norm knows that Alex Campos
4-H
To the point where he hates Alex so much
He doesn't want to represent
I think it's unlikely
Considering how much of a
Predict our collective in the past
With that
My big senses
Financial aspect
Strong
Contender
The other second strong
Is it normal to realize that that case was going to end
How do you know that would be bad for his particular brand
It's fun and profitable to be the Firebrand Rebel lawyers supporting Alex Ruiz free speech
Until you have to make
It's really good
Postponing things
Make the argument
If your lawyer like Titus
I think this might just be
I'm going to end up seeing the inside and I can't do that
Again if I'm the guy who's trying to defend Alex on this shaky ass crowd
So I think those are the most likely hasn't commented on it so there's a
There's an entirely other explanation
By Alex
I'm going to say that
I'm not saying it's just saying that people are talking
Here in the minimoys voices all around
Jason I saw several tweets about it just a week ago
Lawyer to represent him
And his options on
Completely give them up to speed
It's a huge
Being as well
Because like he has Barnes and Norm
I was like I said.
Tag team of lawyers
Celebrity lawyers say they was there
Who is Hozier
The guy who hates Rodger Stone
Brown bar we can go to Alexandra
Going to happen
Inclination
Steak on outer case
The most likely thing
Is probably a combination of
The money and the we're going to lose
This isn't worth
It for me anymore
That's just my sense of it who knows
Also you can't be thrilled with Rob dues deposition deposition
Probably like
The money is part of it
In such a way that
The money now allows him to do what he's always wanted to do which is
Kick Alex to the car
He's always hated Alex but the money was too good now that the money might be even shaky it's like
Finally
F*** you man
Wobbly
The New World Order is going
To bring in this absolute
It's going to happen
There's some people who aren't
Going to go along with
The plan man
Now the problem is there is a large minority of Americans
Along with this
Unless there is a giant Awakening now
Total understanding of this fraud
We don't have a
Hanson how
Woke the world up level is
Verity
We were turning the tide the Chinese spies were being arrested
And then the Deep state that I can set up account in Chinese
Rockefeller
Foundation
Waxwing
Randall locks
The vaccine for weaponized time you're at the other 19
It's already writing they just wanted to make you beg
Before boarding
Years ago
It's too pretty early on
Stone something actually real
I saw ABC News
I'll need an atom has 5 eyes
Shane but it was a bioweapon
Avalon lab
The author of the US law by 11
Prosecutes dictators
February
Concord
The same thing
How to steal
Consistently doing we developed
Adopted supposed to be inverse
This is honestly one of the most scary roads
I've traveled
Talking about something real
Pierce
2B is tariff
Over the weekend
Fox News reported on a
Intelligence Alliance
Chinese actions over the course of
There's a good amount of discussion of
The theory that the virus accident
Escape from
But it's also clear
Presented to definitively point
Scenario
Sources who spoke
The Fox News say it's being
About how the alpha
The article is pretty explicit that no matter what theory is being believed or natural origin Siri
Scenarios are attributable to
2 mistakes
There's no malicious intent behind it
In the Box
Snooze story
Daily Telegraph
A tablet out of Australia
The Daily Telegraph is owned by News Corp Australia score on Fox News
Echoes of the same operation
Velox
Step if you will
The Daily Telegraph article claims actual size report
The information they claim it is absolutely terrifying
Reading over the telegraph article there's some
2015 UNC Chapel Hill
Origin of the virus
Covid-19
The idea is that it's a part of it
In foreign policy made me feel more worried
Read as it discussed this supposed intelligence report that was
Australia
That leaves us and Zealand as member states
Tried to dispute
This intelligence.
Making an argument that a majority of countries
Do not support
Keep in mind specifically reporting animus
Which it is not
And the distance just gently saying Iraq
Iraq
Iraq all over again
Let's make up a reason
The foreign policy article points out that everything
The telegraph article
Source until a
Meaning it's readily available online
There's nothing
That's new or would be indicative of an intelligence
Product or some sort of secret
Compilation of things you can find out
Which socks it's a bunch of
Papers from Alex's death
Facebook
Intelligence service
From the article
Davis
Is Intuit
Canadian former colleagues
The White House
Position is bad
As for the other five I Centre she said
Stand is also being used
American politicization
It's almost like they did that on purpose
I can't sleep
Using crowdsourced theories about the origins of the Coronavirus
This is just unfortunate misreporting by the telegraph
But how this all could
Play out
It represent the first time I can think of that Infowars
Conspiracy theories made their way into a couple
Intelligence
Report
Which makes me shudder
National
The following
Where do you have any evidence in the answer was
But somehow
People who read headlines
The way to go
Is definitely Mike Pompeo
Mike Pompeo lies who are f******
Places with no information
That's the way to go
Real serious proof about
This conversation
A happening at this level and like
You're absolutely
Are you are you ready
Just getting involved in situations
Greenway over on
The ramifications of a could be
Ridiculous
Complain to the next clip but he's been right
About fauci
And because of that
He's got a tail on
Exactly
Play
She's involved
We saw the exact virus to chimera
Show me the white papers
It doesn't look shows on it
Let me not start
That's what goes on in this country
Get ready to General phlegmy that's fine
All American
Getting ready to General Flynn
I mean I think what you have here is
Continuation of Legend building
Comes to pass whenever
Private investigator
Gator on his current wife
It's not they wouldn't be the first time that a lawyer's hired a private investigator so yeah
Why not
Yeah that's a possibility
Concretely say that
It's a Tesla
To create the narrative that allows the end of his career
Tubi
A noble thing or something
Is an FBI agent
Alex take something
Reported as news
We've got
The Prado articles for there just
That's what he
CDC
Did instead of over
United States Coronavirus
This claim was taken and repeat it over and over again
Booking Twitter
Check the data where it came from
From the cdc's
Provisional Council covid-19 tracker
And it's something real
The cdc's website is not the most epic
Today tour
Apple website
That's not necessarily
Process doesn't cater to up-to-the-minute reporting
These claims are taken from says very clearly
Provisional death counts may not match
Cancel other sources such as
Arkansas
The reasons listed are quote
Steak timer
Completed
State States reported
It takes extra
Time to code covid-19
And other reports
Systems use different definitions or methods
Workout
They further go on to say that
Exchange
From the very
It's being used as a source
The claim is that the numbers
Picture of what
Possibly glimpse
Hindu how things look
22 weeks ago
If you look at other trackers like world
You can check with the total death count was
2 weeks ago
Pretty close to 37th
So that kind of makes sense
In 2 weeks on the cdc's
For now this isn't
Is Alex's recording
Decided to report it without
Consulting the CDC page himself to get any
Further information on the subject
He doesn't care about the stories he's reporting only about advancing the narrative
Regardless of how much she has to make up along the way
Naive listener
Alex is reporting on hard research news
Any idea about the subject he's covering
It's factually inaccurate
Has ever done
It used to be drug chat line
Turn sound on for
Channel Twitter
That's what his show is in terms of information
Yeah yeah it's a war
The war on information
Reality is nothing
Sitting in a nap
Another article
This one's about
The election
Very exciting
We got that
You didn't just hear this year
If you heard this year
The Hillary
Oh here we go
Officially
That they are considering the plan
For Hillary
Run but Obama to be her VP
Groudon
God
Conversation
Your stone was saying This Is the End
Or you got arrested
Call Metallica
It literally has his header
The views expressed by
Contributors are there
Hillary Clinton Barack Obama tickets
Is it even possible
It's a fantastic
Suggest
Doesn't seem to be in primaries this election
Can seasoning
Reconsider
Idea of Hillary and Obama
And then the discussion president
There's literally nothing to be at other than one person's fantasy booking of the elect
So this was written by Douglas MacKinnon
Inconsiderate
Concluded
Communications
Consultant was a writer in the white house for president
It also be good to know a little bit
Without a grain of salt
Don't need to know anything more than right
Got it all
Bit of a resume for him to be spouting nonsense about the Democratic
I really do think
The time for us to listen to what Republicans have to say about what
They've got a great track
Yourself
A2014 McKinnon published
The book titled the secessionist States of America
The blueprints for creating a
Country...
Now
His book was legitimately call for the South Teresa seed
And created new country
Just right principle
Basically Fundamentalist
Caliphate
A proposed name for the new country
Reagan
Would make sense
Name
Country Reagan
I really think somebody with ideas that bad needs to be kept
Kept somewhere safe
Apparently this country
Georgia and South Carolina
Get on board
To be disappointed to learn
But he specifically left
Texas out because quote
Incursions into Texas and other places from Subway
Los Angeles
And Broward County number 10
What is playing
Tolerance
I was thinking of another name
I think they tried it one time
What was the name of that Dan
Heard about this that's probably right
Promoted his book on a right-wing radio show
Confederacy
In response to
A Tribune
Conservative writer for places that have low standards like Tucker Carlson
Trash rag Daily Caller
Jeep 2020
This dude is a trump loving columnist is largely
Suggested democratic
It's because they really like yelling about Hillary and Obama
Absolutely
Should not have done
Thanks but whether or not it was
Potentially possible for Obama to run as a vice president
It's another thing to publish this b*******
6 years ago
Was writing a book
States to secede from the country because he was mad about lgbtq
Acceptance
Seriously
Is there
Coming out
Pics of this work for his narrative so whatever
Controlled opposition for alley
Mad about it it really does seem like they're working together
Actually working together
Together
Together like Lego blocks
Very stupid
Has episode Alex decide
He needs to
Discuss the fact
But everybody
About him
Here in this
Return I'm going to respond
What are the biggest stories Friday and Saturday for 2 days
Number one on
Thanks everybody by the way
It was a shame
A modest proposal
Sure
I misrepresented exactly as I thought they would
They beautifully on that
Until now I've been able to
That millions of millions of years on other videos we put out
Where we talked about a modest proposal
Now we could
Suppose the absurdity of eating children
Opposed
Cannibalism
Free Press
Given the circumstances
Yeah I agree
All the time to get attention after on Tuesday and Wednesday
This is why it's really important
Do you have outburst
Ludacris prison
A failure and a waste of time
He didn't get what he wanted out of
Now we can pretend that what he wanted
It was always about getting himself attention
More people
Exactly what he got
I am so mad he said that Direct
Likely to us
Because we
Google I mean
The exact
The exact thing of how it happened
At least trying
Exactly how I hoped it was
Man
Not fair that in the moment he was like
Really like
I'm going to get press out of this
As soon as he went to commercial use like
Cover that
Get take a clip and
Attempt to take out contacts
Because that's just money on the table
So Alex talks a little bit about
This rant
Not to talk about this more
The more frustrated I got
Google
Yeah you'll see you'll see why
Virginia
Really does that
He didn't say instead of killing babies
Piece of equation
Completely new element
What he was saying
Make some sort
Sixth Sense
The ad
Literary layers to it
In hindsight
He was saying is out of food
To trick my daughters into eating a human be
Alex
And he starts talking
The actual
Press
Because of this
Lichen
Why what Alex Jones said is so dangerous
You think I want to say
He is commanding the people in Michigan
Who stormed the capital they make star
You talk about satire but they're writing this as serious
Does not say
The pieces could probably be summed up
This paragraph from the art
The consequences from
Taking words literally
Millions of Americans have reason to be concerned about their economic well-being
And suggesting that violence might be necessary for cell survival
We're living in days when openly armed protesters are storming
So it's not
Further provoke towards
Spirit violin
Apps they might not see their neighbors as recently see them as adversaries in the world of accelerating scarce
News articles
Dependence is being in this together
Neighbors to feed your children is the sort of thing that's based on the opposite
Mentality on their own
And at worst
The threat to myself
The author of the article is really clear about this dangerous
Does free speech by necessity be
Constitutionally protected
Is dangerous messages of distrust and division need to be combated with
Solidarity and common cause
Alex
Does these publicity stunts
Responding
Irresponsible
Sources of information
I think the Sports Basement
Tickets in importance
Remember
That's crucial to look at
People around
Collaborators knocking
Competitors are food
Ultimately
Make an appointment response to Alex's ran is probably
Counterproductive
What's going to happen coverage of a stop in order to
Do the mold
In order to further insulate izadi
And
Gaslight people who are coming
Going to check him out based on
Yep
Talk about a modest proposal
I'm not sure he's ready
Proposal
Was Jonathan Swift
Irish
Cleric
And the English
Describe
Butcher them
I did
The most famous pizza
Proposals from 7029 not 1730
Small difference
It seems
Proposed
Text
But it does make sense
GPS John Birch Society book
I mean like he's talking about
Beggars
Institute for
Text primary
Concern
Modest Proposal from the academics
Determining if Swift himself is the speaker in the tech
Disconnected
Persona he's created for the pamphlet
Elizabeth Hedrick
Explores this question under piece for the journal Stetson philology
Fall 2017
This is irrelevant
The suggestion of
If it's understood
Swift himself is the one making
Proposal
There's a problem with the irony
Neighborhood
Is well-documented is absolutely
His writings and sermons have been shown to include
The distresses of the Irish pour on their moral failing
Is this is a person
His proposal
And thus be more widely accepted
The character speaking in the pamphlet
But fully detached
Trump
Open Swift
Persona
Consider Swift
Other writing
Secluded
In particular
Particular
Better understanding of exactly what the target of a modest proposal
I need directions
Taken in the context of his body work
Hedrick argues that the main thing being attacked in a modest
Proposal
Andy wig assumption
The good manners were innocent transparent
Performative
Goodness rather than
Pleasing front for malice or a gresh
Ethically simple-minded and politically dishonest
Narrator of The Proposal is perfectly polite
Juxtaposition would be barbaric suggest
Seen himself as the savior of the country for proposing
Solutions
The problem of poverty
This was the equally stupid
Delivered
People were making at
What time have you considered
It's pretty clear that this is the large
Or just part of what do you attach Rising
So essentially
He's
He's talking almost about
Like the difference
Between Obama and Trump bombing people
Obama's
Is putting a very calm and polite Cesar atrocities
Position
Exact
Veb polite
Is more important
Myself
Who's the head been suggested
Help with the problem of poverty
Working Solutions
Delivered politely
For the sake
Putting a mask on your own
He wrote screeds against
Parishes of Dublin
That piece was very much
This description
Lazy to work
They're not afraid to steal Norris
To be seen with a badge
His many of them has confessed to me
Until I see better regulation
To persuade brother Walker
For if Bakery be able to beat out Pride
It cannot deserve charity
Swift did not care about the well-being of the poor
Sweet polite
Which solution to the problem
Propertyware
Suggestive
Ultimately
Effective bushing
Miraculous Solutions
Primary concern
How does this relate to Alex on his Ranch
Simply put it does
Because nothing Alex did had a point
He's trying to
To claim that he was making a modest
Proposal
Completely apps
From his actual rent
He was just talking about being willing to eat his neighbors so that his children don't
Starve
Is there's any word
Connection to people starving
Could possibly claim
Is it is worth or condemnation of people
Don't kill their neighbors who feed their children
That doesn't seem like
Kinda
That is a
I could read it that way
You couldn't
No I'm traffic I will
I think I have your welcome
Actually you can make that was a brilliant piece of satire on Alex's part I don't think I've done stink
People in countries
Indigent
Just be pleasing facade that his people's real cruelty would it be possible
How to connect
I still say
If you are covering the people starving the developing World in
Suggested we eat them
Connection
Would be really clear
Track that yelling about you your neighbors to feed your child if so how
Suggestion that lamp
The politeness of people offer
Suggestions on how to help
But don't actually care
Could reasonably be
Purposeful
And everything I can come
Fails to satisfy basic
Applications
Also let's not
Forget that
Campbell after like 14 15 days with no food all the time
It's something that I'm concerned with four and hunger
And his disgusting of his willingness to eat people isn't even really knew
Body show from December 16th
If people were coming to eat him he would
I wouldn't go out and grab
I'm just being honest
What's a trading party
You haven't eaten
Self-defense
Use these fantasies a bit
It's a long way to go
You know
Care about people in the developing world that he never has
He supported Ron Paul for most of his career which is disqualifying when you try to protect
Seems to care now because he believes businesses easier
He thinks his trump card you can play
People going hungry
If we do get through this virus crisis and things go back to
Someone normal
Without completely forgets
People having food in Africa or South America
He's just a sick f*** who sits around and pretty regularly thinks about how
And what are you doing now is just
Pretend to take
A moral High Ground
After getting a ton of Free Press
He's trying to make his unhindered outbursts seem like it was some brilliant piece of art
Also fun fact
Proposal Swift has an imaginary America
Looking for his proposal
Knowing American
Things in London
Young healthy child well nursed
Most delicious nourishing and wholesome food Weatherspoon roasted
Baked or boiled
And I make a note
I guess this outlandish idea
Better
She probably was at that if he's ever read it if he's doing 1720
Imagine that the other implication there is that
People who live in America are all Savages along with the Native Americans
That's why
Z
Grade my friend
We had to read a modest proposal and do a creative thing on it
Sada baby it was delicious
Is very
It wasn't an actual
What you do in 11th grade
Alex's 46
This was this
Swiftian satire and all that in the media
Was shot
People starving in covid-19 lockdown
National file
Basically my run propaganda associate and probably
It's a swift reference
People starving in covid-19 lockdown
Quote
Explanation
Article
At least twice calls into question about word
We're really satire
Is directly in this
Notably Swift essay is largely about class
Send the poor being used as
Commodities in society with little regard for
And not about a viral
Pandemic
Jones insists that the covid-19 lockdown
Third world
And causing billions of poor people
Starbucks
This is not about our teeth
It's an article covering out to the temp to explain himself actually sound like
Alex
Music
These people get in
They're not
There
They don't buy his argument at all
However it is very expedient to put the
The headline up there that makes it look like
He's got a defense for himself
That would make the most sense to me
You said his piece about the great respite he's getting and
Sure he gets to just ranting about
Stanford ask coronavirus nonsense
Even harder on me
All the doctors are partying
Medical workers
Most of them are partying their asses off
Hospitals are empty
Because Lily I get $39,000 for covid patients
Lookout you coming down with a cold
They're going to snake
Kill your ass
Can I collect the money on your dead ass
What's Isis
Dangerous rhetoric
Do not go see a medical professional help
Understands how a medical work work
These hospitals
Even if they're getting
$39,000 for these patients
Do you think that's more than
Normally operating hospitals
Everybody's everybody's everybody's pretty f****** ridiculous
Alex
Defending his
Really actually
Because
You get some too
Begging people to write
Total collapse and everything
You're right I won't I won't eat
They're good
I won't go out with the lamp
Governor Northam
Alex Jones wants to buy aborted babies and eat them no
Text Oregon because it's real
Because
I'm the bad guy
For the corporate media
Continues
Available again
If you can't turn it into an ad
Francis Boyle on
It's mostly pretty standard stuff
I do think of this clip
Is pretty interesting
About how Alex was saying
The CDC admitted that there's
The number of death
Very different
We have to understand
Come to grips with that we are at war with
Existentially dangerous
Figures we're being given
Casualties
Completely bogus
Financial
Times last week
Ran
An article
Casualty
Get the real
Figures here
Are not the one
Casualties
Play one country by
Country
And the extra
Casualties
40 casualties
So icy
Probably
What is happened to your the United
Santa today
We're being told it's only 6
4000 people who are dead
Casualties no one's given us
My guess is
Icewarp what we are being told
And these officials at
CDC many the
Fathers
Largest Dow
I'm playing what we are released
Situation with Coronavirus
Actual number of
It's worth pointing out that what you saying
Claim to know
For a fact earlier
Opposite
The factor of 2 let's not worry about how they're using the math
It's twice as much it's the same basic
What is referencing
Statistics of how many more deaths have been reported in the week ending April 17th
Show me articles
351 registered in England
According to the office for National statistics
Comparable weekly data started in 1993
The past 50 years
The average
Comparable week from 20
15 to 2019 with 10,000
The conversation
Is being recorded in England and Wales
The total of 27000
Average bean
Between
April 7th
It's too premature to draw too many conclusions
The state up but it's
It's definitely notable
Further exploration
This article doesn't country-by-country
Just about to describe
Pineapple Times article the overall fatalities
During March and April across
14.
Foreign countries
Excess deaths in these countries
As compared to the average number of
That's during that time for
It was compared to the approximately 77,000
Unreported covid-19
Which they suggest
Good memes
Pretty low
They go on to suggest that if the same pattern of under-reported
18000 unreported covid
19.
So we're not capturing
Statistics
This again is something to eat
Further study
It's definitely hard to look at some of the day
Much higher number of deaths are in various places than the normal average
Numbers and even higher
Plus the official covid-19 count
And thick
Something's being mister
It's tough to explain
Requires further explanation
Account for the
Extreme
Politico
Desire that people would have her
For under report
A report
It does seem like
China food
Withholding information about that end
To downplay the severity of the threat
As though that isn't exactly
Prompted
At the same time
Sure
So the idea that these
These two battles
They I do these two governments are going to report things honestly
Utterly you can't believe it
It's simply not possible to
Maybe it is true maybe they are reporting it but
Believing it without
Absolute
Information seems
Ridiculous
Glass globe from May 3rd and it's Alex talking about
What is
The comments
More in this one really set me off
John Deere
I don't try to get up here and say Sensational things just to say it
Serious news
Like
Today's
I said I'm not going to eat people's children during class
Dominate my neighbors
Then I went on to explain on diapers
Dwayne Johnson
Swift
Allegory
People that came and found
Sojourn I'm sorry
What's an advance
Appointment
They were about to embark on today
And completely
Listen to the entire cannibalism
Neighbors
Instead of eating
Also at no point did he say you was doing a Swiss
Whatever he's pretending
In fact multiple times
So I was listening to
And I kind of realize that if we accept
It's essentially impossible to discern
Approximately
Total shift
We we different standpoint
It starts with him talking about how the Great Depression
Sufficient
Alex believes that face
Statistic about 7 million people starving in the Great
What is cleanliness
Declaration
3DS
There's clearly nothing more to the conversation of the beginning from this
He's cleared this is about his children not starving and whatnot
I'll kill humans to survive
It's conversation about how you
His neighbors and wondering if he would kill and eat them
And he's decided
He will
Possibly
A r
As opposed to realistic
Scenarios that may come to pass
Zerochan
Interpreted as any other kind of satire
There's just nothing
Nothing going on there other than
This goes on for about a minute and a half
That's why I want you
Dissection
Completely abandoned his hungry children
People is becoming specifically violent
Murder fantasies
Sprouts
Because they didn't accept
Christ
Clearly cannibalism
It's meant as a punishment
The instrument of punishment
During the section people for sustenance is
Wheatley forgot
He did forget that
From defensive to offensive
Very quickly
40 seconds later is children starving
He's eating his neighbor to feed his children and also
Just punishment
Says you
Physical
But it's not really
To get over the gym
So metaphysical hypothetical
Probably just means hypothetical
He's expressing that this is not
Pathetical
There was a modest proposal
It sounds like satire but it's not
Back brakes
Put this in a society like
David Foster Wallace
Somebody the performance
Considerably if he actually has some kind of attempt
Serious as everyone kills for food
14 most
Super cannibals
Something
Alex's world
He's using sources that are real to him and his audience to just
Society active
Place has kids
The entire section has to show them they're wrong about God is supposed to be
Which is not the mark of the master
Craftsman
30 seconds later Alex gets back
Punishment cannibalism
The spirit
Hookers out there drink
He said they will cut them into
Before watching his daughters
Which is weird because now
These two different
Context of eating people
Are getting mingle together weather
From this point
Nothing makes sense
Because it's two different
Discrete ideas that are being
Combine
Because neighbor for survival
These are not the same ideas
But they're being combined
So you think he'll barbecue your leftist ass so the kids won't start
This kind of only makes sense if his neighbor is
That's another Point as to why this isn't satire
Explicitly says that
Because you have a lot of storable food
If This truly was something that was meant to be swiftian satire
How does that element factor into it
They don't all have storage
Crisis
Talking about is already
Man in 2 years
Connected
A couple years down the road neighborhood
Nothing
Yeah that.
To help out people
Oh thank God
Understand them it's just like Bruce Lee Angie
Do you have
To attack while defending and defend well attack
That's the trick you're saving your daughter's life and you're punishing the global Assault
The same time
He realizes in the middle of his violent rant he smells storable food
So he needs a caveat
Call from my Patriot Supply
Disaster nutritional plan
What is a page field for them
You can kind of tell
What's going on
Closest to being what
Eastside
Before I leave I'm starving Africans
Before doing
Commercial Bank
Performance artist
Taken in the context of the show
Is MattyB a signifier that
He's not perform
Sardis
It began custody hearing a few years
Determined
Because
Alex got mad about that
And since then
You got really defensive
Some people say he's a performance artist
So when he goes to break saying something like that
Regular listeners know exactly what
About starving people in the developing World in Africa
Unrelated
Subway
Also what is living off starving Africans
Be interesting to hear that concept
Wrestle with
Fiscal arguments
Italo's nutritional assistance program
This a little bit more
People from developing nations he just wants them to starve on their own two feet
Cannibalism is really all about
I just realized when I listen to it as well
The speech
Is it really important
Pamphlet arguing
Politely that people should eat for children
No
Is intensely difficult because it requires a Precision that most people aren't
Capable of
And you can definitely count Alex
Serious
Set the right-wing even knows the word satire because they are incapable of it
And yet they
I keep trying to use it as they know it is
Memes
You guys don't have any
F****** clue
Satire is
It's fascinating
Bodies thing that you are incapable of understanding
In theory
If I wrote
Alex's ribs
As a satire of what
That would make sense
Because I would try to
Probably
I really do
Sit with us for a long time
Really trying to
Figure out a way to
Jason punch-up I really
Come up with
Coherent
That you Bridges
The Gap what he's trying to say
He's trying to say something
As aspect
He's talking about
He's trying to say that it's really just
Disingenuous opportunist
Satire
The 4th
Monday comes around
For however you crazy
It really bad
We start in familiar territory
Now let me get into this
Do this right now
Controversy
When I came out last Tuesday and I
Was going on with a fat tire
Irish children
Because the Irish were subhuman
Taking care of the Irish it was overtaxing another regulating they were starving to death
She said
How about we just start
Publish it like it was serious and it's the most famous in the world
30 + million starving to death right now 135 million
Then I shovel time once all the food runs out I'll just eat my liberal Neighbors
Pick it up
But they edited one minute
Attention to
Starvation
That's a catchphrase that Alex is trying
Episode
Pretty Clear Lake
Gyros
Proposals give badges
Is specifically control regulations as he was asking for the mark of the beast
Toradol
Proposal
As part of our public miseries
Tina
In 20 of those starving condition
Call the work of God either
But merely from their Oneida list
Yes. Cheating
Distain
For the poor
There's a really good book auntie Tracy
Violence and fancy suits
And one of the one of my favorite lines is when the main character just says
The rich always think they can starve
To the behavior
They want
And it's just such that
That kind of s***
If we just
F*** them over enough still do what
We say it
For whatever
Lakers
Recalls evil infestation suggest
British Aristocrat and 1729 or no 1737 or whatever
That was 70-37 from here
Silverline Toronto
Understand the underlying satire
Presentation
This is all just a
Pathetic Act of gaslighting
You can't keep the story alive
You saw good returns from it so you just begging
People to keep giving him that attention that he needs
Yep
Defensive about it
His attempt
To use this in some way
The developing world
The prop for his own purposes
He's cheaper
That
By virtue of
The way he's incorporating it is
Is pretend motivation behind
So very sensitive really when you get down to it
Before
Comes out and says we need to reopen the economy in order to help other countries I would give it a week
It's the way you make that
Cuz I really care but
Keys on the hook for like an hour
And he's kind of
You started making that same sort of
Yes we are
Spine
With distancing in clothes
Businesses
Because
We don't want to hurt other people
We're not scared we don't want to hurt other people
Make the argument
And getting sick
Is
For everyone
He kind of has that
$0.30
Because it's really
Boring and I don't really like
Alan Keyes
There's a sense of
Throughout
Interview
The first
There's very much
We got to get back
Got to go back to work
I think
Expressed is a real desire for this
To be over
And I think there is a
This feeling
That Alex and his gaster presenting
They seem to think
I don't know who those people are
Everybody
Wants this
Feel like this is
Basically like a bad
Acid when I was younger
Play some people have
What is pretty bad
Things that allowed
To not be so bad
And I talked to other people who done far more psychedelics and I have
Rings true with a number people I've spoken to
Is that
I recognize
But I taking a drug
And I accept
The terrible things that I was
And that this is going to end
Do you get into more trouble in situations like that
If you feel the need to
Argue and try and site
The ghosts that are
So what's going on is I think
You see these differ
Reactions to what is essentially
Inconvenience
Is an overwhelming inconvenience
Control
That's right out
It will
You can make it worse
Maybe
I don't know I don't know
Pharmacology
The same thing with the circumstances we find ourselves in
Everybody is having
Metaphorical
And you can either choose
This is
Just something
Is there is it
Through this
B
If you
The people who are fighting against
All of this like Alex
Existing we need to go back to
Work prematurely and all this
People who are fighting at are going to make are all worse
Inconvenience
B
Their problems
Are being sought
By actions people like our
Just thought that I had
I couldn't shake it
I think we're in a situation where we have
To recognize that
Height has nothing to do with whether or not you're an
We continue to treat these people as though they're adult
And they are not
We we do not want
You don't want to argue with these people you would do they need a daycare
They need somebody who knows how to
Deal with children
Because I also need to eliminate Financial incentives
I mean it's it's just so
So take this
Necessary for it to be over
King ants
I got some magical thinking that we're dealing with
It's just like
If we say it's over that it will be over
Recognize that
Cooperates and goes along with things measures that we've been
That there's a good chance
That eventually we will get through this
The doctors will make some break
A cruise that are able to maybe it is a vaccine
And that is a nightmare for them
Because
The possibility that doctors
The evil people in there
End up being able to
Return to more of a normal State of Affairs
Totally against
Everything
So I think there's
Hoping to Sabbath
Yeah if the government
Is the solution than that the reputation of everything they've ever believe
Sprite
Even if it's the worst government in history
Even if it's a government
Is the reason that we get through that job
And everything that I ever believed about
F******
Whatever
Yep and they would rather die
Exactly the case
Noticed
Because I thought it was maybe a little bit ghost
Abet on-air and
Alex
And it's interesting
His interpretation
This is
Covid-19
When I'm in this new studio
Because
Watching the show last night Sunday shows you like
When I come in here baby
But it just makes my
Bixby coffee
Condition
For lookup
Something something going on
Is trying to put in place
Possible
In case he ends up getting covid-19
Because certainly
Pics of it
Open everything up rallies and then
Ends up getting sick
No no
Put something in the air
Or whatever
Cuz he brought it up
And from my understanding
That feels to me like
Preemptive
Just in case
Astorian place in KC
Maybe they should call it mole
Okay go on are sure he's hospitalized for a few days
So he gets to talkin about
To get surgery about it but he can't because I need be off air
Couldn't talk for a few days
There's not a plug there's a plug
121 Clinton
Website last night
How much you got
I guarantee you got to get that check
Do you have protein
No I have not had a checkup since I was
And I definitely got a lot of
Very very cheap
This is my voice and it does need a good rest
Some point
But I told him I do apologize
Able to talk
I had two polyps removed and then my voice would be a lot better
But I do think I do a check
Got the guys eat is going from Hobby birthday
Weather tone
The Shining like rocks being put into a blender
Tramadol
Lot of folks like my voice I
Proceed
Exacerbated
With whatever is in this room
Palate cleanser while I'm here
This
Just a plug for his lungs
Cleanse
Nobody's probably worried that they'll call it covid-19 and kill it for Sunday
Infowars website
That's wolf
Yeah probably I don't want to go to that hospital
What is an interview
Monkeys
Important
Also the second hour of the show
Is almost entirely and it's
Tower of David Icke being interviewed on that London real show
They did their third interview series or whatever
Stupid
Simultaneously which is literally
Those dudes got to get those clicks doesn't matter
Expressing
Enough
Prophet
Again this is an interviewer is arguing that there actually is norovirus
Which is an absolute
Everything
Claiming to know just
Promoted
Issue with the things David
Deconstructing how
He's wrong
If you're listening to Alex's show
The virus is completely made up
Alex tries to get around this glaring problem
Stuff like this
Ninety-nine percent of what he saying
Other than just any virus at all know they
Viruses
Opinion
Exclaims that all the things he's covered about the coronavirus are proven
Position should be that Ike is
Raw
Tony Show recently
About this
Concepta
About the virus
That hasn't happened
Another good reason as to why
Alex isn't concerned with
Because if he was
Either convince Dyke
It would.
To convince
Which weather
Really
Neither of these outcomes are good for business
His position in the market
It's because he's staked
Demonstrable
Conversely if Alex
To convince
Delusional
Alex can't Co-op the attention David Icke
Is getting for making these insane claim
Each of these possibilities
Whether or not there is a virus should be a foundational primary disagreement between them
Wichita
To be resolved before you can get into anything
Coronavirus
Conspiracy Alex
Immediately
It's not disagreement
It should be things that Alex knows
David Icke is wrong
If you cared at all that convey information
He would have corrected like about this when he was on the show
That blows up again
Punt
And gives lip service to disagree about that
Phrases
All the negative attention
Disabled
Getting right now
Call Max
Somebody's are outcomes
And not do anything that ruins one of our ability
The grit
Yep
Steve
Ultimate side effect of that is also
Beneficial to them witches destroying
Any trust in anything
Islam even the p
People you trust
Have
A completely fundamental disagreement
Did nothing matter
Lee conference
Francis Boyle on the show on Sunday
Report on Monday Alex
Has David virus
I disagree with that little
It's just the shows dumb
The level of Groundhog Day
It happened yesterday has any effect on today
There's no narrative
Consistent something every single day there's a new thing that is like
That's probably not
Because Trump is president
And so it is
It can impact
Morbid
Yeah I think it's
Stop and
Disappointed
An hour of David Icke an hour of Alan Keyes
That's like nothing
For me I don't I don't care at all
It seems like he's
Really trying
To keep the cannibalism story alive
Because
It's his best play
It's not the only reason
Isn't doing anything
It's because everybody saw that Clipper more like
That is a
Genuine moment of a man saying that he's going to eat
And so everything
Manufacturer
Assuage
Watch
Else you can do like I keep saying as whatever he does stuff like this like I don't know what the
Outburst
Yes
Public's attention
Is now at the level of our neighbors
If you said something like
I'll beat up a stranger
Nothing I just got to buy a rocket
Something like that something big something stupid
Flash
Because you can't
I know he bought a tank but that was
I don't know the strategy for attention is moving forward
Actually eat his neighbor
Maybe try and settle the Sandy Hook lawsuit
Actually eating your neighbor at this
Rightmove
Decided
Represent himself
In the Sandy Hook case
To do
God
Disaster
Absolutely
I guess
Next episode from firework
Because
Point that Monday's episode
At least the news has broken that Norm had left
So the
Some of that stuff
Precinct 4
Frustration towards the middle of the
This week
Probably going to end up seeing
Some Mass
So I'm
Sticking around
Cannibalism
Cuz I am
Brings it up again
I'm not going to discuss it I said
And I'm sorry if anybody
Is is
You've said everything that needed to be said in a little bit more
For good measure
We are also on Facebook
That would be very
Until then
Nope
Trying to make a pond of Taylor Jonathan Swift
Jonathan Taylor Thomas
I can't do it
Hey why what
Alex
First-time caller message saying I love your work