Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
You and yours this is
Does the podcast where
We're couple dudes bike Smithtown
Nope cut it
I wished everyone happy Friday
Don't know anybody
Friday before they were very
Happy Friday happy Friday to you too we like to drink red wine and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
And what he is up to
Now in order to make
So people don't
Alex Jones
It is boring
Is there like a reason that it's you and me
Because I don't know anything about
What makes this Dynamic work
Let's just jump to our out-of-context drop coming to us
From deep in the past I found this clip
And it's hilarious
You are
The sperm count
That's right across the board
Super male vitality
Except so that was a
So I've mentioned that I'm going back and doing an in-depth investigation and Research into Alex's past
And sometimes episodes will not end up
Marrying an entire episode of our show
But something like that gets sad when we got it we got to tell the people everybody
Across the West
Tic-tac-toe info it is
Private eye
The show off with a slight correction
80s episode we talked about Alex claiming that they were monkeys
I would wires in their head getting brainwashed with television
For the screaming monkey
A wonderful bar made fun of the idea that there is all this stuff going on in
Texas
I did not research
I Googled Bastrop monkey
Monkey trials
With monkey in the title
And everything that came up
Was nothing
For this bar
They're pointed out that there is
What is going on in Bastrop
Through the University of Texas
There were chimpanzees
And other monkeys
Right but still
Don't work we're slightly wrong
But we were wrong to clown on it like we did cuz there was
Middle middle
No
It is complicated there was like vaccine research and stuff like that that that
The reality has caused monkey autism
The reality to though is that our country has a really bad track record with animal testing
So what's going on there
Isn't unbelievable
Describing
So it's like a we were wrong
We shouldn't have clowns
Maybe we should have landed this morning
Underneath
And we can all agree
That based on the fact that there was
Monkey research being done there
The name of that Tiki Bar is really shity
So
Hypothesize that it was
We are possible on a thing
With a a joke bar name
Anyway
Uber
That's that's not a great apology
This isn't really the message
I want to get to today or episode we're going to be talking about something happened on the Wednesday show
Which is May 17th
There was a continuation of the rest of the week
Which up till that point had been mostly
Bro downtime between Rodger Stone Alex Jones
Rodger Stone Mike cernovich soda filled in
I just
You know how that was sort of the theme of the week
Wednesday
In the back towards the third hour of the show something really really f***** up happen
That would be
What we talked about
For this episode
But because you asked
Meet before the show
And I did tweet out about this a bit
I want to
The cover
What he was doing on Thursday
Today as we record
On Thursday
Alex Jones
Higher
Joe
The entire show
Just talk about how cold
Is Buck
Jim Comey
Dead to rights
Busta
So as he would say
Metallic
Comey wrote this memo
Has been leaked
Disgust
This memo
What you got
Hard to get those words out
Tim or suggested
Should move on
From the flame
Investigation
Call Miro.
And then later
He was in front of
The Senate
Being questioned
And they asked him a question
And in his answer
He said that
Vietnam people have not asked him
To stop
You haven't been
Pressured
Now here's the important
If that was all
The information
How to have an interesting thing to go on
Misleading
For him to say I wasn't
Invalidate the memos
Called into question perjure himself when he was being
If
The most rational explanation
The reality isn't what I'm about to explain
If Alex's narrative is true
The most rational explanation
He is in the middle of a obstruction of justice building
So
Keyword
He would have to answer
Maui
Fortunately
Alex is using this clip
That I'm about to play
His evidence
They call me
Busted
Probably 15 to 20 time
On the show on Thursday
And scream
Your dad call me
Let's knock on the table
Yeah but he didn't
Going
I will I will like
At work
Run around in a circle screaming
He does Shuffle papers around
But here is the clip
And it is from his
Testimony
5 front of the
Maybe
You'll immediately be able to tell
Why Alex
To the f****** liar
And he knows it
Attorney General
Supposes
Investigation
Can they
In theory
As it
Because it would be a
Big deal
Tell the FBI to stop
Appropriate
We're often times
See a case there and soyou
Resources in it
I'm talking about a situation where we were told to stop
Political reasons
That would be a very big
So he says there is not happened in my experience
Now it's beginning really quick
Listen to the question that she asked
So is the attorney general senior officials at the D
Department of Justice
Does opposes
Investigation
All that
FBI
The Attorney General Department of Justice
Not
The president exactly
Specifically asking about
Yeah
Sessions being a dick to you
That question
Has nothing to do with what Trump
Knows that
Keep playing this clip
Knowing that people are not going to understand what question told me was asked
It's diesel bad propagate that you should cut that out
What the f*** it's so obvious he's lying
It's insane
It's such a desperation move that the only thing you're good at
I think it's because he's been lucky
A bunch of really dumb people in bigots basically created is
Iraq
Yeah he's never really had to work
So I think that's pretty much
What's going on
Excuse me
Who is it
I don't know
I was going to try and come up with a way to pretend that I was but I don't know
June from the jump on that one I'm telling you we got to take at least one
Who is it this is Alex Jones
Alex how are you would be Alex Jones because then he could have busted himself
What's up I was supposed to be like
Alex Jones hey it's me Alex Jones and then as soon as you say that
2 second beep and then we both say you're about to
Tony Todd
Who is it
Oh my God Alex Jones
I know
You're busted
I couldn't take that serious
Apparently
The day
Yes on Wednesday
He had like I said earlier was in the studio today
Smarmy a******
Love white dudes congratulating
Yeah oh my God.
Between crnkovich and Owen
Troy results
I want there to be some sexual tension between pjw and
Somebody
I don't care
He's a he's a faithful to Owen Shroyer needs
Love will do that well robbed need to go Paul Joseph Watson
Tell him stop taking Superman
So on Wednesday after all that gets done
Jerome corsi
Big news
Yeah right
The Washington bureau chief
Jerome corsi
Really needs to drop into Alex's lab
Play weird comparison
Basically says the Trump is a baby
This is so real and so sickening
Channel 10 times or whatever
I know he's real he cares about the country
I was just so crazy
So yeah he's got a battle plan
Baby Trump
To protect baby drop from the red-eyed rats surrounded
Moniker for Trump
Baby truck
So
I'm going to just go ahead and lay out
In front of you
Dealing with
Okay
Jerome corsi
Comes on to Infowars
And basically describes what Infowars does
Right now I'm guessing he does not say
Here is what we do
She says here's what the globalist
Are doing
Trump
And basically
Describes the Infowars
Modus operandi
Now on top of that
They know their own jobs right
His battle plan is essentially wage a propaganda campaign
Against
These globulus
Who are using propaganda against
There a propaganda
The counter propagate
A counter-counter propagate
But the thing that's scary about it is
We do.
The idea that they're bringing it out into the open
Suggest something really nefarious
Okay so so they're already
But now they're doing the Gambit of telling you what we're doing no
In order to live
I think
NetZero
Banking on
Most people who don't like them not hearing this
And people who
Them hearing it
And then they're in on it
Right
So it's like a wink
It's like oh we can get more people
Do you know where upfront about
Is Forza narrative
Okay no it's not now we're talkin we're recruiting the info
To be part of our propaganda
Campaign keeping them believing
Yeah
They're actively going
Leads me to believe the audience engagement
Hilarious
Later in the show
Clifford
Matter but Alex was on the phone
With a collar and the collar
Is maybe a minute into the colony like
Well you got some good points
I'll give you your own show
By the way we're still waiting for that f******
Daffy Duck
That rapper who called in
Who is Alex offered to give Advil
Malik
What is promises
No no if anybody ever won that animation contest
From 2014
The animating contest of Liberty
Do all of
Deposit policy walks we would like
Animation
So much already I really
Please don't
Make it anime
Corsi is going to lay out some of them will get to
I think we'll get to my thesis as this develops
Well I'm Alex what I'm doing
This is something I've been specially trained
Issue disinformation and propaganda
Who is the father
Relations
Responsible for the
Gerbils propaganda
Answer
The techniques that work and don't work when you're under just information propaganda technique
Do you know who's a great guy
The guy who trained
Or whatever
Google's was
Very specifically
Vocally
Inspired
By the work of Edward Bernays
Do you know about Edward Bernays
I don't know
His uncle was Sigmund Freud
But seriously
Why do they sell f*****-up news organization
Explaining fake news
And Coursey
Just said
We're going to spread disinformation
I was trained
I was trained by Edward Bernays
I know about these things
I'm trained in this
This is him trying to say like
Call Dad
Let your boy ride
That kind of thing
Also another thing that's going to develop
His Alex doesn't understand about conversation
You'll get the sense that Alex does not want to be there at all these dismissive is if he had a
Super male Vitality laced hamburger in his hand
Before we move on
Alright
His uncle was
Sigmund Freud
I can't
Confirm this
What's the temperature be like
If you haven't uncle
One of your
Their husband dies and he marries
Your aunt
Let the devil uncle
I believe
And uncle and uncle
Right so
Really
His double Ankh
I can tell really over play the relay
I listen to an interview with
His daughter
The other day in preparation
No contact with Sigmund Freud after he went back to
It's dubious how much of that was actually in itself a PR campaign
You clearly inspired by The Works of Freud propaganda
There's no part of what you
You say that I can
Evertrust
If you spread propaganda also his daughter was saying that
Throughout her whole life specifically made her feel stupid
And always would say that she was stupid
Which kind of fits into his worldview
This kind of this whole thing
Was
People as a whole
Are really stupid
And they live like pack
And they're just heard
Is it need to be ushered in different direction
How do I grill
Select group of really intelligent people
Who are the real
Power in the world who influence them for their own good
Globalist know basically gold for the people
He's arguing for a benevolent
Oligarchy
Somewhat
Somewhat but it but it's not really even an oligarchy cuz it is people like a advertise
Well
We're going to get to
The other problem is
The ivory propaganda
I've read his book
He's decidedly Pro propagate
He's not against
He felt a little bit
A little bit better I didn't realize that this could be a tool used for evil
In a lot of his public statements theme oblivious
Of the idea
That like
People
Cuz he basically cautify
In creative
The art of public relations
But what he would do
Is he
His main contribution cuz I never study doesn't college or anything but I
Some books on him and read his own books
Whooping is he would take people want
How you spy
Over glamorized
Giving something
Like attaching celebrities to a product
Pioneer that sort of thing
And then on top of that
Because you have celebrities
It would make it appear that there was this entwined
Elite Class
What is most famous for
Is getting women
Smoke
Do you know anything about this
Was this the one where it was like
Ton of
Medicinal you don't do it while you
You're pregnant
You should do it while your vacuum
You mean was it that
It's not
So he started working for the American Tobacco
Lucky Strikes
Who for the most part it's formally avoided smoking
The first
Smoke cigarettes instead of eating
By promoting the idea itself
Using photographers artist
Newspapers and magazines
Supermoto
Special Beauty in women
Medical authorities were found to promote
The choice of cigarettes over Suites
Homemakers
Keeping cigarettes on hand with a social necessity
When you're serving your
Who smokes sure I want to make sure that you got it
Yeah
Kind of shity
Lizbeth on evolve 90
1820s
So like
You attack it from a modern evolve
Viewpoint
But back then
It was just sort of like his Wild West everybody was just
The death of me
It's still shockingly horrible though
Fitness
So that kind of
Make sure that
The bet
But then there was still a taboo about women's
Smoking in public
So he had to create a cool new thing
In order to make it okay for women
So he gots
Actresses
And what he did is he told a bunch of
Reporters
That's
Suffragette
We're going
To start smoking
Freedom torture
As a symbol of their empowerment
I feel these reporters also the pay plants
In the parade
Start smoking
Through the parade
And it became this
Coupling
Of women's empowerment with smoking
And all of a sudden
It was it was
Cool for women to smoke and it was okay for them to do it in public
It works amazing he's an evil genius totally is this created a New Prague
Beyond chapter
And that is that Lucky Strike
Their packaging was green and red
A green with a very unfashionable color
The women didn't want to smoke Lucky Strikes they smoked other brands
Because green packaging would Clash with their attire
Animated videos
Didn't want to do it
So now bearnaise had to figure out what to do about this
Was he threw the stick called the green ball
We're here
And have them all wear green dresses
Manufacturers and retailers of clothing and accessories were advised of the excitement growing around the color green
Intellectuals highbrow talk
Actually taking place
Newspapers and magazines
Encouraged in various Ways by Bernays office
With all the rage
And all of a sudden everything was okay
People started buying Lucky Strikes
Women smoking in public
Everything was great
So now I'm
Completely on inside everybody's dumb they're pack animals f******
This is awful
No but this is going to be a real rollercoaster ride for you
What is what am I doing here
Why am I wearing clothes
Bernaise did like 60 years ago
Really fighting the good fight against propaganda
The Unabomber
Some truth to that
That was kind of like a fascinating competent
Story
Edward Bernays
Yes
Unfortunately as we mention
He also inspired
Gerbils
And then
The propaganda campaign was a huge part of it being able to succeed
Because without the propaganda
You wouldn't have gotten that bad
The powerlifter take a pool
Make make tons of pronoun
Nazi movies
Like that is a brilliant
A brilliant idea to do that and then he had a s*** ton
Critics I'm
I'm sure give them very positive
Reviews so that would influence me
Movies and then I'm
At the very least
To make sure she started
I don't know
Something that's a little bit more direct
About brene to blame him
For the Holocaust
People were just inspired by him
Company hired bearnaise
To try and get bananas
To be popular in America is like a really weird exotic
They are much more popular now
Chickasha
So we got to really better for you
Absolutely
So I
You tried a bunch of his normal tricks
Like placing bananas
Prominent places public
Consult like that
He tried to get celebrities to get onboard a yellow ball
It was quite working there was no progress being made
What they needed
Supernews also argued that United Fruit needed to put a positive spin on the banana growing
Countries themselves
And for this purpose
He created a front group called the middle American information Bureau
Which supplied
Information to journalists and academics
The mace
He has no expertise in Middle America
He had no reason to do this
That's pretty f*****-up
Getting paid $1,000 a year for days worked on the national press
And successfully drummed up coverage of Guatemala's communist Menace
Protect business interest
Boston Latin America
He's the reason that Guatemala became a Banana Republic
Oh yeah
Guatemala
Disabled Banana Republic
Probably don't know
Yeah yeah
So
1920s
Totally
Yeah so in
Harappa Bernie strategy
Distributed favorable articles
Report on Guatemala to every member of Congress
International opinion molders
They also published a weekly Guatemala newsletter 250 journalist
Someone who used it as a source for their reporting
In June 1954 the US Central Intelligence Agency affected
Named Operation success
Minimal military force
Fronted by Carlos Castillo
With the psychological Warfare campaign to portray military
Defeat as a foregone conclusion
Iraq
Iraq the entire
The entire the entire I know
Beat up to it to was heavily involved with
These Publications
And helping out
He gave people tours of Guatemala politicians and journalists alike
And all that in the heavily involved
And this is
Get a hundred thousand dollars
So as soon as Castillo armaf took power he began to jail is opponents killing many
Historians estimate the number of agricultural workers who killed to be in the thousands
Just a m
All political parties unions and peasant organizations were outlawed
The outlawed voting by Guatemala population
The Constitution
There were tons of attempted coups
Until they all failed 57
Elections were held following Castillo Armada
In which the Centrist Ortiz passarello
Wonderful reality
However
Supporters of
Miguel degorious
Who had been a candidate in the election
After which the Army seized power in an old the result and another election was held
Decorrius Fuentes won this election by
Comfortable margin
And soon after work
Soon afterwards after the Army invalidated the previous one
Crazy that the guy that they like
Soon afterward he declared a state of Siege and please Power
The by overthrowing
The former leader of Guatemala
This ended up undermining its own initial goal of the Guatemalan government
Historian Stephen Streeter is stated that
By installing the malleable Castillo Armada
President
So at the cost of Guatemala's democratic
Institution
Justin Bieber
Learned their lesson
Nope and never did that again
Sentence of this whole thing
The rolling back of the progressive policies in the previous civilian governments resulted in a series of
Distance urgency in the countryside beginning in 1960
This triggers a 36
Guatemalan civil war between the US military government
The frequently had a large degree of popular support
The Civil War ran from 1960
Costing the lives of 200,000
Civilian
Atrocities against civilians
93% of these violations were committed by the United States backed military
Including a genocide all scorched-earth campaign
Against the indigenous Maya population in the air
Hey you know what's great
We're the good guys
Around the world
Ethics that's what America does
I hate it when every Market prosperity
God dammit
I know it's dark
We're so evil
But the reason I went into all that explains
Is it was part of a propaganda campaign
Put on
Bananas
Orchestrated by Edward
This kind of massive Fallout
Now at the same time we can't relive gate history in know what would have happened if they hadn't
But it definitely wouldn't
There were there was
Trouble
Guatemala before but it wasn't nearly this severe
They had any other situation where that at has has occurred like I'm sure
Most of the Middle East has
Very popular with
Without are in a
Negative never overthrown the government
A religious
I'm sure we never did abolish the government
And cause another civil war
20 years now forever now I'm sure we've never created
Terrorist f****** groups around the world
Get this 73 Edward Bernays was hired
Try and make kumquat
Popular
This is what happened in Iran
You pick the funniest
I don't know if kumquats Duran
What a beautiful
His trick
That he uses
Are generally
Nefarious reasons
Propagandistic Lee
Even himself he makes the argument
Quickly
Neutral
What his one of his most famous arguments about it was that there was there was this famous
Who cut her hair really short and I became popular really short hair
Does it make a difference if
Influenced her to do that or she did it on her own
The end result is that women get short hair
Who cares if it was propaganda or not
Which is
Right so his argument is that propaganda is just
A control
Fat
The Kills 200,000
Billions + 36
Sears in Guatemala
But this is true
Every year
Hundreds of thousands of women died because their hair is
Did you not know that I didn't know that
Short hair
What causes heartburn
It makes
Ethically neutral
New conception of the world there's all these people were being influence
Essentially
Utopian
Is
Good propaganda force is doing battle with evil propaganda forces
And then these two competing forces of liars
Who tried to
Oh great I'm really glad that that
Man
He is so right
Evil
Like that is kind of what we're living in right now he isn't eating propaganda
Totally
No no
Trained
Jerome corsi
Sweet like I can't find any degrees or anything that would match up but you did get into teaching
Later in his life
Baseball scores
Course he's like 70 so they're timeline
One year before the end of the Civil War
Yeah it's
Sweet
You look 100
32 I give a
You made it
Stop to the blood of every Guatemalan child that died
You better say that that sounds to Alex Jones
Do the hundreds of thousands
Directly responsible for a lot of
Really f***** up
Also indirectly responsible for
The most
He's a really interesting dude though if you look into him
It's hard to
Hard to say if he understood the power he was mess
Yoda meme
It's difficult to know if he had any conception of
The technique that he was laying out
How much damage
They would do to the world if you just consider advertising
Feeling like they need to buy things they don't need
And it's also you know
Saw a lot of this stuff is kind of inevitable someone would have figured this out eventually
We live in our time
But
Oppenheimer
What's so wrong
He said I am become death to
Destroyer world
F****** bearnaise
Is single-handedly responsible for more deaths
Then the nuclear bomb
Yeah probably
The cancer is
And all the
This is all his fault
Pictures of
Cool women smoking
When I was younger I want to be cool like that
Yeah well I was a big fan of
Casablanca
Frankly I don't give a damn
Laura movie
Forgot my rent
Let's get back to the drum course he's going to lay out what his
Plan B wants
Suggest for trumpet
It's been studied
Follow these rules
Now the first rule
Is that
Create
Russian collusion
Donald Trump
Numps
Repeated statements
Senator Feinstein
He goes on to like name more Senators that have said
Varying degrees of
There's no unclassified information that shows collusion
Signature Collision
All these
The same time
Did just going back to
The analysis of their just saying what they do
Create create
Snare you create a false reality or a map
A meme
I mailed mom from
Infowars all they do is they have created this false narrative that has no evidence
That's backing it up the entire idea of globalist are behind everything
Poison you
I've talked to doctors
I've done some research into this fluoride
Idea
And if
It's murky at best
The idea that's really terrible
Sure their campaign has also killed
They're saying that this Russian thing is a false reality
With lies
I am in the lack of Truth
Lack of proof
Is Infowars
Tire game
Every single thing that we can come up with that they talk about
George Soros is a Nazi collaborator
Of their false
Reality
This is external ization
This is
Projection
This is insane
So
You can
Schleich horses
Doesn't know that they're already doing this
Do you really think he doesn't know
No he absolutely knows
You're so bad
What would their new false reality be
But like he knows
Corsi is
Smarter than Alex
He's being a lot more
He's
Personally torpedo people the propaganda campaign
Nose
He knows
How serious
Right I think
OSHA
They're convenient
Oh s***
Special prosecutor
Relationship in the FBI
PID
Be fair about the Avenue
Is absurd
I think he knows
Either we got a pleb big guns
And if that means
That we have to kind of give up the game a little bit
About what we're doing
We have to take that risk
And hope the people who
Do a podcast about us don't notice I think that is what's going on this is
F****** desperation measures
Trying
Start a civil war
No that's the end games that that the endgame of that propaganda
Ways that propaganda campaign goes
Cuz he does actually spell it out
It's Dom
All he wanted was to sell bananas
Eddie cause a 30-year Civil War
To support Trump
Donald Trump wants
Is tax cuts for the rich
Donald Trump
What Trump wants
What else
Who wants to be the king Paul Ryan
Call Ryan egg
Exist but they don't support call Ryan create text
Temple results for Paul Ryan
Is there an arm of the right-wing propaganda
Actually an important thing that we need to
To clarify
Right just in
They're coincidentally gotten a little bit off base about and I want to clarify
Just because the world is so fun
F***** up now and where
It kind of gets the point we talked a lot about
Trump and we talked a lot about Ryan being an a****** and we can talk about Chase
And we should
In some fashion or another
But at the end of the day this podcast is about Infowars and Alex Jones
Right
They're not really Republican
They hate Paul Ryan
Does he takes money from
George Soros and they think he's a globe
Alex Jones to his credit
Hated George Bush to
So like
He has
Not consistent
Not strictly Republican
He is
Other
Problem
That I want to address more
I need this podcast
To be about
Look at
We still have the problem
We have right now
And that is
Is a media arm of a really dangerous movement
Now they can call it Patriots
They can call it we just want to bring country
Sure not they're doing
That's cold
There is really dangerous
Bigoted nationalism
Going all over the world
Yeah we can we can see it through
Before Rodgers of the world can see it through the pain
MC it in Putin
We can see it
Loved his
His weird tendrils
The rebel media
And that's who we're against
We're not against the Republicans even though we actually are also
We are also a
Podcast
That move
Yes that's
Really what we're worried about
Great
Our problem isn't it
We're not done
Well they're still going to put together their propaganda
This white National
And if
You get rid of trump
See this is why there's no other endgame
To their propaganda
Vendetta
Get rid of trump
We get rid of
Hopefully
Then
What's their reaction
Only be
This is a COO
There can be no other conclusion
Written themselves
Into a corner Network and Alex is
On the show basically getting to the point where he's directly
If
Trump goes
We have almost run out of nonviolent
Solutions
And so he is gearing up for that
But let's deal with that another time when it's
The main course
Unable to record this podcast because
For now
That's not what course is on that's not the Tippy's on yet
Deal with him
By his word
So he goes on in his next Clip 2
Explain propaganda campaigns
I have the nature of them and how you got to deal with
Circumstantial evidence
My information or the truth
That is a very important also related
Infowars
And that's what makes doing this podcast
Kind of a bummer
Because we can fully layout
Document be like no this is absolutely not the truth
Things like whiteboard
Or even just will be played at the beginning of the episode The Comey thing
No I was I was hoping you were
Now we have to research
Measuring dicks
Bush research hey Mike, come from the screaming monkey I don't know where the truth
True
All three
That is the nature of trying
We can prove the wrong until we're blue in the face it doesn't matter
Is clowning on it
I just I just
I have a hard time believing that
I guess it's just
Because I
Somehow
I'm kind of
Hope in humanity
Times Daily
If you can
If you confront somebody's beliefs
With the
The truth that they
Doesn't fit
Within their beliefs
Accepting the truth
And expanding
They instead double down on the b******* that they both
Yeah yeah
That can't
Be everybody
There is a percentage of
Who will accept that
And that's what I think
We are going for
Just like just like with Trump voters
Percent of the
Polls
Will always be for
You're not going to get
Yeah
Used to be
A Tuesday
To be hired
So the idea is that pee
People are unable
To learn from something
Thing that
Contradicts their core beliefs
I can't believe is
Is universal
Over
Throat
Election
Like I imagined we really get just
5% of
People who voted
For Trump
Get out and vote for
For somebody else
That is
The presidential election overthrown
How many republican
Governor
How many republican congressmen
How many of all of the
People go away
Because the
The margins are often times
Razor-thin
And now they are going to be even more
To the point where if you if the if we had a
Competent
Committed Democrat
Party
That actually was
A progressive
Progressive
I think there's a good chance that
Baywood
Overwhelmingly
Use that same Papa
Heelys message
But in a positive way and wind up getting over
I mean
Possible
I could come to pass
I don't think that's the problem again
You don't have to be a computer
No.
We got plans
So don't get disheartened like that just Bisquick
The word plant
Plantain
But
Navigate to the next
Alex
Jerome corsi is suggesting is that they start assassinating people's character
Which is real fun
Because even Jerome corsi
The more facts you a deuce
Right
I like
This is how like interviews don't work on Infowars
Whenever someone who actually knows Alex Jones is doing an interview with there's like
Let me get my words out because you're going to get yours out
Unless we're both talking about how great white
This is going to be a non-starter
No matter how many more facts you produce
He's not going to believe it
Your character interesting because you might
F****** sued you idiot
Which again we have to let me to bring that up they settled that lawsuit which Alex Jones said
On this I will stand
I will win
Less than a month later
He settles the lawsuit with Chobani yogurt
An issue is a public apology
It's been a day and a half
Has it been on the show it hasn't been on the show I was this close to calling in
Maybe tomorrow maybe
Google say if I do
I can't wait to see how quick that gets cut out of every project
No way
Dude if you even said the word Chobani you being f****** hung-up on immediately
I'm at Alex's scream about something I don't know
I'm saying I apologize
Right weight
No you have
That can't be
If that's not your whole
Right just to call in and have like a sound machine that just plays on this I will stand
Tukwila
That that's how we
Close at this podcast
Spent it Thursday today
Well what happened was
He lost against
Can't afford anymore
Giovanni which is why we lost
I didn't land at all
DoubleDown more on the idea that fact
What kind of pointless
Against these
False reality meme
And then
You'll see where he takes it
If you take a look
Dealing with it
Part of the conspiracy theory
The Russian collusion story
Attempts to prove this
Boost
Over this company
Is never going to report
So Adam rhymes with Jean
He even in his book
Rhymes with Jean
That's good of him is not read
He also hasn't read a whole lot pushes that narrative with me
Interview
Get off track
Then you're going to be
Have a two things
Hillary Clinton
To sell the uranium to Russia
Conspiracy we've been over this
It just it's not true
It's absolutely.
There's a write-up on knowledge.com you can find if you want to get the information
What about that
This other one
These shares by a company name
Juul invest
I'm sorry Jule Unlimited
So what happened was a 2011 podesta join the board of Jewel unlimited alternative fuel company
Gordon Massachusetts
With operations in New Mexico and the Netherlands
A few months after podesta took on this role and a totally true bias
Video of Russia backed investment fund rusnano
Also joined Jewels board
There doesn't appear to be anything untoward or illegal about the fact that podesta
On a corporate board with a Russian Banker
Nevertheless
Some of his and Clinton critics of plaited up
Conservative website The Daily Caller
Discloses
What are you doing the Obama Administration in 2014
In any case
The company is American
Not Russian
That is courtesy of PolitiFact
That has
Some good resources you can check out
PlayStation
Absolute nonsense
This idea that Jewel Unlimited
There's some sort of nefarious
Getting money from the Russians
You could interpret
Their name
To be Unlimited
But you know what
Corrupts absolutely
Do you know who searched
Edgar Winter
He wants a high or low
The globalists totally
How do you think he felt about apps
Corrupts absolutely
I don't know
Depression about
Degrade
My wrist game is off my wrist my wrist gun isn't firing right
Work
Against
This
False reality of the Russian
You're getting uranium
Podesta with this company
Conspiracy theorist
Because you're spouting bulshit that isn't reality
It's not going to work
It's not going to work against this false reality that is the Russians
Blackwell
Of course it's not going to work and the mainstream media isn't going to true
Peter verifiably
People have research them it's not blurry ignoring these things
If you say why isn't the Clinton sell Uranium on the front page of every paper it's because it's not true
People
Journalist had looked into it
It's not
Dumb old man
Anyway
Just because it's
So repetitive
It's just like
Choose a new one
No they can't
And you have to
Repeat it loudly
Because then it became
Bring up a false reality
Yeah
You want to make sure that
Even though what you're saying
Isn't true
It's a
Defied again
Echo
A people who are in
Like a herd
And they're easily influence
Buy a loud
Idiotic
Ideas of
People all agreeing based on
Social media
The only like
You have to
To be a full-on psychopath
To do this
What's the next clip
Was jumping
Crossword best-selling books
The ultimate propaganda weapon is truth
According to him
In case you haven't listened to other episodes
He's written
2 books
About how Obamas birth
A bunch of spurious
Provably untrue
Statements about his time in Vietnam
Not sure didn't really change the outcome
In the same way that in the same way that
Like
The opposite is true the most
Open is untrue
Go through it
So many pulls of Republicans
It's like 60% still don't believe that Obama
Quest
Look
You can ask
Just we're just looking for it
They could have faked that birds
He's from Hawaii that's not even real estate
So I will be Guatemala
Shut the
The fuk up
And we don't care if your people die
More about unfit
4 commands
Recently
I read this little tidbit
Answer controversial comments Republic website
Ozarka water
Claimed the course he was not actually a co-author of the book unfit for command
Simply an editor
Southern
Issues
About it
So he didn't write it
Probably not
It's like Tom Clancy
All over again
The theme of the book is that John Kerry's four-month tour in Vietnam have been marked by cowardice Under Fire and fraudulently a
Painting metal
In that regard the book contained statements by some Veterans of the Vietnam
Who starred with John Kerry on Swift boat
Several
Executed affidavit in support of their claim
These claims were repudiated by other veterans
To serve with Carrie and proven by outside sources
Including the Navy's official records
Oh boy
Buckhead
So the Ultimate Weapon is
Get to the next clip
This point this is the point where
Basically Kursi
Breaks down and advises
Actually start using
Propaganda
How do we deal with men total manufacturing false reality.
My fax
You're not going to Beat It by proving that it was wrong
Continue
Control
Capture the narrative
Take it out
So the first thing is really fun there is just like Alex does not understand what's being
He doesn't get it
Course he has to keep saying don't matter when you're up against
Spain facts don't matter
But you know what
You know what it is fascinating about
Suggested Alex
Is a True Believer
Yeah because he constantly says
You know the reason that were with
Is because we have
The truth the reason that is
Because we
Care about the
The truth we care about the
Like even if he does
Say that
He can't come out and support a propaganda
Because that destroys
Everything
Him being aware of it
Then this acetate him having
To be aware of what
Exactly
Interesting
And then if he's if he does become aware of that
He does participate in
In the propaganda
That means that either his listeners
Will Venable
The the propaganda
As they do right
But if they
Then what
What do you really believe
Right right really believe all the sudden the same stuff
They're saying now
But they're also telling you
That is true
And they're doing it for
Evil
Or for good
Perspective
Because otherwise yeah it does
It does call into question
What we've been listening to for 20 years
We'll get what can you what can you do
Narrative even if they say they're deliberately
They're still going to stay the same s***
So you have to dance
Resume
If you are at all
Conscious and self-aware
That then you have to
If you are a regular listener of Alex Jones you have to be like wait
This is what you said
2 weeks ago
Before you told us it was
Was the propaganda
You're saying it now
Campaign
So what was
Yeah but it's kind of it's kind of like his
Is wiser under child lock
You know what I mean like anyone
Who's smart enough to figure out how to unlock
The Box
Chose
3 a.m.
They
They've already unlocked box mankind of paradox
Kind of figure it out
Are going
Be like
Oh
Yeah that would only make them feel like they were now working on something
When you're stupid
Your boy do you love it when
People tell you you're
Yeah usually too dumb to realize you're not
If you will
Next
Discussion of trump
Has become.
The news
Then
Clipmaker
A really funny noise
Accidentally
It's real good
What is traffic right now
That the changes the narrative
That I have isolated just that really enjoy that
It's snowing bibelen
So I mean
I know it's it's kind of a clown on it for a little accidental noise
He's just like course he is
Just straight like Sweden to make that noise
Didgeridoo
David Mamet
Just trying to figure out how to make that pot
Liking it in reality with you
Corsi is the guesting
We need something
That will
Completely change the narrative
Whether or not it's manufactured
Narrative
A what's behind
Oh oh this is fake
And people are trying to Railroad him
It's a sphere sphere I believe
We can't stay on this narrative any longer
Yeah it's starting to unravel
Right I believe wholeheartedly that's what
Corsi realizes
We got to do some
Right
Maybe they are
Going to try and change the narrative
Because obviously they know
Hold on
Hold on has been on f****** Fox
News
Thing is real course he's going to get into it in this next clip
I want the article for tomorrow want to do this step-by-step so it's things been
When Trump
Everything about
Russia's stock
I do it
I knew
This is really a methodology I'm laying out the plan
So I read the article
Cuz it came out today
So the first thing in the article is he claims that the appointment of Robert Mueller is effectively changing
It's changing the story but it's not
If you have to pee
Pick somebody
With that kind of
Level of credential
Send
Interfere with his
Direct quotes from Jerome Court his article is not very well written
Wellbutrin May reach a conclusion this year there's no time limit placed on his special counsel investigation
Nor is there any restriction for Mueller examining whether the Democrats
Including Hillary
Were the politicians actually colluding with the Russians during the 26
16 campaign
That's a big new there is no
There is no there's no but there's nothing stopping him from investigating Mai Tai
Play by the way I mean also the drink Mai Tai
My Toys R Us
I didn't even catch that I was like wait why are you talking about this
You got it also the tie I'm using the belt right now
My belt broke
Hugo's
Love you
You might as well put up pulled out of karate belts
I'm from the stick
Entwine
Stream media just got bushwhack
Skillful
Who's the subject move
Engineered by President Trump's wife
True
Weights
Trump him
Is using the switch to Miller
Mueller yeah
As
Giving Trump some sort of 12 level dimensions
Genius
Right
No
Cuz cuz
Rosenstein viz Attorney General
30 minutes notice
Appointment
This was
Come out in that interview and said that this is ridiculous
Framing of a just completely absurd
So he goes on here's the other thing.
If they if the investigation Hilary of colluding with Russia
That would one
Feed the most
Wild
Out there every Night Shyamalan twist there's ever been
I'm for it
I'm fine with it too but it won't be about the uranium or the solar power company
They'll still Alex will still be wrong even if that's the outcome
Egos on imagine
Boner he would have on that episode super male vitality
Super male Vitality ever again it would just be with them
Never say that
Always need Supernova corsi's article goes on to list subways
But Trump
Can go ahead and change the narrative
And get people
Stop talking about the Russia stuff
First one is kind of diplomatically Base
Basically
Fix the Middle East
Cuz drop is about to go on his first out of Country tour
Around the article
Is it is the quote from the article
Beginning serious discussions in the Middle East between Israel and the Palestinian
Or getting Saudi Arabia to take Serious steps to
Control
As would be the articulation of a new balance of power structure in the Middle East
Military action in fh4 Russia agreed to contain a ram
None of those things are ever going to happen even remotely possible
To the Middle East
Six 1,000 make is really the Palestinians hog on camera
That's fine
We agree
Conception
Good call Ken execution impossible for me too if I was like
President of my lifetime
Accidentally
Propaganda effort
Fix the Middle East
Yeah
That would be
Is the polar opposite of causing the Guatemalan Civil War
Long
Thousand-Year fight
Religion that does seem to match the world we live in
So his other suggestions are not as good
Here's the next one
Wieczorek
Members announced plans making dramatic reductions
Enforce downsizing agencies
Like the EPA or Department of Education already doing
Meaning and or implementing Trump's various executive orders
Controversy
President Trump will force the Deep State and the mainstream media to shift Focus
From the Russian collusion meme
To attack each Doucette
Takes by executive order
Which is basically
Hey hey
Destroy the environment and everyone schools
That'll distract
But not enough education
Shinto
So I guess I'll be fine
Your car's not going to pass inspection
All right look
You don't have good brakes on
Here's what you do
Blow it up
Destroy the country
Good call
That I was last one is the worst
Okay this is really bad
Understand
Consider North Korea a developing nuclear threat President Trump
Listen to this paragraph
He's going to advocate for
Blowing up
North Korea
When cruise missiles are flying towards North Korea military bases
Korea's nuclear weapons capability
The American public will not be able to focus on the Democratic party's efforts to bring impeachment proceedings against President Trump
Because
Suspicions he colluded with Russia to steal the election from Hillary
Kosolapy on fire instead of like okay
You can
Fix the Middle East
Right you can set your own car on fire
You can blow up that cop car that's about to stop you
Car cuz it's like it's someone else
Whose car
100 buses full of kids
Basically cuz it's just
The consequence of us
Attacking North Korea is
South Korea is
Phuc yea it's gone
Whatever differences we put in there
But it's not enough
20 miles away
Corsi's whole articles
Just full of
Bad ideas
Really bad eye
One of them
Would change the narrative completely
The other two will either lead
Horrible climate change
Asterisk
Stupid children
Radar country of millions of people in South Korea
Depending on
Inevitable start of a
Possible
We would get to the
Billion mark
Responsible
We don't know the full extent
North Korea's
Capabilities
We don't have good Intelligence on them
Because what they do
About security
Yeah it's
We don't really know the extent of what they've gotten
And we get some information
Oceanfront
Full out with the
So whenever they shoot missiles and they go into the water
Whatever
That doesn't mean that that's all they've got
True
Those are those are more
Would be like
Well I mean what they really ours
To continue presenting themselves
A very small if you're in Jurassic Park
They're the dinosaur that Puffs out its neck and Spence
And spit all over Newman
Very historically inaccurate
And now we're back on the
Hope you all have a good Friday now you're Lost Woods warrants
His article
That's the whole thing
There's a little
If me and if he just went Whole Hog on any and every idea
Here's what I could do
Bring universal healthcare
Hey here's what he could do make Africa part of the United States
Solve every problem
What's the weather like
Here's what he could do
Discovered unicorn
Yeah it's I mean it's as
Useful as that article
Assertive
That's kind of where I'm at as far as it goes
You
You spent the entire f
Episode up to this
I just waiting for that
On the Fly
What was on the floor
I don't
I don't suppose your battery
Meet
Clip
It just feels like Alex doesn't have
Music I know I invited you on my show
Cernovich is on hold
We have fun
Horsey you're a bummer
Kilbourne is s***
Even boars hours
It's clearly it just feels like he's like
I want to hang up on you
Wish
I wish I could hang up on
Business has been proven state department is done
Is it proven by the experts to the CIA
I studied it for 30-40 years
Depressed
It sometime to reorganize the government
And take control over sometime tomorrow
Leave me alone
Forget it
You're torturing me it gets worse
What make you had of a bureau
It's important
The purpose of this
Is a deep state
Hitler
Eugenics
But that like if you made into a
Cosmology
That's the Gamble
That lie
Is advocating like here's what we need
Creates
That gets out of Arkham
Control
And causes a
He's doing is playing
This argument is being put forth
Trump is involved with the Russian
Is on par
With demonizing the Jews
I believe so
Okay I'm going back and give a new at-bat
If using the same
Right
Which
I don't know if that's fair
Doesn't
So whatever I listen to
Play on audio
But you could just be in Alex's face
He was
Grateful
Not so the more I listen
Listen to the more I listen to
The more of that idea of
Competing property
Doesn't act
At least
Because
We're we're using those same
Like his show is
Yeah his show is wildly entertaining
If you are into that
It's
It's a consistent
Spelling of narrative
As as if you were to bunking
Constantly his idea is
They're spinning the false narrative so I'm going
With my wild outlandish
Just repeat them over and over again
What we're trying to do
Is create
Bu
Same effect
Tube that propaganda disagree we're creating a real real
Disagree
Disagree to creating a false reality we are creating a real reality like that is playing into this
I disagree with that I just want to have
Spun
AutoZone have a good time
I'll have fun
Oarfish
I disagree with that because
To create
Any reality
I'm not
Even
Necessarily
Defend
Someone else
His version of reality
Lake
What if we have listeners who are conservatives
I don't give a s***
Believer
Breadwinners who were Libertarians
Some of your ideas
Go ahead
Whatever
I don't I don't care about building people's reality
I believe
F****** stupid s***
I kind of believe in Atlanta
I don't care if I understand pink makes good music
You understand like all I all I'm interested in as much as the show
Propaganda campaign
I hate Alex Jones and I hate the movement
I mean that
It is it does seem to me that the
The main weight
To fight against
Is by
Making some
Something that is as entertaining
Now you sound like horsey
Just fact
Damn
Witch Hunters
Split right now my dick is
So this next clip again just whatever you saying
I feel about Infowars
It's interesting because
They fully
Describe what it would be like to argue with them
First of all you're not going to defeat this false
Untrue
It's killing me
It just reinforces
And that's right around
Work Remix
That's pretty much what you do
Like whiskey
2. and not getting
Projecting really hard
Yeah cuz he's like once we start arguing we lose
And then Alex
Yeah we argue all the time
Yeah every lose
So it's it's
This is more revealing about Alex
Is idea of how
How to
Fight against
Then Coursey Coursey is trying to
To pull this kind of course
Is Gold's Gym
Call people
He just wants to
You just want to have fun he's like the damn freezing of
Ministry were both the boss
I don't know about that
My McAdoo
Now we're getting into the sexual tension
That's what we really want
So this
Next clip
Course he gives a little bit of a preview.
Bye and I spelled out already
Came out was about until
Kind of touches on
Stuff a little bit
Steps
Which would change the subject
And you got one coming
Was going to be a major Foreign Traffic
Buckeye cut too early
Owen Shroyer
Been sitting there
I was almost like he was going to say like maybe because
Obama got rid of
I mean they are probably
The preview theories didn't really let him talk with
Not interested in his
Get on to talk about how the media
The story
And that
Once he suddenly got in 5060 days
Then suddenly he stopped leaving
With the propaganda
You're not going to win on that
They're going to win
Is a complete lie
Is total propaganda
Fear of argument that the Russian collusion argument fits into
You can't beat it with facts
Nope I mean he's he's absolutely right
Could you don't
You don't have any
Sfax
With facts
The facts are not on your
Super unfair rhetorically
To be like
The Who
Like trying to kill millions of Jews
You're shaking your head
Giving 44,000
Email
I want it I want to talk about this a little bit
We talked about this the other day
Emails then
People who will
Only 144,000 are going to get home
Exactly what I wanted to go so
Seth Rich was DNC staffer who got murdered
Late night
The one
Home Fox News
F*** everything up yet again
We're going to get into that back in the day
What month back when the murder actually happened
Black conservative
Conspiracy message boards
And a lot of people were using the murder as
Conspiracy theory
They were saying because
Stumbled into evidence
That the Russians
Working in
20 conspiracy
Then got repurposed
He was the one who is
Leaking emails WikiLeaks
Stolen the podesta
The emails and what have you
And
Even Julian Assange
Hinted
He is the source
But it never said that he
Because he wasn't
But Julian Assange is
Committing a
The propaganda by going out and saying
And we never divulge our sources because sometimes they get murdered on the streets where I was sort of like little
Little turtles
So now recent
Couple days back
Fox News got into the game
It took that conspiracy theory that it already existed in the nether regions of the internet
Animated main screen
Pushing it really hard
When they had a guy named a Rottweiler
Be on Fox News
He was a private message
The gator that's how they built
But the reality is is he's a Fox News contributor
He's also sucks
Also moonlights as a private investigator but they
That he was the family
He's private
That was
Not
Bulshit to investigate
I don't remember I'm not sure that it's all that important
But I
Set up any red flags
I did see the name
Cuz it's secondary to what the main story
And that is what he went on
Fox
And I quote
My investigation up to this point shows that there's some degree of email exchange
Between separation Wiki
I do believe
The answers to who murdered Seth rich
Sits on his
Computer on a Shelf
The DC police or FBI headquarters
However
Anna Stubbs
Rod wheeler said
He had no personal knowledge of riches email
And I quote
I don't even know where the computers are
He went on to say that he got the information
Interview from a Fox news reporter
Jesus f***
He was
Just repeating stuff that he was told on
He's just fed that s*** here's what we want you to say you're on Fox News
You're going to say what we tell you to
If you ever want to come back on
TV again
You say what we tell you to
And they put
Vista
Year of unsubstantiated claims
Do you know facts
We see no evidence
We've been approached with no emails and only learned about this when contacted by the Press
We Are Family
Not fake evidence
The surfaces every few months to fill the void
And distract lawn forcement and the General Public
I'm finding stuff murderer
Now Dustin sternbeck the Chiefs books
Coming for the DC police
Force
Set this
Quote there is nothing we can find that any of this is accurate
Sad Dustin
Spokesman
Which is leading the investigation into Richard's death
He would refuse to be more specific
FBI spokesman
Think the agency is not
And referred questions
DC police
Law enforcement officials have said that
Computer email activity
And nothing
Suggest that we connected
Which
Publish 20000 emails that embarrassed
Secretary of State Hillary Clinton
Have the DNC and force the ouster of
So
They look he was involved in any way the thing that ever
Narrative
Who is that he was murdered
In what appeared to be a
Street confrontation
In the middle of the night
But he wasn't wrong
And the reason that that
I mean that's weird
It's not that weird is if you're in the middle of a robbery and it goes bad and you accidentally kill somebody
You're not going to vent aches
You're going to just leave
You're going to least
Run
Especially if you're not
A hardened murderer conspiracy
Jerome corsi killed
Don't do that
Bringing up complete horseshit
Evidence of
Whatever
No this is Vince Foster
Yeah absolutely absolutely
It is suspicious that he died
It's okay
So you should investigate
And when you investigated
You should find only what you want to fight
30 years in
They haven't
F****** around with Hillary Clinton
When they got to
He was going to blow the whistle
My aunt still thing
That's why
Smartflow
It's wife
Describe there is f******
Drug
Crimes or anything
Chirp
Just like
Yeah we have evidence about it
If you're going to take a plea deal even though you're not
Because because
You know we don't know everything
I can't sit here and tell you with a hundred percent certainty that reached
But I can save it
Every piece of
Conformable
So I'm inclined to believe that
And
Hymen
Inclined to believe that those left-leaning
Conspiracy theorist
For disrespecting his death when they were making that argument
Absolutely
Disgrace
They're horrible
Sickens me
I mean
Just wanted to
Propaganda baby
Really is it is
It's such a weird coincidence that it happened
That it happened
Now and then
Or what they are officially now that we have this guy another we have this this
Russian
Going on
Which a lot of it will turn out to be
True
But there is still that kind of red fear that
It's still been hanging around
The Cold War of course if we're investigating a Russian
Thai
And somebody
Tertiary involved
Dies
Then you're going to get there
If you want to
Connection even if there's no evidence
Even if there's no point
You're just going to eat your brain is just
Go there especially if you have propaganda
Siri on Julian Assange
Is
I don't think
He started out
As the evil prep
No
She started out as the holy war
He started out as
Is this like
I want to do good
For the world that's why Chelsea Manning
Did so much good for
And I'm really happy
Everybody May 7th
Cheapest Chelsea Manning
But
All of the hate
From the United
And all the
Request for extradition in like
All of this
Is just really kind of like hey
You revealed we are evil
So we're going to do our best to demonize
Put you in prison for it like we do
Did Chelsea Manning
So then he's in the embassy
Trapped
Getting more and more hate-filled and losing his mind
Now but I think
I think that's
Already had that right before I already I
Think that your premise but he started out with good intentions is probably true
Then the same way that like I
I blurted out I think Alex probably did too
But I
I don't think it's as simple as you cooped up in a room and he turns super villain
I think there's negative parts of himself
Through either
I don't know man if you've been put in solitary confinement you lose your mind
Don't matter if
It doesn't matter if you've got a couch
If you're in solitary confinement your brain is going to melt
Dalton solitary can
He's basically
F****** farraj comes in
The Visitor
Nevermind I hate him
Sandwich
Stereo
Isaac I retract that I have
I think there's negative pieces of
These characters
The Julian Assange is in the Alex Jones that weather through ego stroking or
Direct
Compromising
They've changed
From their initial goal of doing good
Into
Holding a line carrying a narrative
Yeah
I will absolutely
Julian Assange is not a megalomaniacal
Lunatic
Your complex
So this next
Just really
Pleasures out that Alex Jones
Not get
The conversation there have
And also the
Jerome corsi
So what of all the things are what are the true narrative
Alex
There's no argument
Is it going to be
Argument
Real dinosaur
We're fighting
The Holocaust music
It is gone now it's got to be stopped by techniques and find out
Military
You do not understand
Bugattis bombs
It kind of does
Make your argument stronger
Willfully not getting it
Cuz it does portray him as possibly understand propaganda
He can and Mike or self-defense mechanism because he comes
Exactly what he wants to talk about
Course he wants
Come in with a battle plan
Rat conceivably they haven't done show prep
Cuz I never do rightly comes in
He starts
Oh
You think so
No probably not
I think this is innocent
I think Alex
Really is
A simple idiot
That doesn't know
He is
He doesn't know when he
He's lying
I do think
He doesn't see himself as a propaganda
Take that as a
An insult
If you called him a proper
So Jerome corsi is basically saying
Invalidate
All the stuff
You believe in
And now engaged
In propaganda
Maybe yourself
It's not all the stuff
Text to generator
In in yourself
Where you're coming from but I think
Let's do generous
The lesson
On this episode
Let's get the
It's just
Isn't it
First of all trumps not good
He cannot lie
And will not hear
And secondly
Thirdly this point
Your plan sucks
Just the plan of a propaganda campaign is good
In terms of like
Yeah
Millions of listeners that seems to be pretty effective
But all of your s*** on
In your article is not good it's not good propaganda
Bombing North Korea would be really disaster
It would get off of the Russian narrative but it would get back to it
It would only be a distraction for a temporary
So much.
Fixing the Middle East
Is not a reasonable goal
It's not something Trump
Can do you know what butt Trump
Okay trumpkin dream of fish
Destroying the schools in the environment will get him attack
Attack
In addition
Do the Russian stuff
He's already doing it like a
What's what's
Grant the loan forgiven
When is program at least she's trying to destroy everything
Food
They don't don't stop
No
Stop calling her
That's how you change the narrative
I'm very conflicted because I miss episode you
Pic pics Alex
Very sympathetic light
Sympathetic at all
I think I'm calling him
Dumb
Sympathetic compared to
Like
Compare bearnaise
Well I guess it's
But like
They're giving up
Some of their cards
And the only reason that they would do that
Is
Desperation
Oh absolutely
I think this is a really bad sign for Infowars
And another really bad sign
Alex has just launched
Product
Unceremoniously
Oh no usually whenever you launches a product like you has doctor group come in for an hour and they talk about how great this new meta
Yeah but now like
Within the span of sensor last episode
He's got a new thing that helps you jump your car
Is that a product that helps you generate ever your car you just stick it in and jump
I don't know I don't know
I don't know is it is it just like a repurposed
February
I have no idea
It's insane
Computer and then
I meant he's also come out with a product is like mouthwash has a line of mouthwash and shampoo and stuff like that
Gotten into toiletries
Because I think you started to like a f*** people are buying my weird silver
Items
We have to go more mainstream with
Right
You're going to buy all this stuff anyway from us
Buy it from us
Squeeze
Get on a subscription
Program
Where comes automatically every
You're in trouble
This is falling apart
You're trying to get all these
These like
I want a slug into the whole I want to see
Herbalife
Commercial sober
Alex
Northern Aether waterfall
Every magazine
So yeah I mean I just think all of this rings
Smells like desperation
It sound
Bad
We'll see what happens
If you watch Fox News one thing that I've noticed
In the past
Is that
They're pulling a lot of the
Like they're pulling
Pulling like pulling all of this
Look at what Hillary did don't look at it don't look a
Don't look at all this s*** we're going to
We're going to do an interview with f******
Ted Nugent
Fresh
Yeah
Which is the biggest sign
Used to hang their hat on
Pretending to be
Do you know what it is it's a landslide that Scott happening corporate conservative news is now
Flipping down
Hosting the shows that are going to get them
Kicked off the air
Then at the same time because it is a
Complete Landslide on the right
Where Alex was
Where
Fox News is now has flipped down
Let's start an actual property
And you know what they are on the Vanguard
Yeah that is
Is there were a few
Like ratings
Evaluation
And
It's starting to
Too because Fox News used to be Far and Away the most highly-rated
Sure
News
Exactly
The highly-rated Bulge
The truck stuff is
Started
It's actually been more CNN
And NBC in the light
MSN
Because
Because Fox News is
Blatantly
Ignoring
Every possible app
They are not dealing with
Anything so
Attention Lisa
To the point of they are
I mean bald-faced
Running a propaganda
Yeah like they might as well be talking to Jerome corsi and I'm sure that the next
Sting on Fox News is going to be like
Will trump bring pizza the Middle East by going to Saudi Arabia
Pulitzer prize-winning author of course
So also I agree it's a mess
But before we get out of here I want to give an update
A week and a half ago
Alex had as his guest this weirdo from New Orleans
Who rides around on a bike with
The TV behind him
Infowars
Okay
I want Alex
Taken out
My son was brainwashed
So you don't understand
This guy is
About like
Free speech
He puts out this video
And all this
So this guy
Don't talk about
Until you talk about all the Falcons
Put it on YouTube
Start a GoFundMe
Is Infowars
Can we get a knowledge fight wagon
Ice cream truck
Maybe I'm in
Pictures of Jordan
Is 10 a fever
Reviews on the show and he's trying to raise $30,000
Jamaican
Info wagon
Right
So I've been keeping track
Massive audio
Write 80 million a week
Millions an hour 45
This GoFundMe campaign was started on May 10th
What guess how much they have now of the 30,000
Million hundred 450
A first time I've got something even remotely close
That's crazy you have no motivation
Well yeah of course I do
So
F*** the info wagon
You know this great knowledge might.com our website
That's true girl so you can follow us on Twitter knowledge
Email us at the knowledge fight at gmail.com
Has no mother really likes
Send an emails and directed
That's awesome unlike unlike Alex Jones we like to learn things and you can only learn things when you're wrong
Stroope please also we can
But I would appreciate it I'll review
Give us a rating
It's cool and fun and validates us
To pick a date
Where in Alex Jones episodes will be discussed
Feel free to donate $10 to the
Where can you find
Just waiting on knowledge fights, we can check it out if you want to give any amount
You choose whatever you want to do
Any amount makes you a policy walking become a policy
Yes that's true
But you know what Rodger Ailes
Dad
Rodger Ailes still dead
Rapoport
Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color