Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for knowledge
B b
Chicken
Knowledge fight
Sit around and talk just tiny little
Jordan
Today
And I love it
Expression for a length of time a cup of coffee
GTA use at the Dodgers for a cup of coffee if you moved over to the gate
Think about it a tug and everytime I smile
I don't know why
Adventure Time
Call Michael Coronavirus
7 seasons in Lancaster
Fantastic 10 minutes right love it
SoundCloud
Alex
Episode
Be content just to the 5th and the 6th
This was only in studio for the first hour of the six
Jumped off air to take care of other business sounds like
Let's check in on the 7th
And check in on the year of the Seltzer so first
Thank you Karen
Mitch
Henry
I was going to say that
Text Julian Vegas
Something untoward
It's not a horrible reference to something
Thank you so much and I apologize walk
Crazy crazy
Reagan
We got to go Full Tilt Boogie on this watching all right
Heroin
Ida Claire
Yes we would appreciate but apologies we are
We're trying to find the best ways to get closer to current but it is a hassle
I don't want to sit here to press that button over.
Redo in the near future
How we doing
Strongly
Alright
I'll tell you
I'll tell you something
And that is the things are going well until the dog days of summer
Okay
Yeah that might be the case but that's why I'm keeping things like polar at 11
Keeping the Faith
As an option for later as those dog days of summer
So we're ahead of pace and I got to say this is going to piss off the purest
Alright
But I will save it something I'm excited about is
The candidates this week
Pedal
Okay not pedal
No pedal
Apparel yes yes
No petal
So each of the ones
Flowers
Mostly water flavor in it even if
Disagree
Another one
Where the light Euro's flavor pretty good
6900 lemongrass
Interesting plants with strawberry in it
Flower flavors
Very like
There's an aromatic qualities
Yeah I appreciate something that is a bit different it's not
Great
Cross 75
705 is huge
A couple more flavors in the fridge
Who that I'm holding off on
Like just completely nuts
And I will see you respect the hustle
Pretty good
Jordan Reed or going to start here on May 5th
Cinco de Mayo
There's no mention of
It's akeila
It's just
To speak of that little bit of Spanish
No probably not
So we start time with Alex
Vaccines
And he has a good source on this
Savage
Came out and
And then said he will not be taking the covid-19 vaccine in that is very very dangerous
Do Michael Savage does have a PhD degree so he's not just one of these cats we run into so constantly you just calls himself a doctor
Superfund
However Savage is not a medical doctor
So no one should be listening to what he said about vaccines
Biology master's degree
Ethnomedicine
His dissertation was on the Botanical and Nutritional Health practices in Fiji
The medicinal applications of 188 plant species found in Fiji
It's a cool area of study and I'm sure Savage had a lot of fun researching it probably getting to go
CD back in the 70s
Still he is not a medical doctor
Dr. Azar
Needles
Under his real name
Michael Alan weiner
Savage has published a ton of books about non medicine
Weirdly a 1984 called getting off cocaine
These books were published
I don't know I don't know cuz he did
You did like to hang out with the a lot of beatniks
Electric Kool-Aid Acid bus
I don't think you are because
Specifically he didn't do drugs
Who's the straight edge guide
Kara people
I get desensitized
So maybe the book wasn't him getting off cocaine so much is like eating plan to help you get off cocaine
Between 1972 and 1995 but also from 1991
Is Michael Savage alias
Starting with 1991's the death of the white male a case against affirmative action
We are the first few years there he was writing polemics
Healing children naturally and that he
Michael Savage's strange
Michael Savage is not a medical doctor Coronavirus
Completely meaningless
Alex Alex
Meant that he's been making
And that is the whole all deaths are being counted as covid
Some piece of his narrative
Talk about a little bit here
Almost all the dads to covid-19
Daily death rate
In each of these countries with her
We now know it is an ultra massive
Number of levels
First
Misrepresenting something Dr birx
A while back
But leaving that aside his claim that there is a normal number of deaths is demonstrable not true
Explaining that very fact
Couple of articles in the financial times where they analyze all-cause death statistics
In 14 countries they could get data from
They found that the number of deaths in almost all of them
Hugely I'll pay somebody long-term averages for the same time.
Italy saw a 90% increase
Spain 72% the UK 61 Belgium 60%
Amvets
New York City reflected a 386% increase in average
Which was still behind the Providence in Italy
96% increase
These numbers require further study are the same as they always are
Is a complete lie
There's no way around if he's telling his audience something that's the opposite of reality
That's just soap
Everything's pluck
This is fun
Something
Time the opposite
Trusted expert
So we get into this nice club sets up something
Pay off later
We're going to have
Royal Society Overland
Complete
Because they're lying
On
In a systematic way
Rent control
Possible
Insulation
It's all fun and games
Avoid the worst-case scenarios that are depicted in those graphs and prediction
Grass and predictions
It's all fun and games for him because nothing means anything on this show
Also if he's grasping projections that were being put out
What does Alex think about Mike Adams self-made projection which Alex reported on on his show
Mike's model showed two million people dead by July if nothing was done of course
It's reported that is an official model
How many has to be corrected by bike that this was a model to represent
What would happen if the viruses spread
When Alex cover this model biking made who's back in early March
When the editorial is going to kill everyone
So even like numbers being 2 million
Possibly could be
Worse
Millions and millions died
There's a new
Computer model out
Bye
July
These are just models
Says it's 15%
2 million / July grass
Amen
Explicitly says underestimation
Because
I don't know why it's being intentionally bought
Bring it up from
When it explodes
This this is their neck
The CDC is
Try to take out Trump
Wow well
Help for the word has
For the worst
March 6th
Because everything was very different
Was that part of this elaborate
Because it seems like a worse even more Sensational version
They're coming out around that time
Was this Alex on the health Ranger
Salesmanship
Because his narrative has completely changed
I guess the latter
Access
Datapoint
Higher
Then what
Rebecca Mendes
And being really mad about a grass
Stop it
Spell exciting
So
We used to run the baby harvesting program in Virginia
That's why I went on TV and said
We'd only law enforcement
Doctors in the mother
Germination
May's wife
We keep
Gender baby it's gone now
It's an award that went to the order some of the organs
Comfortable
Canopy
This all sounds shocking
Dallas Texas
Chicago Illinois New York City
Los Angeles
California
All the 60 minutes
Patience
Talking
He was healthy and I have to have somebody
One of that liver
Indy's millionaire nurses nurses
Notoriously overpaid I looked up the average salary for neonatal nurses at 6 p.m.
Brutal
So pretty much all that stuff
I'm just going to ignore that s***
Focus on here is Alex's claims that there were a ton of organ harvesting scandals in the 90s
Witches eat what he's using to lend credibility to the outlandish claims make a organ harvesting
Those under the guise of abortion
I've looked into the bed and from what I can tell this is Alex misrepresenting something that I suspect he never actually understood in the first place
Which is organ donor
Nation standards
Be home don't sign an organ donor card because if you do the let you die in the ER to take your organs thing
What's a super old urban legend
It's honestly probably the actual basis for Alex
The Narrative here
He said his dad told him that hospitals that do that another point on the board
We're like weird things he believes just cuz
It's like you're a dentist
I don't think he was actually going to
I imagine Alex's dad being like s*** this guy needs a root canal
I need a liver
Make a necklace from Dad
Just harvesting
What would you
Toby on the urban legend aspect I was able to find a New York Times article from 1997 that deals with some of the controversy
Remembering
Maybe both
Traditionally the standard that have been used to determine when a person has given to others in need
After their hearts stop beating
And it didn't resume
That was a long while back
Okay I cuz I thought it started at sprained ankle
And then
All bets are off
Traditionally the point
Declared brain-dead
That's not you know that is a term that gets thrown around
Who's there
Then in the 1990s became more prevalent for doctors to discuss donation options with families of dying patient
Already decided to take them off lights
Right right right
So this isn't entirely a decision to take the person off life-support is not influenced by
Anyone suggested Uso to provide organs for donation
And this shift is actually led to a grape increase number of donations
Were you laughing about
And they just
Hit them in the head
Image
Which is more fantasy than reality
This 1997 New York Times article discusses the Cleveland Clinic which engage did that for your donation
Whose family decided to take him off life support
They're beginning
Drugs to prevent blood clotting and white blood vessels
We could help preserve there for donation
The controversy with surrounding whether or not one of those medications
And would that be considered euthanasia
Who doesn't matter that this article clearly shows is not a question that doesn't have a consensus answer
It would make your death more quick and therefore the doctors are
Making them die sooner
That's me that's the issue
I think it's a relevant question is only because of like the Avenues it opens up
For like well
Is it
Where is the
That is a rat irrelevant medical ethical question
They're being decent arguments on both sides
I also understand why you're not tickled
Hey just
I'm Pro euthanasia like even when I'm fine and I start look
I want Terrell
I'm pro-youth
Travel back to 1997 and taken up with New York Times
I don't care
Because
D7 article also mentions of Doctor Who
She cannot comment in detail because she'd signed an exclusive
Agreement
CBS News 60 minutes
Broadcast tonight
Pretty sure this is the news program Alex's vaguely remember seeing
Has no idea what it was actually about
I was just telling his audience a story about doctors killing patients are at
Maliciously letting them die to steal on the black market
Stories very very different
Can't find
Examples any modern American Hospital System of people engaging in that sort of practice
Just have to jump over in order to pull off something
Ridiculous
If you
We're sound
Been negligent
In care that leads to someone.
You can be
Absolutely
It's just that
60 Minutes Bank 1997 that he does not understand
What do you shoot
Mixed with his dad telling these urban legends
Complete
Fundamental inability to understand people
A person would look at the amount of s*** you have to do
And be like
This is way better than getting a job like it just doesn't make
You know and it also is staggeringly
Respect
For what people in the medical field
To helping
Is is its foundational to the job
Episode
450 bucks
Half-a-million is so offensive
They are almost always underpaid working on
Operation Familia
Great so I told you
David Knight came around
And
Will show
Diction
And they already said
Before anything opened up here
Cases for example
AB people open up twenty-five 50%
What they're telling everybody what they're preparing everybody
The new narrative
Is going to be
Everybody's dying so we got
Narrative
Be likely outcome of trying to force a reopening
It's very likely that
This is we'll go upstate three open everything before it's safe to do so
This is a pre-emptive rationalization
Infectious diseases spread
Inevitably when you see the number of cases go up after these states reopen
The conspiracy is supposed to be exact
Expect
To happen
That's just so f***** up
Don't worry when people die
Don't worry about it it's not it's their fault
It's a doll Ally pretend everything is fake
Establishing
Multiple times this year
On March 23rd CNN reported on how he had done a really good job of containing the virus
150 cases
Now however long is providing a different object lesson
What happens when
The number of confirmed cases has almost doubled in the past week
Is there containment measures infection
Considerably
They have the situation under control measures
Draconian
Controls put in place
Must undergo a strict
Stay home quarantine
Answer face criminal prosecution if they're found in breach of it
Over the weekend police could
District looking for those
The wristbands off in order to go out
Good work guys because
You have to even stricter measures than you
Would have done in the first place
Suggest
Putting them in the room
Putting a sheet of metal over the door
Because you don't know if
Easiest
Consideration
David Knight doesn't know
University warning about this phenomenon and how it's
Prettymuchit
Explode
According to an article in the Denver Post
Illnesses and inspection
Which we do not have
And even if we did even restrictions in that scenario is only advisable if there's also a robust testing system in place
To be able to catch new album
Brakes before they become big new outbreaks
We don't have either of those basic components
After doing the Safeway understand
This is not a
Criminal
This is a crime it might be this is like this is Nuremberg trials
Like when we get through this this is time to be like hey guys
You
I knew this was going to happen
This is premeditated
Those
Those people's deaths
Are on you
Personal
Maybe Nuremberg Trial conciliation
The pattern of Hong Kong playing out in our states
Cases have continued to rise.
This stuff is pretty clear experts have warned us about what the most likely result of premature opening as
And all you see Alex and David
He's going to end up killing people but it's not really because
Conspiracy or something
Yep and I'm sure that they will be held accountable for their rack
Probably not maybe
Great that'll work
So Alex over the course of the last few weeks about people
What stores telling him to wear a mask and yells at them
Continues here on the 5th
You understand that it's incredibly
They're ignorant they love it
They love getting into it even though their whole future
Destroyed by evil
Stories about people who asked
Funny glimpses into how much of an impotent man child he is Raging because it's
Resume slightly
I meant last Friday
Flint Michigan Family Dollar
In retaliation for the store without a mask
He was a father and it's an absolute tragedy
I'm pretty much the exact pattern of all the stories outbreak
Pet stores
Much further
I'm not saying this woman to return to the store with her husband and son who then murdered
No reason to suspect that there is even a concrete connection nowhere that she was a listener or anything like that
The reason I bring up the story at all is because the underlying behavior of fighting and arguing with security guards are enforcing
And you've been very very clear about that
I'm sure you wouldn't Advocate someone go so far is it
Normalizing what are the steps.
He celebrates lashing out
As a positive thing
Even
This is a story that I haven't heard if he ever does
I'm just not sure there's a way he can cover the story about kind of supporting which I'm sure he'd rather not do
Falls apart
Cuz he got David night in there he's boring
And then Robert Barnes shows up
Three-way is not good
Yeah it's
It's
Almost done listenable I would not subject
Our listeners to that
With varying degrees of a lack of Education
Bitching about
David Knight & Barnes probably pretty well educated there just
Opportunity
That one of the things that I think is really interesting is I don't
At the job
Cuban
I think that he's given up on being a lawyer
Or something
Angels descended fully into this like
Yeah I think maybe he wasn't getting enough donations for the free America Law Center
Or whatever the f*** you was trying to do
This seemed to be the only type of barns
It seems like he's reading a f****** script
About like hay hay barn
You're smart
Back me up on me boy
General Flynn
That's being uncovered
Vulnerable
He like this
Indoor plants
Doesn't happen
Represented some of those other white hat
Invoice is an Institutional narrative
CertainTeed
Demon gate
For political harassment
False news stories
Trunews
Shoe storage
Discontinued campaign because Infowars
Keeps managing to jump
Institution
To personify
Complaining we chose this
YouTube targeting
Station within the Free Press
Preston American
Martin Luther King
Absolutely
Independent
Because they're afraid
Raises the question
Civil rights cases
Civil rights lawyer
Assholes want to own black people so much they're trying to own their stories
How to pronounce disgusting
Toomey sounds
Different
Used a bit of Independence to him
Sounds like the tools and Robert Barnes kit
Being used as an Infowars
Employee
About this 100
Because Alex
So
Conversation
Because who gives a
Alex
So he gets a social distance
I bet he has great thoughts
6 ft
That's how many feet your underground we just
Maybe maybe you think of the Sneaker Pimps song 6 Underground
Regular height for folks to be right
No
Comes from
Social distancing
And it just so happens to be a foot
Is
Wow
F****** while
That is a trip
Yeah
Oh my God number is Kevin Bacon
All of this
Tragic
Call Ben
Is 5 + 550
Whenever you and stuff it's always very suspicious
VSCO
Suspicious circumstances of that
Close to me
Lesbian couples come in
Hospitals were people of the time
Hawaii
Symbol of a ritual
Yeah
What kind of f****** world do you have to be living in if you hear that
Or like
Show me the ball did this ever happen
What in Houston one time never any time
I highly doubt it
Is always real
Oblivion
Putting brains in
Computer like it
He loves the idea that all of these sci-fi things about brains and computers are real
Naked men
The.is
Screenshot on my phone
The producers
This weekend of a new movie out
What a guy
As is
Auditions for the new a computer that it's wonderful once he does it
This is all just absolutely sexy
Your Consciousness you're going to be
How you talk
Your boyfriend
What you doing
Computer
Is there
Relationship
You and your family and it's just the next level of fraud
Here it is
So he's sick he's dying but it's
Okay because
You have to
Die
When they do the upload
Just like
When is bodies transfer another whole life into transferring all the thoughts without a soul there
Then why couldn't you just transfer then once the up
Whatever you want
Globalist
Movies
Also in Avatar character Sully doesn't have to die to control the avatar
I need to find out of those tanks
The bad guys
Fight alongside them
After that he's beloved by the navi and they do some magic to make him in his Avatar into one
Honestly I have no idea
Breathe on Pandora
Either way the ending is totally about
I assume they donated
Mostly about specialist
Really hate
I don't think I was got the point of it
So it turns out the reason
There's so many people Coronavirus
Decade
You're in a test positive
Remember most
Have you
It's a
Positive Coronavirus
Or so
You will show anybody
It's the same family that make sense
Coronavirus
So that's dumb
In the United States million covid-19 tests at this point
Alex
Haven't had a cold in the past decade which is pretty f****** absurd
Underneath tested we have particularly for antibodies
A great level of accuracy yet
Alex's pretending but they're not sure shots
May 4th article in discover magazine available between 83 and 90
6%
In terms of specificity
Meaning there between 4 to 17%
Audi positive results
These are not the result of the Coronavirus
Develop a more accurate test
The task is to Coronavirus
That's absurd
Nothing to say
Elementary questions of people coming up with a tattoo
If you create a test that always just returns positive result
You can easily see how no one would consider that a worthwhile task
This is a childish over-simplification
A particular antibody
If that's true coronavirus covid-19 antibodies always turn out positive
People who previously had a cold
Everyone test positive for SARS and MERS
Is it possible because scientists understand that the test
Maybe I don't know Dan
Didn't graduate
College
So I'm going to assume scientist about
Virology and I got to tell you I exclusively
My follow-up questions I was talking to
Clearly I got you really
Of course everybody can't test positive so they only used
The tests
Sometimes in the other ones are fake
And they only use the test test positive
Some people you can't have conversations wedding Wings because
Reasonable
So am I supposed to call
Listcawler
This person seems to remember that Alex said he was going
Tell everyone
And this guy
You're welcome
Run
You need to get
Austin Stein
Qanon on the show
DIA
T.i. last month
Like they did
Unlike
Chewing on the real military
Overwhelming
Email shooting
Despondent
Button and
I Got Hijacked
But I haven't done that yet I'm still thinking about it
Austin steinbart is one of these guys
I don't think anyone
Believe that
This guy does
To say that I didn't
Call up Cubberley.
Problem
But
People don't want to believe the truth
Play Fantasyland
As well imma go they all go
I do think
That is fair completely just
Didn't do his follow-through on me I'm going to review
How you can get too busy to do something you already know the answer to all you have
How to do
Guys got to go back to call next caller
They're calling in and they say that
They know that the New York dating
Because
Their sibling
Isn't Healthcare
Play Tyga
They get too much information
New York Jets vs
He's in Pennsylvania.
Pennsylvania
Nova and Einstein
Be as men
Cases at all they were seen
In Pennsylvania are you say
This International listeners
Pennsylvania is not in New York completely different state
Did they ever call Alex loves it you like it
Then I thought you was done with it
Start thinking more about that
Realizes like
I am
So I'm done talking about it
Calling about it when I asked you about
You don't believe me anyways
World
A real consequences for what I do
Doesn't know anyting nothing
He had a claim that you wanted to make
You wouldn't believe me if I told you you don't deserve to know
Mary Howard
So there's a couple more calls and
Who cares got very bored
He's only hosting the first hour then Paul Joseph Watson
Big projects to deal with
I don't know
So he the first hour
Education
In the country
Disappeared
Calling for that
I am
The people that run
Where were dropped into a black hole
Okay
Don't they run
Confirm this without
I am
What you say a certain areas
Alex doesn't know where Harvard is
What
Hockey
She lives in Harvard
Go fuc yourself or confirm the G's daughter goes to Harvard
He's using the present tense
On a number of occasions when Francis Boyle has been on he's complaining to Alex G's daughter currently
Realities use daughter did study at Harvard between 2010 and 2014
Under an assumed
Name
This makes total sense to grantura certain amount of anonymity because otherwise would be impossible
Bachelors of Arts degree in psychology and English
So I don't really know what the nefarious conspiracy is here but
Man I do not know what you're doing is somebody whose English in literature
That s*** is all
I was recruited into a Chinese Communist Party
You start reading
What's a you start reading A Farewell to Arms
Pages in place
Manchurian Candidate where's Manchuria
So you can find Business Insider articles about G's daughter from 2012 from 2015
None of this is anything close to new information
Here's the thing
She wasn't even the president of China until 2013
What time you was at she was almost done with her degree
What I'm getting at here is it none of this matters
China and higher education simultaneously
Is basically catnip
Incoming
Us and UK intelligence Warren China's trying to hack
Biolabs work
So they can put out false
Until now
Behind the whole damn thing
Hysteria in the media
I know she is
Behind the
Decoding the hospitals by the NIH
Play Joe control
That's a lotta editorializing
So Alex is making
What is the possibility of Chinese state-backed
Attempting to gain access to sensitive areas
Morning early this week primary
Obtain Intelligence on National and International
Acquire sensitive data on covid-19 related research
Accessibility fabricating the part about China's motive for the hacking being put out in
Weighted covid numbers that's just his imagination real story which ultimately makes this story
Who's really good example
What do you will do real story then make up a fictional telling of that story to report
This is actually a fantastic strategy for him because he knows that his listeners are not big readers information
They make you read up
Pages that's so much
So in this case is one of his listeners things to check into the storyville Google it was a joint usuk
3 put out about coronavirus
But Alex is just a
Also if you read the actual advisory these hackers are from China
Just that they're advanced persistent threat groups
Apt groups are not unique to China and it is possible
Kaiser
Like North Korea Russia it's not necessarily
So to be clear it very well may be the case of the Chinese government is somehow involved information
Alex could be operating also
If you would like reporting that is death
Is a little bit premature but it doesn't matter
I'm going to I don't know details about that so I'm not going to say this in reality
Based on the United States
Specifically acting in regards to not sharing information
I'm kinda on the side of
People
Maybe life-saving information
That is
Is the kettle not sure about this
If we're talking about right
Pharmacy is going to charge everybody
For this is just not going to release
Information information sharing
Yeah I think that's an imaginary version of eggs
And I love it
Your fantasy of
Finding a cure that's what I believe
White hat
I'd like you to write the screenplay but I don't think
Advisory I don't think about
I think they're trying to
Things for probably
Stuff like that
Alex talks about more
Stop about China that
I don't know if this is fair
I mean like there are a lot of very fair complaints you can make about China
Do stuff like this it just shows what you're about
Video Senator cotton says China's provide evidence
The government knows
Get it
Because Obama
Has the receipts
Okay
So you can always tell when someone is a dishonest actor when they demanded someone prove a negative
To be impossible for China to satisfactorily prove that the virus did not leak from the lab so demanding
In theory the way you would demonstrate that the virus didn't leak from the lab would be the show evidence supporting the natural progression
From bad to intermediate animal-to-human
Even if you did do this it totally wouldn't satisfy someone like Tom Cotton
You still say even if
Trajectory they still haven't proven
Also come from the lab results
This is basically what elementary school kids do on the playground
Those are some s***
Three chapters levels of communication and it's coming from a member of Congress towards another country
Which is
Unaccept
Scapegoating racism
To Tryon
That they absolutely deserve as well as their followers
Listen to trying to win elections
Is going to get us all killed
That's how I f****** racist they are they would rather
We go to a World War than accept responsibility for being shity at what they do and trying to kill ourselves
So it is next clip
From the May 6th episode Alex
Bill Gates
Planet Earth
Dictator
The planet
Major leaders
White
White people
Jack Sprat
Midwife
Fell between the two they licked the platter clean
You want us divided again
Each other
He wants us
Chandler
The future
Rhyme Jack Sprat
Different
I guess something is actually a satire about Charles the first
Parliament 1629
Opinion
Estranged
The planetary Decatur
Facing
Death
Will continue because
So brave
Let's go ahead and go over the facts
Major insurance companies in South Africa
Have openly come out instead
Death battle
Lockdown
Warfit
Massively
29 times more distraught
Then the covid-19 deaths
So it would be Financial Telegraph is not a major or even real publication
If you go to their website it's clearly just a front for cryptocurrency promotion and Future
Followers
That's probably not the financial Telegraph Alex's talking about though
Team followers 2012
Listening I think you got to leave
Very confused you got this
Call Joseph
Didn't you say the story from the financial mail mail Telegraph safe
Right
In this article use models to claim that the lockdown in South Africa
Based on the outbreak it seeks to stop
I knew there's another reason to hate Tyra Banks
To consider here
The first is that even if you accept this conclusion that's not a figure that's in anyway applicable to other countries in South Africa
This is an analysis specifically
Second
Easy elements built into it that represents a massive asteroid
Probably Financial malar
South Africa's covid-19 data is so sparse
Researchers use New York's public
South Africa's population
Isn't this kind of data
Create a representative glimpse of the actual situation in South
Population densities and distributions are different city patterns
Different levels of access to healthcare.
Responses to the virus
Have been different
This may not be a holy bankrupt way to gather some data for the sake of conversation
As far as I can tell that's a pretty big hole in the bottle which mysteriously doesn't come up
Really odd
So what does model
Data
And they assumed average because because the older patients with covid-19
Each coronavirus death represented a loss of life
4 years
Assume that because of the projected loss of between
Percent of South Africans will become and as a result lose a few months of their lives
I was just trying to pretend that this model shows 2019 times the death coming from the lockdown as opposed to the virus
And the reason that he doesn't do that
Paul Joseph Watson article covering the financial
Doesn't paint the full picture
Natural information
Two filters for delivery
A major point is that according to this model the losses months of people's lies would they do to poverty
Which of the conditions do significant work to remedy
Directly addressing those issues is a policy decision
If you want to use this model to strike up a conversation about battling poverty
Even before any of the virus concerns around more than half of South African
Live below the poverty line
So presumably their lives are being shortened
Before this ever happened
Because he knows he can use this
Tell bo3 his arguments that everyone in the United States
You don't care about the actual details
Disgusting
Also considering
Institution of statistical modeling
Where the virus models are in fraud
He's willing to accept another bottle of Everly digging into the methodology of it
Bottles that agree with me
The operating
Function
Any of that information from that article
Didn't know the publication's name that was sighted in
Message across so you can see like it's just a really bad source of information
Is that Alex keeps saying something that should also give everyone pause
Of course there's always going to be a new path
Glad he runs and funds
Pathogen isn't a word
He always says pathogen instead of pathogen is he like mixing up
Parthenogenesis
Just because I just think it's kind of
Consistent
If he's going to s*** talk every he's still got that f****** video
People do seem like Miss speaking tell me one of them
Steer away from
From the 6
Name is the end of civilization
Being held
I wasn't sure
Ted 2 weeks I said it's never it's not
200 years
Not the economy
You know the people producing this is going to say
Bill Maher
Taking over with modern feudalism
Credit
Buckets of
Food
Something was happening
He's going
Really start the way I expected
Tattoo
Video where
Bill Gates
Just pure joy.
Besides
Red eye demon
When I talk about
This year the world
The leading the show talking about
Okay that's where I expected to go somewhere
And Dad
Watching review article pointless celebrities
Call for world not to return to normal
Transformation
New World Order
How to make a really important
Alex is reporting on a Paul Joseph Watson article about how stupid these celebrities are and how pointless their statement is
I had no idea these celebrities did this until I heard Alex complaining about it
Only people who actually really seems to care about the symbolic statement
Episode
Madonna and Robert
Peace Prize winner
Nobel Prize in chemistry
Famous person astrophysicist
And of course
Iggy Pop
Anyway there
Nothing can ever be good again or we got to shut down forever who's Morgan optimistic statement
Is an opportunity to recognize the parts of our
They were destructive and unnecessary
Let's not just check out for no reason
It's basically just saying we can do better
Juju stop by celebrities
The same cannot be said for Alex
You love getting mad at famous people I only have one response to that is that now I Wanna Be Your Dog
That's what I want
Iggy Pop
Sorry
I have a cat
Come on
We know one thing about Alex Jones
And that is that
I mean
He's a racist
We know two things about Alaska
He's a racist and he's really good
Whip quotes
Didn't really say let them eat cake
They use that too
What did she say
That's the same thing
Giant Asian hornet
Sade
I need to hear about the
Sir Alex's story is nice but it's also probably not true
The story of an obviously oblivious Queen
Responding to news people starve
Marie Antoinette
The first time the specific phrase like
Yo ends up being less
The first time that specific phrases used as it's derived from Jean-Jacques Rousseau's confessions book
The instance of it doesn't say that Marie Antoinette said it
That was attributed to a quote great princess
Child in 1767
About her
As Alex's Berry brother being picked up and used against marie-antoinette Encyclopedia Britannica
Those writings inspired the revolutionaries supposed
X-rated is propaganda
Monarchy
However
Contemporary researchers are skeptical of such claims
Newspapers pamphlets or other materials published by the revolution
It sounds like something they would
Just no evidence
Because it sounds good it's true
Operate
It's because he's very dumb and he doesn't even basic
Looking into the ideas that he has
The Encyclopedia Britannica
The first instance of this quote being a
Attached to Marie Antoinette comes from 1843
It's a guy debunking some rumors that she said that with recirculating at that time
50 years after her death
Also Alex subject supper
It's been documented first case of coronavirus in the United States
At least six times
Easy enough for one of his listeners to accidentally
You probably should have
Yeah that's a good idea
No
Exquisite
Kids
These caves
No
You're going to get hurt real
Have all the weird trendy's that are in.
Asian
That's a big training thing right now and
Totally
Worried
I'm gone
Even my pants.
Yara sterilizers
Calendar
This is
Complained about it
Apparently according to Infowars website this is very serious.
I guess my take on this would be a solid who gives a s***
This is just one of them
It's kind of embarrassing to be a 46 year-old due to takes time on his supposedly very important radio show to shake your fist at
Teens f****** around on Tik-Tok
He's the tip of the spear
Yeah protecting everyone in the info
Is a long history of the sort of trivial performative outrage
Like you can easily imagine Rush Limbaugh being terrified the kids are posting videos of them doing stuff inspired by jackass
Evidence of the generations complete collapse
I guess the generation before that would be like people doing prank phone calls
From now
Asking me if my refrigerator is running and they are not asking for the
Allure Alex by Tik-Tok
It's just trouble
Not exactly
So I started on the 7th
Putting in the conspiracy world
I found surprising
And that is of course the plandemic documentary that was going around the circle
CVS
It's also doctors in Black
Call the VIPs
You're right. Dressed in black
Your dog but this is all your f****** rain might know all the lyrics
I definitely will Smith soundtrack
Why why why
I don't know karaoke
Numbers as I think it's pretty funny
I think what it was I was fascinated when I was like
22 or so with this phenomenon of Will Smith just like songs that were the entire plot
There's something really fun
It is kind of nice
Short synopsis
Just like little mini movies with music
Came out like right when I was watching tons of music videos
What you going to do and
Also go to bed
Wiki wiki Wild
Quick Wok
Mechanic
To like
Two generations further down like
Will Smith used to be a rapper
Infinite
You tried
I think that even like some people our age mites
Soy documentary
On this episode
The same thing seems to just want to be off air
And it's playing a bunch of this documentary gives him the ability to do that
I want to take your calls there's also a
Documentary
Is it called Banda Mac
Doctors in Black
Play part of it
Today reposted
Video
A woman at work rate closely toward winning
Without
Exposing his
Destroyer
The food chain
Doctors in black is part of the name of the plandemic documentary
From stuff to
It's a garbage coronavirus conspiracy theory content
Just covers the same kind of grounded Alex does regularly
I have not watched
Imagine
9 / my time
Every
Could have caught five
Leonard maltin
Yeah yes
Pointed out there
Talking about
For speaking the truth
Because of course
This is Julie McCullough
And talk s*** about fauci
Weirdly she has a new book coming out about how bad it's probably but I'm sure that's not a part of this at all
It's amazing hurt I'm sure she's been working on that book for a couple months
Basic stories
2009 virus called
Fatigue syndrome
This is published in the journal science but as people tried to recreate her experiment and reproduce a result
Coronavirus did not appear to have any connection with their chronic
The same day she had her paper
This led to a partial retraction from the December 2011
Attract
Virus-related virus
In chronic fatigue syndrome page
In addition there is evidence of
Poor quality
Control a specific experiment
In the report
That time because it's was a research director at Institute for neuro immune disease
Which is a private business not a part of the pouches operation or any
In the Fallout of science retracting the paper she was one of the authors that strongly defended her conclusion
Even after some question popped up about misused figures which is a very serious
This thing in terms of a published research
The Institute
Very shortly after
Because they claim
Excel computer answer proprietary data
She was eventually arrested because she was a fugitive from this suit
Because she was releasing any damaging info or anything like that
Chicago became a careerist in the anti-vax world
Tying her discredited work at regarding xmrv to all sorts of things like autism
Vaccines and what have you
Can the actual field anymore
Only place they can
Nescience denialism Market
She doesn't seem too interesting to me in that sense in the only thing people keep bringing up a batteries out of and tried to arrest her cuz she was
Putting out this
Whistleblowing shittin that's nonsense
There's no cover-up of any discussions about any other research
Results
Cool allegedly stole from her employer
I don't care about this at all
Conspiracy world this week so it's only a matter of time for Alex drive to
Somehow cashew nut
I just wrote a book
Since you started
Talking about her called
And I publish immediately after
Interested
Is this what you this is okay
Interesting
So he doesn't playing a bit of it but
Jumping in interrupted
You said something
That I honestly think
In the right
Circumstances could lead to a lawsuit
2 days
Hospital
New York
Pennsylvania
Line body bag
No one ever goes in
Because they were
So Alex would be very very careful about calling people involved in high-profile tragedies actors
Is Jordan Beau
Speaking specifically
Figure out what hospital
You might be able to force a retraction out of Alex
Trying to search for that was difficult because there's also
If you search for Tyler Dixon Hospital very unhelpful results
I tried to find the video I can't figure out where it is at a hospital
Either
Tyler Texas
Fun fact
In 2011 also had his license to practice law suspended after
See tabs do plastic bags
For sale
In his possession
Charged with drug trafficking
Misdemeanor drug charges and
You did not Escape his license intact
Let's do 60 days in jail
He's probably generally song
I just think it's funny that Alex's friend did Rodger Stone supposed attorney was Moonlighting as a drug dealer
Entrepreneur
Just imagine for a second
Zit like Rachel Maddow
Imagine that
Lady doctor makova
This is just an imagination you just making this up
That is woman is who she says one of the top scientist
Neurologist in the world
Really
You're putting him
Enterovirus
Call Gina
We're getting so unhealthy
None of that stuff is at all related to what ended up being her fall from grace
Even the stuff like her anti-vax stuff later in her career has nothing to do
Ended up
Pretty much
Torpedo in her career
It's all a late addition
Into the story
You change your muscle
I met because he wants to he's fallen
14 in the downfall of the human races
Probably just going to be the fact that
People want to believe stuff
And they will do anything or anything that's a pretty negative
Alex
I would say
Pretty basic
Problem with some jazz ideas
And that is Cyrus covid-19 stuff is all
How did these globalist plan this out
Seems like it would be hard
You know you'd leave a trail
Grills grills and everything Worthen planning Secret
Get caught for whenever they laundry that's really smart
And then there's a moment
This that like
It broke my
My heart listening to this clip
It was like when you see a jugular drop a ball
But if you study these big events
But you at has a drill
John Hopkins
Has a drill
Goodwill
20 sixty-five million people die from a coronavirus escapes a while
Gates Foundation
Mobile model
With the Rockefeller Foundation
Before
They call it event
Looking up and ran into water department
You are so selfish a
But God chapter
U.s. code
Legalize lethal biological chemical
Nothing on you
Research or law enforcement
Coof
Detention
Today
Is it
Remember how to Rattle off his favorites
To be more reliably
He does like a party trick to impress
Yeller clip
It's one of the saddest things I've ever heard
That's like really late-night drunk things like
Then time passes they're impressed by the crowd
People just over it
All the sadness that came really
Something impressive even is executed perfectly
The portrait in tragedy
Dolar a pesos begin to lambat line
That's not good that's from 95 to 81
He doesn't know what to do about it
It's just words
Also the words of 200
It's just something Alex is making up because as he was ripping.
And how many inches are in the number 200 stamp
We talked about memorandum 200
Bring it down again
To show his 200
And because the moment of him trying and failing to say his favorite subsection
Is a real sad
Sad moment
Freud
So enjoy
Your questions about the drill thing
Is that clip didn't spell it all out
He's got you cover
How they do this
Of course you did
It's a drill he's running that's kind of a metaphor of the joke
Now this is not a drill this is not a game
Assimilation
That's a metaphor
What don't you get
Maybe clear metaphor
Satire
Maybe
I don't know I don't even think that would be
Allegory
Not a metaphor of a joke
So is Ender's Game
It's like it's telling me how to do this.
I love that
Love that book when I was 15 some feelings of Alexandra
Watches that movie nose
Alien planet
After movie
They blow up
They're called xxxx
We destroy you we rebuild you
More this Illuminati crap
Thank you
The rescue of the thing is him atoning for his math
Massive mistakes
She's daughter
So
You know the episode is not so great
I do not care over it it's really terrible
Adidas Google if you want
That is all taken care of already local library
So are we equipped here and it's this story about beat there's a salon owner
The situation
She wanted to open up her salon and
So she got arrested right
The governor of Texas
She should be let out
You just said that they didn't actually do anything
Which they could have died
They could have been they didn't they just
Superman the state supreme court
And so she's got she has been released by the timer recording this
She should be in prison for that
Extraction
Should be in prison
Especially non-violence
Fine or something I don't know
I don't know what the right answer is
Pretend situation
He commuted her sentence
The judge
Said no I don't care how mad
Please he's trying to say that she was acting in some kind of a way it was
Roach
Just being like hey
Official motion
This is the narrative
Is presenting that story which is fraudulent
But it does lead to him saying this which I think is
Way revealing
The governor tells him to let loose
Do it
Well
Hotworx
So
Alex believes is above a million
Alex is pecans
Alex
I keep pocket Constitution with me
And I can tell you right now.
The Constitution says
Trump is the king
There are three not separate
I will say least consistent about this
Read with a cord
Alex is more powerful
The courts
Just don't understand people who say they read the Constitution
Because I speak.
Crazy
That's just crazy
Just say you want to f***
Because you think you're better than everybody else
Episode it's
Not
Most interesting stretch of time
Coronavirus tafen
Trying to
Drift
Along
Last time it was David Ikes
Episode
The plandemic documentary
He's just trying to get whatever you can and I guess it's kind of working but who cares I really care
He's very.
Distracted
I don't know what he would be distracted
It rhymes
Troubles mounting all around
What happens in the near future
He's such a dick
I just I don't
Get why it is so hard
For people that
Just not
People are
Getting killed people are dying
People are dying
All the time I'm going to get up to 3000
Do their own bugging projections
And we're still doing this
The stakes are not f******
Obama tan suit
Be a dick while Obama has a tan suit
Fart
Mistakes are
This is this is the problem
Freedom of speech
Taking things as seriously as they need to be taken
Like I don't know how you do that
It's not normal time
No I don't know what the answer is
Nope
Would like please donate
36 36 36 years old
I'm the devil
Alex
Same color