Air Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge fight
We are the bad guys
Knowledge fight
Let's sit around and talk a little bit about Alex
Jordan Jordan
What
I think for a minute
Card game partner and I we run out of
Board games
Play the little heads up poker 888 whenever you take crazy insane risks and have
No interested but it sure has more than two people
Quit being Nikki giftisa live together we had a running tally Board of like heads up poker game
It was just so boring
Just don't be able to each other and stuff
It's hard to play card games between two people sometimes
The things that you shorten up the game and I like to play Spades and you get rid of everything below 10
Two people I'm telling you it's great Cards into a hat
SoundCloud second next week
I guess for me my bright spot we was going to go with the food one
I tried these cookies called a crispy crepes
And they're like rolled up little mini crepes
So good maybe my favorite thing ever
They're very tasty
Not to their small you don't end up eating too many of them unless you
Can't stop if you see the whole box of something I do but if you can restrain yourself
It's a really good like little cookie thing that's not too unhealthy and
Potassium
Even even if they work small and like
Reasonably
Acceptable if you're dry and good
How do you offer
I've got one more
I wish today wasn't food-based but
Oh well
Check in with the Yoruba seltzer
Ryan thank you so much you're now if I was wrong
Policy wonk weetzie thank you so much
Text John
Hey John John text Melinda
Zachary is that sack with a nature without an ID
Elevated love
Appreciate that very much so
Democrat
How's your 401k
What's the business
Heroin
Is freakishly large
Ida Claire
Infowars
Generosity and direct
Georgia
That would be wonderful as well
Almost a week ahead and believe that we're already into this incredibly exciting
To get the 500 we're supposed to be at about 10 or 10
At this point
Been trying to go through the Waterloo Seltzer's
Waterloo
Dubai water
I want to see the Waterloo is a rangy beast of seltzer
Watermelon variety coming in 67
A lot of black cherry
Nelly
That gutter really good
So bad
There's something wrong
Flavored wrong with that Seltzer a f***** up something that it's not good
Chris
Chiropractic
It's just water.
Is something wrong in the other direction with that Waterloo black cherry and I don't know what it is and I do appreciate it
Also I tried this is hi ball Energy Water
All energy is one of the cans of the other ones is a grapefruit one
Hey there's a vanilla
It smelled just like maybe a Seltzer version of a cream soda
Terrible I trash 21/100 that's bad
Throw it out the window in this installment of
The year the South air
But that's to be expected and I'm glad you know just middle-of-the-road stuff
Boring not all that exciting I would rather encounter a2153
Probably
I believe you
Streams are we will see you again
Next time I'll be over this album
Today we got going is I was looking over our episodes and I realized like 10
Episodes straight that we've been in the present avallac'h
Another Alex Jones episode for this one just be able to cover Friday's episode of a show
They will be able to have
More content to go over a little more more time for things
Now's as good a time as any for a break
I wanted to see what our old Harry Caray
Over there was up to talking about aliens and what have you
Be coronavirus may or may not have been turning Chinese people into vampire
Steel City
That was the working Theory over there
And
I don't know if that bread continues okay
What we have today is an interview that Kerry did her most recent episode where she was talking
Tui super Soldier by the name of Anthony Zender
This is his third time being interviewed on the show and I want to make something abundantly clear before we begin
That's what we're what
I know Alex has some thoughts about Sarah's Ender's Game
No one thing I want to make
Is that I don't make fun of Anthony himself
I don't know of what he's dealing with
From listening to his first interview with Carrie there was some discussion of him being in a rock
And possibility of some PTSD type of situation
So I don't want to sit here and beat up on him
And I'm not going to
We probably wouldn't cover this too much
If it weren't for
The way that it's being used
The information that he's presenting and carry is allowing to be presented
You stuff deserves to be talked about
And
I think this is just on the other line of my only this allowed
I don't I don't know what it is going on in his world doesn't seem like some of these people
On Project Camelot that I'd be like I'm not even touching this
I still have a lot of empathy for him and I would
Prefer to err on the side
Of not beating up on him
But
That doesn't mean that this interview itself is necessarily off-limits there's some teachable moments
And some things to be learned through it so
Generally speaking of somebody with PTSD is is
Saying something along those lines I view it blesses them and more is a complete failure of any kind of support structure
For them to process
I think there's probably something to that
So as far as that goes it's a it's a failure of the entire system that
I'm interested in not him particular
He doesn't seem to be somebody
Listen to chew these three interviews that he has doesn't seem like he's a bigot or anything like
Eddie page rehab
So I don't have any like
Vested
A desire to likes
Knocking down to pay the rent for the third time Ontario
A super soldier expert on Xbox
He just tried silvercraft or whatever
We're talk about this and be trying walk that line as best we can
Carrie starts at the interview poorly
Because their Tech is working and so she has to call him back
And try a second time
So what
This again so
Everyone
Camelot
Hi Carrie
Herewith
Xender
Go ahead
Okay
You know I just
Notice.
A cutout
That's what happens
There's some Echo there that will go for the first like maybe
20 minutes but it gets resolved
Speaker something I think it's her
Because there's no conversation of it but it does fix itself I don't know who's
And it was
There was a problem with the recording but you thoroughly that little bit of a knockout
This dude is a super soldier
Interesting things to consider when we think about that
The introduction of it's been going on since he was 6
Okay
I like it
The past
And
See you again
Anthony and
Show again
Haven't seen
My previous enter
You are no other
I will
Can you carry on
Good to be on the show
Because
Understand
Super soldier
Not right now
Basic free in my life
I
The child
And that was
What is called operation
GreenStar
Is the CIA off
Operation
Children
So they returned the super soldier
To the CIA program called operation GreenStar but of course I wouldn't
Before I'm there anything
Government has used for project
That's the
Where the PMD Defense Forces use that operation name to do things like in 2019 when they cracked down on immigrants
Suspected of job-hopping
The head of that operation Lieutenant Colonel Nelson Rapala Zealand post career that quote
The operation aim to restore the state's presents provide a community healthcare and evangelize the word
God
I like one out of those three ice Motor Service to the
Earlier in 20
Do you know operation green star
They were believed to have been quotes across the border from Indonesia and used for poaching
No word on if those guns were taken for Evangelical purposes
In 2013 a separate operation GreenStar made headlines in India When They confiscated illegal plastic items
They were in violation of their environment
Well it's great in North America operation GreenStar was the name given to a closing books Drive
Help those less fortunate than ourselves
In 1967 at the University of Montreal
A perfect cover for a super-soldier program Dan that's where they drop babies off to
Adoptive
I can't even really find any references to GreenStar on conspiracy or paranormal sites and what are they
Come up as a site called true vision of peace
And the reference to GreenStar is just in a bio that's attached to an interview they did with Anthony
Navigate to think of this might all just
Springport
I'm not entirely sure
So apparently there was a this program
It was
The part of a treaty
Date the government did with the Breakaway civilization or something
Explication of that
Operation green star is
Is a CIA operation
That way
Created to abduct children
With a certain
Genetic traits
Or
Eugenics
Bioluminescence
Zacian
Was
Letting
Demagogue
When I when I
So if I understand this correctly as a government and then there's this Breakaway civilization
Breakaway civilization may as well be called the globalist
So they're the bad guys in this scenario
The CIA operation since they were running GreenStar which means that the creation of the secret Superstar
Soldiers with something that was being done for evil ends
This must mean that Anthony is an evil creation
And that all the super soldier has been doing are directed by the bad guys
If you really think about that is about the good guys taking control of the secret Superstar
Soldier program
To conclude that he's an instrument of The Darkside
He was created in the way people perceived this is but it's not a Frankenstein
Monster was created by explicitly evil doctor Frankenstein
Evil videos dr. Frank
Yeah you probably assume that I suppose if we're going to go that far
Right so I adjusted that's interesting because he'll talk about some of his missions later on
Hero
They don't seem to be
Incompatibility with the secret space program
And the CIA Breakaway civilization key
Do that to me is a little bit difficult
It's not hard for someone to
Across like there's elements within it that are good that's why I was working or something
It's it's all
Whatever that explicitly not loud
Injection to be very suspect
What if you're going to or if you're going to make a treaty wouldn't you doesn't that suggest that everything's on up up above board
You know you're right.
Yeah but you're not enforceable
Eisenhower sign the treaty with the aliens at the Grays could kidnap
People for research and stop it
There
So
It's important to recognize as operation GreenStar
Nations that were done to him
Okay at the age of 60 since then
He has been some sort of a super soldier
And
At 6 years old I was
You know Devon
Sonic on Military
Terry bases
And
You know
Experiments were down on
Government in that
Implants
You know the one they call the
Pardon me
And they
Queen
Turn into a Super C
Soldier so he's turned into a super soldier the black do was put into him and so forth
In Theory been a super soldier
I just got the black goo
He talks about like a some of these missions happening in other dimensions like he's in another body
Or whatever alright
This is explicitly his own body when he was young
Could I support
Because there's two Divergent Paths of these
The super soldier dumb that's going on
That's very hard to make sense of
So are you telling me that they do they remove the implants as the body grows or the implants
Grow with the body
I'm sure they grow with the body
Set my work on it I would like further
Location of
Where are these implants
Are around
So every good story like this requires a backstory
Even though you need some sort of a
A reason why your lineage is important to be in
And here we get a little hint of that from Center
As
A child you know
Grandpa
What's involved in our
Ocean system
And all this
Baseball bats
You can talk about
So if Anthony is saying that his grandfather designed the SR-71 aircraft then he's definitely claiming that is Grant
Father is Kelly Johnson
Because that's who did that
Disclaim initially appears to be a good player but upon closer examination actually impossible
The reason it looks good at first is that Johnson was married three times
So you have three possible
This offers so many more possibilities for making claims of parentage is opposed to someone who's only married one
But if you read up on Kelly Johnson's life you'll quickly learn that this is no good
Johnson released his Memoirs in 1985 titled more than my share of it all
And in it he discusses the heartache of being twice widowed
And never having children
Johnson the designer of the SR-71
And therefore cannot be anyone's grandfather
To make these sort of claims credibly he's going to need some really solid evidence Pastor saying it to a woman who believes literally anything
So maybe he had a maybe at a lovechild maybe that's government
Jumped in his
That's what I'm saying and that's that's why I
Illegitimate
Child is it whatever
Do you need to prove that then cuz otherwise I could just say that I am the illegitimate love child of
Anybody I want to
Did he actually
Design
Weave
Well obviously he could have gone through a previous super soldier
Program that we are
Are obviously aware of
What if
It's all a
Cover-up and Kelly Johnson didn't even design that s*** and it's actually zender's grandfather did it but they
I had to get rid of him because his right you good
For the super soldier program he has a kid there
Back in time
Time travel is very heavy in this version of course it is
I mean sure
You know whatever you could you could come up with any kind of
Sort of Bo sex Machina explanation for how all this fits together
Sure
That's got to be a
So he became a super soldier at 16 formerly before that was
Preparation for it piece of information
They sort of use as evidence that I don't find super
Compelling
They you know I would
Things like that
Romanian
And all that stuff
Then
Be a super soldier 1 hour
Resolve
When I first start
Basically my whole child
Tubi
A Black Ops
So he claims he had bloody noses
That's some sort of evidence
Mistaken him or something for all sorts of reasons
Dry climates picking your nose
Allergies because if there's a ton of reasons people have bloody noses
It is not
Uncommon
So for that to be the case Sookie and so centralized a piece of evidence
He's being taken to be experimented on
I just I see that and I like that
Not good
It doesn't help that doesn't sell me on it I need to know about the graduation ceremony
That's what would get me if you if he gave me a detailed idea of what happened when he was 16 like
Did he walk up there do they give him a diploma do they put a hat on what happened I want to know
Debate
They stuck it out of
I'm not sure is involved disclosure
That's what you supposed to be doing right now which is on carries show
Supposed to like
Get a lot of this information out
I've been involved
Working a lot of ice
Basically
Involved with
Disclosure
And then bring it out
Pretty good band
In this
FaceTime
Obviously seeing that
You know people are going to want ants
What's going on
And I do have
Knowledge tube
Survive that
And
I've been
A lot of
A lot of missions
Lately
You know and
Enemies mission
Lately
My doing
Black Ops
But I'm also
Involved
You know like heads
Give update
And all these things
Center going on
What is going on right now
Ball is getting
And
That's why I work
So for me a little bit
Every time somebody says that
What's going on right now
Cabal is getting taken down
1 assuming that they are totally up or what
There's no other way to say that the cabal is going to take these live
Suck but having meetings with Trump
He said that the cabal is getting taken down right now
Whoever qanon says is back
Alright alright lately
Who's getting taken obviously through this nightclub UE says one
Okay
Do you have any
In terms of
You know about
What you know about
So rather
Generalities
He look you and Carrie are on the same page kicking ass at this interview
Yes p
I've heard there are
Going to be a rash
Jose urbina
However
We don't really see
Do you have me
Interested
I do I do
Because I'm involved in
In this
Involved
You know
Making
People sign
Pelosi
I've been involved
Meetings
Where
I've been involved
And the Tribune
I've actually
Been there
And seeing it going on
Ivibe.
The courtroom
Man I knew that
And this is all going on behind the
So he has something at being in these tribunals
Yeah
And it's basically that what he's describing is dreams he's had
Has come to his mind while he's meditating these are describing as real memories and
Experiences and Carries allowing him
To just
Save all of these dreams are real situation where was a competent
Non-abusive interview were talking to this person
You could have a conversation about these really interesting dreams that he's had
Recovered memory
Kind of language about the CIA
He's he's he's
They they wipe his memory or something along those lines in order to keep him from telling even though his job is
Disclosure
I'm confused on on exactly what's going on makes sense but yet
Make him not remember these missions
But your soul remembers
Record themself VIP access like his higher self
To these memories when I dreams they come back or is that kind of thing is definitely in the mix
What do you think you got Nancy Pelosi
It's not clear if she's under arrest auto loan now I think it's a confession or something
It'll come back up later but
Carrie asked about these memories and mrs. this is sort of like where I'm thinking like
This is mostly dreams
When you get these
These memories are you getting them
Because
Initiative
Situation in a
During the day how to
Right
Aimm
I'm so
I do go to sleep
Access
What they do
Dream situation
Amor real
In real life
So I mean you can have vivid dreams and there are phenomenon that happened in your dreams where you can have like pretty
Intricate
Elisa Gilbert
Reason to believe that
You would
I have a dream of making a Pelosi sign something I'd be like I did that
Mystery School
Yeah probably
You can't open your mind to the mystery
That's probably why
Like I said I don't want to make fun of Anthony
I do think this is worth discussing for a number of reasons
One of them is because
In this interview you see exactly the same sort of mentality that Alex Jones has
Being presented by this guy
One of them being
It movies and TV shows are real
Disclosure movie
That's out right now
Is a Cold Blood
And not that
Afternoon
Vin Diesel
The whole thing
Soldier is
And how they
Do memory
Population
In memory of
Rachell
To basically
Keep using the super soldier over
And over and over and over again
And
Another
Disclosure
Show is
The dollhouse
Do you have these like Sci-Fi movies and TV that are actually telling us the reality
Everything that's going on secretly
Andy has had exactly mentality
So
He is Alex Jones's believe of what the globalist
Playing a guitar
I'm coming from Alex Jones it has this air of like I've researched I know all this stuff I know what they're doing
They tell you their plans in the
In the movie
When you hear it coming from this guy who claiming to be a secret super soldier
It kind of
Better light
The behavior that Alex Jones man
He's him for Anthony it's far less
Nefarious
Is also less effective just based on an appeal to Authority kind of situation there because Alex is in control
He's filling the room up with his
So you know he can push that on you and you can
Just kind of accepted into dude
Giving an interview and he's telling me that movies are real
Well you're not here in the wrongs to tell me the movies that really does feel that way and the dollhouse
Rough start but ended up going pretty good who's pretty good and I'll Rush.
Disco
Another thing that's really similar to stuff with Alex
Anthony Sanders says that he is in direct communication with
The president
And
He's sort of ideas about what's going on in the world right now are also
Very very similar
With Donald Trump
And thanks for
In guidance
Baton
He is receiving right now
And
I'm also
I'm also having
Memory recalls
Mission
That I'm involved
On this Earth
Because this is an
Interdimensional
Relaxed
Star War
Going on
That's very similar to what Alex believe there's extra-dimensional demons that he's at war with
Better behind the globalist in all this shape very very similar
Alex says b
Throughout the show I talked to him and he listen
There's
Very
Very heavy overlap
Between this guy
Alex I want to know what they mean I don't mention
You just can't see it happening around you right now something
There's a world above our world world existing with our world that were incapable
Experiencing
Like that's why I'm very frustrated with cuz they all use it like
Catch-all and I think they all if they were going to like draw out what it is they mean when they say interdimensional
UT completely different pictures don't do that because if you do then you have to stand by that.
Anthony's Mission largely involves being a spy
Publix
Show
It seems like trouble I think he's I think he's been burned
Is Roses by infiltrating evil organization
Cover God
A little bit
One of the
The mission
Recalled
Just
Because I'm always
Intuit
Into the dark
Side
Saying enter
Wichita
People don't know this but
Which are monarch
Mobius
Umbrella
Massive
And these are all
Corporations that are in
And
One of the
Mission Zion
I recalled
Was on
Cuz right now
Is going on is
The covid virus
Ibio
Employed
You know I'm
We're calling
Mission
Where
I've I'm involved
Getting
Going on
In these other
Fireplaces
Similarities there
Is the name of the fictional Corporation it was set up to try to kill Godzilla Godzilla franchise
2019 Godzilla king of monsters in the upcoming Godzilla vs. Kong
It also factored into the 2017 King Kong movie Skull Island
The movie of Corporation is the name of the evil company in the video game The Evil Within which was a survival
Resident Evil Creator Shinji mikami
With the first one released a 2014 and a sequel in 27
Umbrella courses evil company in the Resident Evil series
Massive Dynamic was a company founded by Leonard Nimoy
Which was kind of looming Specter of evil for the protagonist in the film
Ultimate comes from do you know cuz I receive
Anthony is operating as a very similar
There's a fundamental unwillingness to separate reality and fiction
And the lines are really arbiter
Like why not include Viet Industries in there
Primatech paper fan
TV shows
Of all like it was cute too obviously fake fictional companies not real but these are
Other ones are I don't know who cares
I hate it whenever they believe that movies and s*** are real and then they say stuff like biochemical AI
If you believe movies and s*** are real
Has a biochemical AI ever worked out in the end for humans
It always it's always
Why would we make a biochemical AI if they always
Wind up killing I said because the fiction is just predictive programming to make you
Would never work
Fair enough. It's always waiting around is always ways around
So I noticed
Whenever I heard Anthony talking about missions that he's been on but honestly sound like
Some dreams
Basically
You know when you're at
A lot of the time
Found out
You know your car
No
Emissions
Braun
And I have to
But but
You know one of the most recent memories was
I was obviously
And in one of these
Corporations
Umbrella
You know they are linked
DARPA and miss
Reality
But
I was involved
Being involved in the mission there
And
I had to
To escape and
I was out getting shot at
And I had to
Getting
And the elevator door closed
Understand there are all sorts
Through the elevator door
And
Against the wall
And the elevator door
And then makeup
Cut the cord
The elevator
And then I fell
Mike Hunter
Stories or something
Because I was in the sky sky
Android Wear
It basically the elevator
And I'm I was
Still alive
Because I was obvious
Body
And I got out of
Elevator
Agents all around
People that works
Now and
I started
Basically running up
The size of the wall
And shooting every
And then. That's what I asked
A runners
Doing
Let sounds like an action-packed I got a dream
No just
Just me
If I'm if I'm one of these
Government operation directing spies in the places
I wouldn't use the guy who's
Describing his own job
As my cover gets blown a lot I'm in a recon mission and then I just wind up killing
Everybody haha
The smash-and-grab Spy Shop
B-2 stealth video game would like that kind of strategy
Attack strategy
Yeah it is counter to
What the goal is not to kill people
Well you want the information and you also don't want the person you're getting the information
Exactly the lever
I don't know
Also that's a
Judgment
The corporation
For sure knows that they're being spied on and all their guys are murdered
Heather just like well
Will give you this one bad but keep moving forward plan
They know about
Guys back to business as usual my bad my bad
Elevator
Go to work
Isabel newer Super soldiers that apparently we are involved in having created cuz we're the Bad Guys
Very complicated I don't pretend to understand but
Anyway there is a reason there I'm doing this episode even though like if you just listen to that
Pretty clearly a guy who's
Describe a sort of dreams that use interpreting as real
And that is something that is addictive of not a perfectly healthy mindset necessarily
Which is why I'm trying to dance around this fairly delicately to beat up on this guy I think that you probably
Is dealing with something and probably needs to be the target of compassion as opposed to read
Ideas are kind of funny but
Only within the context of understanding the
You know he
Did not him or last
No it's like the children of the childcare facility that they're recovered memories
Suggested that the daycare worker
Cuz we're satanic satanic satanic pedophiles and
They sent him to jail over forever and it was all made up
I'm not mad at
The kids they were being manipulated the whole way in a very similar way that Terry is manipulate
This guy might actually go back and we'll get into that as we go along
So Carrie wants to
To know about this sort of
Sovereign citizen
In front flags with no gold Fringe on them
Christ
Leads to a pretty big revelation
That should tell about maybe some of this path started for xender
You have like
The last
What weeks have you known
Change
In
What's going on because
That on
Lately on news
French's
So are you aware of
Yeah I know there's there's nothing
Going on
And it's very
Clear that there
They're trying to
You know in many different ways
Make that clear
And if
I've heard
You know the Federal Reserve
Is gone
You know
Finally got the three Senators out of there
You know they they they switch it over
What I know
Tubi
Call the nesser on Jessie
He is happy
Because I've actually
Memories
I'm being involved
With a Donald Trump
In
The
The Great
The Hidden City
And in China
And they're okay
Nation going on
Celebration
Obviously
Nasir and Jester attack
Which is obviously a whole new change of government
Happening
We can actually see his half
With
This martial law
Fildan America
So the whole idea about the coronavirus in the covid-19 in a locked out and all this has to do with a hoe
New government being rolled out because of neferet and Jesse
A good just hasn't heard about this
Their belief system says that gold Fringe around the American flag
Indicates that something is under the control of maritime law
And therefore it's all invalid common Sovereign citizen
You'll see it whenever their record trying to get out of a fine for driving without a license
Tubalcain so I was pretty sure that mess Aurora and Jess Aurora sounded like some kind of an allusion to a Biblical Beast
Or something I got that bike pretty interesting and depressing
Jersey stop
Nesseralla is the National Economic Security and Recovery Act
Which is something that was proposed by a systems researcher named Frances Barnard
In the late 80s
His basic argument was that debt was holding down the economy and the compounded interest was the greatest factor in the maintenance of that
That that doesn't ethical matter
It was unethical to allow Co-op
I mean it's fundamentally anti-biblical
So there's that NASA red dress run
Pennywise
His proposals were never put into law from starting posting a bunch of conspiracy theory
Worries about it
Under the screen name actually
Was actually secretly passed
Every National economics
Security and Reformation
Version of Nazareth
Curtailing the actress supposed to take effect on September 11th
2001 911 was somehow done to a verdict or something
Totally
According to a fantastic article about by Shawn Robinson
Abolishes tax
Income taxes
Forgives mortgages zeros out credit cards and declares
Peace
Except otherwise specified the quotes in the passage passages
They all come from Robinson's reporting in advance Tribune fantastic article
The media apparently I'm not allowed to talk about this law
Basketball course
Because there's a gag order in place
That would be punishable by Death
Whatever
From the show
It's Showtime at the Apollo she gets ripped off of that believes it's an anonymous episode about
Are still around so we can get away with talking about it a little bit I saw if need be
Establishment they can't do it
Goodwin of Oneness got her start as an anonymous internet
By guy named Clyde Hood
Who did started this thing called the Omega trust in trading Limited
You claim to be a high-powered investment Trader and offered people quote units of Omega for $100
Which would quote
Rollover 425 275 days with return
Investors could let it roll again for another 275 days again
50 to 1
After that they could do one more roll but that was it
If you do the math hundred dollars into 12.5 million dollars no work involved
How could you not say yesterday
So naturally this is
Just enjoying it
Is dead now but no bituary for him estimated that he ran the scam from 1994 to the year two
I made about 20 million dollars from 90th and Chester
Man 2000 to guilty to a bunch of charges in it
Anyways that's 240 years in prison
Do not give up hope
Is Omega investment
Even though their payments were never materializing
As the scam was coming to a close and he was veering being arrested
The devil Oneness spun Fantastical yards by there was a conspiracy against Omega
And Heather forces including judges who are trying to fight for people to get their money
Brooker stories on supposed updates about Hood scam she gained a following
Probably mostly of people wanted to know where their 12.5 million dollars was
When he was arrested she created a narrative that the whole bus was a farce
And the people needed to keep their spirit I
She posted quotes stay away from the website that has information on this case through!
That's a good that's a good way to that's a good place to start if you don't keep information away.
Scream don't look at the information I like it will be tracked if you go to that website
We avoid any complaints are you going to lose your funding if you do that
Review about the Better Business Bureau
Investigators had taken claims to be reimbursed
From the money they seize from
Many investors refuse to file refused to even talk
The government investigators
The problem was the internet and the never-ending stream of rumor is led by Dove and others
Omega victims to clam up
Us attorney Steve Sanchez told the News Tribune quote
Everybody kept saying I'm told that it's going to pay tomorrow so I'm not talking to
We tried to persuade people that the information being put out there was erroneous
People didn't want to believe it
Good lawyer would even get calls from investors who wouldn't accept that he'd confessed to the fraud
Some of these people they just really really believe it acceptable to being victimized
Again
Who's all the load of s*** but it seemed to be some sort of a following
Above one misses work
According to her Omega was just one of many of what she called prosperity
Program
Apparently these programs were to be put in motion by this nesseralla that she imagined have been passed into law
By Bill Clinton
Arabia's by Messer I've been debunked by the guy who came up with the idea in the first place Harvey Barnard
The conspiracies to Sedaka
Land has its roots in people for of million
What Goodwin is done
2001's transmuted that human impulse to hold on to hope that their ship is coming
Cultish following further south to profit off of
And now it's being attached
Conspiracy theories about
Donald Trump
And that is
Kush
I got to give it up so she took
Working on this scam
With another guy
I don't think she was working on it with him
And that's something that comes up in this article that's really fascinating alright that because of how large this scam got and help her
Attracted
BC working theory around it was as it attracted a bunch of other scammers who wanted to drink
The long way
But shark
Looks like a little fish that clean sharks back that's what it's that's what's going on and if you look at is a microcosm of the
Trump Administration fraud going on
People who run Konza like
I've got to get a taste of this action by conscious or not that is a phenomenon that I think
See whenever you get too big
Well I mean if you see a bunch of people getting
Frauded you're like well obviously these people are right target audience
These people are susceptible to being victimized again because
They just want to believe right
You feel like an idiot
Really stupid Hood in one of his quotes that really likes stuck out to me was
I didn't realize how big of a liar I was
Because you made up
This whole thing
There was a point you made a choice you know who really got conned
Me
I was the real victim here I conned myself that that Chloe is a little bit of that
Mentality and then also a little bit of like maybe
Peking self-awareness have access to
Wow you was deluded himself into thinking he was doing something else
And that's fascinating to me.
This is what
Anthony believes is going on with the world today is this implementation of this mess around
What's Jessie
That's just a new one for Global
Is the same thing
It's basically the concept in the idea that we're going towards
With Trump and all this is it Google resetting of all economy
To be like
You know what shaking off of all debt and everything that everyone's going to be living in wonderful perfect prosperity
It's utopianism being funneled
Okay so
He believes that a man
Whose primary well
Comes directly from
Property ownership
Bankruptcy
Is going to suddenly switch tack
And Institute a utopian society
Eliminates those things I think it's probably because he believes that
Trump is being Guided by aliens
If he's suddenly got bleeding help very shortly and we saw a big change
I'm fine with that
Right now I'm not a big fan of the pleiadian
Hey babe been here since
The jump
Nah get melee ATMs out of here bro I'm done with it
So it turns out that
Anthony is a really big fan of qanon
Very important to study
Isn't the idea that
Is she definitely
Maria's
One of the people that are going to
They're actually already
The thing is is like
You said earlier
.
What you heard about
You know we're kind of
Society
Kind of behind
About what's really going on
And in those people that are under no
I kind of
In in more knowledge
But they have to roll it out as
What I like
I want to talk about
Qanon
And who qanon
Chewing on his
Because
That's pretty much like
People understanding WhatsApp
Is Adele
Thank you Anna
Qanon
Even saying this is Zach
Insane
Because they don't know if I
Mj-12
Is the organization m.j.
Is the government m.j.
Mj-12 was a credit
To infiltrate
What people
No as the Illuminati
They're actually not the
Because the Illuminati
Are the ones that actually
The glove go globalization
And the odd
The old world
Order that was being rolled out it's not a new world
It's actually an old
That has been
Implemented on Humanity
This leads to a really interesting conversation
Is like a really old school conspiracy
Paranormal
I know they're not all
Also this
He's framing
Most conspiracists call the New World Order the old world
Illuminati isn't really the Illuminati Illuminati
Globalization
I understand what you're trying to say
Okay I understand but you can't just
Call those things those things
Because everybody
You're going to confuse you
Words have to mean things if you want to communicate there's a good problem with reverse branding
So I think a lot of the ideas
Babe does Ender's expressing a lot of these things are probably have gotten into
Is subconscious is belief system because
Engaging in Italiano
Q conspiracy theory is another pretty solid clue of what might be leaving him down
Having these dreams where he is
On reconnaissance missions against the Umbrella Corporation in Michigan
For sure though I did it makes a lot of sense
So Carrie asked him if he's been dealing with the greys the Alienware
Scary
K & R
Familiar
Have you been dealing with
The grey
Not not not recently B
Because I mean I'm done with the
Gray's because that
You know
Very far back
Back in my in my
I'm like why
Like when I was 6
I'm getting up.
Definitely dealing
Retire
Beans now because even
Even now I'm remembering memories
A being involved
Soldier wear
I'm on fire
They actually
Talking meow
They they actually had the
The ability day
Ramble to wake me up
Telekinetic
And just spin me around
Throw me against the wall
So
I mean NASCAR
That's that's that's
That's what I'm
Okay
Nordx or not
Don't know their there they're not
They're not but they are
More advanced
Right
Okay
Into the Nordic
All right.
I think that the nordics are good guys
Right after conception
Racist version of
Alien white people
Yeah these are the champions
But yeah
I've never heard
I don't see I don't see
Zubs
I mean there are indications
Space Program super soldier there's creepers
Part of a treaty that they did with the good guys do enable them to kidnap children
He has been fighting aliens are traditionally on Project Camelot are seen as deposited right
It's complicated
I don't think those were humans that he killed after he fell down that elevator
Retract my credit
There is a Carrie doesn't
Bring up that sort of
Stumbling block the nordics
Testing about him just not straight up to
Instead he then says dealing with the gray
What that to be a euphemism for some sort of bathroom activity
I would like it to not be
Disagreement
So Carrie asks about some more qanon stuff the idea that JFK jr.
Crash
Standard JFK jr. selphius leads to a bit of confusion
Is really telling
You have
Inside knowledge
Is going on with
With Trump and
Qanon
Yes
Yes I do
I can
Confirm that
That is all
Everything that's
What's going on
Trump
Qanon
And Robert Half
Randy Junior
Technology
And everything
Is the truth
Because
Basically
Actually Robert
He is not John
John John
Julie died in the
Supposedly
Jonathan
But about anyway
You're you're talking about
John F Kennedy
Junior
Talking about yes
Who supposed
Julie died in a plane
They say now that
He and Caroline
His wife
And he is
Working with
I have
And I have
Not if not believe but
But knowing
That that is true
So I mean
From straight the problem is they're both sort of involved in the conspiracy
Junior is the one that does supposedly
Fake his death so we could help Trump now
Famous people shouldn't die in plane crashes
It's just a terrible idea is troubled
Oh God
That press conference be amazing
Casino here's my now we realize our opening back up the states as a consolation
Buddy Holly and the Big Bopper
What working with Trump all along
They didn't stop that song from happening now I want American Pie will never be played on the radio if it's too long to
Begin with
Subway
Don McLean
My career
I'm sorry what are you saying
I've completely forgot which
Tenergy junior is so they think
JFK jr.
Fake his own death some people believe he might even be the one doing the Tuesday okay
Cute might be JFK jr.
Cute communities about whether or not they believe JFK jr. is alive or not
That sounds foundational
I just I just hear this stuff inside
He was ready to say the RFK Jr
There's a confusion to the
No I'm talking about JFK jr.
Not believe that I know that it makes me think that this is a little malleable
Whatever it is you just said presented as conspiracy
This intersects with sort of more reality and again Alex Jones specifics
Is some of this conversation about the actual covid-19 situation
So-called
Right
What I know
Coronavirus
Is there are definitely making it worse
Seems like I
A starset
Way
July debates
Make more case
Happening than Iraq
And then there
Blaming
That aren't
Related to the
Coronavirus
Virus
How to make the numbers
More
You know
To make the numbers
Provide more feeder
That's just it you could hear out
You see a lot of overlap here and it's like wow this is the same thing
It's the same thing it's just Alex pretends that he something
We've allowed him to get away with it forever
I mean I guess I kind of know why
That means
Part of it is
You seem fun for awhile
I don't know
It's awful
It really is like it's the tragedy that is at the scale of it
How many people are dying and
How they're being
Push toward that death-like f****** Lemmings in a Disney document
But we have to look at it you can't deny it
You can't deny it and that's what it seems like everybody in this circle really wants to do
Yeah they just
They just can't look at
Because in a movie it's fine
You know it's not real
Right real they have to find a different movie two kind of retreat into yeah I mean that's kind of that kind of thing
Oh yeah
Dial for all movies to be reality you kind of allow for stuff in reality to be a movie
Burning of fiction and reality
Until it's
There's no blurring it
They simply both exists simultaneously and you just picking
Can choose whichever one you feel like believing at any given point in time
Coronavirus conspiracies that are being overlapped here
It's not surprising resource
In
Pushing this
In the Illuminati
Is AI a car
Call Doug
And it's basically got
Vaccine
Is on there
This is all part of the
Being rolled out
It's not it's not
What it seems to
Spoiler alert I have the Illuminati card game up on my wall wondering if you have that particular
But there's also like a ton of other things like Godzilla is one of the cards
Why was real
Let's get up and look at the Bigfoot that's one
Broccoli
Just fine I think soldiers are definitely part of the plan
Moonbase.
Monster monster is going on
See what else we got
No
Clone arrangers they arranged clones indiferenta Xanadu
Xanadu Buffalo real that was actually real we all have to wear roller skates
It's for the rest of the day
Are magic
Just just are magic I mean that's wind
Please call their women
Yeah I mean sure you can say whatever you want about this fun card game and what have you but
You do you got to recognize what else you're implying
Like all of those other things must also be part of the plan
Those things are put in to make the plan look silly to order a real card is
Universal game
The card game that's Steve Jackson Studios put out
Is somehow a revelation of
Of the plans
Scandalous Carrie decides to go to commenters
Text Vanessa Rose Bowl
Big shout-out to this commentary
In my whole life
I
And reality
Jesser nsra
St-germain
And the grand jury
Leanne
And all of that
I've been involved my home
Entire life
Not only
Restarting it
Knowing it's true
And I see it on
And in my
In my reality
It is it is
Corsair is Missy
Information
You know that you're go
Going to go through
But in the end
You you will get
Manuel
Actually
Unbearable
Do not doubt
What it is.
And then I do I do
I dunno
Through my purse
Spell memories
And it
Information gathering
Bring that that is
What is happening
I remember
Being involved
Is Nazareth
So that would be
They would not want
Sounds like b*******
You're so like that that there's going to be misinformation and stuff is exactly the same thing we do
It's dead when the scheme was falling apart
Don't look at that other information believe website
Such an intentional scam a spectre as
Clearly
No it's misinformation
Confirmation bias as a religion
Listen to this a lot of those overlaps of Alex and stuff
Wanted to get more information
His first interview with Carrie
Because this is somebody who she is now presented as a
Super soldier
On her show
The first time
If you listen to that episode
You get a ton of indications that there is
Something that he's dealing
He talks about healing himself from PTSD head from being in Iraq
Tell Ron Hubbard still seeing a psychiatrist
When you talk to him about stuff and the next time he came another guy was there with the secret space program
If you are a person like Harry and you were dealing with things responsibly
Probably a follow-up interview
You might not even put that one out to begin with
And it's one of the reasons why I'm trying
To be as careful as I can surrounding Anthony himself
Because
I kind of look at it
I kind of look at him in the same way I would have looked
Address khashab
Before she
Realize what she was doing makes sense he still has every potential in his
You know
Get to a point where he's living
More realistically
And have some more clarity about these things
Vanessa rotten Jessa run-on sentence and all this super soldier stuff that he's falling into
I don't I don't think that he
Is necessarily
Running what you do
Describe is a full-scale Khan
At least
As far as I can tell there's not wholesale bigotry going on
Start the Hallmarks of someone who's too far I guess he's
Metaphorically
I don't I don't see the indications of someone who's lost
Just someone who's maybe in a bad
Place yeah I like
There a lot of people
That I noticed
So hard was the way Carrie
Was manipulating him
By using those pauses
After he says something like she's not allowing him to continue speaking and you can tell the way he
Noises the pause mean
I didn't say what she needed
I didn't say what she wanted and she knows
She's definitely exploding him in in that kind of way as like
Is a scientific in this circumstance
Because the dead kind of
A larger awareness that important
About what she does
Like what this show is
On sublevel is masquerading as like
It's not necessarily that there's there is
Enabling
Making
A business out of other people's unhealthiness just like Alex's show what's
Far more important than any conversation is
Making sure the narrative is what she wants it to be
Got2b a call-in show
You can you can say I've got a whole I talk to everybody and s*** like that
If you're doing this show you're talking to people who are going to support the things that you were
Give you a sounding board to get what you want out of
Dwell in this kind of a space and you're doing interviews like this I think you have a heightened responsive
I think that you actually have
A greater standard that you need to live up to then somebody
Who's doing
Let's just say like a show where you interview people have a new book coming out
Is about some sort of the mainstream talk show I think you have a far greater responsibility
In terms of
Being aware
That the water is you swim in
Attract
People who are having
Trouble sometimes a higher likelihood of someone
With an idea closer to what you believe
Having some sort of
Ology behind it
And it is important if you want to deal with things responsibly
Cater to people
Look after people
And what I see and absences in anytime
I've looked at Camelot
An absolute
Responsibility
Yeah
Then people expressing pain and exploiting
And I don't know if Anthony is expressing that much
Because I don't think
He doesn't appear to be struggling nearly as much as
Like the people who I wouldn't cover right they had similarities to Alex or whatever
It's not worth it and he's not talking about this
Feel like it's pain to him his
He's not even have a completely flat affect
What are you saying
He seems to have like some points for he laughs like he doesn't seem like it's somebody who's
Right Right Alright context clues to be able to like okay this isn't a secret
Space Program super soldier
This is somebody who believes
Stuffed is right on qanon
And has some sort of a whole
This is is satisfying
Yeah and I think that it's irresponsible is your someone like Harry to not
Be
Hyper aware of that
Because you're in a position where you have a show
That has an audience
You are in a position where you could
Take somebody who's going through something
Maybe it's being influenced by some negative things online
Maybe it's a phase for them or something they're trying it out because they need something to hold onto
There's tens of thousands of people who have listened to their story
And are giving them reinforcements
And now you put them in a situation where
One path
Leave towards
Getting help
And being healthy
I am that requires you to reject all the endorphins and the sense of meaning of this
New conspiracy world has given me
You have to give up whatever that
Crutch it's been built here
Sense of safety
Yeah it's a sense of life
That's that's the that's the thing that I keep noticing so much of these people is that they
Cannot allow for an utterly
Chaotic
Nonsensical universe
Universe
It's it's crazy
Somebody has to be in control
Somebody has to be in power
Somebody has to be orchestrating stuff
It can't just be
Ludacris Psychopaths
F******
Floundering around like
Flounder
Can't
Just sad
Yeah so we have a couple Clips here of the original interview because I think there's some Towing things in here they
They give us a little bit more insight into
Things that would have been like.
Pursue this further carry
But you can't because she's not very good at isn't responsible
What are the things that gives me a strong indication that this is like
Her game is not good
And I'm also
Not one that
The documents
Baked
And therefore
On
Either
So I human
Are the
Natick Library
Bible
Archivist
Well out of our own
You're so
This is testimony
Testimony is it
Law in fact
So
Take it for what it
It's worth this is not a court of law
Document
No you can't you can't lie
You can take a document chili that's the rule strong distrust of documents
People saying
Wow
I don't stand on documents because humans are the archival archivist
I'll just talk to Sean David Morton
Documents
Like a really workable system I want to believe
F*** everybody
So in this first interview that came out about a year ago
Gives a little bit of an indication of how his path down this road I came
To be Maya Maya my mentor is
His name is name is Rob.
That's just one of one of the mentors
I'm back basically when I started
Waking up
Space Program
Iiii
Rumpke
And I actually attended the school
And and and that was
What was being taught there was
And I'm obviously at the beginning I was
Ready to handle
Stan of what we
Top there
Because
He always says you know it comes in levels
And he always says you're not ready
Handle what I'm going to tell her what a happy
Because you have to
You know
Raise yourself up to the level
The knowledge of the truth
So Trump has come up with a few times on the show on the map the 40,000 year-old lemuria and warriors.
Spirit
Who's been described as racist anti-semitic a super 10
Channel 840 thousand-year-old lovari and spirit actually does have 100 problems
So JZ Knight is made a ton of money on this hustle and for a long time
In fact
She was doing it back when Clyde hoods Omega scam according to the News Tribune article
Attorney Prosecuting the case Steve Sanchez
Realize several victims were linked to JZ Knight
The Ethereal New Age Guru claims to channel the spirit of a 40000 year old Warrior named Brahms.
Later in the article
That's how I became involved in it was through the school one student said
I was involved practically everybody else I knew at the school was involved in it
There were tons of people involved in this on just a cash basis
People were sending in cash cash with no paperwork no receipt no nothing
People were promised their money was going to come in before the next snowfall
Probably just a coincidence that also took classes at the school
Cool cool
What's going on here
This Anthony guy isn't a super soldier he's just a guy who has fallen under the sway of a cult
Yeah and Carries using him to advance around there It Is by presenting the story is genuine and that's really unfortunate
Because there is a better
Cute future black guy
Do they ever like a like wouldn't fight
Skaneateles
Not like not like he's just a guy who's trying to hunt
I'm not driving sure
Start a lot of this stuff like it starts to come into focus it starts to make sense this is what
What's going on
Pretty involved in chewing on stuff
To like a promotion of the qun allowed to roam free
Yeah yeah
Yep wow that's not good
They shouldn't have
All of this Bruns
Perfectly
Sensibly if you start to look at okay
Started to have these ideas
He pursued this romp the school
He went there started to learn about all this stuff
And as it turns out that school was a hotbed of people who are involved in the Omega Trust eomer
Course he now believes in as being involved in some kind of a magical play
I don't know seem like there's so many of these people are just searching
Like just going from call to call
Just like
Please just take away my personal responsibility please I want nothing
To do with it
Tell me what
To do remove me from having to think or feel
That's the goal when I listen
If
Some of these ideas about the secret space program super soldier
Or started by herself
Yeah because
You definitely listen to her other interviews cool with super soldier
You know I've been
A fair number of
Say
And so I guess it wondering
If you're familiar with
Indianapolis
Interview
Did you watch any
And at the time did it trigger you and also
Where you aware
That I was in my lab beef
Told you about it I mean I think
You said you heard
Staying on the show
Were you aware of it
Before I said it
Yeah I would definitely where you were my last
Watch money
I knew that
All the other super soldiers that you interviewed
Aaron
Max spiers
At work work
Earring there
Did
You know support mining
Help me smile
The others
You know the interview
So it was pretty old interviews early on in Camelot throughout and
I can't help but think that maybe
What is an expression of
I got into this form of oral tradition the storytelling medium that you were engaged in with these people
All the time I started having dreams and then I realized that the only reason that it could
Possibly Vibe with me this much
And why I could dream about it all the time it's because
I myself must be one of those super
A soldier it's a possibility
Also if if there's only one answer to the question
Did you know I was in my lab before or
There's only one answer that question
If you answer that wrong
Get out of the game
Jordan do you think that you could beat up a super soldier
I mean I'm not really Nordic you know I'm more Irish
So you think
Not a super soldier
What is the point of having a super soldier if I could defeat
Well I don't know if you could
I should tell you that from 2011
Xander was an MMA fight
Okay how did he do
His record
Was six
6 + 12
Backtracks with only 133
His last fight was a 8-second knockout that he lost
Stuff like that
If you were super soldier you're not going to lose 12
Unless all MMA fighters are Super Soul
That is possible from 2018 to 2020
And flight was
February 14th 2020 you started boxing
Okay amaru became a boxer and his current record is
1 + 7
Okay that's not great that's not great
His second most recent fight was on December 5th
Buy a debuting
Boxer
Okay
First boxing match in 2018 in January 2018
Since then all seven I've been losses three times knocked out
Good that's really bad but should be knocked out once
I mean for your brain
It's tits sub
In the martial arts in the in the pugilism
Someone who was
I prepared for their entire life to be a super soldier and at the black put up them and all of that
You would assume
Might be unbeatable
And it seems to me very difficult to square that with
Losing records in boxing and MMA going back to 2011
I mean I guess if part of his super soldier thing though is that he's in an inter-dimensional body too it's not always
That's why I always that's why it's really difficult right stuff when it's in a different body in a different truck
Problem is his real body was kidnapped at 6
Dental implant out of it it's difficult for me to square
Kind of makes the story hard to believe that
I mean more like just theirs
But there's permanent brain damage that comes with being knocked out that many times
Like that some serious tough assumption to make
You know
Maybe to be considered I don't
I don't I don't know why.
Certainly if you were boxing and be like 80s doing that you do pro wrestling back when they did a
Protective
Then yes I would be far more
Concerned but since they started fighting in 2011
Hey baby I don't know we've evolved along ways
And fairly recent
Understanding
Because in a little bit better but
Yeah I don't I don't I don't know
I don't
Decently well
Outside of times and there's like
He clearly doesn't know which Kennedy is being disgusting I don't think there's any kind of cognition problem that's just
He doesn't know the story
Communicating and telling a story that has a beginning middle and end
Any indications of diminished
Function
Never ask him about the other people that I haven't listened to so I don't know if it comes up in those
Seems like a different you know that how are you draining all the time for MMA and also being a super soldier that strength
Transferring from
Dimensions dimension
It's not important
It's not a Borden probably that's a good answer
Wava wave
But I don't recall it coming up and Carries interviews I didn't watch the second one I only watch the first and the third
I didn't I just enough time
Clips from the original interview which is very confusing for me
Anthony talks about a raid that he went on
The alignments of the
People who are supposedly his superiors
How to recall where I was
In a blackout
You know here and everything
Oswegatchie Squad
We're out
I'm doing a race
And then
The next day
You
It was actually a real
Stronghold
And I just kind of hours like
Okay.
Memory
Miranda sings. About this
Radon
Courtney Armstrong
I definitely believe that I
So that's a dream
I like that I like that mess that checks out for me
So the secret space program super soldiers
Running raids against Clinton
I don't know I can't keep track of this
I think I think alliances and in such changes
In in their world everybody's eating people for Chuck
Who knows mesirow require strange bedfellows
This next clip makes me think that Anthony is probably a decent hearted person
Actually you
22in expand
Believes
The things that you saying
Because otherwise I don't know why you would make this up
You also
Involved
If I wasn't
Life revolve
Germany
Be involved
Nazi
Situation
Yeah yes
Yes but from my understanding I was
Traded as a Nazi
Because I've had many memories
Being with Nazis
Indominus
Gathering
And all that
But I might I do I do
I definitely have
You know I I believe that
He carries response is exactly what someone's response would be
Make that up
Probably because even if you are presenting it is I was infiltrating them to get information
CU road to walk it still open
Are you sure I really feel like that should have been a very obvious question to answer as well
Are you a Nazi
Well it's not the way to go Highway
Okay I think I was going to know I've spent a lot of time with Nazis
You can even tell a recognition in the way that you talking of like
This is bad probably have
He's definitely in better with some nothing
And it makes total sense when you consider the soda that he conceives of his being the Spy
Cast The Umbrella Corporation thing is there then the Nazis
So obviously if I was doing Secret work
I would have been doing that if there was anything to infiltrate it would have been Hitler
If you weren't such a bad spy maybe we could have taken down the Nazis a lot earlier
He probably blew his cover and this is that was
That was the whole Valkyrie thing we got Tom Cruise involved now this whole thing is terrible I'm telling you
That must be better spies that must be what happened
Yeah I don't I don't know but you mean
A non-malicious
So good
I had to been involved in trying to take them down
Which is a pure hardness on level you would never bring that up if you were
Just trying to come up with
I feel like it you just leave that off the resume
Cutting there too if you're like in my dreams in my past life I would I would remember being around a lot of Nazis
So I'm assuming that I was a spy
Good that leaves a lot of open to interpretation
That's almost done
A Reconciliation you always like in my past life I was a Nazi
I know they're bad now
So I'm going to hope
Set my past-life knew they were bad as well
Last year from the original one
Watching The X-Files
Everything in it is true and it responds to this is pretty
Diamond Naturals
So much the best
X-Files
Mexico
All about Logan
It's all in there it's on the Xbox
Are not communicating
I want sword arms out a wolf guy
My favorite X-Files
That's a good vial of X-ray to me that someone who was career is in this space
The X-Files are and fix their the X-Men
It also doesn't know what the X-Men are
Do is David Wolverine
Don't even know Weapon X
So f****** funny
X-File is Logan
Delightful
Wake me up by one of those episode is it was difficult
Trying to figure out exactly
You know how you'd look at this I think there's enough stuff that makes it interesting
Carrie is the bad person
Yeah you can look at with
Compassion
To an extent
I'm not nut tree
Somebody was falling into something
Baby is way deeper
Waters then
Baby
It appeared at first
Getting involved with Robinhood and the JZ Knight nonsense and the qanon
Now being
Assertive enabled by a high-profile internet
Yeah it's very
It's very difficult
And I don't I don't
I don't know I ate
Stop it stop
To figure out exactly where the line is of how much empathy people deserve
Because he's still putting out like messages that are destructive Coronavirus
Nihilism
You know Paving the way for Trump's authoritarian move
You know denial about that
And that's still really bad that I feel needs to be countered with
A full-throated rejection and development by
Yo I think someone like this
You can take
Contacts
Excludes to see exactly how this came to be right
It's hard not to feel bad for the guy
Who is Dad or Mom
Watch too much Fox News and became
Something that's almost unrecognizable
BS the thingy
Is bad
Kind of
Have a lot of empathy for the path
Right maybe didn't know you were going. My family is great example
Full of people who've been manipulated by
All of this
Right-wing nonsense but
You know they want to believe that s*** too so it's like
Pamela is way more fun
Fraudsters
It's like
Now we have a clear Villa
And
He's bad
I'm glad cuz I don't want to give the impression they project
Plot is
Relatively benign in in that kind of senses when you know like this this show is destructive
Along the same lines as info I mean not more so cuz obviously Alex is audiences
Cupboard
On her show are maybe more Insidious because
To certain minded people there's so much more attractive
Yeah
Like the the Escape ISM MB the
Tension look like
I have super powers
All this kind of stuff it's very much like I have swords for arms
Seductive attractive and then the real world
Implications of it are things like
Coronavirus denialism Trump boosterism qanon beliefs
Two things where the road leads
And it's not that much different than Alex
Most
Infuriating thing to know that these people are clinging to these conspiracy theories and
The idea that Trump is not an amoral monster
As a way of feeling safe
And in control of things are at least somebody being in control of things
And yet that very
Feeling of safety is what's killing you
You know like that's
That's this I feel safe because I think
Trump is not an amoral monster
And because he is
You are not safe
Legacy
Yep you're the vector by which
Your lack
Safety becomes Usher
That's the modern crisis
Yeah
So anyway
Need to take a little break from Alex and imports
Project Camelot
What is uplifting
Maybe a mark Richards
Interesting on sublevel aspire
That's my next tattoo
Jordans
Israeli review donate and if you would like please find a local charity in your area and donate to them
Absolutely
Alexandra Thurston color with your trip and I love your work