Knock knock
Damn important
I have great respect for
B b
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Acknowledge
I love you
Just a little bit
About Alex Jones
I don't know you
My bright spot damn is Dennis Rodman
I know you were texting me about watching The Last Dance
Because I was huge
Chicago Bulls fan
Specifically
Loving Dennis Rodman so much but I was only like
8 or 8:10 at the time and I remember all of the anti
Just grab clear identity stuff that I got from my more Library himself and when
Is hole like oh you can't do that and all that s*** and then I'm watching
An awesome
I love Dennis right enough to help do his
Yeah what's up
Now but in the 90s
Those are rough and tumble.
Detroit Pistons
Nice recommendations from people about
Filters to try and throw the people are getting in on the ACT
And simultaneously I'd like to I think
Some of the people who have
How about you still being weird Road
I appreciate both of these these responses to people are having
Is there tolerance
We're going to be talking about May 10th
+ 11
20/20 abandoned
Sunday and Monday
Throw Tuesday and as well keep us up Soopers
Up-to-date but
Couldn't do it
Too much
In so many different ways
How many different ways he
Canby
It's a masterclass
Yes more less do you cook
Ambien
And we'll get down to business on that before
First robber
Thank you so much
Text Marcy
Smart cellular
Daniel
Spell Graeme
Spelling of Grey
Next
Thank you so much you and I'll probably walk
Who donated
The first
Great. Thank you so much you are now a technocrat
Second-generation rosicrucian
Thank you so much you are now it's
Technocrat
We got to go
Heroin
Thank you so much Craig and thank you so much second-generation rosicrucian
I'll try.
In your area that help
We would love it if you did either
We got to do a little bit of the update on the ear of the seltzer
Hi.com and people reporting the show
You sometime today
There should be a
Part 1
Of Acumen a series up on are just on our homepage
Ave
Together and we drank some Seltzer's
And
Thank you so there's some
On that to be
Have you found them for your enjoyment
Feel free to listen to it now if it's if it's up or you want to wait till Thursday give yourself a nice little bridge between
I didn't want to put it up on the regular podcast 3 because I felt like it might be over bird
People people want it so that's
255 South
There's now there's a lot of lot of the progress being made here
And you know it goes good on the Western Front as they say
I got some Whole Foods brand
Shelters that come in large glass bottles
Okay and they're great
Celtics
Good and lemon raspberry coming in at 72
It was better
Bears
Elderberry never buy this
But I realize
I don't know what elderberries
I have no idea
Could be great could be terrible I don't know
Will find out
Pineapple passion fruit
And I have a slight expectation that that might end up being
One of the one of the ones that breaks into the Ada
Oh well
Pineapple is done
I may have an unknown or realized
Improved as we discussed
The Dark Horse
Cool food pineapple passion
Fruit but I'm keep it in the fridge cuz I don't want
I feel like I have to get through every coconut one I can find if you disappointed in horrified
Sephora
I treat myself
Up to something so wonderful is pineapple
10th and 11th
Lot of f*****-up nonsense to get through
From Jay Chou
What are we doing today
Take me to Everyday pinky taking over the world
You bet it is
I got excited that
Woody's River Roo
Even as he gets
The quote
Going wrong
Yeah
Stickler they never actually succeed in taking over the world
As far as I recall from my brain
Viewing
Start on Sunday and Alex number of narratives that he wants to
Do I get busy on in this country
Chips
Did you know
5 years ago in Sweden
Free bus ride
More than 10
Stockholm syndrome named ROM
Wow
Congrats
10000 people I guess that's
Come syndrome
Dot-com
Implantable gym
Look at is
Look at those little juicy
Benjamin Netanyahu says he wants
Child in Israel
Next year to get chips
Elegant agency
You're inside the New World Order
Just like that
So there's some is representations going on here and some irresponsible reporting
Snooze a little piece of
Did you see
That's gross that's kind of
Par for the course
This guy tells the story about Sweden
If you can get free bus ride
What he's referring to is a pilot program that a train company called SJ tried in 2017
Tips to store their electronic
Train tickets
On this check
I found an article about this in the independent and this line seems particularly relevant
Before you pack your bags for Sweden to steam is only app
Already have implants
S.j. is not offering to chip
Around 2000 Suites
Most of them employed in the check-in
Already have a chip
Here let's try this out and you guys can try it out never
The biohacking idea took root and start-up companies with the implant being offered to be used as an optional
Access building
And was specifically designed to not be able to be tracked
2017 article in the Washington Post
Power supply
Can't send signals about its position
Obviously their concerns one could have about what
The technology could grow into in the future and the challenges presented through the privacy
Doesn't seem to be that effective in terms of
The Beast that Alex wants to breathe
Yeah why
2000 people already have implanted train company decided to test if they could use them to store
The consumers still has to buy two get two free tickets
That's where the chip isn't it
They're not chipping people by luring them in with free transportation and if you don't want to get one of these chips
There's still tons otherwise goodbye
It's the ride
And I do all the other things that the chip enables you to do like
Get into building
Lubbock ecard
I'm always fascinated by how terrified these people are of a computer chip
The phone that can be remotely turned on without their knowledge and record everything that they're saying
You know one of those is Boris
Moore's more scary
Some of these articles about the Swedish
Chip thing
Clearly bring that point out
A July 2019 article New York Post
I would assume he's just exaggerating from headlines like quotes
The swedes are inserting microchips under their skin
From NPR
That number is not 10,000 BC
Assuming that's what I guess is going on
Route number
The story about Benjamin Netanyahu his proposed is something completely different
He suggested that is a part of reopening after the coronavirus Israel should put chips in all school children which would that be
Beeping noises if I got too close to each other
Which presumably would help
Looking for some social distance
That doesn't sound like a great idea but
Okay
Expensive roundly rejected the idea saying it's practically on feasible legally impossible
Achieve the desired results
It seems from what I can tell that this proposal is not going to get off the ground
Resilient expert Enoch Mehran in the article
Kind of makes clear why
Is the information with the kids location is uploaded to the internet a pedophile with some cyber knowledge man
Stock them outside their school
Distribute the information on other platform
Miron said
Can the state take responsibility for that
Concerns like that system for a state to put in place
Until I see evidence
To the contrary this kind of seems like a world leader blowing hard
About how they Envision returning to some kind of normalcy
And let's not forget that just back in January
Three separate corrupt
Jim cases
These cases are ongoing and since he's been convicted
Is prime minister
May not go on indefinitely
Yep
Anyway
Here is it
These two situations with microchips
Completely deaf
One of them is a passive chip that's not run by the government and does not track people being used you know
Music like a key card
Whatever
The other is a
Suggesting geo-locating chips in children
Dishonest have a conversation where you treat these is equivalent to even related things
Riley involved microchip
Especially since one of them took me all the four-second
Can stew be like
That's a terrible idea
Very easy to know that nobody's going to follow through on netanyahu's ridiculous nonsense
You can have a conversation about how like the idea of this weekend
Programmatic
Facilitator
Jordans that conversation by all means
Talk about it
It's not even close
Do the same thing
As what
Just makes them the same thing
So
Dokken
Nothing love
I'll tell you what I mean
It's impressive
The old
Vikings
A lot of the Viking tribe
When a man die
Alright
A ship and send them out the water on
Call Halla together
I'm listening
That netanyahu's idea
Why do people a
Call Sharonda
Just to be clear Alex's reason for the cultures all doing this
Because interdimensional demons are compensated for their pleasure or something
Unfortunately this appears to be yet another thing that I was selling a movie and decided to call
Deep research
For one thing Viking funerals at see we're absolutely not the standard form
You can easily see how absurdly expensive that would be calm if you were making boats and burning them it's easy for every person who died
Infinite resources
There were some people who have funeral pyres in boats on the sea
Really important
Certain people
The different groups that are all lumped in his liking we're not uniform culture but most people were cremated or just buried
Typically a really important symbol in their culture representing
Play passage to the afterlife
Or even cooler their burial mounds be made to resemble ships
Themselves
That is fun
This was far more common than the funeral at sea but the funeral
Besides it's starting
This
Put on a boat
It actually started in the 1958 film the bike
Has been a really popular truck ever since then
It is
Really
I mean listening
Is really cool
Even hit it so far away
So what are the difficulties on this subject is the actual written history of the record about
People's is limited precise reasons were for why they did the things they did
In terms of funeral ritual
It's a really
Diverse set of funeral rituals
Seem to involve
Chaos
I know exactly what was going on
They're up there may have been some instances where of Norsemen being buried with their wives
Like murdered you know
But was far more common was them killing slaves
To be buried with a person to help them on their trip to the afterlife
Which is company unfortunately do see a lot of older cultures
Also there's no reason for Alex just to think that women were property in Viking communities
Archaeological evidence
Not property
And that's allowed to have to have some sort of
Autonomous life
Additionally in 1904 the remains of the Ellsberg ship were found in vestfold Norway
The ship was a funeral vessel which served as a burial site for two
Norse women who died around 8:34 Cee
Disappear like a particularly large boat casket
70 ft long 17 ft wide and 30 ft High
Forgive the strong evidence
Position in their community
Possible
Because he's only see movies and TV shows
Cuz that's where the Viking you should have asked
Marley bird about
Gallagher love it
This is not to say that
Finger probably
Just flipping
Perspective
It just watch some TV and movies
This is nonsense
You could not tell you whether or not
A ship
All of it
Parts have been ripped
Flexed
Interesting philosophical question
Sure and also there's one
So there's that too
Askew
If
You're Alex Jones
You're circling the drain desperately
And things are falling apart
Michael Wright
Follow through with
Plan that you had
Before the virus outbreak
Where you start talking more about Seth
Can't think of any reason why not
Can I say has Seth rich and Wikileaks attorney Klein
Y'all know it
Was
The Laker
So the story here is
Is that name.
Clevenger
The claims regarding 7
Mercedes van
Substantiating anyway
Corduroy
His first claim is that he's been told that the NSA or other related agencies are in possession of communication
Between Seth rich and WikiLeaks
There's no evidence provided for this claim never stopped Alex from believe in something
Before
Clevenger he claims several high-ranking FBI and NSA officials have seen the correspondence
Between Bridge
And Wikileaks first
To which I say
Prove it probably
He's probably talk about
Clevenger goes on to claim that he has
Seymour Hersh
Clients and claiming that he spoke to someone at the FBI
Confirm emails between rich and Wiki
This recording is not available in the Infowars article
To this I say let's see that audio
Because I have found somebody
It related to this topic someone
This guy needs to put up
This what I'm saying I think he's one of those guys probably
I don't need to put a
So this seems to be a
Conspiracy theorist
Threads it existed from the beginning
Seymour Hersh thing was a claim that goes back to at least 27
Debunked
What are the odds
Conspiracist
Ed butowsky was a trump associate donor
Became convinced of the FBI
Including the Seth riches
After speaking to the legendary reporter Seymour Hersh
Who was also investigating Richard
Is that
According to the transcript to confirm the report
That's for me 2017 thing
NPR interview verse about this and he said
I hear gossip
Petoskey took two into inmate 45 out of
Alright
This misrepresentation
Universe was passed from Petoskey to Fox News
Which ended
In lawsuit
Define smelling like a rose
Exactly clevenger's.
Vlog
Fflogs La Flaca
Another reason that I'm kind of worried about clevenger's work is
Because he also said in this post about the Seth Rich stuff
Back to the NSA
Former NSA officials Bill Binney at Loomis and Kirk wiebe or prepare to testify
Could not have been
Obtain
Is it a huge problem because build in his walk
Back that quick
From everything I can
He would not tell
Because he was about
Wheatley wrong
This again is another element of these claims being made by
Clevenger that just the old separate
Conspiracy ship.
And pretending that it all hasn't already been discredited
This is pretty sad
My time watching Howard Pretenders new information
Careful though because this is a topic that has led to a number of people being sued already
And the family of separate does not seem thrilled people are
Keeping this alive in his situation though part of him must be like
What else do you got
Bugaloos
Join the fun
Club
You're going to be the last one to sue me if I have any money left at the end
You still might be able to get a little press out of maybe I can
Make a arrangements or something
I can saddle
Whatever
Jangling Keys away from his guy being the worst human being on the
He doesn't want to
No and one way is he
You know distracted attention
Understand
Episode is one of the rare instances where Alex is throwing
Spaghetti at the wall
See what we can
Course A lot of it does Dylan Coronavirus denialism
That is you know
The craft the Giant
Conspiracy is
Of course Bill Gates's
Right right right
Unfortunately the number 6 has come back up
In another place
Congress bill
Malawi government
For covid-19 in their homes
The gentleman
Let me give you
The bill number
Now that's one too many buddy
Bracelet
I got to say that it's satisfying all the satanic actually ever 66
I know I understand the bill numbers just sixes but it's not 666
That patent filing number to may have been 060606 that is not 666
Is the number of the Beast is 666 that isn't Revelation saying
Hey weirdo look out for numbers that remind you of
Insects
6666666 and I reject some lazy level of death
The devil is fungible is always willing to play a little game around
Suggestion
The f*** out of here
Here's some other bills that are the number 6666
2017 2018 legislative
Which
Relates to authorizing the care and treatment will be licensed and certified acupuncturist
Under the Workers Compensation Program
Go see an acupuncturist
Who was fighting the devil
Let's not get bogged down into it because
Cuz this s*** run
Deep-seated satanism
Twenty-eight teams US House of Representative
Bill HR
664 as you might remember a quote
The bill to authorize the Secretary of the Interior the grant to States and local governments
Human
Federal Gateway National Recreation Area
For construction operation and maintenance
Birth control and prevention of flooded
That's
Exactly like
Did you choose to hear about that level of evil
Easements
Sweetheart
Shoreline erosion
Stop
Is 6666 is basically just 666 scouring phone number
Shades of devil worship
But it was phone number is
Suspiciously
969 6666
That's an extra 6729 there's basically upside-down sixes
This thing goes
Realize how deep
You know you know
They're even pockets of satanists in the world of early 1900s Texas Rangers how else could you possibly explain that one
What's the most famous Rams
King County Texas is literally named D 6666 Ranch
He's close
I sent a little bit of personal
Yeah
So house resolutions are numbered in the order they're introduced
6665 resolution
Pop up
You're not to get a sick sick sick sick
Legit means nothing
Bill 6666 in the 2007/2008 session
Congress is actually support
Quotes
The greenhouse gases are not subject to the bill
I bet that number would become
Yeah that one actually does sound
66c to me
Ordered this year you know there was already a bill 666 right that happened already
I don't know what I was thinking
The stupid numerology
Want to play
I guess he's free to
He just looks pretty f****** embarrassing from where I'm sitting
Quote to authorize the Secretary of Health and Human Services
These to conduct diagnostic test
Sing for covid-19
And related activities such as contact tracing units and is necessary at
Individuals residence
And for other purposes
Let's pause there
When is authorizing
Secretary of HHS to give G
I was just realize the Trump gets to decide who the Secretary of HHS
The Deep state
This is a presidential appointed position
Currently in that role
If this were some kind of a nefarious thing or this bill was meant
Facilitate you
It literally could only be done by the action of the person Trump hired and
Could fire unless they're blackmailing Alex Azar
Already
After just the first line of attack you can see how any conspiracy about this is mostly
Not on content
Who's very short film
He's going to complain about like some news article being four pages long
It's not like
He's a guy who likes primary information
If you read this
It's pretty clear that what this bill is about is allowing Secretary of Health and Human Services
Eligible organizations
Increasing artistic capacity
Conceivable
To return safely to something resembling normal
The part about doing in-home testing Debbie something
We could do this already
You can imagine
How much better is system it would be easy to get reliable testing at home
As opposed to thinking you might be sick
If doing so is a risk
The others
This whole conspiracy is a lot of bulshit and at this point I'm weary
I'm just weary
To create the appearance of something
It sounds like something I didn't see that
Give them a Grinch
2 people who will break into your home and test you for a disease I think that's
That's a great idea
I don't
I don't think they put forcibly in that go
Think so
Hyzaar could stop it
You could just say I'm not going to
Problem-solve
Even if you're evil pocket version
You have the Ace of Spades to play pretty sure everybody
Everyone's in on it
So tired
You know how like hotels don't have 13 floors
Superstitious
Get rid of these Bill numbers that are weird 420
Bill 69.1
Yeah we got to do something cuz these
Dum Dums
I just can't handle things
Alex Wassabi Coronavirus
Conspiracy to ramble about in this line
Baby dumber than some of those others
President is
Neurologist
Everything that's fine
Presidents named John
Anther is
Top biology
Doctor in chemistry which is not biology
I have no idea what else is claiming he's invented and now it's isn't specific about it
Is a viral meme that
It's been going around about Michael Cooley claiming that he sent a sample of
Quail
For covid-19 and they came back positive
There's been absolutely no evidence provided to back up his claim
Is currently facing a great deal of pressure
Over his handling of the virus
Whole lot like something someone would say they were earlier
Maybe some more replicating
Controlled environment I think
Probably a Tanzanian president talkingshit
Also Alex should definitely not like
2018 article in the mail & Guardian
Discusses his government
Assaulted
Kidnap hit with papayas all over
In 2017 began operation
There were not to his liking
Including five prominent TV stations and the Swahili language
He introduced a $920 license for the government
Required to obtain to be able to post things online
Licenses that the government
If the writers post content that they disapprove of us just to protect against fake news down
And then there were these threats to have
Anti-government protesters beaten like stray dogs
Just forget
Displeasure with the way the government was operated
Everything Alex
Pretends is happening in the US
Because he's not allowed on Twitter actually is happening to journalists and activists
Tanzania
He doesn't know any of that s*** and he doesn't care
This guy came out and said something useful for Alex's Coronavirus
So he's not only a great president
Troubleshoot means anything
0 works
To go from
Nothing to top biologist
Fun for Alex to use and guess what you just got a promotion
The top biology
Alex gave Nobel Prize
If you have any publisher you're not working for a prestigious universe
University
Blog post
Ever winner of the Nobel Prize in literature
Sure
So there's been some trouble going on in the world
A real the real world as they call it
With some cases of the virus
Meat Packing
Robust conversation
Alex
300 +
Blood test positive
Not one God
Fever
Symptomatic
You're so smart
Of course
Deposit
So smart
Tyson plant
On September 19th
The story of
Complaint tested positive doesn't actually make the argument Alex's claiming it does
The last decade or whatever wide 300 out of 2010's positive
Introducing the idea that some tests are always being positive and some additional Eric
I don't think I was ready or able to prove at all
I'm not positive
Exactly what planet he's talking about unfortunate
Because there were a number
Number of situations
Similar to this or Longview
Do you talkin about a Tyson plant that's
For sure
To tell you the Business Insider reported on Monday that 585 Tyson workers and 15th
Shapes of a diagnosis
Covid-19
And 18 have died
That's the reality that Alex is sitting at the propaganda as a Meredith
It's pretty important not to lose sight of that
These arguments are ghoulish
And even if the numbers are accurate
They don't make the Casey thinks they do
Now does not make sense
Now these this
Insane
These people are
Tyson plant
Here
Later in the episode we find out
He thinks it's the same thing
As a port
Plant in Missouri
Which isn't run by Tyson
Is the story that was about a plant that was run by
Triumph Foods
Alex conveniently ignores
Update about that story when he
Covers
Not that
I was just hanging on the asymptomatic thing here to argue that none of these who are actually sick and it's all a charade
I feel like
If this guy who's unidentified
The story is that
Maybe this
Way to do it
Yep
Possible
Join the class action lawsuit that will eventually I assume
Tyranny of the United
States of America
Why not
Make it a slap Alex gets slapped suits against everybody
Do in this next clip Alex discusses how like you know
Virus
That is all we need
The focus on
Sure
That means
Left by the wayside
Will you ever understand
That this
Covid-19 thing is the launch of the New Order take
Everything else is just a side
Issue I mean
Police report said that
Somebody
No
Feeling four-wheelers
Force
Robin house
You got to go to prison for what they did probably not
Some of the details of the shooting of Ahmad Arbury
It does seem like a lot of
Details around this one
Kind of sounds like he's describing a police shooting of somebody who was suspected
That's not the case
In reality Aubrey was shot by Travis McMichael
Who's used to be a cop but is not anymore
Michael and his dad chase down
This was not
Excessive lethal Force being used by police
/ appeals to racism
In the police report the Elder McMichael claimed that he saw arbore out jog
Must be a burglar
This makes sense
Considering that he wasn't carrying anything
McMichael stated the unidentified male began to violently attacked Travis and the two men then started fighting over the shock
Travis fired a shot
This story is contradicted by video that have been released of the altercation
Which clearly shows arbore trying to jog around McMichael
Truck
Immediately after that you see Travis
McMichael outside the truck
Can a bit of a lock-up with arbery
After which there are two more shots
The varying timeline of events
Are number of shots between McMichaels version of the story and the video
Isn't that I find particularly troubling
And effective McMichael is a former cop leads me to believe that he should have know a lot of
Training in the field of reporting events
It's one thing for a random person in the Heat of the Moment to get some major details wrong
It does happen
It's something else entirely for a
Former cop
To get basic details
Of an event
Wrong
That's so it's surprising
Text until May
Then on May 9th videos released it appeared to show Arbor
House under construction
This video has been used by all the races
Rights to kill him
Personally I've done way worse things are construction sites Never Killed Me Over
Disclosure
Midwest
I think they're there might be a fairly common
Experience of f****** around on
I was really hoping
This one
Repair
Cuz this one is simple litmus test for whether or not you're a giant
Because Aubrey looked around a house under construction the McMichaels had probable cause
How to do a citizen's arrest
But that doesn't really make sense
They didn't actually see him commit any crime
Flimsy defense
Answer I think
What can you do we make sense
Curious person looking around in a cool down on their job
It's hard not to think that a racial component has something to do
Even if the McMichaels weren't acting from place of racism two people bending over backwards
People like Millie Weaver certain
So much this is a horrible tragedy and there is an investigation going on
What's the matter and we'll see what happens
For now I want you to take note of Alex discusses this case
After month
Yelling about how Katie steinle was murdered because she was white
Couldn't stand
Think about how Alex promoted rallies against immigration in the name of steinly
And set Owen Shroyer out to cover them
It's important to recognize these differences because they are the places you see Alex's racism on full display
He's too sappy to say the n-word or talk about hating on white people
You can see clearly how he
Differently he engages with situations depending on the
Races involved
If there's a case of a non-white person accidentally
Discharging a gun in the bullet ricocheted and hits a white woman
It's a case of a brutal murder
That was done because the victim was white
If there's a piece of two white men chasing down a black man
It's a situation where Alex would have done it himself
Didn't do anything wrong
This is
How is racism is on Fulton
He's too smart
To make it to
But was it a leaf
The courts
Right
Suggest
This is the second one should ever need
Ever
Ever this is such a simple
F****** thing and it should the fact that it
All out in the open
Disqualified every single person who says anything other than
Hey he was murdered by two bucks
Modern lynchers is a race
Vietnam
Alex
Since the coronavirus situation has popped up
A number of times Alex has seen videos
He has decided
It's real
So Alex has been
Trick by another
Were you get the term
Dojo
Local news
Children the women and
Convulsing
So that's not true
I want to see some videos that are making the rounds online
The aftermath of a deadly covid-19 vaccination trial in New Guinea
This was a video Simply put
Someone took already existing video people in New Guinea protesting after some children had allegedly gotten sick from a vaccine and they
Reclaim this
Covid-19 vaccine 2019
On a new station called
The actual news report was about a community displeasure after a few children experience
Dizziness and fever
After being in a quote
Drug treatment program to reduce the prevalence and intensity of
The parasitic infection
Crystal bios
Also known as snail
The editor-in-chief
The editorial staff of begin an rvt group
Notes with deep regret that some internet users have been allowing themselves since Monday April 6th 2020
Do use one of our old
Reports
Recent cases of discomfort due to vaccination campaign
In schools in do breakup
We would like to point out that the report was
Produced on March 8th
18th 2019
We invite you to refrain from such games during the sensitive. Marked by a global Health crisis
This makes me think like I said of all the times Alex instead he just knows when he see the video if it's real or not
Here's the reality
The lazy propagandist meatballs for hoaxes like this regularly
Which audiences fact
Because he wants
They conform to his Merit is enough they feel true to him
Problem is
None of it's real
It's really frustrating that is is an airtight defense to say they're doing what we're doing well
Really
Because all the
Videos and all of this s*** is all fake
In the media's all liars and all that
And all he ever does well
Perfectly comfortable assuming that Alex has no idea
Oh yeah I would be like I don't know
Because I mean
Like this
Deceitful
But he goes around like oh my God I can't believe New Guinea
Yeah what matter what is frustrating is also that it doesn't matter if
If it's true or not
Well that's true
Also didn't have nothing to do
It is
Guinea pigs are likely named for their association with Kenny
Name for the area in Africa around the Gulf of Guinea
And in the
Exotic far-off places
Is across the sea
There's no real consensus among Scholars about exactly how
Guinea pig got its name but one thing
Is that has anything to do with New Guinea
It's just another thing that Alex is making up
To sound smart for his audience
Based on nothing
Immaculate
You heard him report on a hoax video as a
Real makeup a piece of trivia about Guinea
Which is standard operation
For him memes
Anything yeah that one
Now I really got you just open with
In New Guinea
We're guinea pigs are from
Soca
Because he wants the association to be like you do tests on guinea pigs
Of course the math is simple
Right
Everything about this
Very angry
So Alex
He knows
Right
You know that they're a bunch of studies that prove the vaccines lower your immunity right
He knows that there are
Okay but there are and now he's really confused because he sat down to try and find those study right
They must be being taken offline conclusion
You still you can type in
Lower immunity
I spent
Today
Find the article
Remix
Lowering
Vaccines are perfect there's no side effects
All this emotional crap
You complaining about these doctors being fake
Fake doctors
I'm not saying they're actors
On the level man
A real guy is a real real friend
You hang out with me
Difficult
He found them forever but his website
Indication of yourself
Because of that I really don't know what claims Alex is making
Inserting Infowars website there's a number of articles about immunity issues and back
Adjust things that Robert Kennedy Jr Road and Alex's repost
These cases be claimed as weakened immune systems has to do with vaccinating children and exertion
Unrelated
Infection
Doesn't sound
Biomedicine
Sandwich taken at face value claims the children
Times Higher mortality if they had received
Tetanus
Pertussis facts
Compared to unvaccinated children
These are children vaccinated between 1984
This isn't even a steady but the currently used
Dtp vaccine
The pointed out which
Conclusion not entirely reliable
The first is that the study involves a very small sample
They're only
Current total in the study which is not enough to generalize
Conclusions about vaccine effectiveness
Or side effects
However is that
There's nothing in the study that actually shows that any of the children's deaths had anything to do with the vaccine
These are all cause death numbers
Which means that the death could have been from drowning or some other acts
And it still be factored into the rate
And this makes the conclusions are very difficult to apply generally
Studies have not come to the same thing
Conclusion and the argument the vaccines lower your
Other than what the vaccine is targeting is rejected by science
2018 record in Jama
District Lea significant differences in the level of immunity against a non-vaccine targeted infection
Between our control and experimental group
That might be what I want to talk about but I'm only guessing
Based on what's on his website
There's another argument about vaccines lowering immunity
From Andrew wakes
This one is basically they would use vaccines immune response
And while the other part is
Is not used in buses weekend
Basic gist here is that he saying that you get better immunity by dealing with
Naturally
So you should get measles if you want to be immune to it
If you takes a shortcut of vaccines and mediated response
Related immunity
This is nonsense to know in the medical field takes
Seriously yeah that sounds like
Like magic
Sincerely I'm sure a precise claim Alex is trying to make butter
It's not too hard to separate similar
What time is very easily
Rock ideas
Vaccines do not lower your
Finding studies cuz they probably weren't there to begin with
I imagine you just read some headlines 10 years ago embellished it into being a prestigious study
The most reputable Journey Journal known to man
And now he goes and tries to find it shockingly nothing comes up
That seems to be what's going on
I have the okay okay fine you know what I'm actually going to prove it this screaming about
Lower your immunity for forever so f*** you I'm going to look it up and I'll find it
And I can't
I can't find it because they got rid of it
You know how the internet
Famously allows people to hide
So
They're trying to get rid of this consumers to not have
The information they need Alex has an amazing comparison
Symptoms
They're just not letting
Bianchi at Lewis's the jungle
The level of abuse of the citizens
Consumers
I want to be sure everyone
Want to hear that
There's no other name TS Lewis
Probably a fun combination of TS Eliot c.s. Lewis
It's always fun to pretend to be into someone
But but also believe that everything that motivate their life's work is death
And plus the jungle was
Even a blind squirrel finds
No.
Weird
Alex
What does my
One of the reasons
Yummy I hadn't heard this episode when we put out episode on Monday
Would you listen to this
Kind of understand
Why I feel like that sort of stuff does fit into the body
Of our work
The Bourne Supremacy
Movies the origin when I forget the name of it
Publix
Only eats
Certain
Brain
2000-lb but
You know you're a white lie.
Imagine
He's talking about the childish nonsense
There's a phenomenon known as hysterical strength
CB2
Car to get someone
You're saying someone is trapped underneath
It's the idea that in moments of severe need we find ourselves capable
Naturally this is something that's almost impossible to
Study in a controlled setting
How Could You reliably create the conditions that we needed to produce this response in a person while controlling for other variables
Basically you can't
Researchers who work with muscles kind of understand the basic idea without needing
To trap a subject
A test subject a loved one under a car
Okay what you do because you can't let them in bed
Experiment otherwise they'll know that they're sure I don't know if science
Ashton Kutcher and then we go from there
I think that's
One of brilliance
Sure and to
A great way to run
Muscles understand
Like for instance
Do you use exactly as much
Muscle as you need to open
Your fridge
If you're tearing up like a bunch of groceries applied to allocate more
To use
German article on the BBC
Estimate the amount of muscle mass recruited during
Maximal exercise around sixty percent
Even Ali deathly to train to get more output from their musculature
Why don't we harness around 80 per-cent of their theoretical strength
Why do we keep so much in reserve
Safety
Essentially
If we were to exert our muscles to or beyond their absolute maximum we could tear muscle tissue ligaments tendons break
Nothing Dire Straits
That Governor your brain is there because if you were allowed to expand all the available energy
You died long ago
Doobie
Completely debilitated due to all of the bodily damage you would have supper
Only lifting a small part of the
The car with two or three wheels remain on the ground Distributing
Plus their bodies are full of adrenaline shoc
They might be feeling from the heavier whip
It even so
Pretty f****** sore afterwards
These parts of your brain could be overridden
Viking cases when you're trying to escape certain death
Your brain realizes that in order to stay alive higher risks need to be taken
On the other side of that coin is part of the brain also appears to be overridden when you're on meth
PCP
Which may play a role in
Explaining the seemingly height and strength
Two people on those drugs
You need to these cases however
Free of this Governor your brain
The party braids are for a reason
Yeah usually helps out whenever you survive
Long a
You do like he's crazy Feats of Strength
When you come back to be in so much pain
Then how dare you
Is this some kind of a magical thing that allows super soldiers like Jason Bourne to use more of his strength than normal people's brains
Maybe operate on the level of an elite athlete
Is a person like a human person were to do what Alex is imagining their bodies would not be able to handle it
They're just physiological realities that he's pretending exist
The whale
If your life is at risk
You could jump down a big drop breaker ankle that run a mile to safety
When you get the safety
Your ankle is still going to be broken
And it's going to hurt like hell
Just ran a mile on
What the f*** do I know I've watched or is Alex
Stop f****** dumb dumb
Remember I don't think
The Bourne movies
Featured super soldier strength
He's just
Really really well-trained
Imma give him some psychotropic
Is really really good at being a spire
Yeah that was just like look at what happens when you're really
Whatever Alex got something out of it so that's great
You can't
Trent like you can't have your brain
Drop that Governor without comp
First of all
Second of all there is a season
Thinking it's it's the
It's ludicrous
Alex ideas is this predictive
ShopRite the globalist to put stuff on TV they're going to do later
Exactly like been a
Sometimes
It has to do with
They need to get your permission
Of course there is
Have to pay in the afterlife or something
You can only get sick if you allow the virus
Sometimes there's a metaphysical last
Back to it and then sometimes it's presented as
Trying to desensitize you to what they're going to
Do to make it easier
Is next clip
Begins with Alex talking about
Predictive programming
The desensitizing level
Find and start screaming
Grandpa
Psychologist psychiatrist at the high levels
Psychologist
Home
And pizza
Marriott
It wasn't because he couldn't handle violence
With the real thing you don't know what hit you
So first of all I don't need to see Alex's citation on this stuff from the high-end psychologist to Arnot pop psychologist
Information when he tells me what he's actually talking about and where it's coming from
That clip is fascinating
Because I really think it highlights how poorly Alex's brain tracks ideas
It begins I'm claiming three of these high-end on pop psychologist to know
They know that if you see something on TV
Pizza good
I can definitely tell you that it is not true from buying personal experience
In the last few weeks
Cars app
F***** on in movies and TV shows sometimes
It doesn't affect me that much
In the movie
When I was walking to the store the other day
A driver turning right didn't see me when I had to walk signal
I was legit seconds away from getting run over
I heard the car accelerating and the split-second as my brain was putting it all together in a
Associated with being at home eating pizza
My reaction was quite
Send pictures
Because it wasn't real life
And my adrenaline rush
Others considering Jumping On The Who tour trying to die backward
Thankfully the driver saw me at the last second hit the brakes
Next block my body was full of that Rush
Both of those things on TV and movies
Primarily because I know the difference between real life and movies
From this idea Alex
Talking about his grandfather
What is because he
An argument could be made that this is the exact opposite
The point Alex
He's saying
Exxon TV desensitize a 2X in real life
Where is it this example
Representative
At 8 or his kids seeing it on TV
Whether or not this hypersensitivity was driven by a fear that the children would become desensitized to violence
The case example
Because it's disconnected from the point you're trying to make
From there Alex make the jump to our simulated violence on TV you think it's funny
So you think of murders funny in real life
Weirdly claims that this is because you didn't see any consequences for the fictional violence who's on TV
Which is weird that's bizarre
I don't know who he's hanging out with
Get the idea that a large number of people think
Real murder is funny
That's a foreign concept to me
I don't think it's real
Least
Say I'm walking
I didn't
You didn't pass huge wasted
Most people intuitively understand the difference between reality and fictional portrayals of
Unexpectedly they react differently to them
The same person who could tolerate seeing the depiction of a murder in a horror movie
Would react completely different they saw something similar in the real world
Good enough people
Do you remember Meet Joe Black
Whenever
12 different cars all at the same time
It played for Laughs like there
It's the weirdest thing I've ever seen
Leatherface
Like longingly look back at each other each expecting the other one to look back
And it goes bad
Back and forth like 4 different times
And then Brad Pitt just walks into oncoming traffic
Can gets hit
Once bounces up in the air
I meant the singing is basically over and they just move on I have not seen that movie in a long time
Did not affect the way I responded.
Spiritual embodiment of death took over your body for a while and Paramore
That's so ridiculous
Some studies that suggest
Children and Adolescent
Almost impossible
Computer for a second even go about trying to set up that study at
Like to really track that
Ashton Kutcher
There's some correlations the people of sound
He's acting like if you see a bomb go off in a movie
And you can counter a bomb in your daily life you like that
Like that booty cool
For that make people laugh and I survived because it was
Yeah
No this is just a video game
Desensitize children
It's not just that operates differently than most people
Recognized
The distinction between
Fiction and reality
It seems to be
Like it seems to be something he is unwilling
Or unable to differentiate between
Doesn't realize if it is something that most
People can differentiate some confusion around why other people
Can't see what he sees does
Steam Jenny
That frustration he's emanifest
Don't seem like someone who's like
It's so clear to me why.
That is that is wild
Don't you get it the Hammers can fly now Dan you just call him to you and the hammer will come to
Ugly to you whenever you need it I'm honestly starting to work on a little bit of
Siri this is one of the more like
Strongly correlated
Things throughout
These conspiracy world
The inability or unwillingness
Differentiate between reality and fiction
Run so strongly on Infowars
Many of the associated people
Anti project experts
It's
It seems to be
One of the defining character
Valentine's Day rant
And of course
Familiar territory
Is your brain
Didn't pay any consequence
The real thing you don't know what hit
You're all dead unless you wake up and decide
The created
I need money to just go straight to an end
Attempt Sunday show in the books
The goddamn place
I kind of appreciate on someone
You got a loan Alex
Viking funerals pretty fun
Alex is weird
Fiction reality
To learn a little bit about
Antboy this day
Say what Alex has a goal
Well you're not having to look at it right now
The Bill Gates uniform
Mark Zuckerberg
With a
White
Shirt
To look like Mister Rogers
Nonce
Hitler war war
Because he would have loved
Non-threatening
This is really funny on a number of levels
The first is that Alex decided this Bill Gates wears pink B was
You kind of can't help but think he's hoping people online make fun of him so you can be all over Twitter again
The second part that's hilarious here is a Hitler War Pinkie be non-threatening
Alex claims to be a military historian but somehow he doesn't realize that the US army officers winter service
I'm starting in the 19th was known as the
Pink and greens
US Army officer uniform during that very time that they were literally had p
Pink in the neighborhood
Military.com
Complete buffoon
He's just
I love it I love the idea that his operation so f****** kapital
Everyone's going to love it love
Blow Minds
Look at me
Alex Jones work
Everyone
And so I thought maybe it's just like all right
ChaCha
Get out of business
I've always said
Hitler
Or a pink uniform he would have won World War because people would have
Said
Somebody
Nothing but good
Bella Melinda Gates always wear pink in public it's why
Characteristic
T-shirt
Female wears pink
Sweaters
Under his mentor Bill Gates
I was curious about the claim that Bill Gates always where is Pink's image search
51st 100 images
In 56 of the images
Is Gators in a suit
Might as well
Exactly two pictures
Navigate to the pink sweater from his 2015 TED Talk
At least one of these is from a site that
From Gates's five-year-old TED Talk
Constantly wearing
Weather
As for Zuckerberg I have no idea where Alex saw him wearing a sweater but I also don't care
This is just a super weird hang-up Alex has Batman wearing colors he thinks
We better pray that he never finds out
The Trump wear a pink striped
Virus press conference
Or the Trump sells a bunch of different
Their manly pink too bright
Which is the difference
I understand
I'm just glad that he's gotten this out of his system and we can move on to other is
Warren Buffett
Almost
With a nice
Look
Scream town
Like a little boy
He's like a little child he doesn't longer
The drug money
Are doing it
So this Obsession has got to stop
We retook
Compelling content is just naming off his enemies of discussing the nefarious implications of what they're wearing
Past its expiration date
This is not hard hitting stuff
Yeah I tried to find pictures of Ron Paul
I will do that I couldn't find any pictures of your bolsonaro in pink but that totally makes sense since he's a
Invested in
Performative masculinity is Alex's so
It shouldn't surprise anyone to hear
Batman suit
It's kind of Hispanic
I can't find any pictures
Peak outside of the possibility some pink dress shirt in a suit or possibly pink tie
Hopefully he doesn't get photographed all the time with ice cream definitely has a few times
And the reason isn't
Innocent child
It's because Berkshire Hathaway the holding company that he owned
Old Dairy Queen
I was going to say
It's so awesome
So f***
It's the most
Ridiculously obvious thing that you can say
But the only reason they bought
Dairy Queen is so later on in life
He could f******
Broadcast
Also worried about the money laundering
In 2010
But there is this represent
In 2010 the DEA conducted
And concluded a 22-month investor
Navigation that it uncovered
The dollars that cartels
Through Wachovia Bank
By that point I had been bought by Wells Fargo
Of which Berkshire Hathaway is the fifth largest shareholder
Wells Fargo
The choir Wachovia until 2000
She's definitely exists an issue to Berkshires involvement with
The back
There's definitely some
2007 timeframe
Imagine
I was just desperate to lash out his imagined enemies to the point out right now
Make false accusation
Because he's been trained that there are no consequences for that
Bump it is too busy to sue Alex or this
Clear instance of defamation Alex knows it
There's just enough reality to the story that Wachovia did get in trouble for laundering drug money in 2010
Alex knows that his listeners will find a headline about that inside that out the story about it is true
You just a most pampered of radio personalities when you get right down to it
Easy easiest f****** job imaginable
Yeah just like too frustrating and times
Consuming to sue him
Just a trained audience full of people who has died
Oh he is right I saw headline
People would not
Appreciate our show if we just
Listed people and talked about what
Play War
Might want to consider it cuz I think of easier
What time coming
McConnell
Sevens on his stuff and that's obviously
The unrestrained whatever real devil
So Alex is another story
Thankfully it has nothing to do with the color pink
I was getting a little tired
Green
San Antonio
Pass the law last Thursday saying you'll be arrested if you say
Because the whocash Dozen
Come from China
I guess the WHIO can say the Moon is
Haha
So sweet to San Antonio city council passed a resolution that just roundly denounced the use of the term Chinese virus
Send Kung Fu virus
The resolution does it say lb arrest
Before using this term
It's really more just a declaration of a commitment to protect the safety and dignity of the Asian residents of the city
I'll just bring this up to your but there's also a business resolution about anti-semitism
Which has been marked by a bunch of people on the extreme right-wing
They say you need drink
The Pretender
Just crazy
Housing Chinese virus anti-Semitic
Looney left-wing safespace nuts are out of
Control
And the revolution
Quickly spells that out if you actually read it
Reading is hard for the
In the preamble to the resolution they include
Whereas the Jewish Community has been targeted with blame hate anti-semitic trope
Conspiracy theories about there
Creating spreading
And profiting from covid-19
The city council's make
Nature propaganda surrounding covid-19
Ross opens the door to the very people relying on those ancients meditropin
Conspiracy theories
Play Dom and pretend they don't
Get the point
They're always going to do that anyway man my birthday the first thing my dad
Send me that morning
Like
Hey how you doing with the
Kung flu and I texted him back I was like I would appreciate it if you didn't
Yeah thanks happy birthday
Look up fuctupmike
Like really funny
And I was like please don't I would appreciate you didn't do that and then you text back it is what it is and I have not spoken to him
Since then
In my head all day writing this whole like the only reason that you associate
Diseases with a certain group of people is
Set the groundwork for a program later
And I
There's just no way to deal with
I'm sorry to hear that
Photo bomber
So I don't think
More.
So I don't think it's the World Health organization's ever said that the virus didn't originate in China it's just
Calling it The China virus
In the preamble to the resolution they say quote whereas covid-19 will not be stopped by political
Created or caused by any race nationality or ethnicity
And the World Health Organization has cautioned against using Geographic descriptors
Naked racial discrimination
That's the only time the World Health Organization comes up
Who makes perfect
San Antonio City Council
Works better for him
If you're keeping score
Any 16-second clip that we listen
Come to light about the idea that
This Revolution was a bill to a rat
Chinese virus
Organization saying the virus didn't originate in China
Like he's trying to set record
I am speed
I mean in even in the even in the function of their
Conspiracy theory
Even if the
Chinese government
Somehow created this and then released it it's not the Chinese people
From you associating it with
What is what's going to happen
The people who are going to get f***** up
Become flu is going to really
Yeah yeah yeah just going to be somebody across the f***
Street from you
Guitar rest for the rest of the goddamn the consequence that you're willing
Existence
The Chinese government isn't going to be affected by you call
Cool
So
A rocky start
Water focus on pancake and we can move on
Little pink shirt
I am wearing
It's all show that
I'm wearing pink
Oh my God
Is this is
Very desperate
Salmonella
Clips are we going to get
Pink shirt I might be done
For now
Really funny cuz David Icke
Is on the show
So you can comes up later
David Icke
Sweater
Bill Gates
And what will revisit that
Some headlines from the way he's delivering
For any of this
Coronavirus spread
Depending on the graph there 50
Lower covid-19 death rate than they predicting the very same groups now
All these new fake numbers
Predicting
Millions more cases because
Invoice better Public Health crisis because
He also can't ignore them
What about the virus rates in Germany I'm just going to leave that alone not because I don't care but because it's kind of complicated and secondary
Camp not address the fact that Mike Pence's staffer Katie Miller test
Positive for covid-19
Too big of a story that he doesn't have to play catch-up
If she wasn't sex
Possibly exposed to the virus
Including most of the executive branch leadership
Miller's husband is Stephen Miller advisor to Trump
Pence
This could be a disease Vector the touches a whole lot of folks and some of them like Trump
In high-risk population
But the virus is not something that Alex
I'm really ignore
Alex knows he has to touch on this
There's not much he can do
If he says that it's a globalist infected and try to get the truck
This basically in assassination of
Escalation of his
Probably shouldn't make
The globalists are trying to kill the president. Well guess what
It's fine if you or Alex
Attempt on the president's life
He knows that stained
What are you left with
There's no real option for covering that story other than
This is like a bully was no comeback resorts to doing a dumb voice
Like that makes
That last story there is with his pattern is really on
Display
How does absolutely no good explanation for administration
Buried that CDC report
And where he's talking about it makes it clear that Alex doesn't actually even understand the story
Alex seems to think it is a story that has something to do with
Projections and grants
In reality the report the Trump shelves was quote
Detailed advice from the nation's top Disease Control experts for reopen
Communities
During coronavirus pandemic
Presumably he came out with a detail
Help communities do just that
And then the White House Shelter report on April 3rd
Weird
I think maybe
He
Agreed with the
I think
He was like
I don't like
Report card
Associated Press obtained emails
The head of the CDC
Redfield head approved this report
And sent it to the White House for approval
But they killed it
Not even be allowed to post
The decision tree
On May 7th be Associated Press reported on this very document which looks really bad
Worse is that according to ABC News
Quote after the story ran the White House called the CDC in
Trees except churches
An email obtained by the Associated Press confirmed Thursday
Hours after the news broke
It's clear intention here and none of it's good
It's a sort of thing we're obviously Trump wanted to reopen everything is pretty Rush uncontrolled way
Was much more careful in measure
Would you be slower
Girl bummer
Instead of letting the expert advice be released
They covered it up
What's the evidence of the report was reported on by the Associated Press
The Manning Report.
Call pathetically transparent stuff and absolutely no good argument
Is a goal is to safely reopen the country
His actions make no sense
Thumbs up
Completely fictional version
With these narratives where you misrepresented
Projections from January
Who's the best you can do
I was reading headlines about a very serious thing
Stanford
Testing positive for the virus or Trump
Varying reports that could end up jeopardizing Public Health
Tone
Amanda wyss
Show anymore
Ridiculous
You can be very large and yet still be at
Child
Did you know that
Maturity
The head part
Doesn't doesn't
I don't know how you feel good about this work
Like I feel somebody
I tried pretty hard sometimes to walk away with
Better I can't imagine
Imagine what it feels
Freedom
It feels like.
LeapFrog
That's a great show thanks
Alright
So
In this
Episode
Keep saying
That he has like
Clips of Bill Gates saying that he wants
To kill children
Right
No you don't end up playing it
Of
Bill Gates talking about
Childhood death in depopulation and work vehicle
I'll get rid of all people
Very well
Nutrition
Reduce
Thinking he says produce
Play the clip
Again
Because they play it slow down and it tells
Wow
This is the Smoking Gun the Bill Gates
Excited while talking about
Producing
Uh did Geraldo just open of what the f*** has happened there
That is wild
Did he not
Listen to it before the show
I mean
I don't know they could be motivated
Hearing tell yourself
Like if I told myself to hear produce there I probably could
Pretty clear you saying take a lot of mental effort
Yeah you got a really water
So it is next clip Alex
Gets to the issues surrounding the Justice dropping case against General Flynn
Very clear intent on
Where's part two crime
Hero now he's covering it up because that's what he's
Irrelevant
The Cobra Golf crime
Literally why
The only reason you hire Bill Baris to cover up.
Hero no I'm pretty sure that
Admitted to lying to the FBI
Crimes in that in covering this story
Chuck Todd
Right
Situation coming out
With
Errol Flynn
And some of the Articles dealing with that
Infowars.com
Now even the doj is slamming NBC's truck
AG Barr interview
How's that feel bar
When the media lies about what you say
New York legal action against
Say that
Covid-19 treatment
Any such thing
Kind of dead
Just got to make it about yourself got to make
Chuck Todd Meet the Press General Barr history look back on this
Decision
All the show Bars response was well history is written by the winners so it depends on who's writing the history
The full answer the bar gate was closed
Well history is written by the winners so it largely depends on who's writing the history
But I think a fair history would say that it was a good decision because it upheld the rule of law
It helped it upheld the standards of the Department of Justice and it was a ninja
I see both sides
Chuck Todd very clearly contacts
It's very hard for me to imagine that
The decision
So f*** him
But that being said even with the full context
Comedies f****** chilling and scary
His first thought is still the
History is written by the winners
Good decision based on the
History witch
Feels kind of like rationalization of the immediate answer
That even though he must have realized under the
Villainous a little bit like well so long as we remain in power forever
I think it'll be a great day
Decision guys
Even with the
Doesn't
Excuse
Why Chuck Todd
Even though
I mean honestly
I don't
Think it matters because the rest of it was a liar
No no
Even Bill Barr in his heart
Can possibly believe
That what
He did would be treated
Fairly by history
But at the same time
Jeers must go to Chuck Todd
I don't even care I don't even think in terms of like being
Jennifer actor
Get the thing
Presented misrepresentation because Chuck Todd did also say that he didn't
Justify this based on the rule of law
Concrete
Misrepresentation
Spirit
That's not right
No I understand
My my feeling is
Getting abused
By being fair
Buspar
William Barr to pretend anything other than that he's covering up a crime
I'm abused by
I don't think I don't think I should have done an interview with him.
I can agree with that conclusion
To justify misrepresent the person on a new show
Butyrate the entire
Queen of what you're doing
In the process you don't get fire powers
People that would provide cover for the cover-up
Or whatever I think it's
I don't know
My issues letting him talk in the first
I don't know justify
Sacha Baron Cohen
But while we're on the subject of things being taken out of context
I should bring up they want to be major sources of justification for the Department of Justice dropping their case against Michael Flynn
Pokemon said that her words are being used inappropriately it support
Conclusion she actually opposed
Attorney general for National Security New York Times that includes the following
Quote
Attempting to support its argument insights more than 25 times
The FBI's report of an interview with me
In July 2017
My interview is no support for mr. bars dismissal of Flynn's case
It does not suggest that the FBI had no counterintelligence reason for invest
Navigating mr. Flynn
It does not suggest that the FBI's interview with mr. Flynn
Would you like to the false statements charged with unlawful or unjust
It does not support that Mr Flynn's.
Material
Justice is assertion
Continue prosecution
The case against Mr Flynn
Who pleaded guilty to knowingly making
Materially false statements to the FBI
Would not serve the address
The working Theory
Legal experts is that there was not good cause
To drop the case against Department of Justice
Macavity argument
In order to avoid Trump
Trying to Pardon him
Which would have been a real klusterfuk
Would have been
In Trump's Administration would want
To try and do
They will
Well
Justice argue
Which is to say that they were irrelevant to other cases
And therefore lying about those things
This is not a very solid argument internet
The Hobbit.
Conclusion
Last we don't live in the same world and so here we are
I'm here again we have Alex looking up to Bill Barr
The guy who you should absolutely unequivocally hate for
And all of the issues that it careers
Just don't understand how
It wasn't
Immediately an arrestable offense to hire Bill Barr
Should be ready literally like saying
It was the previous
I hired something completely fractured Trump
Bass
Then I covered up all their crime
Navigation with
Problem
Patriot militia right way
They should have seen
A bit like if he does that we're out
MN Trump should be played it right cuz turns out they don't care
When they don't care
So you talking about cuz Alex
Favorite country or something
We talked about the death toll
Coronavirus in Sweden
Just make some stuff up
Dead sweet waiting for me
Pretty please cupcakes on top
What does the new
European size
Coronavirus
The show is good
So we have two claims being made there
The first is that they were 15,000
Flu deaths in Sweden
Pushed about the 2019 flu season
Total
You've got seems to be a little bit High
They reported 505 of these people died within 30 days
Other diagnosis
Give you some idea of the
The scale
In the 2011 20/20 season the death girl almost hit 1000
Invitation I can find out to just making up that number about Swedish food at
If it's number were accurate and you applied that rate based on Sweden population
We would have about four hundred and ninety-two thousand
Flu deaths per year
Which again leads me to believe that I was just making
Maybe he just saw they had about 14,000 cases last year and he's misrepresenting that Miss
Reporting it as death
Whatever the case he's just presented bad in
Information to his audience Authority
Is lame yeah also Alex is going there's no cases of flu being reported because they're all being called covid-19
Complete lie
You can easily find Daytona
The cdc's website that reflects newly reported cases of influenza there confirmed each week
The number is going drastically downward
Because flu season is
Pretty much over
Heather usually ends around you know like the end of March or in April
They're still 21 new cases in week 18 of 2020 which ended May 2nd
26 cases the week prior
You can find week-by-week data for influenza-related deaths on the website
Week 18 had 20 baths and week 17 at 106
If you look at their data for previous years
Pretty much
Common pattern
A flu season
Workouts
Increases the season begins
Another gradually go down as we come to the end of the season
Is drop typically comes in week 16 to 19 of the year and sometimes a little bit
Just calling all flu deaths covid-19
Health officials are
Still counting flu deaths
Alta just making this up because it's important to minimize the danger covid-19
Because he's a lazy
Can fraud
Which makes me actually kind of Alex basically just admits his life
Life's work has amount
Giving up on phone
God
Trying to fix things
We failed
Psychometrist level
You'll be a biological weapon attack
Endgame
But you failed
Stop
Yeah that's
What's that
Yeah he's accomplished nothing in his entire life
You should be ashamed of himself for being
What are things that started his own reality reality
He's a massive destruct
Failure
Alex's operation is doomed
The failure to begin with
Because it doesn't mean
Like none of the stuff he's talking about goes anywhere it's all bulshit
Musically if you have smart
Engage competent people in your audience
They're going to end up looking into the things that you say and eventually
Be able to retain a decent audio
Engaged
Critical
In the audience
Text self-select
For people who are gullible or baby dumb
Be your audio
You have that as your space and eventually overtime
Maybe some of them will start
To realize that nothing ever
Realize
Disenchant some of the
Respond to this by
Turning off the critical thinker
Whatever Alex says is right is right
A hundred percent on the ride with him
Wherever it goes you can say they've given up and have failed in their
Whatever coldest Devotion to a war
The other
Subsets of people are going to be like
Alex is not doing it
We'll find some other
Conspiracy
Guru in that world
Also have a piece of their story be like
Hey
Alex
Is controlled opposition
Because that way
You can start being called by someone else
And pretend that they've woken up
Yep they can pretend
Couponing them
This one isn't
And so now they're out of
Constantly Inward and outward
People who
Get tired of the b*******
And the only people who really stick around people who trained and coached
Turn off
Critical thinking
Capabilities
And that is not
I mean
You know you can go for quite a while apparently
Using that as a
Sumbitch
Eventually
You know
You're not going to be able to do much
Watch with it
Diminishing returns
The other things happen in your life like
You get sued by everybody to be able to maintain the standard of living
Become accustomed to your billion-dollar Studios
And all this s*** it
This is destined to fail
Is the system that needs to continue
Yeah
Content
The content
Definition is a spinning wheel
Yeah it is it's never going to get anywhere
And no matter how gullible you are sooner or later everybody wants to finally get
And they'll go somewhere else
And so the only people who are not going
To do that
Be people who don't have a chance
Began what kind of helpless to the
Fraud and manipulation that Alex
That's not going to be that's not going to be a basement
Is going to sustain you forever and furthermore it
It's not going to be like
2 releaf
Do any
Know if you can't get another generation into real
And there was a certain kind of be able to do that
Conspiracy propaganda he's not that anymore recruits
Minimize via social media
Inflow has been stymied as opposed to the outflow
Like it's just it's just screwed like
To the country
This is this is kind of
Began
Ya-ya-ya High highs
More or less
Because
Think it's impossible
Everything is so stupid that he saying
He can't possibly
Anybody
HughesNet
Vulnerable or an idiot to be a
Yeah yeah
I mean if you dissolve select
It's it's at
Paranoid perpetually in fear and paralyzed
Spy
Their slavish devotion
Into a guy who's supposed to be doing everything
Sing for them
Yeah and then think about how his business model also relies on self-selecting people who are gone
Because like you know placebo effect
What is his business
I'll be fine
Slowly poisoning use supplements everything will be fine
Those sorts of sales pitches are not
Things that you do with
An audience that is critical
Critically minded
What am I looking at
Scariest
I really need the burpees
Yeah it's
It's sad
What kind of bummed me out
Surprise coming up on this episode
You know San Antonio so they'll arrest you if you say the word Chinese
I hear it
Let's just say we got a
Price of our sleeves
What's going on
Nothing happened
I don't know if
You play something later in the shower. Like I'm going to be
Like real lated to the San Antonio story
Swing for the fences on some Asian Bakery
I don't know what he was talking about
I expected him to have somebody in San Antonio saying racist s*** in front of a cop
That seems like the obvious thing for him to do nice out there
So Alex
No payoff to this that I'm aware of
Make
Okay go radio broadcast
Dido
We'll figure it out the sales pitch products
Impact
Pictures of white burgundy in Friends
Yourself
Percent off
The 8-pack powerstack is
13 pills
Is confusing
Infowars store to try and figure out what was up with as soon as it turns out
It's cold
Different formula
Lazar double pill
Deflection
The nootropic brain and immune support formulas are each two pills
Where's the other six formulas are a single
If you do some simple bath
That is 12
There's even a visual on the website that shows each of the pills clearly 12 of them
Where's the 13th mystery Pale Ale
What are you hiding
Invisible
And info Warriors can see
Is that right yeah they don't put it on the website
Because I'm just anybody
I could see it then you got to order it and then if you're man enough
Kingsville will manifest
Man manifest
Makes perfect
Yeah you're right I should have thought of that
Also it's called a pack power stack
There are nine
Thursday Plex Android
Covid brain and immune support
The airport the morning one has five
As for
And I imagine putting that much s*** in your body
It's a lot of pills that's a lot of pills
Yeah
It's also none of the numbers match up and I don't know what's going on at their marketing in orders
Problematic I think it might be too late for that
Now could be
It's goes to call for David Icke shows up
David Icke
But I can listen to
A respected man
Alex
Call
Scorpio
Kind of hard core information out of
You're going into hardcore Terry we're all in grave Danger
Figure medical worker what's your viewing
Remember I offer
What is your view on all this
My view
Exaggerated
The doctors and other medical workers around you think what the
They're just taking a
Josh and I feel like it
Intuit some orange
Are you calling today anything else on your mind
No
Call I
Her breath
Brevity is the soul of Lies I really feel like
Information
Appreciate
Summerville
Extreme precautions
How do you feel about it
Okay then
For Alex
It's one of the fake one
How long can the media get caught staging
As we let them
President
Brother God bless you I appreciate your call
The color things
Mad at both of these guys
I'm really mad but I like that Alex doesn't even recognize
Attributing it to a different day
Just don't
Sonic
Just don't man
Alex
Facts about how there's nobody
Things and still getting MRIS
I
Only I'm going to play this clip
Because there's a really important that I need to make about it care about a lot of this content
But there's something that he's doing it
This clip that is a
The big problem
Phone call
Where is tsuyu you play more hospitals doing that
Tia
Sandy Hook
The walking around in circles the media lining up cars
Just him taking his Sandy Hook talking
And reapplying at the hospital.
Coronavirus
He needs to be
Bucking careful
He's doing it again
He's in the middle of this doing it again
Tragedy
You just can't resist
Being drawn to denying tragedy
So it's it's all he knows how to do to make money so their people who are walking
In and out
Performative
For the media to
So
So they would be so when you're
Performatively doing something
Unnecessary
30 black actor
Is what they they would be doing I think if I understand this correctly this has to do with
Came out of
Someone doing a remote shot and beating an establishing shot
So like
People to stand
News report would have b-roll
Or whatever
Yeah alright that's cheating or something
It's not it's not the
Dead to rights
Proof that Alex's
Sending a video of Alex
Things like that
It's not
PB news.
It's not dishonest
Tulsa
Strictly Auto
Whatever reality TV show
Is reality TV star
They were given to them by a writer Dan can you imagine that
Hellboy
So earlier in the show
He speculated pink sweater
To Bill Gate he did it
Alex accidentally asks
A follow-up
Zuckerberg
In the last London real
Bill Gates little non-threatening pig sweater
Contact David Icke
Six-letter sometimes
That's fine. What Ike
I know he doesn't need to because I don't think
I don't think he understands without weird masculinity
Doesn't care that much about that
Pictures of David Icke over the years work
Sweaters wardrobe
Thanks a nice color
So Jordan
A that we have
We know the David Icke has been coming on out to show and saying that there is no virus completely
Alex keeps allowing him to come on the show and dozen
Really fight with him about that
Pretty based on everything Alex says he knows that there is
Unfortunately
Every single time David Icke is on he swings out
Alex
This is so cool
Stupid
Never acted before
You're right it's just completely made up
Eva
I didn't even need to come to that conclusion Alex doesn't
So I guess when Alex is like eventually
That's what you think
That is
That's wild
Agreeing with you can't do that
Can't you just had it should be
Like that should be part of every human being
I can't do that
Yeah do that thing
Thing that I was going to do what I said
Everything that I believed was false and I agree with you and then later
Five minutes later I'm going to
Completely forgot that I
Rocket defensive about it probably think that I said that
Things that I think I said that I know I didn't say I think I said
Wild walkthrough
I believe we have reached the end
Next episode on Friday
Check back on the rest of the week so you about
Falls apart completely a disowns
It show
I really like to hear particular about how his life is a failure
I'm hoping for a real Coach mcguirk style like a off all of his clothes and just goes into the forest
Leave the guns behind braces the blade episode
That sounds great
We'll see what happens with this
Protracted meltdown
Never end so
Can't wait
We also on Twitter
But if you'd like
It would very much
EBenefits
Herberg
Alex
In color
I love your work